EP. 1— THE PASTMASTER ALWAYS
RINGS TWICE
Maybe this wasn’t such a good idea, Tom.
This old boneyard is supposed to be cursed!
What are ya, Jack, a scaredy kat? We find somethin’
valuable, and the museum’ll pay big bucks for it!
So shut up and keep diggin’!
Hey, I think I’ve hit paydirt!
Gimme a hand here!
There’s probably treasure inside.
Ugliest treasure I’ve ever seen…
Yeah, well this old watch has
gotta be worth plenty of- What?!
Wh-who are you?
I am the Pastmaster, imprisoned
in here for 800 years.
I told ya this place was cursed!
At last I’m finally free! Now to
find my book of spells.
L-L-Let’s get outta here!
No way! We’re gonna sell that old
gnome to the museum, watch and all!
Curse the council!
My book isn’t where I hid it!
- You’re comin’ with us, Pastmaster!
- You foolish mortals!
Even without my spellbook I have enough
power to deal with vermin like you!
Let them go!
I have more important work for you.
Start digging, and find my book of spells!
You are violating a restricted area! Put
down those shovels! You’re under arrest!
Do those modern fools think some
infernal machine can stop me?! Attack!
- Do we read these things their rights?
- You have the right to remain buried!
These bones ain’t movin’ now.
What’s this thing?
I don’t know. Headquarters wants us to
take it over to the Museum of History.
Roger.
Perhaps this “museum” has my book.
So, this is what’s
been accomplished in 800 years.
I want the Dark Ages back! And when I
find my Tome of Time, I will arrange just that!
Mach 4! Ready for more?!
Mach 5!
All right, ten seconds.
Beat that, SWAT Kat.
- What?
- New personal best! Ten seconds at Mach 5.
Yeah, well, if you say so.
Of coruse, I didn’t see it.
Sure you didn’t see it, you were
out like like a blown engine!
Then how do I know you made 10 sec.? I mean,
you could’ve passed out too, and just made it up to yank my tail.
That does it! Two outta three!
You’re on!
Why don’t ya just admit it! I can
take more Gs than you!
I’ll believe it when I see it!
And so when the museum re-opens,
our new exhibit will trace...
...the evoloution of Megakat City from
prehistoric swamp, to urban sprawl.
This should be enough for me to
write the Mayor’s press release.
Thanks, Dr. Sinian.
Will that be in the exhibit?
Oh, just came in, but it’s definatly
a part of history. The darker part.
These inscriptions date back to
the Dark Ages.
Really? Any idea what was inside?
Jewels, perhaps. Who knows what
our ancestors might have buried in here?
Here, the past is dead.
I prefer my past alive!
How’d you get in here?
The museum is closed until further...
And I say it is open!
What was that?!
I do not want to be disturbed while
I look for my book!
Oh good heavens!
One of the exhibits has fallen!
One of the exhibits is alive!
Where is my book?!
Jake! Callie’s callin’ us!
Oh and by the way, eleven
seconds at Mach 5!
T-Bone here. What’s happening, Ms.
Briggs? Ms. Briggs, do you copy?
Sounds like big trouble!
- What?
- Up and at ‘em, partner!
- Got a fix on Callie’s signal?
- Yes! Megakat City Museum of History!
We can get out through the garage!
Seems pretty quiet.
Quiet?
Popping canopy, now!
Bingo!
Let me give ya a hand, ladies.
T-Bone!
Thanks, Razor. I think I
could’be taken him.
Just makin’ sure the cement
machine gun was operational.
Exhibits are gettin’ kinda lifelike,
aren’t they?
Looks like the Enforcers are here,
late as usual.
My Tome of Time. 800 years is far
to long to be separated from such power!
Only a sorcerer’s dark power could have brought these
ancient bones to life. It must have been the Pastmaster.
- Do you mean that weird little guy in the hood?
- He’s stolen an ancient spellbook!
- All right, buddy, hand it over!
- The Tome of Time belongs to me!
Hear the spell  of this immortal, send
this creature through the portal!
It’s a Megasaurus Rex!
Out of my way, you fools! I command the
past, and your future looks bleak!
Hang tight, we’ll take care of this.
- Let’s kick some tail!
- Roger! Octopus Missiles, away!
It just kicked our tails!
- The SWAT Kats!
- They’re gone!
Now who will save Megakat City?!
Come on, baby! Gotcha!
T-Bone? I’ve got a feeling we’re
not in Megakat City anymore.
Yeah, sleepin’ beauty, looks like that
giant lizard smashed us into the past.
Any idea how to get back?
Well, I’ve got a better question. How
does a jet stay in the air without fuel?
Answer: it doesn’t!
Well, I’d better get to work fixing
that torn fuel line.
Fine. The closest gas station is
only a million years away.
- Ejektors!
- Engaged!
- I guess we showed them.
- Yes, but now we have to show them!
Fire!
There is a way to destroy this modern monstrosity
called Megakat City, and bring back the Dark Ages!
It’s no use, Commander! We’ve
thrown everything at that lizard!
- I’m surprised SWAT Kats aren’t here.
- They got taken out early, sir.
Really? Well, we can handle this.
Launch gas grenades!
Yes sir!
The spell must be cast from the
tallest clocktower in the land.
Once that was my tower, but now...
- You stupid beast!
- They’re not going anywhere!
- Get that spellbook from the Pastmaster.
- I give the orders around here!
Dr. Sinian knows what she’s talking
about. She’s the curator of the museum.
All right. Throw a net over that guy!
Hear the spell of this immortal, send
these creatures through the portal!
- Too little too late, Feral!
- This is Feral. Bring me chopper backup!
Yes, that clocktower will do nicely!
He’s headed for City Hall!
Spider Missiles, now! Goin’ down!
T-Bone, follow me!
Into a live volcano?! Razor,
you’re crazier than I am!
Oxygen masks, now!
Lucky for us those leather-wings
don’t have gas masks.
Smells like prehistoric fried chicken.
Volcano was fun, but I don’t wanna spend the
rest of my nine lives stuck in dinosaurville.
Affirmative. And I’ve got an idea that just
might get the Turbokat back in the air.
- Let me blast that gnome and his buzzards.
- I give the orders around here, Feral...
and you’re not going to blow up my City Hall,
until I know who we’re dealing with and what he wants!
He’s an 800-year-old sorcerer
from the Dark Ages!
Perfect! Well, don’t just stand there! Get
up to the tower and find out what he wants!
Fuel tanks are modified.
- Give me some gas!
- You really think this is gonna work?
Theoretically, the natural volcanic gas mixture
should get us off the ground. Or blow us up.
When this clocktower strikes noon, my Dark Age
city will return, and your Megakat City will be no more!
The Mayor has authorized me to give you
anything you want! Money! A parade in your honor!
How generous. But I’m already getting
what I want! A return to the past!
- Our only hope is to destroy that book!
- And we’re running out of time!
You’re really going to enjoy the
Dark Ages!
Guess it’s up to Feral now, especially
without the SWAT Kats.
- Maybe we should’ve tried the unleaded volcano.
- Well, at least we didn’t blow up.
Feeding time again, guys?
Sorry, SWAT Kat
ain’t on the menu!
T-Bone! Looks like another one of
those time holes is opening.
Feral, you’ve got only three minutes to
blast that sorcerer out of the clocktower!
My pleasure! Fool should’ve
given the order an hour ago.
Get them!
My office!
It won’t be long, now!
- We’re back!
- The SWAT Kats!
Looks like our city’s having
an identity crisis.
SWAT Kats, you have only one minute to blast
the Pastmaster out of the City Hall clocktower!
Who says we can’t fight City Hall?
Eat afterburner!
Watch this!
If the Gs don’t knock you out!
Nice flying, T-Bone! Hey! I didn’t pass out!
Wake up, buddy! We need a pilot now!
- Why didn’t you eject?
- And miss that look on your face? No way!
They’re too late!
Time’s up!
Nooooo!
I wish they’d got back in time
to save my office.
I guess the Tome of Time won’t be
making it into the new exhibit.
But, at least we don’t have to worry
about the Pastmaster anymore.
- Yeah!
- Rock and roll!
Episode 2
THE GIANT BACTERIA
Does that crazy megalo think he can
blow up every refinery in Megakat City?
He’s doin’ a good job so far.
He’s shreddin’ those Enforcer choppers like
an old scratchin’ post! Guess it’s up to the SWAT
Kats to kick some tail!
- Can ya get a lock on him?
- Workin’ on it.
Locked and loaded, T-Bone!
One Octopus Missile, on its way!
Sucker doesn’t even see it comin’!
He suckered us!
How’d you miss him, sure-shot?
That guy must have eyes in the
back of his head.
Whoa, he does have eyes in
the back of his head!
No excuses.
You’ll have to do better than that,
SWAT Kats, to catch Morbulus!
So, four-eyes wants to play
canyon tag, huh? Crud!
- He’s goin’ after the Megakat Refinery!
- Head for that cloud bank, I’ve got an idea!
I hope it’s better than your aim.
Scratch one more refinery!
Let’s see if four-eyes has eyes
under his head! Bingo!
What’ll it be, Razor?
Dunk or deliver?
Dunk!
Belly flop?
Mega-belly flop! Guess Feral and
the Enforcers can handle it from here.
Keep away, Deputy Mayor!
He could still be dangerous!
Yes, he could be. If he was here.
Looks like you’ve come up empty,
Commander Feral. And the SWAT Kats
practically gave him to you!
If they’d held Morbulus until
we arrived, he’d be in custody right now!
Mayor Manx, is this the end of what has
been dubbed “The Refinery Reign of Terror?”
Absolutely! The authorities have
apprehended the villain!
Mayor Manx, I’m afraid that’s
not the case.
- But Callie, you told me on the phone...
- You were obviously misinformed!
Well, which is it, Commander?
Do you have this wacko or don’t you?
Despite our valiant efforts, the
villain managed to escape. Although, we
believe he may have drowned in the bay.
No way I’m gonna rot in some
Megakat City prison!
I’ll put you to much better use
than that!
Chalk up another one for the
SWAT Kats!
- Nice flyin’.
- Nice shootin’.
Fun’s over.
Back to the greasepit.
Let’s see if we made the 5:00 news.
- Hey, there’s Feral.
- Guy looks like he hasn’t hit
the litterbox in a week!
Turn it up, I wanna here him take
credit for what we did.
So you don’t have Morbulus
in custody?
Due to the interference of the SWAT Kats,
this is all we have of Morbulus at the moment!
- What?!
No one asked for their help and they
allowed a dangerous criminal to escape!
Escape?! We practically
handed Feral a gift package!
And if I ever find out who they are,
I’ll...
Aw, great. Morbulus is gone,
so’s our TV!
I need your help, guys. This crate
pinged all the way from Megakat Bay.
- What were you doin' there, Callie?
- Didn’t you guys hear?
The SWAT Kats shot down
Morbulus! They were magnificent!
- Really?
- They tore him right out of his plane!
- Nu.
- Yes!
But somehow Commander Feral
managed to lose him…
- Yeah, so we heard. When we had a TV.
- When can I pick up the car?
Jake’ll start on it right away.
You can wait for it, how ’bout some milk?
I can’t. I’ve got to get  back into town and
help “his Honor” write his speech for
tomorrow’s park dedication.
I’ll be happy to drive you.
No need. Mayor Manx is waiting
for me outside. One  of the, um,
“perks” of being Deputy Mayor.
Thanks, Chance.
- Did you hear that? She’s crazy
about me! - Bye, Jake!
So, this is the secret lab
of the legendary Dr. Viper.
Quite an eyeful, isn’t it, Morbulus?
Very impressive. Looks like you’ve got
everything a mad scientist needs, right here.
Everything except the rare biochemical
compound known as Katalyst 99.
Well maybe I could help
ya get it, doc.
We see eye to eye, Morbulus.
I do have need of  someone to get
me into Megakat Biochemical Labs!
Megakat Labs? Are you outta your mind?!
That building’s impenetrable!
Up until now.
What? What have you done to me?!
I’m letting you help me! As a living
test tube for my new bacteria strain!
- No!
- Yes!
I have big plans for you!  With your help, I will
have Katalyst 99, and the power to destroy
Megakat City!
I’m not sure using these turbo plugs on
Callie’s engine is such a good idea, Chance.
I say she’s gotta have extra horsepower
in case of an emergency.
I say you’re gonna blow the engine.
Jake, I’m a pilot. I know what
an engine can handle.
See? Purrs like a kitten.
Growls like a tiger!
Blows like a volcano!
Now what’ll we tell Callie?
I’ll think of somethin’.
Problems, guys?
Maybe we can add to ‘em!
Hit it, Murray!
This makes my day, Burke!
They come a long way from bein’ pilots.
A looooong way – down!
Sign here.
Here’s your copy! We’ll tell Commander
Feral, you sent your love!
Adios, amigos!
“This makes my day!”.
If those dipsticks knew we built
the Turbokat outta stuff like this.
They’d cough up a hairball!
Check it out. We can drop this baby under
Callie’s hood. With a little modification, of course.
And I think I found our new TV!
What’s goin’ on out here?
Get away!
I’ll teach you to tamper with my
experiment!
And now that you’ve had your breakfast, it’s time
to begin our commute into Megakat City, by sewer.
Follow me!
As Mayor of Megakat City, I am proud to dedicate
this beautiful new park, which bears my name.
That Callie sure is pretty.
Yeah, but she’ll be pretty mad if
we don’t get her car running.
From the new Manx Municipal Park,
this is Ann Gora for Kat’s Eye News.
What in the…!? Quick, get a shot of that!
It’s every kat for himself!
- Better let me drive, Mayor!
- Just get me out of here!
- Hey, that’s Callie!
- Out of my way, slimeball!
Let’s hit it!
Come on, Mayor! Hurry!
- Relax, Mayor. The Enforcers
are here, now! - So are the SWAT Kats!
- Looks like Callie’s safe.
- Not the way Feral flies!
Back off, you vigilantes! The authorities
are handling this! Fire on my order!
I don’t think that’s a good idea, Feral.
We saw what happened when Callie hit it.
- He’s right!
- I’m in command here!
I think he’s blown us off.
Fire!
Now he’s done it!
Those fools have given me three
ways into Megakat Labs!
- Normal weapons won’t stop them!
- You’ve made that abundantly clear, Feral.
They seem to be heading for the Biochemical
Labs. We’d better get there first!
- Any idea what to throw at these guys?
- How ’bout Feral?
- Thanks to him we’ve got three to fight!
- Then how come I only see two!?
- Hey, where’d the other one go?
- Use the X-ray Beam!
- Oh no, one’s going in the subway!
- Gotta move fast!
Oh no, too late!
So, it doesn’t like heat? Maybe it’ll
follow me onto this electrified rail and die!
Bingo!
- Razor, what is cookin’ down there?
- Fried bacteria! Rendezvous in 5 seconds.
3, 2, 1... Gotcha!
- The other two  giant zits are closin’
in on Megakat Labs! - I can handle ‘em.
They appear to be giant bacteria.
On such short notice, this is the best I could do.
It contains the most powerful antibiotics
known. Hopefully, it should stop them.
- It better work. There heading right for us!
- Don’t worry! These windows are practically
indestructible.
While the bacteria wreak havoc, I
will raid the labs!
I’m coming too! I don’t want to be
around here if this stuff doesn’t work!
- You’re a coward, Manx.
- You don’t get to be Mayor for ten terms,
without being cautious!
- Say ‘A’!
- One Megavolt Missile, away!
- I thought you said this would work!
- Give it time. 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- The SWAT Kats took care of that one, Feral.
- And I’ll take care of the other!
Got him!
It worked!
You were always an arrogant fool,
Dr. Zyme! My bacteria is immune to antibiotics!
- Time for another Megavolt Missile!
- Guess I’m one short!
- You won’t get away with this, Dr. Viper!
-  No, Miss Briggs. It’s you who won’t get away!
- Callie!
Lead him onto the bridge, then
double back! Now!
Game’s over, Dr. Viper!
Still one more play!
- Miss Briggs, are you all right?
- Yes, thanks to the SWAT Kats.
Whoever they are.
Thanks to them, half of Megakat City
is without power!
Hey, you know a better way to cook
a giant bacteria?
Looks like Burke and Murray have
got a looooong day ahead of ‘em.
Episode 3
THE WRATH OF DARK KAT
Halt or we’ll shoot!
Citizens of Megakat City, this is Dark Kat.
My business at this facility will be brief.
I warn you, do not interfere!
I repeat, do not interfere! You have witnessed
only a sample of my destructive power!
Any more acts of defiance, and Megakat
City will suffer on a grand scale.
Stop! This is a secured area!
Put me down!
They’ve breached the reactor!
Everybody get out! Get out!
As usual, Kat’s Eye News is first on the
scene of this late-breaking story at
Megakat Nuclear Plant.
And it appears Deputy Mayor Callie
Briggs has just arrived.
Everybody stand back! This area is under
Enforcer control! That means you, too, lady!
Back off, Steele. Let Deputy Mayor
Briggs through.
You must forgive Lieutenant Steele,
Miss Briggs. He’s green and a little too ambitious.
- What’s the situation here, Commander?
- Dark Kat has broken into the reactor.
We’re just about to move in, if you’d
like to stay and watch the fireworks.
Fireworks? Commander, you can’t
fire this close to the reactor!
One mistake and the whole city
could be poisoned by radioactivity!
And what do you suggest I do, Miss Briggs?
Wait for Dark Kat to steal all the nuclear matierial inside?
Feral to all units!
Move in now!
Blast that  Dark Kat! Very well.
Let’s see what he can do against this!
Dark Kat will never be able to hit three
targets traveling faster than the speed of sound!
Kats alive! Those
were the best pilots I had…
I know two better ones.
- Pepper number one.
- Well, I’ll see that, and raise you this.
It’s Callie.
He’s broken into the Megakat Nuclear
Plant, and the Enforcers are helpless to stop him.
Got it, Miss Briggs, we’re on our way!
Razor, tell the truth. Did you really
eat that last mongo pepper?
T-Bone, I can’t believe you’d even
ask me that. I can still feel the afterburn.
- No doubt about it, Razor. You are one
macho kat. - Ain’t it the truth?
- The SWAT Kats! What are they doing here?
- Your job, Feral.
So, Dark Kat’s back. Well
he won’t get away from us this time!
Good morning, Dark Kat, this
is your wakeup call!
Razor, those Baby Boomer
Missiles didn’t make a dent!
There must be some kind of
a forcefield surrounding the ship.
Since explosives don’t work, this could be the
perfect time to try out my new Scrambler Missile.
Good idea. If one million megavolts
can’t take out those shields, nothing will.
- Don’t wimp out on me now, Al! Get in closer!
- It’s too dangerous, Annie!
For Kat’s Eye News? Come on! I wanna
see Dark Kat’s expression when
the SWAT Kats whip his tail!
Great kats! We’ve lost our man
rotar! We’re goin’ down!
- We’re hit!
- Where’s that Scrambler Missile?
Jammed. That heat blast messed us
up good. We’re sittin’ ducks!
No, we’re outta here!
- Look, Commander. The SWAT Kats have failed.
- Shut up, you idiot. This is no time to gloat.
Sorry, Commander, I just thought...
Don’t think, listen. The only way to
stop Dark Kat is from inside that ship.
I’m going to try to sneak in. I’ll take along
a signal device, so you and the
Enforcers can follow me.
- Yes sir. It’s an inspired plan, sir.
- No, it’s desperate and it’s stupid!
Captain! I want you to throw everything
you’ve got at Dark Kat on my order!
Yes sir!
- If I don’t come back, you’re in command.
- I’m hardly worthy, Commander.
You can say that again.
Fire!
Where’s Feral?
He left, and I’m in charge.
Lt. Cmd. Steele, that’s with two Es.
Steele, I’m on Dark Kat’s ship.
Set up tracers while try to stop him.
Yes sir. Good luck, sir,
and break a leg.
- That Dark Kat’s never brought us
anything but bad luck.
- He almost hit our fuel tanks.
We’re here, Miss Briggs,
repairing the Turbokat.
Well you’d better hurry. Dark Kat
escaped with some nuclear fuel rods,
and Feral sneaked aboard to stop him!
Feral?!
Steele, this is Feral.
Are you following my signal?
I’m sorry, sir, but we haven’t had a
chance to scramble any jets yet.
Mechanical problems.
- Steele, where’s my backup?
- Be patient, sir. We’ll be there as
soon as possible.
But not too soon.
He hung up on me!
The little creep hung up on me!
It’s about time you said hello, Cmd. I
imagine it was getting rather chilly in
the cargo bay.
You’re too late, Dark Kat!
The Enforcers are right behind me!
You’re referring to the signal this
communicator is sending. When your men
will arrive, Megakat City will be in ruins!
Welcome aboard the Doomsday
Express, Commander! Enjoy the ride!
This is all too weird, Chance.
I mean Dark Kat, Feral, it’s like deja vu.
Deja who? What do you mean?
I mean not only are we going after Dark Kat,
but we also have to save Feral’s tail.
- Do you remember what he did to us that day?
- Remember? How could I ever forget.
- Chance, Jake, let him go it’s too
dangerous! - Negative. We’re bringing
Dark Kat in.
You guys get yourselves some
donuts.
- You two are nuts! We’re
breakin’ off pursuit! - We’ll bring
this psycho in if it kills us.
Now I’ll destroy the justice
machine that protects Megakat City!
- He’s locking missiles on the new
Enforcer building! - Then we gotta
nail him now, Jake!
No problemo! Missile deployed!
- No! My missiles won’t fire!
- Knocked out his weapons system!
One more shot and Dark Kat is
history!
This is Feral. Fall back, you two.
I’ll handle Dark Kat.
Negative, Commander Feral, we already
have our missiles locked! It’s our tag!
- I’m ordering you to back off!
- I repeat, sir, we’ve got a lock!
We’re outta the game, Chance.
We gotta eject!
Dark Kat’s gone! All because of
those two young hotshots!
- Heck of a loss, Jake.
- Monumental disaster, Chance.
I’m glad you both agree. Because this is
the last act of vandalism you will ever
perform on this city.
It was our tag, Commander! None
of this would have happened if you
hadn’t interferred, sir!
- That’s it! You’re off the force!
Both of you! - Suits us.
Who needs this crud anyway?
Just a minute. I said you’re off
the force, but not off the hook.
There’s still the matter of paying for this building, and
that’s what you two are going to be doing for a long,
long time.
Hey look, Burke. it’s those two hotshots
who wrecked the new Enforcer building.
Don’t look so hot, now, do they?
Hey, Feral says you guys gotta run the
salvage yard, ’till you pay back every penny it
costs to rebuild the Enforcer building.
Yeah, and at your present salary,
it’ll only take a thousand years!
- Take care of the place now, boys!
- We’ll be checkin’ up on ya!
This can’t be happening!
We’re pilots, not junkmen!
Hey, y’know Chance, there’s enough
military salvage here to build our own jet.
And do what?
Get back in the air and get back at
Dark Kat! And all the other criminal scum who
rear their ugly heads in Megakat City.
Only this time, we do it our way!
Well, whata re we waitin’ for,
buddy?
Time to take care of Dark Kat!
And this time, we do it our way!
My Doomsday Device is nearly complete,
Cmd. The nuclear fuel rods I just stole
are the last components I require.
In less than on hour, I will destroy Megakat
City! And from its ashes I will create a new
city, where lawlessness is the law of the land!
- Feral’s signal is coming from inside
that volcano. - Inside? You sure?
No doubt about it. Swing around.
Maybe the X-Ray Beam will show
us a way in.
The volcano’s honeycombed with
passages, but no real entrance.
- Guess we’ll just have to make
our own door? - Affirmative. Realeasing
Mole Missile, now!
Bingo! We’re in!
Time to settle up with Dark Kat.
Careful, my creeplings. We don’t want any
accidents. The SWAT Kats? You didn’t
mention they were joining the party, cmd.
The signals’ coming in strong.
Dark Kat should be dead ahead!
Watch this, Commander. The SWAT Kats
are about to discover that tunnel offers
no escape!
- T-Bone! - I know! What do you
want me to do, stop?!
So much for the SWAT Kats. Now,
where was I? Oh yes. Doomsday!
- The Glovatrix. Don’t leave base without it.
- Roger that.
Now sit there and be quiet.
This won’t take much longer.
Heads up, Dark Crud!
Too late! My bomb is armed!
Game’s over!
T-Bone!
Nevermind me! Load the bomb!
Hey, what too ya so long?
Dark Kat is getting away!
- We have to stop him!
- What do you mean, we?
Looks like you won’t be
needing a ride, Feral.
- Commander Feral, you’re okay?
- Lights against you all the way, Steele?
Sorry, sir, we had trouble
getting organized...
Mister, you don’t know what trouble is.
But I’m going to introduce you to some!
Bit sir- I’m not really trained for this.
You want my job, greenhorn?
This is how you learn it.
Today will become the blackest
day in Megakat City’s history.
- We’re too late! He’s ready to unload!
- It’s not over ’till the fat kat sings!
And now, it’s doomsday time.
Why won’t the bomb release?! It’s one
of those meddling SWAT Kats!
Your luck just ran out!
Holy kats!
Megakat City is history,
my creeplings!
Razor, jump! I’ll blast the bomb
as soon as you’re free!
No can do, T-Bone. It’ll explode for
sure and destroy the city.
I’ve gotta try to disarm this baby
right now, or we’re all goners anyway.
Any lasts requests, buddy?
Yeah. Get Dark Kat!
Just remember, always cut the red wire.
Aw, Dark Kat, you miserable psycho!
Will I never be rid of those
infernal SWAT Kats?
Switching to auxillary weapons
panel. This is for you, Razor.
Dark Kat, I am takin’ you down!
No! My shields have
shortcircuited!
- Say goodnight, Dark Kat!
- Back off, SWAT Kat! The
Enforcers will handle this!
You back off, Feral! It’s my tag!
- Steele, return fire!
- I, I don’t have any experience in this, sir.
I’ve never been in an actual air fight!
I think I’m gonna be sick!
You wanted my job?
This has gotta be the right wire.
Well, I’ll soon find out.
Out of the way, SWAT Kat! I’
m taking Dark Kat personally!
But he’s not
crowdin’ me out this time!
This one’s for you, Razor!
Too bad Razor wasn’t
here to see it.
- T-Bone, how’s it going up there?
- Razor! Mission accomplished.
And I guess you must’ve stopped
the bomb from wreckin’ the city.
Basically, yeah, but, you better pick me up
at Enforcer Headquarters, before Feral
comes back and sticks us with another bill.
On my way.
Episode 4
DESTRUCTIVE NATURE
At 300 stories, Megakat Tower is the tallest,
most modern office complex in the whole city!
Very impressive.
Oh yes! Why, it’s the perfect place to house
your corporate headquarters, Mr. Young!
Perhaps.
- How’m I doing?
- Greed brings out the best in you, Mr. Mayor.
Thank you.
He sunk most of the city treasury into
this place, but that’s off the record.
Gotcha, and thanks again for
giving me the exclusive, Callie.
Now, why don’t we continue this meeting at
Megakat Golf Course? We tee off in ten minutes!
So close to the golf course?
This is an excellent location!
That’s what I’ve been tryin’ to tell you!
Right This way, gentlemen!
Not this time, sucker! You’re dead meat!
Ha! Gotcha! Uh oh, sneak attack!
Got ‘em! Two million points and
I’ve saved the universe!
Well I’m tryin’ to save this place
from the smell of sour milk.
- So that’s what all this plant business is about.
- Good for the environment, good for the air.
But not so good for my game score.
And I was goin’ for a personal best, too!
Relax, buddy. Space Kat!
There's always another universe to save.
Today, only a few potted plants occupy the
Megakat Tower, but when it opens next month
this place is guaranteed to be a bustling
business center!
This is Ann Gora, Kat's Eye News.
And this is Callie Briggs, klutz. No, it
couldn't be!
Get some good shots of the courtyard.
What the?!
Thanks to my growth formula, this
building is now impenetrable!
But I count on you, my creations,
to protect me from Feral, his Enforcers,
and most of all, those meddling SWAT Kats!
It is Dr. Viper!
Soon, this foul city will be one giant,
glorious swamp!
- I’d better get some help!
- A spy!
No way out!
Not connected yet!
- Yes, Miss Briggs?
- We’ve got problems! It's Viper!
- Viper?! Where?
- At Megakat Towers! And this time he’s got
an army of plant monsters to...
Misd Briggs! Let’s kick some
Viper tail!
Report!
According to witnesses, Commander,
this stuff just sprang up in minutes!
But it’s gonna take
a week to cut through.
Not if we burn our way in!
That’s a ten story wall of dry brush, sir!
If our fire gets outta hand it’ll torch the whole city!
Objection noted.
Ann Gora, Kat’s Eye News! Commander
Feral, are you aware that Deputy Mayor
Briggs is trapped somewhere in that tower?
Briggs? That figures. Get the choppers
ready, we’ll take the tower from above!
Kats alive! This stuff’s acid, eating
right through my chopper!
Weapon systems gummed up! Viper...?
Should’ve known that crazy lizard would
be behind this mess!
Run, Feral, you fool. Because there’s
nothing you can do to stop me!
- Let me go!
- Save your breath, Miss Briggs!
My plantimals obey only me. Besides,
you don’t want to run away and miss out on
all the excitement!
What is that thing?
My spore pod? Why it’s going to explode!
And at this height, it’s beautiful spores will
cover the entire city!
I can see it all now. A spectacular new
Megakat City. No more ugly metal and plastic,
only beautiful swamp...
ruled by me! Dr. Viper’s Megaswamp
City! It will be so beautiful!
Wake up and smell the coffee,
Viper! Here come the SWAT Kats!
- Looks like a farmer’s market down there!
- It’s Viper alright, and he’s got Callie!
Attack them, my little pets!
- We’ve got some plug-ugly company!
- Ok, T-Bone. Weapon systems ready.
- Hey these things are spittin’ acid!
- So I’ve noticed! I’m takin’ evasive action!
Piranha Missiles, away!
- T-Bone, those things melted my
missiles! - Attack! Destroy them!
You see, Miss Briggs, my armies are
endless! She’s gone! You fool, you let her escape!
- Say again, Razor? You must be jokin’!
- I said, I’ll penetrate the building, and...
- ...come up on Viper from underneath!
- That’s a negative, Razor. Plants are
takin’ over the whole building.
- Affirmative, but Callie’s in there, T-Bone!
- Right.
- Maintain radio contact at all times, do you copy?
- Affirmative, T-Bone. I’m goin’ in!
- Razor, you okay? Talk to me, buddy!
- Looks like a swamp in here, but so far so good.
- What’s your situation?
- It’s weird. Those flying cabbages don’t
attack me unless I’m close to the roof.
Just keep away from ‘em. I’ll call ya
when I find Callie.
Don’t like the look of this.
Chew on this!
I don’t believe it!
- Any progress, Razor?
- No sign of Callie.
Gotta run! Out!
Cmd. Feral, do you have a plan for
getting Deputy Mayor Briggs out of there?
Yes, a simple one. We’re going in!
Fire!
- That did it, Commander! We’re through!
- Let’s move in!
- Blast it!
- Looks like Feral got stopped at the door.
What?!
Excuse my clumsiness!
You play through, I have to a phone call.
Get me Feral!
Soon, my lovely, soon! Let those fools
waste their time. In fifteen minutes,
Megakat City will be mine!
he toughest tanks we have, and that,
that thing melted ‘em like butter!
Now you listen to me, Mayor, Dr. Viper has
turned your pet skyscraper into a living
weed patch, and...
No, you listen to me, Feral! The city has
a billion dollars sunk in that tower.
Use weed killer if you have to, but
get that wacko Viper out of there now!
- And don’t damage the building
doing it! - You don’t understand...
Don’t do it, Feral! My friends here are
about to sign a ten year lease!
- Is there a problem, Mayor Manx?
- Don’t be ridiculous, not at all.
Great! I can’t burn, cut or blast!
What does he expect me to do?
Leave it to the SWAT Kats?!
What’s it take to stop these things!?
- That should buy me some time.
- Oh no. Wake up! Oh, Razor I’m so sorry!
- Callie? Uh, Miss Briggs?
- Are you okay? I hit you pretty hard.
- Good thing we’re required to wear
helmets. - I thought you were one of them.
This way, hurry!
Make room, Miss Briggs!
- Copter 1 is on approach from the chemical
factory. - We’ll try it the Mayor’s way.
Let’s see how that cabbage
likes a thousand gallons of weed killer!
Drop payload on my command!
Roger! We have target aquisisioned!
Now!
Gotcha! We’re goin’ in!
Oh no! Commander, weed killer
only makes it bigger!
Is there no way to destroy
these things!?
Feral’s strikin’ out big time down there.
Razor, what’s your status?
I’ve got Miss Briggs. We’re in the
ventilation shaft heading for the roof.
The roof?! That’s a negative!
Those critters won’t let me get
close enough for pickup!
- No time for that. Miss Briggs says Viper’s...
- He’s growing a pod to destroy the city!
- We’re gonna have tos top him from inside.
- Well ya don’t have much time.
- From what I can see, that ugly thing is about
ready to burst! - We’re on our way, big buddy!
Am I just scared or is it freezing
in here?
- Now, Razor! Blast ‘em!
-  With what!? I’ve got nothing left but
grappling hooks!
- It worked!
- Yeah, but the cold stopped ‘em first.
- Too bad we couldn’t freeze the whole building.
- Hey, maybe we can! Come on!
T-Bone, I think we found a way to stop Viper.
But you’re gonna have to make a fast pickup
at the space center.
- I’m there, buddy. What do you need?
- Super rocket coolant! We’ll meet you on
the roof in 10 minutes.
How can you be so sure we’ll
make it in ten minutes?
‘Cause we’re gonna take a shortcut!
- You call this a shortcut?
- Hang on tight!
- I don’t know about thi-aaaaah!
- This is easy.
Yeah, piece of cake.
Turbokat, I say again, this is flight control,
you are not cleared for this area. Over.
Understood, flight control. But I have
an emergency situation here.
- Explain the nature of your
emergency. Over. - Here’s the deal…
- What’s that SWAT Kat want
with a tank of super rocket coolant?
- Who cares?
Yeah, but that one barrel has enough
coolant to freeze a whole city block!
Razor, we’ve got trouble!
Big trouble!
It’s just you and me now, sweetness.
Feral is helpless, and the SWAT Kats
have run away in their stupid jet!
You’re so beautiful!  It’s going to be
a shame to have you explode!
If anything’s happened to him, I’ll….
- Nice knowing you, Razor!
- Thanks, and it still will be.
I’ve been
saving this for last! Hang on!
Attack! Protect our spore pod!
Time for some real flyin’!
I owe it that much to Razor.
Eat my backwash, you lettuceheads!
Barbecued cabbage, my favorite!
They’re tougher than I thought!
- Don’t tell me your givin’ up!
- Razor!
The SWAT Kats have failed!
In a few minutes, it will be all over!
- You can say that again, snake-puss!
- What!? it’s not possible!
- Anything’s possible, ugly!
- You can’t stop me now!
- It’s oblivion for you, SWAT Kat!
- Razor! No!
Yes! But don’t worry, Miss Briggs,
you’ll be joining him!
Need a lift?
- This is great! My weapons systems are
all gummed up! - Musta gotten too close
to those sap-slingers.
Yeah. Well, I’m gonna have to drop our freeze
bomb by hand, if that flying produce
doesn’t drop us, first!
Get ready, Viper! TheSWAT Kats are
gonna put the big chill or your big plans!
T-Bone, go for that big air
conditioning unit on the roof!
Right on target! It’s now or never!
Get clear! On the double!
Next time, Dr. Viper better make his
plans frost-free.
Better drop me off, guys. I think the
Mayor’s gonna need sedation.
Thanks! It was fun, w ehave to
do it again sometime.
- Yeah, right. Take care!
- See you later, Miss Briggs...
...we have to get back. Razor
has to water his plants.
Oh, no. I think I’ve had enough
gardening for one day.
Thank you for the golf game,
but I think we will pass on
your most generous offer.
Now, now, now don’t be hasty!
A fresh coat of paint, I’ll upgrade
the carpetting!
We have some lovely parting gifts,
just don’t part! Free golf clubs!  Come back!
Episode 5
METALLIKATS
Best katnip in Megakat City,
Katscratch.
See? It’s the good stuff!
Where did you learn to drive, the
demolition derby?
- So I run a couple a’ stop signs.
- Yeah, and here they all are.
Look, are we goin’ in, or we gonna
yammer?
Who the-?
Sorry we’re late, boys. Unavoidable
delays.
Mac? Molly? Is that you?
- Mac, they remember us.
- They oughta! We used to run this mob!
We heard youse drowned, tryin’
to bust outta Alkatraz.
Yeah, and what’s with them voices?
How come you guys sound so weird?
- It’s not just our voices that’ve changed.
- We had a complete makeover.
- Whaddaya think?
- I think youse two should’ve stayed dead!
It’s my mob now, and you
guys are history!
What a shockin’ developement!
The rest of you lugs listen up! The
Metallikats are runnin’ this city, now! And as
soon as we finish some personal business...
- Like rubbin’ out that crud Mayor Manx!
- We’re gonna tear up this town like a scratchin’ post!
- You’re the boss!
- Whatever ya say!
We’re with ya, guys!
Thanks for your confidance, creeps!
But traitors like you don’t fit into our new plans.
Molly and I are our own gang now,
and we’re dealin’ all of you out!
So long, losers!
- Thermal sensor has detected an
explosion by the harbor. - Better take a look.
- It’s the tuna factory. What a waste!
- Lowering the X-ray Scope.
- What the heck was that?!
- Well, whatever it was, it’s goin’
over 200 miles an hour!
- No kiddin’. I’m goin’ after it!
- Negative, T-Bone. We’ve got other priorities.
The X-ray Scope reveals activity
inside that burning building. We’ve gotta
help them first!
- Put us in hover mode, T-Bone. I’m gonna
try a foam bomb. - Roger that.
Fire’s under control.
Goin’ in to help casualties.
- Looks like the cavalry’s arrived.
- Which is our cue to split. They
can get inside faster than us.
The SWAT Kats. I figured those
hoodlums had something to do with this.
And you say the SWAT Kats are
responsible for this fire, Cmd. Feral?
Absolutely! Alot of you out there may
consider the SWAT Kats to be heroes, but I
think this wanton destruction proves what
criminals those two really are!
- Mrs Briggs, do you have any comments on
this? - With all due respect to Cmd. Feral,
I don’t think he has a shred of evidence
to support his attack on the SWAT Kats.
Fango! Up to your neck in trouble
again, I see. Talk to me, you creep. Did the
SWAT Kats do this?
It wasn’t the SWAT Kats.  It was
Mac and Molly Mange. They did it.
You’re crazy! Mac and Molly have
been dead for months.
No, they ain’t dead! They’re some
kinda robots now! Callin’ themselves
the Metallikats! They’re back from...
...the dead to get revenge! And Mayor
Manx is next on their list!
- Mayor Manx? Why him?
- Didn’t the Mayor deny their parole,
Deputy Mayor?
That’s correct. If anyone deserved to spend
all their nine lives in jail, it’s those two.
Then you better tell the Mayor to crawl into the
deepest hole he can find and stay there!
Bullets don’t stop the Metallikats! Nothin’
stops ‘em.
Take this trash out of here. Don’t
worry your little head, Briggs, the Enforcers
will handle this situation.
And if you can’t, I know two
heroes who can.
Have you seen the paper?
Hey! I’m tryin’ to watch Scaredy-Kat!
It’s an 80-hour marathon!
It’s about that fire we put out. Paper
says it was caused by a couple of robots
called the Metallikats.
Fine, let Feral handle it. Now, if you
don’t mind, I’m trying to watch Scaredy Kat.
- Chance, it says here the Mayor’s in danger.
- Look, watch what happens when
Scaredy-Kat opens the closet again.
Callie could be in danger, too.
Hey, come on, you slouch! We’ve
got work to do!
There’s too much at stake here.
Can’t afford to fail. Last ball, Manx.
This one’s for the game.
Mayor! You’re in grave danger!
All units in the area,
please respond.
Got an interesting emergency call
comin’ in, T-Bone. Try the police band.
All available units, armored vehicle
out of control, main and central. Please
respond.
- Could be the Metallikats. Whaddaya
say, T-Bone? - I say let’s kick some robot tail!
- Make way for the Metallikat Express!
- Mac, you are absolutely the worst
driver in history!
I don’t have to drive well in this little
hotrod. Everyone else jumps outta the way!
- Deploying Shark Missile, now!
- What’s goin’ on?!
- It’s the SWAT Kats!
- Those pests!
I’ll teach ‘em a lesson.
The Relentless Missile!
Hang onto your stomach!
We’re climbin’!
Just glad I skipped lunch!
You can forget about supper, too,
if we can’t shake this missile!
20 meters and closing!
It’s a heat-seeker! It’s stayin’ right
on our engine exhaust!
It’s like tryin’ to lose your own shadow!
Yeah, but this shadow’s carryin’ high
explosives!
Feral will hold them. I mean,
nobody’s better than Feral, right?
Let’s hope so, Mayor, for our sakes.
So sue me! How was I supposed to know
that was your sister’s car back there?!
You always hated my side of the family!
Sometimes I don’t even know why I married you!
Wait for the order, men.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Mac and Molly Mange, you’re
under arrest! Surrender, or we’ll fire!
- Knock yourself out, Commander!
- Fire!
The Mayor’s on the tenth floor.
Take the inside route.
- And what are you gonna do?
- I’m goin’ up this way!
No, no! This can’t be happening!
- You’re still there?
- I’m goin’, I’m goin’!
We’re done for! Nobody can stop
those machines!
Except the SWAT Kats. I hope.
- Callie’s calling on the distress band!
- One crisis at a time! Guess it’s time
for Plan Z!
- T-Bone, I hate Plan Z!
- No other choice, kiddo. Prepare for
engine shutdown!
Engine’s cold. Launching Decoy
Missile!
- Great job, T-Bone. What a team!
- We’re not outta the woods yet! The
engines won’t restart!
This is why I hate Plan Z!
I don’t know about you, but I’m
getting the heck out of here!
Mayor, stop! The other robot’s in the
building somewhere!
- We have to eject!
- No way!
- Oh, how did I know you were gonna
say that? - C’mon, baby, you can do it!
One tiny miracle is all I ask!
I thought we bought the big litterbox for sure
that time! Ah, but the Turbokat came through
for us, just like always.
- T-Bone, it’s Callie again.
- Yes, Miss Briggs? What’s the problem?
I’m in the Mayor’s office, T-Bone, and
right now I could really, really, use your help!
Mayor’s office!
Come on, come on.
Mayor Manx, I was just lookin’ for you!
- Well, well. Look what the kat dragged in.
- Please, please, I beg you! I’ll make any
deal just don’t hurt me!
Too late, Mayor. You had your chance to
make a deal with us earlier, when we offered
you a fat bribe for our parole.
But ya turned us down.
Bribe? I swear I don’t know what you’re talking
about! Molly, please. Life’s just dealt you
some bad cards, that’s all.
No! You dealt us the bad hand! You
don’t get it, do ya? It began two months ago,
on Alkatraz Island.
- Okay, first Katscratch.
- What about money, and transportation?
- Okay, okay! First the bank, then Katscratch.
- We’d get there faster if you’d help me row.
- Shut up! I hear somethin’.
- Whaddaya hear?
I dunno! Can’t see a thing in
this soup…
I’m still alive. What’s wrong with
my body? Mac? Mac, where are you?
- Behind ya, Molly.
- Mac, we’re all silvery and weird! What’s
happened to us?
I don’t know, but I’m gonna wring the
neck of the guy who did this to us!
That would be my neck, young fellow.
I think the masks are good likenessess.
I’ll create full bodysuits for you
to wear. No sense scaring everybody every
time you go into public.
- Who are you?
- Why’d you do this to us?
My name is Professor Hackle.
When my robots found you, your bodies
were destroyed.
The only way to save you was to
plant your minds inside my robots.
We’re robots?! You turned us
into tin cans?!
I know this is a shock, but in every
way, you are faster and stronger. The only
differance now is your bodies are steel,
instead of flesh.
- We’ve still got our brains, right?
- I’ve transferred your memories onto
a hard disk.
Mac, I don’t like this.
I dunno, I think I could get to like this.
I’ve never felt so powerful, like I could rip
apart this whole town with my bare claws!
Indeed you could, my boy, but fate
has delivered you to me for another reason.
My whole life I have created such weapons
of destruction for the military. Laser weapons,
rockets, even bombs.
However, now I have
turned my efforts toward making a contribution
to katkind. That is why you two are so important.
As soon as you are healed, I will present you both
to the scientific acadamy. Imagine the great minds
that could be saved...
...with this form of brain transplant. And history
will forgive me. Goodnight, children. Sleep well.
- Sleep well.
- Yeah, goodnight, Professor.
-  Imagine leavin’ us alone to swipe all this
loot! - Yeah, what a sucker!
- Hey Mac, look at this!
- Kats alive! Transportation! Let’s go to town!
End of story, end of you!
Leave him alone, you metal morons! He
didn’t turn down your parole, I did!
And who are you?
Calico Briggs, Deputy Mayor. Manx hasn’t
done an ounce of paperwork around here for years!
I turned down you parole,
bribes and all.
- You? You let us rot inside that prison?
- That’s right, sister! And I’d do it again in a
heartbeat!
- You don’t scare me, you brass bimbo!
- Remember to land on your feet, Deputy
Mayor!
- Hey, need a lift?
- It’s about time, you guys! Catch you on
your lunch hour?
- Careful, Miss Briggs.
- Thanks, Razor.
- Think you can handle the Mayor while I go
ather them? - “Think you can handle the Mayor?”
I’m gonna get the Mayor,
you stay here!
Right here, Mac!
Hey, I guess we’re better built
than I thought.
Don’t you know a rust-proof robot
when you see one?
Party’s over! Aah! That ashtray!
- The sand jammed the gun, and my parts, too!
- Well, Mayor, any parting words for your
fellow citizens?
- Molly! I don’t feel so good…
- Mac!
-  I didn’t do it! It’s not my fault!
Jump, Mayor! Jump on the wing!
Hey, lady! Don’t mess up my jet!
That’s it, right this way.
Come on in.
I asked you nicely!
Thank you, SWAT Kats! And don’t
forget about SWAT Kat Day!
Are you really going to have
a SWAT Kat Day?
Don’t be ridiculous. How would it
look if I through a parade for a couple of
vigilantes?
I was just being polite. Feral!
Have this mess cleaned up! Take it to the
metal salvage yard!
- Well, there you go, Professor Hackle.
- Oh, yes. Thank you, lads.
- This will advance my research considerabley.
- Sure, Professor. Glad to help.
You two have been very naughty!
I’ve been looking for you for days! I’m afraid
I’ll have to make some adjustments on you
two before I can allow you to be examined by
the acadamy.
- Since you’re gonna make adjustments,
why don’t you make him taller?
- And her better lookin’!
- Must you two always argue?
- Better lookin’?! Listen Mr. Cyclops...
- ...you ain’t exactly easy on the eyes yourself.
- Hey, Professor, can you make it so she
can’t talk?
Oh, drop dead!