The fight to control
illegal immigration isn't just
on our borders... Lawmakers in Arizona
passed a sweeping overhaul...
In a few months, president
Obama will push
legislation to legalize the
nation's 12 million illegal immigrants.
...I feel bad when the bus is leaving--
And I know that he's there.
Illegal immigration...
America's 21st century dilemma.
It's estimated that more than
a million illegal immigrants
enter the U.S. every year.
They face countless dangers.
Some succumb to dehydration
and exposure.
Some fall victim to human
traffickers and warring
drug cartels.
And others...
Simply disappear.
Why do they risk their lives?
Because the American dream's
still so powerful.
Hey, Spielberg.
We get it. Come on, man.
Got a headache.
Dude, dude, guys, check out
the bullet holes in that sign.
I feel like a bear took a
shit in my head.
Hey, Brad, can you pull over,
brother?
Brad.
Brad, pull... Brad.
Hey, we do need to shoot some
b-roll on that.
Pull the shit over, Bradley.
Thank you.
No, no, no, no.
We're already late.
How do you be late?
We're in Mexico.
Jim.
What? I'm sor--, I had a big
night last night, O.K.?
I slept in.
Because... Sake bombs.
Where were you, by the way?
Uh, you didn't invite me,
douchebag.
Right.
Next time.
Next time, definitely... maybe.
What's up, kid?
Guys... I think that
kid took my wallet.
What are you drinking there?
Electrolytes, bro.
You look like shit. Mmm.
I love being around creative people
like you guys; You're so, like,
in the moment.
So... Brad.
Where are you from again?
Uh, well, I was actually born in Dallas.
And, and, and how long did
you live in London?
I was in London for about a year.
A whole year?
Travis, don't you...
Have anything to do?
Keep yourself busy?
No, this is all I got to do
right now, actually.
It works out nice.
Babe, babe, I can handle
myself, all right?
Yeah, west Texas boys could be
quite rambunctious.
How do you say "suck my cock"
in an English accent?
Suck on my cock.
Suck, suck on my cock.
Cock, cock, cock... Suck on my cock.
I'm the queen of england.
I suck cock... With Brad.
You know what's really funny?
She actually hates London.
Didn't you say that?
You, you hated...? No, I
just hated London with you.
Ooh... get a little e.C.U.
On that one.
Excuse me, Mr. Whitaker.
No comment.
What's your response to the
allegations you ran a sweatshop
of illegal immigrants?
I run a family business.
A family business.
That's very noble of you, sir.
Does a family business threaten
and intimidate their employees?
Does it deny their workers
safety equipment?
Does it fire them when they're
injured on the job?
Whoops.
Get that camera out of my face!
Mr. Whitaker, what about
Miguel Gonzales, the man that
you crippled?
Was he family?
Would you apologize to him?
Car troubles?
I have a Mexican friend,
he can fix that.
He's a citizen though, is that
gonna be an issue?
Did you get that?
Tell me you got that.
...all right, let's get going.
Got everything.
O.K., I'll ping you.
All right.
That sound good?
Sorry.
Be safe.
See you back in Austin, babe.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Bye, babe.
Hey, later Brad.
Let's hang out.
Yeah? No.
Si.
Guys, guys, this is my cousin
Alberto.
...my friends...
This guy is the director.
Yo, man.
Hi, Liz.
Yeah, Liz.
Will.
No, no, no, no, no.
No touch, no touch.
No touch-ey.
Whoa, whoa...
So, how much is, uh, how much
is this trip costing you?
Much... eh... eh, si...
Yes, yes.
...my daughter.
Si.
...have a family.
Gracias! Gracias!
Here's, um...
Here's one thousand dollars.
Mmm.
What?
2500 is the best he can do.
No, you told me 200
each-- that's one thousand
dollars, comprendo?
Would you tell him that?
Hey, hey, hey!
Would you stop filming,
please?
I stopped.
Thank you.
Now it's a thousand dollars
each.
Fine, fine.
2500.
- Bueno... bueno...
- Bueno...
What?
He says we won't regret it.
I already do.
What?
He says you're very beautiful.
Right.
Thank you.
Como esta...
Come on.
You all set?
Behind me, two dozen men, women
and children have sacrificed
everything for this moment.
They're about to cross over 300
miles of treacherous terrain for
Miles of treacherous terrain for
the promise of a better life.
We're gonna join them.
How was that?
Patronizing.
Come on.
Jim!
Let's go, man. What are you doing?
O.K., coming!
Sorry, bro.
Had to take care of some
business.
You're trying to get
some bud?
What?
I get nauseous on long
car rides.
When I found about out
what happened to Miguel, I cried.
...probably for the first time
since my daughter Claudia
was born.
Family is the most important
thing to me, supporting them and
when I found out, I had to do
something.
Boo!
What are you doing?
I'm doing an interview, silly.
You can't do that.
I'm doing an interview. I'm a blessed man.
I'm a blessed man.
I love you.
I know.
Gracias.
Disneyland. Disneylandia!
...have a safe trip. Ciao,
amiga, good-bye. Gracias.
Shh.
All right, all right,
we're recording.
Come on, let's go.
Wait, wait, wait...
Good, O.K.
Um...
I can't disclose our exact
location, but, um, as you can
see behind me, everyone is
heading to the point of entry.
The border fence is just past
that hill over there.
Uh... We're about to cross,
illegally, into the
United States. Got that shit? Good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, go, go!
Watch the camera! Holy shit.
Holy shit.
It's dark in here, guys. We're gonna
have to turn on the night vision.
Night vision.
Fuck me.
Hey, dude, you O.K.?
- Yeah. What is this place?
- It's a drug tunnel.
I don't know about this
at all.
You a little scared?
No.
A lot scared.
You all right?
Yeah.
[Indistinct whispering
What was that?
I don't know-- go.
Let's move.
Don't worry.
Fine, I'm fine.
Not nervous.
[Man speaking Spanish,
Shh, shh. Shh...
What is it?
Shit, I can't tell. Wait-- no, no!
Oh, my God!
Davie, get, get back here.
Get that fucking camera off me.
Amen.
Hey, t.
I'm gonna make sure everyone's
all right, O.K.?
Hey.
Hey, man, you O.K.?
No.
O. K.
Fucking bullshit.
Jesus.
What the fuck did we get
ourselves into?
I know.
Listen to me.
In eight hours, we're gonna
be... we're gonna be back,
back in our apartment.
All right?
Take a shower.
We'll have a beer.
Oh, a shower, man.
We'll smoke a fatty.
All right? Relax. You're O.K.
Listen, this was a mistake.
I'm gonna call Brad,
he's gonna come pick us up.
No, no, no.
Do not call Brad.
I have to call him.
Hey, what did we say?
Are you kidding me?
What? Are you kidding me? We're done.
We're done.
We did not sign up for this.
I know, this is a thousand
times better.
You think that was better?
How was that better, Travis?
Somebody died back there.
That is not better.
Put your phones--
Listen to me, O.K.?
This trip, this whole thing
was your idea, all right?
We got shit here, we got shit
we got shit here, we got shit
no one has ever even
seen before.
That's true.
Let's go finish.
The worst is over.
Let's just... let's just finish
All right.
We're falling apart.
Is he O.K.?
Are you O.K.?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You all right?
Thirsty, you want some water?
Yeah.
Do you have any?
I don't know what happened
to mine.
Don't worry about me,
I'm fine.
No-- do you have my water,
actually?
Hello?
Hey, hey, yeah, it's me.
We're in the U.S.
You're not gonna believe what
happened.
No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
It's O.K., yeah.
Um, he's, he's all right,
he's not bothering me.
Fuck you, Brad.
Yeah, that was him.
That's fine.
I can handle him, O.K.?
Come on.
Go on. I love you. O.K., bye.
Are we rolling?
Yeah.
Follow the coyote when he's
over there.
Make sure you get the coyote
when he's going up over there.
There he goes, there he
goes, there he goes.
Shh.
It's O.K.
[Indistinct
[Indistinct whispering
We're now on American
soil, where it looks like our midnight
where it looks like our midnight
ride has arrived.
Everyone seems to be in good spirits.
If you look around, the tension
has died.
There's a stillness to the
night.
Seems like it's gonna be a
pretty tight fit.
Shit, grab your shit.
Grab your shit, come on,
go, go, go.
Are you getting this, filming?
Wait-- no, no, no,
my camera!
Fuck!
O. K., it's working.
Selina, selina, come here.
Wanna do shadow puppets? It
looks like a mouse to me.
That's a very good one.
It's very cramped in here.
We're about a hundred Miles away
from the safe house.
The air is tense. Let's go
talk to some of our travelers.
Como?
Yes, officer?
I'm gonna need you
to step out of your vehicle.
What did I do wrong, sir?
Shh, shh, shh.
Yeah?
Can you hear me,
it's an emergency.
Hello?
He-- damn it, nothing.
Put the camera away.
We've gotta put it away now.
Put them away now.
Do what I'm saying.
Put 'em away, just do what I'm
saying, put it down. All right.
All right.
Everybody should get your
passports ready, I'll try...
We're Americans!
Please! Don't shoot!! Please.
What is your full name?
Travis Williams.
Why am I blindfolded?
Full name. Now.
Elizabeth tonin.
My name? Uh... It's James.
Bowman.
David Juan Luis
Martin decario.
All right, we'll do this
the hard way.
What are you doing here?
I'm sound.
Speak up.
Sound.
Sound guy.
I'm a director.
Director of what?
I already told you,
we were shooting a documentary.
About what?
Illegal immigration.
Are you a U.S. citizen?
Come on, man, you have
my passport-- what is this?
Look in my wallet please.
Check-- give me my wallet.
Look, there should be
a wad of cash--
You want your wallet?
There's your wallet.
We're grad students.
Making a thesis film.
Nobody's gonna see it.
That is peyote.
It was in your backpack.
No, uh, that's,
that's not possible.
Because... I don't even
own a backpack... sorry.
Ah! Ow!
You feel that?
...listen to me very carefully. Whatever
you think this is... it's far worse.
What do I have to do? What, what do I have
to do to get them out of this, tell me.
Uh.
Hold on, just gimme a second.
My crew and I have been detained
by a group... Of patriots.
They promised, they said that
they would let us go if we
document their activities...
And their philosophy. If, uh, if we
spread word of their movement, so...
Is that good, is that it or no?
Is that O.K.?
Over here.
Come closer.
Illegal immigration is a plague
that threatens to overtake the
United States of America.
We are sick and tired of these
vermin pouring in over
our borders...
Crawling up on our shores...
Bleeding this country dry.
We are slowly losing our
country, but we are determined
to take it back.
Well, as you will see,
we're not without mercy. All
children are free to go. Psst, mira.
No, no, no, no!
No.
No, mija.
No, mija, no.
Mama.
Te quieres, tu mami...
Children are smart.
They'll find their way home.
Dios mio.
Let's show them
what we're really about.
Mi Nina, mi Nina.
Listen up.
I need one camera.
Him, to film over there.
Excuse me.
Yeah, you put
that on-- hey, not yet.
Come back here.
One camera.
You, stay here with me.
What the hell do you do?
I'm a producer.
You're a what?
She holds the batteries.
Listen up.
I have only one rule with you.
I talk, you film.
If you interfere, if you say one
single word without being spoken
to, you're not gonna like
what's gonna happen.
Is that clear?
Good.
Let's roll. You there, not too close.
That's enough.
This charming fellow forces
women to cross our border
as drug mules.
They have to swallow condoms
filled with cocaine.
It's about
the only time you ever hear of
Mexicans using condoms. If they
refuse, a family member gets shot.
He said "fuck your mother." He
said "fuck my mother"? Youmother.
I got this.
Open up, come here, open up.
Open up! Open up!
Open up!
Take it!
Take it all!
90% of drugs in America come
from vermin like this.
You know what
you're doing to my country?
[Translates
The harm that
you are causing?
The people that
you're hurting?
The families that you're tearing apart?
Enough, enough of this, enough!
Aw, shit.
What? The condom broke.
Fuck.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
What the fuck.
What is this place?
Oh.
Come on.
You too.
That's my camera.
That's a security
camera now-- don't touch it.
Now try and get some sleep.
You've got a long day tomorrow.
Jesus Christ.
They're gonna knock our
fucking teeth out.
No, they're not, o. K.?
We're gonna stick together.
Oh, stick together?
Stick together and do what?
What was that?
I'm gonna get us
out of here.
I'm gonna get us the fuck
What was that?
Oh God.
- I'm getting us out of here.
- Fuck this.
Put the camera on.
Now!
I'm turning it on!
Turn it on!
It's on, it's on!
It's on?
Yes, it's on.
Rise and shine, everyone.
Z wants to see you.
Now, just keep filming, O.K.?
Get some breakfast, have a
good time, take a load off.
Good time, take a load off.
Have a little bite to eat,
but keep that camera on, O.K.?
Come on.
You must all be hungry.
Welcome, everybody.
Please sit down.
You want me to bring
them breakfast, Mr. z?
Oh yes, please do. Thank you, marta.
I am really impressed what you
got here.
You've got some very interesting
shit on this.
Really nice.
Thank you, marta.
Eat.
Hungry?
What?
Hey, sweetheart, it's impolite
to stare.
You have maids?
Well, they came to this
country to work, and by God,
I'm not gonna stop 'em.
Please. Please. Eat.
Where is he taking her?
Hey, come back, come back.
This young gentleman
had a question.
Get this on film.
I want to know where
you're taking her.
She's sick.
I'm taking her to the infirmary.
You don't have
a doctor here.
Of course we do.
We're not savages.
Grab that.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm giving it to her.
Pick it up.
We have people for that.
You heard me.
You pick that up,
you motherfucker-- hey!
Rosa, give that back.
What do you want
Throw it out!
Throw it out.
That's her job.
Don't ever do that again.
I think we've gotten off on
the wrong foot.
So, let's start over.
Get to know each other.
Jim.
I'm hungry.
Marta is a fantastic cook.
What about you?
Are you on a diet?
Here.
I don't want it.
Come on.
You have to eat.
It's protein.
It's good for you.
Chew, chew, chew, chew. That's
how we do it.
This, I can show
you, this is El toro's room.
Up here.
Giving a tour.
Giving a tour!
He's got all kinds of, like,
computers and, and stuff
in there.
Let's see.
These gates right here,
they're meant for,
originally for cattle.
But they work real good
on the Mexicans.
And it just keeps them
right in line.
And then if you look down,
there's, we painted this
orange line here because some
of them...
Some of them aren't,
aren't real smart.
So you paint the line and then
they just follow right along.
And it's like, it makes it
really, really easy.
Just on this side, that's where
the artist's room is.
He's got all kinds of stuff
in there.
And my room is just on
the other side.
And then a whole, this is all,
this is like right in the middle
of everything.
And that's the, um,
the infirmary is over here.
Where's that pregnant
girl that you guys were supposed
to bring here?
Um...
And then just supplies.
We keep supplies right here.
Oh, and then, um,
here's the food.
We just mix it in.
One of my jobs.
Oh, here.
She's, she's one of
my favorites.
Her, her name's espa-something,
but I, I just call her Maria.
And, I like to, I like to spoil
her real good.
Because she's my favorite.
Why is she your favorite?
Oh.
She's real smart, real smart.
I'll show you this.
Apple slice.
♪ Maria had a little...
Lamb?
See?
Here, this is the women's room.
We keep all the women
just over here.
Everybody say hi.
They're real shy.
They're real, lot of them
are real shy.
Hi.
Must be, must be that time
of the month.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
You need to stay over here
with everybody else.
He's just filming.
Travis!
Oh God, Alberto.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
'Cause, listen.
You gotta stay back, 'cause, listen.
'Cause they will bite you.
'Cause, listen.
'Cause they will bite you. They
will bite you and you'll be sorry.
No, shh.
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
I'm not a Mexican like you.
I'm a God damn American citizen.
Get his wife.
You and your wife have
been granted a rare opportunity
to gain entry into the united
states of America.
This is the official
citizenship test.
Take it away, Remy.
O. K., I'ma give you
the rules now.
O. K., we're gonna ask
you some questions.
And for every one that you get
right, we're gonna undo one of
her wrists, so we're making it
real easy on you.
Question one. How many representatives
are there in congress?
How many representatives
Oh yeah, no, it's not a
English question,
it's a math question.
You know math?
435, you're wrong.
O.K., question two. Who
wrote the star-spangled banner?
Huh?
Que?
Now that is very close.
Francis Scott key.
It's not que, it's key!
Stop, stop it!
Please!
Please stop.
When I applied for my
citizenship, I had to take this test.
And I was proud.
I studied very hard.
But you're defending a man who
entered a country he
doesn't even respect!
He doesn't understand
what you're saying.
When it comes to fucking food
stamps, these people understand
English perfectly well!
O.K., question three.
How many stripes are there in
the U.S. flag?
Hey, hey, hey! Cheating. No cheating.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Twelve?
No, no, thirteen.
Thirteen.
Thirteen!
Ah!
Thirteen, thirteen.
Correct.
Thirteen!
Undo! Undo her wrist.
Good job.
Keep up the good work.
Question number four.
O.K.
O.K. Hey, hey, no, you, no. No, no, no.
Who said, "give me liberty or
give me death?"
Please.
"Give me liberty or Clock is ticking.
No.
No!
Thomas Jefferson.
What is that?
This is one of the most famous
quotes in American history.
And it defines the
American spirit.
Give me liberty or give me...
Oh my God!
I thought we had
an agreement... huh?
We talk, you film.
Pick up the camera.
Someone pick up the
fucking camera!
O.K., O.K.
O. K.
Get that up.
You hear me?
O.K., O.K.
Pick that thing up.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Jesus.
Continue filming.
Now... What is the answer?
Toma jesserfee?
Toma... Je-Jeff... Huh?
Je-Jeffrey...?
Oh.
He's very close.
Now, the answer is
Patrick Henry... hmm.
Put him on the rack and bring
in another wetback.
Wait, wait.
No, no, stop, stop.
We need him.
We need another cameraman.
Davie can't do this shit
by himself.
Well, she seems to be
handling herself perfectly well.
She's a producer.
She doesn't know shit.
She's never held a camera in her
entire life, please.
Alberto told me
on the truck he knows how to use a camera.
We need him.
You're not gonna get
an illegal immigrant
when there are Americans
who can do the job.
You have marta.
- Hey, hey, hey.- O.K.
Let's continue filming.
Get him off the chair,
get her out of here.
Bien.
They're leaving.
I couldn't see how many,
I don't know, three or four.
But they got in their truck
and they're leaving.
Are you sure?
No, I mean I'm not
"sure sure", but yeah, there's a
truck leaving.
Yeah, it's gone.
What are you doing?
Liz?
What?
What are you doing?
Trying to get out.
Liz.
Don't break, don't break.
It's unbreakable.
We tried that last night.
Does anybody have a
screwdriver or something? To try and get
What the fuck?
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me see, let me see.
What are you doing?
Hold on, hold on.
You're smarter than this,
listen to me.
I'm not listening to you, I
listened to you... shh, shh!
...anymore with you!
I'm not gonna calm down!
Maria is dead.
- And William is dead!
- Hey, hey.
- I am not gonna be the next one!
- Sorry.
Hey, hey.
Sorry.
You all right?
Why do you think they
left that door unlocked?
We are fucking mice.
It doesn't matter,
man, listen, the door's open,
they're gone.
We've gotta take a shot.
Sorry, listen.
I just need you to think
about this, O.K.?
There's a right way,
there's a wrong way.
We use precision.
We have some strategy, we have
our tapes, we have our points
of entry, exit.
We're not just gonna
go blindly into the dark.
Wait a minute.
Jesus.
He's right.
O.K., we think about it for a
second, O.K.?
Listen to me.
We can help them.
We can.
Please.
We can't stay here.
O.K.
O.K., good.
All right.
Give me a flashlight.
No, no, no flashlight.
O.K., be quiet.
O.K.
Why are you bringing the tapes?
It's for the police. Someone's
gotta shut these fuckers down.
Alberto.
O.K.
Here, here-- take, take this.
What if they see the lights?
They can't, it's night vision.
Travis, I can't see.
Just follow us.
We got night vision.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
They make them sleep like this.
Hey.
Shh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, where is it?
Oh, oh shit.
What is it?
Hold the fence.
Travis, what the fuck
are you doing? Get down!
Travis, what are you doing?
All right, this is taking too
long, we gotta go.
Take this. O.K., O.K.
Easy, easy.
Oh shit.
Fuck, fuck.
Can't see shit.
- Fuck, where's Alberto? We gotta go!
- Hey!
Shh.
Alberto.
Come on, Alberto, back up.
What's going on?
We gotta go, now.
O.K. Which way?
- Which way?
I still can't
see, I can't see.
It's all barbed wire.
- What is that?
- Oh God.
Shh.
Oh shit, run, run!
Help me! Help me!
Ahh!
I'm coming back.
Liz!
[Shouts in pain,
Ah, get him off!
Get him off! Help!
Pancakes.
Thank you, marta.
Good bacon. No, not him.
He's not eating.
I'm not hungry.
I must say.
I'm a little bit disappointed in you.
You said you'd let the kids go.
And we did.
No, you didn't.
Because we saw his daughter
there and there were dogs and
razor wire and-- they were given clear
instructions, but his daughter
didn't listen.
She took off in another direction.
But there's a lesson to be learned here.
Don't fuck with me.
The only way you're going
home is to do exactly what I tell you.
There's a few more things I'd
like to get on camera.
And if you challenge me again,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Could you please pass me the syrup?
Thank you, Travis.
You'll have to excuse the mess.
Marta and the maids aren't
allowed in here, and...
I don't get too many visitors.
Sorry about that.
I've been wondering something.
When you came in through the
drug tunnel, what did you think
of my work?
I mean the, the, you know,
the body in the tunnel.
Did it frighten anyone away?
Yeah.
One, I think.
One.
That's, that's a problem.
You see, I'm not here to build
a better mousetrap.
I'm here to build a better scarecrow.
The hell does that mean?
I'm glad you asked that.
Think about that body you saw.
All these videos that you're
shooting right now, when we send
them to the Mexican media,
it'll put the stopper on.
It'll say, "stay where
the fuck you are."
The right image can make all
the difference in the world.
I mean, that's why you're here.
That's the point of this video.
And to do that, the message
needs to be stronger.
Jesus!
"Jesus."
Oh, that's interesting.
You know when the guy comes to
school and he wants somebody
from the audience, it's just like that.
I just want you to come upstage.
It's hard because she's lying
flat and she's all stiff.
I, I need somebody upright.
Well, you're a botticelli now.
But if I let you rot in the sun
a few days, you'll be rubenesque.
I'm gonna take a bone saw to her
skull, right below the hairline.
Right here.
Skull cap comes off.
Remove her brain, her eyes,
all the soft tissues.
Then, I'm gonna run electrical
wiring through her sinus
cavities to a hundred-watt bulb
at the back of her brain pan.
It'll look like a glowing, white halo.
Like an angel.
Imagine.
Our sweet, innocent girl here,
naked at the end of a tunnel.
Cradling her baby like the
Paints
quite a picture, doesn't he?
What's the surprise?
Gonna lecture again while you
kill someone?
On the contrary.
El toro screens the blood of
everyone who comes here.
And if they're clean, we'll make
a donation on their behalf.
And this man has been matched...
For a kidney.
The equation is very
simple-- by saving an American
life, we will spare his.
Hey.
We're not doing it for the money.
We're doing it for our country.
Hey, Remy, want to play spic-tac-toe?
- Can I go first?
- You can be "x" s.
Help me or get out.
Is he really a surgeon?
'Course he's a surgeon.
Ugh.
Gallo, you're a bleeder.
You know, he's the first
one to graduate from high school
in his family.
And then he just kept going
right through med school.
And then in his third year of
residency, on his way back from
the hospital, a gang of illegal
immigrants approached him.
All right, let's
clamp off the blood vessels.
O.K., get the cooler, let's go.
He gave them everything
he had in his pockets.
No, no, that wasn't enough.
Shh, he's a real good doctor.
Know what they did?
They fucking cut his throat.
Gotta sew him up.
Doesn't make it right.
What was that?
It doesn't make it right.
Would you say the same thing?
Hey! Shut the fuck up.
Fuck you.
Just film this.
If someone came up to you
with a fucking box cutter and
just did this to you.
Hey, z.
I'd like to remove his corneas.
What do you think?
As long as he lives!
Take whatever fits in the cooler.
Jim-- shit!
Jim, Jim.
Hey, come back!
- It's all right...
- I got her.
You O.K.?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine, no, don't worry about it.
Worry about Jim.
Fuck, I don't know.
I don't know where he is.
I don't know.
They're playing with us.
They're never gonna let us go. Hey, don't.
They have no reason to.
We just need to find some leverage.
Somehow we just, we gotta find
something, there's gotta be...
All right, get up, come on. Bring the
cameras, let's go. Not until we see Jim.
I want you to record that
we're taking really good care of him.
Continue filming.
Hey.
How you feeling?
Feel really good.
Yeah?
Good.
I want you to hang in there,
O.K., because we're gonna get
you home really soon.
Feel good.
Good, good.
Listen, man.
About last night, that was
just, I didn't, I was...
Don't worry about it, t.
All right.
Visitation's over!
Wait a minute.
Can we have five more minutes?
No.
Got a documentary to shoot.
Come on.
You know what?
All right, you want a documentary?
We'll have a documentary.
Over here.
Why are you doing this?
Why am I doing this?
Isn't that obvious by now?
Oh no I, I, I completely get it.
Illegal aliens cause crime.
They carry diseases.
So does everyone else.
This is all just racism posing
as patriotism.
I bet you rehearsed that all morning.
You want to know what
I think?
I'm thinking you're targeting
Oh, she can think now!
People like him and the people
I'm thinking you're targeting
people like him and the people
outside because they're
undocumented, and you get to do
your sick things on them and
think you can get away with it.
Your propaganda, your patriotic
front is bullshit.
You're not a patriot.
You're fucking insane.
Don't take it!
No, no.
You feel that?
Now that's what the brain of
an idiot feels like.
You want to be an idiot?
Leave her the fuck alone!
This is how it ends.
Continue filming.
It's not coming off.
Yeah, don't worry, it'll come off.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, what's that?
Shh, shh, shh. Shit, is that a truck?
Oh, shit.
Where is it?
Hold it, hold it.
There it is.
Oh, God, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on-- fuck.
Fuck.
Shit.
Oh, oh, God, fuck.
Lizzie.
Lizzie, Liz, get up.
See? I told you, a truck.
Oh, my God.
Hey!
A truck, come on.
Liz, Liz, a truck.
Just please help us!
Please, call, call the police.
We've been kidnapped.
They're trying to kill us.
Be quiet, keep quiet.
Oh, shit, he's right behind you-- run!
Where the fuck have you been, man?
Had to change a tire.
Fuck.
Jesus. Fuck.
I thought I made myself
perfectly clear, huh?
No, no.
You chose not to listen.
Me and my men have shown you
a lot of hospitality.
And a lot of respect.
What do we get in return?
We're sorry.
Yes-- no!
It was, it wasn't like that.
We're sorry.
Huh?
Fucking respect.
Bring 'em in.
I have to say, your tapes
were very informative.
Tia!
Oh, fuck, please, man.
Maybe from now on,
we'll have your attention.
Tia!
Tia! Tia!
Fucking shit! Hey, hey. You
fucking drop your knife.
You fucking drop your knife.
Drop that fucking knife.
Drop that fucker right now.
Don't do this.
Fuck you!
Davie, you're making
a big mistake.
Give me the fucking keys now,
retard.
Give me your fucking keys.
Drop your gun.
Fuck you!
You shut the fuck up!
Davie!
Fucking Christ!
No, davie! Please!
Are you happy now?
Fuck... Are you happy now?
Motherfucker.
Fuck you.
I'm gonna break your fucking
face off.
Mr. director, are you
happy now?
Please just...
Now, Travis, tell me.
Why did you make this
documentary?
Those people you killed.
They were davie's cousins.
Yeah, I know.
Davie was my best friend.
This was important to him.
We were trying to stop the
people that hurt his family.
I'm really glad
you told me that, Travis.
Really am.
Do you mind if we talk some economics?
Travis, I want you to meet...
Supply.
And demand.
Go ahead. Interview them.
English, please?
That is one of the biggest
suppliers of illegal immigrants.
What the fuck is the matter with you?
Have it your way.
My dear Travis, I hope
your second interview will be
a little more in-depth. Please,
guys, don't fucking kill me.
I know you.
You're that fuck-- what the fuck
is this about, man?
Mr. Whitaker, what is your
response to the allegations that
you ran a sweatshop...
What do you want, huh?
...for illegal immigrants?
You want money?
I'll get you money, I'll get you
anything you want, just fucking
tell me.
Just listen to me, just
answer the question, O.K.?
Just answer the question.
Just concentrate.
Say you're sorry.
Just apologize.
What are you talking about?
Just fucking, just please.
O. K.
O. K., o. K.
Just say you're sorry. I'm sorry...
Too much.
Too little, too late.
He said he was sorry.
Before you go, we would
like to leave you with a small
reminder of our time together.
El toro has prepared something
to dull the pain.
Would you like the injection
now or after?
Now.
I really have to commend
you, Travis.
You're a fast learner,
a survivor.
If only the rest of the group
would have followed your
example.
What about you?
You want an injection?
Now, that's my type of girl.
Give it a couple of days,
goldilocks, you'll be fine.
What did you...
What did, what did you give me?
You like it, huh?
Hey, come on.
O. K.
It smells.
Give me the camera.
Come on.
We couldn't send you off without
a real wrap party, huh?
El toro... Musica!
Yes!
It's a party! Do it right.
Ahh... ♪ come over.
Travis, no.
No-no-no!
Hold it up.
Travis, no.
There we go.
There's someone in there.
Travis, there's someone
in there.
One more!
It's Jim.
No, Travis, no, no, no!
It's Jim!
No, no, no, no, no, no...
No, let me go!
Liz!
So close.
Ay-yi-yi, ay-yi-yi.
There you go.
Gracias. Take it easy.
...what did I do?
What did I do?
Oh, God.
Shh.
Shh, shh, shh.
I so fucked up.
Shh... I did.
I fucked up.
No, it's O.K.
It's all right.
You did everything you could.
I know, I know. No.
Z wants to see you.
Just her.
I said...
Mother... fucker!
Fuck you!
Fuck you.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you!
Fuck you, you fucker!
Travis, grab the keys.
Grab the keys.
What the hell happened?
What happened?
I'm unloading the truck, I hear
shit going down.
Klaus is out cold, and they
- Idiot!- You wanna go home?
Casa?
You want to go home, casa?
Where they hiding?
Just point.
You can see your family.
- You want to go home?
- We're wasting time!
Ninos, you want to see...
We're wasting time! Lock the exits.
Come on, run.
Which one of them shot you?
He did.
Rip your fucking jaw off!
If you catch them, don't fuck up
that bitch's face, man.
I need it for that thing.
I just want him. I
want them both dead.
Go, go, go, go.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
There we go.
Where the fuck were you?
Shit.
Hurry up, what the fuck you doing?
Come on.
Oh, shit. All right, look at me.
Ven aqui.
Go, go, go, fuck.
It's O.K.
It's O.K. I got-- come on.
Ugh, fuck, go.
Hey, Remy,
make sure that the South gate's
locked up.
Fuck.
Shit!
They're over here, Remy!
Get in the car.
Go.
Shit!
Travis, he's coming!
Holy motherfucker!
Stop it! Stop it!
This was unfortunate.
You'll have to, uh, excuse
this prerecorded message.
There are matters elsewhere that
require our attention.
By the way, I hope you don't
mind, we kept some of the
footage for ourselves...
As recruiting videos.
America may be a nation of
immigrants, but it's not
a landfill.
Give us your tired, your poor,
your huddled masses yearning to
breathe free. And we'll give
'em back to you. In pieces.
The fight to control
illegal immigration isn't just
on our border.
In a few months,
president Obama will push
legislation to legalize the
nation's 12-million ill--
Too often in law
enforcement we see individuals
that are getting arrested for
d. W... Lawmakers in Arizona
passed a sweeping overhaul that
would require police officers to
profile illegal immigrants.
The law is needed
because the federal government
has failed to enforce border
security with Mexico, allowing
more than 450...
...In law enforcement
we see individuals that are
getting arrested for d.W.I.,
sexual assaults, what have you,
and they're foreign-born.
One Arizona police
officer is saying he won't
enforce the new immigration law
and is suing.
The Mexican government
says that 90% of guns used by
the drug cartels come from
the United States, so now you...
Tensions are high as
anti-immigrant sentiment along
the border is on the rise.
...Here at the plant
on international boulevard
are as young as 12.
...Allowing more than
450,000 illegal immigrants
to move into the state.
We supposed to get
first dibs on all them jobs,
and they was taken them jobs
away-- If the border agents
had grabbed hold, it's likely
they would have met the same
fate as the illegal immigrants.
...From jails in
54 counties, from...
Radical groups,
vigilantes, minutemen,
mass grave--
People in charge at
the plant had no comment.
Their bosses in--
I feel bad when