Yeah yeah, hey, man,
check out this
clown-ass nigga out front
- Oh, that's Sanchez. Buzz him in, man
- Oh, okay okay.
Hey, so you ever been having sex
with a female and she, like,
' slapped you?
- Slapped me?!
Yeah, I didn't ask her to slap me
She just slapped me.
So I slapped her back
- you know what I'm saying?
- Yeah yeah.
Then it got real awkward after that
You never get mad.
Ho, Sanchez, my man! What it is
- Come talk good to me.
- What's up, my good dude?
Oh man, same shit. You know,
still up in here doing that thing
Hey, that Charlie Sheen
kush you brought last time
was some--
Man, that shit went in one day, man
Please tell me you got
some more of that shit
Man, I got something
better than that.
Trust me-- this stuff is
from the backwoods of Kentucky
Man, ain't nobody growing no weed
Em mm motherfucking D mam“
Oh man, you got
a lot to learn, grasshopper
This is it.
This is the HBH
- The HBH.?
- That's that hillbilly highway shit
Whatever, man
You gonna let your boy
sample this here or what?
Yeah, I actually prefer it,
because I don't want you to go ballistic
- when I hand you the ticket
- Aw, man, whatever, man.
- There you go. Fire it up
- You know we all good.
Shit, we all good, man
Hey, oh, it's cool, man.
This here shit is magically delicious
- I told you
- Damn!
You smoking
with your boy or what, man?
No, I quit, man. I quit.
No, I'm just messing with you
Here, give me some
Give me some.
Hey, how'd a motherfucker like you
come across some fine like that?
Though.
You got a minute?
Dude, I sell weed for a living
I ain't got nothing but time
All right.
Then I'm gonna tell you a story
about two homies
from the hood in Atlanta
- ATL's on it?
- Yeah.
Sneak that thing in
- All right, we good, all right
- Okay, what do I do?
I want you to pick
which one my ball's in
I mean I want you
to pick the ball. Pick the ball
Where it's at? Is it in this one
or is it in that one?
I want you to pick
which one.
- Hurry up, baby. We ain't got all day
- Pick the ball.
Mam“
ooh, that one!
Aw, man,
it ain't in there. My bad
- Hey, baby.
- That's all my money
- Easy come, easy go.
- Hey, man, you gotta live, you learn
- Who else next?
- Yo, man!
Shut the fuck up
Now I done been out here
for an hour and a half
and I ain't seen
nobody win yet.
Hey, man, you tripping, man
Let my hand-- oh shit. Okay.
Shut your fucking mouth
before I grab your friend
- and beat your ass with him
- Whup his ass.
That muthafucker was here
and with that girl cheating that guy
Did you start speaking in Hebrew?
I'll beat your ass.
Hold up, man, we're just trying
to get our shit together.
Everybody shut the fuck up!
- Lift up the cups.
- Everything good, man!
- Give him $100.
- It's good, man!
- Lift up the fucking cups now
- Lift the cups up, monkey.
- Lift 'em up!
- Okay, that's one. That's one cup.
- There's another one.
- Okay, it's not under there
- Two.
- It's under there
Which one of y'all took
the fucking ball?!
Who the fuck took the ball?
You two bitch-ass niggas
in a whole lot of shit.
- Motherfucker-
- Hey hey hey, look, there's the police
That's the motherfucking police
Yeah, yo, time to
roll up some, man
Smoke something
Grab a drink
Grab something to smoke on
Yeah, it's about that time
We get high
Yo, how much is that?
110 to spend with a friend?
Why not?
My shit look like my eyelids
are inside out
Not a dime this time,
but a nice-size quarter?
We call our shit coffee
but we don't dip it in that water
We honor it with no sugar
and cream, straight green
Then it's chicken and ribs,
baked beans, my plate's clean
Then I find the rhythm,
mind if l give them a little?
I'm kinda high right now
so I'll just go and hit a McGriddle
And I'll twiddle my thumbs
My direct connect is gone
But my middle man is about
to come with some mo' 'dro
Oh yo, you know the logo
We higher than mofo,
we get high...
- Hey, son.
- What's up, Pops?
Hey, son, so what'd you do today
for the betterment of your people?
Come on, man, we gotta
do this every night?
Every night of your life! As long as
the pigs are out there on the street
killing your brothers
with the cold heat of their billy clubs
Here
Come on, man,
I'm out here struggling
- Man, I ain't got time--
- Struggle!
What you know about struggle?
Try being
a political prisoner,
locked up for the rest
of your natural life, brother
- That's struggle.
- But you're not a prisoner, Pops
You're free.
You retired from Ford, Pops
Now you see? That's what's
wrong with you kids today.
They've got you all brainwashed
Damn rap music
You know
y'all had one cat. Um
Teapac Secure
Now that cat,
he was a soldier
Then one of you young
ignorant bastards killed him
You think you know everything, huh
Shit!
Well, go on. Go on, boy
Ain't no sense in watering
a tree that don't want to grow
Hey!
You got any weed?
Man, I gotta get out
of this motherfucker
Gourmet fiender
for the gourmet fiender
From the gourmet fiender
for the fiender
For the gourmet chocolate
So many people ask
Who is the gourmet chocolate?"
Nigga, I done told you
about slamming my damn door!
Earl, you hear me talking to you?
Yeah, you
Bring your ass in here
- Where the fuck have you been all day?
- I've been--
You know today is the first
and I've got to pick up
all these checks
from all these people, honey
Shanequa Adams, Tamika Terry
Samantha Jones
and this lady right here
and so on and so on
and so forth.
- I--
- Do you know how hard it is
to WIC office to the next
with five kids?
- You didn't--
- What?!
- You fucking some other bitch?
- What?
Hell no, nigga. Let me find out your ass
out here fucking around on me
with one little ole ho and I swear
to God I'm a drag you and that bitch-ass
- Yeah, that's right.
- Well, if you do all that,
then how am I give you
these flowers?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm,
you see it.
- Mm-hmm
- Baby!
- You did it!
- Yes, I did.
- That's so sweet.
- Isn't it? Who am I?
- You ain't had to do me like that
- Who am I?
You my big-dicked Earl
All right, that's what I thought
- That's my baby.
- Mm-hmm, come here
- You ain't had to do me like this
- Come here, put the ass on me.
- Put the ass on you?
- Put the ass on me. Put the ass on me
- Mm-hmm, roll this shit up.
- Like that? That's how you like it?
Save me, they're killing me!
Get off me.
I gotta get out of this shit.
Lately, man, I've been thinking about
just getting out of the hood, dawg.
Give me your change!
No shit.
You know what?
Man, I've been thinking
about the same shit, dawg
Man, I'm just tired
of all the drama, man
- Watch that bitch-ass
- Shit, me too.
You know what I mean?
The hood cool and all. But, I mean
- Fucking with her man!
- ...l think I need to find my own way
'Cause I mean, shit
I'm better than this.
East Side!
- Shit crazy, dawg--
- Freeze!
Freeze!
Don't you move, dawg
You gonna get a gun?
- Freeze!
- Okay.
Next thing I know
the nigga gonna come try me
so I grabbed the nigga by the neck
like this and just started choking him
I'm choking the shit outta the nigga,
the nigga just shakin' and shit,
trembling, his eyes
rolling back to his back
I say, "Pussy nigga fuckboy!'
The nigga started
regurgitating and shit
So I pulled my little thing out
I just started
- hitting the nigga with the pistol
- Hey, y'all keep it down!
- This ain't no Def Comedy Jam
- Oh, okay.
Nigga said calm down
- Appreciate it.
- Fuck all of your crap
Yeah, man, this shit all right
- I can do this.
- Do you hear what you saying, nigga?
- What's wrong? We got cots
- That some bullshit, man.
- We livin'.
- I'll be glad
when we get up out
of this motherfucker
- Soon, man. This is bullshit.
- There ain't nothing wrong with this
Plus we straight. We already talking
to girl that work over at city hall.
She got all our
paperwork and shit
That shit gonna disappear
by tomorrow.
- Oh yeah, all right
- Yeah, we good.
- Know what I'm saying?
- Lockdown! Lockdown.
This motherfucker happy
he got some authority.
It's gonna be all right, man
- He is upset.
- Don't start no shit up with me
Man, I don't give a fuck about
this shit. You know how I get.
I like you
WEE
What the f-- hey, man,
put me goddamn down!
I'm a real nigga. I boo-boo on myself
so you ain't gonna want this.
I got a little story
I wanna tell you.
Story?
About what?
Kentucky.
Now lay down
Oh shit
Use protection
and don't tell nobody!
- They raped Earl?
- No, man, he doesn't rape him!
Not all convicts are gay
- Really?
- You see, Wilbert is
headed upstate for life and he wanted
to share some of his secrets
with someone who could
benefit by them.
You like plants
[mm
Well, shit, it depends
on what kind of plants
- you talking about.
- There's a hidden part
in a rural part
of the highway of Kentucky
where there's nothing
but acres-- I mean acres--
of pot farm
Now that's what I'm talking
about right there.
That's right up my lungs
I'm talking about
the best weed you ever seen
I'm talking about Sour Diesel
I'm talking about Train Wreck
I'm talking about Master Kush
You name it
What you know about that hydro?
All these strains, Early Girl
Purple Haze, Afghani,
straight Candy
Nigerian weed
Maui Wowie
Blueberry, Island Lady
Indigo weed
Holland's Hope,
Hindu Kush
Master Kush,
Northern Bright
That sound like some
old fairy-tale shit, man
- That can't be real.
- Oh no, my little friend
Why do you think I'm in here?
So which highway
are you talking about?
Highway 420
Told you I had a little secret
Shhh.
Tell me more about
this thing, man.
Don't drop the soap
Don't drop the soap, la la
Yeah
Teddy Riley? Come on
All right, man. Stay up
And Ray McGathy.
Let's go, you're free to go
- Mcwho?
- McFuck-You, man
You told them your name
was Teddy Riley?
Hey, man, I need a job after this
Fuck this shit.
Ain't nobody tripping
ain't nobody tripping
cause the money already made
Cause the money already made,
'cause the money already made
Ain't nobody tripping
You said acres of chronic, man?
- Yes.
- Where at?
Somewhere off hillbilly highway
Hillbilly highway?
Where the fuck is that?
- Kentucky
- What?
You heard what I said
Kentucky.
Man
I'm telling you.
I know what I'm talking about
I got all the logistics
and all the directions and everything
You just gotta trust your boy
Pocket for a pimp, drop it
low, show me some shit
- Bread in the bank bank
- You know what?
- You might be onto something.
- I just know this might be the thing
that gets us outta the hood
You know what?
You might be right, man
Like 10, 20 lbs, man,
we come back with that shit,
we be ballin' like a motherfucker
You feel me?
Hillbilly highway, huh?
Fuck it, dawg. Let's roll then
Did this bitch just fart?
Fuck it
Fuck this, man
- Hey!
- Oh.
- What's up, Pops?
- Hey, son.
Me and my partner Earl-- we're about to
go see some friends up at the college.
Ah, man, I remember
Me and Huey used to take
road trips all the time.
Down to Birmingham, up to D.C
all for the betterment
of the cause.
I hope your trip has
as great a cause.
Well, it's for a very--
high cause.
- Well, right on, boy
- All right.
- Hold it down now
- All right, carry on
Right on
All you need is weed
and nothing else
Sit back and roll one
Hey, Ray, go! Pull out
Don't make me chase you, Earl!
Don't make me chase you, Earl.
Get your ass whupped
like Lionel Richie, nigga
Hey, when you get a bitch,
you can tell me about bitches, bitch
I get a bitch
every night, nigga
They oughta call you Pizzazz
'cause you a pussy-ass nigga
Nigga, Shante is the only
woman you ever have,
so you ain't even qualified
to speak on women, nigga
I know what I am
qualified to speak on
Oh shit, don't show it
blow it, nigga.
Tell me I'm the shit first
I'll throw the shit out
- You the shit, you the shit!
- Oh okay.
- Put the shit down
- Give me a blunt.
So go call up the loved ones
And get ready for the ride
It's about that time, y'all
Let's put one in the sky
Lay back and enjoy the ride
Cause that 420-I
With my Chocolate Thai
Feel my bricks grow
with my Chocolate Thai
Let's put one in the sky
Lay back and enjoy the ride
Cause that 420-I
With my Chocolate Thai
I'm gonna have me a beer, darlln
Sir, you gonna have yourself
another shot there?
Jack Daniels. I like it.
One Jack Daniels coming up
I've been driven
from my home..
It got quiet in this bitch, ain't it?
Howdy
- What do you want?
- Let me get a chili cheese fries
- and a fruit punch.
- I'll have the same thing
We don't make
no chili cheese fries
Okay, well, fuck it.
Let me get a cheeseburger
We don't make cheeseburgers
Let me get
two of those motherfuckers.
You're pushing it, boy
-"Boy"?
- Mm-hmm
Maybe we oughta just get up
outta this motherfucker.
Man, fuck that shit
This ain't no goddamn J. Edgar Hoover
back-in-the-'60s shit.
Is there a monkey talking?
- How you doing, Run DMC?
- You're in trouble now, ain't you?
Half a Dollar.
I understand that your little
tour rap bus
broke down up yonder
Now I heard you say you want
some kind of burger.
There's a McDonald's about three,
four miles up the road there.
You can get all
the chicken nuggets you want
and fruit punch Kool-Aid
And I'd advise you
to get your black asses up
and head the hell
on outta this town
We moved here
to move away from ya
Everywhere we move,
here come a couple of ya
moving in, sending
the property value down
I'm about to drop
this cracker ass.
Whatcha gonna do, son?
Hey, fellas, would y'all
take care of 'em,
- make way and escort them out there
- We good, we good.
- We good.
- Don't touch 'em
You might catch it
Touching you on the hand,
I tell you, the next time you know
your fingers turn black
Hold up, hold up, hold up
- Hey, fellas?
- Yeah, what's that?
I want to thank y'all again
for showing me the nice hospitality
Y'all showed me so much love
and I'm trying to figure out
which one of you cracker's jaws
I'm gonna let suck my black dick!
Holy Rick Astley shit!
Get them mother-crickets!
What? They are so fucked
right now, nigga.
It is a done daughter.
Them rednecks must've caught 'em,
then sodomized them
and murderized them.
Oooh
Man, what is it
with you and sodomy?
I mean that's the way
all these stories end, man
They fuck you
and they kill you
Nigga, ain't you seen "Deliverance
II?
No, they don't get screwed or killed
They get away
- Itch, though, right?
- I don't think so, man
Use Blue Star ointment?
But that don't usually work
most of the time.
- No shit?
- Not really
Gotta shave all the hair
off my nuts, huh?
- I had to shave my asshole
- Oooh.
Howdy, cowboys!
Welcome to the Dixieland Hotel
So tell me, how many
"D"s are in Dixie.
- One.
- No, darling!
There are 35.
DD-DD-DD-D-D-D-D-D-D--
Okay, you boys look exhausted
Like you've been out
on the range all day.
I'm gonna tell you
what you need: a good meal,
a hot tub
and a nice warm bed
to put that little head on
That's what I'm talking about.
You gonna come put me in the bed?
- Sounds good to you, doesn't it?
- Mm-hmm.
What's it gonna be?
Two rooms?
Or maybe one?
- One.
- And is that gonna be
two beds or one?
- Bitch, two! What the fuck?
- Two!
Okay okay, I got to ask.
It doesn't happen very often,
but every now and then we get
some of those life "partner" types
- You know what I mean.
- No, there ain't nothing like this
- We're definitely not life partners
- Okay.
Now y'all want smoking
or non-smoking?
Smoking
- Smoking that weed
- Feeling fine
- Got me a party
- And a fat-ass dime
How about
a little weed for me?
- You a Compton sister.
- Just go on upstairs and have a ball
All right, baby.
She all right to me
Boy, those chili cheese fries
was off the chain, man.
Oooh, for real. I think
she cooked them mothers herself
Yeah, man.
Mara's kinda feisty
She probably was fine
as fuck back in the day
If it was the '60s, shit, I'd fuck
While you're bullshittin' it
I'm fucking that.
Man, hold up, man. You smoked
too much for real this time, man.
You blowing my high, man
Oh shit
- Man, it's the Kush
- Oh, that's my shit
I ain't never seen
this shit before.
Man, watch, check it out,
while we be tripping.
- I heard about this shit.
- Here, smoke. You need to smoke
- while you look at that
- Okay.
And US veteran Akura Kushimota,
publically known as Master Kush
is wanted for murder.
Leading the investigation
is Special Agent Rico--
Yo yo yo yo,
that's some mad lies
Leader Kush never killed no one
Hey, true dat.
Get out, Kush
Get down! Smoke him
Move in, move in
Pull back, he's got a gun
It's weapons of mass destruction
Watch out!
It's the kush goo!
HEB?
Oh no, no-ooo!
Will Master Kush be hunted down
and captured by the ICU?
Will ICU propaganda
successfully tarnish
the good name of Kush?
Will the ICU
use their evil influence and release
the dark energy into the world?
Will fear, mass paranoia
and government conspiracy
be the ultimate downfall of Master Kush?
All this and more
When Kush Comes to Shove
- That hurt.
- M-M-Master Kush
I'm having a meeting with the toilet
You gonna have to hurry up, man
What you doing?
Making a decision
You gotta
come back later, man
Smoking up all the fucking weed
I know what he doing.
Free up your mind and pull up
some fresh brew
Blowing out my mind
cloud nine
Where I stay,
so I blaze some weed
We've been riding forever, man
I'm tired of this shit.
What time we gonna get there?
- Man, you know what?
- What?
Before we get to where we're going, man,
I think we need to get some new gear.
Think there gonna be
some mothers out there?
No, nigga. I ain't-- I'm talking
about some clothes so we can fit in
So we won't stick out
as much, man.
Like what?
What type of gear?
Shit, I don't know.
What do country motherfuckers wear?
Cowboy shit?
Yeah, I guess
Man, when we get
up in here, man,
make sure you play it cool
Don't be doing shit that'll
bring attention to us, man
Come on, dawg
I 9011 you
All of you freaks
And all of you boozers
All of you cheats
Emil
Yeee--
--haw
Hey there,
Boom Boom Belinda
Let me get some of that--
both of them.
It's another lost weekend
stuck in this town...
He ain't gonna need this
Hey, where you going?
Where you going?
You can get that two in that
corner pocket if you just go at it.
Smile!
I like that.
Let me get it
Okay, babe
Give them a little "Whoa,
ho ho ho!"
Hey, come on, man
You're crazy.
Listen to me.
You're tripping
- Can I get you guys something to drink?
- Yeah.
Let me get a li'l sarsaparilla
Knock off that cowboy shit
This ain't the place
Oh. My bad
Now if you're looking for some reefer,
stick around till after we close
- For sure
- Whoo.
Uh, was that drunk bitch pregnant
or was that pregnant bitch drunk?
- Is that what I think it is?
- Oh, yeah yeah.
Bring it here.
Come here, come on, come on in
Now let me guess.
You guys are here
- looking for crops
- How you know?
The only black cowboys I know
play football in Dallas
mama
Yeah well, shit.
What's up with the trees then, man?
My man here said they got acres
of that shit growing out here.
- That's an understatement
- Fuck.
Kentucky yields
the most marijuana crops
in the nation
If you're driving through,
just roll down your windows
- You could smell it in the air
- No shit.
I thought I smelled it.
When I was on my way up there
- I did smell it.
- That's 'cause we was smoking on one
You ain't wrong when you're right
Let me guess:
you guys came up in here
in hopes of finding
one of those crops?
Snatching a couple of pounds
and going down to sell it in the hood
You're damn right, Iron Sheik
Oh, I get it
You're the funny one.
Well, we'll see how funny you are
when one of these hillbillies
has a cow prod up your ass,
forcing you to drink ice water
and chew on aluminum foil.
My booty hole just started burning
What type of gay shit?
All right, man,
for real, man.
Can you tell us
where the crops are?
Well, you gotta be a little
more specific than that.
You just don't walk into McDonald's
and say "I want a hamburger."
- You got the Barack Obama?
- What kind they got?
- EL Presidential
- It all depends
on how far are you
willing to go.
I mean you can hike
for about a day
and find a pretty decent
chronic crop.
But if you're willing to dodge
a couple of bullets
- and booby traps
- Mm-hmm.
You can find that sticky green,
crystallized,
extraterrestrial-type shit
that shit that tastes like candy
when you smoke it.
Oh shit, I'm up in that
Man, did you hear what
he said before that shit?
Man, I'm not fucking with no bullets
or no booby traps, man.
Can you tell us how to get
to one of the ones, like,
right off one
of these roads somewhere?
All right, all right,
but trust me.
You'll be back
Can I get some
of that now? Shit
Y'all done passed it back and forth
like y'all know each other.
So what the guys didn't know
was that I was waiting
for this opportunity for years
- What opportunity?
- My sweet little baby girl
my daughter Marie--
she was held captive
by sick, sadistic hillbillies
- A group of them
- Oh, I get it.
So he get him a piece of that
young hillbilly kinootchi
while he up there, fuck around
and leave a seed
in the background, huh?
- Exactly.
- Should've pulled out
I'd do it.
Called the rhythm method
or some shit like that
I tried several times to free her,
but it didn't work out
Damn, that's fucked up
Yeah, so I seen these guys
as the perfect opportunity
to set her free, but first I had
to bait the hook a little.
Man, where in the hell
this fool Sanchez send us, man?
I don't know. He said
look for the Highway 420 sign
There it is right there
That's it right there.
Let's do this shit
Come on, let's go
- You hear this shit?
- This is the forest, nigga.
Man, let's just be rappers.
Let's go back home, let's be rappers
Man, come on, man.
Bring your scary-ass on, man
- Let's go, man
- Eh, shit!
Fucking with you
Okay, according to Sanchez,
there should be somewhere
- to camp right up in here somewhere
- Camp?! Hold up, hold up.
The fuck you mean "camp"?
Black people don't camp.
We cook out. We picnic
We party, have a good time,
get on that cocaine and leave
You got me fucked up, nigga.
I'm gonna stay out of this motherfucker
I ain't gonna be
on nobody's news. Shit
Man, you trying to get
this weed or what, man?
Now if I can remember correctly,
this was your idea from the beginning
- Not this part.
- Shit, man, I don't know about you,
man, but I'm tired of this
nickel-and-dime shit we've been doing
I'm trying to get
this paper for real, man
This right here could be
our meal ticket outta the hood
So what you want to do?
You should be a actor, man
'Cause I felt that. I felt like
the movie-- on "Menace ll Society
when he said "You gonna let
that nigga kill your cousin?
Let that shit ride?
Fuck that!"
That's how I-- whoa, shit.
What the-- you hear that shit?
Man, whatever, man
Come on, man.
No, but I'm for real though
I feel what you're saying.
- Real good talk.
- Pfft, that's bullshit, man
Man, what if we do come up?
What you gonna do
with all the brick?
Shit, first thing I'm a do, man,
I'm a get me a motherfucking
'58 Chevy Impala, nigga.
Put some bang in that bitch
throw some "D"s on that ho
You know, get it ready for the summer
You know what I'm saying?
- I feel you, nigga
- Yeah yeah.
Shit, after that though
I'll have to get me a spot
You know,
somewhere outside of the hood
where I don't have to worry about
catching a stray bullet in my sleep
Nigga, I definitely feel you
on that shit, nigga.
- Shit.
- What about you, man?
- What you gonna do?
I might take Shante
on a trip to Jamaica
Probably sit on the beach
or some shit, chill out.
- With a fat blunt of course
- Mm-hmm.
Me sittin' there smoking a good one
and have her run into the water,
with a nice pretty thong
where I don't see nothing
but her ass just jiggling.
And then, shit
I gotta buy something
for the kids,
so I'll probably take all them
motherfuckers out to the toy store
and just let them ball till they fall
you know what I'm saying?
But I'm definitely moving out
of the motherfucking hood.
- Hell yeah.
- Shit, but I been thinking
I don't really know
where the fuck to go
- What do you mean?
- Shit, I mean
I don't want to be around
no white folks and shit.
You know what I'm saying?
I ain't trying to live by none of them
Yeah, I know
I wonder is there a spot
for people like us,
like rich broke niggas.
You know what I'm saying?
Niggas that made a little money
made their way up out the hood
You know, I don't know.
There's gotta be somewhere
Baa,
I'm about to crash, man
It's been a long day.
Holla at you
All right, cool.
You got some lotion?
No no,
I ain't got no lotion
Give me that Off.
It'll work the same
Off?
You meaning Jack-Off?
- Don't judge me.
- Man, you a nasty motherfucker
- Shoot that way.
- Don't be in my way
- Uh-oh.
- What's up, man?
I gotta boo-boo
Can you hold it till the blunt?
No, man, my-- my stomach
is beefin' with my asshole.
And I think my stomach
winning this beef.
- Hurry up, man.
- Hold this for me, man
I gotta go boo-boo
Damn, when did I eat almonds?
Uh-oh, that ain't it
Shit
Can't use that shit.
Don't know what you gonna
wipe your ass with.
Whoo!
'Bout time, man. Shit, I was
about to leave without you.
Hey, boy, don't go in that
west wing of the forest.
I shut it down
I'm just living, man.
All these daggone--
Man, take this, man
This heavier than a motherfucker
Oh, you ain't say nothing
so what am I supposed to do?
Say, man, you smell something?
Hey, man, stop playing with me
I wiped my ass good
with that furry rabbit.
- What, nigga?
- Nothin', never mind
- These trees are--
- No, but for real, man
I smell something
Man, that's weed.
That smell like some fire too
That shit's some killer, nigga!
- Oh shit!
- Whoo.
But where it's coming from?
- Thattaway.
- Find it, Earl
Get it, Earl.
There you go
That's my dawg
Get it, Earl.
Rover'll find that motherfucker
Get it, Rover!
Yes, you got it!
Rover, find it
Thatta boy.
That's my dawg
Oh my God
- We found it.
- Chronidocia
WEE
We shall call it Chronidocia
Yeah
Oh shit!
Chronidocia, bitch!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh my God
oh my God
Oh my God, oh my God
Oh my-- oh my God
Oh my God.
Oh, I can't touch it
Oh my Lord,
it's so beautiful
Oh my Lord.
Oh my-- oh, I want to--
Well, boys,
looks like we've got ourselves
some pot farmers.
Well, let's get 'em!
Yeehaw!
Yeah
Time to roll up
something, man
Smoke something
Grab a drank
Grab something to smoke on
Yeah, babe, it's about that time
We get high
Yo, how much is that?
Man, I don't think I had
no weed like this ever in my life
Man, this is some good shit, man
No shit. We done
came up on a lick, man
I'm telling you. But I'm hungrier
than a motherfucker.
I wish they had a Busy Bee's
around this motherfucker.
I feel like eating
some catfish or something?
I'm a fuck you up
with this one though, Ray
Adam fucked Eve raw
- That's some deep shit
- I know it is, boy!
Man, we gonna be on top,
nigga, when come back to--
Hold it, you hear that?
- Nigga, you tripping
- No-- okay.
Man, I might go ahead and give
myself to God after this, man.
Man, you know what? I was gonna
tell you something too, man.
You hold on to the weed too long
Freeze!
Are we high?
Tell me your name, boy
Man, I ain't saying nothing
until I talk to my lawyer.
Ain't no Minister Farrakhan
gonna help you here, boy.
Now my daddy's the judge
in the only courthouse for 200 miles,
so I suggest you
show me some respect!
Man, I ain't saying nothing
until I talk to my lawyer.
Damn!
I hate that
Now you lookie here, Earl
You're looking
at a whole mess of jail time
And let me tell you,
those big hairy redneck convicts
sure ain't gonna go light
on your little black butthole
Unless of course
they take a shine to you
and they tell you that
you have a purty mouth
We call it "Deliverance 2
- The Dark Side
- No no no.
So tell me who you're with
The Gatsfields or the McRoys?
WEE
Don't play dumb with me, stupid
I'm telling you,
we have been watching
the McCoys and Gatsfields
for more than two years now
Neither one of these clowns
would have anything to do with them
Well, then who the hell are they?
Don't know.
Mutt and Jeff
Frick and Frack,
Fucking Kid 'n Play
Who gives a shit?
Let 'em go.
Come on, Earl. Suck it up.
Tell me whose pot farm it is
Yeah yeah!
Hey hey hey,
you're free to go now
- Come on.
- What what?
Let him go!
You got the wrong guy
No no no, but he just confessed
Yeah, you scared him
half to damn death, man
- Hey, my man, get outta here. Go go!
- Huh?
Stop slobbering
and get your ass up outta here
-Me?
-Bye-bye.
You sure?
I can go.
Okay, I can go
- Pussy!
- Hey!
What are you doing, man?
Let me tell you something:
you are wasting our time, all right?
And you're bringing
too much attention to this investigation
with your hillbilly style of cop work
Lemme-- lemme tell
you something, my man,
this is how this is
gonna go down, okay?
You gonna leave
the drug bust to us,
while you stick
to writing traffic tickets
and breaking up domestic
disputes, you understand?
- That's a pretty good accent
- Thank you.
Yam
- Yes.
- Good
Feds
Look at Tony!
There's Tony.
Hell no
Told y'all we was innocent!
- Yeah, nigga.
- God damn it
It's just like the white male
trying to keep a brother down
Oh yeah, and I forgot to tell y'all
Minister Farrakhan said what's up
Alaikum assalam
Sign there
- Where my EBT card at?
- Hey, wait a minute.
- Where are my keys, man?
- You mean these?
Damn, did I forget to tell you?
No, you ain't getting 'em back.
What the fuck you mean
you ain't give me my keys, man?
Apparently you got expired tags
so we had to impound it.
- My car?!
- That's my car
- Oh.
- Now you boys are resourceful
I'm sure you'll have a long refreshing
walk all the way back to Compton.
Unless of course you want to stay.
We're gonna do some shooting later
No, we're good, we're good
Let's go, let's go.
Just gonna shoot
some cans is all. Jamai-cans,
Mexi-cans, Puerto Ri-cans
Afri-cans.
- Now what the hell we supposed to do?
- Shit, I don't know, man.
Shit, who the fuck can we call?
Now with no car, no money
and no way to get home,
I had them just where
I wanted them.
It was time to put
my plan in motion
Shit, I don't know
Hold up!
Sanchez
Fellas, back so soon?
Yeah, man, we're in
a real fucking bind now, man
They done fuck around
and pop me for my shit
- and they took his car.
- We barely got any money left, man,
- and no way home now.
- Man, what the fuck we gonna do?
I've already made preparations
for you guys to crash at my crib
- I knew you'd be back
- Your crib?
We ain't about to stay in your crib!
You see how this shit look?
You got Christmas tree lights
around this bitch.
I know your house look even worse
Baum
- motherfucker?
Sanchez,
you, my friend, is living
hillbilly fabulous around this bitch
Hell yeah. Why you didn't tell us
you had shit like this?
Oh, you thought when I said
I was stuck here, it was all bad
Hell no. Come on,
I want to show you something
Right over here
You living lovely, Sanchez.
Hey, why don't you
tell us what it is, shorty?
Yeah, put me on some of this thing
you got going on around here.
- Yeah.
- Fuck with me
I don't know about that,
but check this out.
- Shat.
- Oh my God
Oh shit
Hush, mamacita
Oh shit, oh shit.
Can-- can I go-- in?
Yeah, go right ahead
and grab a bud to smoke
Oh Lord Jesus
You see, this is what I do
What, smoke weed?
No, I cultivate it
I know what climate it likes
what's the best
source of nourishment?
I know how it grows
I know how it thinks.
I know how it feels.
I am one with the sativa plant
And most importantly I know
when it's time to harvest.
Right, well, I'm trying to
harvest this weed into a blunt
Or a zigzag or something
Right over there in the box
Appreciate it, folk
So that's what I do. I teach
these hillbillies how to grow weed
and they pay me well for it
Why don't you just start
your own crop?
Oh, no way
This mountain is
basically controlled by two families
Two families
of inbred, backwood
animalistic hillbillies
the Gatsfields...
and the McRoys
My crop came up
a few pounds short again!
I know your sons had
something to do with it!
I got my own crop!
I ain't had nothing to do with that
- Shit.
- These two families have been feuding
for years-- decades
First it was moonshine
and now it's chronic.
You got me fucked up. I ain't
going up there with them crackers
See, I told you from the get-go we
should have just started rapping, man
Man, what the fuck
you talking about, man?
It was your whole stupid-ass
idea in the first place, man.
Until I seen all that camping shit.
I knew this was some fucked shit then
It's too late now,
Captain Dipshit.
All right, come on, pendejos,
stop it, all right? Listen,
I got a foolproof plan
to pull it off.
That mean you gonna roll
with us then, right?
- No, I can't
- Why not?
I've been banished from up there
Why is that?
It's a long story,
but I tell you what
I'm gonna send you up there
to meet somebody that I know
Her name is Marie.
She's Jim Gatsfield's only daughter
She works at the only bar up there--
The Last Call
Oh yeah
Hey, what's happening?
How you doing?
- I'm fine.
- Yes, you are
I'm Little Earl.
This is my player partner
- Ray Ray.
- I'm Marie.
Can I get y'all
something to drink?
Yeah, can we get two cognacs
and a chaser on the side?
- Hold the chaser.
- Coming right up
- She's fine.
- What brings you around these parts?
Well, Sanchez sent us
up here, you know,
- to holla at you
- Sanchez?
What would he send you
up here for?
To get some of them trees.
- The what?
- The crops, lady, the crops
How about some drinks, sweetass?
The hell you boys doing in here?
You know you ain't welcome
in Gatsfield's bar.
Me and my brother was sitting up
on the hill drinking whiskey,
when we decided tonight was the night we
was gonna get a piece of that sweet ass.
The only thing y'all gonna get
is a hole in your head.
I get it.
You're only into dark meat
Oh, I got your stuffin', baby
What about you stuff
some Febreze in your mouth?
You talk pretty bold for a nigger
Did you just call me a nigger?
What the-- whoa, shit, he's strong
But not you
Punk, you hit me?
I'm not talking about mine, huh?
- Ooooh.
- Fuckboy!
- You gonna get yours!
- You just got yours, pussy!
FuckboY!
Y'all all right?
I want to thank y'all for saving me
Here you go
What the fuck
is going on in here?
Where'd y'all get
them guns from-- T.l.?
Are you motherfuckers
trying to put your
ginormous-sized penises
into our sweet Marie?
- She's a virgin, you know
- No, she ain't.
How do you know?
It was the crop
Just so sweet.
You fucking maggots were
trying to touch my sister
in places that family's
only supposed to?
- What?
- I say we take these two pieces of shit
- outside right now!
- Yeah, and then dump their sorry asses
down there by the river
- Sounds like a plan.
- No, y'all, they helped me
The McRoy boys was here.
That's why I flipped the alarm
And these two
ran 'em up on outta here
Are you shitting me?
These two?
- Yeah.
- I swung first
Beat the crap outta them,
had them running outta here
- like a couple of sissies
- "G" shit.
Well, dip my balls
in sweet cream and squat me
- in a kitchen full of kittens
- You're such a poet.
Anybody that fucks
with them McRoys
- are friends of ours
- Absolutely!
- You boys come over for dinner tonight
- Aw, but, Paw,
I wanted to kill them.
I never get to kill nobody
In time, son. In due time
This barbecue's banging, man
- What kind of meat is this?
- Raccoon.
Told ya
Told ya not to eat it.
Say, Earl, why don't you give us
a song from back home?
No, I couldn't play like that
- Y'all ain't ready for me.
- Hey! My old lady wants you
to sing a song, sing a song.
And it better not be Hank Williams
Some songs are
sacrimonius around here
- Spell sacrimonius
- N-l-G-G--
All right, all right, all right
All right
Yeah, pluck them
goddamn strings on that guitar
Let me show you how to get down
Oh, I got one right here
Turn me up.
I stay smoking kush,
she look like Reggie Bush
Y'all look
like some slackers
Oops, I meant some crackers--
Crackers?! You want some crackers,
go up in the house.
- They're in the pantry.
- Behind the moonshine
Shit, that ain't nothing.
I can do better than that
J.R., pluck them strings
you always pluck for me
June Bug, bust a beat
Yo, I chose this life,
this life chose me
I didn't choose this life,
I'm a hick from the sticks,
bitch, don't sneak
I puff a lot of pot,
I drink a lot of booze
Rhyme against me,
I guarantee you'll lose
Don't get me pissed,
tryin' to dis my folks
Next time you try and rap,
wrap you lips around this and choke
That's my son!
Came from my nut
I can tell
So what is it like growing up
here in these mountains?
Well
it's all right, I guess
I much rather would've grown up
somewhere like Atlanta.
- Hmm, yeah
- Yeah.
Tell me what it's like there
I always wanted to know what
it's like to grow up in the city.
I mean,
I grew up there all my life
It's cool I guess,
but it's funny though
When I came out here, I was
just dying to get away from the hood
- From what?
- The hood.
- The city.
- Oh, sorry
No, but like I was saying,
I was just dying to get away
But now that we're here,
I kinda miss it, you know what
I'm saying? Just the little things
The liquor stores, the people,
- the food.
- You didn't like raccoon?
No.
Huh-uh
So
what brought y'all
around these parts?
Sanchez sent us over here
to get some crops.
- We gonna--
- Oh, shh!
You trying to get yourself killed?
Say, Earl,
you want to smoke some?
Did LeBron mama get fucked?
Try that shit out
You ain't said nothing
but a word, man.
He's gonna fucking do it
The fuck you sniggling for?!
That's fucking
crystal meth, dude
You retard !
So y'all are here
to snatch some crop?
Yeah, Sanchez sent us
up here to holla at you about
snatching up some crops,
so we try and come up.
You know that'll get you
killed around these parts?
Pfft, killed?
Niggas face death every day
living in the hood
Well, you're a brave man
I'm just trying to make a credit
Make what?
Never mind.
So what's up with the crops?
Mmm, you sure that's all
you wanna talk about?
Business first, you know
- Maybe a little pleasure later
- Mmm.
Well, how about a little of both?
- Mmm, well...
- Marie!
- Yeah?
- Time to come in
Look, you want
to finish this later?
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm
- Yeah, later.
Marie!
Here I come
I'll holla at you in a little bit
Where do I... sleep
Mann
Don't put that thumb in my ass
Where are they going?
Oh, they're all going on
to work on the crops.
- Earl.
- It's a curable disease
- Oh, come on, Earl, get up.
- It's a curable disease, baby
Get up!
They're going to get the crops
- Who?
- Let's go, man. Come on
Don't forget your lunch
Oh, you flirt.
You old flirt!
There you go
- Scoot!
- Don't look at my booty
How can I help it?
- We got a big day ahead of us, bro
- It's just weed, man.
Yeah
Yeah, let's go
- Let's roll, buddy
- You're strong.
- Aw, no, shit.
- What's up, baby? You good?
Everybody that voted
for Barack Obama?
Get outta my truck.
That means you two
- We got work to do
- I can't vote.
We don't mind working, though
We can work all day.
- I like to earn my keep
- Paw said you can't go
So I suggest you two get
the fuck outta this truck
before I skin one of you
city motherfuckers.
- I do not need a haircut
- All right, damn, man.
All right, all right
I know when we're not wanted
- Let's roll.
- Yeah, I can tell when we ain't wanted
It's a damn shame. Okay
Yeehaw
- Fucking bite me!
- Oh, Lord!
Why he do that?
His daddy must be
running up in here.
Man, this really sucks
We ain't got no weed,
we ain't got no money
And on top of that,
I had to see this white man's ass
that look like
an empty eye socket
I'm gone.
Man, I'm tired of this
- Where-- where you going?
- I gotta go boo-boo.
Now what the fuck are we gonna do?
Hey, come on
Game
The hell this fool go?
Hey! You left me
Yodelayheehoo-hoo.
Hi there, sexy
Tell me, what would you do
for some of this?
- Hmm?
- Unfortunately anything
Oh, that's kinda what I thought
Won't you follow Ma?
Come on now.
Don't be shy
Come on.
- I wish I was shy
- Whoo!
Oooh!
- Hey, where are we going?
- You'll see.
Mam
all timid and shy
You're just a little
cute little baby is what you are
- Don't you want to smoke?
- Yes, now. Can I do it right now?
- Huh-uh-uh.
- I need it right now
No no no.
No love, no bud
Can we get this over with?
That's just what Paw said
on our wedding night, you poet
Come on now.
Slip them panties off
I'm so stupid!
These are not panties neither
- Oh really?
- These are briefs!
Oh my goodness,
now you're all the man, aren't you?
Oh my! Look, I was right
You are packing.
I'm gonna have to take
my teeth out for this.
Teeth?
Ahh-- Oh
Oh-- oh my God
Oh-
This weed--
this weed right here
is the bomb, man.
- Your pops grow this shit right here?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I got it out
of a secret stash.
Secret stash?
All the weed they growing up there,
why they don't just give you some?
Give"?
No, sugar.
They don't give me anything
Shit.
Thank you
The only time they
pay attention to me
is when the McRoy boys
are bothering me
or if they want me to sleep
in the bed with them
so they can grope
all over me and shit
- Your father too?
- My father, my mother, my brothers,
the uncles, cousins--
all of them, shit.
- That's how family does
- That's fucked up.
- Pilot?
- Yes.
All right, we want to make sure
we fly nice and low. Make sure we get
- the faces of these bastards
- Roger.
Looks pretty good
Think I'll leave it
out here another week or so
All right,
get ready, get ready
You see that sumbitch
taking pictures?
Who was it?
I don't know
So we gotta harvest this
sooner than I thought.
Now you know you was wrong
for having me in that boat today
- Ah, you all right.
- You know black folks
and water don't get along too good
What if I could've drown?
Oh, I guess I would have had
to give you mouth-to-mouth.
Oh shit,
you can do that anyway
Maybe we should hurry up and get back
before my dad and them get home.
- Shit, let's do it
- All right.
- Oh yeah yeah
- Mmm...
What? What's up, fellas?
Hey, what's happening?
You took a wrong fucking
turn somewhere, buddy.
Uh well, we just took
a cruise in a boat.
And we was headed
back up the hill
and we about
to bounce right now
- No, you ain't going nowhere
- Hey look, y'all,
- we're Gatsfields.
- I don't give a pig's ass who you are
Strip
Hey, pump your brakes there,
Girls Gone Wild.
Just him
- Oh no no no, hell no
- Strip!
Man, okay, wait a minute, man
Damn, hold up, hold up.
I can't believe this shit, man
What y'all gonna do, man?
We're gonna fuck you
and make your little
girlfriend here watch
Yeah, I'll make you squeal like a pig!
Oh no, wait a minute, man
Hold up. One thing.
One thing before you do that, man,
let me just do one thing.
Let me hit this one time
and you can do whatever, man
Just one time.
Just let me hit this
They ain't shit.
Alls I need is some weed
I'll show them motherfuckers
my "Blunted Master" technique
I 9011 you
Fuck me?
No, fuck y'all
- You know what I'm saying?
- Yeah.
Hey, where the hell you been?!
Come on, man
Chill out, man.
You're carrying
around picnic baskets
Old sucker for lunch--
got you sprung.
- Oh man, chill out, man
- Oh, my ass.
Come on, man.
I'm out there with bugs and shit
- Man, what's happening?
- Man, whatever.
Marie, where the hell
is the goddamn weed at?
Shh.
Hey, chill out, man
I got this under control.
You know what I'm saying?
We leaving tonight
And Marie-
she going with us
We ain't going nowhere
with this basic-ass hill rat.
- No?
- She look regular as hell in the city
Well, I know where all
the booby traps are, so fuck your face
- Fuck your face!
- Fuck your mother's face!
Fuck your face,
waffle-house, teeth-ass bitch!
Fuck your damn face. Fuck your
goatee and your big eyebrows
- and fuck your little-ass neck!
- Chill out, chill out.
Look here, you gotta pick
either me or her. Make a choice
Oh, Earl,
I just wanted to thank you
for all that plumbing work
you did for me
this morning.
You really cleaned out my pipes
I'll step in any booby trap
you want me to. Let's go.
Let's go.
I'm ready to die
Watch out
- Who the fuck is this?
- They only guard it like this
- when it's a close call
- Close call like what?
Pot snatchers or the police
So they gonna shoot it out
with the fucking police?
No, they got flamethrower things
at each corner of the crops
- That's some smart-ass hillbillies
- Mm-hmm.
Man, I'm glad you're
so impressed with their criminality
But now how the fuck
we supposed to get this weed?
I guess we're gonna have to
come up with another plan.
Oh shit, come on
Come on, nigga.
See, Ray and Earl
or even I didn't realize
we had picked
the worst possible time
to make a move
The DEA agents were hot
on the Gatsfield's tail
and preparing to make a bust
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
- and Deputy Dick
- Dan.
Whatever. We are gonna send
our ground troops
on the ground right here,
while simultaneously
choppers will be landing
here on the field.
- Okay?
- What day are we doing this?
Tomorrow
- Now--
- Tomorrow's bowling night
- Can we do it Thursday?
- Deputy Dan?
You're not stuck
on stupid, are you?
You're dangling on dummy
Shut the hell up.
Where the hell did you
find this guy?
Are we clear?
Any questions?
What's he mean by that?
All right, look, y'all
- we gonna come out right here
- Uh-huh.
Start here and we gonna come out
somewhere about right here.
And we gonna be off on the freeway
and then after that we home free.
- Cool.
- Okay?
- Yeah yeah
- Good.
That shit sound good,
but so did your other plan
that got fucked up.
Look,baby,
this here is foolproof
That's what your mouth say
I don't believe that shit.
Well, this is right
this time, I promise
- I know it for a fact.
- Hell, all your shit always-
Shut the hell up!
Get your girl, man. I ain't buying that
fucking shit. You know how I get.
- Carry your ass
- I slap bitches.
- Get him.
- Man, you better get your girl
before I Chris Brown her ass
Chill out, man.
Let's concentrate on the weed
Man, you concentrate on checking her,
man. I'm tired of all this shit.
- She know what she doing.
- Fuck you and motherfuck you!
You know what?
I thought about it, I'm a chill
- That's cool
- I'm a chill.
Cool. All right now
I take my fuck back from you,
but still fuck you.
- When are we gonna do this?
- Tomorrow morning.
I heard my daddy and them
saying they was
harvesting the crops tomorrow morning
We're outta here.
Shit, tomorrow morning
it is then.
Yeah.
Uh-huh
Mm-hmm.
You a sucker-for-love nigga, man
- What are you doing here, Marie?
- It's the McRoy boys.
They got my daddy
and them down at the house
daddy
Him
Come on, y'all. We don't have
enough time. Come on, hurry up
What the hell are you doing?
Who's guarding the crops?
Marie's guarding the crops. She said
the McRoys are back at the house.
What?
Ain't no McRoys at the house
That little sweetass is lying
Let's get back up the hill!
Yeah, finally going
to get to kill somebody!
Center mass, Lil June,
center mass!
In between the nipple
and the knee.
Hey, y'all come on
and hurry up now
- before they get back.
- All right, just one more row
Ugh, God!
No, come on, y'all! Come on!
Oh shit
Stop shooting! Don't shoot the shed
You know what's in there!
Hold up, man. All we want is
the weed and we up outta here
- Man, that's it.
- You sumbitches ain't leaving
this motherfucker alive
- Yeah, you city queers
- Hold up, son.
Who the fuck you think
you talking to, buddy?
I will flame all you mothers
Especially
Range-Rover-face-ass.
- You better shut your boy up
- June,
shut your Range-Rover face up
Now listen, maybe we can come
to some sort of comprise.
It's compromise,
you dumb fuck.
And we ain't coming to no compromise
We taking all this shit.
We're gonna take all
your kids from you, bitch
I'm afraid I can't let you do that
- All right, all right, all right!
- Whoa whoa whoa!
- Whoa whoa whoa
- Stop.
Listen, you can take the pot,
but Marie's staying with me
- No no!
- Go ahead, take that bitch
- I don't want nothing to do with her
- No, that ain't going down.
Oh yeah, she goes down a lot
- Mm.
- Fuck it.
My dawg say she coming with us,
so I guess we get the weed
- and her-- for now.
- Are you just gonna
leave my earthworm
to suck that black snake?
Hey, it is what it is, man
- Oh shit!
- Come on, come on
Let me drive. Get in
Oh oh, let's get flow
- California shit good, state grown
- Let's get moving!
That was fun
I'm glad you had so much fun,
cause here these motherfuckers come
- Huh?
- Oh shit!
You know, we--
we should be getting the hell up
outta here. You know?
- Yeah.
- What the hell are we doing here?
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I want to do?
- Can we land this thing over at KFC?
- Sure.
Yeah!
You're my dawg, dawg!
Hey, if a tree is burning
you know, in the forest,
anybody $11211  IQ
- That's deep, man
- Right?
I never thought about that
Man, I can't believe
outta all the bullshit-ass
trucks you would get,
- you'd get the one that'd break down
- Oh, fuck you, Earl.
At least you got
your goddamn weed, babe
Yeah, we got the weed, but shit!
We ain't got no way
to get home now.
- How the fuck we gonna get home?
- Use your thumb.
Or your mouth.
Maybe that's more like--
That ain't gonna
get us nowhere-- nowhere
- Fuck you, fuck him
- Fuck her.
- Hey, want to get lifted?
- Daddy! Hey, Daddy!
- Daddy?
- See, honey, I told you
I was gonna get you
outta here someday.
Man, what's going on?
Why you didn't tell us
this was your daughter?
Yeah, that's how I got stuck here
I couldn't leave here
without my baby.
Yes! Told y'all I could
get y'all a ride.
Come on, get in.
I'll tell you all about it
- on the way out.
- You're hiding a ton of things
Look here,
that's one hell of a story, man
Is it true?
- 100%.
- Damn!
So I know they made it back
to the hood with all that sweet sativa
and flipped that shit,
now they sitting on fat
Hey, I know they got cheese, man
No, they flat broke, man
They spent it
on lowriders and hookers.
How much of this do you want?
Of this shit right here?
Man, I want all of this
motherfucking shit, nigga
Kick that in, right now
It's always a pleasure
doing business with you, baby
- Shit, right on
- There you go
D-E-V the D-U-D-E
Coffee for the E-X-E-C
Just as I am with dandy
Fifth Ward, Ailey Dance,
street club freaks, Spice Lane
To all the killers
who nose full of 'caine
To all the underclassmen
who rose from the fray
For those who never has-been
thinking they sired Cain
To all of those who wanna be,
really thinking they are
Even though they reach their
limit and took it too far
This for those who are
really thinking they focused
Never up the nose,
dipping cigarettes is bogus
All we need, we roll it
inhale and hold it
Exhale, 'cause hell,
all we need, we smoke it
All you need is weed
and nothing else
Sit back and roll one
and enjoy yourself
All them other narcotics
fuck up your health
Yeah yeah yeah
All you need is weed
and nothing else
Sit back and roll one
and enjoy yourself
All them other narcotics
fuck up your health
Yeah yeah yeah
I got an old school partner,
he smoke crack
He's fierce with the lyrics,
but he probably won't come back
To the studio, because he
might be out creepin'
In somebody's house, trying
to clean 'em out, thievin'
I know another nigga,
he smoke fry
He always cry,
but we don't know why
We tried to give him advice,
but he wouldn't take it
Saw him last Wednesday
walking down the street beggin
My homeboy used to holla,
but he's out there snorting powder
Hour after hour,
but he'd never take a shower
And I guess it's cool
if you can handle your thing
But it's kinda fucked up
if you dismantle your brain
Like my nigga poking his
veins with tracks in his arm
He ain't real cool,
but he's always calm
He disappear real quick
and shoot up one D
I tried to pass him the weed
the nigga asleep.
What you know about that hydro?
All these strains, Early Girl
Purple Haze, Afghani,
straight Candy
Nigerian weed, Maui Wowie
Blueberry, Island Lady
Indigo weed
Holland's Hope, Hindu Kush
Master Kush,
Northern Bright
I'm riding to the chronic
smoking chronic
Blueberry balls
are called sonic
Man, it picks me up,
you know about me
Please don't come around me
if you don't smoke weed
I'm smoking like a teapot
Are you scared of this shit
that we've got?
Push 'em good, nigga
No seeds
Droski
In addition I've gotta
track the police
And everybody within four feet
I'm looking like I got no sleep
But I'm cool like a bag
of ice with no cold feet
Two blunts I roll, home sweets
I see two hos, I get ball freeze
We hook up
then we smoke weed
We blow the blunts
then they blow me
What you know
about that hydro?
All these strains,
Early Girl
Purple Haze, Afghani,
straight Candy
Nigerian weed
Maui Wowie
Blueberry, Island Lady
Indigo weed
Holland's Hope,
Hindu Kush
Master Kush,
Northern Bright
What you know
about that hydro?
All these strains,
Early Girl
Purple Haze, Afghani,
straight Candy
Nigerian weed
Maui Wowie
Blueberry, Island Lady
Indigo weed
Holland's Hope,
Hindu Kush
Master Kush,
Northern Bright
“He
Burnin' one
I fina burn one
Yeah, I fina burn one
Rats dressed in all black
Burning one up,
blowing one back
Chick on my lap
from the mini Gap
Twisting back my cap,
bending down her back
Pawing that shit like that,
beat that pussy, I beat that cat
Come on in,
shine like a full-blown lamp
All inked up like
a full-grown man
Said I'm 1 7
and the bitch say ' Damn
Said I do it better
than her goddamn man
Get your eyes brown
like a full-blown tan
Centerfold girl like
a full-blown fan
Bitch, whoa, hold up
Who the fuck you talking to?
'Bout to blast off?
Like a motherfucking rocket do
Your girl tryin' to kick it,
trying to kick it like soccer shoes
All up in her mouth like
the dentist saw the doctor do
My flow unstoppable,
you do as I do and I rap with you