[  %% music  ]
[  %%  ]
Ah, listen to this.
According to
the welcome wagon,
Miller falls has
a population of
Four thousand, one hundred
and eighty-six people.
Welcome wagon?
They still have
welcome wagons here?
Well, you're in Ohio.
I can see
the headlines now,
"newcomers run over
by welcome wagon."
Where are we?
Honey, you can't find your
way around unless you're
willing to explore.
Aw, honey...Please
don't get us lost.
Our first day in town's
not the time to play
Lewis and Clark.
Okay. Slow down. It's
up on the right.
Oop. Let me guess.
The blue one.
Nice.
Nope, nope, nope,
it's the brick.
Well?
Who owned this,
Rockefeller?
Charley?
What?
How do you like it?
I'd like it better if
it was our old house
in Denver.
No, you wouldn't.
Our old house in Denver
is full of the Andersons...
All ten of them.
I don't even know why
we're here at all!
Sweetheart, we talked
about this.
No, you talked about it!
No one ever asked me!
This, too, shall pass.
I like it.
Hey, it's four-thirty.
Who's hungry? You hungry?
I could eat.
You could eat. Does
that mean you know how to
eat or you want to eat?
If it's pizza.
Ah, we have a consensus.
Honey! Dinner! Come on!
Ho, that was great.
I'm liking this town
more and more.
They didn't even
have pepperoni.
Well, that's 'cause
it's a seafood restaurant.
Honey...
Dad, look out!
Stop, Ben! You're
gonna...Hit him!
[ squealing tires. ]
[ yelp. ]
Is he dead?
Uh...No, he's
still breathing.
How bad is it?
I don't know.
There could be
internal injuries.
What should we do?
Well, we gotta get
this guy to a vet.
Is he gonna die?
No...Charley, he's
not going to die.
Come on, get in the car.
Man, next time you
decide to play chicken,
Do it with a
scooter, not an SUV.
Here he comes.
Well, I've done
what I can.
Internal injuries?
Well, I-I...I was
afraid the bladder
might be ruptured,
Which would
be very bad.
The animal could develop
peritonitis...
Go into shock and die.
Fortunately...That
wasn't the case...Here.
Excuse me.
The kidneys are bruised.
Uh, some of the muscles
have been pulled.
I don't uh, I don't
know about uh,
all the organs yet.
So he'll live?
Yeah, I--
Bless you!
Aw, thank you.
I think so.
I have to run a
couple more tests.
You know, the foreleg
seems to be bothering
Her quite a bit,
but it's not broken.
Her?
Yeah, it's a...Female.
What's her name?
She's not our dog.
Oh. Stray. Yeah,
I....Thought that might
Be the case when
I didn't see a collar.
Okay, uh...
...You want to be
responsible for her?
Otherwise, they're going
to send her to the county
And, in most cases, injured
strays are euthanized.
Well, uh...Yeah,
I guess so.
Can I see her?
No, buddy she's
just been sedated.
Um, maybe another
time would be better.
Uh, it's okay. We don't
need to see her.
Where will she go
after she wakes up?
Not with us, pal.
Why not?
Sweetheart, remember
our lease agreement.
We can't have pets.
Well, she could
stay here...
Bless you!
I have a cold the
size of Mount McKinley.
You know, you don't
have to do this.
Euthanasia...Might be
the most merciful thing.
No. I don't want
to do that, okay.
Okay. Great.
Listen, just give me
your name and your
Phone number, and I'll
contact you about
The boarding fees.
This dog has good breeding.
Really?
Yeah, I'll-I'll...Bet
she's AKC registered.
What's AKC?
American kennel club.
It means she's a
Really special dog.
I'm indebted to you,
Dr. Elliot.
Thank you very much.
And call me doc.
Most people around here do.
Don't worry, I'll
give you a good rate.
Thanks, doc.
What? It was an
accident.
I didn't know she
was a thoroughbred.
That would be
horses, sweetheart.
Horses, dogs, whatever.
Did you say your
prayers, sweetheart?
No!
Not you.
Yes.
Mom?
Mm-hm?
What does "youth and
um, Asia" mean?
Euthanasia is when they
put an animal to sleep.
You mean, kill her?
Well, sometimes...It's
Better to do that than
to let it suffer.
But you can't do that!
Well...Your dad's not
gonna let that happen.
(to Ben)
are you, sweetheart?
Nothing's gonna
happen to her.
Now go to sleep.
Dad...I really
want to keep her.
We can't keep her. No
pets allowed here.
Mom?
We'll go to the vet
tomorrow and make sure
She's all right, okay?
Okay.
He should put
us all to sleep.
And the good news
is, none of her
Injuries were life threatening.
Well, that's a relief,
isn't it, charley?
Yeah.
Thank you, doc.
You're welcome.
So, when will she
be able to be let go?
Never.
Never?
Yeah, you know...I
noticed that her foreleg
Was bothering her
when I-when I examined
Her and it is, but
it has nothing to do
with the accident.
What is it?
Cancer.
Can't you stop it?
Yeah, charley, I can.
Unfortunately, there's only
Really one way that
I can do that.
You mean, amputate her leg?
Yeah. Do you want
to go to that expense?
How far advanced is it?
Well, I will tell you
that it is a Miracle
That it hasn't
metastasized before now.
This is...One special dog.
But if you want to
save her, it's gonna
Have to happen soon.
Mom?
Aw, sweetheart I wish we
could adopt her,
I really do. But we can't.
But we can pay
for the operation.
I think you've made
the right choice.
Oh, have I? Now,
who's gonna adopt a
Three-legged dog?
Oh, I don't know. How 'bout a
Two-legged boy who
needs a friend?
That's right.
You sure? No charge?
Not if you give her a home.
Oh.
I'll see what I can do.
Okay charley, you
can have a couple more
Minutes with her.
(to Dr. Elliot)
doc, thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
You...Are very welcome.
You know, son, I wonder
what happened to her puppies.
What puppies?
Oh, I noticed that last night.
She uh, she must have just
finished weaning a litter.
Really? Where?
I don't know. Maybe
where you found her.
You think so?
Seems like a pretty
good place to start.
You're not sneezing today.
You know, that's true.
It's the strangest thing,
I-I'm not sick anymore.
You brush your teeth?
Twice.
Want to take a ride
around the neighborhood?
What for? I
don't know anybody.
Well, if you stay home,
you won't meet anybody.
I-I just don't want to.
Charley-
And what-what if they
don't want to play with me?
But what if they do?
What do I say?
You say, "hello.
Hi, my name's charley".
Um, when will
our stuff be here?
'bout four days. Listen,
sweetheart,
We're all in the
same boat. Your dad,
You, me, we're
all gonna get used to
It. We're all gonna
make new friends.
Yeah, easy for you
to say. You have a job.
I've got my cell
phone with me. You can
Call me every two
hours. And I love you.
I love you, too.
Keep your helmet
on. Don't you take it
Off when you're
out of my sight.
I won't. Ha! Ha!
We're breakfront tower.
Cleveland metro
Life flight number
four, five Miles to
The south leading
to Cleveland clinic.
Level one trauma.
Repeat, we have
a level one trauma.
Right, breakfront tower.
Metro life
Flight number four
is descending for
Final landing at
Cleveland clinic.
Caution advisory is
appropriate during flights.
Landing gear lever
down and locked,
Breakfront tower.
Cleveland metro life
flight number four descending
For final landing
at Cleveland clinic.
Current wind at
two-seventy and ten.
Gusts at fourteen. Cleared
to land at the clinic.
Emergency lights off.
AFCF off. Avionics off.
After-landing check complete.
Cleveland metro
life flight number
Four, ER is ready and
waiting for level one trauma.
Coming through!
I've prepped her.
I've called radiology.
I believe she's in stabilized
condition, sir.
Okay, I want a
full set of x rays, fore
And aft, anterior
and posterior knee,
And uh, all quadrants, okay?
Do we need to check for any
internal injuries, doctor?
No, no, no, just
the knee.
Allright? I'll get
everything ready.
And one other thing.
It's very important.
Get me the score
of the browns game.
Oh, I already checked that.
They're up by a touchdown.
Well, my day's
looking better already.
Sorry I'm late.
Or maybe not. You're
too late, Malone.
I am?
No, she's going
to be all right.
Cuts and abrasions and
a shattered left kneecap.
All in all, I'd say
she's a pretty lucky lady.
They flew her on life flight
just for a shattered kneecap?
This is Kelly Maguire,
one of the top
Ten tennis players in the
world. They want the best
orthopedic surgeon
In the country.
Which reminds me.
You know, you've got wonderful
instincts as a resident, and...
...I think you're going to
be a really good doctor...
...But you've gotta
stop forgetting the
Fundamentals! I mean,
when you're on
Duty, you've gotta
remain in the area!
I don't want to have to call
my residents more than once!
I know, I'm sorry.
When I got the page-
Sorry doesn't cut it!
Yes, sir.
There's another thing
you've gotta learn.
The art of diplomacy.
I do?
Yes. Dr. Kay and I want you to
go and greet our new medical
researcher.
His name is Ben Logan. And
I don't want him to
Feel like he's
been forgotten.
I've actually read
some of his research
That he did for
uh, Boston children's.
That's the guy.
Okay.
Now, go. And remember!
Fundamentals.
Right, right.
Dr. Logan.
Yes?
Andy Malone. Welcome
to the clinic.
Thanks. Good to
be here. Resident?
Ah, yes, actually.
Six months next
Week. I've heard
quite a bit about you.
All lies.
Right, right, right.
I actually read the paper
You presented to the Boston
children's clinic.
"minimal invasive thoracic
surgery techniques for
newborns."
It's pretty impressive.
Thank you.
Yeah. You're here
on a research Grant,
is that correct?
Yeah, convalescent and
rehab strategies.
Yeah, what disciplines?
Pretty much everything
from oncology
to brain surgery.
Sounds like you've
got the run
of the hospital.
Well, yeah. Any patient that's
in rehab or convalescing is fair
game.
Actually, this is me,
but uh, it was a
pleasure to meet you.
If you need anything,
please just holler.
Well, thank you. I will.
Dr. Logan.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, Dr. Kay!
Hi, good to see you.
You, too, sir.
How's everything going?
Just fine, thank you.
Listen, let me know
if there's anything
I can do for you.
Yes, sir, I
will. Thank you.
Good morning.
Hey, Leeza.
Is she here yet?
Yes.
Hi.
Welcome to the
Cleveland clinic. I'm
Leeza Madison, your
administrative assistant.
Well, hi. It's nice
to meet you. I'm
Glad you're here. Can
you tell me where
The overnights are?
Oh, right here.
Alphabetical, by departments.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Guess I have to get up to
speed on the routine here.
Oh, you will.
Your husband's here on a
research Grant, right?
Yeah. He took the Grant
so we could be together.
Okay, stay in front
of the ball.
Keep in front of
the ball. Oww!
Atta boy. Nice catch!
Double play! All right!
You charley Logan?
Um ... Maybe.
Your mom asked me
to give you this note.
Okay.
Do you know where this
um, waiting room is?
Mm-hm. Third floor,
out the elevator,
Hang a left, about
halfway down the hall.
You lost?
Hi.
No.
Maybe. Maybe, yeah.
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
My mom said there
was an empty waiting
room on this floor.
Yeah, who's your mom?
Terry Logan?
Ah, the assistant
administrator.
That means your dad
is Dr. Ben Logan.
How did you know?
I'm gifted that way.
Are there patients
on this floor?
Yeah. This is actually, the
geriatric convalescent ward.
Old people.
Oh.
Dr. Malone?
Andy. You can call me Andy.
Hi, Andy. I'm charley.
Hi, charley. It's
good to meet you.
Well, charley, I
have afternoon rounds.
I'm gonna leave
you here, okay?
All right.
You gonna be good?
Yeah.
Promise?
Mm-hm.
All right. Later.
Mrs. Mannion?
Who are you?
Dr. Logan.
Where's Nate?
Nate?
Nate Ecklin, my physician.
Dr. Ecklin's out
of town today.
They asked me to stop
in and see you. I'm new.
Well, I'm old, and I don't
want a different doctor.
Well, I'm not.
I mean, I am, but
I'm not here to take
Dr. Ecklin's place. I-I
just need to ask
You a few questions
about your treatments.
What are you doing here?
I'm doing research.
But you can't just
barge in like this.
Well actually, you
can go anywhere you
Want as long as
you look serious
and carry a clipboard.
Um, you're leaving.
Yes, as soon as Edward
comes with the car.
You're scheduled for
chemotherapy tomorrow.
Well, they can schedule
whatever they like.
I'm going home. And you
can't make me stay.
My money built this wing.
Well, I'm not going
to make you stay,
Mrs. Mannion, but I
suggest you reconsider.
Because without the therapy,
your cancer will return again.
Dr. Logan ... I am
tired. I'm alone.
Albert and I had only
one daughter.
She died a few years ago.
So I want to go home.
Sorry. Home, madam?
Where else would I go?
That went well.
[ phone rings ]
Hey, pal.
New town kind of a bummer?
It's okay.
Want a ride?
No, I've got my bike.
Look, charley, I-I
know this has been
Kind of tough on
you. I mean, you made
The bigger sacrifice
coming here, and
Your mom and I both
know you'd really
Like to keep that dog.
Annie.
Annie, right. Look,
as-as soon as I can
Get my research
going and this
Teleconference finished,
I'll find us a
Real house, one
where we can have a dog.
Well, what if
we're too late?
Well, we'll tell doc Elliot
we want to keep her, okay?
Hey, thanks, dad!
You're welcome.
[ dogs barking ]
Hi, girl. How you doing?
Let's see, I'm gonna
name you Annie.
She's my best
friend in Denver.
And you, you're a Max.
Yeah, I'll call you Max.
So, Annie, is
Max your boyfriend?
Are you feeling okay, girl?
Whoa!
I'm sorry.
No problem, ace.
You work with the animals?
I catch 'em.
Oh.
I'm here for a pickup now.
Oh, man, have I got a beaut.
A headache?
Migraines. Since I
was a kid like you.
Maybe my dog can help.
You got a dog in here?
Her name's Annie.
This is your dog?
Well, not yet. But
she will be soon.
I just have to
figure it out.
Well, you better
do it quick.
Why?
Well, it says right
here that she's scheduled
To be transferred tomorrow
to the county pound.
What does that mean?
Well, it could mean anything.
Sometimes they ... Put
'em to sleep.
You're taking her tomorrow?
Yeah, I'm sorry, kid.
I had to put some
puppies down last week
that nobody wanted.
That's what the
red tag means: Transfer.
Can't I do anything?
Come on, pup. You
ready to go?
Yeah.
You can try and adopt her.
If I can find her
puppies, then they
Have to let me keep Annie.
Here, puppies! Here, puppies!
Here, puppies!
Puppies anywhere? Puppies?
Puppies?
Puppy! Puppies!
Puppies.
Puppies!
[ puppies whimpering. ]
Oh, the doc was right!
Oh, I bet you
guys are hungry.
We're almost there.
Ah, here we are. It's
a little place for you.
Here you go.
You guys gotta be quiet.
Quiet.
I'll try to find
a safer place tomorrow.
Listen, I can't wait
for my dad, you know,
To bring your mom
home, so I'm gonna
bring her home tomorrow,
Okay?
Shh. All right. Quiet.
Would you care
for something, madam?
Oh, uh, just tea ... Edward.
Oh, Albert.
Albert, I wish you were
here. I need your strength.
I don't know ... That
I can face this alone.
Shall I pour, madam?
Uh, yes, please, Edward.
I brought your medication.
I don't want it.
Yes, I know.
I won't take it.
As you wish.
Why do you stay?
Habit, I suppose, madam.
Well, that's a fine
thing to say to
Your employer of
twenty-five years.
I've noticed it matters
little what I say to you.
Get out.
As you wish. Will there
be anything else?
No!
Mrs. Mannion...
What?
You know, being alone is ...
It's a matter of choice.
Stay here and be
quiet. I'm gonna go
get your mom.
Come on, Annie. Let's
go. We're leaving.
Come on, guys! Let's
go! Let's go!
Come on! Come on! Let's
go! Come on! Come on!
What is she doing?
She likes you.
What happened to her leg?
Cancer. They had
to amputate it.
Kind of like me.
You still have your leg.
Yeah, well, they
may as well have cut
It off. I can't
play tennis anymore.
Oh, you play tennis?
I did.
Well, what happened?
Car accident.
Shattered my knee.
It'll heal.
Yeah, but I'll
never play tennis again.
Do something else.
I have to go.
What's her name?
Annie.
You understand,
don't you Annie?
She knows what people need.
What's your name?
I'm charley.
Hi, charley. I'm Kelly.
Hi. She really does
know what people need.
I believe you.
Bye.
She needs a dog like you.
Do you mind?
Uh, no. No. No,
no, no, no.
Meniscus.
It's a little
bit more than that.
Kneecap?
It's a car crash.
What are you, a
Physical therapist?
Doctor. I--resident. I'm
at the Cleveland clinic.
You know, I know
some great exercises.
We can-we can get
you back up to speed.
Not the speed
that I was used to.
What were you used to?
Tennis.
Is that so?
I know you.
You're Kelly Maguire.
You're the number one seed
from the emergency room.
Was. I was the
number one seed.
You know, I was serious
about the exercises.
Thanks, but I think
I'm getting all the
Help that I need.
You know, sometimes it's
better to get a little bit of
Help at the right
time, than a lot of
Help at the wrong time.
What were you thinking of?
Lunch.
I meant about the exercises.
So did I. I thought
we could discuss it
Over lunch.
Let me guess, this is
"take a gimp to lunch" week.
The ballpark. South
of the center.
I will bring you lunch.
Say one o'clock?
One o'clock. Don't be late.
Hey, get back in
there! Stay! Over
there! Come on!
Get in there! Stay,
stay. No! No!
Get in! Move back in
there. Come on. Stay!
What are you doing?
You can't come down here!
I-I'm sorry.
I-I didn't-
Get your tail outta
here right now.
Now!
What's this?
A dog.
I know it's a dog.
What's it doing down here?
It's with me.
And who are you?
I'm charley. I'm
trying to save them.
Save them from what?
Being killed.
What do you
mean, being killed?
Killed put to sleep,
s-simonized?
Somebody's gonna wax
them to death?
Uh, yeah, may--I don't know!
Ah, excellent. Do they
show all the surgical suites?
All five.
Uh-huh. Well, I'm
going to need to have
A camera in one of the
convalescent areas.
Uh, how many people?
About half a dozen.
Okay, I could set
the room up for
Video. When do
we do this?
Next week. I'm
sorry for the short
Notice, but I was
just told by Dr. Ecklin.
You know him?
Yeah, I know him.
Uh-huh. Well, I
just uh, found out from
A memo. Actually,
I've not met him yet.
You will.
Uh-huh. Well, I
need to be able to
Show, uh rehab,
some of the different
Procedures, operating
techniques,
Pretty much anything
that has to do
With post-op or post-traumatic
uh, convalescence.
Got that?
No, but I will.
Good man. Any questions?
No, sir.
Aha. Good. Well, uh, you
can stop calling me sir.
I keep thinking
my dad's here.
Oh, look at you.
Look at you. Yeah.
Oh, hey, charley.
Cute little dudes, ain't they?
Yeah. You have a dog?
I did once. A long time ago.
What's your name?
Didn't I already tell you?
No, you were
too busy yelling.
Yeah, right.
My name's C.W.
Huh?
C.W. Like the two
letters, c and w.
Well, does it
stand for something?
Of course it
stands for somethin'.
Carter Wyatt. What's
your last name?
Logan.
Logan?
You mean like the new
assistant administrator Logan?
Yeah, that's my mom.
Listen, you've got to get these
mutts out of here.
And don't you tell your mom
about this do you understand?
I won't.
You better not.
She's kind of a
Miracle dog, you know?
What kind of miracles?
Well she makes
people ... Better.
Yeah? What do you mean?
Like she makes
'em do nice stuff?
No. Like, if you're sick
and you touch Annie,
you'll get better.
It-it's true.
See this scratch
right here?
Annie licked it and
now it's all better.
Really?
Well, uh, listen, you
best get out of here now.
Okay.
See you, charley.
Bye.
Hi.
So ... What's for lunch?
To begin we have
a wild green salad, with...
...Bistro-grilled chicken.
You're kidding.
Come on, he resets
elbows, he cooks...
Maybe I should have
broken both my knees.
A little garlic, a little
onion, some papas fritas...
They're pan-fried potatoes.
And then for dessert we
have a little crme brle.
I'm impressed.
As you should be.
How's the knee?
Uh, it's better. Uh,
a lot better, actually.
We'll have you on
the court here in no time.
Yeah, well, I won't exactly
be playing Monica Seles
Tomorrow, but--but
uh, but it's better.
I'm glad.
Why did you want
to have lunch with me?
Well, I was hungry.
Ask a silly question and...
I thought I could help.
Why me?
Because you're prettier than
most of the patients I see.
Tennis was my life.
I know.
I can handle it.
I just thought
that maybe you'd
Like some company
while you're doing it.
I don't need another
disappointment.
Is that what I am, just
another disappointment?
Not yet.
Not ever.
We'll see.
Hey, girl, what
are you doing here?
Hey, Eddie, send
security up to the ICU
On the first floor, will you?
I think there's an
animal on the floor.
Uh, I don't know.
Maybe a dog.
Yes, I know a dog
when I see one,
But this one had
three legs, I think.
No, wise guy, it is not a UFO.
Just send security, okay?
Hey, Chad, how you doin'?
Good.
Aren't you still in pain?
No, my leg feels great, doc.
It's kinda like I
could run out of here
All the way to
the football field.
Well, not yet, but,
hmmm, you're close.
And I can't figure out why.
How's your range of motion?
Great. It's almost
like, uh ... A Miracle.
Yeah, that's amazing all right.
You want a Miracle?
Get me tickets on
the fifty-yard line.
That's a Miracle.
You got it.
Oh, Leeza! Leeza let me talk to
you for a minute.
Are you feeling
okay, Dr. Marchant?
I feel fine. It's Chad Ripley.
He's recovering too fast, and
I just can't explain it.
The man's just
gettin' better, I guess.
Well, nobody heals that fast,
not even superman.
Let me ask you something.
Have you noticed
anything peculiar or
Strange going on around here?
Other than the
usual mayhem? No.
Huh.
Good morning.
You're gonna love this.
Oh, yeah? What?
A mysterious animal
around the hospital.
And get this ... It
had three legs.
Oh, yeah? How many
heads did it have?
Just one, I think.
(hums the "twilight zone" theme)
do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Welcome to area 51.
And by the time security got
there, some old guy with
Congestive heart failure had
made a miraculous recovery.
Really?
Somebody needs to
call Oprah.
No, no, don't
you call Oprah.
Call the custodian. Tell
him I need to see him.
I'll find him.
Okay.
Hey!
I cannot believe
how fast you're healing.
I don't know,
it's weird, huh?
It's spooky. I mean,
you blew out your
Anterior crucial ligament,
and all of a
Sudden it's reconstructing,
like by itself.
I had surgery.
Nah, only to reattach.
Anyway, I gotta
get to physical therapy.
Right, yeah. You've
gotta keep that up.
You'll be playing
Wimbledon here by next month.
I don't know about
that, but, uh, maybe
Back on the court, huh?
Um, I'll call you later.
Yeah.
Okay.
[  %%  ]
Um, have you seen a
little boy about yea high?
No, sir.
No? Okay, thanks.
What you doin' here
during the day?
I had to feed the puppies.
Well, I'll feed
the puppies.
I got some food for 'em
up in the cafeteria.
You know, people
notice a kid like you
Roamin' around,
you know that?
I'll tell you what
you gotta do, though,
You have got to find
a home for these little
fellas, and quick.
I know. I just
need a little more time.
Well, you've got
'til the end of the month.
That's it.
I'll try, CW.
All right.
How come you
don't like dogs?
I never said that.
Yeah, well, you never
said you did like 'em.
You don't have one.
So ... Why don't
you have a dog?
I had one ... Once.
Did it die?
Yeah.
Five years ago.
His name was Horace.
He was a mutt. He sure
loved to ride in the car.
They all do.
How did he die? Old age?
No, uh...
I was just heading
down to the grocery
Store, and Horace
was sittin' right
Next to me, and
he jumped in the back
Seat with my boy,
Dwight, and he'd
Just, uh, turned twenty-five.
We was up on the
I-90 and, all of a sudden,
Horace, he starts barkin'
like nobody's business.
And I turned around
to look what was goin' on,
And this truck had pulled up
behind us and this dog was
Leaning out the window
and Horace was just
lettin' me know, and
Maybe he was just sayin'
hello to that other dog.
I don't know. I took
my eyes off the road for
Just a second. I
mean, it was just a
Split second. And
Dwight, he-he sees
Somethin' coming up
ahead and he yells
At me and I turn
around real quick, but
... It wasn't quick enough.
There's no way I could've
missed that station wagon.
Plowed right into it, head on.
I never seen nothin'
like it, I mean,
Everything went
black as night.
When I woke up, I was right
here in the hospital ...
And, uh, m'back was broken,
My spleen was
ruptured, so they
Told me. I-I don't
remember much of that.
But ... Horace ... Dwight ...
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, listen
... I gotta get back
To work, and uh,
you know, so do you.
You have got to find
a place for these puppies.
I will, CW.
I know you will. You're
a good boy, charley.
Now you skedaddle outta here.
You know, since
I been seein' you,
My backaches have
absolutely stopped.
Is he right about
you being one
of those Miracle dogs?
Huh?
Bark the truth now.
Thank you, Mr. Crawford.
(announcer)
IV nurse to PCU.
(kiss)
What are you doing here?
I heard about this mysterious
night visitor. What is it?
Well, you got me.
Mr. Crawford says it's a
dog ... A Miracle dog.
Only has three legs.
What? A three-legged
dog in a hospital?
Yep, he said once the animal
touched him, he was healed.
And was he?
You'd know better than I, but
his physician says
that his arteries are
Suddenly clear and his
arrhythmia is stabilized.
That's impossible.
I know. Have fun.
A three-legged dog?
Whoa.
Hey, hey, hey, wait,
wait, wait!
Where you going so fast?
Oh, I'm gonna go meet some
friends at the park.
Oh, you got some new
friends. That's nice.
Bring 'em over.
Sure.
Uh, when will dad be home?
Soon. He's checking out a
prowler at the hospital.
Burglar?
Hmm.
A three-legged one,
according to witnesses.
Three legs?
Mm-hm.
What did he steal?
Well, some hearts, apparently.
You see, last night, a dog or
something went into some of
The patients' rooms.
What happened?
Well, nothing bad
from what I can gather.
The patients seemed
to improve because
Of this mysterious visitor.
They got better.
Yes.
You know, I asked
the custodian about
It because, um, having
an animal in the
Hospital would be a serious
infringement of the rules,
And could get a person
into a lot of trouble.
But he didn't
know anything about it.
Didn't they catch her?
Hm?
Uh the animal?
Did they?
Oh, no, no. She just vanished. A
wondrous visit from a UFO.
UFO?
Mm.
Unidentified furry object.
Charley.
Yes?
Don't be late for dinner.
I won't.
Oh! Good heavens!
What are you doing on
My property, young man?
Um, I was taking a shortcut.
Do I know you?
You were at the hospital.
Was.
How come?
Cancer.
Sorry.
Makes two of us.
My dog, Annie, had cancer.
Doc Elliot had to
cut her leg off.
I wish that would
work for me.
Well, maybe my
dog could help.
How on earth could
your dog help me?
She's a Miracle dog.
It would take a Miracle,
if I believed in them.
Run along now. I've wasted
enough time on you.
Are you going back?
What business is
that of yours?
It isn't.
Are you?
I-I don't want
to, but I have to.
When?
This afternoon.
I'll come visit you.
You want to come
and visit me?
Sure, my mom and
dad work there.
I'm charley.
Charley. Katherine.
I'll bring Annie.
Oh, now, that'd be
quite a trick. I'd
Like to see you
sneak her in there.
Bye.
Little hooligan.
Yes. How dare he
try to be friendly?
Edward, if you have
a point to make, I
Wish you would do so.
No, no, no, not
at all, Mrs. Mannion.
You make all the
points around here.
Will you be
staying outside long?
I don't know. Perhaps.
Yes, of course. Ring
if you need assistance.
I need assistance.
No, Mrs. Mannion. You
never need assistance.
You are forced to accept it
on occasion, but that's all.
Edward?
Um, could you stay awhile?
Perhaps we could talk?
Of course.
But only uh,
if you want too.
I mean, it is
not an order.
I know, Mrs.-
Katherine.
[  %%  ]
We're here ... Katherine.
Annie can you make
people better? 'cause if
You can, then your
puppies can, too.
[  %%  ]
Mama?
Sweetheart?
Where am I?
You're in a hospital.
[  %%  ]
You know how many case
histories I have from
these dog stories?
It's the talk
of the hospital.
Yeah, but these
were all puppies.
We have puppies now?
Well, look, I've
talked to security,
The custodial staff
and the night nurses,
And nobody has seen
anything. Just nothing. Zip.
You know what's
really amazing?
Hm.
Each one of these
people is actually
Healing at a much
faster rate.
I know it's unbelievable,
but it's verifiable.
I'm writing a
report on it.
When's the conference?
Tomorrow, and I've
got the proof right here.
I just don't know how
the board or Dr. Ecklin's
gonna take it.
Sweetheart, you're
gonna hit a home run.
Honey, I couldn't hit
sand if I fell off a camel.
This is remarkable.
That's a good thing, right?
Yeah. You know, a short
time ago I would
have said that uh,
There was no Chance of you
setting a foot on a tennis court
for the rest of your life.
But, uh, being
an ardent man of
Science, I would
say this is nothing
short of a Miracle.
Dr. Marchant. Hi...I uh ... I-
You were just in the
neighborhood,
So you thought you'd
drop by, right?
Right, yeah, yeah.
Haven't you
forgotten something?
Oh, I didn't- I
didn't know that I
Needed a mask in here.
I th- I thought that-
Your charts.
Charts, right, right.
And I expect a full report.
Right. Th- thank you, sir.
Charley, uh, has, like,
A surprise he
wants to show me,
And I was wondering
if maybe you'd
like to come.
Anything to get
out of this bed.
Okay.
Well, these are the
puppies I was telling
you guys about.
I love puppies! I
saw his big brother.
Oh, uh, mother.
This is Jennifer.
You want her?
What, you mean it?
Yeah.
Well, I-I can't
take her now, but...
Okay, but you
can't wait too long.
Everybody is talking
about these Miracle dogs.
Okay, wh-what are their names?
Well you guys
just met um, Jennifer.
And next to her is a
boy. His name is Lopez.
And over here is
Elton and there's John.
And there's Max and Annie.
Where did you get them?
They're hers.
I found them the second
day we came to town.
You know, you are
right about one thing.
What?
You have to get
them outta here.
Are we ready?
Rock and roll.
Great.
Uh, welcome, doctors.
If you'd care to take your
seats we can begin.
Um, by the way, we're
doing a live statewide
hookup today.
Okay, in suite one, a heart
pacemaker implant is in
Progress, and, over here...
...A patient who
just had the procedure
Two days ago
is being monitored.
Um, if any of you would care to
communicate with any of the
physicians or patients,
Feel free to do so with the
microphones in front of you.
Now the implantation
of the device, as you know,
Is accomplished through
the aorta, with the
aid of a small camera...
I gotta make a
call. I'll be right back.
...Chest cavity. Okay, now first
a little historical data about
the pacemaker device itself.
We have chosen to use a
demand unit
Which will take control if the
patient's heart beat falls below
the pre-programmed...
Ho! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey!
W-w-w--
[  %%  ]
Hey!
Round 'em up!
I got 'em!
Here we go. How
many we got?
Oh, uh. Hold
on, hold on.
One go in there?
There's one right there.
One went in there.
[  %%  ]
Oh, oh, oh. Good dog.
Wait, wait.
Ooh, ooh. All right.
Hold on! Here we go!
I got one! Okay, no,
no, no. C'mere, c'mere.
Hey, hey, hey! Here's
another over there.
There's one down
here, too. Look out.
Get this one over here!
I got them. I got them. Okay.
Wait, wait! One, two, three!
Where's the other?
The implantation of
the device,
As you know is accomplished
through the aorta
With the aid
of a small camera....
...Inserted simultaneously
through the chest cavity.
The pacemaker leads
are then threaded
Through the veins which lead
back to the heart.
These leads employ another
breakthrough in technology.
Now, as you can see, the uh,
implantation is very...
...Smooth and quick.
Now here you can see the
dramatic change
That's been documented in this
patient in just two days.
As you'll note, the patient, a
man in his uh, late...
...Sixties, has completely
transformed his um,
physical appearance.
Can there be a more
magnificent sight for
a surgeon than this?
As the venerable saying
goes, make sure...
Jeez Louise! What
are you doing in here?
...As you can see, this one
really tells the tale.
Thank you.
(clapping)
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Oh, don't be. She's wonderful.
But what is she doing here?
Uh, exercise.
You exercise dogs in the
hospital?
No...They exercise me.
Is this that dog
that little boy,
Charley, was telling
me about?
I sure hope not, ma'am.
Oh. Oh. Can she come
back and visit me?
I don't-I don't
think so, ma'am.
I'm sorry for
the disturbance.
Bye. Bye, Annie.
Good girl. Good girl.
There we go.
(sigh)
Hello? Animal control?
Hi, this is Leeza Madison at the
Cleveland clinic.
We have a-a-a
situation here,
And I need for you to send one
of your officers over as soon as
possible.
Yes, that would be
fine. Thank you.
What a day.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Aldrich,
but I have no choice.
You can pick up your
severance pay at the
cashier's office
When you deliver your keys and
your security card.
Why didn't you tell me
when I gave you the Chance?
It's a long story, ma'am.
I have the time.
But I don't, do I?
Ma'am.
Dr. Elliot.
Ooh, hey!
Didn't expect to see you.
Doc, did you get
my message about Annie?
Yeah, I did. Didn't
you get mine?
No.
Oh.
What?
She's gone. Uh, I had-I had a
visitor a few days ago, let a
bunch of my animals out.
Kidnapped?
Mm, more like a jailbreak.
Animal rights activists?
It's hard to say.
Charley's gonna be heartbroken.
I'm sorry.
No, uh-ac-actually, it's
something else. Um, you
know a Tom Donaldson?
Yeah, sure, he's
a good friend of mine.
Well, then you knew
he had a heart bypass.
Yeah.
Well he's made
a remarkable recovery.
That's not a surprise. He
is a tough old bird.
Yeah, yeah, but he claims it was
because a mysterious animal paid
him a visit.
Zoo medicine.
What?
That's what they call
it sometimes when-when
animals are used, uh,
For recovery therapy
Yeah, it's-it's uh, it's kinda
like a placebo effect.
You know, the patient
thinks it's the animal,
but really, it's them.
Mm, like a positive attitude.
This really works?
...You'd be surprised.
I already am. What do
you know about it?
Well, a lot. Here, come
on in the office. I'll
show you some stuff.
What are you doing?
Hey, kid.
Funny thing. I had
another one of my migraines.
I picked up the
puppies and now it's gone.
Maybe you were right.
What are you doing
with the puppies?
My job animal
control, remember?
You can't take them.
I got no choice in the matter.
What's gonna happen?
I'm sorry.
I done what I could, charley.
What happened?
Well I told you, we just
couldn't keep 'em that long.
Did someone say something?
No.
They just ... Ran out. They were
waitin' for me when I opened the
door
And...
Where you going, C.W.?
Oh, it's about time
I got me another job.
This one's wearin' me out.
They fired you?
Yeah.
It's okay. It's no big deal.
You take care of
yourself now, you hear?
Hi.
How was your day?
You have to give
him his job back.
Who?
C.W.
Why?
Because he wasn't the
one who had the puppies
in the basement.
I did.
You did?
All by yourself?
Why did you do that?
Because they would
have put the
puppies to sleep!
I had to save
Annie's puppies!
I was gonna try to
give them all homes...
...But now they're
all gonna die.
Annie, Max and the puppies.
Well?
How would you feel about
moving back to Denver?
They didn't fire
you, did they?
Uh ... Well...
All right,
that does it. I quit.
The-the Grant, everything.
Well, you don't have to
worry about the Grant.
There is no Grant. They
took it away.
They didn't even
talk to me!
Well, it wasn't
the clinic.
The clinic wanted us to
stay, and the board
really wanted us to stay.
They did?
Yes, they did! It was Dr.
Ecklin. He refused to give Mr.
Aldrich back his job.
So ... I quit.
I had to. It was a matter of
principle. I'm so sorry.
Nah, it's okay. Look ... I'm
still a pediatrician.
I know we were
counting on the Grant,
But I can still practice.
No it's a-it's a black Mark
on your record and I'm sorry.
Aah!
Black, blue, it doesn't
matter what color it is.
We're together.
I never liked
you working, anyway.
I love you, doctor.
Umm, good.
What are you doing?
You can't do that!
You can't throw
your research away!
Sure, I can.
No, you can't!
You'll need it!
No, I won't. I got you.
Oh!
Hey.
Have you seen Dr. Logan?
He's gone.
Oh, I just wanted to
tell him something. I'll
give him a call later.
You can't. Dr. Logan and his
wife were let go this morning.
What?
It's true. Andy, he's-
He's already gone. Andy?
Here, sweetie, I'll take it.
Charley ... I'm so sorry.
I tried to call the
county, but it was too late.
I'll get him a dog when we
get back to Denver.
Somehow, I don't think
it'll be the same.
(cell phone rings)
Hello.
No. We were just--
now? Okay.
Who was that?
It was Andy. He wants us
to come by the ballpark.
Why?
To say good-bye, I guess.
Good thing you called.
We were just on our
way outta here.
I just wanted
to say good-bye.
And to you, Mrs. Logan.
Take care, Andy.
Good luck, Dr. Malone.
You're going to
make a fine GP.
You think?
Yeah.
There's actually someone else
who wanted to say good-bye.
Hi. I just wanted to
say thank you to charley.
Come on and give
me a hug, charley.
Here. Come on.
You changed my
life, charley.
It wasn't me.
Sure it was.
No, it was Annie.
And the puppies.
You're not going to
leave without thanking
her, are you?
What?
She deserves some
thanks, too.
Oh, you guys, come here!
(to Kelly) but I
thought they were-
No...
...Dr. Elliot went and
got them himself.
He did?
After you told him
about the recoveries
And your research,
he went down
the very next day.
He kept one of the
puppies, charley. John.
Great!
Uh, I never showed
him my research.
I know.
There's one more
stop you need to make.
Ah, come in, doctor Logan.
I believe this is yours.
Yes.
I showed it to Dr. Ecklin ...
And he agrees with me
That it's-it's remarkable...
.And should be
implemented in the clinic.
He does?
Mm-hm. Isn't that
right ... Nate?
Yes it is...
...Aunt Katherine.
Um...
...I threw this away.
Oh, I know. Dr. Malone
retrieved it and
brought it to me.
You see, it's really quite
remarkable research.
Isn't it, Nate?
Dr. Logan, um, I was wrong.
The clinic would like to have
both you and your wife resume
your duties immediately.
Uh, that is, uh, if you'll
accept my apology.
And...
And I've reinstated Mr.
Aldrich, as well.
The truth is, the clinic never
wanted you to leave.
They informed me
of the decision,
Which it seems Nate
had made on his own,
And since...I'm the largest
donor to the clinic,
Without whom this
wing would not exist,
I persuaded Nate to reconsider.
Didn't I, Nate?
Yes.
And what's more...He's also
instituting a zoo medicine
Facility right here
in this wing.
Isn't that wonderful?
It's uh, unbelievable,
is what it is.
Uh, if you'll excuse me?
Now..Where is
that son of yours?
Um, he's outside in the hall,
waiting with his mother.
Well would you mind asking
him to step in here?
No, not at all. And ... Thank
you, Mrs. Mannion.
Uh-uh. Thank you, Dr. Logan.
Here comes your dad.
Uh, she wants to
talk to you, charley.
Me?
Our charley?
Yep. And guess what?
Mr. Aldrich got his job back.
He did?
Yeah.
Oh, that's great!
(to charley)
okay, go on, son.
Go talk to her.
Now ... What's goin' on?
It looks like we're
not going back to
Denver after all.
We're not?
No. We've been
reinstated, too.
We have?
Effective immediately.
Oh, well ... I don't know if
I want to be reinstated.
Why?
Well...
I was thinking about
what you said, about ...
Sometimes a mom should be at
home, and I think maybe this mom
should be at home now.
It would be the right time for
this mom to be at home, maybe.
You feeling all right?
Oh, yeah, never better,
but I'm hungry.
We just had
breakfast an hour ago.
I know.
And you're hungry.
Mm-hm, very hungry.
For something like...Um,
ice cream.
Ice cream?
Um, and...Pickles.
And pi ... Pickles.
Pickles.
Bingo!
Hi.
Oh, charley. Listen, there's one
thing I want from you.
What?
I want that puppy you brought
by to see me, Lopez.
Sure!
Charley, thank you!
Thank you for everything
It was the dogs. They're
special.
No, they're...Miraculous.
Thanks for giving
C.W. His job back.
Oh, don't mention it.
When can you
come home again?
Next week. The
cancer's in remission.
Where's that?
Well, it's-it's a
very wonderful place.
Well...Then I'm glad.
Yeah, me, too. Will you
promise to bring
Annie by to see me?
I will.
Promise.
Here he comes.
Come on.
Dad, wait! Wait!
It was so nice of charley
to give us Jennifer.
Yeah, but I think
our little friend
Charley gave us a lot
more than just Jennifer.
Well, ain't you the one?
I didn't expect to
see you around here.
Heard you got your
job back. I'm glad.
Yeah, I got lucky.
I just wanted to stop
by and say thanks.
For what?
You know, for not
saying anything about
me and the dogs.
Oh, I'd have done
the same for anybody.
My mom says you
were protecting me.
Well, mom says a
lot of things.
Truth is, I
was protecting myself.
I can't let people think I'm
gettin' soft.
Hang on a second.
Where you goin'?
What in tarnation! You
want me to get fired
all over again?
You know, he looks
just like you.
Got a runny nose
and his-his
tail's always waggin'.
He's yours.
He's mine? Wh-...
Bye.
Charley!
Oh, whoa...
Oh, no, no... He's not
even housebroke,uh ...
You see this? You
gotta use this now,
Elton. You got to
use that paper.
Huh?
What you say, boy? Oh, your
breath is worse than mine is.
That's sayin' a lot, huh?
I can tell you're nothin'
but trouble, huh? Are you
one of those Miracle dogs?
Well, with you around, it's a
Miracle I don't drown, huh? Hey,
little buddy!
[  %%  ]
Master Charles, come
over here. Yes.
Uh, hi. What are
you doing here?
Well, master Charles.
How are you?
You?
You, my boy. Miss
Katherine asked me
to fetch you.
Fetch me?
Yes, and your friends.
What for?
A surprise.
Oh, cool! I'll
go get the guys!
Before you do there's
just one other thing.
What?
Do you remember the day you took
the shortcut through Mrs.
Mannion's mansion?
Yeah.
Hm, well, I wanted
to thank you personally.
I didn't get a
Chance at the hospital.
What for?
For changing my
life, charley.
Oh, don't thank me. It was
Annie and her puppies.
They're the Miracle dogs.
Well, I would consider
it an honor if you would
take that shortcut
Whenever you please.
On one condition.
What?
That you stop by
and say hello to miss
Katherine and I
every so often.
Sure. I'd like that.
So would we. Go on,
call your friends.
And the dogs. We have a
surprise for them, as well.
You're full of
surprises, aren't you?
You know, miss Katherine
says that very thing.
How would you like to go
to a major league game?
Today?
This very moment!
After one brief
stop. Go on, go on!
Call your friends!
Okay.
[  %%  ]
Whoa!
Whoa, see that?
You guys are
really famous now!
[  %%  ]
---the end---