- [Bell Sounding]
- [Crowd Cheering]
[Man]
"I'm in with Hancox, the trainers."
That's what he said, right?
Look, Ray,
he got me by the elbow.
See, Ray?
Messing about...
movir the flesh about on it.
I was just goir in. I had my three
and six ready when he come up to me.
"I'm in with Hancox, the trainers,
and I'll give you two.
Two for the third race.
Come on. You'll just make it."
So I pulled out...
this inordinately large sum of money...
which he immediately grabbed, you see,
Ray, and he'd give me two...
Hermosa of Selsdon as number one
and Polish Otto.
Hermosa of Selsdon, Ray.
"Do it on the tote," he said.
"Do it on the forecast."
So I went in and I shelled out
10 shillings on Hermosa of Selsdon...
and the other dog, right?
I come back outside again
to see how the bettir was goir.
Hermosa of Selsdon is 10-1.
Ray, I don't know why...
this guy instilled faith in me, Ray.
I don't know why.
Anyway, the fanfares blew.
They brought them out.
This fellow I went with said,
"There's yours.
There's your dog... Hermosa of Selsdon."
So I looked at him. I swear to God, Ray,
I looked back again...
they lengthened to fourteens.
I thought, "Everyone has gone mad."
I said...
"Everyone has gone mad!"
Then you won't believe it.
Ray, I'm watching the dog, right...
and they're marchir it
around and back again.
And just as they're about
to put the dog in its trap...
he stops dead in his tracks.
He tightens up, shivers,
lowers his little ass...
and has the mother and father
of all dumps right there.
Dog was 52 pounds as it was. After that lot
shot through his glory hole, he was nearer 40.
- Wort make much difference.
- Of course it does.
Ray, that's how to catch out
those eggs in the ring.
Ray, they got their backs
to the dogs and the dogs' psychology.
Anyway, the bell goes off.
The hare comes shootir out,
sets off the trap.
- Some bloody egg behind me shouts,
"They're off!"
- I know.
I'll cut it short for you, Ray.
It was the dog Mystic Nora all the way.
Hermosa of Selsdon wasrt even in it.
Nowhere! Dead out!
I just stared, Ray.
Ray, I just stared.
Then you won't believe this, Ray.
When they went down to the track
to take the dog back...
it didn't wanna go.
It didn't want to go.
That's what really got me, Ray.
I wanted to go down there
and kick it to death, Ray.
I saw that dog
for what it really was...
nothing but a dirty little whippet.
Dachshund on stilts,
filthy little fart...
with a horsehair shirt
to stop it from gassir everyone.
Yes.
I usually don't bother
with the forecast, actually.
Usually double up on the favorites.
Very fair last Thursday,
as a matter of fact, Graham.
I used to do the Duella pools
sometimes on the off chance...
but they closed 'em down
for the forecast betting.
I'm talking about last Saturday
at Wandswon'th, Ray.
We're just leavir, right...
when this fellow I went with...
says to me,
"What you gonna do about it?"
I said, "About what?"
He said, "About the guy
who gave you the dog."
Ray, I'd completely
forgotten about him.
So we go back up the stands
into the bar.
There's the guy give us the dog.
He's sittir there with his back to us.
This fellow I went with, Ray, he's a bloody
egg, in fact. You know what he did?
He takes a lit cigarette.
He walks up right behind the guy...
and he burns a hole right in
the back of his jacket, just like that.
Then he taps him on the shoulder
and says, "Hello."
The guys turns around, right?
He don't recognize us at first,
but then he does.
He says, "Oh, hello, boys.
Hello, hello. Have a drink."
The fellow I went with, Ray...
Jimmy... he says...
"Two double scotches."
And he gets 'em.
He gets 'em.
And then this guy I went with...
he grabs him and he says...
"I wonder if you could help me.
"I'm interested in recoupir
certain losses made recently...
"in an ill-advised venture.
"And I got with me here
this tin ofbandages...
"which I'm willir to sell.
"Matter of fact,
I'll sell it so cheap...
it would be a pleasure
to cut yourself."
- Heard that before. Huh.
- Anyway...
this half-hard idiot
that give us the dog...
he gradually catches on
that he's being threatened...
and he shoots off his mouth.
We get thrown out.
They wouldn't let us back in.
Oh, well, you had a good day.
You shouldn't let it worry you.
Graham, you remember that time
I was barred from the queer pub...
in Earl's Court for adjustir
the vertical hold on the television set?
Yes, Ray.
That was ironical, wasrt it?
Barred from a queer pub for
adjustir the vertical hold.
Yes.
Why don't you go unravel in the bath?
You're startir to sound like Auntie Daisy,
you are, pushir out the dirt.
Bloody dog!
Bloody little animal!
- Oh, forget it.
- I have forgotten it.
And you've forgotten about
forgettir it as well.
Oh, yes.
Yes! Yes.
Yes.
- I don't know.
- What?
You don't know what?
Got out of bed on the wrong side.
- It must have done.
- I did.
Oh, did you?
Right, then.
Right.
Sharon should come around.
- Bringing any food?
- I didn't ask her to. I didn't give her any money.
I never pay for sex, Ray.
That's 'causeJesus Christ
paid for our sins.
That's got nothing to do with it.
I like her, Ray.
I like her very much.
Let's give her a miss.
Let's go up the West End.
Right, then.
What's the name of that place
you got thrown out of? Let's go there.
The Earl of Strathmore... Strathcona.
That's in Earl's Court.
Oh!
Close the bloody window.
"With railers drawn on the outside...
"and wide runners on the inside...
"tonight's heats of the Ben Truman Stakes
at New Cross...
"present a really
difficult assignment for punters...
"and I would not be
at all surprised...
"to see more than
a couple of shocks...
before the six for
Saturday's finals are known."
What they wanna do that for?
Balingaddy runs wide.
They should shove her on the outside.
That's a very pacy little hound.
Clocked 28:06 solo last Monday.
Remember? Why ain't they written it up?
Here.
"She is also no stranger
to New Cross...
"having won over
the course and distance.
"And connections were wise to renew
her associations with the circuit...
by giving her
a 500-yard spin on Monday."
She'll be on big offer.
She won't be on a big offer at all.
What'd you say that for?
She got Miss Vanilla
and Spring Guest against her.
Half an hour's boredom and agony
for a few seconds' pleasure.
- Ha.
- If Sharon were here, she would say...
"That's like a lot of things, Ray,"
and leer at you.
I spared you that.
How bothered was I
about being spared it?
- I don't know. It's all on the cards.
- I don't see it.
It don't matter.
I'm not goir that far with you.
[Chattering, Indistinct]
You got Country.
You got...
[Indistinct]
No? You got Taste.
[Man]
They're not for perusing, those magazines.
"Wedding bells for Mervin Gloyer."
He'll marry the Queen Mother
before that bitch.
I've seen him in action once.
- Witchery Snow.
- Oh?
That's who.
I talked with him.
- Did you?
- He asked for you.
- Speak about me, did he?
- I said they're not for perusing, those.
Is there a voice in back of me?
How's your wife and my three babies?
Gettir fat?
Fame is the first disgrace.
Why? Man wants to know
why fame is the first disgrace, Ray.
Why, everyone knows that.
Because God knows who you are.
God knows who you are.
[People On Film, Indistinct]
I remember comir out
of the pictures once with a fellow.
And we walked the whole way...
to Holborn Viaduct.
He didn't say a word.
Finally, he turns to me and says...
"Those Italians really know
what life's about."
I could've kicked him in the crotch.
The last time I went
to the pictures with you...
you said you went
with some American.
And after you came out,
he said...
"Some very poignant songs
have come from the mines."
I could've cut his balls off too.
I remembered you sayir that.
Came from Pittsburgh, huh?
I remember that.
- There aren't any bloody mines in Pittsburgh.
- No, not in Pittsburgh, Ray.
No, no.
But as far as I remember, Ray...
Pittsburgh is the center of
the mining district in Pennsylvania.
I forced that out of him.
Let's go have a drink.
- My nerves are bloody wound up.
- I could drink you under a table.
- Have to be a small table.
- You're gettir very kittenish.
- Huh?
Let's go have a drink, Ray.
Where's the nearest pub you got
thrown out of? Let's go there.
We passed it.
- Which one was that?
- Strathmore Arms.
The barman came up to me and said,
"You'll have to go.
I'm sorry.
You'll have to go."
- Why?
- "You're always reading.
You bore the customers."
"You're always reading.
- Huh.
- Let's go there.
Hello, there.
How's it goir? All right?
- Hello.
- Who was that? Are you playing your game?
[Graham]
That turned him over.
Let him cook on the other side.
Didrt look that sort to me.
For a start, he was cut to pieces
and reeling about the street.
You could've pissed in his face
and watched it evaporate.
Right. You don't
believe me then, Ray?
Turn around.
We'll catch him up.
Come on.
- Hello, there.
- Huh?
Hey. How's it goir?
- You're notJoseph at all.
- There you go.
I seen you, haven't I?
Catford Dog Track.
Why, you're notJoseph at all.
Get out of me fucking way.!
Huh? Don't you touch me!
I have every right
to walk up and down here...
without you bloody fucking
drug addicts comir up to me!
You know what Winston Churchill
said about dogs?
He said they were animated roulette.
He had all the wit in the world.
That'll keep you thinkir for a bit.
And what'd you come up to me for?
Why don't you just
walk about the streets...
with rays coming out of your eyes...
lies coming out of the tips
of your fingers.
That's what you're at.
You damn well go away.
What a naughty little man, Ray.
He's tryir to break the rules.
Huh? You might have been a fellow
give me a tip last week.
- Excuse me?
- I might wanna thank you for it,
or kick you to death.
- Hermosa of Selsdon at 20-1.
- What are you talking about, Graham?
Hermosa of Selsdon at 20-1.
Well, I want no thanks from you.!
And when I wanna thank you
for something, I shart!
Damn well go away.
Bloody split-arse.
Ruining the bloody streets.
- Get out!
- Hermosa of Selsdon at 20-1.
[Whooping]
[Whooping Continues]
Hermosa of Selsdon at 20-1!
Whee!
Hermosa of Selsdon...
at 20-1!
[Whooping]
If you say "You see what I mean?"
I think I'll go quietly mad.
Look, next time,
you go along with me.
You bloody go along with me, Ray.
- The dog didn't win.
- Oh, God, Ray, I give up.
Go along with me!
You bloody go along with me!
He was shakir all over.
It's all very well, your sayir
you're gonna go quietly mad...
if I say,
"You see what I mean."
Poor, old bastard. For all you know,
his wife might've just died.
- He might've been laid off or somethir.
- Oh, God, Ray.
"Laid off."
You see what I mean?
I'll fuckir well say it now.
What?
[Chattering]
How much thought did you give it?
What?
- Hermosa of Selsdon.
- Oh.
I didn't pay much attention to it.
I had Fairlands Mandy
and Matson Wonder.
Fairlands Mandy can catch pigeons.
That wasrt very adventurous of you,
was it?
One of the selections said
Hermosa of Selsdon...
would be a back marker
most of the way.
- That's a bloody lie.
- It was in Thursday's Greyhound.
It was?
I've got the cutting here.
Here.
You find it, Ray.
Go ahead.
You bloody find it then.
- What's that?
- It's the Weekender.
"How would you spend your last hour?
"Weekender asked 16 famous people
what they would do...
"given the choice
as the seconds ticked away.
Sixty minutes to live."
- What would you do?
- I'd read the bloody thing.
If I said I was gonna read it,
I'd read the bloody thing.
"One hour to live.
Sixty minutes...
"left on the Earth
to wind up the account.
"Many men have faced up to it.
Some bravely, some with a whimper.
"It is about the most profound subject
a human being can think about.
"But it is only when people stop talking
about those vital 60 minutes...
"that the infinite variety
of views emerges.
"Would you pray?
Would you cry?
Would you leave with a smile?"
- What's it say about the dog?
- I think it's interesting.
"The future prospects
of personal pets...
"will be the first concern
of writer Beverly Nichols.
"'I would ask Gaskin, my manservant...
"'to take care of my three cats...
Anthony Trollope and Five."'
That's only two, Graham.
That's only two cats.
That's the price you have to pay,
isn't it?
It's three, you silly cunt.
Anthony, Trollope and Five.
Three.
"'I would then give Gaskin
the time off...
"'and I would play some records...
Rachmaninov's 18th Variation
on a theme by..."'
You've read it then?
- I've read it, sure.
- What are you going on about?
- Why can't I read it?
- I don't care. Bloody read it.
- All right.
- I couldn't give a bugger what you do.
As a matter of fact, there are
a lot of people you follow in here.
Anna Massey, David Frost...
the Duke of Bedford...
Lesley-Anne Down.
"What would be the last fling
of socialite Mrs. Bunty Kinsman?
"A parachute jump over
the Sussex Downs...
to buy two gorgeous dresses
from Balenciaga."
I'm just picking out
the funny ones, Graham, for a laugh.
Right.
Didrt you say you met her?
Let's go, Ray.
Let's go down the road.
Come on.
I didn't read you out
the best one, Graham.
"Barbara Can'tland,
the famous novelist, she said..."
Look, you can go back home to that
old cow of yours if you like, you know.
You don't have to come along with me.
What with her mange
and your socks...
you'll have to open the fuckir window!
And the next time,
you go along with me.
You can go home if you like. If she's not there,
go have a row with yourself in the toilet.
Go unravel in the bath.
I don't care.
I tell you, I don't care.
I don't.
No, I just thought...
I mean, I like
going out with you, Graham.
Yes.
Yes, Ray.
You. It's all right with you, Graham.
You're right, Ray.
You're quite right.
Oh, yes.
Listen to this prick.
"Hermosa of Selsdon...
"has more than an average
turn of early foot...
"and from a favorable draw...
"may well reach
the first bend in front.
"Should sweep away into the lead...
"and career away
for what could well be...
"the most decisive winning
margin of the evening.
"Great Gusto should outstay
all but the selection...
Hermosa of Selsdon. "
Now, they got the nerve
to bring that dog up again.
We've seen that bloody hound.
Seen that bloody hound.
"Favored by having trap three vacant."
Wouldrt make a difference
if they're all bloody vacant.
We've seen that bastard dog.
Isn't that him?
That one?
Who?
Wouldrt make a difference if they're all
fucking vacant. Who? What's the time?
One of those people you follow.
There. No... See there?
No, there, there.
There. There he is.
You see there? There.
Yes, yes, yes.
No. It's not him.
It's another one.
I know who you mean.
I know who he is.
Let's go chat him up.
Yes, Ray.
Whatever for, Ray?
Well, you know.
Next time you see him...
you can say to yourself,
you know...
that you and me, we chatted him up
and how it went or something.
I don't know why
you follow these people.
They follow me.
Coming along with me, are you?
- Hmm?
- Well, yes. Yes.
Yes, Graham.
You're beir a bit kittenish.
Hmm?
Graham.
Excuse me.
I would just like to say...
that I admired greatly...
the way you extricated yourself...
from that dirty little bitch
on the train to Santa Fe.
Oh, yes. Yes.
You-You-You saw that, did you?
Y-Yes, yes.
Yeah, my friend and I, we happened
to spot you over here in the corner...
and we just thought, you know,
we would just come over...
to let you know
we were on your side.
Oh, yes.
Well, uh, thank you.
You know,
they're releasing that again...
- Oh!
- As a matter of fact.
I was very pleased about that.
I suppose you'd be...
Oh, no. We'll be there.
Oh, no.
Oh, definitely, we'll be there.
Oh.
Yes, I thought it was fairly
well buried... that one.
- I must say, it is nice that you should...
- Oh, no.
We're great admirers of yours, David.
Great admirers.
You know, when we first saw you...
oh, you had a part in Oklahoma...
at Hastings five years ago.
Right? There are not many people come up
to you and tell you that, huh, David?
No. Oh, yes, yes, I remember.
I remember that well.
The local newspaper said...
it was a once-in-a-lifetime
clinch with gaiety.
That's a giggle, huh, Ray?
Can I get you a drink?
Yes. Well, yes.
Campari. Thank you.
I'll get It, Ray. 'Cause I don't want
to rush you off your feet.
Campari.
That's port and lemon in disguise.
You're sewn up, aren't you?
Can I have a Campari?
Glass of scotch and a glass of tonic
with a slice oflemon.
Dave? You heard the oldjoke.
Hey, she been...
she been taken up, huh?
That dirty little bitch
on the train to Santa Fe?
Oh-Oh, yes. Oh, ye-yes. Yes.
She's been... Yes, thank you.
She's been, um...
- Yes, she's been taken up in a big way.
- Yeah?
Oh, yes. Yes.
Cheers. Thank you.
This recent one
you been working on, David...
- This recent one...
- Mm-hmm?
What's the director like
to work with?
- Oh, you-you've been reading
about that one, have you?
- Yes.
Well, it is very difficult work...
to begin with, but I've found...
that the only way to avoid
a direct clash...
personalities... was to, um...
well, almost...
the exact opposite
to what he wanted.
I mean, not quite the exact opposite,
you see.
Do you see what I mean?
But almost the exact opposite.
And then, you see,
he-he knew...
that you werert kowtowing
to him like everybody else...
and at the same time,
you werert sort of...
you know,
playing the game of doing...
the exact opposite...
in order to show that you were obviously,
as it were, standing... -
uh, standing up to him.
- You see, it's very...
- Brilliant, David.
That is absolutely brilliant.
- Ohh...
- Ray? Huh?
Yes. Very, very clever.
It's funny you should talk about
that film, because you know what?
Ray and I were talking
about that very film just before.
- Yeah?
- And he bet me...
you really lived it up there, David.
Oh, yes, yes.
Well, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Well, no, no, no.
No, no.
It's not, um...
- It's not what you'd imagine at all, really.
- Oh, no, no, no.
We've got no illusions about it, David.
No illusions at all.
No, I can imagine what...
just what it's like, you know.
I saw you rehearsing the other day.
Hammersmith. Some hall there.
- Oh, really?
- I often pass that place on my way to the dogs.
- You know, do you go to...
Do you go to the dogs at all?
- No.
No, I don't.
L-l-I, uh...
Well, l-I never have the time.
I'd lose, I suppose.
Somebody was saying something
about greyhound racing...
the other day.
Some remark.
No, no. No, no. I was...
I was reading it.
"Animated roulette."
Winston Churchill.
Animated roulette.
No, I don't...
I don't follow it, really.
Graham follows it.
Yes.
Yes, well, I'll, um...
I'll be with you in a minute.
[Groans]
Just going downstairs to, uh...
to shake the icicles off.
- Huh? [Chuckles]
- Oh.
Gone downstairs, Graham.
See a man about a dog.
Huh.
Coming along with me, are you?
You gonna hedge your bets?
No. No.
It's like you say, Graham.
It's just like you say.
The old black magic.
[Footsteps Approaching]
Who's the third man
who walks beside you?
Hello.
What?
Knock 'em back, don't you, David?
I bet your liver goes on living
long after you're dead.
Right? You'll have to hire a couple
of guys like us to beat it to death.
What about coming
down the road with us?
Place we know.
Oh, no, no, no.
I have to get back. I really...
I really must get back.
I'm very, very, um...
very, very tired.
- Oh, well, we'll walk along with you.
- Oh. Very well.
You know, David,
you haven't let us introduce ourselves.
My name is Graham, David...
and this is my very good friend here,
Ray Summers.
- How do you do?
- Hello.
Do you mind at all being
recognized by strangers?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's just part of the old, uh...
Well, they, uh...
They usually get my name wrong...
and then they get embarrassed
and walk away.
No, it doesn't... It doesn't, um...
doesn't take much out of you.
You know, I expect a lot of'em
must come up to you...
ask you for your autograph,
then say it's for their small son...
their niece, someone you've never
heard of just to cover up, huh?
- Yes.
- Can I have your autograph?
- It's funny you should...
- It's for Ray.
[Chuckling]
You've got one of those pens
that writes underwater.
What?
I never knew that.
Oh, well. Came in handy to play
the Duke of, um... the Duke of Clarence with.
Oh, they wouldn't let you.
He was Jewish.
You know there were 50,000
SephardicJews in London in 1066?
They all got to the top,
then nobody knew who they were.
There were 20,000 Negroes
in England in the early 1800s.
- Nobody knows where they are. Ray's Jewish.
- Oh, yeah?
He had to have it cut off.
I bloody wore it off.
- [Chuckling]
- Stop laughing.
You sound like a clam goir mad.
Yes, well, um...
Yes, well, perhaps, um...
Perhaps I shall run across you again.
Run across us again?
David.
You'd have to run very fast.
Very fast, indeed.
Don't you live in Knightsbridge now?
I was readiryour house
in Chiswick is up for sale.
- Property column.
- Oh, were you?
You're very funny to me, David.
What do you mean,
I don't live up to the old, uh...
No, no, no, no!
You got it all wrong!
And even if that were the case,
we'd forgive you.
Wouldrt we, Ray?
Huh? You're very, very tired.
But you sell yourself so cheap.
Don't defend yourself.
You've got to put yourself out a bit.
They'll defend you as much
as they can, David...
but when it comes to crucial issues,
you're out on your own.
You haven't done half of it.
Well, let's leave that for a bit.
Right?
Turn to the more rational side.
How would you assess
his physical condition and stature...
in a few words, Ray, for guidance?
Well, I'd say about six feet...
thirteen stone, well covered.
Fairly good working order,
I should think.
Said you were
very approachable, David?
Kick him in the stomach,
get him on the ground...
put your handkerchief in his mouth,
kick him again, we see what follows.
[Grunting]
All right, David.
Now.
Okay.
Let's put it another way for you.
It's the simplest thing
in the world once you grasp it.
Now, you take Ray, for example.
This girl he's shacked up with... Sharon...
she thinks he's you.
And when they're in their bed,
David, he thinks he's you...
and she thinks she's being done by you.
Well, it's not quite as simple as all that.
Kick him again. Go ahead.
It's got nothing to do with resenting you.
Nothing at all.
It's just that it seems stupid...
you're not there with Sharon and Ray
to defend yourself.
I think he's ready now, Ray.
Have his face done.
[Muffled Groaning]
What's that on the left-hand
side of his face, Ray?
- What's that? A birthmark?
- No, I just did that.
Wasrt I gonna tell you a story?
Listen. Listen.
This man and wife go into a pub...
and the man says to the barman,
"I'll have a Guinness,"
and the barman says with a wink...
"That'll put lead in your pencil."
"I can't write," the man says...
saving his wink for another time.
As a matter of fact,
I've swindled you, David.
I usually like to tell that story
at the beginning to ingratiate myself...
but I thought I'd keep it
till the end with you...
out of pure selfishness.
I like to give my stories
a good airing.
This one's off the record,
mind you, but...
what keeps an old Englishman happy?
Tell him a joke when he's young.
See what he's got
in the bottom drawer, Ray.
We don't want him to be typecast.
[Muffled Groaning]
I'm surprised at myself, David.
Giving you this publicity.
Touch you.
I wouldn't touch you
with a sanitary towel.
Where was it, Ray?
Monmouth Street.
That's it.
You had a beautiful woman
with you then, David.
Beautiful buttocks she had. Mmm!
I think it was your wife, Ella.
She was slightly pregnant at the time.
Nineteen thousand men
were having blood tests.
Beautiful buttocks she had. I watched one,
going like a fiddler's elbow.
Then I lost track of it,
watched the other.
Backs of her knees...
almost edible, David.
I was with a friend
of mine from my office.
I watched him come
without trimming the candle.
But as we were walking
in your direction...
this friend of mine,
he recognized you.
But he looked away.
See, David? He looked away.
"I'm not gonna give myself away," see?
That's what he was thinking.
I'm not gonna give myself away.
Oh, I can ask you now, David,
what danger was there of that?
Huh? You wouldn't have
remembered him...
even if he'd given
himself away, would you?
But what he didn't know...
what he didn't realize...
was the reason
he wasrt looking at you...
is 'cause you're a dirty leper.
You're a hideous, hideous cripple.
It is extremely rude
to stare at hideous cripples.
I don't see any blood, Ray.
This.
A little daylight through his cheek.
Wait.
Glamorous, Ray.
It's too glamorous.
- No, no, no, Graham.
- No?
I don't want to leave any false trails.
I don't want to leave it screaming.
Let it sweat.
How do you feel?
I feel quite enthusiastic.
Go ahead, then.
We'll have to make
some concessions.
Don't want them to think
it was sleeping tablets.
- That little number.
- He'll have a new number.
Graham.
Ray.
That's all for now, David...
except for a few cheap,
ironical statements...
such as, "Thank you...
for having spared us the time,"
and "We'll be in touch with you."
I expect you're familiar with those.
Ray.
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Clock Chiming]
I met that fellow the other day.
Who?
The...
You know.
You met him?
I walked past him.
He didn't recognize me.
He didn't recognize you?
Well, he's got a nerve.
Not recognizing you, Ray...
that takes the bloody biscuits.
- Was he looking at you?
- He looked at me, and then he looked away.
Well, he recognized you, then.
No. No.
That was a bit of a moody, Ray.
Made the game simple for him
so he could understand it...
and he blatantly chooses
to ignore the rules.
[Sighs] Well, you know,
he might have thought we were jealous.
All that gone to waste.
Huh?
Yeah.
No, I don't think...
No. He's not as stupid as that, Ray.
It was double bluff.
Double bluff.
I don't grudge it him,
all said and done.
He's entitled to do
what he likes, you know.
He's been out of work for six months.
He's probably on the streets now.
Poncing around like a blue-assed fly...
and flogging...
flogging his chops into the bargain.
Poor fellow.
The Salvation Army does a lot for them.
Ray.
Fairlands Mandy.
You chose that, you silly cow.
Give him a ring.
It's ex-directory.
Belgravia six...
one five two seven.
Use your Douglas Fairbanks voice.
Hello. Hello. Is David there?
Hello, David.
Is that you?
Well, we've been
watching your movie.
You know?
Yes. Spellbinding.
I expect you've had your fill, but I wanted to
register it with you before I leave tomorrow.
You put on a great, great show.
"Well, can I know who this is?"
That's the game, kid.
That's the game.
You put your finger on it.
I just wanted to say
what a fine showing.
That's all. Yeah.
No, that's all right.
Yeah. Yeah.
Bye, now.
Tsk. Isn't he slow?
- Oh, it makes you sick.
- Yeah.
You know...
in three years' time...
he's gonna have 10 face-lifts.
Every time he winks,
his legs are gonna jump up in the air.
Belt up, Ray. Belt up.
Go on.
Belt up.
- Sorry.
- That's all right.
What's the selection say?
"Fairlands Mandy. 100-8."
Oh, fat chance.
Their selection, not yours.
- "Polish Otto."
- Otto?
- What's it say about him?
- "Polish Otto...
"traps well and is well placed
for a wide runner.
"If she can lead out from
privately trained Fairlands...
"she should outstay the field.
But she tends to get badly balked..."
I'll take that. Otto.
Bring it with you.
Coming?
- Yes.
- Well, come on, then, Ray.
"Privately trained," Ray.
Huh?
Ray.
- [Bell Ringing]
- [Crowd Cheering]
Epilogue to follow credits
http://www.divx-titlovi.com