( alarm beeping )
♪ You know you can't keep
letting it get you down ♪
♪ And you can't keep dragging
that dead weight around ♪
♪ Is it really all that much
to lug around? ♪
♪ Better run like hell
when you hit the ground ♪
♪ When the morning comes
♪ Can't stop those kids
from dancing ♪
♪ But why would you want to
Uh-oh, ladies, he's here.
♪ Already getting good?
( telephone ringing )
Customer Service,
this is Neal,
how can I help you?
♪ But don't go blaming
the kids again ♪
( alarm beeping )
♪ When the morning comes
What up, Neal-dawg?
( telephone ringing )
Customer service,
this is Neal,
how can I help you?
Whoa! You do not
look good today.
( telephone ringing )
Customer service,
this is Neal,
how can I help you?
♪ When the morning comes
Sir, if you would just
let me finish,
I can tell you that refunds
are only issued when--
Yes, as I was just saying
refunds are only issued
when you--
Sir, I've been trying
to tell you
that for last five minutes.
Oh, well, I'm so sorry
for ruining your day.
God, how terrible
your life must be
if the one thing that goes
wrong is someone telling you
to write a letter
to get a refund.
You know what, sir,
I can safely say that
I would love your problems.
I would kill
for your problems.
I have wet dreams
about your problems.
You see, I'm still reeling
from walking in
on my best friend
and my girlfriend having sex,
okay, and now I wake up
every morning at 7:29,
1 minute before
my alarm is supposed to go off
and it leaves me unsettled
for the entire rest
of the day, okay.
You know what the best thing
that's happened to me,
you know what's the best thing
that's happened to me
in the past few weeks?
I caught my lunch
from falling off of my car.
That's it,
that's the only thing.
Well, that, and the also
a piece of peanut butter bread
fell on a piece
of jelly bread.
Okay, but that's it.
Two things, two things
have gone right for me
in the past few weeks.
So, sir, if you want
your refund,
just write your letter
and shut the fuck up!
( cell phone ringing )
Hello.
I went home.
No, I don't think
I'm gonna be coming back.
All right, bye.
Are you looking
for your booze?
Shit!
Bryce!
Yes.
Wait, are you saying
my name or is that just
the noise you make
when you're all surprised.
No, I'm just saying your name.
Oh, hi.
I'm sorry I scared you,
but I was gonna say
if you are looking
for your booze,
it's not there
because I took it.
Why?
Oh, we were making mojitos
and ran out of rum,
and your door
wasn't that locked.
Do you have any more?
Oh, no, no, no.
No.
After my sex friend left,
me and Zoe finished them.
You and the dog
finished the mojitos?
Yeah. We shared it.
She can't use a straw.
Clearly.
Why, do you like
really need a drink?
No, you know, I'm just at home
in the middle of the day,
in my underwear, because
everything is awesome.
Rock show, dude, I'm glad.
Okay, bye.
Holy shit.
Wine cooler.
WOMAN: ( on answering machine )
Happy birthday, Neal,
it's your mother.
In case you didn't know.
I hope that you are having
a wonderful day,
and that all of your dreams
come true today.
Kisses baby.
Kisses. We love you.
ALLAN: I don't see
what you're so upset about.
Allan, I walked in on you
fucking with my girlfriend.
Was it really that bad?
Yes, it was really that bad.
Look, I know Christine
means a lot to you,
but she means
a lot to me too--
You know what, I don't care.
Why are you naked right now?
I don't know,
it's your dream.
( knocking on door )
( door opens )
Christine.
Oh, my god, Neal.
What are you doing here?
I came to get
the rest of my stuff.
I can come back later.
No, no, no.
You came here
to get your stuff,
I should be okay with that.
Are you?
You could have
given me a heads up first.
Yeah, I could have.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
All right, so what are
you here to pick up?
Oh, I have to get the rest of
my clothes from the bedroom,
the plates in the kitchen,
and the towels.
Oh, and I am really want my
autographed copy of
Three Men and a Baby.
Yeah, that's a big deal.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, you're serious.
Yes.
Okay.
Well, I'll help you
in any way that I can.
You could put
some pants on.
Right.
Let's do that.
Put some pants on.
Fuck!
Are you really gonna
keep that shirt?
What's wrong
with this shirt?
You hate that shirt.
I do not hate this shirt.
I remember when your mom
sent you the shirt.
I believe your
exact words were,
"Hey, look at this
shitty shirt
my mom sent me."
Well, it is a shitty shirt.
It is.
Do you want it?
Yes.
Okay.
Hey, what's this?
What's what?
Oh, no, no, no,
don't open that.
I've been meaning
to return that.
How long
have you had this?
Couple of months.
Neal, why didn't you?
I walked in on you
and Allan fucking.
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I can't.
Because I'm with
someone else, Neal.
That hasn't stopped you
in the past.
I'm going to go.
That's probably a good idea.
Neal, please don't make
this anymore awkward
than it already is--
Can I have the ring back?
Thank you so much
for stopping by!
Neal.
Hey.
Hey, man.
Happy Birthday.
Thanks.
Where's your car?
Um, I walked.
Wow. That's bold.
Where's Christine?
Really?
What?
Darren, we've been broken up
for a few months now.
Really?
Yes.
Well, you must've said
something, come on in, man.
Hey, honey, Neal's here.
I'm not saying come down,
I'm just saying
your brother's here.
JILLIAN:
Well, I'm not coming down.
I'm not asking you to.
JILLIAN: What?
Nothing.
Where are the kids?
Oh, they're at their
grandparents.
Adults only tonight.
Really?
Anything you want to do.
Orgy?
Anything within reason.
Give me $10,000.
No.
$20,000.
and I have given you
three pretty
good suggestions.
Well, comparatively the orgy
would be good,
because I will be
sleeping with your sister.
No, I don't want to have sex
with my sister.
Yeah, I know, only
I get to do that.
You talking about me?
Talking about having sex.
With me?
Yeah, having sex with you.
Damn right you do.
And I love it.
Fantastic.
Yeah.
Happy birthday, bro.
Got you something
for the party.
Aw.
Yeah.
The chicken was great, dear.
Thank you.
Is anyone else
coming to this thing?
Supposedly.
It's no big deal, I just
cooked this amazing meal,
and sent the kids away,
and spent the whole day
cleaning the house but--
Well, the three of us
are having a great time.
Oh, Neal, you know
who I was thinking of?
No.
Do you remember
Professor Henry?
Yeah.
That guy was nuts.
Happy birthday--
Let's just clean up.
Please.
Okay.
DARREN: So Professor Henry
was this crazy old history
professor
He worked in the White House
under Kennedy.
Anyway, he was
giving us this lecture
once on Kissinger.
And this girl raises
her hand and asks him
if he knew Kissinger,
and he goes, "Knew him?
I shat on his chest!"
JILLIAN: Gross.
(Door closes off screen)
Neal?
And I'm like, why would
I fake heartburn.
Holy shit, are you getting
ready to fuck your guitar?
Yeah, do you want us to
come back some other time?
Thanks for coming
to my birthday party.
Was that tonight?
Yes.
Guys, I just sat there,
with my sister and Darren.
Nobody showed up?
Seriously though,
what's with the underwear?
Christine came over.
Holy shit.
Great.
She found the engagement ring.
Holy shit.
Oh, and I quit my job.
Great.
Holy shit.
Can you please
stop doing that?
What happened with Christine?
She kissed me.
So, you're guys
are back together.
No, she said she didn't
want to cheat.
Wait, she cheated.
Yes, and then, I left
Jillian's house
because no one came
to my birthday party.
BARRY: Yeah,
I would hate that.
And so, I'm in my underwear.
BARRY: You're out of beer.
Make yourself at home Barry.
BARRY: Done.
Great.
Okay, so you could probably
use a little cheering up?
From the two guys
who can't even
make it to my party?
Hey, can I drink this?
Well, we have the greatest
birthday gift for you.
Yeah, look, just bear with us,
because
what we're gonna tell you
is going to sound crazy
at first, but trust me,
it is genius.
If I said no, would it
make a difference?
We're gonna to get you back
into the dating game.
No, come on.
No, no, just listen.
What I have in mind
will almost assuredly
get you laid,
and at the very least
will get you a handy.
A hand job?
Really?
Do people still do that?
Yes!
Just fucking
show him, Barry.
A hand job?
No, the thing.
Oh, yeah.
Check this out.
An internet date.
Really?
Shut the fuck up please
and trust me.
Oh, I get it.
Casual encounters.
Great.
Better.
Casual encounters is where
desperate people
who are looking to get
laid meet up.
Those are two desperate people
having meaningless sex.
I mean,
where's the fun in that?
Do I really need to tell you?
No, no, no, I have
something better.
Missed Connections.
See, these people
are beyond desperate.
They're so obsessed
with the idea of making
any sort of human connection,
that they put
all of their faith in destiny,
and they post it out
on the internet.
Like this.
We were driving
northbound on the 5.
I was in a black pick-up,
you were in a red hybrid.
You caught my eye.
I hope to hear from you.
You see.
No.
Dude.
This girl was so turned on,
so aroused by even
the sight of this
fucking guy,
that she goes to a website
where people sell
used couches,
on the off-chance
that the same guy
is going to see
that same website
and write her back.
She's got to know that the odds
of that are a million to one.
But...
what if he actually
did write her back?
She'd probably go insane.
Yep, she probably would.
So you are going
to write her back.
What?
But I'm not the guy.
You're not the guy,
but here's the beauty part.
You don't have to be.
You write her back
as the guy.
You tell her to meet you
somewhere.
That guy's not gonna show up.
You go and you watch
as her disappointment grows.
And then she is at her most
vulnerable, her most exposed.
You walk over to her and say,
"Hey, what's wrong?"
as her new knight
in shining armor.
And she's gonna
take all that emotion,
all that anticipation
and she's gonna
transfer it into you.
Whoa.
I know.
It's crazy, right?
I mean, when girls are
at their absolute lowest point,
they will fuck you.
That's just science.
Wow.
Does this actually work?
I have no idea,
we're gonna find out.
No. But I mean, you know,
it seems like
it would work, right?
I don't know, guys.
I mean, it sounds
really great in theory,
but I don't know
if I could actually do this.
Well, we thought
you might say that,
so we already
set one up for you.
What?
We gotta be there
in like 10 minutes.
No, no, guys.
I don't know anything
about this person.
There's nothing
you need to know
except she saw some guy
in a Prius,
and she wants to fuck.
She doesn't want to fuck.
Girls looking for nice guys
don't post ads
on the internet.
We'll take your car.
Can't.
I left it at work.
Why?
Reminds me of Christine.
Wow. We need
to leave right now.
Okay, look,
just get dressed,
we'll go down there
and check it out,
if you don't like her,
you don't have
to even talk to her.
No. No.
You have to talk to her.
Listen, how much more
pathetic can your day get?
I could embarrass myself
in front of some random,
severely disappointed girl
from the internet.
This is so stupid.
Just relax,
it's gonna work.
How do we even know
which one is her?
There's like
10 or 11 girls here.
That's her.
How do you know?
Let's see, number one,
she reeks of desperation.
Number two,
she's scanning around the room
every 5 seconds
looking for somebody.
Three,
she's milking that drink.
She doesn't want
to order a second drink,
because she knows
that one drink
by yourself in a bar,
that's okay.
Two drinks?
Now you're pushing
on lush or alcoholic.
Four, she's checking
the time constantly.
She's thinking, he's not
that late, but he is.
Five...
Is there a five?
There's no five.
There's no five, okay.
So what, I just--
I just go over?
Not yet.
You gotta wait, man.
You got to wait until
she's just about
to leave, you know.
Till she gets to
that point where she's like,
this was a terrible idea.
I don't why
I'm doing this, I feel silly.
That's when you go over.
Trust in this.
Trust in this?
Yeah.
George, you have a girlfriend.
I know. I don't get to do
cool stuff like this anymore.
Okay. Please.
I need this.
Shit, shit.
This is it.
She's leaving.
NEAL: What, now?
BARRY: Go, yes.
I don't even,
I don't know what to say.
Just go up to her and say,
"Giving up, huh?"
That's it?
Oh, you also
have to say, um,
"Hey, if I was him,
I wouldn't
have stood you up,
because I'm cool."
Don't say the cool part.
Guys, I can't--
I can't do this,
this is crazy.
Picture Christine and Allan,
just twisted,
sitting on
each other's faces.
Assholes in mouths.
Fingers in ears.
God knows
where their feet are.
All kinds of weird
oiled up shit.
Picture that.
Smells.
Go.
Why would that motivate me?
Just go.
Go, go, go.
Okay, okay, okay
okay, okay, okay.
Giving up?
What?
Did you say something?
I don't--
I don't think so.
It sounded like
you said giving up?
Oh. Yeah.
I was just asking you
if you were giving up?
What's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Just forget I said it.
Thanks.
How could you tell that?
How could you tell
that I was giving up?
Well, I don't
mean to intrude
but, you're sitting here
and you're, you know,
kind of playing
with your drink,
and you know,
looking around a lot,
and you're dressed
really nice.
So, I just, you know,
figured you were,
you know,
here to meet someone.
I guess,
it is pretty obvious.
It's not that bad.
Thanks.
Look, um, for what it's worth,
if I was that guy,
I wouldn't have stood you up.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
You, you keep up.
Hold on.
Have a drink with me.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm Danielle.
Oh, I'm Neal.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
What brings you out
tonight, Neal?
Um, it's--
it's my birthday.
Really?
Yeah.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
So did you get
anything nice today?
Um, well, I think
I'm talking to her.
Wow, I'm sorry.
That's really stupid.
You're sweet.
Oh, well, if you--if you
think my stupid is sweet,
I got a boat load
of stupid for you.
Such as.
Um. Can I borrow
your phone?
Why?
So I can call my mother
and tell her I met
the girl of my dreams.
If I could rearrange
the alphabet,
I would put you
and I together.
Yeah, is that a mirror
in your pants,
because I can see
myself in them?
You know, I'm sorry.
That was also dumb.
You have nothing
to worry about.
Oh, okay.
( cell phone buzzes )
Oh, you know, I'm sorry,
I got to take this.
I told my friend to call me
and make sure
I wasn't in
a basement somewhere,
with a rapist.
Oh, well,
the night's still young.
You should probably
take that call. Okay.
Holy shit, I cannot
believe this is working.
Who says it's working?
It looks like
it's going great?
I have no idea.
Dude, I can't keep this up.
I'm flying blind up here.
You're going to have to
because here she comes.
Can I stay?
No, get out of here.
You're glowing.
I wanna stay.
Get out of here.
Who were those guys?
I have no idea.
Um, listen,
it's pretty loud in here.
How would feel
about getting that drink
someplace a little quieter?
Yeah, sure.
Where were you thinking?
How'd it go?
Holy shit!
We want details.
Did you guys sleep here?
Yeah.
Why?
We were too excited.
Yeah, we wanted
to hear how it went,
and please,
be very specific.
Why did you move
my furniture?
Stop stalling!
Okay, I guess
I can look past the fact
that you guys broke
into my house last night
and slept here,
and just say that,
it was awesome.
Yes.
I barely had to even say
anything before,
you know, she's asking me
back to her place for a drink.
And when we get there
it was like
she couldn't get
the door closed fast enough.
I had never been with a woman
who had so much pent up energy.
She literally said...
Let me do
all of the work.
The only weird thing was
that she insisted that...
The dolphin
stays on the bed.
Wait,
a dolphin?
Like a stuffed animal?
He likes to watch.
I like that.
It's just weird enough
to be sexy.
I was able to look
past that though
because the sex was--
BOTH: Amazing.
Happy birthday, my man.
Thank you, guys.
Don't mention it.
So what's
the plan for today?
Don't you have work?
Yeah.
Shouldn't you go?
What are you
going to do?
I don't know.
I probably should start
looking for a new job.
Good, because we lined up
another girl for you.
Yeah, we figured
it went well last night,
because you
didn't come home.
Yes, but--
And we also figured
that since you have no job
and you have
no girlfriend,
you probably just sit
around here all day
in your underwear thinking
about how miserable you are.
And we're getting
little tired of you acting
miserable all the time.
So we got a new girl
for you to fuck.
Because we love you.
Last night was really great,
but it was a fluke.
You're a fluke.
That's not an insult.
Guys, let's be honest.
I got lucky.
Okay, here comes
Captain Miserable again.
It's not going to work
every time.
Well, prove that to us.
Just go to work,
and let me enjoy my day.
No. Come on, big boy.
Show us.
Show us it was a fluke.
Will you leave me alone
if I'm right?
Yep.
Okay, then.
All right.
Saw you
at Culver City Park.
You had
the cutest little dog,
and I was sipping coffee
by that big tree.
Did you see me?
Okay, so we know
she likes dogs.
We thought you maybe you knew
somebody who had one.
I do, but he is
the craziest person I know.
Good. We're taking it.
Where is he?
He's next door.
Let's go.
What do you guys
want her for?
Just give us
the fucking dog, Bryce.
No, we're gonna have the dog
for maybe an hour or two.
We'll bring her
right back.
Thing's gotta walk
or something, right?
Okay, hey, whoa.
Slow down, fella.
It's not an it,
it's a Zoe dog.
That's a kind of dog
named Zoe, it's my dog.
Second of all I take
her for three walks a day,
and one of them
is a dinner walk.
Well, just tell me
what you guys are doing.
Fuck, fine.
We need the dog
so Neal can get laid
by manipulating some girl
we met on the internet.
Huh?
Okay.
Okay, you can have the dog,
but I want in.
No, Bryce, you cannot
fucking join them.
Neal's not going to have
a three-way with some dude.
Oh, no, no--
No, I don't want that.
I mean, I want you to teach me
how you internet the girls.
Well, it doesn't even
really for sure work--
You know, what? Sold.
What?
Yeah.
We'll have her
back soon.
Bye, Zoe.
Oh, sometimes she likes
to pretend she's a horse.
But don't let her
take it too seriously,
I don't want her to think
she is a horse.
This is a bad idea.
She said
by the picnic table,
she's not
by the picnic table.
And she's
reading a book.
Does someone waiting
for someone read a book?
Dude, that is the only girl
in this entire park.
That has to be her.
Oh, my God, she's
practically begging for it.
George, when was the last time
you and your girlfriend had sex?
What month is it?
Stop stalling.
Go talk to her.
Okay, I will go,
and you guys will see
that last night
was just luck,
and we can go home.
Okay.
That'll be fun for us.
To see that.
Giving up?
Excuse me?
Giving up.
You seem like you were
waiting for someone,
and they don't seem
to be coming,
so I was asking
if you were giving up.
Oh, I'm not, I'm not waiting
for anyone, I'm sorry.
You're not?
I think I'd remember
something like that.
Yeah, yeah.
That's--That's
what I thought. Okay.
I'm just reading,
and enjoying the weather.
Are you
waiting for someone?
Oh, no.
No, I'm not.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just, you know,
walking my dog.
She's a pretty dog.
Yeah, she is, yeah.
I groom her myself.
Is that true?
No, it's not.
I don't know
why I said that--
why I said that.
You lie a lot?
Anyway, I'm gonna go.
Sorry for
bothering you.
You're not bothering me.
Actually this book
is not as good as I remember.
Oh, Little Women.
Oh, well, maybe I'll--
Maybe I'll see you
at the park here again.
I walk her here
all of the time.
So...
You do?
I come here a lot
and I've never seen you here.
I don't know
why I keep doing that.
I don't walk her here
all the time.
You must make me
nervous or something.
Okay, bye.
How'd you fuck it up?
She wasn't waiting
for anyone.
She's the only one here.
It has to be her.
There's no
other explanation.
How about
last night was a fluke?
Come on,
I'll buy the first round.
Oh, you know what sounds
good right now is a mai tai?
BARRY: Hi, I drink mai tais,
and I don't sleep
with my girlfriend.
Who am I?
I'm you.
NEAL: No, he lives
in total squalor,
but the weird thing
is that Bryce is like
really rich.
Neal.
What are you doing home?
He still lives here,
remember?
Shouldn't you
be at work?
I quit.
You did, why?
I just didn't want
to go anymore.
because I didn't see
your car out front.
I left it at work.
Just didn't want to
drive it anymore.
Well, I just came
to get my stuff.
Yeah, I figured.
Did you find my
Three Men and a Baby?
No.
Do you want to look?
You seem busy.
I mean,
Barry and George are here.
Oh, don't mind us.
Yeah, we'll be
quiet as mice.
Not gonna say anything.
GEORGE: Uh-uh.
Yeah, I think
I'm gonna try again later.
All right.
Suit yourself.
Oh.
Can I?
You can absolutely
take those.
Yeah.
I don't want them.
Take 'em.
Thank you.
Uh, Christine?
Yep.
Maybe, call next time.
I will.
Because for me,
my heart is racing right now.
What is with her
and the
Three Men and a Baby
thing?
It's signed
by the entire cast.
Even Gutenberg?
Yep.
Oh.
All right.
Hey, I have an idea.
Giving up?
What?
I thought you were
waiting for someone,
so I was just asking
if you were giving up.
How would you know that?
Well,
not to sound weird,
but I've been here
for a little bit,
and I've noticed
you checking your watch,
and looking around.
Yeah,
I'm meeting a friend.
Oh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just so you know,
if it was me,
I wouldn't have
kept you waiting.
Wait.
Was I that obvious?
I'm mean, you're
the prettiest girl
in this bar,
how could
I not notice you.
Thank you.
Um, would you--
would you like
to sit down?
Yes.
I'm Michelle.
Neal.
My place might be
a little bit of a mess.
Oh, I won't hold it
against you.
Oh, thank you.
No, it's really great.
Can I just make
a suggestion though?
Sure.
Can you
do more of this?
You could
tell that I did that?
Oh, yeah, I mean,
it hits your eyes,
right when you walk in.
Of course, you're
showing it off, you know.
How could you not
be proud of this?
It's just that most people
don't even notice it.
Yeah. Well, those
people are dense.
I mean,
the amount of detail
you put just
into the musculature.
Whoa.
Hold that.
Okay.
I've always
wanted to do that.
Sure.
Neal, you came back
to the party.
You're a little late.
Can Darren come
outside and play?
Do you think
I find that funny?
Okay, you walked out
in the middle of a party
that we threw for you.
Do you know
how important a night away
from the kids is?
No, you wouldn't know
because you don't have kids,
you don't have
a girlfriend,
you don't have a job--
Can I just talk
to Darren please?
I'm not done yet.
Apparently you
don't have a car now?
Neal, hey, man.
How are you doing?
We missed you.
Where did you go?
It's a long story,
I just came over
to apologize.
Well, get in here.
We didn't get a chance
to give you your present.
Oh, yeah, we also have
three day old cake.
You want some of that?
I would love some.
I would love
some of that cake.
Thank you, sis.
Excuse me.
And before I knew it,
we're doing it
on her coffee table.
That is
easily the coolest thing
I have ever heard
in my life.
What about
your kid's first word?
No.
Does it work every time?
I've only done it
three times,
and one time
the girl didn't show up.
I gotta tell Jillian
about this.
No.
Why?
I don't want you talking
to my sister
about me having sex.
She doesn't talk to you
about me and her having sex?
No, she doesn't.
What are you saying
about me, Neal?
He didn't say anything
about you.
I got to try this.
Dude.
I'm just kidding.
Jillian would turn my balls
into a magic trick.
Did you say
my name, honey?
No.
This is
a really good cake.
Go fuck yourself.
Are you gonna let her
talk to me like that?
Yeah.
That's why I love him.
So, there was something
about a present?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
It's a moleskin,
'cause you are always talking
about doing more writing,
so I thought you'd enjoy that.
Wow, this is--
This is actually
really cool. Thanks.
Yeah, we figured since you
weren't working right now.
Thanks.
Anyway, I got to go.
Thanks for the cake, sis.
Oh, it was my pleasure.
I have an appointment.
For sex?
Do you want to,
we have time
before the kids come home
now that Neal's
leaving.
Oh, uh, yeah, yeah.
Let's do it.
Ugh, I'm got to throw up.
The girl from the park.
Hey, thanks for letting me
use your shower.
Again with you.
Why are you always
in my dreams?
You tell me, pal.
Well, at least
you're not naked.
And there it is.
Look,
I want you to know
how bad I feel
about the whole--
Just save it.
I don't want
to hear it right now.
Okay, let me
get this straight.
You're bummed
because you've been stood up
by a girl
that you were going to trick
into thinking that
she'd been stood up?
It's not that.
You're thinking about
the girl in the blue shoes
right now, aren't you?
It was her
at the beach, right?
I don't know.
But it's time
for you to--
God dammit.
( cell phone ringing )
What do you want, Barry?
BARRY:
Where are you?
I'm at the laundromat.
Oh, okay, great.
You're out of underwear.
You're
wearing my underwear?
When are you coming home?
What difference
does it make?
We're bored.
Hey, do you mind
if we start a small fire
in your apartment?
Bryce!
Oh, my God, that's huge.
I got to go.
I said small.
Has the book
gotten any better?
The book.
Little Women.
Yes,
I am reading this book.
Do you not remember me
from the park?
( cell phone ringing )
You can get that.
'Cause I'm gonna--
I have to.
Remember, I was asking if
you were waiting for someone?
I--I had my dog with me.
The one you
groom yourself.
Yes.
The one I groom myself.
Yes, very funny.
Hey, were you
at the beach yesterday?
I think I saw you.
No, I wish.
I was...working.
Oh, well, I guess
I must have
been seeing things.
Unless you have
a twin sister.
Do you have
a twin sister?
No, I don't have
a twin sister.
Do you have
any sisters?
No.
Effeminate brothers that
like to dress up like you?
No.
So you're
an only child?
Wow.
Do you want to see
my tax returns?
I get it, too far.
I don't even know you.
I'm Neal, by the way.
I'm Jane.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Pretty sure
my name is Jane.
Okay, do you mind
if I sit down?
Well, I'm gonna be
leaving.
Oh, okay.
So, has the book
gotten any better?
Not really.
Then why do you
keep reading it?
Well, I have a thing
about finishing things
that I start,
which usually means I stay
with them too long, so...
Are you sure you weren't
at the beach yesterday?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I mean, I saw
those blue shoes.
The same blue shoes that
you were wearing at the park.
You got a foot fetish?
What? No.
I don't even
own blue shoes.
like the color.
( alarm buzzing )
Oh,
those are my clothes.
Okay, it was
nice talking to you.
Where?
You're leaving?
and I don't usually hang out
in laundromats.
Hey, shopping is done.
You ready to go?
Yes.
Ready to go.
Jane, if I could just--
Well, well, well,
who is this?
This is Neal.
Hello Neal.
I'm Cassandra.
Her roommate.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
How old are you, Neal?
32.
Did you go to college?
Yep.
What'd you study?
Creative writing.
You have
a girlfriend, Neal?
No.
When was
your last relationship?
I know it's--
Answer the question.
It ended
three months ago.
Did you dump her?
No.
You cheated on her?
She cheated.
You have a job, Neal?
In between.
Times are tough.
Yeah.
You exercise?
Try to.
Sense of humor?
( imitates horn )
Oh, my God.
Where did you
find this guy?
He was sticking to
the lint screen.
You have to get back
to that, right?
( alarm buzzing )
Looks like I'm done.
Great, you can come
join us.
We were just about to get
an afternoon cocktail.
JANE: Cassandra.
What?
Were we not just
about to go do that?
Yeah, but Neal's
practically a stranger,
a very busy stranger.
I literally have
nothing to do all day.
Oh, great, then you
can come join us.
We're just going to a place
right around the corner.
Oh, I would
love to come.
Oh, I walked here.
I live just down the block.
So that means
we're all neighbors.
What?
That is very convenient.
You want to throw
your clothes in my cart?
Oh, well, don't mind
if I do, m'lady.
Yeah, he's fun.
Did you hear that?
"He's fun."
Okay, I'm going
to have one drink.
Yeah, right.
This girl is a lush.
I am no such thing.
I am--
CASSANDRA:
Probably drunk right now.
Oh, right here.
This is
a really cool place.
Nice blue shoes.
Thanks.
Yeah, this lady
has a pair just like them,
but they are way too big
for my tiny little feet.
Is that right?
Lots of people
have blue shoes, Neal.
Yeah, but how many
who look exactly like you?
Okay, about that drink,
we don't want to
keep Neal all day.
Again, you're not
keeping me from anything.
Well, there
really must be something
that we're
keeping you from.
I have absolutely nowhere
to be but right here.
Yay, that's great.
Yay.
So what's your
story, Neal?
Oh, so now you want to know
something about me?
Yeah.
I mean,
who is Neal?
Let's see.
Um, born,
grew up,
middle class,
college, Los Angeles,
here.
I mean, I'm sure there's
some stuff in between,
but I don't
really remember.
You?
About the same.
Born, grew up, parents
divorce, two Christmases,
yay.
Uh, college,
Los Angeles, here.
Mine just
goes born, here.
Two steps?
Yeah.
Sounds about right.
So, what
should we drink to?
Here's to a long life
and a merry one.
A quick death
and an easy one.
A pretty girl
and an honest one.
A cold pint
and another one.
Huzzah.
Yassas l'chaim.
All right, now
that the pleasantries
are out of the way,
what's next?
♪ You'll never get that taste
out of your mouth ♪
♪ You'll never
get the paw prints ♪
♪ Out of
the hen house now ♪
♪ And you can't go back
same way you came ♪
♪ Round all the pieces up
♪ But they just
dont fit the same ♪
♪ White knuckles
♪ Maybe it's not so bad
♪ So let your hair down now
( in accent )
Hello, my name
is Michael Caine.
Sometimes as an actor,
you will find yourself
breaking during a scene.
So, I don't know.
No, it's really good.
Yeah.
Your accent is amazing.
My father
is from London, so...
My father is from London.
You don't say.
I have dual-citizenship.
So do I.
I'm sorry.
I, uh...
I don't know
where that came from.
I'd like to apologize.
It was you
on the beach yesterday.
No.
You little liar.
Don't turn it on me.
You're the liar.
Wait, I'm sorry.
How am I the liar?
Because you've been lying
to women on the internet, Neal.
What?
You've been responding to
Missed Connections ads.
What?
Yeah, you've been
lying to women online.
I don't know--I don't know
what you're talking about.
I was your
"Missed Connection"
on the beach yesterday.
I knew it was you.
God, why did you run away
when I was trying
to talk to you yesterday--
Oh, stop. Just stop.
Because it was
the second fake ad
that you responded to.
Fake ad.
Second.
You were
my "Missed Connection"
at the park too.
Yep.
I'm sorry,
why would you post a fake ad?
What do you
possibly get out that?
What do you get out
of lying to women?
What do you do
when they realize
that you are not the guy
that they were hoping to see?
I don't pretend
to be anything I am not.
I just sit around
and, you know, wait.
Wait, you don't pretend
to be the guy.
No.
Oh, man.
Like a knight
in shining armor.
Yeah.
Fuck.
What?
So wait, you gave a fake
response to my fake ad?
Hoping that you would use
my vulnerability
to sleep with me?
You never answered
my question.
What do I get out of it?
Yeah.
I think
this conversation is over.
Wait, no, I'm sorry,
I just confided a lot into you,
and I think
I deserve a little bit
of an explanation.
Shut up.
So, we're back
to this again.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
I'm having a hard time.
I feel like
the room is spinning.
It's definitely spinning.
Hold on.
All right.
I just wanna...
Yes.
I just need to close
my eyes for a second.
It's so spinning.
I'm just gonna
close--
Okay.
All right.
Fuck.
Jane?
No, that's totally fine.
I should
probably go.
Morning.
Go fuck yourself.
See, honey,
it's like I always say.
No hesitation.
Welcome home.
For fuck's sake,
do you guys not pay
rent somewhere?
I do, but my place
is kind of a dump.
Plus, you have cable.
Oh, my girlfriend's out
of town for the weekend,
and I don't know
how to be alone anymore.
So...
Bryce?
I live next door.
That's terrific.
There's a new painting
on the wall
that wasn't here
when I left.
Yeah, this clown
is in my top five clowns.
Uh, there's a grill
here in the living room.
It's off now.
Yeah, but it's
still probably a fire hazard.
Not anymore.
Anymore?
Well, when it was on
it was dangerous as hell.
Also, thanks for
all those phone calls
yesterday afternoon.
Appreciate that.
Yeah, we
ran out of beer.
I was gonna see
if you could pick some up.
Just go get it yourself.
I did.
Thank you.
So where you been?
I ran into the girl
with the blue shoes.
Really?
I spent
the night with her?
Really?
It was a little of weird.
Oh, did she get freaky?
Here we go.
What,
she try to like dress you up
and like do you
with a strap on?
Or was there a swing?
Sex swing?
Or video tape?
She wanted to tape it.
Naughty.
Wait, was it
something really specific,
like, oh, you can't breathe
while we're doing it?
Or did she try
and strap you down
to an apparatus
of some sort,
or like, go
second knuckle on you,
or try to bite you
on the dick or--
Are you done?
No, she was a furry.
She was one of those furries
and you had to like dress up
in rabbit costumes,
and like there was holes
in the costume you had
to hump through.
Did she
try to shit on you?
Are you done?
Yeah, probably done.
Yeah.
I don't mean
weird sexually.
I just mean, it just
wasn't what I expected.
In a good way
or a bad way?
It wasn't her house.
And, now
I'm interested.
Yeah, so I wake up,
and she's gone
So I get up
and go to look for her
and it wasn't
her apartment.
Wait, what do you mean
it wasn't her apartment?
Say those
last four words again.
It wasn't her apartment.
That's what I mean.
Did you fuck her or not?
I'm pretty sure we passed out
before we could.
Bryce.
The problem is
the she posted a fake ad.
Whoa, what?
Say those
last four words again.
Uh, fuck you.
So, so wait a minute.
You posted a fake response
to a fake ad.
Yeah, but she's
not doing it to get laid.
In fact, I don't think
she even talks to the guys
who show up.
That's fucking sick.
I know.
I want to meet this woman.
Oh, yeah, I could drive.
I'll drive us right now, go.
You're okay,
you're okay.
All right.
So wait a minute,
wait a minute.
The two people that are lying
about missed connections
actually met up?
Well,
that's serendipitous.
I know, right?
Yeah.
I don't see that.
No, it is.
Okay.
Good.
I mean...
Fine.
What's happening?
No one knows.
Yeah.
It's a mystery.
But seriously...
Are you going to go back
to fucking random women?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Okay.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Good, because I have
the perfect woman for you.
Have you now?
I never do this but I saw
a very good looking
tall man today
at the supermarket
on Colorado Blvd.
If this is you
and you are single
and possibly interested
feel free to e-mail me back.
I mean,
she is practically begging for
it.
I'll take her.
No, you're in training.
Hand down.
Thank you, sir.
You are
very much welcome.
Oh, why, thank you.
Why, thank you.
Oh, indeed.
Indeed.
Okay, okay, okay,
are we done?
Yeah, that was weird.
Jane.
Yes.
What are you doing here?
It's a seafood
restaurant, Neal.
I'm eating seafood.
You're my missed connection,
aren't you?
I'll take that
as a yes.
So what happened
last night?
You don't remember?
No, I remember.
Where were we?
Whose place was that?
Oh, I didn't mention
I was housesitting?
No.
I'm housesitting.
Great.
Why weren't you there
when I woke up?
Oh, I'm sorry,
were you lead to believe
that one thing
was going to happen,
and then something else
happened?
You know like you do.
These women expect
to meet a guy and they do.
They don't expect to just meet
some guy and hook up.
Do you even call them again?
Not yet.
That's fantastic.
Neal, you seem
like a nice guy,
but what you're doing
is more than a little douchey.
You're a bad guy now.
Hmmm?
But I'm not looking to
get rewarded for it.
CASSANDRA: Hey, Neal.
You're late.
I was just saying
what a great time
we had with you
last night.
Yeah, I had a great time
last night too,
but Jane here thinks
I'm a bad guy.
Okay, you guys need
to leave me out of this.
All right, I'm done.
I'm done.
Sorry, Neal.
Hey.
Hey, you're right,
you know.
He really is a bad guy.
He's such a bad guy.
I know.
You should have known
by his thin mustache
and ambiguously
European accent.
His weird obsession
with hairless cats.
Always detailing
how he's going to kill you
before he
actually kills you.
I don't understand that.
Like we're there,
just kill us already.
I know right?
So Neal
was your missed connection
again, wasn't he?
Ah-ha.
I see, you used a European,
thin mustached,
cat-lover to trap me
into this.
Yeah, I'm really
good like that.
Yes, he was
my missed connection again.
That's pretty serendipitous.
Not really.
He lies
to a lot of women.
You lie
to a lot of men.
It's not the same thing.
Anyway, you're not supposed
to worry about this.
Oh, yeah, I know.
I'm--I'm aware.
Hey, remember
when I promised you
that I would not ask
why you were setting up fake ads
and kind of going
bat-shit crazy?
Why are you
setting up those ads
and going bat-shit crazy?
None of your business.
Can I take a guess?
I think that you are
doing this to see
if men are capable
of being hurt like you were.
Okay, all right.
So you set up
these like vague ads
and you sit there
and you watch these men
and you see if they are
able to be hurt or affected
by this potential new love
that just never shows up.
Yeah.
I knew it.
I thought I knew.
I wasn't really sure actually.
Really? You're some
kind of evil genius.
I am.
I will never
like cats though.
Me either.
Hey, listen.
Mike was an asshole.
All right?
He was a liar,
he was unfaithful,
he was stupid.
He had a stupid face.
He did have a stupid face.
He never
washed his hands.
Why?
You know they never are.
Who?
What now?
The guys.
They're never hurt.
They just act
like nothing happened.
I think
you just hurt Neal.
Neal is a bad guy.
He said he had
a girlfriend that cheated.
So maybe this is his way
of dealing with it.
Maybe.
Aw--
You are so fucked up.
I know.
But now
that you know my secret
I'm going
to have to kill you.
And I'm going
to tell you how.
Here is how
I'm going to kill you.
No, don't tell me,
don't tell me.
I'm going to--
I'm just
gonna shoot you.
That's what I'm going to do.
No.
I'm just
gonna shoot you.
I think
I'm gonna shoot you.
Thank you so much
for letting me in.
I really needed to talk
to someone.
Sure.
Yeah, I can't go home
right now because--
I told you,
he'd show up here.
What are
you guys doing here?
Oh, my God,
great question.
They just showed up.
This is good cake.
Can I please just talk
to my brother-in-law
and my sister?
About what?
Nothing.
You saw
Jane again, didn't you?
How could you tell?
Holy fuck balls.
Is this one
of your internet sex girls?
Darren?
Oh, come on.
You know I can't hide
anything from her.
She'd kill me.
I'd cut his balls off.
Did you at least
have sex with her?
No.
Really?
Holy fuck balls.
Stop saying that.
Just let it--
just give it a chance.
I can't.
Just let it breathe.
No. She saw me,
she got freaked out,
and she left.
She has to admit
there's some kind of force
that's dragging
you two together.
She doesn't.
She just blows it off.
That's what she said.
That's great.
Thanks for the sensitivity.
That's what she said.
Oh, well done, master.
She definitely said that.
Okay,
you all have to leave. Okay.
And then she said
I was a bad guy.
Am I a bad guy?
Absolutley not.
No.
You're my hero.
No, you're
not a bad guy.
I mean, there's
nothing you can do.
She's clearly got
issues of her own, so.
So I do nothing.
Yes. You wait for her
to reach out to you.
She has
your phone number, right?
No.
E-mail address?
The fake ones
that Barry set up.
Yeah, I forgot those passwords
right when I set them up.
Two words,
plausible deniability.
He doesn't know
what that means.
I do too.
Okay,
you know what then?
You're fucked.
That's not
what I want to hear.
Okay, well, here's
something else
you might not want to hear.
I think it's time
you get another job, Neal.
Oh, eat me.
Oh...Pass.
All right,
let's not start you two.
Come on.
He started it.
You started it.
I started it?
All right. Okay.
All right.
Why is everyone
so against employment here?
Okay.
Guys, come on.
It's America.
Come on.
Get jobs.
( doorbell rings )
Oh, they're early.
That is Darren's
boss and his wife
and we're having
them over for dinner.
Yes, we're staying.
No.
Everybody out.
Get--
go. Get out.
Out, out, out.
No, no.
Take the back door.
That's what she said.
Get out of my life.
I'm just gonna go ahead
and bring the cake with me.
I will bring back
your pretty green plates.
What's good?
Midnight?
Just go. Go.
Okay, bye, I miss you.
Bryce!
Oh, my God.
Look, I'm sorry.
Um, eat me?
I'm your sister.
It's the best I could do
on short notice.
It's disgusting.
I'm sorry.
All right, I'll do
better next time.
Oh, and
this is my brother-in-law,
Neal. Neal, I'd like you
to meet Ted and Alicia.
Do you guys
know each other?
No.
Yeah.
Seriously, guys,
what's going on?
We saw him
in his underwear
in our house.
Randomly.
There was a woman
staying at your place.
Do you by any chance
have her phone number?
Are you serious?
No.
You know what the best cure
is for a bad date?
Nyquil.
Dayquil.
Just got to get right back up on
that horse.
Oh, I don't know, guys.
I mean, I really feel like
this whole Jane thing
is the universe
telling me to stop doing this.
No.
Look, I have
like nothing interesting
in my life right now,
but what you've been doing--
What?
I have been
doing it too.
Yeah, but you have been
having meaningless sex
with women for years.
True.
( clearing throat )
Bryce, you did it once,
and it was a disaster.
Yeah.
He needs a chaperone.
I think
it's a good idea.
Look, for Neal to do it,
it makes me feel
like I'm right there
with you.
While I'm having sex?
Yeah.
Okay, I just don't
feel up to it, guys, okay.
Are you
fucking falling for Jane?
No, the last thing
I need is another Christine.
Do you
really believe that?
I don't know.
I just--I'm not sure if
I should have anymore sex.
I think it's
just gonna get me more twisted.
That's not a bad thing.
Oh, my God.
I just don't think
I can do it, Barry.
So the universe
made you a pussy?
No, that's not what
I meant.
Allan.
Hey, Neal.
What's up?
Oh, what's up?
You mean,
what's up since I walked in
on you fucking my girlfriend,
and the two of you then
consequently moving
in together?
Is that what you mean
by what's up?
Is that
what you're getting at?
I just wanted to see
how things were going.
How are things going?
What an awesome question.
Let's see, I have quit my job,
I have two to three people
in my apartment
at all times,
none of whom pay
any sort of rent,
I have started to feel guilty
for all the random sex
I've been having
with girls on the internet,
But on that note,
how has fucking
Christine been going?
Look, man, I'm sorry.
I know you're mad.
Oh, do you now?
Oh, what's
giving that away?
I can come back.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please don't go.
We don't even know
why you're here yet.
Well, Christine has been
trying to come over
to get the rest of her stuff,
and I wanted--
Jesus, fuck
with the stuff.
She is obsessed
Let me guess,
"Three Men and a Baby" tape.
It's her favorite movie.
It's that
limited edition copy--
Signed by
Steve Guttenberg.
Signed by Steve Guttenberg.
Yes.
It's fantastic.
I know.
So she sent you over?
No, I told her
I wanted to see you.
I wish I could say
the same to you.
Come on, man,
we've known each other
since we were eight.
You don't mean that.
The last time I saw you
it was a view of your bare
ass fucking my girlfriend.
That fucking haunts me.
God,
why you
two insisted on doing it
on the couch is beyond me.
Well, she said you guys
always did it on the bed,
so I just didn't want
to overstep my boundaries.
Okay, you should
probably go now.
Thank you.
Can't we just
talk about this, man?
Can't you just
shut the fuck up, Allan?
You know what, Neal,
you weren't listening to her.
From what
I saw on your end, there
wasn't a lot of listening
going on either.
You know what, don't talk
to me like you know.
Just get
the fuck out of here.
Real mature.
Yeah, whatever. Go shave
your ass, you fucking yeti.
Thanks for the help
there, guys.
We thought you were doing
pretty good on your own.
Yeah. Right up
to the shave your ass thing.
Otherwise pretty good.
I like the ass line.
Thanks.
So what now?
Get back on that horse.
Yeah, daddy!
Yeah. Let's get me
an internet girl too
and then you can be
my chaperone.
Chaperone!
Mmm-mmm.
Absolutely not.
He does
need a chaperones.
And I thought
for some reason,
the guy was going
to meet me here.
It's crazy.
No, no, it's not.
You have
to take risks sometimes.
Bottom line is, you came here
to meet someone, and you did.
Oh,
look what you did there.
I try to bring it
back to myself
as much as possible.
It doesn't make you
seem conceited at all.
Good, good.
I just wanted to be sure.
Dude, I don't know
if my sex stranger
is even here.
Should I like--
I don't know,
make an announcement
or something?
Excuse me,
I'm in the middle
of a conversation right now.
Fuck off.
I'm sorry,
I'm very confused.
My drink is red.
Who was that?
I have no idea
who the fuck
that person was.
Probably just
some crazy guy.
I need another drink.
Um, actually
it's getting
kind of loud.
Do you want
to get out of here?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you're
taller than me.
That never happens.
You know what,
I see an old friend of mine.
Do you mind if I go over
and just say hi real quick?
Okay.
Great.
Jane?
Not now, Neal.
What are you doing here?
I'm a bit
busy right now.
Holy fuck.
You do not
want to do this.
You don't see me
stopping you.
Everything okay, Neal?
Hi, I'm Jane.
I'm Neal's friend.
Neal was just leaving.
No, I wasn't.
Everything is fine.
Jane's
an old friend of mine.
I was just giving her
some advice.
But I don't need
any advice,
especially from him.
You do realize
what he's doing--
That's probably
enough. Thank you.
I don't think
she's gonna come.
Actually,
she's right here.
Really?
Yes,
she was just leaving.
Giving up?
Nope.
I'm a little confused
what's going on right now.
Okay, so what
he's doing tonight,
he has done over
and over and over again.
What is she talking about?
She's lying.
That's what she likes to do.
She thinks it's impossible
for two people to meet,
and she wants the whole world
to feel the same way.
Well, that's not it at all.
Well, then why don't you
enlighten me?
Wait, is this
your ex-girlfriend?
Oh, fat chance.
No.
Absolutely not.
Happy?
Yeah.
I'm so okay with you using me
to get back at her.
Nothing bothers you.
Nothing.
you just seem to move right on
like everything is fine.
Are you talking about me
or all men?
All men.
What? Even me?
Okay, you know that men
aren't the only ones
who do horrible things.
I was hurt
just like you were.
Not just like me.
Because you were
able to move on
and start fucking
random women.
Excuse me?
I can't let it go.
He hurt me, and moved on
with his new life.
So why don't you
move on with yours?
Oh, like this?
Hi.
No, that's not what I was
getting at--
I didn't want her
to beat you.
Oh, it's on.
Oh, blue shoes.
But don't feel bad, anyone
would have lost to blue shoes.
How tall are you?
Um, like two websters.
We shouldn't
have done that.
Which part?
All of it.
Was I not just
in the same room?
I thought
that was pretty amazing.
All the more reason,
we shouldn't have done that.
I get it.
Good.
You know what?
No.
No, I'm sorry, no.
I like you, okay.
I said it, I like you.
You really haven't been
that cool to me lately,
but I can't deny the fact
that we have
some sort of connection.
It's great.
It's--it's really great.
In fact, I can't
get you out of my head.
And I can't deny
that we keep meeting up.
That means
something to me.
That means that someone
or something somewhere,
maybe wants us
to be happy.
Maybe thinks
that we've been trying
some really fucked up ways
to find happiness,
but in spite of all that,
maybe thinks
we deserve to be happy.
Let's face it,
we're damaged goods.
We're cracked.
And anyone
in their right minds
would see how fucked up
we are and run away.
But after all that,
I still like you.
Any reaction to that?
Anything?
I can't get
hurt again, Neal.
I don't think I could
pick myself up again.
Sorry.
Holy fuck.
Jesus.
I thought
she'd never leave.
Were you guys
in there all night?
Yeah.
We hid when you came in.
George, are you ever
with your girlfriend?
No, that girl hates me.
Wait, did you guys
hear me having sex?
This door
is not soundproof.
Yeah, I know. Is that right?
How did you keep
the dog quiet?
Um, she has a lot
on her mind.
Uh, well,
there's good news.
Oh, there's good news?
we found Christine's copy
of "Three Men and a Baby."
Really?
It's signed by
all three of them.
Yeah, even Guttenberg.
That's a tough get.
Not really.
Neal?
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Oh, you found it.
It was buried under a bunch
of stuff in the closet.
Oh, my God, thank you.
Did you walk here?
Yeah.
No, no, no.
I can't--I can't stay.
I just wanted to come by
and bring you that,
and let you know that if you
wanted to come over tomorrow
and pick up
the rest of your stuff,
I'd be okay with that.
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah.
Well, no,
not in general,
but I do know
that I'm okay
with what
I just said about you
coming over
to get your stuff.
So...all right.
Hey, Neal?
Did you really
want to marry me?
I mean,
you bought that ring.
Why--
why didn't you propose?
I don't know.
I think maybe I was doing
what I thought
I was supposed to.
You could have
quit at any time.
I know.
Now.
Okay, seriously,
what is going on with you?
What?
What do you mean?
I haven't seen you
this rational
since we started dating.
The party side
got raped out of me,
and this is all that's left.
That's like
one of the weirdest things
I've ever said.
I don't know why,
that was really weird.
I'm not sure what that means.
Please, let me--
Christine, I--
I just want you to know that
in spite of everything,
I do genuinely
want you to be happy.
I am happy.
And that's all
I ever wanted for you.
I know.
Thanks.
Bye, Neal.
♪ Oh, no, I don't recall
♪ I can't remember
anything at all ♪
♪ The life we knew
is lost and gone ♪
♪ And it's hard
without you ♪
♪ I know
the world is new ♪
♪ And what you lost inside,
inside of you ♪
♪ And all the love
we shared is true ♪
♪ And it's hard without you
♪ Ooh, life is gone,
what I had is gone ♪
♪ But it's hard to go
♪ Ooh, without you
♪ Oh, no, I don't recall
Get a job, hippie.
Hey, fuck you, man.
Excuse me?
I'll handle this. Excuse me?
It sounded like
you said fuck you.
I did.
Well done.
Thank you.
Waiting for someone?
Yes.
They're not
coming, are they?
It doesn't seem that way.
Love.
It's a sticky business.
Yes.
Yes, indeed.
See, honey, you have
to allow a man to respect you.
I love you, baby.
Giving up so easy?
What?
I asked
if you were giving up.
It seemed like you were
waiting for someone.
And you wanted to know
if I was giving up.
If it was you, you
wouldn't have made me wait.
Um,
how did you know that--
Look, I'm--
I'm really flattered. I am.
On two levels, one, because
you're hitting on me,
but two, because
you're using my technique,
which either means
I'm not the only person
or I 'm just
this amazing trendsetter.
But either way,
I'm just going to go ahead
and just end
this right here
because I'm
in a really weird place,
which in the short term,
could make
for some really interesting
and bizarre sex,
but in the long term,
is probably just going
to fuck me up more.
So I'm just gonna say,
good day to you.
And, uh, shake your hand.
And take my leave, and yes,
I did just say take my leave.
So keep on trying.
Oh, and the guy
you want is over there.
But...
Hello?
Coming.
Good morning.
Yeah,
we don't believe in Jesus
if that's what
you're selling.
No, no.
I, uh,
responded to an ad
about a couch.
Oh, oh, well fuck,
yeah, I'm sorry.
Um, oops.
I'm Derek.
Hi, come on in.
Sorry, we get a lot of
Jesus pushers around here.
No, it's all right.
Yeah, oh, good. Um,
well, uh, you are looking
to redecorate?
No, I walked in
on my girlfriend
and my best friend
fucking on my old couch.
Oh, well,
that's a good enough reason.
So,
uh, well, this is the couch.
Okay.
Oh, and these are my roommates
Jessica and Cassandra.
Oh, you've got to be
fucking kidding me.
I'm sorry,
Jessica was it?
Wow, I could have sworn
your name was Jane.
No, it's actually Jessica.
That's weird, I knew a Jane
that looks just like you.
It might have been you.
No, it wasn't.
Okay.
So this is the couch.
It's vintage.
It's
totally comfortable.
But not like in a suffocating,
like scary way
like I shouldn't be afraid
to go with this couch.
Um, and it also has all of
it's original upholstery.
So you know what, what you
see is what you get.
There's no surprises,
but at the same time,
I'm never going
to get bored with this.
No, it's just
what you are looking for.
Well, I'm not really looking
for anything in particular.
Oh, good because I'm the one
buying the couch, not you.
Okay, so if this couch fits--
I don't really feel like anyone
should be looking
for anything
in particular.
Good, because usually
when you are not looking
is when you find
the best stuff.
Or potential pitfalls.
Or potential awesome.
Okay.
Back to task.
Uh--uh,
but I'm totally
willing to negotiate.
Oh, as am I.
Okay.
How do you know
if the couch is worth it?
Jessica?
What are you
afraid of?
You see a couch.
You like it.
You sit on it.
You know it feels nice,
so you want to sit
on it again, right, Derek?
Sure.
It's a fucking couch.
We're not asking you
to take out
a car loan or a mortgage.
Neal, just relax.
It's just a couch.
It is a really
great couch.
Goddamn
right, it is.
Yeah, but a couch could lead
to a matching love seat
or an apartment
or a fucking house
with a goddamn
picket fence.
Or it could lead to this
really great partner in crime.
Or another
totally devastating--
What are you afraid of?
This couch
punching me in the gut.
would never do that.
Okay, we're clearly
not talking about
the couch anymore.
You don't know that?
I do know that.
But I don't know that
and I don't think
that this couch
or any couch
can change my mind.
Well, this couch is not leaving
without a fight.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, this is the guy?
Oh.
BOTH: Awww.
So you're
wearing clothes this time?
Neal, for the tenth time,
this isn't a dream.
It isn't?
No, it is.
It's a dream.
Okay.
Yeah.
So Jessica seems nice.
Don't even
think about it.
What?
This is a dream,
and in actuality
every person in a dream
is like a manifestation
of yourself, so.
What are you
talking about?
By me saying
Jessica seems nice,
it's basically like you saying
Jessica seems nice.
Oh, well, then,
yeah, she is.
She's nice.
She is, isn't she?
Why are you naked?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing's wrong.
♪ In your fitted raincoat
and tangled winter hair ♪
♪ Cheeks a little rosy
in the February air ♪
♪ And running through the subway
to catch the uptown train ♪
♪ Spend the night
just dancing ♪
♪ And running through the subway
to catch the uptown train ♪
♪ Spend the night
just dancing ♪
♪ I want you,
yeah, I want you ♪
yeah, I want you bad ♪
♪ So bad
I can't think straight ♪
♪ So bad all my bones shake
♪ So bad I can't breathe
♪ And in the midnight quiet,
outside the world away ♪
♪ We could have just one more
night that you could stay ♪
♪ And in the light of morning
for 21 days straight ♪
♪ There you are beside me
♪ And in the light of morning
for 21 days straight ♪
♪ There you are beside me
♪ And I want you,
yeah, I want you ♪
♪ I want you,
yeah, I want you bad ♪
♪ So bad
I can't think straight ♪
♪ So bad all my bones shake
♪ So bad I can't breathe
♪ So won'tcha?  Oh, wantcha say
it? ♪
♪ So won'tcha? Oh, wantcha give
in? ♪
♪ So won'tcha? Oh, wantcha come
on? ♪
♪ I can't breathe
♪ cause I want you, yeah, I want
you ♪
♪ I want you, yeah, I want you
bad ♪
♪ So bad I can't think straight
♪
♪ So bad all my bones shake
♪ So bad I can't breathe
♪ I want you, yeah, I want you
♪ I want you, I want you
♪ So bad I can't breathe
♪ I can't breathe