This is "the comedy central
Roast of roseanne barr" brought
To you by...
and now welcome your roast
Master, jane lynch!
[cheers & applause]
Hello.
Thank you!
[applause]
Thank you.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm jane lynch.
Welcome to the comedy central
Roast of roseanne!
Goodness
What a night.
Roseanne, ellen barkin, casey
Segal, carrie fisher.
It's like a menopausal palooza:
This show is serving up more old
Spoiled hens than a chick-fil-a.
Oh, that reminds me.
[bleep] chick-fil-a.
And roseanne is referred t as
Just one name, bitch!
Ellen barkin is here.
Huh?
[applause]
Ellen, your sxcene is "sea of
Love" is the reason I'm a
Lesbian.
Nothing like seeing al pacino's
Bare as on the screen to make a
Girl want to eat [bleep] like
She's about to be executed.
Carrie fisher is here!
[cheers & applause]
Now, carrie's here to put
Roseanne's weight and drug
Problems into perspective.
Carrie was one of the hottest
Actresses in hollywood.
Tt was long ago in a galaxy
Far, far away.
One of the good ones.
Wayne brady is here.
[cheers & applause]
Now, wayne, you're going to hear
A lot of jokes about how you're
Not a real black man.
I want you to know, I still hid
My purse.
Good, good.
[laughter]
But enough about these vile
Degenerate failures.
Before we bring roseanne out
Tonight, let's take a look back
At her many career highlights so
Her viewers under the age of 20
Can stop asking who the [bleep]
She is
roseanne barr.
A husband thinks a wife knows
where every thing is.
Like a uterus is a tracking
device.
[laughter]
I like that joan jett.
I can't even remember the
last time we had sex.
I can.
That's why we ain't doing it.
When I was 12 years old, I
Signe a deal because I wanted
To get famous no matter what.
You ever sorry we got
Married?
Every second of my life.
Why are you so mean?
Because I hate kids.
She starred in the
Ground-breaking show,
"roseanne," she never shied away
From contentious issues.
It featured the first lesbian
Kiss on tv.
And then I had this tragic
Singing accident.
Oh, yeah.
ｶ and the home of the brave ｶ
disgusting.
So anti-american.
Scratching herself and
Spitting.
The nationa anthem?
I don't think so.
You think I'm pretty?
Don't say that on television.
[bleep] you!
So those macadamia nuts...
those are my nuts.
I need to run for president.
I'm not kidding.
This is america, land of the
Free.
I have to call my
Psychiatri.
That's what makes me me.
I can't begin to tell you
What a privilege it is for you
To have me here tonight.
Let's start this show!
[cheers & applause]
She is a personal inspiration
To me an an absolute comedic
Genius.
Please welcome america's
Domestic goddess, roseanne!
[cheers & applause]
Hi, gilbert.
Hi, carrie.
Awesome entrce.
Awesome.
Hi, honey.
Hello darling.
Oh,
hi!
[cheers & applause]
Roseanne, it's greato
Finally meet you.
You know, I waved to you outside
But realized it was one of
Those inflating parking lot
Gorillas.
What a huge mark you've made on
The entertainment industry.
There your ground-breaking
Show "roseanne" and then
There'... yes!
[applause]
And then of urse there's
Reruns of "roseanne."
And having a hit show finally
Allowed you to do what you truly
Love to do, fire people.
[laughter]
Let's not forget your movie
Career like the rest of america.
You co-starred in "she devil"
With meryl stree
That movie got 2 1/2 stars jt
Like this stage.
Of course, you've experienced
Controversy.
Everybody remembers your version
Of the star spangd banner.
What could have predicted your
Beautiful speaking voice
Wouldn't translate to singing.
In your defense, you said there
Was something wrong with the
Sound system that y.
There was.
It had been turned on.
Then you moved on to spiritual
Pursuits.
Roseanne, you're a jew that
Converted to more man, that
Converteto kablah and in
1990 you converted to white
Trash when you mried tom
Arnold.
Now, roseanne, it's not your
Fault you're attracted to tom.
You saw with all that white
Powder on his upper lip, there
Must be a doughnut somewhere.
[Ghter]
Roseanne said she had plastic
Surgery to get away from tom
Arnold much like a nonazy
Peon would use a car.
[laughter]
By the way, tom arnold wted to
Be here tonight but at the last
Minute nobody asked him.
[laughter]
I really don't know a lot about
Roseanne's current boyfriend.
I do know one thing.
He's into fat chicks.
[laughter]
Roseanne, you've admitted to
Having multiple personalities.
It's amazing you couldn't find
One that was likeable.
And it's true that roseanne goes
Off the grid from time to time.
This allows the grid to maiain
Its structural integrity.
[laughter]
But this year she's announced
Her campaign for presidency.
[cheers & applause]
Mitt romney sent roseanne
Flowers for making him the
Second most hated morman in the
Race.
Like joan of arc, you'r a
Strong wman that has a lot to
Say.
Fears nothing and whose ass is
About to go up in flames.
Let's bring out your first
Roaste
[cheers applause]
Our first roaster is amy
Schumer.
[cheers & applause]
Now, amy didn't have to blow
Someone to be on the stage
Tonight, but she insisted on it.
[laughter]
Ladies and gentlemen, let's get
Her out of the way, amy schumer.
[applause]
Oh, eat a dick, jane.
[laughter]
Try it.
Look at this stage.
Roseanne, ellen, jane, kate.
You are like the women's
Gymnastic teams.
Tired, sweeting.
You don't getour period
Anymore.
I haven't seen this much skin
Since jane lynch's circumcision.
[lghter]
I don't want to mess wh you,
Jane.
I know your fans would eat my
[bleep] alive.
[laughter]
I'm sorry.
I cannot stop looking at ellen
Barkin.
You're so sexy.
Jane, isn't it weird to see what
You would look like as a woman?
[laughter]
Weird.
I think it's weird.
Wayne brady is here.
[applause]
Wayne, you're crazy talented.
You're so brilliant.
Why doesn't anyone care?
No one up here can do what you
Do
When someone mentioned whos
Line is it anyway?
Carrie fisher yells out "mine"!
[laughter]
Because you're a drug addict.
Right.
[laughter]
Now, carrie, you've had more
Lines than a crippled kid at
Disneyland.
[laughter]
Ellen barkin is here.
Ellen caught a lot of flak for
Dating a man half her age.
So what?
You're dating a 43-year-old!
[laughter]
I don't see the problem.
Ellen has married some of the
Richest men in the world.
I'm not saying she's a gold
Digger, but she ain't messing
With no broke wayne bradys.
You know what I'm saying?
Ellen has been quote as saying
She slept her way to the middle.
You've inspired women to put
Their best clit forward.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Seth, a clit is this small...
You won't need to worry about
It.
Take it down.
Seth is here representing the
Lollipop guild.
Thank you!
[laughter]
For over 30 years, seth green
Has been one of hollywood's top
Child actors.
[laughter]
Speaking of children, gilbert,
God, you look like a tony asian
Kid.
Hang around long enough and jane
And her wife will try to adopt
You!
[laughter]
Jeff ross, still gross.
Jeff ross.
[laughter]
Jeff, you look lik krusty the
Clown dressed as joe paterno.
[laughter]
Thk it will help for all your
Work at children's parties.
Is that a rape whistle?
[laughter]
Jeff, you look worse than when I
Started this sentence.
How did you do that?
[Aughter]
Which brings me to michael
Moore... mean, roseanne barr.
[laughter]
I'm such a fan.
Roseanne bought a nut farm, a
Nut farm, which is also the name
For ellen barkin's mouth in an
Audition.
[laughter]
Amy, what did I do to you?
You just swallowed a ton of
Ejaculate.
That's all I'm saying.
Roseanne, you have the voice of
A parakeet and the face of a
Much fatter parakeet.
You know you're unattractive
When sara gilbert is eye candy
On the set.
You loo gorgeous.
I was surprised you were running
For president.
I thin a lot of people couldn't
Picture you like running.
[laughter]
Truthfully, you've been making
People laugh and feel better for
As long as I can remember.
You're a personal hero.
I'mhonored to be here.
Thanks so much.
[cheers & applause]
Thank you.
That's funny.
The comedy central roast of
Roseanne is brought to you by...
coming up, seth green, katey
Segal, wayne brady, carrie
[applause]
Our next roaster is seth
Green.
Seth is the man he is today
Because his mom smokes during
Pregnancies.
Please welcome the only peron
Here tonight, the only person
That wants another austin powers
Movie, seth green!
Wow, jane lynch.
Seriously, you're one of my
Favorite comic actors.
Jane lynch is the funniest man
In america.
I'm real rady for you to come
Up here and do your stupid jokes
About my height.
I have a job.
It's on cartoon network.
But I don't have to sleep a yea
And wait or the the next roast.
Carrie fisher is here.
[applause]
Carrie and I go way back to the
First austin powers movie where
She played a therapist.
There's no irony there.
[laughter]
Carrie used to be paid a lot to
Take work as a screen writer.
Now the only scripts she takes
Are from a friend's medicine
Cabinet.
[laughter]
I'm reall glad you're here.
It's a nerd's dream to be on the
Same show as carrie fisher and
Amy schumer.
Princess leah and princess blow
Ya.
Amy, you have a part in the new
Steve carell movie.
Congratulations.
A great change for your usual,
Seeking a dick for the end of
The night.
[laughter]
I can't believe ellen barkin is
Here tonight.
[applause]
I got so excited when s looked
At me back stage with that sexy
Crooked smile.
Actually wasn'ture if she was
Saying I'm io or hell, I'm
Having a stroke!
[laughter]
Ff ross is an old friend.
He's got a new show on roasting
The news.
It would be perfect for people
Who find jon stewart handsome
And funny.
[laughter]
People have said wayne brady
Isn't black enough.
He got a job as a game show
Host.
That's going to show them.
Gilbert gottfried, I don't know
Why you squint a lot.
We're the ones that have to look
At you.
[laughter]
Katey segal, I've known you
Since you did married with
Children when I was doing "the
Fact of life."
Now you're a star on the sons of
Anarchy.
I'm here for roseanne, our guest
Of honor.
[applause]
Roseanne, you need another show.
You're spending too much time on
Twitter.
It's annoying.
I tweet a lot but you tweet more
Than big bird when he's getting
Ass raped.
[laughter]
Okay.
Last time I saw roseanne, she
Was in a snickers commercial.
Because that's what america is
Thinking.
I want to eat what she's eating!
[laughter]
Most of all, I love princess
Leia strangle you with a chain
At the end of return of the
Jedi.
Most of all.
I love you.
Oh, thank you.
Our next roaster is katey
Sega.
[applause]
You may remember her for her
Sitcom "married with children."
She's currently starring in sons
Of anarchy as vicious
Criminal.
She's finally here to kill her
Career.
Please welcome katey segal.
[applause]
Thank you, jane.
I have been a fan of your work
Since you were cutting down the
Redwood with your big blue ox.
I'm not sure if u know this,
But jane came out to her parents
In a letter.
There hasn't been a letter that
Unnecessary since the p in
Pneumonia.
Ellen barkin is here.
Ellen, you're a survivor.
When your second marriage fell
Apart, you didn't sit around
Feeling sorry for yourself.
You took your $40 million...
20.
Your $20 million
Settlement... whatever!
My kids think they're richer
Than we are.
You took all that money and
You paid someone else to sit
Around and feel sorry for you.
And amy schumer
You know, this business can
Really be tough on women.
Many of them develop eating
Disorders in an effort to be
Thin.
Just a suggestion.
[laughter]
Speaking of things that are
Thin, it's so good to see seth
Green.
Seth, you being here marks the
First time someo your size has
Beenn comedy central without
Jeff dunham's hand up their ass.
[laughter]
It's also reallyyoodo s
Wayne brady.
Wayne is kind of talented, kind
Of funny and kind of black meet.
And then there's jane lynch.
Jane, you were named one of
Power up's ten amazing gay women
In show biz.
Quite an honor even in there are
Only seven of you.
[laughter]
Jeff ross was also on the list
After they confused him for
Being a lesbian.
Ands will for being in show biz.
[laughter]
And I have to say it's great to
See roseanne back in the
Spotlight.
Thank you!
Thank you, katey.
I mean, you know, technically
It's two spotlights.
But you get the idea.
Roseanne was a trail-blazing
Comedy icon that created the
Character of an irrevent smart
Talking mom that nobody had ever
Seen sce I did it on "married
With children" the year before.
[cheers & applause]
Roseanne broke into the reality
World with "roseanne's nuts."
The show about her and johnny
Argent running a macadamia farm.
Roseanne, I feel honored that
You and I broke grou for tv
Moms that didn't cook, didn't
Clean and didn't make any money.
In the 90s, it makes you a bad
Mom.
Today it makes you mitt romney's
Wife.
[cheers & applause]
As an advocate for justi,
You're willi to speak for the
Voiceless many as well as the
Manyvoices.
All of whom are in your head.
Telling you to eat it, [bleep]
It, fire it or run for
President.
Roseanne, thank you so much for
Asking me to be a part of this.
Thank you!
Still to come, jeff ross.
You look so good in my joke
You night not work.
Carrie fisher and wayne
Brady.
I want you to tweet me.
I want to tweet you.
Let's do that.
I'm going to tweet you so h
[applause]
Our nxt roaster is jeff
Ross.
[applause]
Jeff jus finished a national
Score.
He's the only man that has
Jerked off in more theatershan
Fred willard.
Please, welcome the roastmaster
General, jeff ross!
[applause]
Yeah!
Fantastic!
Give it up for your host
Tonight, denis leary.
[laughter]
I think chris is here from
Lee."
This is so cool.
I love "glee."
Jane, it's my favorite show.
It is.
Except for the one time they let
You sing.
I haven't heard sounds that
Disturbing since I hung out in
Sandusky's basement.
Too soon for the "glee" joke?
[laughter]
Folks, if you're offended by
What you see tonight, just do
What joe paterno did.
Look the other way.
Again, jane, thanks for hosting.
You're probably the most beloved
Person in comedy right now.
Before the show, I even heard
The crowd chanting "lynch,
Lynch."
And that was just during wayne
Brady's introduction.
[laughter]
Please, is that wayne brady or
Didl jolson forget to take off
His makeup?
How did you make a career out of
Corporate teen-building
Exercises?
If you're just tuning in, no,
This is not a lifetime original
Movie.
[laughter]
Thank you.
Ellen barkin, you always been
Ahead of your time.
Voted hottest woman over 30 at
Age 36.
Carrie fisher, make yourself
Comfortable.
Chain yourself to roseanne's
Chair.
What does that mean?
I don't get that.
It's a [bleep] star wars
Joke.
Oh, I don't get it.
You should know.
You're dressed like yoda's
Grandma.
[laughter]
I'm telling you, this roast
Stuff doesn't take commercial
Breaks.
It takes a menopause.
[laughr]
And anthony, I'm hearing you're
Very excited about your new
Pilot.
John travolta.
[laughter]
I see the world's uglyist
[bleep] gilbert gottfried is
Here tonight.
You look like benjamin button
When he was 6.
[laughter]
Gilbert has kept a low profile
Since he was fired from aflec
For an insensitive tweet.
Gilbt, if you want an
Insensitive tweet, tweet about
Ellen barkin's makeup.
Too soon, too soon.
No, too good.
You look beautiful.
I have to hand it to you, you
Have been torchered and abused
All night and still hanging in
There.
Roseanne, I'm not talking to
You.
I'm talking about the chair
You're sitting on.
[laughter]
Oh, wait.
You know what?
Normally when I roast a pig, it
Has an apple in its mouth.
[laughter]
After our last roast, I said, we
Need someone bigger than charlie
Sheen.
This isn't what I meant.
[laughter]
Last year we roasted charlie.
This year we're roasting the
Chocolate factory.
What?
What is that joke?
You want me to explain the
[bleep] jokes to you?
I didn't hear it.
It means your fat.
Oh, okay.
I'm looking forward to your new
Show, "tons of anarchy."
Instead ofunning for
President, why don't you try
Walking on a treadmill?
[laughter]
I'd vote for you but I'm against
Big government.
[laughter]
Roseanne joined the green party
Because she was kicked out of
The tea party for eating all the
Crumpets.
[laughter]
Nice one!
How manyersonalities you
Have?
Eight, nine?
At are the odds they are all
[bleep]?
Comedy comes from pain, people.
And nobody knows tt better
Than this woman.
The legendary roseanne barr.
[cheers & applause]
She was molested as a child.
Oh, that poor molester.
[laughter]
Roseanne neverot over it.
She felt violated.
She had trust issues.
She never got the candy he
Promised her.
[laughter]
Roseanne, I'll always love you
For saying whatever you want,
For never holding back.
In these alarming times when
Comedians are second guessing
Their imaginations and sometimes
Even apologizing for jokes, I
Conside you a hero and a martyr
And a friend.
Thank you.
Thanks very much.
I love you.
[cheers & applause]
W, I'm going to take seth
Green and hit thshowers!
Up next, carrie fisher,
Anthony jeselnik and wayne
Brady.
That's one of the black
Handshake
[applause]
Our next roaster is wayne
Brady.
Wayne said he got his
Inspiration when he watched a
Summer camp production of "hello
Dolly" and thought that's what I
Want to do, be gay!
[laughter]
Please welcome wayne brady.
[applause]
Thank you so much, jane.
Now, this is comedy central.
Don't make me choke a butch.
Just saying.
Just saying
Just want to let you know.
There's no giving away of
Prizes, none of that stuff.
No making up songs.
I'm about to tell the truth on
This mother [bleep] stage here
Tonight.
I have to preach a little bit.
I have to preach.
Carriefisher.
Carrie, you're the only
Celebrity whose action figure is
Worth more than you are.
[applause]
Ellen barkin.
So good to see you.
You are hot.
So ellen, pture me, you, red
Wine, candlelight, a time
Machine.
[laughter]
No, I would [bleep] you.
And schumer, I wouldn't [bleep]
You.
I wouldn't [bleep] you if you
Used watermelon flavor flavorel
While watering a fried chicken g
String.
I wouldn't.
You couldn't get a black dude to
[bleep] you if you were on the
Set of a brand new tyler perry
Movie call "how to get black
Dude to [bleep] you."
[laughter]
That's okay.
That's all right.
Jeff ross.
Oh, by the way, those al jolson
Jokes go over big with kids.
Yeah.
You're current as [bleep].
[laughter]
Now, the thing is, jeff, these
Are all jokes and I really like
You.
Really, really like you but a
Lot of people hate you.
Especially sarah palin.
Because you remindmer of what
Trying is going to look like
When he's 40.
[laughter]
And... and now you boo me.
[bleep] you all.
I don't want to hear this.
You don't boo me because of
Trig.
And now to the reason we're all
Here.
Roseanne barr.
[applause]
You have overcome a lot to make
It in hollywood.
That's why I love you.
Bad marriages, mental illness,
Plus you look like roseanne.
[laughter]
You're oversized, beat up and
You wreak of marijuana.
That's seth ross.
You're kind of like willie
Nelson's tour bus, except people
Still want to ride that.
And now, all that being said, I
Really think that your a comedic
Gem and I thank you for letting
Me be here.
On behalf of intelligent
Brothers everywhere, you can
Suck my black [bleep].
Good night.
Thanks so much.
You're so funny.
Our next roaster is carrie
Fisher.
[applause]
She became famous with
Travelling into space.
Now she can be seen from it.
May the force help her get out
Of that seat, pase welcome
Carrie fisher!
Okay.
Thank you.
Ere's nothing funier than a
Good menstruation joke.
Unfortunately there hasn't been
Any tonight.
But okay.
So I'm carrie.
I'm a alcoholic.
Okay.
Roseanne... I can't say oops,
Wrong room!
Roseanne, when they first asked
Me to do the show tonight, I
Said y?
And then ty explained that we
Were good friends and that we
Apparently have worked together.
[laughter]
Did younow I wrote and episode
Of your show?
I do.
I didn't know that but...
[laughter]
It must be true.
Read it online next to the
Posting about how much I look
Like elton john.
[laughter]
As you may have noticed about
Me yes, I do have big tits buts
Will I'm mentally ill.
Yay!
Thank you, thank you.
Makes this a lot easier, believe
Me.
But you know, I'm not the only
One.
Jeff ross.
God, you give so much of
Yourself entertaining our troops
Overseas.
Not by doing standup.
They just like watching fat guys
Get out of helicopters.
There you go.
[laughter]
Eaking of electro convulsive
Therapy.
I learned two things tonight
Bumping into seth green back
Stage.
He is a big star wars fan.
And I apparently was in star
Wars.
[laughter]
So amazing!
That must have been great.
You know... now, wayne brady,
How a you?
You're so white that I tried to
Snort you back stage, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
[laughter]
Wow!
Now, I have seen gilbert
Gottfried at 12-step meetings.
He was not actually there.
They held a picture up of him
And they said, if you [bleep]
This man, a, how humiliating for
You and b, you must be a
Alcoholic.
[laughter]
At least I hope so.
Jane...
love yo carrie.
Oh, dear, I love you, too.
I do love you on "glee."
I do.
It's a change to see a coach
That doesn't take showers with
Little boys.
Hey, wait a mite!
What?
You're going to take exception
To that?
You did that joke.
No, no, no.
Not that?
N
I'moing to do another
Period joke and another white
Joke, short joke, old women
Joke.
[laughter]
Okay.
So...
[laughter]
Yeah.
[cheers & applause]
Hilarious!
Anthony jeselnik, I've heard
That you are a pretty gutsy guy.
You say what other rapists only
Think.
You don't get your period
Anymore, do you?
God, I could laugh about that
All night.
Now, I'm going to talk about
Someone I have a lot of history
With.
Someone who has always been
There for me... not really, but
Roseanne.
You know, roseanne and I, we're
Both feminists, am I right?
You're right.
[applause]
That's it.
You know, we think women can do
Anything that men can do.
In fact, we were discussing this
Earlier at the urinal.
Remember that?
[laughter]
Okay.
Roseanne, you battled the voices
In your head to become one of
The greatest comedians and
Become one of the greatest
Sitcom stars of all time.
If I had to come up with a
Reason why I love you so much,
It would have to be because I
Have done so much dope that I
Have no idea who the [bleep] you
Are.
Or who I am or where I am.
[laughter]
Thank you!
[cheers & applause]
Coming up, ellen bain.
I'm a stand up comic.
And anthony jeselnik.
Ur next roaster is an tony
Jeselnik.
[applause]
This fellow is famous for his
One-liners like "I never touched
Her."
"I have an alibi."
Or "talk to my lawyer
Clap your hands or pretend like
You recognize an tony jeselnik.
[applause]
Thank you, thank you.
When comedy central asked me to
Be here tonight, I told them to
[Suck mybleep].
Now I'm here.
[laughter]
Jane lynch, I love yourshow,
"glee."
No matter how I think it's going
To turn out, there's never a
School shooting.
My good friend jeff ross is all
Dressed up tonight.
Yeah, man.
Jeff, you look like something
A mongoliod kid put together at
Build a bear.
[laughter]
Katey segal.
Katey, you're a incredible
Actor.
You worked on "married with
Children."
A show that changed comedy.
"Sons of anarchy."
The show that took drama to a
New level.
And "eight simple rules".
The show that killed john
Ritter.
[laughter]
Wow!
Boo, bitches, boo!
Seth green is here
Everybody has that one weird
Creepy uncle?
Well, seth green looks like he
Got raped by all of them.
Ellen barkin, baby doll.
You're upcoming tv show, "the
New normal" premiers on
September 11.
Yeah.
September 11th.
That sounds about right.
[laughter]
I never thought of that!
Every clip I've seen feels
Like I'm watching a third tower
Collapse.
Suck it!
And wayne brady.
Wayne, I don't understand why
People keep joking that you're
Not black.
Wayne brady, you are black!
After all, I only remember you
For all of t years you played
An uppity slave on "whose line
Is it anyway."
[laughter]
I was good.
Now for the lady of honor,
Miss roseanne barr.
[cheers & applause]
Oh, boy, I can't wait!
Roseanne, your bid for
President was a failure.
You said that you'd like to
Become prime minister of israel
One day.
That could happen.
Those people are [bleep] idiots.
[laughter]
Roseanne, even though you're a
Feminist icon, so many men have
Gotten rich off of you.
Tom arnold, john goodman, the
Guy who owns the cheesecake
Factory.
[laughter]
And roseanne, you were knnotoris
For being a tyrant on your
Sitcom.
In fact, the entire cast and
Crew always had to wal on
Eggshells around you because you
Could not stop eating eggs.
Here's something positive.
You had gastric bypass surgery
In 1998 and then youeat it.
[cheers & applause]
But roseanne, despite everything
I just said, there's not a comic
Alive who doesn't owe a great
Debt to you.
You're a great sport for being
Here tonight.
Thank you for being here tonight
And letting me be here too.
Thank you.
Our next roaster is ellen
Barkin.
[cheers & applause]
Older vwers might noel len
From "diner" or "sea of love
Younger viewers might know her
From [bleep] her.
[laughter]
Ellen stars in the nbc sitcom
"the new normal" which critics
Are already describing as
Cancelled.
[laughter]
Ladies and gentlemen, please
Welcome ell barkin.
[cheers & applause]
Thank you, jane.
I had a cocktail before I came
On.
I admit it.
And then I had three more
Cocktails
[laughter]
And then I had a valium.
I was very scared and very
Intimidated by being surrounded
By real comedians here tonight.
Luckily the [bleep] jeff ross is
Here.
That was a relief.
I hear you have a n show.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Don't you think you should say
Thank you to roseanne for paving
The way for bus-size women for
Getting their own tv shows?
You're right.
[applause]
Katey, my little peg bundy.
Hi, len.
How does it feel to go
Through lifenown as that horny
Red head that could never get
Laid?
Seth green, same question.
[laughter]
And gilbert gottfried.
I am so glad you could take a
Break from starring directly
Into the sun to be with us
Tonight.
[laughter]
But now it's time to turn our
Attention to the sexiest [bleep]
Bitch on this stage.
Miss roseanne barr!
[cheers & applause]
Now, roseanne, I'm only here
Because shon stone dropped out
And w all know how hilarious
That [bleep].
[laughter]
Hat's not true.
Roseanne, it was very
Important for me to be here for
You.
Do you remember that [bleep]
Bitch that tweeted at me and
Called me a [bleep] crazele
Robbing washed up s-been pig
Who should find a man my own age
Instead of parading around with
Some boy toy that I would never
Get if I didn't used to be
Famous in the 80s?
In the end, roseanne, in my
Defense, she took to twitter and
She told that [bleep] bitch,
Shut the [bleep] up!
[cheers & applause]
Now, graned, I was with that
Woman's son at the time.
[laughter]
It was late and he did have
Homework that night.
But there was no way I was
Letting that little hairless
Play thing out ofy sandbox.
[laughter]
My frie, roseanne, you are a
Pionr.
You became an icon for female
Comics, for working mothers, for
All women.
And then you married that
Jittery coke head and you
[bleep] it all up.
[laughter]
Oh we.
I love you.
I love you too.
Thank you!
The comedy central roast of
Roseanne is brought to you by...
still to come, roseanne gets
A surprise visit from her ex.
This is the best for mat to
Do
[applause]
Wow!
Okay.
So I was just told we have a
Last-minute guest that stopped
By to say a few words.
Ladies and gentlemen, tom
Arnold.
[cheers & applause]
Oh shit.
She's right beside me, isn't
She?
You know, hi.
We... we have not been in the
Same room for over 18 ars.
Yay!
Yeah.
[applause]
I'm not here to tear roseanne a
New one.
Quite frankly, I've seen the old
One.
It is spectacular.
It could use little paint,
Maybe a couple plants in the
Corners, a wicker love seat.
Trust me, that baby is move-in
Ready!
[laughter]
Trt.
Why am I here?
Well, I'm here to honor roseanne
And I'm here because I [bleep]
Earned it the hard way.
[laughter]
Have any of you guys eve
Wrestled her?
Huh?
I have.
Has she sent any of you to pair
Mount to beat up anybody over
Fat jokes?
I did.
How many of you been arrested at
Lax for defending her singing?
This guy right here.
[laughter]
Have you ever had her pull a
Knife on you for spting on her
Diet cookies?
Yes.
That's right.
[laughter]
Have you ever been sucker
Punched in the face by her purse
In front of bob hope and his
Frickin' 90th birthday party?
Yes.
Not.
Yes, you did.
Yes, it's true.
At oneime we we obviously
Very, very close.
When I was with roseanne... and
She's talk about this a lot...
She had 27 personalities.
Only two of them liked me.
One of those was a small german
Boy.
[laughter]
Rosy and I were once
Inseparable.
We lived together, we worked
Together, we even got tattoos
Together.
You remember.
I got rosy's face tattooed on my
Chest.
Believe me, it's hard to get a
Woman to have sex with you when
[bleep] roseanne is staring at
Her.
True.
It's harder to masturbate.
[laughter]
You know, rosie, it's true.
She had "property only tom
Arnold" tattooe on her hip
Which made me the fourth largest
Prerty owner in california
[laughter]
Now that I'm allegedly sober and
We're both in stable
Relationips...
[laughter]
I want you to know, rosie,
There's no reason to be jealous
Of my wife, ashley.
She's tall and thin and wasn't
Born when we were married.
And I learned fromour mistake.
I made her sign a prenup.
That was so good.
Right.
[laughter]
I just want to say something
About yourboyfriend, johnny.
Johnny, I want to say this to
You, man.
No matter what, you have to stay
With this woman.
She maynot be the perfect wife
But she's the worst ex-wife on
The planet.
Literally!
[laughter]
You don't want to be a guy lying
On his couch with a date and
Hear how small your dick is on
"Saturday night live."
And then "the view."
And cnn and al-jazeera.
She holds a grudge, people!
You kw what?
Recently roseanne got in trouble
For accidentally wishing cancer
On chick-fil-a customers.
But...
[laughter]
Accidentally.
But you guys can all rela
If she had the power to wish
Cancer on anyone, I would have
Been [bleep] dead in 94.
You know, I met roseanne 30
Years ago.
You know?
Remember that?
That's right?
Yeah.
30 years ago.
First time I saw you perform I
Knew you were one of the
Greatest.
When I got off stage, you said
To me, you sure are a funny son
Of a bitch.
I said thanks.
You want to do some blow.
We sold the car and disappeared
For three days.
Do you remember that?
And so began our white trash
Melot.
For one brief shining moment.
In 1985, roseanneent on johnny
Carson, which was every comic's
Dream.
She killed, he laughed his ass
Off, game her a thumb's up and
Invited her to sit on the couch.
She g validation from the king
That can never be taken away
From you.
[applause]
And I just want to say that
Roseanne, youere my johnny
Carson.
And thank you for the thumbs up.
Thank you forllowing me to sit
On your couch for a little bit.
Good night.
[applause]
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
And you know...
yeah.
Onward we go right?
I know.
Good look.
A[applause]
Our next roaster is gilbert
Gottfried.
Now, gilbert is famous not so
Much for his comedy but for
Pissing off more asian people
Than hiroshima.
Ease welcome that scary kid,
Gilbert gottfried.
[applause]
Jane lynch!
Ladies and gentlemen, I hope you
Can hear the sound of my voice.
This microphone is covered by
The thick layer of pubic hairs
That shot from between jane's
Teeth.
[laughter]
During the commercial brea,
The produers wipe away the pelt
Of saliva-coated pubes that
Accumulate upon the mic.
And each time jane returns to
The stage, she once again sprays
A carpetf short, pearly hairs
All over the microphone and the
Front row of the nauseated
Dience members.
So forgive me if my voice is,
Shall we say, muffled.
[laughter]
Carrie fisher!
Thank you for visiting us from
The past.
[laughter]
Comedy central looked at
This dais they said we just
Don't have enough washed up,
Repuant, drug-addicted
Menopausal has-beens.
Get me carrie fisher!
[laughte
Because if there's anything
We're certain of it's that
Carrie fisher is available.
[laughter]
- D2 has gotten more work from
Star wars than carrie fisher.
But tonight isn't about carrie
Fisher or jeffs or any of
The other diseased-ridden
Transients that were forced from
Their shanties and refrigerator
Box dwellings to be here.
[laughter]
Tonight we honor a monster in
The entertainment industries.
And like most monsters, she goes
By one name, and that name is
Rozilla.
[cheers & applause]
Rozilla!
She's been descrid aseing
Covered with a thick layer of
Scaly gray skin.
Emitting a strong disgusting
Odor of taco grease and ass
Cheese.
[laughter]
Her sharp yellow teeth can take
A man's arm off in one bite if
You are foolish enough to try
And feed the beast her mountain
Of pork crackling and one
Slimfast candy bar.
Rozilla!
Stomping through hollywood for
Decades, breathing fire from her
Hairy snout, burning bridge
After bridge, her glowing red
Eyes striking terror in the
Art of anyone unfortunate
Enough to look in her hideous
Face.
[laughter]
Gnarled cow-like hooves...
Crushing and destroying
Everything in her path.
Stopping only to feed every ten
Minutes and make one sitcom
Decades ago.
Her rolls of fat swaying and
Crashing like a japanese
Moonami.
[laughter]
Let me just stop for a second
And go on the record about
Moonami.
[laughter]
One should never spoke about
Moonami.
One should never joke about
Moonamis.
And most important of all, one
Should never tweet aut
Moonamis.
[applause]
But if one were to tweet about a
Moonami, he's probably learned
His lesson by now and should get
His endorsement deal back.
[cheers & applause]
So he won't have to keep doing
These horrible [bleep] roasts.
Rozilla!
Or as she's known in tokyo,
[laughter]
Tonight it's our chance to end
The reign of rozilla forever.
And don't forget about the tail.
Powerful enough to sweep an
Entire ox into her throbbing
Colon.
People always forget about the
Tail.
They say, let's get rozilla.
I say but what about the tail?
Ey never remember the tail.
[laughter]
Those people have paid the
Ultimate price.
And if all else fails, remember
Good people, blame it on the
Jews.
[laughter]
And now for dumb jokes.
A drunken farmer stumbles
Upstairs into his bedroom.
Waking his wife, roseanne.
She sees her husband holding a
Sheep under his arm.
The farmer yells, "this ishe
Big I've been [bleep]."
Roseanne says, you idiot.
These not a pig.
It's a sheep.
The farmer yells, shut the
[bleep] up.
I was talking to the sheep.
[laughter]
[cheers & applause]
Thank you.
Good night!
[cheers & applause]
He must have a small dick
Because he has to act like that.
Coming up, reanne goes off.
Roseanne, 2012!
The comedy central roast of
Roseanne is brought to you by
Klondike and taco bell.
And now, it's finally time to
Unleash our guest of honor.
[cheers & applause]
An icon, a superstar, a woman
Whose balls are as big as her
Mouth.
Roseanne chased the face of
Television and then changed her
Face.
She's told so many people to
Kiss her ass, it could take
Until the next decades to get it
Done.
And now tell everybody to go
[bleep] themselves.
Ladies and gentlemen, roseanne!
[cheers & applause]
Hey, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank a lot.
Greetings roseanne-archists.
[cheers & applause]
I just want to say to all of my
Peers, when comedy central calls
You and tells you they want to
Honor you, and they will, just
Hang the [bleep] up.
I got a dais half full of
[bleep] losers.
I've seen people in front of
Home depot less desperate for
Work.
[laughter]
All I know is I better get my
God damn parking validated or
Some ass hole is getting fired!
[apause]
Where the hell are the stars?
Christ, I must have pissed off
Everybody I've ever known.
I had a number 1 network show!
I was in a movie with meryl
Streep.
And I get amy [bleep] schumer?
[laughter]
Meryl streep won three oscars.
This bitch came in fourth on
"last comic standing."
[laughter]
Thank you for your votes.
But I guess you people are
The only ones that can take the
Roseanne retort.
Since I am the meanest, baddest
Bitch on earth.
[cheers & applause]
Thank you.
[laughter]
And that is the reason why I'm
Running for president of ese
God damn United States of
America!
[cheers & applause]
That's right.
Put that in your [bleep] pipe
And smoke it, you honky [bleep].
Obama will get my weed when he
Pries it out of my cold dead
Fingers.
[cheers & applause]
Thank got for jane lynch.
You are one ferocous bitch.
I love you so much.
The most revolutionary character
On television.
But I hate you because you are
Thin.
But I guess I'd be thin too if
All I ever ate was [bleep].
[laughter]
But I love this about you.
I really do.
Ellen barkin, wow!
I thought you were dead!
[laughter]
Sweet!
So glad to see you.
But I said I wanted that butchy
Blond named ellen, I meant
Degeneres.
Carrie fisher, the literary
Voice of a generation.
I'm your biggest fan.
What a career you've had.
Actress, writer, drug mule.
[laughter]
Seth green, I don't want to
Overlook you, which is easy for
Anyone over 5 feet tall.
Jan lynch has vibrators bigger
Than you, seth.
She can use it.
The only difference is, they
Can give a woman an orgasm.
[laughter]
Wayne brady, you have
Single-handedly redefined improv
By scripting it.
[laughter]
You can do anything with an
Audience suggestion.
Here's one for you.
Get the [bleep] off the stage.
[laughter]
Y schumer, thanks for
Reinforcing the stereotype that
Women ain't funny.
Actually, I just loved your
Set.
I think you're [bleep]great.
I loved it.
Amy schumer.
[laughter]
An tony jeselnik.
You know the different between
Anthony and a gay porn actor,
Judging but your looks and how
Much you sucked tonight, none.
[laughter]
Jeff ross.
Jeff ross is the third-rate
Comedians to what kim kardshian
Is to no-talent fame whores.
Hero!
[applause]
Gilbert gottfried.
You know, the difrence between
Gilbert's voice and a sandpaper
Dildo?
Do you?
[laughter]
After 20 minutes, you might
Start enjoying the dildo.
[lahter]
And hence the difference.
And last but not least, tom
Arnold.
I'd really like to thank tom for
Showing uptonight.
It was very brave.
And he was very funny.
But jesus christ, ow much
[bleep] jobs do I have to get
For that guy?
This night has been one of the
Greatest nights of my life.
That's not saying shit for my
Life.
[laughter]
No but it was a blast, you
Guys.
Thanks to the audience, too.
Laughing.
There's nothing better than a
Good laugh.
Nothing on earth.
And here is the teachabl moment
Tonight.
If I can bury my royaling
Boiling creaseless hatred for
The likes of tomarnold, maybe
There's a chance that we can
Have world peace, ladies and
Gentlemen.
[cheers & applause]
But the truth is, I would gladly
Give up even that dream if I
Could just sing.
[cheers & applause]
ｶ o'er the land of the free ｶ
ｶ and the home of the brave ｶ
[cheers & applause]