Pika.
Pi.
Pikachu.
Well, Pikachu, we're here.
lt's a Pokémon paradise.
-This looks like tons of fun.
-Yeah, the Pokémon love it.
Just keep your eye on
Togepi, okay, Pikachu?
Come on, come on, come on
Let's go
Vacation, need a little sun
I'm going to get my friends
together and have a little fun
Ain't nobody going to
tell us what we going to do
Because today it's up to me and you
Temptation calling out to me
A little relaxation I'll be free to be
Come on and wicky-wicky lou
I do believe it'll start now
Kick it back to the track
Vacation's where I want to be
Buddy on the beach
where the fun is free
We don't need a holiday
to start to celebrate
Repeat after me: I need a vacation
Let's go
Vacation's where I want to be
Buddy on the beach
where the fun is free
We don't need a holiday
to start to celebrate
Because I need a break,
I need a vacation
Vacation's where I want to be
Buddy on the beach
where the fun is free
Pokédex observation unit
now activating.
My function: Monitor
Pokémon activity...
...to understand behavioral
patterns of the Pokémon...
...when they are in a state
of total relaxation.
Togepi, the Egg Pokémon.
It exhibits a low
tolerance for hunger.
It is able to communicate this
condition in a very effective manner.
Pika, Pika. Pikachu.
Squirt.
Saur.
Psy.
Bulbasaur
Bulba, bulba
This is the first known recording
of ''Bulbasaur's Bulbabye. ''
Bellsprout.
Activating Pokémon database.
Snubble, a newly discovered Pokémon.
A Ground-type Pokémon, Cubone.
Cubone-bone-bone.
Cubone-bone-bone-bone.
Raichu, the evolved form of Pikachu.
Marril.
Marril, a Water-type Pokémon.
Snub.
Rai.
-Squirtle.
-Bulbasaur.
Pokémon do not battle unless
directed by their trainers.
Translation activated.
''Let's set a good example
for the baby. ''
lKarp.
Togepi.
Slooooooooow.
Pokémon enjoy competition,
but not always in Pokémon battles.
It's not uncommon for Pokémon to
challenge each other in contests.
Oh come on, try to catch me
Oh catch me if you can
-Exeggutor.
-Oddish.
Pikachu and Raichu are both
Mouse Pokémon of the electric variety.
Combined voltage approaching
shockingly dangerous levels.
This is the perfect place
for a comfy catnap.
What's that?
What's the rush?
Farfetch'd, Farfetch'd....
Hitmonlee.
Chansey, Chansey.
lKeep it down!
Mag.
Magne. Ma.
Magnemites!
Cubone earned its classification
as the Lonely Pokémon...
...from its usual attitude
of caring only...
...for itself.
l told you to keep quiet!
Well, this ought to
shut you all up, you--
Duck.
l think l'll take my nap right here.
Good night.
Preliminary analysis: Pokémon,
by nature, are friendly creatures...
...and prefer cooperation
to confrontation.
Final conclusion:
Despite earlier uncertainties...
...Pokémon vacations are
highly recommended.
Pokédex observation unit
now deactivating.
Pikachu, it's time to leave!
Goldeen! Staryu! Psyduck!
Come on back!
Geodude! Onix! Zubat!
Vulpix! We got to go!
Did you have fun?
Life.
The great miracle and
the great mystery.
Who am I?
Since the beginning...
...humans and Pokémon alike
have searched for its meaning.
What am I? What am I?
Many strange and wondrous
legends evolved...
...from the pursuit
of life's mysteries.
Where am I? Where am I?
But none is stranger
than this tale...
...of the most powerful
Pokémon of all.
I am ready...
...to be, to be....
Where...
...am I?
This is not the same.
Was everything before just a dream?
Why?
-Doctor, look at this.
-What?
lts brain waves, they're surging!
-Let me see!
-She's right!
-Let's run another scan.
-lts mind is racing!
Those voices.
l hope we don't lose this one!
They're outside.
We can't!
Where I must be.
Tell Giovanni what's happened!
Quiet!
Let us hear its psychic powers.
Psychic powers?
For years we struggled to successfully
clone a Pokémon to prove our theories.
You're the first specimen to survive!
That is Mew, the rarest of all Pokémon.
From its DNA we created you, Mewtwo.
Mewtwo?
Am l only a copy?
Nothing but Mew's shadow?
You are greater than Mew.
lmproved through the power
of human ingenuity.
We used the most advanced techniques
to develop your psychic powers.
So l am simply the end
result of your experiment.
What becomes of me now?
Our experiment isn't over!
lt's just beginning!
Now the serious testing begins.
These humans, they care
nothing for me.
Congratulations. We've
done an excellent job.
-We'll observe Mewtwo for mutations.
-ls the new tank ready?
We'll have to come up
with a cage for it.
Excellent. We'll start testing.
Is that my purpose?
Am Ijust an experiment?
A laboratory specimen?
This cannot be my destiny!
We dreamed of creating
the world's strongest Pokémon...
...and we succeeded.
Behold my powers.
l am the strongest Pokémon in the world.
Stronger even than Mew.
Those fools thought you
were a science experiment...
...but l see you as
a valuable partner.
Partner?
With your psychic powers
and my resources...
...together we can control the world.
l do not need your help
for that, human.
A wildfire destroys
everything in its path.
lt will be the same with your
powers unless you control them.
l can help you do that.
How?
l'll show you a way
to focus your powers...
...that will make you invincible.
Show me!
You say this armor protects my body...
...yet it suppresses my powers!
Your powers are not being
suppressed. They're being focused.
Learn to use them to
accomplish your purpose.
What is that?
Patience, my friend. Your
purpose will become clear.
So this is my power.
l am in control now.
Alakazam!
lKazam!
But why am l here?
Now l fully perceive my power.
But what is my purpose?
To serve your master.
You were created to fight for me.
That is your purpose.
That cannot be.
You said we were partners.
We stood as equals.
You were created by humans
to obey humans.
You could never be our equal.
Humans may have created me...
...but they will never enslave me.
This cannot be my destiny!
Stop this now!
l was not born a Pokémon!
l was created.
My creators have used and betrayed me.
So l stand alone.
Who am l?
What is my true reason for being?
l will find my own purpose.
And purge this planet
of all who oppose me.
Human and Pokémon alike.
The world will heed my warning.
The reign of Mewtwo will soon begin.
Today, Ash, Brock and Misty are taking
a break from their Pokémon adventures.
As always, Ash is determined
to become a Pokémon master.
And, as always, he's ready to endure
any hardship, bear any burden...
...with strength, stamina
and a will of steel.
Hungry. Need food.
Oh, Ash! You haven't
done a thing all day!
l'm too weak to work, Misty.
l haven't eaten since breakfast.
This lunch is going to
be just perfect for you.
lt's my lazy-boy ''no-chew'' stew.
You there! l'm looking for a Pokémon
trainer named Ash from Pallet Town.
-You know him?
-Yeah, he's me.
Let's have a match.
Unless you're afraid to lose!
l'm afraid you're going
to lose this one!
Ash, you just said you
were too weak to work!
l am too weak to work, but
a Pokémon battle isn't work!
That's progress. At least
his mouth is working.
I want to be the very best
Like no one ever was
To catch them is my real test
To train them is my cause
I will travel across the land
Searching far and wide
Teach Pokémon to understand
The power that's inside
Inside Pokémon
It's you and me
I know it's my destiny
You're my best friend
And the world we must defend
Our hearts are true
Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you
Pokémon
Got to catch them,
got to catch them all
Great job, Bulbasaur! You did it!
You can challenge along the way
Encourage our faith
I will battle everything
About the place
Come with me, the time is right
There's no better team
Arm in arm we'll win the fight
It's always been our dream
It's you and me
I know it's my destiny
You are my best friend
In a world we must defend
A heart so true
Our courage will pull us through
You teach me and I'll teach you
Got to catch them
Got to catch them all
We did it!
Well, that sure was a shocking ending.
Shocking that Ash moved so fast.
Another credit on Pikachu's
''charge account!''
We've got to grab it!
l know we must grab rare
Pokémon for the Boss...
...but it wouldn't be a bad idea
if we grabbed a bite to eat.
We didn't come here to steal a meal!
l'd settle for a taste
of that Pika-chow.
l'm starving.
l can cook something.
The last time you cooked, you
wiped out eight of my nine lives.
Master, shall l extend an
invitation to these trainers as well?
As you wish.
Watch where you're flying.
Something for me?
Greetings, Pokémon trainers.
I bear an invitation.
She's really small,
but really pretty!
You've been chosen to join a group of
Pokémon trainers at a gathering.
It will be hosted by my master, the
world's greatest Pokémon trainer...
...at his palace on New Island.
A ferry will leave Old Shore Wharf...
...to take you to the island
this afternoon.
Only trainers with this
invitation will be admitted.
If you decide to attend,
you must reply at once.
My master awaits you.
ls there a rewind button?
-Should we go?
-Of course! l've got to meet her!
l guess the world's number-one trainer
wants to challenge me to a match!
-We've got to let him know right away.
-l'm saying yes!
What's so special about
the twerp trio's special delivery?
Hey, look!
''Yes''? To what?
Raticate!
Chill out, Raticate!
lKingler! Save your energy!
This is going to be so cool!
Officer Jenny, report to
the ferry entrance.
Officer Jenny to
Togepi's totally soaked!
l can't believe how
fast the storm came up.
What?! The ferry is canceled?!
But l've got to get to New lsland!
-lt's only a little rain!
-lt's more than just rain.
The harbor manager thinks
this could be the worst storm ever.
Listen to me.
The prophets have predicted
the return of the Winds of Water.
For years...
...l prayed mankind would never
witness that deadly storm ever again.
lsn't that just a legend?
Ancient writings tell of the storm
wiping out all but a few Pokémon.
ln their sorrow...
...the water of their tears restored
the lives lost in the storm.
But there are no Pokémon tears today.
Just waters which no one can survive.
That's why the ferry
has been canceled.
l'm going to New lsland anyway!
All my Pokémon are Water-type!
We'll just swim over to that palace!
l warn you, the waves will
be savage! You will never make it!
lf you try that stunt and
your Pokémon got hurt...
...you'd be out of luck because
we closed the Pokémon Center.
How come?
The nurse in charge of
the center disappeared last month.
lf any of you see her,
please contact me at once.
That's a picture of her
over there on the wall.
She's cute.
She sure looks familiar.
Come back here, or
l'll place you under arrest!
Come back!
Some trainers have no fear.
To them, this is just
one more challenge.
They follow their hearts.
That is what sets them apart
and will make them Pokémon masters.
Good luck to all of you.
The world's greatest Pokémon
master is waiting for me.
Let's use our Pokémon
to get to that island.
Our Pokémon aren't strong enough.
They can't handle waves like this.
Guess you're right.
You vant to cross maybe?
Ve take you?
Ve Vikings are used to big vaves.
Ve get you to New lsland faster
than you can say fahrvergnügen.
Stroke!
Stroke! Stroke!
l think l'm going to have one.
-l didn't know Vikings still existed.
-They mostly live in Minnesota.
Something's not right.
Are you sure this boat's safe?
Don't vorry. This ship
von't let you down.
Ve alvays sail in da
rough veather. Don't get upset.
Tell my stomach.
Heave! Heave! Heave!
lt's all right, Togepi.
We're going to be okay.
-Those aren't Vikings.
-lt's Team Rocket.
l knew there was something fishy
about them besides the smell!
-Prepare for trouble.
-Make it double.
Forget the motto.
We're going to have to....
Ash! Misty!
-Have you seen Ash and Pikachu?
-Not yet.
Stay together. lt's our only hope.
Look!
My master bids you
welcome to New lsland.
lKindly present your invitation.
Here it is, miss.
The bearers of this invitation may
be admitted.
l knew l recognized that face.
What?
Aren't you the nurse
from the treatment center?
You do look just like her.
l fear you are mistaken.
l've always dwelt on this island
and been in the service of my master.
Please, come this way.
My master awaits your arrival.
With you here, all trainers...
...worthy of an audience with
my master are present.
There's only three of them.
Aren't we waiting for the others?
Only the trainers capable
of braving the storm...
...are worthy in my master's eyes.
Do you mean that storm
was some kind of test?
Release your Pokémon from
their Pokéballs and join the others.
lt won't be long before
my master's intentions are clear.
Now we'll never know what
kind of party we're missing!
We'll just have to crash that party.
-You know another way in?
-Look over there.
But how are we going
to swim up that thing?
Pretend you're a catfish.
-Something wrong, Jessie?
-No. Come on. Let's get going.
l think this plan's all wet.
Psy-ya-ya duck.
What took you guys so long?
How did you get here?
l decided to fly over.
lt was easy.
Hurricane winds are
a breeze for Pidgeotto here.
Guys, say hello.
Those are my Pokémon.
lt was no problem
getting through that storm.
l rode over on Gyarados' back.
l heard it takes a lot
of skill to train Gyarados.
Yes, but once you train it, it's
the most dependable Pokémon there is.
You haven't met my
Pokémon. Over there.
You are about to meet my master.
The time has come to encounter
the greatest Pokémon master on Earth.
What's that?
Yes. The world's greatest
Pokémon master...
...is also the most
powerful Pokémon on Earth.
This is the ruler of New lsland
and soon the whole world.
Mewtwo.
A Pokémon can't be
a Pokémon master! No way!
Quiet, human. From now on,
l am the one who makes the rules.
-How's it talking?
-lt's psychic.
We'll show you! Let's go, Gyarados!
Gyarados, Hyper-Beam attack!
Gyarados!
Child's play.
Your usefulness has ended.
Nurse Joy!
Where am l? And how
in the world did l get here?
You have been under my control.
l transported you here
from the Pokémon center.
Your knowledge of Pokémon
physiology proved useful to my plan.
l have cleansed your tiny human
brain of memories from the past weeks.
Who are you?!
l am the new ruler of this world...
...the master of humans
and Pokémon alike.
You're just a bully!
Look at these.
They're Pokémon.
Are they real?
l was hoping there'd be a party.
This is the Pokémon replication
system. System activated.
Pokémon based on genetic analysis.
Pokémon DNA sampling
sequence now in progress.
Put me down.
What are you--? Let go!
-Help!
-Grab him!
Help me!
l made it. But just by a hair.
Look, there's your hair.
Analyzing Pokémon biomaterial sample.
Analysis complete.
Pokémon identified.
Begin replication sequence.
-Who's that Pokémon?
-lt's Meowth.
Meowth!
But l'm Meowth.
-So is the one in the tank.
-Your clone.
I haven't got much time.
I pray this record of
our experiment survives.
A year ago we discovered...
...the remains of
the ancient Pokémon, Mew.
There was sufficient
genetic material to replicate Mew.
Giovanni insisted on super-clones...
...more powerful than
any living Pokémon.
Finally our experiments
proved successful.
We produced a living Pokémon.
We called it Mewtwo.
But the creature's anger
is out of control.
With its psychic powers,
it's destroying our laboratory.
We dreamed of creating
the world's strongest Pokémon...
...and we succeeded.
-Sounds like a real Pokénstein.
-Sure does.
One bad cat!
So this must be the lab.
But if Mewtwo destroyed it....
-Somebody rebuilt it.
-Yes, but who?
You humans are a dangerous species.
You brought me into your world
with no purpose but to be your slave.
But now l have my own purpose.
My storm will create my own world...
...by destroying yours.
So you hate all humans? And you're
going to destroy us to save Pokémon.
No.
Your Pokémon will not be spared.
They have disgraced
themselves by serving humans.
Those Pokémon are nothing but slaves.
So, you say l am wrong?
You are not this human's servant?
You are his friend?
You are as pathetic as the rest.
Humans and Pokémon
can never be friends.
Are you okay?
Don't pick on Pikachu.
lf you are Pokémon, there's
no reason l can't capture you.
Go, Rhyhorn.
-No! Rhyhorn!
-Fools!
Your Pokémon attacks cannot
weaken me. My powers are too great.
No trainer can conquer me.
You won't mind proving it
in a real match!
ls that a challenge?
You bet it is!
They're awake!
Blast.
Saur.
-l'm scared.
-Me too.
Like most Pokémon trainers...
...l too began with Charmander,
Squirtle and Bulbasaur.
But for their evolved forms...
...l used their genetic material
to clone even more powerful copies.
-Copies!
-They're clones.
A stadium! Mewtwo
planned this all along.
Your fake Venusaur
can't beat my real one!
Right, Bruteroot?
We'll blow away that Blastoise,
won't we Shellshocker?!
lt may not have a nickname,
but l do have a Charizard.
l choose you!
Charizard, l didn't say start.
Your Charizard is poorly trained.
Which of you will oppose me first?
Saur.
l underestimated you last time,
but that won't happen again!
Go, Bruteroot! Razor Leaf!
Vine Whip.
Bruteroot!
lt looks like l'm up.
Go, Shellshocker!
Blastoise.
Blast.
Shellshocker, Hydro Pump!
Shellshocker!
You better forfeit, Ash.
Those clones are too powerful.
l'm not giving up.
Charizard, use your speed,
not power, and you'll win.
All right, go!
-Can't Charizard move any quicker?
-The clone is too fast.
-Charizard's in trouble!
-Finish it.
No, Charizard! No!
Are you okay?
As the victor, l now claim my prize:
Your Pokémon.
Wait!
What will you do with those Pokémon?!
l will extract their DNA
to make clones for myself.
They will remain safe
on this island...
...while my storm destroys the planet.
You can't do this!
Yes, Mewtwo! We won't let you!
Do not attempt to defy me.
This is my world now.
Let's go!
Gyarados!
l know!
Mewtwo can't catch them
if they're inside their Pokéballs.
Bulbasaur, Squirtle, return!
lt's no use.
lt's futile to try
and escape my power.
Never mind the Pokéballs.
Carry them away!
Give back my Psyduck!
Vulpix!
Run, Pikachu!
lKeep running, Pikachu!
You're not going to get Pikachu!
There goes Alakazam.
Dewgong.
Vileplume.
Sandshrew. Nidoqueen. Vaporeon.
But me, l got a special
place in my tail for this one.
Look there!
l don't have time for
your dumb motto today.
Who's that Pokémon? lt's Pikachu!
Let go! Stupid machine.
Give me back my Pikachu!
What's happening?
l'm so glad you're okay.
The copies are hatching!
-They're fabulous fakes!
-Send in the clones!
But where are the real ones?
-l wonder if they feel....
-Clonesome?
The Poké originals!
Squirtle's back!
You're all okay!
Humans, you have served my purpose.
l am sparing your lives,
for the moment.
But you cannot escape your fate.
The hour of my vengeance draws near.
Behold!
With Pokémon and humans eliminated...
...the clones shall inherit the world.
You can't do this. l won't let you.
-lt's Ash!
-All right!
-Psyduck!
-Vulpix!
lt is useless to challenge me.
lt's not going to end like this,
Mewtwo. We won't let it.
You're mine!
-Ash, no!
-Look out!
What?
Can it be?
-What is that?
-l don't know.
Mew. So finally we meet.
l may have been
cloned from your DNA...
...but l will prove that Mewtwo
is better than the original.
Superior to Mew.
Mew and Mewtwo!
So Mewtwo was cloned from Mew.
This world is too small for two of us.
Why do you flee from me?
Are you afraid to
find out which of us is greater?
So you do have some fight in you.
But l have no time for games.
Destiny is at hand.
Who will rule? My super Pokémon?
Or your pathetic group
of spineless inferior Pokémon?
We were created with powers
far stronger than the originals.
-Mew's got a good point.
-What's it saying?
You don't prove anything by
showing off a lot of special powers.
And that a Pokémon's
real strength comes from the heart.
My clones don't need
their powers to prove their worth.
l will block all the Pokémon's
special abilities...
...using my psychic powers.
Now we shall see who triumphs. Go!
Pokémon aren't meant to fight.
Not like this.
lt's useless.
What can come out of it?
Nothing but pain.
Can't Mewtwo understand it's
not right to force Pokémon to battle?
They're all living creatures.
This just proves
that fighting is wrong.
l was prepared for trouble,
but not for this.
Make that double for me.
Now l can see how
horrible fighting really is.
Even the best of friends
will fight sometimes.
l'll promise never to
fight again if you will.
What am l doing?
Let's get something straight!
You-owth ain't pushing Meowth around.
You mean, we don't have
to fight with each other?
But how can l trust you?
You was born different.
l almost made a clawful mistake.
How do l know you're not
going to pull a fast one on me?
You're right, we
do have a lot in common.
The same earth, the
same air, the same sky.
Maybe if we started
looking at what's the same...
...instead of always looking at
what's different, who knows?
Quit it! Please, stop!
Are you okay?
We got to stop this.
How? Mewtwo wants to prove
how strong those super-clones are.
l'd rather risk my life
out in Mewtwo's storm...
...than watch Pokémon
destroy each other.
Me too.
l wish there were some way to
stop them. l don't know what to do.
l don't think they'll ever stop.
Those Pokémon are ready
to fight to the death.
That's a fight that
nobody's going to win.
Someone's got to take a stand.
Someone's got to say no
and refuse to fight.
Just like Pikachu.
Ash, wait!
You've got to stop right now!
Stop!!
Oh, no!
Fool, trying to stop our battle.
Please, no!
The human sacrificed
himself to save the Pokémon.
l pitted them against each other.
Only when they set aside
their differences...
...did l see the true power
they all share deep inside.
l see now that the circumstances
of one's birth are irrelevant.
lt is what you do with
the gift of life...
...that determines who you are.
Mewtwo, where are you going?
Where my heart can learn
what yours knows so well.
What transpired here,
l will always remember.
But perhaps for you,
these events are best forgotten.
-This could be the worst storm ever.
-You must listen to me.
You have got to find shelter.
Excuse me, please.
The Pokémon Treatment Center
will open as a shelter.
Anyone who needs a place
to stay should come with me.
Nurse Joy and Officer Jenny
are really great.
They keep getting more beautiful
every time l see them.
Guys, how did we wind up
in this place anyway?
Well, l guess we're
just here because we're here.
Yes, let's eat.
Look, it's a miracle!
l can't believe it.
-The storm disappeared.
-That's so weird!
lt's good to have things clear again.
What's that?
What's what?
-l don't see anything, Ash.
-Except the sky.
The day l started
my Pokémon journey...
...l saw a really rare Pokémon.
And just now, l thought
l saw another one.
Maybe you're just seeing things, Ash.
Maybe he's not.
Maybe we'll see.
Many strange legends
surround the mysteries of Pokémon.
Just as many adventures
await our heroes...
...as they continue on their quest.
For Ash and his friends,
the journey's just begun.
l don't know how we
got here, but who cares?
-This is paradise!
-For once, a happy ending.
Team Rocket's signing off again!
Have any unscreen?
I'd really like to go sailing
in one of them catamarans.