Moments... This is one.
Right here, right now, is definitely a time
.
Tessa?
Anything can happen at once.
- Tessa!
- What?
- You're not listening.
- If I'm listening.
- What did I just say?
- I was not listening...
He said that this is a big night for you
.
- Number one on the list.
- There is no list.
But you do list.
I have not started.
Start now.
Go!
Claro, which is what you want,
truth does not bother me.
- The blonde.
- The blonde? Are you sure?
- You want it?
- Like I said, I do not care.
- You can have the blonde.
- Only if you're sure...
- So...
- What baby?
If I do this with someone who does not know
.
Does that make me a slut?
It makes you feel alive.
So this club...
Do you always go?
No. .. Do you?
Sometimes.
Sure...
Is there another side we can go?
Do you want a cup of tea or coffee?
Sure if... Anything.
Do not have coffee...
Okay.
- I can not find the tea...
- A little water is fine.
- So... What is your favorite...
- Do you want to kiss me?
I can?
Jesus Christ!
Okay!
- Jesus Christ!
- It's okay!
- What happened?
- Got out the hair.
Did you laugh?! It's not funny!
So what usually disguised sales?
How fake hair?
Not get anything, so.
- Just as I am.
- Really?
Right.
Not supposed to do that, a little longer?
Not think so.
Wait... Can you look at me for a second
?
It's my first time.
Wow that's amazing!
Obviously not yours.
Stop talking already.
Yes, well no.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Not going to happen.
Are you kidding?
- You get this far and...
- I'm sorry, really.
Whatever.
Okay...
Okay.
- Thanks.
Do not understand. I just do not understand
always tell me everything.
- I never say anything.
- Why not start now?
What were you doing last night.
Dad keeps asking,
for 15 th time is a charm.
Hi, I'm Caroline, producer.
Spoke on the phone.
- Hello, it's good to meet you in person.
- And she should be Tessa!
Me.
The elevator is not working,
mind using the stairs?
- Yes, you are right.
- Okay.
Tessa Scott and his father.
- Hi guys.
- Hello.
- Sit.
- I'm happy to be here.
- Yes, we are big fans.
- Great, let's talk a bit.
Most natural
and I can help you. Right?
What angle will be?
Is this "girl dying"
Original or have something planned?
- Excuse me?
- Tessa!
I know it's difficult, but try to keep him quiet
, OK?
And now I am delighted to have as my...
... Guest in the studio, a very brave young lady
...
Tessa Scott Tessa
has lived with leukemia for the past four years.
Y is here with his dad,
to talk about it.
Tell us, when you realized that Tessa was ill
?
4 years ago, her mother and I think she had the flu
.
But flu would not leave,
blood test confirm our worst fear.
They said there was
chance to survive.
The point is, Tessa said...
... Had no choice, more
than chemo therapy.
Tessa So, you decided to stop treatment
,
that's a big decision,
for a 17 years.
If I could... The more aggressive treatments
,
only have prolonged the life of Tessa, slightly.
There are other ways to maintain their health.
- Dad... - For example, studies show that
good nutrition...
Can replace a system entirely.
's Why we
here, really...
- Dad!
- What?
He's going to have to stop at some point
.
Tessa Stop what?
He knows he has to go.
But
can not help but wait, that does not happen.
Is true that if I continue with the chemo therapy
,
probably live a little longer.
But I feel very bad.
And there are things I want
do before dying.
Things?
If... I have a list.
- Oh! Your dad did not mention that.
- Is why it does not know.
Most of what I want, is illegal.
But mostly I have sex last night.
Which is
something against the law, of course.
But it was so bad, the guy should be arrested
equally.
Okay...
I think it's all we have time for.
I plan to take drugs too, do you have any advice for
which should take?
- That's enough, Tessa.
- Very funny.
Sex, drugs and rock n 'roll.
Ladies and gentlemen, I think they agree
...
... That is a young,
taking life by the horns.
Thank you to Tessa and her dad.
Thank you.
And now the weather, as always this morning...
's Cloudy, a little chilly afternoon clearing
and the rest of the week.
- Is he out?
- No.
Dad.
Wait...
It's after nine.
- Do not tell me?
- Hi honey, happens.
Hi Mom!
- You look stressed.
- Cúlpala it! Back-to four.
Is a new trick mom,
I can make a coin disappear.
- Want to see?
- No honey, not before coffee.
- Nothing before coffee, show your sister.
- She is never interested.
- She does not mind!
- Sure.
- I really do not care.
- Why do not you go see CBBS or something?
Because I have nine years.
I heard you on the radio...
Met a guy.
Tessa, promise me you'll use a condom always
.
It may seem great, but no one is saved
gonorrhea.
Can you stop? But my panic attack,
have a panic attack.
And do not have casual sex.
- Really?
- No honey.
Always try as much as possible.
I have to get a tattoo.
I want one in a while.
Length
About me and bigger tits.
- What about?
- He's a fucking liar.
- Who?
- Scott.
- Said he'd be here.
- Is that why you came?
I can not believe I planted,
I gave him the best sex of his life.
- Fucking idiot.
- Look.
- What?
- Is there.
Hi handsome.
What about?
Well...
- Hello.
- Hello!
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
I know you leave nothing,
the other night, I just wanted...
No. .. No, it was my fault.
- What?
- I just...
- I could have been a little more...
- Did she tell you?
- What?
- You did it?
You told on me.
Should not have done that.
Tessa waiting!
Tessa!
You missed lunch.
You Eat.
- What's with all this?
- There is a fire in the next door.
Do not do that.
Please do not, if your
do not want these things, I do.
This is Spain! We were in remission.
Teaching me to whistle, you took that picture.
I said I would never forget my first whistle.
If...
But if I want to.
What are you doing?
Do you mind?
Surely not.
'm Adam.
And you... You Tessa.
I've seen around here
since you moved.
Do not know how to introduce myself.
There are love letters.
Not my business.
Just saying, I
let anyone or anything like that.
Not thought of that.
Anyway, I have more things to burn.
Great, go ahead.
This will also leave.
It is probably best.
Is a dangerous dress.
Are you okay?
Tessa?
You fainted.
Are you diabetic? Need sugar?
Take a little of this.
- This warm.
- I'm sorry.
It sound like a bad thing.
Very good, excellent, nothing embarrassed, ashamed at all
.
Do not worry, it's okay.
Do not worry, I never had that effect on someone before
.
And as I like.
- It's a nice garden.
- If you, is like that... What I like.
- If you are not happy.
- What about your dad?
Only the two of us.
- I should go home.
- OK, if you need help...
Not exactly far.
So, if you burn more than
...
O if
I fainted in front of someone.
- You know where to come.
- Right.
When Tessa dies,
we go on vacation?
God!
That's something horrible, what you say!
Can not remember when we went to Spain.
Was so long ago, that
may not be true.
- Enough, go to your room!
- Dad!
- What happened?
- Go!
What I said was wrong?
- She will leave in peace.
- No, of course not.
It's your day.
- What does that mean?
- That you can do whatever you want.
- Buy more?
- Sure.
Where does the money go?
A credit card
buy now and pay later.
O you know... Never.
Careful where you fly, lest you be
serves someone's eye.
Really wish I could fly.
OK?
Awesome!
That was better than the best in the world!
- I can do it again?
- I think it's time for your sister.
- I'm fine, I just want to see.
- Are you sure?
This patient can not
do such things.
Okay buddy, that fix
there again.
The truth... You know what? I will.
- Ready?
- List!
Tessa ! Not sure if that...
- Right?
- Right! Just who is ill.
- It was not your money.
-'re Late...
Did you hear what I said?
- Promised to come.
- Tessa!
- Want to be refunded?
- Why should he be punished?
- What are you doing?
- Does this have to do with your list?
- I have a list.
- I said that to the guy on the radio.
- It was an invention.
- Yes, it was an invention.
Equal cheated him and me.
How do you think that makes me feel?
I do not care how you feel,
she's not coming, let's do it.
Tessa,
feel a prick and you burn something.
And then anesthesia will effect do you think?
Okay, now pulled up and down.
To break the fabric,
around the point of incision.
You may feel pain around the chest
.
Once the glue line, simply slide
Now, of course I can not reinsert the cavity
.
Would you recommend other treatment?
- I'm saying is that you can change your mind
. - Do not change my mind.
Daddy?
Not going to change my mind.
Very well, then.
Grab that for me.
Good girl.
Do you want to stop doing that?
- What? No! - Then I tried
like a horse.
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's done now.
's Done.
- You know you watch?
- If.
Fever, headache, chills.
Bleeding, loss of strength.
're Good.
Thanks for all your help.
- He likes you.
- I doubt it.
I mean, you got something there!
You should ask her out.
Tessa! Wait, I'm here.
Already low, stay there.
Oh God, how I missed it?
Time I went out, but there was crazy traffic.
Definitely went out on time.
- Just...
- Sure, whatever.
- Tessa!
- I do not care.
- Do not be like that.
- How do you expect?
Sorry
Does this have something to do with you?
- Is that a serious question?
- Yes, it is.
Enough!
Both stink  one is
obsessive with cancer...
... And one can not even get to the Hospital
.
Which is fine, I understand.
But neither is what I need.
Are just wasting my time.
- All I'm saying is that...
- It will not be what you say.
- All I'm saying is...
- Say no more.
All I'm saying is that you have to stay with me
.
You can go out and see your friends more often
- Okay.
- That's all I'm saying.
Did you ever use drugs?
Excellent Have you met my mother?
- Hello!
- Hello.
All I used were
fungi, which are natural.
And not strictly...
Legal ...
My friend gave me, but thought...
... That something else would be
ugly, so...
Ate mushrooms.
See you inside.
- Well...
- I think so.
- How much did you eat?
- Not much.
- I do not know, really do not know.
- I do not either.
Look, I'll take you somewhere,
to keep you out of trouble.
I'm not sure how much effect do
delay.
Do not both?
- Do not be afraid.
- What?
What?
What did you say?
All right, look I have here.
Here I can see them going crazy.
Do not want to go crazy, for nothing!
I'll only be up here.
What are you doing?
Low  Okay!
- Let's get down to three!
- No!
Come on down.
- Please!
- Why, force me down?
No, I'll tell you one low.
Okay.
Thanks.
Where is Tessa?
What?
- We have to go after her.
- I do not even know where it went.
- We have to find it now!
- He'll be back, no big deal.
- I mean... Here there is no danger.
- Yes, of course.
Why?
- Zooey? -
Is supposed not to tell you.
What?
Tessa!
I just discovered something.
Are you okay? Can you come down?
Not want.
Just wait... Wait, I'm coming.
Just wait for me !
Tessa! You have to download please.
Please let me help you down.
I'm going to tell you something.
And you must promise
not tell anyone okay?
I do not feel sick... No more.
I just need to stay here.
I have to be away from the modern world.
And then I will not be sick.
You can stay with me if you want.
I would like if you did.
And build things, shelter traps...
Will cultivate vegetables.
We'll be safe.
- Tessa...
- No!
Please... Do not say anything.
- Tessa!
- What?
You still be your brother when you die?
Still be here.
Are you going to haunt me?
No, if you want.
Only  not scare me.
Well, dad says
go down, when you're ready.
Enjoying your cake?
Is adorable, thanks Tessa.
Do not look as if you feel well.
You would feel good?
Do not take it personal.
's Been like for the past few weeks.
Shauna, I think this is called
the other girl who came.
Do not pretend you've forgotten your name
dad invited her to dinner.
And she said no.
'll Be next.
Does everything wrong.
- How do you feel about that?
- I laugh.
Know... There are support groups, you can...
... Meet people in the same situation as you
.
I went to one of those once.
My advisor called Angela.
Why
not talk to her about all this?
Because he died.
The last time I make that mistake.
Are we done?
Not have to look at me like that.
I'm just dying, not contagious.
- How are you feeling today?
- Fancy a ride?
Always answer a question with a question?
Does that bother you?
I have to fix this thing.
I'm cleaning the engine.
Do you feel more comfortable with?
What do you mean? Not a problem.
At least this is productive.
- Where did you say you were going?
- I said nothing.
Climbing THROUGH A nice field.
Maybe my biggest problem is...
...
I have no much energy to burn.
Yeah, right.
Was worth it?
If.
What's the story with you and your mom?
My dad died last year.
And I had a place in
college, but...
Rejected him.
Should go yet.
I'm not sure it's good for something.
Are you afraid?
It comes and goes.
Most believe that when these
sick, you become brave and courageous.
Not so.
Most of the time is like
be stalked by a psychopath.
As you enter
in shock for a second.
Sometimes I forget if I go or come.
What makes you forget?
That's another thing.
I should think that, all afternoon.
Look.
Now I feel no fear.
- Why do not you want to go?
- I should not say that other thing.
Do not think you can go now?
- The party who is?
- I'm not sure.
- Did not I invited?
- Not how it works.
- But all your friends are going.
- I guess so.
It's complicated.
Two of us.
Hey, wait for me here,
'll bring something to drink.
If.
- Or better come with me?
- Okay, I'll go with you.
- Hey There!
- Hey guys.
Sorry to bother you, only
know someone who looks like your friend.
'm Tessa, a pleasure to meet you.
On behalf of the entire house,
it's good to meet you too.
How's college?
Good place to learn, you should try it.
Yeah, yeah...
- You Drinking down this?
- Yes! Actually yes.
Yeah, well, the girls did not appear at parties
and...
... Easy, but when you
it, you are no longer welcome.
So, you have a serious problem with me
.
You should get out more.
Well, not everyone has the desire
right?
- This is in L.A.?
- Contrary.
The girl hit my jaw,
when he was pointing at my nose.
- You have to be careful.
- No, of course not.
That's the thing...
See you then?
- What do you mean?
- This is your house.
Nonsense, come on, you
led to the door of your house.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, Sure, no problem.
See?
Thanks .
Hello.
Hello?
- You dropped that.
- What?
That.
You dropped.
Not mine.
I saw it out of his pocket.
- Really?
- If.
Because I was fixing.
Thanks.
- That was so cool!
- I was completely.
Broke the rules? Always do that?
No!
You who came at the perfect time.
- Now what? - Now we are going to get and
money and party.
With the card?
- Okay.
- And what is the number?
What do you mean?
- Did not you see the number?
- No, you had to have.
I'd dash!
- Stunk like criminals.
- Probably for the best.
Is better right?
Maybe we should try to return the card.
- How do we do that?
- Do not interrupt anything right?
Go! The card!
Come with Cole, I know he's crazy about me.
- How do you know?
- Why is man?
I would not believe much, either.
Well why did not you call me last night?
There's something I have to tell you.
Let's do it quick.
Remember to steal, it's all security
you have.
You need to be ready.
There, we separated.
- Why not together?
- Will be more suspect. Come.
- Tessa? Tessa? Scott?
- No, sorry.
Yes, you.
Do not we remember?
In school.
Oh yeah!
You left when you were eleven you?
So how's it going?
Still with all this treatment?
- Not anymore.
- So are you better?
No.
What want you two?
- Zooey Hello!
- Why are you here?
- Ready to go?
- If.
Is it true you've been dating Scott
?
- What do you care? Do you know him?
- Okay, let's go.
Everyone knows him, came to me
sister for about half an hour.
Oh, yeah?
I have to go collect my funeral invitations
.
- Really?
- If.
Also  I have to read a lot, so...
... See that damn poem
put on my grave.
- Let go.
- Are idiots, they know nothing.
No. ..
- I have to go find it.
- Now?
Yeah, sorry, I have to go.
Hey!
Another! Agárrenla her too.
Sit.
Empty your pockets.
Well, I'd call that evidence
do not you?
Name, address, number of parents.
Do not call my dad.
We have an option we can
call him or the police.
Police.
- Anytime.
- I told the guy from outside, which would handle.
- And if you do not...
- Listen.
This is for chemo therapy.
Access  A
my blood for medical treatment.
Linfoplástica I have leukemia.
Please componte your shirt.
Do you know what that is?
- No, I'm afraid I do not know.
- Is cancer.
Even so, I have to call your dad.
Do you?
- What's your excuse?
- What took her?
A Clear Blue pregnancy test.
That was on the list? Does stealing?
What you Tessa? What are you doing?
Doing all I can,
as fast as you can.
Well, you should stop.
Prefer to spend the rest of my life, below...
... The blankets on the couch, with my head
on your shoulder.
If... I wish. Can you blame me?
Yes, of course I would.
Look, my point is...
My point is,
I like strong women.
Always want to be loaded to bed.
Once carried me to the bed.
I do not understand, is going to a party.
Y appear with a very young pixie Warlock!
She is not a Warlock,
say, she started a fight.
Apparently if you can.
What are you doing here?
I've been harassed all day.
Just did not have the courage to warn.
- Really?
- No.
My dad's in store.
It's nice to see your friends again.
Always becoming apparent.
- Well... See you around, maybe...
- Sure, yes.
I know you're looking!
I'm not looking.
Liar !
You should think about going back to school.
Normalize your life.
Not return to school.
I should give many tests.
I'm kidding.
Daily.
Take care friend!
Idiot!
He wants!
Tessa where are you going?
? Tessa?!
Tessa!
That was very good.
You drive a motorcycle, in fact
was on my list.
Tell me more you have.
Fame.
How famous will you be?
Enough
that the world does not do, what you are doing.
And personally come to say goodbye when I die.
Do not think you're asking too
there?
Only
I have my name in the world out there.
Not worry, I will not forget
Tess.
Enough?
If.
What are you doing?
Just want to swim.
Do not go swimming without clothes.
Of course not, do you think I'm crazy?
No naked.
Tess! Tess!
Okay, on the count of three right?
- What?
- Come on, just run.
- Deal.
- Sure...
- Demons.
- Here we go.
One, two, three!
You are evil!
- How about this?
- Yes, really very good.
- Really?
- No!
Come What are you afraid of?
A nothing!
The great thing is...
That truth, I always wanted to try to dry myself with
half.
I'm glad you did that to me!
Do not worry.
The stars around us.
If...
See that group of five, up there?
In the form of a curve did you see?
- Do you see?
- If...
I have no idea how they are called.
Keep.
No. ..
What?
I'm sorry.
Do not you like me?
Not that.
Not think I can handle it.
See you later.
Tess, Tess wait!
We Tess! Come!
No, I made a mistake.
What? What error?
Can not save.
When you were a baby...
Your mom and I used to stay awake at night
, watching you breathe.
We were convinced that if we stopped looking...
Just forget the how.
When children grow up, is a different kind of concern
.
Never as a ghost.
Please think about it.
You know I prefer when I yell?
Tessa?
Nurse!
Okay sweetie.
Do not worry about that.
I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Okay sweetie.
Tessa Hello how are you?
Well, I think I did well vomit.
We did some tests last night.
And I fear that the cancer has spread to your
spinal fluid.
Things are progressing faster than we think.
Have advanced beyond the limit line.
How much further?
Encourage you to do the things you want to do
.
That attempt.
- Adorable.
- Boring! Runs other!
What to do?
I shot a rocket?
- Yes! A rocket!
- Okay.
Remind me again why you're here?
Your father told me to cut the legs
if not come.
Well, this will be very noisy.
Okay...
- Right?
- Okay.
- Not bad what else you got?
- Enough for a show.
YES! Runs more!
Ready? Okay, here we go.
One, two...
Three...
Four...
Five!
Six, seven...
Eight, nine...
Tessa.
What's the worst that could happen?
Do not know.
'm Ready.
Zooey was right, I feel alive!
Good morning Dad!
Did you sleep well?
Who are you and what have you done with my daughter?
Sit.
Eat, drink coffee.
- Dad, I want you to meet someone.
- Oh God!
- He is Ajon, Ajon he is Dad.
- Nice to meet you Lord.
- No need to call Him Lord.
- Lord, be well.
- Excellent, who wants a piece of toast?
- Can go.
And miss the fun?
Okay Tess.
- Sit.
- If.
Is terrible
life of a man, the...
... Day her daughter
brings a boy home.
Always thought that if he killed the
first, the others would voice.
- Are you going to college?
- Yes, I had a place.
Only
I have to do some things first.
Is what happened, I'm sorry for your loss
.
- If...
- How's your mom?
Some days are good, if...
Should think Tessa.
- You know, about your condition.
- I told him.
No, of course not.
Want
find her attractive and believe me, has not told you everything.
How old are you?
Why?
Because at your age, you should not have to be
caring for someone.
- Tessa needs no care.
- Yeah, sure you do.
Every day more.
And you, my friend, you are not
height task.
So why do not we
do everyone a favor...
... And let live
what's left of his life.
How did you make your dad
lend the car?
Do not do not you talking?
Knew there was one thing I forgot to ask
.
Well, thanks for the ride.
I thought all the girls would be
clutching handkerchiefs and crying.
I can at least pay for privacy.
You'll get over.
No, never.
Never exceed He hates me.
Do you hate me?
Only talk to them today.
On another visit?
Yes, I want to finish. Yes?
Zooey Walker?
We're ready for you now.
Just want it out.
Do you hear that?
- It was not my fault.
- The brake must be wrong.
Okay.
Tess, you know I have no choice.
Do not even know that those words mean.
You should not go with me, if
not going to agree.
Because that's why you asked.
Good night.
It was the first time you drive.
The first in the world.
- Well, you did great.
- You think so?
YES! If you just have to learn to use
changes.
Is my dad's car,
deserves what he gets.
- Just try to keep you safe.
- I think that ship has sailed do not you think?
Do you want to go on a date with me?
Only
than in the day, maybe a...
... Appropriate or
Maybe once we get dinner?
You know, do not have to be tonight, but there is much time
, just let me know.
That's fine.
Tessa, you could have called.
- What are you doing here?
- Dad has been looking Where were you?
Maybe talk another time.
Why?
Because I have an appointment.
Yes, I came.
Demons... Please not today!
Talk to your father, I said I do not know...
- Oh my God!
- Only a nosebleed.
No, Tessa is going to sea.
What should I do?! I do not know...
Take a towel, sit.
- Oh, oh! You have to go to a hospital!
- I have to be somewhere.
Call your father.
Should  call your father?
Do not know what to do, tell me to do.
- Just bring me ice.
- What?
Ice! A bag of frozen peas
would be much better.
Sure, frozen peas.
There sweetcorn.
Okay sweet corn?
- Oh Jesus!
- You have to take me to the Hospital.
I can not, it's something your father should do
...
There's a first time.
- Okay.
- If an ambulance please fast.
Who is? Who is?
- You can not!
- I need help!
- Do not let him!
- You can not see me like that!
- Tessa, I can not do it alone.
If, # 25 Preston, is the house...
Come here, help me to take down.
- Come on! Will not you help me?
- Just leave it there, please.
Okay come on!
Must be thirsty,
has lost much blood, it looked like it came out like water.
What good, there you are!
Great, any sign of bleeding
, before today?
Mom?... Mom!
- I'm sorry, did I?...
- I've been with a headache?
Did you notice any bruises?
- I set, to be honest.
- When was your last incision?
I'm not sure, I can try to find
.
Did you use some kind of aspirin
recently?
I do not know... Sorry, I have no answers
to all those questions.
The last transfusion was  May 18.
Okay, thanks, do not talk.
Mom! Grab the hand of your daughter.
Okay, grab the hand of your mother,
once to say "yes"
and twice for "no".
Understood? Do not talk.
- If...
- Any sign of back pain?
- Headaches? Bruises??
- No.
- Did you use t-gel or other anti-inflammatory
? - No, no.
I'm afraid we'll have to cauterize your nose
.
You been seared before?
- If.
- Okay.
We will need many units of blood.
It will be a tough night, coming home tomorrow
.
Already know everything in the end.
They said it was  a nosebleed,
you know, the kind of bad.
Had to close his nose...
- Gauze obstructive.
- Yeah, that.
And before transferring units,
I did a little cleaning.
's Stable.
You did good.
I'm home,
can go now if you want.
I can stay?
YES!
How are you feeling?
Sleepy, thanks for being there.
It was a little difficult,
for your guy too.
But it was understandable.
This is a sweet pastry.
Yes, it is exactly as you describe.
What would you say?
Well, not with me, so I think
left me.
- Did not call or come after us?
- No.
Perhaps  panic.
Oh my God!
- What?
- Look at the bridge.
Are you serious?
Tessa wrote everywhere!
I did.
Put ​​my name in the world.
Juggling sticks!
Would I buy this?!
- Happy Birthday!
- Can you teach me?
If... A little, yes.
I will help you to practice then, if you want.
- Dad I can stay for dinner??
- No.
- Mom?
- I do not know honey.
- Thanks.
- But let it stay.
It's a conspiracy!
Okay, on with the show of magic
.
Choose a letter...
Five of hearts.
No. ..
Why  I can not say right?!
And that day, shall be in the pants.
Cute,
was about to say that right?
Demons!
Fall into the hands of fate.
How goes the list?
The things that I thought mattered
no longer interested.
- What about you?
- Have something you want to put in there?
I want to fly.
Never think of that sort of thing... Right?
But... I guess so.
Come on, you know, just like you.
- Adam...
- Yes?
Stick your head in the game.
Think.
What are your expectations?
Your dreams...
- Right now?
- If...
- Hands off me!
- Right!
If your nose gets elsewhere.
Anda, runs through
other hand, you can.
Running, well, concentrating.
That's it! Tessa Scott is in the house!
How do you stop?! Use the wall.
Hello you.
Hello.
You had to leave.
I kept falling, my bones ache.
We're staying with the baby.
- Really?
- If...
If...
Y is a girl... We're having a girl.
And call her Lauren.
I will.
I want to be there!
If you do not want me at birth, I can sit outside and enter
then.
I want to be the first person to
the world, to embrace your baby.
Will be in 5 months.
So I have a goal.
Some people find this very beautiful.
All I can think is that
is killing my poor plants.
What about Tess?
Not enough.
What do you mean?
Stay with me.
Stay at night.
Tess do you want?
At night, sleep together and wake up together
.
Breakfast...
What you really want?
I want you with me.
You to hold me.
You take care and follow me loving
help me when I'm scared something.
That touches the edge of my bed and see
is there.
What would happen if
make things right?
Is impossible to do it wrong.
For you.
Is a snow angel.
- No, no, no and no.
- Dad!
This is in the list?
That a guy will get to sleep?
- Forget it, no.
- You know? This is not easy for me.
Well, it's easy for me
, answer that.
I thought you wanted to talk.
Not about this, do not let
, end of discussion.
Do not be like me.
I have rights, I am your father.
Not by much.
- Are you ready?
- Is very far.
- Just jump!
- Too far!
- Good night, then.
- Wait!
- What are you doing?
- I can not jump.
Not going to step
bad, do not worry.
Oh my God!
- Are you okay?
- No, I broke my nose.
- And both arms.
- I broke everything.
- Hello.
But you're here.
He's in there right?
If.
I told you not want that.
Why not?
Do you know why?
I think so.
Tessa's a good guy, but guys...
You can not trust them.
Can you disappointed.
It will not.
What if is that if you do?
So, although you'll have to you.
As always.
This is too good.
Except for onion.
For just eat at home.
- I wish I could do that.
- If you can.
No. .. I can do two and you.
I will teach you.
I'll put on my new list.
- With what?
- Many things.
Spring.
Roasted Potatoes.
A train journey.
- A peacock.
- Breakfast in bed.
A joint bank account.
Hearing you snoring years and years.
- Do not snore... Or if?
- You will, when you are old.
Fighting for parenthood, but
know that our son is a genius.
Actually, our three children.
Three children.
Justin, Marilyn and Daysi.
God!
Be with you, be with you...
Just to be with you.
So you still love doing her magic
?
- You tell me about it. - Should
recommending to all my patients.
YES! I got a text message!
It has a new cell .
- Is growing.
- E51.
That was by the fountain in the park
, that I put E1.
Account
what you've been doing recently.
Oh yeah, I'm doing
hidden treasure games.
Tyre
garlic all doors and corners.
Which is disgusting, but I thought...
What?
What happens?
Tessa?
- Where is your father?
- Saying something my mom.
What is he saying?
Hopefully come right?
I'm the one who is sick, not them.
Not them.
How sick please?
Your spread of cancer is very high.
Your immune system is collapsing.
Cancer is now everywhere.
How long more do I have?
I will not go to timescales.
Not sue if he was wrong.
My best friend gave birth in April.
Can I know your baby?
No.
Adam?
- Hello.
- Are you Adam?
Oh no! I'm sorry honey,
not return until evening.
Too bad!, Where does it go?
's On the train, on the opening day of
.
- Inauguration Day?
- If college.
I was so happy when he said he would take his place
in September.
There were times when I thought,
would lose another 12 months.
Not want to be the oldest among all.
Right?
No.
No one wants that.
Tessa?
Tessa  are you here?
Honey?
No!
Monster!
Do you want to leave me with nothing?
Is this all?
Does the list?
Why do not you showed me?
You should show me.
I could have helped with a couple.
Just wanted to help.
I could not help.
I can not help.
Not want you to go.
Not want you to go! I can not!
Oh please.
Not want you to go, please.
're My baby.
Jesus Tess, I've been looking everywhere
.
How long have you been here?
Why did not you tell me?
Can not touring around, only
back with me, please.
Why not tell me?
I will be I,
to stay here alone.
Do not you dare feel bad about yourself
, because you'll be left behind.
- Do not you dare!
- This was what you wanted.
Come on, I know, this is what
wanted, we have to follow and...
... You must know, if not
out for you, I could not...
... Go anywhere or do anything...
I just sit in a fucking garden.
Will happen.
I know.
Pronto.
Okay?
What was it like?
Grande, many buildings, I missed.
We'll manage.
- Shall we?
- If...
Back as someone else.
I a girl you harass,
when studying.
Then
I fall in love with you at first sight.
Again.
Tell me, how it will be.
Not want to eat much,
from now on.
'll Thirst.
Y. .. Sometimes you have fever.
You'll want to sleep much.
Will have little or no energy.
- Hurt?
- No.
Morphine prevent feeling pain.
Will give a very beautiful dream.
Hello.
I keep thinking about my own baby.
What's she like?
Gorgeous.
You'll love it.
This is happening?
I know it's not real.
I'm...
Do you think you will be afraid?
I think you hit the worst luck in the world
.
And if I were in your shoes
, be afraid.
But I think the way you handle
in recent days.
Be exactly like you wanted them.
Hate when you say days.
'll Reach a point where you are not fully aware
.
Sometimes, you can not
respond, but know...
... That people are there, hear them speak
.
Thanks for staying with her.
I love.
Tess And eventually, you just go
.
Got a question?
No. .. No.
-'re awake...
- I just wanted to say hi.
You still looking for a cure?
Pain relief.
I can use the computer for a second?
Yeah, right...
Your hair is growing.
Not fast enough.
What are you showing me?
A better page.
- Jobs?
- You have to stop thinking.
Not yet.
You'll have a life again.
I'll never have a life.
Now you can do whatever.
'll Tell
Tessa and dad and everyone else I know.
- Mom wants Mr. Welmont.
- Of course I never said that!
You did! Mom would like Mr. Welmont
.
All moms want one like
Mr. Welmont.
- Hey how do you feel?
- Where have you been?
I've been to a PTA meeting.
- Did you go to that?
- Right.
If... It was very boring.
How Mr. Welmont?
Says it was fine, so
that mom bought me this.
- I turn around and make sounds like that.
- Yes, but not in the house.
How come you awake?
These all sweaty.
- I'll change your sheets for you.
- I will.
- I can make your bed.
- Not a nurse.
Not true!
Okay! I'll do without.
Listen Tess, like whistling.
Coming.
'll Be there in a second.
'll Be okay.
- Adam.
- If beauty?
- Do not let me fall.
- I have.
- I'm falling.
- No you're falling.
Moments...
Our life is a series of moments.
Each is a trip to the final.
Let them go.
Let them all go.
Should  goodbye.
No. ..
Come on baby, is important.
May make it die.
Nothing you say,
can make it die.
Okay?
Hey honey, we're all here.
All love you very much.
You did so well!
You can go now.
Can go.
Bye Tess,
embrújame if you want, I do not care.
Our life is a series of moments.
Let them go.
Moments...
Together.
Aimed at this time.
Now is Good (2012)
TaMaBin Times and corrections from the audio translation DinaB