[no sound]
Greetings, my friend.
We are all interested
in the future,
for that is where you and I
are going to spend
the rest of our lives.
And remember my friends,
future events such as these
will affect you in the future.
You are interested
in the unknown,
the mysterious,
the unexplainable.
That is why you are here.
And now for the first time,
we are bringing to you
the full story of what happened
on that fateful day.
We are giving you
all the evidence
based only on the secret
testimony
of the miserable souls
who survived
this terrifying ordeal.
The incidents, the places,
my friend, we cannot keep
as a secret any longer.
Let us punish the guilty.
Let us reward the innocent.
My friend,
can your heart stand
the shocking facts about...
Only moments ago, after five
long weeks of searching,
Capri Johnson was discovered
just a few feet from here
on this deserted road,
just outside of Reno, Nevada.
Thanks to an anonymous tip,
Channel 11 was first
on the scene.
I must warn you the footage
you are about to see
is extremely disturbing.
Sensitive viewers
may not want to watch.
[woman crying]
[consoling voices]
[female] Cameron,
what are you doing?
I'm just trying to find
a condom, babe.
Get back into bed.
Oh, I'll be there.
Come on.
[whispering] Get ready for the
Cameron Townes Show, baby.
Hoo-hoowa.
Mm-mm.
[car honking]
Oh, shit, I gotta go.
Wh-what?
Where are you going?
I'm gonna take my grandma
to the Star Trek convention.
What the fuck, are you
fucking recording me?
No, never.
Are you fucking serious?
Shit!
Give me that camera back.
A bold remark, Miss Stewart.
Hello, my name
is Cameron Townes.
And I'm working
on a documentary
about the greatest 21st
birthday trip to Las Vegas
in the history
of 21st birthday--
Yo, brown bag special,
shut it, man.
[Townes] You're ruining
your intro
to your birthday video.
No shit, I brought him
so you could have this
to remember.
[Townes] No shit, this is
Graham, he's the birthday boy.
But I love this man.
Not-- there's not many people
out there that'll go out...
How is he related
to this guy--
and do a full brown out
in fucking Vegas!
Brown is the way
to the woman's heart.
It is, I agree, I've done
the brown out before.
My shoes are brown, as well.
They're made outta hemp.
Because--
...or a rapist.
One, you need to stop dressing
like a boy scout
and two, you need
to stop saying things
like, you know, it's not--
But, this is actually--
How those are bong rips
treating you up there?
Not, good there, Cameron.
Maybe that's because
it's like,
eight in the morning
or something.
You know what, smoking weed
at eight in the morning
is actually the greatest thing
ever invented.
Who, someone invented smoking
weed at eight in the morning?
I think it might have
been Freud.
Freud, Sigmund Freud.
Sigmund Freud,
you mean Siegfried?
No, not--
Siegfried and Roy--
Not the tiger,
no, I'm talking about--
That's what we're going
to see, dude.
You guys are fucking stupid.
Did you get tickets
for Siegfried and Roy?
Yes.
You got that in common,
at least.
I think I smoked too much.
What?
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna fucking puke.
I'm not even
on the road yet, dude.
Don't puke in my car, dude.
What a fucking pussy.
I'm serious, don't puke
in my car.
He's gonna blow,
he's gonna blow.
Do what you want-- puke.
Close.
Puke.
Don't puke.
I'm actually gonna puke.
I know-- puke.
I wanna see it.
[both] Oh, shit!
What the fuck did you eat?
Something pink.
So,
Anyway,
As I was saying, I don't think
I even need to give an intro
to the trip anything more
after our buddy, Graham here
just set it up for us.
Let's go pick up Tommy Kay.
Ho, ho, ho, hee.
That was good.
Cameron, you didn't say
he fucking worked here.
[speaks Spanish]
What the fuck?
What's going on?
How are you all doing?
What's up with the camera?
Can you take five?
Tommy Kay, baby,
the opposite of gay.
Get it straight.
Hey, can you take five?
What?
Can you take five?
We need to talk.
We gotta talk right now.
About what, how?
You guys are not going
to get me fired from my job?
This shirt come
with this job
or did you have
to buy it yourself?
Tommy, Tommy,
can you hear me?
Tommy Kay has no idea
we're about to yank his ass
out of this job
and take him to Vegas.
He says no--
You guys are gonna
get me fired, bro.
Hop on, hop on.
Who's gonna see this?
You guys are gonna get me fired.
No, no, no.
Come on, let's go.
No, no, no, you're gonna
get me fired, dude.
You 21?
Happy mother fuckin' birthday.
Don't stay too close 'cause it
gives me a wide angle like,
distortion of my face.
We're going to Vegas.
You always do this, man.
I'm not going.
We're going to Vegas.
Yeah, you are.
Wanna see the move, man?
We're going.
I am not going like this.
It's my fuckin' birthday.
We got you clothes, man,
let's go.
Come on, Tommy,
we don't have time, dude.
Let's do it!
You got Matt Hardy?
You know it.
Even though I could pick up
women with anything,
I don't wanna be, you know--
Stop that.
Why do I have
my apron on right now?
It's all right,
you're fired already.
Just keep it.
Dude, your dad better
give me a job then.
I'm not playing.
Just keep that hair net
on all night.
Take it off.
Oh, shit.
You got gel?
Yeah, we got gel.
Where's the gel?
Projectile vomited.
Like, all over the street.
Almost in the car,
we almost had to kick his ass.
It was like gray
and amber, dude.
How'd he throw up?
I don't know, I guess
I smoked too much or something.
Are you bulimic?
Not bulimic, he was sick.
What do you mean?
Yeah, I took theater class
in middle school,
but you wouldn't know
about that.
Anyways, um, and action.
Hey, guys, this is
Tommy Kay reporting
from the back seat
of the ca-- of the car.
[giggling]
I'll-- I'll finish.
My friend, Graham,
is bulimic.
And I'm gonna call him out
on his shit
'cause that's what
friends do.
I'm-- I'm a little worried now.
A little bit.
What do you want me
to fuckin' say?
I fuckin' smoked
a little bit of weed--
okay, a lot of bit of weed
and I fuckin' had
my cranberry scone
like I do every morning.
I mean, you shouldn't
be vomiting.
It was pink, for God sakes.
Yeah, because I had a fuckin'
cranberry scone, dick!
Does Cameron have a rape face?
Now, put the camera
in your face really quick.
And tell me, you should have
played American Psycho.
[whispers] Did you make her?
Hey, Capri.
[Capri] Hey, Luke.
Hey, Capri, baby,
boo-boo bear, no, no, yes.
[Capri on phone]
[no audible dialog]
[chuckles] You want us
to take you to Vegas
so you can see Jake?
That sounds like more
of a gift for you
than a gift for me.
On my brother's birthday?
[Capri on phone]
[no audible dialog]
Does she have-- does she have
women with her?
[Capri] Hello?
[whispers] Ask her.
Yeah.
What?
We'll be there in 20.
No.
No, no.
I'll see you in a minute.
What the fuck, dude?
[clamoring]
She's not my friend.
You still play pancake at 22.
What is pancake?
This is so gay, dude.
We're backtracking
to go pick up pancake.
Get off, I'm not--
What is pancake?
Patty-cake?
Oh, patty-cake.
No, fuck off.
Yeah, you see, you know now.
Okay, I play,
because I'm the only one
who's got quick enough hands
to do the fucking patty-cake.
Graham, reject me
one more time,
see what happens--
just one time.
See watch.
Whoa, God, you're pinching me,
you fucking weirdo!
Tommy?
Oh, my God.
Were you worried they were
going to send you
back across the border?
I'm not Mexican, dude.
I'm-- I'm from Illinois.
Same difference.
Happy birthday, Graham!
You don't get
anything you want.
What does it matter?
Because we were going to have
the fucking four of us, man!
It doesn't matter.
She's gonna ride with us and
then we're gonna drop her off.
You can't-- I don't understand
why you're so mad, Graham?
It's not-- it's not a big deal.
See, you're not a big deal.
Tommy Kay's down with it.
Bro, I'm gonna fuckin'
sock you in the mouth.
Tommy Kay, you weren't even
gonna fucking come.
You were gonna fucking
flip pizzas
for the rest
of the fuckin' week.
Yeah, you weren't
gonna fucking come.
All right, I'm sorry.
Can you stay quiet for a second?
I need a vent.
I don't ha-- and back to me.
I don't have a fade.
I don't feel comfortable
with the shirt.
I can tell when you're lying
to me, go ahead.
Okay, go ahead.
You feel happy now?
This is the--
this is the hospital
where Graham was born.
Quick, get a shot of that.
That's beautiful.
[laughs]
It's brown too.
We goin' to Vegas?
Let's go to Vegas.
Yes, we're going to Vegas.
Let's get pumped up.
Whatever.
Vegas on three, Cam.
On three-- Vegas.
[all] one, two, three.
[shouting] Go.
All right, for everybody's
information,
moving on down the road.
We got a little stowaway
in the back seat now though,
because somebody
just had to tag along.
Guilty, right there.
You know you wanted me
to come, don't lie.
Oh, and I came bearing gifts.
What are you drawing over there?
Oh, that's so sweet.
If...
them two were to have a kid,
this is how it would look like.
I agree.
His name is Pepe.
Oh, shit.
We're all gonna die, we're never
gonna make it to Vegas.
Okay, say something.
Um, [clears throat]
Why are you here,
where did you come from?
Because I am going
to go see my boyfriend.
And you guys
are giving me a ride.
So kindly, my good friends.
Can I draw a dinosaur
on your cheek?
He's holdin' the camera.
You're holdin' the camera,
it's my turn to play.
[clamor]
You're not here.
You need to practice
invisibility--
Okay, I'm tired
of the attitude.
We're pretending
that you don't exist.
Why are you guys so mean then?
You exist, I see you.
This was a dude's trip.
Dude's trip only.
And you are gay for sure now.
How am I gay?
You're sucking your banana.
Just because
he has feelings, okay?
Gay, gay.
Stop!--
Yo, fuckface, film me humpin'
the fuckin' stegosaur.
The what?
Get it, dude.
What'd he say?
Yeah, you like that?
Yeah, man.
You gotta thrust
the hips, though.
Hey, easy dude, don't bust a
nut on this thing.
Hey, Graham.
Oh, boy.
You wanna hump
this thing?
Yes, I wanna hump that thing.
Oh, yeah, get some.
Hey, wait your turn, buddy.
All right, all right.
No pleasure for the dinosaur.
You're up, buddy.
And it's a guy.
I don't do this shit.
Short and sweet, just like
your mother likes it.
That's great, you're talkin'
about my mom again.
What, man, she has soft hands.
Uh, that's really weird.
Why is that weird?
It's not like I'm saying it
sexually, okay?
I just mean,
her hands feel like
they're dipped in shea butter
or something.
It's actually quite amazing.
Well, how would you feel
if I showed her
this fuckin' tape?
I would say, "Mrs. Cohen, you
have silky, soft, smooth hands.
And I love you."
Okay.
Let's get outta here.
I'm not fuckin'--
Ready?
I can't believe those two
haven't fucked, dude.
What, yeah, they have.
What?
When?
Holy shit, wait a second.
Hey, how come you guys didn't
tell me you've screwed before?
What?
Cat's out of the bag,
just answer the question.
Hey, you know what?
This is perfect,
this makes sense.
Yeah, okay, turn the camera off.
It's evolution.
I'm being serious
right now.
Cameron, come on,
this shit's not cool.
No, I'm being seriou--
Let my talk to you
for a min-- oh!
Uh!
I'm telling you,
you guys make a c--
[car starts]
Sorry, buddy.
Thanks, still love you.
[clamoring]
I don't tell you guys
everything.
Oh, fuck off,
it's about the group.
I tell you everything.
Hey, you guys, this was
something personal.
[Cameron] If there's
inner-group fucking,
I have a right to know
and so does the documentary.
[clamoring]
Not only do you tell everybody,
hey, but now I'm gonna tell it
in front of Capri
and on camera.
Guys, guys, guys, hello?
You guys are a--
So, there, no, it's not.
What the fuck is going on?
It's none of your business
either.
No, it is my business
because both of you
are my friend
and I think both of you
make a perfect couple.
And I don't know what
the fuck you're doing.
I mean, I don't know
what you're doing with that guy.
You've known him
your whole life.
I don't understand what is
stopping you from committing.
Why would we want to ruin that?
Our friendship,
our relationship.
[clamoring]
Graham, shut up, please.
Yeah, there's no fucking trust
'cause you didn't trust me
enough to tell me.
I think that it's not fair--
You can't tell me?
I fuckin' told you and you're--
So what's the big deal
if Tommy Kay knows?
Let's hear what Tommy Kay
has to say.
I think it's not fair that
you're keeping Luke on hold.
And I think it's not fair that
you are still single, my friend.
I got side girls.
And that is just--
that's just--
Why am I keeping him on hold?
I mean, a friendship
isn't good enough?
I think your boyfriend
should be your best friend.
But why can't I have my best
friend and my boyfriend?
And have him always here,
always--
Wow, always here.
No, I don't mean like that.
Do you live in like,
never-never land?
I don't mean it like that,
obviously-- now, look you guys.
What do you think
about Luke's side girls?
Oh, yeah.
Well, that shouldn't affect you
because he should be able
to fuck
as many girls as he wants
'cause you guys are not
in a committed relationship.
I'm going on a fucking spree
tonight.
Fuck, yes, amen!
Okay, well I thought you guys
were doing me a favor
and I didn't know
you were going to give me
such a hassle about it
and make things awkward.
While everything's awkward,
I'm gonna tell you
about this thing.
This story.
This awkward story.
So, when we were actually
doing the dirty,
Why do have-- no.
[clamoring]
She's on top
and she's like--
"Hey, I want you to F me
in my little P."
And I was like,
"What the fuck?"
You're such assholes!
You're such an asshole.
I'm not talking to you
the rest of the trip.
Let go!
Did she actually say D and P?
Or was she like--
That is some kinky shit.
I'm not talking to you
the rest of the trip.
Ow, you're hurting my wrist.
Please put your D in my PPs.
I wonder what little Jakey-poo
would think of that?
Oh, my God, that wasn't easy.
I'm not talking to you
the rest of the trip.
You know what, Capri?
You know what, you're payment
for us driving you
is us showing Jake this tape.
You're crazy, turn it off.
Taco chan, yummy yum-yum.
Hey.
Cameron?
Hey?
Yeah, what?
Team Jacob or Team Edward?
Team Jacob, dude for sure.
Love Lautner.
Right, that's what
I'm talkin' about.
Steve Taylor.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
You kind of remind me
of him, dude.
Really?
Maybe with your shirt off,
especially.
Do you think?
Yes, yeah.
Yes, definitely, I know.
TK, TK?
What, what?
Team Jacob or Team Edward?
What?
Edward or Jacob?
Fuck you talkin' about?
Dude, don't be a fag.
Team Edward or Team Jacob?
Oh, I'm the one being a fag,
and you guys are talking
about which Twilight character
I like.
[laughing, clamoring]
All right, fine,
I seen Twilight a couple times
and it's not a big deal.
A couple times?
Truth comes out.
Dude, you know what, give me the
camera.
Okay, Capri,
now I want you to swear
into the camera.
I swear.
Uh, swear on your burrito.
I swear on this burrito
that this fine establishment
has made for me
that I will be one of the guys
for the rest of the trip.
And once we're in Vegas,
I will find my boyfriend
and let you little boys
have your bro time.
And I swear I'll pee
standing up.
That's gross.
Ooh.
Oh, wait, and I also swear
that I won't tell
about our yoga class Friday.
Oh.
Toga.
Just a minute, it's okay.
I'm really getting
into Roman culture.
Toga.
Douche bag.
Graham, Cameron,
could we just let her eat,
and go.
I want to learn how
to lick my elbow.
Hey, get a room,
get a room, guys.
Stop.
Seriously, gross.
Gross.
I mean, I'll punch you
in the face.
Oh, wow, okay, that's--
That was my burrito.
Just 'cause you swore on it,
doesn't mean it's yours.
Yeah, it kinda was.
Why-- [no audible dialog]
[Cameron] I just don't know.
He kinda just swept me
off my feet.
Oh, that is so lame.
You don't think it has anything
to do with the fact
that he's like,
a marine adonis?
Despite how perfect he is,
there's no way this guy
is right for you.
Don't you think maybe
it should be me and you?
I just think you and I are
some day kind of relationship.
Jake and I are a today kind
of relationship, Lukie.
When do you think
some day will be, Capri?
I just don't know, Luke.
Don't put so much
pressure on me.
What am I supposed to do?
Dance.
Tell me, just tell me
what to do.
Just dance.
Okay.
Yo, what are we waiting for?
What are you guys doing?
Spotted.
Go, move, move.
Move, we're spotted!
No, you ruinin' my gain
right now-- hello?
Damn you, Tommy.
With what guys?
Listening to us five minutes?
Call you right back.
Cameron.
I thought it was past
five minutes.
No.
He didn't hear anything.
Let's go.
We gotta go.
Can you talk to Ashley,
tell her that you are
not a girl.
Ashley, Ashley,
I'll buy you a drink.
It's for the documentary.
For the better of all of us.
It's Graham.
[Capri] You're in time out.
Graham, take it easy, brother.
Graham,
Ow!
Oh, you're gonna
fucking crash, dude.
Holy shit.
We're going to be there
in twenty miles.
I'm pulling off,
I'm pulling off.
We're gonna be there
in ten minutes.
Where are you gonna pull off?
There's no exits.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to hold it,
like a man.
Do you have like, a fucking box
or something?
A box?
[yells]
He's gonna shit in a box.
Let's make him shit in a box.
Hold the wheel for a sec.
No.
Hold the fucking wheel!
I don't know.
What is he doing, dude?
Come on.
Graham.
No.
If you do this,
we're turning around.
Oh, my God.
Okay, okay.
Ohh!
What, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[coughing]
I'm over the hump,
I'm over the hump.
[Capri] What's wrong with you?
What did you eat today?
Oh, my God, ahh!
All right, seriously,
this is the kind
of fine establishment
you do not go inside of
unless you want to get
man raped by a truck driver
with a Fu Manchu,
you know what I mean?
And Graham's been in here
for like, 30 minutes.
We're gonna go check on him.
Yo, Grahaminator?
I just pooped.
I was guessing you had.
Jesus, it smells great.
Well, hello.
What do we have here?
There it is.
Women willing to do anything
to make you happy.
In all caps, anything.
Believe you me, I can put
that to the test.
[group] Capri and Luke,
sitting in a tree,
k-i-s-s-i-n-g,
first comes love,
then comes marriage,
[Capri] Are we going to have to
deal with this the whole trip?
Are we going to have to deal
with this the whole trip?
[group] That's not all,
that's not all,
baby's fucking sucking
my balls.
Oh.
...in Vegas, stays in Vegas.
What stays in Vegas,
stays in Vegas.
...stays in Vegas.
What happens in Vegas,
stays in Vegas.
...stays in Vegas.
[hollering]
I'm taking your girl!
All right guys,
I gotta show you this--
this is too awesome,
check it out.
These colors look familiar?
Women willing to do anything
to make you happy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
at long last we have arrived.
Las Vegas, the strip, sin city.
We're gonna find out
why it's called sin city.
[falsetto] We're here,
we have arrived, we've come.
Still get's a little wild
because of Graham's stoner ass.
Ohh, check out that chick
over there.
Graham, get her number, dude.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have arrived at long last.
Start your engines.
The crew is in the house.
[engine noise]
That was
the engine starting.
That is Graham's engine
starting.
Hey, check this place out
for a second.
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
Hey, special thanks
to my father, Dr. Townes,
for hooking us up
with the most bomb-ass suite
that this town has to offer.
All right, hey,
one of you jokers take this.
Film me.
I don't know
where the room is.
I'm out of breath already.
I can't breath anymore.
I can't--
Ow!
You're such a pussy.
[Capri] What floor are we on?
Okay.
And we go-- the hallway
that's gonna lead us
to the scene of the crime.
Where did you get that?
This is my documentary.
Actually feels pretty good.
Okay, so tell me, what's the--
oh, shi-- oh, my God.
Oh, Graham.
Graham, what the fuck?
Graham cracker.
Dude, I missed it,
you gotta do it again.
Nothing happened.
Do it for the documentary,
come on.
Are you jealous, because I just
got the most amazing footage.
No, and actually
I have a good idea
because now we can get
some tag team double footage.
Two different angles.
Dude.
Fuck.
But I'm gonna need
your camera.
You all right, buddy?
Hey, you think you can
do it again?
I think I ruptured my coccyx.
Think you can do it again?
Move, move, move, move!
[Capri] This is amazing.
Thank you, Daddy.
You kidding me?
This is what I'm talking
about, Cameron.
Who wants some shots?
Watch it.
Seriously, thank you, Daddy.
Wait a second, where's Graham?
Graham?
Where the heck is Graham at?
Hey, where'd Graham go?
Graham?
[falsetto]
Where's little Graham crackers?
Sh-hhh, you can't see me,
now can you?
Dude, you're scaring the kids.
Or can you?
You're scaring the kids.
Bitch.
Uh! My ear!
[clamoring]
Did you guys check out
this here?
Oh, my gosh, that's amazing.
Look-- oh, look,
there's a girl.
I'm gonna bang her--
tonight.
You mean the girl
in the reflection?
Oh, you mean you, Cameron?
[all] Ooh!
Right back at you.
Okay, you guys,
let's bring it in.
Hands in, right here.
To Graham's 21st birthday.
And to your dad.
Thank you, Dad,
for the wonderful room.
To Dr. Townes.
Gracias, Dr. Townes.
[all] Bitchin!
That's the greatest
cheers ever.
Documented, look,
did you see these?
History is in the making.
Ready, ready?
Get a close up on this, Cam.
One more, for good luck.
You-- one more for good luck.
If you don't do it,
your whole family could die.
Dead, forever.
Come on, don't kill your mom.
Don't kill your mom.
Fuck it!
Go.
One more shot.
[cheering]
Yeah, man!
Oh, gross.
My mouth is on fire.
It's on fire.
[clamoring]
I'm not doin' it, I'm not--
Hey.
I'm pooping while I play
Brick Breaker.
So, a lot tonight, Bro.
Yeah.
Before we go out,
I wanna do a couple jokes
with you, okay?
Just get your confidence
a little bit higher.
[groans]
Hear what I said?
Yeah.
You gotta trust me, man.
Can you leave?
I gotta wipe.
It's okay.
Part a life.
I gotta wipe.
Would you get the fuck out,
I gotta wipe!
First tip-- white teeth.
They love white teeth.
Second tip--
[whispers] Cameron,
Oh, my God, it smells in here.
Cameron,
Hey, baby.
Daddy's home.
World good.
Cracker Graham.
Hey, dudes.
Nice to meet you.
Douche bags arrived.
Dude, he looks like a douche.
You're better off without her
if she's gonna go out
with that guy.
I don't know.
Hey, give me
a little Lukie smile.
Give me a little Lukie smile.
Just one?
Nah.
It's gonna be all right, dude,
fuck 'em.
What's going on, man,
I'm Chad.
Hey, did you bring
a space ship?
Uh, no, no, it's time out, dude.
What's this all about?
It's the Cam cam-- smile.
What's this, what's this, what's
this?
You're on Cameron camera.
You guys been playing since--
Just smile at the camera
and say hoorah.
What's this--
Yeah, can we get a hoorah?
I'm just--
I'm just kidding, man.
Hey, whoa, we're leaving.
Get that fucking shit
out of my face!
Hey, you guys,
what is wrong with you?
Cam cam, get away--
Cam, stop.
[clamoring]
Shut the fuck up, man.
Whoo! whoo! whoo!
Fuck those bitches up!
Fuck.
Dude, put your sh--
I'm not kidding.
Put your shirt on.
I swear
on my grandmother's life
that I'm gonna take
you out tonight
and you're gonna get laid.
And you're gonna forget
about Capri
'cause you are
a handsome motherchucker.
You are sexy as hell, man.
I didn't mean to fight.
Graham, you play too much, man.
I did.
You were going to give 'em
a piece of your shit.
I kinda like-- I kinda like you
with your shirt off.
All right, camera off,
IDs on, let's go.
That is pretty awesome.
Changin' my clothes.
We're goin' out
and I'm gettin' dick
in my pussy.
Dick in your pussy
is what we're doin'.
Dick in your pussy?
There you go.
Oh, my God!
Here, here, here,
here, you want a pickup?
[chuckles] No.
What are you doing?
Stop, stop.
This is so cute, guys.
Sleeper hold.
Hey, no more fighting,
let's go get drunk.
We're here on a mission
to find the rare creature
they call the Grahaminator.
He's a-- he's a rare,
rare, spectacle.
He's been know to wander
this jungle aimlessly
looking for muff to burrow into
for hours and days at a time.
Some say he eats kids.
Some say he eats adults.
Some say he lives off nothing.
Some say he's the hardest thing
to spot in this--
Hey, Graham.
What?
Come here real quick.
One sec, dude.
Big play in the game.
Just real quick.
Hold on.
You want another card?
No.
All right, sorry,
sorry, sorry.
Cameron, Cameron.
Come here.
I'm winning.
Cameron, I love you.
How are you winning?
I'm playing blackjack.
Hey, pussy.
About that chick at the pool.
Oh, I know.
You know how you guys
said she was a hooker?
Yeah.
She mighta been.
I knew she was.
Hey, I'm sorry
about that, okay?
Sh-hhh, don't.
Come play with me.
Happy birthday.
I'm coming, let's go.
I want you to play ball.
Let's go.
Come on.
I wanna-- I wanna go--
remember that--
Let's go talk to that hooker.
Let's go find her.
Because I have money now.
Let's release teddy bear back
into the wilderness.
I have money.
I have-- wait, wait--
Do I look good
sitting backwards?
Do I look cool?
Look so hot.
All right, let's go.
Hey, guys, listen.
She was fine.
I got a solution.
No, what?
I got something else to do.
What?
It's sure thing.
Read it.
Yo, this girl just texted me,
she has two bottles of--
Paradise, this is--
Two bottles and a friend.
You can do that
any time back home.
We're in Vegas in a suite.
We're willing to do anything
to make you happy.
Read it again.
I just-- why do I have
to read it twice for you?
Read it again.
You heard it.
7-0-2-GET-2-WET.
It's a water park.
Luke, you are a articulate,
intelligent, good looking
individual that is gonna
go pay-- and back to me.
Hey, Tommy Kay.
That is going to go pay
for pussy.
One night, this one night!
Explain this logic to me.
And you Cameron,
I forgot about you
'cause you're a really
ugly looking dude
so you have to go
pay for pussy.
That makes sense.
I agree with him for--
What's the difference
for one night?
We're in Vegas, don't you want
to do something crazy?
Do you always play it safe?
No, we won't play it safe.
Let's go to the club
and get herpes.
But I'm not paying for pussy
and I'm not going
to a strip club
because I got
a bad feeling about it.
Hey, if worse comes to worse,
it'll make for a good story
and we'll leave.
Come on, let's just call
the number.
What's it--
It's not gonna hurt anyone.
[clamoring]
Luke, Luke, Luke--
Let's just go check
the place out.
What?
Why are you trippin', man.
I'm gonna get you a girl,
you'll never even remember
the name Capri.
Come on, one night.
What is one night?
We're in Vegas!
It's your brother's birthday.
Just call the number.
That's true.
Call the number.
Fuck it, give it here.
See, let's call it.
Tommy Kay, you won't regret it.
We'll just go for an hour.
Let's just go.
Are we going?
Hey, you're not
gonna regret it, buddy.
You won't have to pay
for it, I will.
This weekend's on me, man.
It's Cameron Townes'
party weekend.
You're not gonna regret it.
All right.
[phone ringing]
[whispering] Oh, my gosh,
there's so much alcohol
in that drink.
I put a lot of tequila in it.
I believe it.
Hey, there, welcome
to Paradise.
Hey, babe, what's goin' on?
Oh, she's hot.
Who am I talking to?
Uh, Cameron.
Cameron, nice to meet you.
Hey, nice to meet you.
It's Candice.
Oh, Candice, nice name.
Um, what's goin' on, Candice?
We're trying to get
some strippers over here.
Why don't you come here?
Come to you?
Yes.
Dude, that's how it works.
[Candice] I promise I'll make
it worth your while.
[Cameron] See, they got
kinky shit there.
That's how it works.
Where are you guys located?
We are very close
to the strip.
I'm getting paper,
I gotta get some paper.
[Luke] Hold on one second,
I gotta write this down.
Here, write this down.
Write it down like your life
depends on it 'cause it does.
All right, go ahead.
Okay, coming from the strip,
take the 515
to the next light.
Okay.
They better have like,
16 girls, at least.
Hey, Cameron, you excited
about it now?
Yeah, I'm cool,
yeah, let's do it.
Somebody grow some balls
and give me a smile,
Jesus, come on.
Come on, dude, let's do it.
We're gonna get you a woman.
On me, tonight it's
on me, boys.
Twenty-one,
you're only twenty-one?
What do you say,
what do you say, Graham?
[clamoring]
You have the option to stay,
if you want to, okay?
Whatever.
Let's do it.
Whatever, let's go.
Okay, for the record, I am
very we-- very, very, I am--
Stop taking-- I told you
to stop taking shots.
For the record-- why?
I am aware of the fact
that this a--
might be my worse decision ever.
And I come from a long line
of bad decisions.
But on the other, hey--
on the other hand,
this might be the brightest,
shiniest moment of my life.
Not at all-- it's probably
the worst idea ever.
Oh, come on, dude,
if nothing else
we'll have good stories
in the morning.
Graham, what's up, dude,
are you happy?
I'm excited.
Excited.
It's your hat.
Hey, guys, you guys
are so cute.
Luke, you're just so cute.
Graham, Cam, you guys
feel the energy?
I'm in, baby.
To a long life,
to a great trip in Vegas,
and you guys
are my fucking best friends
in the whole world.
On three,
happy birthday, Graham.
One, two, three--
[clamoring]
We gotta work on that.
Oh, shit, I don't think we've
ever done that once.
We've never done that right yet.
You guys know what?
What?
You know, there's really
only two things
that I'm really good at.
You know?
You know what they are, right?
One is making-- one is making
really bad decisions,
which are almost so bad,
they're awesome.
Like now.
And the other one
is thumb wrestling.
So, I'm gonna pay some hooker
and extra ten bucks
to thumb wrestle me,
and I'll be two for two
at everything I do wonderful.
What's next, where we goin'?
Huh?
Uh, what do you mean,
where are we going?
We're goin' to the whore house.
Paradise.
Cam, focus.
Yeah, hey, I'm lookin'.
Um,
Give me the directions, bro.
Yeah, I don't have that--
I don't have that paper.
What?
I know, I said I had it.
And I don't.
You douche.
It wasn't that-- hey, it wasn't
that many directions.
We're gonna find it, all right?
It's cool.
Chill out, dude,
chill out okay?
I'm chill,
I just don't know why--
Dude, look, hey, there's
the truck stop, right there.
Where?
It's right there.
We turn right there,
that's what they said.
There's a truck stop.
Turn the camera off.
That's the truck stop,
let's go.
Turn the camera off, please.
Look, we're there.
We made it.
We have arrived.
Is that a cop behind us?
Still okay.
This officially might be
the sketchiest place on Earth.
Shit, check this place out.
Might be offi-- yeah.
My worst idea ever.
Okay, Cam, you're now
Captain Obvious.
What are you guys waiting for?
Who is that?
On the count of three--
one, two, three.
Who is that?
We're goin' in.
Whoever said this is a bad idea
is a dumb motherfucker.
I like your camera.
Boys, boys, boys,
which one is Cameron?
Cameron is right here
and you're on here.
You're Cam cam, hello.
Uh, who is your friend
over here?
Yo, you.
Come here.
I wanta talk to Tommy Kay.
I'm not interested.
Uh, yeah, I'll make you
interested, baby.
Come here.
Come on, you're coming
with me, honey.
You're coming with me.
No, no, no, I can't, I can't.
[clamoring]
I want you and you.
You and you right now.
Us?
Together, same time.
One, two, three, so, let's go.
Hi.
Take me to-- Graham,
get yourself a girl.
Before we get started,
I will need a credit card.
And I will give you more
than that,
but take this to start with.
No, no, no, no.
Well, boys, welcome
to the Paradise.
Tommy Kay, it's on me,
quit being a little pussy.
Get it.
Don't do it!
Thank you Daddy, Dr. Townes.
Hoowee!
Let's put this thing down
for a second.
Oh, boo, we'll get it back
in a minute.
[female] Okay, let's take
your pants off.
[Cameron]
Yes! Cameravision anytime.
Well, ladies.
That is what the black card
went down for.
I gotta get a better view
of this.
There we go.
Yeah.
All right.
There's plenty to go around.
Wait right here, sexy big boy.
I'm gonna go put something
more comfortable on.
Okay.
Do it in the kitchen.
Okay, it's weird.
I want you.
This place is like
a fuckin' maze.
I hope you guys enjoyed
what you just saw.
Hey, look, we're back
to the start.
It's Tommy Kay.
We're black to the start?
I'm glad you're sober.
Nice to see you--
I'm sotally tober, dude.
Very funny.
How come you haven't gotten
a girl?
Ladies and gentlemen,
Have you gotten a girl?
we don't get--
Why are your pants on?
Dude, what are you saying
right now?
Whoa.
Dude, where did
this one come out of?
Hi.
Hello.
What's your name?
My name is Dr. Cameron Townes.
Dr. Cameron Townes.
Dr. Cameron Townes
looks like he needs a drink.
He does and he has
a drink here--
Hey.
Enough stuff, pass, Cam.
You'll get yours
in a minute.
Cam, please, lookit.
Hmm.
Hey.
I'm done.
Yeah, you'll get your--
hey, get yours.
Drink up.
It's on Daddy Townes.
So, Dr. Townes, hello.
Yes, mam, Dr. Blonde.
Sam.
Sam, sexy.
What would you like to do?
Do you want to go upstairs
and talk?
If by talk you mean fuck,
then yes.
Okay, then that is what
we should do.
All right, I'm comin'.
Come on.
Let's go.
Cam, be safe, man.
Hey, Tommy Kay, be a man.
Watch your step, please.
Grow some balls.
Dude, I don't pay for pussy.
Watch your step.
This place is crazy.
There's like 30 rooms--
All for you.
Don't you love it?
Perfect, it's all for me.
Close your eyes.
All right.
On my way.
Huh?
[door slams]
Hey!
[knocks]
Come on, funny, open the door.
So, you had some fun
for yourself earlier.
I'm tryin' to.
How you feelin'?
I'm feelin' good.
Yeah?
A little drunk, maybe?
Don't I know you from somewhere?
I don't know, maybe.
Where do you think
you know me from?
No, not sure?
So, a little sleepy?
[mumbles]
Yeah?
You wanna lay down?
That set's cool.
You like my outfit, baby?
Uh-huh.
Are you ready for this?
I was born ready for this.
Yeah, are you sure?
Yeah.
Hello?
Luke?
Graham?
Hello, this isn't funny, guys.
Hah.
Tommy!
What the fuck is this?
[door squeaks]
Tommy?
Yo, what is this?
Untie me.
You know, we paid you
good money for this.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Stop.
Help!
Somebody!--
Where are my friends?
Luke!
What are you doing, dude?
Stop it, please stop.
Help!
Graham!
Where are my friends?
What are you doing?
No, hey, what are you--
hey, don't do that.
Don't do that, don't do it.
Help!
Don't-- what are you doing
with that?
Stop.
[clunk]
[groans]
Stop, please just--
[yells]
Hey, guys.
Okay.
Holy shit!
What the fuck, man!
[praying]
God.
Come on, get me,
no, get me out--
Luke, Graham!
For fucking sake.
Get the fuck off me!
Luke!
Okay, please, okay, please,
I wanna go.
[wails, pleads]
Please, I'll give you
anything you want.
Come on, please.
...way that's gonna lead us
to the scene of the crime.
[Capri] How does it feel to
have the camera in your face?
Actually feels pretty good.
[Capri] Okay, so tell me
what's-- oh, shit.
Oh, my God, oh.
Oh, Graham, what the fuck?
[Capri] Graham cracker, oh!
Dude, I missed it,
you gotta do it again.
Just do it for the documentary.
[Capri] Okay, are you jealous?
Because I just got
the most amazing footage.
No, actually I have a good idea
because now we can get some tag
team double footage, you know?
Two different angles.
Dude.
Fuck.
But I'm gonna need your camera.
You all right, buddy?
Uh, yeah, I think I--
Hey, you think
you can do it again?
My coccyx.
Think you can do it again?
Let's go take some shots.
Do it.
You can fucking dance, dude.
I didn't know
this guy could dance.
I'm very limber for my size.
What do you mean,
for like a midget?
Now I'm just tired.
Speaking of midgets.
Hey, Capri?
Welcome to Luke cam.
Why don't you tell
the millions of viewers
what you're getting
ready to do.
How you're about to ditch me
for that douche bag
boyfriend of yours
after we've been running around
on him for the past year.
Luke, it was one time.
Well, one time--
one time at my house,
one time on the fourth of July,
one time at your grandma's
banquet, one time--
Why are you doing this
right now?
What do you mean,
why am I doing this?
Because I want to be with you.
Look, Jake is my boyfriend,
you're not.
You can't fuck around
with somebody for a year, Capri
and just expect him
to forget about it.
Have fun.
Thanks, you too.
[Capri] Hey, it's Jake--
you guys be nice.
Booo.
[Capri] Hey, baby.
Daddy's home.
Daddy, world dud.
What the fuck is this?
Get this out of my face.
We talked about this.
Uh, I don't think so.
Hey, dudes.
There gonna be
no documentary shit.
Ahhh!
Get wasted!
Woof!
All right, all right.
Yeah, I'm kind of in the middle
of a game right now.
Give me the ball, man.
Please.
I'll be over there in a second.
Come on.
There it goes,
this one's going in.
No way, come on, come on.
Watch this shit.
So, so much for our weekend
together in Vegas.
So, Salter, did it ever
get lonely
out there
on the battlefield?
I mean, it wasn't so bad--
there were girls.
Jake said there were no girls.
I mean, there weren't any
in the corps, you know,
but there were-- locals.
If you're willing to pay.
And I'm sure you were, right?
Six months is a long time
without the touch of a woman.
So, yeah.
Did Jake ever get
that desperate?
How the hell
am I supposed to know?
I wasn't watching him every
minute, you know?
What the fuck, man?
What up, bro?
Who's buyin' the next drinks?
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Jake, did you ever pay
for a hooker?
What?
I don't fucking know,
I don't wanna know.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
What's that, what is that?
Did you pay for a hooker?
I never paid for no hooker.
Yeah, I have no idea
what's going on, dude.
She's asking questions about
hookers and stuff like that.
I have no idea.
Did you ever pay for a hooker?
It's crazy.
What's goin' on?
Dude, hey, can you please just
get that shit out of my face?
Come on, man.
Happens.
Paid some whore.
What does that even mean?
You listen to one of my
drunk-ass friends?
And so I'm automatically accused
of fucking a prostitute?
Come on!
Why didn't you tell me
you did it then?
What does it matter, you're,
you're--
You couldn't answer.
You couldn't even answer
that question!
Did you? Did you?
Does it even fuckin' matter?
Yes, it matters!
Really?
Tell me, tell me the truth.
Right now, did you?
[Capri] Surprise!
Hello?
You guys.
Hello, where are you?
Hello?
[door closes]
[phone rings]
At the tone, please record
your message.
[beep]
Hey, Luke, it's me.
Things didn't work out
with Jake and I, so,
just, I wanna know
where you are-- call me.
Paradise.
Oh, my gosh.
Really?
Please tell me you guys
are not at a whore house.
Oh, my gosh.
I think I may have lost
my best friend.
And for Jake,
who turned out to be
a complete fucking asshole.
And now I'm gonna go find my
friends at a whore house.
This is definitely not
the night that I imagined.
Hi, honey.
[Capri] Hi.
How are you?
Is this Paradise?
Yes, it is.
How can I help you?
I'm just looking
for some of my friends.
Oh, let's see, four guys?
Four young guys wanting
to have a good time?
Yeah, were they here?
Yeah, they're here,
they're upstairs.
Do you need anything?
No, I just wanna find them,
yeah.
Well, if you go right up
the stairs and to the left
they'll be there waiting
for you-- go have some fun.
Waiting for me?
So, I can just walk up there?
Yeah, just go right up there.
It's fine, are you sure?
I'm positive.
My boyfriend had sex
with hookers.
And my friends are having sex
I've never actually met
a hooker.
I knew that bitch was lying.
Come on out, guys.
Playtime is over.
Luke?
Hello.
Tommy Kay?
Guys, where are you?
Guys, come on-- where are you?
Hello.
[whispering]
Cam-- Cam--
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[crying]
Oh, my God.
[screams]
Wait!
Somebody help me!
[screaming]
[rustling]
[sobbing]
[male] Hello?
[Capri] Luke.
Luke! Luke!
[sobs]
Oh, my God, Luke,
we gotta get you--
We have to get you outta here,
where's Graham?
We can run, get somebody.
Just hold on, okay?
Hold on, hold on to me.
[coughs]
Get up, please.
[Luke] We gotta get Graham.
Graham.
What did they do to him!
[Capri] We have to go now.
Graham is gone.
Go, go!
Please just come on, Luke.
We have to go.
[whispers] We have to go,
Luke, we have to go.
Get up, get up, get up.
[Capri sobbing]
Please, please.
Luke, Luke.
Leave me!
Go!
[coughs]
Just go, just go.
[footsteps]
[screams]
[growls]
Help, please, please.
We're almost out.
[Luke] No, Capri!
Fucking!
I'm gonna kill you!
[yelling]
My friend,
you have seen this incident
based on sworn testimony.
Can you prove that it
didn't happen?
Perhaps on your way home,
someone will pass you
in the dark.
And you will never know it!
For they will be
from outer space.
Many scientists believe
that another world
is watching us this moment.
We once laughed
at the horseless carriage,
the airplane, the telephone,
the electric light,
vitamins, radio,
and even television.
And now some of us laugh
at outer space.
God help us in the future.
Only moments ago, after five
long weeks of searching,
Capri Johnson was discovered
just a few feet from here
on this deserted road,
just outside of Reno, Nevada.
Thanks to an anonymous tip,
Channel 11 was first
on the scene.
I must warn you, the footage
you are about to see
is extremely disturbing.
Sensitive viewers
may not want to watch.
[crying]