God Damn Yankees!
You are very pretty.
A real doll.
Not touch him!
You doubt my honor?
Jesus will kill the Yankees.
And what are you doing now?
Come on, do something.
Cursed, you bloody fool.
I've already told a million times that
you to keep your big mouth in my house.
Where is my whip?
Father, wait. Let me explain.
Wait? No, my son, it is time
that you learn your lesson.
You don't understand, he insulted my honor.
What is this?
When do we have here?
The Yankees furnish us a visit.
Or do you want to kill us?
Then you have to start with me.
Do you understand that, Yankee?
Shut up, you bastard.
Don't you dare to touch the doll.
You want to fight? Come on...
What is going on here?
Do you see this jacket?
This is the uniform of a Yankee General that
we've taken from him when he came to our country.
Translate exactly what I say you fucking whore.
And what are you doing now, Yankee?
You did not understand. This land belongs
to me, from San Pedro to Santa Barbara.
It belongs to my family for over 200 years.
I am king and lord.
You catch that Yankee?
We'll meet again.
Goddamn strangers.
Wait, wait!
- Shut up, come on!
- Dad.
You ass!
You are nearby.
Stop, Carlo, stay.
No, get up, Daddy, get up.
O God.
He's dead, Dad, he's dead!
Why, why?
You have Carlo murdered dad.
My son... my son.
No, no daddy. Not more blood, Dad.
Daddy, please no more bloodshed.
No more bloodshed.
Forgive me, forgive me.
Damn, woman, what is lost with you?
Take my hand!
No, do not shoot, do not shoot.
Wait... why are you following us?
Do not shoot!
I'm here because of you because I love you.
What are you doing to me?
Why am I here? You guys are insane.
To help you... to help.
No, I will not.
A sling...
Please, Father, wait...
I have no more sons.
My only son is dead
The grave of the man we killed,
is here. They won't hurt you.
I don't kill women.
Now get out of the way.
For heaven's sake, Father, listen to it.
You have lost everything, as we lost my brother.
A brother. They have also lost
a brother and a husband.
My only son is dead,
go out of my way or I'll kill you.
Father, please reasonable.
Good... you .. I just want you.
Leave him alone.
Pick up the gun.
You should pick up the gun, you coward.