♪
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ WIND RUSTLING, MUSIC ♪ ]
[ COWS MOOING ]
[ BUGS RUSTLING, MUSIC ♪ ]
♪
[ RUSTLING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS IN DIRT ]
>> HOW ARE THE EGGS?
>> THEY'RE GOOD, JUST RIGHT.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO PICK UP SOME
ALFALFA IN ABOUT AN HOUR.
I GOT TO SEE IF DREW HAS ANY
LEFT, 'CAUSE STILL OWES ME SOME.
IF NOT...
[ SLURPS ]
MMM!
...I'M GONNA HAVE TO HEAD OUT TO
BOWMAN'S.
THAT WAS GOOD.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
THERE'S STILL SOME HASHBROWNS ON
THE STOVE, IF YOU WANT.
>> NO, I'M GOOD. THANKS.
I WANT TO GET IN BEFORE JIMMY
HEADS OUT.
>> THERE YOU GO, BABY.
[ DOG SNIFFING ]
GO ON. GO PEE-PEE. HURRY UP.
GOOD BOY.
YOU'RE A GOOD BOY.
SOMEBODY SMASHED SUSIE'S PUMPKIN
AGAIN.
>> WELL, I TOLD HER SHE
SHOULDN'T PUT IT OUT THERE.
>> YOU GETTING READY TO HEAD
OUT?
>> MM-HMM.
[ DOG PANTING ]
>> WHAT TIME WILL YOU BE BACK?
>> UH...SHOULDN'T BE TOO LATE.
I JUST HAVE TO GO CHECK OUT THE
PONDS.
MIGHT GO HUNTING AFTER THAT,
THOUGH, DEPENDING ON WHAT TIME
WE FINISH UP.
>> I'M HAVING LUNCH WITH ALISON
AFTER I TAKE ROOSTER TO THE VET.
MIGHT NOT BE BACK TILL THIS
AFTERNOON.
>> WHAT? I THOUGHT YOU ALREADY
TOOK HIM IN LAST WEEK.
>> HE HAS TO GET HIS TEETH
CLEANED.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU.
OOH.
[ DOG GROWLING ]
SORRY.
>> OKAY. I BETTER GET.
[ FLY BUZZING ]
>> DON'T EAT FLIES.
[ GATE CREAKS ]
[ CREEK BABBLING ]
>> THERE'S ONE.
I CAN'T GET HIM.
>> THEY'RE TOO FAST.
COME ON, LET'S GO GET DAD'S
FISHNET.
>> WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
[ CLANGING ]
>> HEY, JIMMY.
>> OH, HEY, ED.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> PRETTY GOOD. HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
I JUST GOT SOME BOOT IN MY GUM
HERE.
LISTEN, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT ME
TAGGING ALONG TODAY?
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO SEE HOW
THINGS ARE DOING OUT IN 30.
>> PRETTY SLOW.
>> DO YOU MIND IF I TAG ALONG?
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE HERE.
[ BOOT SCRAPING ]
>> GET IT OFF?
[ SCRAPING CONTINUES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
ALL RIGHT.
>> HELLO? HEY!
I WAS WONDERING IF WE WERE STILL
ON FOR THIS MORNING.
GOOD! OKAY.
UM, I'M JUST GONNA TAKE ROOSTER
OVER TO THE VET AND DROP HIM
OFF, AND I'LL JUST HEAD OVER
STRAIGHT FROM THERE.
YEAH? I WILL SEE YOU THEN. BYE.
YOU READY TO GO TO YOUR FAVORITE
PLACE?
PLACE, HUH?
YOU READY TO GO TO YOUR FAVORITE
[ DINGING ]
PLACE, HUH?
[ SEAT BELT CLICKS,
[ DINGING ]
DINGING STOPS ]
[ SEAT BELT CLICKS,
[ DOG PANTING ]
DINGING STOPS ]
ROOSTER, STOP.
[ DOG PANTING ]
[ PANTING STOPS ]
ROOSTER, STOP.
[ DOG BARKS, WHIMPERS ]
[ PANTING STOPS ]
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ DOG BARKS, WHIMPERS ]
[ CRASH ]
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ DOG GROWLS, BARKS ]
[ PILLS RATTLING ]
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
>> DO YOU THINK SHE'S SLEEPING?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
>> WHAT IF SHE WAKES UP?
>> SHE'S NOT GONNA WAKE UP.
>> WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
[ DOORS CREAK ]
[ BIRD SQUAWKING ]
>> HEY, MOK. IT'S JERRY.
YEAH, I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO COME
DOWN TO DOLAN'S THIS MORNING.
WE GOT A LOT OF MORTS TO CLEAN
UP.
AS SOON YOU COULD.
OKAY. I'LL SEE YOU. THANKS.
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
[ ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS ]
>> THIS IS THE WAGGS RESIDENCE.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
[ ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS ]
>> HEY, JOHNNY. THIS IS AL.
I WAS JUST WONDERING WHAT
YOU'RE DOING TODAY, BUT YOU'RE
PROBABLY AT WORK.
GIVE ME A CALL WHEN YOU GET A
CHANCE.
[ ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS ]
[ DOG BARKS, BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> JUST A SECOND.
>> T.J.
>> HEY, CARRY. HOW'S IT GOING?
>> IT'S GOING GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
>> UM...
TIRED.
>> ME TOO.
I DIDN'T WANT TO GET OUT OF BED
AT ALL THIS MORNING.
IT SUCKED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> ME? I'M JUST GETTING SOME
FOOD.
>> SO?
>> SO...WHAT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> COME ON.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
I DON'T KNOW. NO, I --
>> COME ON. I WON'T TELL ANYONE.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
NOTHING -- I MEAN, NOTHING
HAPPENED.
I SHOULD LET YOU, PROBABLY.
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE I
WON'T HEAR EVERYTHING, ANYWAY.
>> MM-HMM.
HEY.
UM...
I JUST TOTALLY FORGOT.
UM, LOOK, I'LL JUST -- I'LL SEE
YOU MONDAY.
[ BELL DINGS ]
[ DOG BARKS ]
>> ROOSTER, THE DOG.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
ALL RIGHT.
UH, SO, DID YOU WANT TO DO, UH,
ROOSTER'S BOOSTERS TODAY, TOO,
OR...
[ LAUGHS ]
...OR JUST THE DENTAL?
>> I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS HE DUE?
>> UH, IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
I MEAN, SOON.
YOU KNOW, WE COULD DO HIS TEETH
TODAY AND THEN, UH...
YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE WE COULD FIT
HIM IN NEXT WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON,
IF THAT WOULD WORK FOR YOU OR WE
COULD JUST DO IT ALL TODAY.
>> WEDNESDAY WOULD BE GOOD.
>> OKAY, YEAH, WEDNESDAY.
ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH, OKAY.
OH, JUST SIGN RIGHT THERE.
YOU CAN USE MY PEN.
>> OH, AND ALSO, HE HAS A LITTLE
THING WITH HIS EYE MAYBE YOU CAN
LOOK AT WHEN HE'S UNDER.
HE'S, LIKE -- HE'S KIND OF
CRYING, LIKE AN EYELASH OR
SOMETHING, MAYBE.
>> OKAY, SURE.
I CAN TAKE A LOOK AT THAT.
OKAY, UH, SO, HE'LL PROBABLY BE
READY AROUND 2:00, UH, BUT YOU
MIGHT WANT TO CALL BEFORE COMING
IN.
>> OKAY.
>> HOW'S YOUR DAUGHTER, BY THE
WAY?
>> OH. SHE'S GOOD.
>> YEAH?
>> SHE JUST TURNED 16.
>> OH. WELL, TELL HER I SAID
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> I WILL. YEAH.
[ DOG BARKS ]
YOU BE GOOD.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY, TAKE CARE.
>> BYE.
[ DOOR OPENS, BELLS JINGLE ]
>> NICE DAY.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> WISH I WAS OUT HUNTING.
GOOD PHEASANT DAY.
YOU SEE A PHEASANT, YOU JUST GO
AHEAD AND PULL ON OVER.
>> ISN'T THAT ILLEGAL?
>> EH...
IF YOU WALK OUT IN THE FIELD
BEFORE YOU SHOOT, JUST FROM THE
CAR...
I THINK.
[ POLICE RADIO CHATTER ]
HEY, YOU MIND PULLING OVER TO
THIS HOUSE UP HERE?
>> THE RED ONE?
>> YEAH. I NEED TO SEE IF I CAN
GET SOME HAY.
>> YEAH.
[ CAR DOORS CLOSE ]
>> HEY, THERE.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
>> A SNAKE.
>> CAN I SEE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WOW.
THAT'S A NICE ONE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> IS YOUR GRANDPA HOME?
>> OVER THERE.
>> OH, NO.
WHAT'D I DO THIS TIME?
>> STICK 'EM UP.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> HOW YOU DOING, ED?
HOW YOU BEEN?
>> NOT BAD.
HEY, DREW, THIS IS JIMMY, ONE OF
MY DEPUTIES.
>> YEAH.
>> I SEE YOU'RE CUTTING UP A BIT
OF WOOD HERE, HUH?
>> YEAH, BILLY AND ME WENT UP
LAST WEEKEND UP ABOVE CORRAL,
OVER AT COUCH SUMMIT.
THAT SOMETHING?
>> I SEE YOU'RE DOING DOUBLE
DUTY AS A GRANDPA, TOO.
>> YEAH.
SHE'S SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT, BUT SHE'S
SOMETHING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> YEAH, IT'S FUN, THOUGH, ISN'T
IT?
WELL, LOOK, I'D LOVE TO STAND
HERE AND SHOOT THE BREEZE WITH
YOU.
WE'VE GOT TO GET BACK.
JUST STOPPED BY TO SEE IF YOU
HAD ANY HAY LEFT.
>> WELL, I WISH YOU'D STOPPED A
COUPLE DAYS SOONER.
WE, UH, SOLD THE LAST OF IT
WEDNESDAY.
UH, HOW SOON DO YOU NEED IT?
>> NOW. I NEED IT NOW.
>> OH.
>> YEAH.
LET ME KNOW WHEN YOU CUT YOUR
BOTTOM FIELD, ALL RIGHT?
>> WILL DO, WILL DO.
>> THANKS, DREW.
GOOD SEEING YOU.
[ GIRL SINGING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> WHAT ARE YOU TWO UP TO?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE OUT IN THE
FIELD.
>> WE WERE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WE'RE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
>> DAD'S SHOVEL.
>> DID YOU LOOK OUT BY THE
STALLS?
>> NO.
>> YOU GUYS ABOUT READY FOR SOME
LUNCH?
OKAY, WELL, COME AND GET IT.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING, COWS MOOING ]
[ CREEK BABBLING,
MOOING, CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
[ MOOING CONTINUES ]
[ HEAVY-METAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF,
MUSIC STOPS ]
>> SHIT.
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
OH, SHIT.
>> HEY. HEY.
>> HEY.
>> THANKS.
>> YEAH.
>> LOT OF MORTS, HUH?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> SEE HOW LOW THE WATER IS?
THE FISH DON'T GET ENOUGH
OXYGEN.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THE WATER?
>> SOME SON OF A BITCH UP THERE
DIVERTED IT.
>> WHERE?
>> I THINK IT'S THAT BIT OF LAND
MR. DOLAN'S LEASING TO THAT GUY
FROM CALIFORNIA.
>> DOESN'T HE KNOW THAT THERE'S
PONDS DOWN HERE?
>> HE'S SUPPOSED TO.
>> [ BREATHING RAPIDLY ]
>> THAT SHIT'S HARD FOR A
SMOKER.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> JUST BREATHING IN AND OUT
LIKE THAT.
>> [ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
>> IT'S HARD.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> [ COUGHS ]
OH, MAN.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> WHAT'S UP, MAN?
>> OH, MAN.
>> EHH...
AHH!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
OH, THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
>> YOU UP NEXT?
>> NO. NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> PUSSY.
>> COME ON, DUDE.
I'VE ALREADY DONE IT A BUNCH OF
TIMES.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE BEING CHOKED
RIGHT NOW.
LET IT GO.
>> [ CHUCKLES ] FAG.
>> DO ME, JOHN.
>> DO YOU? SURE, I'LL DO YOU.
I MEAN, IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY,
IT SEEMS A LITTLE WEIRD, BUT,
YEAH, I'LL GIVE YOU A THROW.
>> [ BREATHING RAPIDLY ]
>> ISN'T THAT DANGEROUS, THOUGH?
>> IT'S JUST LIKE ANYTHING.
YOU ONLY KILL A COUPLE BRAIN
CELLS.
>> LIKE A FISH.
>> [ GASPS, GROANS ]
OH...MY GOD.
OH, SHIT, MAN.
[ BOTTLE CLINKS ]
[ GIRL BREATHING RAPIDLY ]
[ BREATHING STOPS ]
[ FLY BUZZES ]
[ CAT MEOWS ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ CAT MEOWING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ MEOWING CONTINUES ]
[ RHYTHMIC KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
>> I NEED TO PEE.
>> YEAH, JUST A SECOND.
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
>> [ BREATHING RAPIDLY ]
>> GOT TO SQUEEZE HARDER.
>> SO, WHAT HAPPENED AFTER I
LEFT LAST NIGHT, MAN?
ANYTHING COOL?
>> NO. I PRETTY MUCH JUST WENT
HOME.
>> DID YOU DO WHAT'S HER NAME?
>> [ Laughing ] NO.
>> MAN, I WOULD HAVE DONE HER.
HEY, SO, UM, DO YOU WANT TO HELP
ME MAKE THIS THING LATER?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> WELL, IT'S LIKE I PROMISED MY
STEP-BROTHER I'D HELP HIM MAKE
THIS VIDEO, UH, FOR SCOUTS.
IT'S, LIKE, A COMMERCIAL FOR
CLEAR PONDS OR SOMETHING.
>> SCOUTS?
>> YEAH, WELL, I GUESS THAT, UH,
HIS SCOUTMASTER, LIKE, WORKS FOR
THEM OR SOMETHING, AND HE WAS
LIKE, "YOU KNOW, MAKE A
COMMERCIAL, AND WE'LL PUT IT ON
OUR WEBSITE."
IT'S FOR THESE NEW, LIKE, FISH
STICKS, LIKE THESE WHALE THINGS
OR SOMETHING.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
WHALES AREN'T EVEN FISH.
THAT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE ANY
SENSE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT IT'S,
LIKE -- YOU KNOW, I GUESS THEY
TASTE LIKE CHICKEN.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> SO IT'S LIKE A -- YOU KNOW,
LIKE A TASTY...
♪ CHICKEN-WHALE, MAMMAL-FISH
♪ DA, DA, DA
YOU KNOW?
OH, I CALL TO CALL MOK...
GET ME SOME FISH.
MOK!
[ Ringing ]
PICK UP THE PHONE, YOU FOK.
[ RINGTONE PLAYS ]
[ Ringing continues ]
[ RINGTONE CONTINUES ]
>> YEAH?
NOTHING REALLY. JUST HANGIN'.
WHAT?
YEAH, WE ACTUALLY HAVE A WHOLE
BUNCH OF THOSE.
I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, I MEAN...
I-I CAN ASK HIM.
UM...MY FRIEND WANTS TO KNOW IF
HE CAN HAVE SOME OF THOSE MORTS
FOR, LIKE, A PROJECT THING.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH. TELL HIM TO TAKE A
WHOLE DAMN TRUCKFUL.
>> UM, YEAH.
YOU CAN BUY IT.
I HAVE TO GO, THOUGH.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> YEAH?
>> HEY, UM, I GOT A QUESTION.
ARE -- ARE YOU THE ONE FARMING
THAT SOUTHERN ACRE OF DOLAN'S?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, UM, I'M
JERRY GARABRANT, AND I LEASE HIS
PONDS.
AND I WAS JUST WONDERING,
BECAUSE YOU -- YOU DIVERTED THAT
WATER UP IN THE FIELD AND PRETTY
MUCH KILLED MY ENTIRE CROP.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT.
>> YOU'RE USING THE WATER FOR
IRRIGATION, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, YOU DIVERTING THAT
WATER KILLED MY FISH.
YOU KNEW THERE WERE PONDS
DOWNSTREAM, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHY'D YOU DIVERT THE
WATER?
YOU KNOW FISH NEED WATER.
>> WELL, SO DOES MY FIELD.
>> YEAH, BUT IT'S MY WATER.
>> WELL, I HAVE JUST AS MUCH
RIGHT TO THAT WATER AS YOU DO.
>> BUT MY FISH NEED THAT WATER.
LOOK, ALL I KNOW IS THAT I GOT A
POND FULL OF DEAD FISH, AND I
WANT TO KNOW WHAT SOMEONE'S
GONNA DO ABOUT IT, BECAUSE I
THINK SOMEONE'S GONNA HAVE TO
PAY ME BACK OR SOMETHING, 'CAUSE
WE WERE JUST ABOUT TO GO TO
HARVEST.
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK I HAVE TO
PAY YOU ANYTHING.
I MEAN, LOOK, I'M SORRY ABOUT
YOUR FISH, BUT I HAVE, YOU KNOW,
JUST AS MUCH RIGHT TO THAT WATER
AS YOU DO.
>> WHAT?
>> I SAID I HAVE JUST AS MUCH
RIGHT TO THAT WATER AS YOU DO.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL SEE YOU IN COURT.
COME ON, MOK.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER, REVS ]
[ CAT MEOWS ]
>> I REALLY, REALLY DOUBT
KIRBY'S DAD GOT HIM AN ALLIGATOR
FOR HIS BIRTHDAY.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
HE SAID THAT WE CAN RIDE HIM
WHEN HE GETS BIGGER AND WE CAN
PUNCH HIM IN THE HEAD WHEN HE
TRIES TO BITE YOU.
>> HMM. REALLY? HUH.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD ASK YOUR DAD
THEN.
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA GO BACK
OUTSIDE?
WEREN'T YOU TRYING TO CATCH A
FISH?
[ CAT MEOWS ]
WHAT'D YOU NEED THE SHOVEL FOR?
WELL, TRY NOT TO GET ANY
DIRTIER, OKAY?
I THINK GRANDMA'S COMING OVER
LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
[ COWS MOOING ]
>> YOU THINK THE GIRL'S STILL
THERE, HUH?
MAYBE A COYOTE GOT HER.
>> A COYOTE DIDN'T GET HER.
>> MAYBE IT GOT HER, THOUGH.
>> SO, YOU GETTING HAY FOR SOME
COWS OR...?
>> NO. WE HAVE A HORSE AND A
DONKEY.
>> YOU RIDE?
>> YEAH, I RIDE SOMETIMES,
MOSTLY WHEN I'M ELK HUNTING.
MY WIFE'S THE RIDER.
USED TO BE A BARREL RACER.
>> YEAH, I'M NOT MUCH OF A HORSE
GUY.
[ POLICE RADIO CHATTER ]
MY MOM MADE ME RIDE ONCE WHEN I
WAS A KID.
WE HAD SOME HORSES ON OUR FARM.
AND SHE DIDN'T TIGHTEN THE
SADDLE ENOUGH, AND IT SLIPPED.
HORSE WAS WALKING ALONG, AND I
WAS JUST HANGING DOWN UPSIDE
DOWN UNDERNEATH IT.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
IT WAS KIND OF SCARY.
>> YEAH, I BET.
YOU GET HURT?
>> NO. IT WAS A -- IT WAS A GOOD
HORSE.
IT WAS SMART.
KIND OF REALIZED SOMETHING WAS
WRONG AND JUST STOPPED WALKING.
I JUST FELL OFF.
>> YEAH, I COULD SEE HOW THAT
WOULD BE TRAUMATIC, THOUGH.
>> TRAUMATIC?
>> YEAH.
PULL OVER UP HERE AT THESE
GRAVEL PITS.
>> YEAH.
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU TAKE, BIKES,
WHEN YOU GO UP HUNTING THEN?
>> I ACTUALLY, UH...
I REALLY DON'T DO MUCH HUNTING.
>> NO?
>> NOT REALLY, NO.
>> HUH.
[ BEEPING ]
SO, YOU EVER WATCH
"WALKER, TEXAS RANGER"?
>> I'VE SEEN IT.
>> GOOD SHOW.
I LOVE THAT SHOW.
[ POLICE RADIO CHATTER ]
>> HI, CARRY.
>> HEY, MRS. GARABRANT.
>> AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE AT
PRACTICE?
>> YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, HAD TO
WORK.
>> BUMMER.
I HOPE SUSIE GOT UP.
SHE WAS OUT COLD WHEN I LEFT THE
HOUSE.
[ SCANNERS BEEPING ]
HOW WAS THE MOVIE?
>> MOVIE?
>> SUSAN SAID YOU WERE GOING TO
A MOVIE?
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH.
UM...WE WENT TO THAT THEATER
OVER BY THE MALL.
>> WHAT'D YOU SEE?
>> UM...I DON'T...
I'M DRAWING -- I CAN'T REMEMBER.
IT'S SOMETHING LIKE "COUPLES"...
SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> HOW WAS IT?
>> UM, IT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
IT WAS ONE OF THOSE -- IT WAS
LIKE...
YEAH.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
>> TWO OLD MESSAGES.
>> MAILBOX 1, MESSAGE 1.
[ BEEP ]
>> HI, MARTHA.
I WAS JUST CALLING TO SEE IF
YOU GUYS WANTED TO COME OVER
FOR LUNCH TOMORROW AFTER
CHURCH.
I KNOW YOU'RE PROBABLY PRETTY
BUSY.
GIVE ME A CALL WHEN YOU GET A
CHANCE.
[ BEEP ]
>> 9:22, MESSAGE 2.
>> HI. THIS IS KATIE.
[ BEEP ]
I WAS JUST WONDERING WHY SUSAN
>> HI. THIS IS KATIE.
WASN'T AT PRACTICE.
I WAS JUST WONDERING WHY SUSAN
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
WASN'T AT PRACTICE.
EVERYTHING WAS OKAY.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
HOPE TO SEE HER ON MONDAY.
EVERYTHING WAS OKAY.
[ DIAL TONE ]
HOPE TO SEE HER ON MONDAY.
>> SUSAN?
[ DIAL TONE ]
CAN I COME IN?
IT'S AFTER 1:00.
YOU MISSED PRACTICE.
SUSIE?
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
HELLO?
SUSAN?
[ Dialing ]
SUSAN, IT'S YOUR MOTHER.
WOULD YOU PLEASE CALL ME AND
TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
THANK YOU.
[ Beep ]
[ SHOVEL SCRAPING ]
>> [ GROANS ]
>> I WANT TO TRY.
>> OKAY.
THE GROUND'S REALLY HARD.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> HERE.
WE MIGHT JUST...NO.
>> WE -- WE CAN JUST PUT THE
DIRT ON TOP OF HER.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO DO, THOUGH.
IT MIGHT BE NICER DOWN BY THE
CREEK.
>> YEAH.
>> IT MIGHT BE A NICE PLACE TO
PUT HER.
AND SOFTER, TOO.
>> YEAH.
[ CREEK BABBLING ]
WHAT ABOUT NEXT TO THAT?
>> THE TREE?
>> UH-HUH.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING, COWS MOOING ]
[ GUNSHOT, MOOING CONTINUES ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
>> SO, WALKER'S OUT PATROLLING
WITH JIMMY, AND THEY'RE HUNTING
DOWN THIS GUY WHO KIDNAPPED
JIMMY'S FRIEND'S SISTER.
AND, UH, THEY GET TO THIS
WAREHOUSE, AND, UH, UH,
WALKER -- HE GOES TO KICK IN THE
DOOR, BUT IT DOESN'T OPEN, SO...
THEN JIMMY...GIVES IT A TRY.
HANG ON A SECOND.
[ STATIC CRACKLING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ CRACKLING CONTINUES ]
[ WIND GUSTING ]
[ SIGHS ]
OH, I THOUGHT I SAW A BIRD.
I GUESS NOT.
MIGHT HAVE BEEN A QUAIL.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH YOU'VE
SEEN OF THAT SHOW, BUT JIMMY'S
TRYING TO SET WALKER UP WITH
THIS GAL, AND --
[ BEEPING ]
LOOKS LIKE THAT GUY WAS DOING
76.
IN A 60-MILE-AN-HOUR ZONE.
>> YEAH, WELL, I-I USUALLY JUST
LET SOMETHING LIKE THAT SLIDE
UNLESS THEY'RE REALLY BOOKING
IT.
>> 76 IN A 60 KIND OF IS BOOKING
IT...IN MY BOOK.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ CLICK, SIREN WAILS ]
[ WAILING CONTINUES ]
>> FREAKIN' JIMMY, MAN.
>> ED?
ED?
[ BIRD SQUAWKS ]
>> I GOT HIM! I GOT HIM!
>> CHRIST.
>> WHOO-HOO!
>> WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
>> UH...
>> ONE SHOT!
>> ...HE WAS JUST...
>> ...HE SHOT A PHEASANT.
>> ONE SHOT!
>> WELL, WHY THE HELL YOU
>> ...HE SHOT A PHEASANT.
PULLING ME OVER?
>> WELL, WHY THE HELL YOU
>> WELL, WE HAD YOU CLOCKED IN
PULLING ME OVER?
AT ABOUT 76 MILES AN HOUR, SO,
>> WELL, WE HAD YOU CLOCKED IN
UH...
AT ABOUT 76 MILES AN HOUR, SO,
YOU WERE GOING A BIT FAST THERE.
UH...
UH, YOU MIND SHOWING ME YOUR
YOU WERE GOING A BIT FAST THERE.
LICENSE AND REGISTRATION?
UH, YOU MIND SHOWING ME YOUR
>> YEAH, I MIND. SHIT, MAN.
LICENSE AND REGISTRATION?
I THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS.
>> [ SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> NOW MY DAMN INSURANCE IS
GONNA GO UP.
SHIT!
>> I'M SORRY, MAN.
BE RIGHT BACK.
>> I'LL BE RIGHT HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT!
[ BREATHING DEEPLY, LAUGHING ]
>> YOU, UH -- YOU SCARED THOSE
FOLKS HALF TO DEATH.
>> R-RUN THEIR LICENSE, LET THEM
GO.
ISN'T IT A NICE ONE?
>> YEAH. I STILL DON'T THINK
THAT'S LEGAL.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> UH, JUST DON'T GET ANY BLOOD
ON MY CAR, OKAY?
>> WE'RE NOT GONNA SIT THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ PUNK MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> HEY, SO, UH, WHAT'S BROWN AND
STICKY?
A STICK.
YOU GET IT?
'CAUSE IT'S, LIKE -- IT'S
STICKY, BUT YOU THINK THAT IT --
>> I GET IT.
>> [ Laughing ] YEAH.
I LIKE THAT JOKE.
WHERE ARE WE SUPPOSED TO TURN
LEFT, AGAIN?
>> UH...
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
[ CAR DOORS CLOSE ]
>> MOK!
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
>> WHAT'S UP, MAN?
SO, DUDE, IS THIS, LIKE, A
NORMAL AMOUNT OF DEAD FISH?
'CAUSE THIS IS CRAZY.
>> NO, THIS SHIT'S MESSED UP.
SOME FARMER, LIKE, TOTALLY
SCREWED US.
>> IT SMELLS, MAN.
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
>> T.J. HEY.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS YOU WHO WAS
COMING OUT.
>> HEY.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> UM...
I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU GUYS SURE DID PICK A
PERFECT DAY TO NEED A BUNCH OF
DEAD FISH, DIDN'T YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU USING THEM FOR,
ANYWAY?
>> UM, WE'RE GONNA -- WELL, THIS
IS, UH -- THIS IS JOHN.
>> JERRY.
>> WE'RE GONNA USE THEM 'CAUSE
HIS STEP-BROTHER...
>> IT'S FOR A SCOUTS VIDEO.
>> A WHAT?
>> SCOUTS VIDEO.
IT'S FOR A-A MAMMAL FISH.
WE'RE SHOWING FISH STICKS.
IT'S GONNA BE PRETTY AWESOME.
WE'RE EXCITED ABOUT IT.
>> WELL...TAKE AS MANY AS YOU
NEED.
TAKE THE WHOLE DAMN PILE.
>> COOL. THANK YOU.
>> HEY, T.J., UM...
YOU SHOULD COME OVER TO DINNER
SOMETIME AGAIN.
SUSIE SAID YOU LIKE FISH.
YOU LIKE TROUT?
>> IT'S A GOOD FISH.
>> WELL, I MAKE A PRETTY MEAN
TROUT.
BUHL'S "THE TROUT CAPITAL OF THE
WORLD."
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
>> MNH-MNH.
>> YOU KNOW THAT?
MOK KNOWS THAT.
WHAT'S THE TROUT CAPITAL?
>> YEP.
>> BUHL. YEP.
WELL, HAVE AT IT, GUYS.
>> JUST -- JUST RAKE THEM --
RAKE THEM UP.
>> HI. UH, JUDY, IT'S MARTHA.
I'M WONDERING IF YOU OR DANICA
HAS SEEN SUSAN.
CAN YOU GIVE ME A CALL, PLEASE?
THANKS.
[ Beep ]
[ FIREPLACE WHOOSHES ]
HI. UM, CAN I TALK TO CARRY,
PLEASE?
>> Yep. Just a minute.
>> THANKS.
>> Hi. This is Carry.
>> HI, CARRY.
THIS IS MARTHA, SUSAN'S MOM.
>> Oh, hi. How are you?
>> I'M GOOD.
I WAS JUST WONDERING -- DO YOU
KNOW WHERE SUSAN IS, BY ANY
CHANCE?
>> UM, I HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE
LAST NIGHT.
WHY?
>> Well, I got call from
Mrs. Brown, and I guess she
wasn't at practice.
>> UM, HAVE YOU TALKED TO
DANICA?
Maybe she's over at Danica's.
>> HER CAR'S STILL HERE IS THE
THING.
>> HAVE YOU TRIED CALLING
DANICA?
>> Yeah. There wasn't any
answer.
WHAT DID YOU GUYS DO AFTER THE
MOVIES LAST NIGHT?
>> WELL, WE ALL JUST, UM...
I MEAN, I-I WENT HOME.
Uh, I'm not sure what Susan did.
They're probably just over at
Danica's sleeping still.
>> PROBABLY.
WELL, IF YOU SEE SUSAN OR IF YOU
HEAR ANYTHING, CAN YOU ASK HER
TO GIVE ME A CALL, PLEASE?
>> Okay, I will.
>> THANKS.
[ Beep ]
[ CREEK BABBLING ]
>> [ SNIFFLES, SIGHS ]
DO YOU THINK GRANDMA'S HERE YET?
I HOPE SHE BRINGS SOME COOKIES.
I'M THIRSTY.
DO YOU THINK WE CAN DRINK THAT
WATER?
>> MNH-MNH.
DAD SAID WE'D BET BEAVER FEVER.
>> WHAT'S BEAVER FEVER?
>> IT'S WHERE YOUR FRONT TEETH
GET REALLY BIG.
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
DO YOU THINK IT'S DEEP ENOUGH?
>> THINK SO.
>> SHOULD WE GO GET HER?
>> GET HER FEET.
>> [ GRUNTS ]
SHE'S HEAVY.
HOW ARE WE GONNA MOVE HER?
>> WE CAN USE THE WAGON, MAYBE.
>> MAYBE.
[ GRUNTS ]
SHE'S PRETTY.
BUT SHE SMELLS KIND OF FUNNY.
[ BIRD SQUAWKS ]
>> THAT'S WHAT MOST GIRLS ARE
LIKE.
>> SHE SMELLS LIKE MACARONI AND
CHEESE.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
[ CHAIN SAW WHIRS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> MRS. GARABRANT?
>> OH. HI.
SORRY. UH...
I TRIED CALLING BEFORE, BUT
THERE WASN'T ANY ANSWER.
UM...I JUST CAME BY TO SEE IF
SUSAN WAS HERE.
>> NO. I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
>> YOU HAVEN'T?
>> NOT SINCE LAST NIGHT.
>> HUH. I TALKED TO CARRY, AND
SHE THOUGHT THAT SHE CAME BACK
HERE WITH YOU.
>> NO, I HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE
THE PARTY.
I THOUGHT SHE TOOK OFF WITH
CARRY.
>> PARTY.
>> YEAH. THEY BOTH LEFT BEFORE I
DID.
[ WATER SPLASHING ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
>> ♪ CHASE THE CHICK AWAY
♪ MAN WON'T THINK HE CAN HAVE IT
ALMOST ANY DAY ♪
♪ IF MOM DOESN'T LIKE IT, SHE'S
A BITCH ♪
♪ CHASE THE CHICK AWAY
MAN, THIS SONG'S GONNA BE GOOD.
SO, UH, THAT WAS SUSAN'S DAD UP
THERE, HUH?
AND, UH, THAT'S REALLY
INTERESTING YOU HAD DINNER WITH
THE FAMILY.
YOU NEVER MENTIONED THAT TO ME.
[ CHUCKLES ] YOU DID HER.
YOU TOTALLY DID HER.
YOU DID HER, RIGHT?
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY, DAD.
>> HI, DAD.
>> WHERE YOU GUYS GOING WITH
THAT WAGON?
>> Both: DOWN BY THE STREAM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CAN I HAVE A SIP OF THAT?
THANKS.
HEY, YOUR MOM SAID YOU GUYS TOOK
THE SHOVEL OUT THERE, TOO.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH? MAKE SURE YOU BRING IT
BACK UP TO THE HOUSE WHEN YOU'RE
DONE.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT. AND THE WAGON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
[ WAGON WHEELS SQUEAKING,
>> ALL RIGHT.
COWS MOOING ]
[ BIRDS SQUAWKING ]
[ BRAKES SQUEAL ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WATER GOT DIVERTED UPSTREAM,
SO NO OXYGEN.
>> WELL, I CAN'T FIND SUSAN.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE SHE'S AT.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I MEAN I CALLED ALL HER
FRIENDS.
HER CAR'S AT HOME, BUT SHE'S
NOT.
SHE DIDN'T GO TO PRACTICE.
UM...
NOBODY SEEMS TO KNOW WHERE SHE
IS.
DID YOU KNOW SHE WAS GOING TO A
PARTY LAST NIGHT?
>> I THOUGHT SHE SAID SHE WAS
GOING TO A MOVIE.
>> YEAH, WELL, APPARENTLY, SHE
WENT TO A PARTY WITH CARRY AND
DANICA, BUT NEITHER OF THEM
KNOWS WHERE SHE WENT AFTER.
>> AND HER CAR'S HOME?
AND YOU CALLED EVERYONE YOU CAN
THINK OF?
DID YOU CALL YOUR DAD?
>> SHOULD I?
>> I MEAN...I'M SURE SHE'S JUST
WITH ONE OF HER OTHER FRIENDS,
BUT...IT COULDN'T HURT.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> HELLO?
HEY.
GOOD. HOW ABOUT YOU?
DID -- DID MOM CALL ABOUT
TOMORROW?
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH, GOD.
YOU GUYS ARE ALWAYS BUSY.
I WAS GONNA CALL JERRY, ASK HIM
IF HE WANTED TO GO HUNTING WITH
ME SOMETIME SOON.
I JUST GOT A PHEASANT TODAY --
ONE SHOT.
PROBABLY HAVE IT FOR DINNER.
YEAH, LET HIM KNOW.
UH...LOOK, WE'RE ON DUTY HERE,
SO I-I SHOULD PROBABLY GET BACK.
BUT, UH, I'LL LET MOM KNOW YOU
CALLED AND --
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YEAH.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU SAW
HER?
WE CAN'T TECHNICALLY FILE A
MISSING-PERSONS REPORT FOR 48
HOURS, BUT, YEAH, SURE.
YEAH, OF COURSE.
YOU -- YOU LET ME KNOW IF YOU
HEAR ANYTHING, TOO.
OKAY?
OKAY. RIGHT.
>> WHAT -- WHAT'S UP?
>> [ SIGHS ]
JUST MY DAUGHTER.
HER DAUGHTER'S MISSING.
>> SHOULD I KEEP DOING IT?
>> YEAH, KEEP DOING IT.
YOU'RE MAKING A CRAPLOAD OF FISH
STICKS.
MMM. DELICIOUS FISH STICKS.
[ Laughing ] WHOA!
OH, MAN. THAT IS GOOD.
[ SINGING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> HEY, UM...
>> HEY, NO, NO, NO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
>> THERE'S TOO MUCH GUTS.
>> NO, THERE'S NOT TOO MUCH
GUTS!
JUST KEEP THROWING THEM!
KEEP THROWING THEM! DON'T STOP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
>> I'M CLEANING IT OFF!
>> TURN OFF THE MOWER FIRST,
RETARD!
[ LAWN MOWER SHUTS OFF ]
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
>> HAVE YOU EVER, LIKE,
ACCIDENTALLY...
PURPOSELY DONE SOMETHING?
YOU KNOW, LIKE, I GUESS IT'S
MORE LIKE -- MORE LIKE YOU DO IT
ON PURPOSE, BUT YOU DON'T...
LIKE...
LIKE WHEN YOU MAKE A MISTAKE,
BUT THEN YOU DON'T -- YOU DON'T
REALLY KNOW THAT YOU'RE MAKING A
MISTAKE, BUT MAYBE YOU KIND
OF...
LIKE, YOU KNOW, BUT IT'S NOT A
MISTAKE BECAUSE...
YOU'RE DOING IT, YOU KNOW?
AND -- AND -- AND -- AND YOU
KNOW THAT YOU'RE DOING IT.
AND EVEN -- EVEN IF YOU DON'T...
REALLY KNOW THAT YOU'RE DOING
IT, THEN IT STILL...
IT STILL DOESN'T TAKE AWAY FROM
THE FACT THAT YOU DID IT.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, EVEN IF YOU
DIDN'T MEANT TO, YOU STILL --
YOU STILL DID IT.
>> IF YOU KNOCKED UP A BABE OR
SOMETHING?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
YEAH, KIND OF, I GUESS.
>> [ Laughing ] YEAH, MAN.
THAT'S BASICALLY WHY I EXIST,
YOU KNOW?
>> RIGHT.
>> MY PARENTS DIDN'T WANT THAT
SHIT.
[ LAWN MOWER WHIRRING,
FISH THUDDING ]
WHY? WHAT'D YOU DO?
>> NOTHING.
I WAS JUST THINKING.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ BIRD SQUAWKING ]
>> I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD KIDS.
>> OH, YEAH. JUST ONE.
>> SHE LIVE AROUND HERE?
>> YEAH, SHE LIVES DOWN ON
RIVER ROAD, KIND OF BY, UH...
YOU KNOW THAT PLACE WHERE THEY
RAISE ALLIGATORS?
YEAH, KIND OF BY THERE.
>> HOW OLD IS SHE?
>> UH...40, 41, SOMEWHERES IN
THERE.
>> HOW MANY GRANDKIDS?
>> JUST ONE.
>> I'M SURE SHE'S FINE.
THEY NEED TO PUT ANOTHER LANE IN
HERE.
OH, SHIT.
SHOULD I PULL HIM OVER?
>> YEAH, GO AHEAD.
NO, NO. HANG ON JUST A MINUTE.
LOOK TO YOU LIKE ANY MORE BALES
ARE GONNA FALL?
>> I THINK THOSE WERE JUST
STACKED UP TOO HIGH.
TAILGATE DIDN'T STOP THEM.
>> JUST LET HIM GO THEN.
LET'S GO BACK THERE AND GET
THOSE BALES.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
GUESS IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY.
>> SO, WHAT?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
YOU COME TO TAKE A LOOK AT ALL
>> SO, WHAT?
THE DAMAGE YOU CAUSED?
YOU COME TO TAKE A LOOK AT ALL
>> YEAH, ACTUALLY, I CAME TO
THE DAMAGE YOU CAUSED?
TELL YOU I'M TAKING YOU TO
>> YEAH, ACTUALLY, I CAME TO
COURT, AND I'VE GOT A WITNESS.
TELL YOU I'M TAKING YOU TO
>> YOU'RE TAKING ME TO COURT?
COURT, AND I'VE GOT A WITNESS.
>> YEAH. HECTOR SAYS THAT HE SAW
>> YOU'RE TAKING ME TO COURT?
YOU SHOOT A COUPLE OF MY COWS
>> YEAH. HECTOR SAYS THAT HE SAW
WITH A .22.
YOU SHOOT A COUPLE OF MY COWS
>> OH, REALLY?
WITH A .22.
IS THAT WHAT HE SAID?
>> OH, REALLY?
WELL, I'VE BEEN HERE ALL DAY
IS THAT WHAT HE SAID?
WITH MOK TRYING TO CLEAN UP THIS
WELL, I'VE BEEN HERE ALL DAY
DAMN MESS.
WITH MOK TRYING TO CLEAN UP THIS
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, WE HAVE ALL
DAMN MESS.
THOSE COWS BRANDED AND NUMBERED.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, WE HAVE ALL
IT'S NOT GONNA BE VERY HARD TO
THOSE COWS BRANDED AND NUMBERED.
FIND THE ONES THAT YOU SHOT AND
IT'S NOT GONNA BE VERY HARD TO
SEE IF THEY'VE GOT A COUPLE OF
FIND THE ONES THAT YOU SHOT AND
.22s LODGED UP THEIR ASS.
SEE IF THEY'VE GOT A COUPLE OF
>> OH, WOW.
.22s LODGED UP THEIR ASS.
IT'S GONNA BE A HECK OF A LOT
>> OH, WOW.
HARDER THAN TAKING A PICTURE OF
IT'S GONNA BE A HECK OF A LOT
AN ENTIRE CROP OF DEAD FISH.
HARDER THAN TAKING A PICTURE OF
>> WELL...
AN ENTIRE CROP OF DEAD FISH.
WE'LL SEE IN COURT, WON'T WE?
>> WELL...
>> YES, YOU WILL. GOODBYE.
[ CAR DOORS CLOSE,
ENGINE TURNS OVER, REVS ]
>> HEY, GUYS.
WHAT YOU DOING? DIGGING A HOLE?
MORE LIKE YOU'RE BUILDING ONE
UP.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING OUT
HERE?
WHAT IS THIS?
[ BREATHING RAPIDLY ]
[ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
[ BREATHING DEEPLY, RAPIDLY ]
>> YEAH. I'LL HELP YOU CLEAN
THIS UP WHEN WE GET BACK TO THE
STATION.
[ GRUNTS ]
WISH WE HAD SOME BALING WIRE.
SOME TWINE OR...
I GOT TO REMEMBER TO REQUEST
THAT FOR ALL OUR SQUAD CARS.
THAT OUGHT TO STAY, RIGHT?
>> IF NOT, SOMEBODY ELSE WILL
GET LUCKY...OR IN AN ACCIDENT.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE HEAD DOWN 30,
STOP OFF AT JACKSON'S FOR A CUP
OF JOE?
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> CALLING ALL UNITS.
A 10-54 HAS JUST BEEN REPORTED
OUT PAST ROCK CREEK.
ANY DEPUTIES IN THAT VICINITY?
OVER.
>> JEN, THIS IS ED.
DO YOU HAVE ANY DETAILS? OVER.
>> HEY, ED.
CALL CAME IN FROM 5317 NORTH
1725 EAST.
ALL WE KNOW IS IT'S A GIRL AND
THAT A MAN FOUND HER OUT IN A
FIELD.
APPARENTLY, HIS BOYS WERE
TRYING TO BURY HER.
OVER.
>> HOW OLD IS SHE?
WHAT COLOR IS HER HAIR?
ANY OF THAT STUFF. OVER.
>> LOOKS LIKE SHE'S PROBABLY IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
OVER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JIMMY AND I WILL GO RIGHT OVER
THERE.
OVER AND OUT.
>> OUT.
>> LET'S GO.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ SIREN WAILS ]
>> HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
YOU WERE THE ONE WHO KNEW THEY
WERE LOOKING FOR A SHOVEL.
YOU COULD HAVE ASKED THEM THEN.
I WAS OUT BACK WORKING.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE THEM.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE OUT THERE
FISHING.
>> EXACTLY. SO WHY WOULD THEY
HAVE NEEDED A SHOVEL?
>> ARE WE IN TROUBLE?
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW I'M
BEING BLAMED FOR THIS.
>> I'M NOT BLAMING YOU.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DIDN'T
GO CHECK ON THEM EARLIER.
>> THAT IS BLAMING ME.
YOU COULD HAVE CHECKED ON THEM
EARLIER.
>> I DON'T THINK IT WAS EITHER
ONE OF YOUR FAULTS.
>> IT'S THEM.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
[ BIRDS SQUAWKING ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
OKAY. UM...JERRY JUST WALKED IN
THE DOOR.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER, OKAY?
I'LL CALL YOU.
OKAY. BYE.
>> HEARD ANYTHING YET?
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> WELL, SHE'S BOUND TO TURN UP
SOMETIME.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE GARAGE
DOOR?
>> I THOUGHT I PUT IT IN
REVERSE.
>> COST AT LEAST A COUPLE
HUNDRED, MAYBE $1,000.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
WITHOUT THAT CROP.
>> WELL, ARE YOU GONNA GET THE
FARMER TO COMPENSATE YOU FOR
ANYTHING?
>> WELL, NOW HE'S THREATENING TO
TAKE ME TO COURT, SO PROBABLY
NOT.
>> WHAT?! HE'S THE ONE WHO
DIVERTED THE WATER.
HE CAN'T DO THAT.
>> AND WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
ABOUT SUSAN?
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ EERIE MUSIC ♪ ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ MUSIC SWELLS ♪ ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ CROW CAWING ]
[ INTENSE LOW HUMMING MUSIC ♪ ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING, RUSTLING ]
♪