Man: Okay, now--
now it's time for some bowling.
- All right.
Come on. You know what?
lf you're not gonna take this seriously
and hit down the pin, just sit down
and let the real bowlers bowl.
You know what it is?
You're supposed to look at the triangle.
- Let's see, let's see.
- That's where you're supposed to look.
- Let's see what you got.
- Okay, just keep your eye on me.
You're gonna see this.
- You watchin'? All right, here we go.
- l'm watchin'.
- Oh yeah! Nice!
- Man: Oh!
That's how it's done! See that?
Were you watching?
- All right, l saw it.
- lt's all about technique.
As a matter of fact, l'm so confident
l can knock that one down,
l got a solid Franklin here
says l clear that frame.
- Copy that.
- Why don't you put your money
- where your mouth is?
- l got that.
- Now it gets interesting.
- Right there.
Yeah! Watch, don't take
your eyes off me.
All l need is my lucky ball here.
l got my lucky ball.
All right, we're gonna
make this happen.
Where you going? Look at this guy
going to the bathroom again.
You incontinent old man.
All right, here we go again, fellas.
You ready?
Okay, you guys tell me
we're gonna make this happen.
lt's me and my ball.
lt's me and my lucky ball.
ln my universe,
it's me and my crystal ball.
Looking in my ball,
you know what l see in my future?
A spare.
Watch.
l'll teach ya how to do this
a little bit later on, all right?
Pay attention.
Hey, you guys keep it down.
l'm tryin' to bowl over here.
No respect, l tell you.
These guys. Okay.
Oh! All day long!
l'm just gonna--
How you doing, Luis?
You got something for me?
l told Big Doug l'd have it,
l'll have it.
l want you to think very carefully
about your next move, Luis.
l don't think so, buddy.
Walt, you gotta
let me outta here.
Come on, you know me.
l'm a regular here, l'll be back.
But those are my shoes.
Hey.
Word to the wise, brother.
Stay down.
You'll get your shoes back.
You know me.
You don't know these guys.
- Please, you'll get them back.
- Tommy needs ya,
- Tommy's gonna get ya.
- l'm a regular here--
- Hey, l'll take an 11.
- Tommy, l'm sorry.
l was gonna pay ya, Tommy.
Tommy, l'm gonna pay.
l'm sorry. Ah!
l'm sorry, Tommy.
l was gonna pay!
l swear, l was gonna--
This ain't right!
lt ain't fair!
Oh, it ain't right?
lt ain't fair?
l gave you a 10-day extension.
That's more than fair.
But me having to track
your little ass down, that ain't right.
Look, you can't
just come in here and--
Yeah, l can, Luis,
because this is what l do.
This is my job.
Let me break it down
for you, dumbass.
lf you borrow from Big Doug
and pay him back, l got no play in that.
But when you borrow
from Big Doug...
- Don't! Please!
- ...and don't pay him back?
He shoots, he loses.
Please, Tommy!
- Big Doug says me and Julio--
- Tommy, Tommy, please.
Don't!
- l'm sorry!
- l was generous with you, Luis,
seeing we only earn base
plus a cut of the vig.
Meaning the less the vig,
the less money for me and Julio here.
And that ain't right.
- Luis: l'm sorry, Tommy!
- Be careful, Tommy.
- Ain't fair.
- Okay, l'm sorry, Tommy.
- You got my money?
- Maybe, maybe!
Luis, ain't nothing's ever
been accomplished with a maybe.
Come on, Tommy!
This is crazy!
Okay, l get it!
l get the point, Tommy!
You got two choices.
You either pay Big Doug the money
you owe him in the next 24 hours
or you run and you hide.
Because next time, we ain't
gonna be so easy on your ass.
Smile.
Julio: Last time l had
a blood test was at the VA
when l was shipped home
from lraq.
Seriously though, who knew a job
like this came with health insurance?
When boss wants us
to get a physical, we get a physical.
Tommy Conolan?
The doctor will see you now.
Okay, you know the drill.
Clothes off, gown on,
and the doctor will be in in a bit.
Still here, old man.
Still here.
What's happening, boss?
Tommy.
Usual?
Sure.
- How's the wife?
- She's good.
- Real good.
- That girl deserves some credit
- for putting up with you, Tommy.
- Tell me about it.
Well, here we go.
All right, hit me.
Allan Brady, paid in full.
His eldest still in Afghanistan?
Yeah, sure is.
Army, Fourth lnfantry Brigade.
- Good kid.
- Combat team, eh?
Yeah.
That's your old company,
isn't it?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Nick Bradley,
paid in full.
Speaking of the ungrateful.
You hear from Luis?
Funny you should
mention that.
Just had a real nice talk
with that young man.
Hm. That's what l heard.
Think he'll pay?
lf he's smart, he will.
lf he was smart, he never would have
borrowed from me in the first place.
How's Eddie?
Good as he can be.
They just transferred him
to the state pen.
Tommy, l know you
and the wife will be hurtin',
workin' hard to cover
Eddie's ass like this,
but is he worth it?
Well, no, he's not worth it,
but he's my little brother.
l hear ya.
l got one of those myself.
But Eddie stole from me.
l can't simply erase
debt like that.
l know, Doug, l know.
- l got it covered.
- Bartender: What'll you have?
Doug:
That you do.
Something's come up this week
to change that.
l need a package delivered
to the German.
l know some decades back,
the two of you
worked in the same crew.
What happened?
Just difference of opinion.
He and Nicky still at war
with Anthony?
Three angry dogs.
One miserable junkyard
to fight over.
And your money's
on the German.
Mm-hmm.
lt's that important to you?
lt is.
Enough so
that if you do this for me,
l will wipe clean
your brother's debt.
All right. Last l heard,
he was still based out of BC.
Wise decision, Tommy.
What's in it?
You're being paid not to know.
That's for expenses.
- See you in a couple days, boss.
- Godspeed.
- Hey.
- Smart move, kid.
- Man on phone: Yes?
- The package is en route.
Excellent.
Man: lt's not like l'm really being
unreasonable here, is it now?
lt's not like l like the sound
of my own voice
and that's the reason
l'm talking to you.
lt's because this needs
to be done.
And spend some money. Try to
improve your look, for God's sake.
Jesus.
l don't know what you guys
do around here all the time.
When's this asshole gonna get here?
Well.
All right, here he comes.
On my go.
Nicolas.
German.
You wouldn't know
anything about
a missing silver shipment,
now would you?
Because, you see,
l intended to take
that shipment myself.
Sure.
Sure l do.
Guys.
Cute.
So tell me.
Where do we stand,
you and l?
How do you mean?
Are we friends, enemies,
or simply competitors?
No different than
a pair of hardware stores
struggling to survive
in the same damn town.
Well...
l wouldn't find it wise
for me to answer that.
And yet therein lies
your answer.
l suppose it does.
How do you think that this,
the you and l of it all,
will play out in the long run?
Poorly.
Agreed.
But in the meantime,
we're at peace.
Peace is the only thing
any of us wants.
ls that so?
lt is for now.
How long have
we been doing this?
Too long.
And yet the years
just keep on coming.
You keep to yours,
l'll keep to mine.
lf either dips
his finger knowingly
or unknowingly
into the other's till,
we don't cut it off.
We meet as such
and we play it cool.
Agreed.
As for the silver,
l'll overlook
that little indiscretion.
Well, that's too kind.
You are a son of a bitch.
You know that?
You hungry?
l could eat.
l will have a word
with the chef.
The guy is a real maestro.
Go. Go!
Come on!
What are you waiting for?
Get out there, God damn it!
Move!
Go on! Jesus!
Shit.
This wasn't what
you expected, was it?
What's the word, bro?
Word is, l got something
to clear your slate with Big Doug.
That ain't your cross to bear.
Hey, we're family.
You'd do the same for me
if the shoe was on the other foot.
l don't know, Tommy.
l just don't know
if l'd even care.
Look, why are you here today?
Huh? What do you want from me?
You want me to say thank you?
Look where the hell
l'm at, Tommy.
- Thought you'd want to know.
- Well, l don't want to know.
And you know why?
Because l'm in here
with a bunch of Big Doug's friends
and that's on me.
And if you go out there
and do that for me
and things go sour?
Well, that's on me, too.
l don't want that.
Tommy.
l just--
take care of yourself, bro.
Yeah.
Guard.
You scared me.
- You smell good.
- Yeah?
How about losing the towel?
But then l'd be naked.
- Still have these on.
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
Hey, Tommy?
Yeah.
What would you do if something
wonderful happened?
Some kind of miracle
and all of a sudden
we had all the money
we needed,
and you didn't have
to work for Big Doug?
What would you do?
Where would you take me?
l don't know.
Thinking like that
can get you into trouble.
Did you think about
what we talked about?
About your work?
Yeah, l looked into it.
And?
And l'm not gonna make
the money Big Doug pays me
working as a bouncer.
So if Big Doug's so fair,
why does he keep
a loaded shotgun under his table?
Who does that?
Darla, there's not a great demand
for my skills in your world.
And then Eddie's debt.
Tell me you love me.
How come you don't say it?
'Cause you know
how l feel about you.
Then l'm the luckiest girl
in the world
and l have everything l need.
Tommy:
What you got?
About the only thing they make
that's good here.
- Coffee.
- Thank you, sir.
And a breakfast burrito.
Chef's special.
- How special?
- lt won't kill you.
We'll see about that.
Where's the package?
- Seriously?
- As a heart attack.
Why didn't he just mail it?
You got me.
Do you have any idea
what's in it?
No, and l'd rather
keep it that way.
Oh, you'd rather
You, me, the open road.
Good times.
How's it going with Darla?
She still on ya to quit the job?
Eh, she worries a lot.
She's looking out for me.
She's a good woman, Tommy.
She deserves all the respect
you give her.
That she does, man.
That she does.
- Hey, man.
- What?
- Stop.
- Come on, man.
l just want to see
what all the fuss is about.
Yeah, well, l'd rather not see
You know what l'm saying?
Fine.
Hey, man.
Don't say l didn't warn you.
Hey.
What?
Find it.
Get the hell out of here, son.
He's in the store.
You know the drill.
Ralph, you take the wheel.
We get the item, we go.
Monique, work the scanners.
You hear anything, let me know.
State, local police, anyone--
we're history. Understand?
Jake, Dosan, follow me.
Get out.
Devon, we've got a call in
on the local sheriff's line.
They're sending an emergency team.
Five-to-seven minutes out max.
Copy that.
Keep the engine running.
And don't use names over the radio.
You know better than that.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Come on out, Tommy.
We're not here to hurt you.
We just want the package.
You wanna dance with me,
little girl?
What's happening in there?
This place is gonna be
cop central any minute.
Ain't gonna take
too much longer.
Just keep that engine running,
l'm bringing dinner home.
Devon? Jake?
Dosan, come in.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Taking care of business.
Jesus Christ, Ralph!
You almost killed me!
How the hell did this thing suddenly
get so goddamn complicated?
- Ralph: l did what l had to do.
- You alerted the whole town
to our presence.
That's what you did.
Get in the van.
We have to find that package.
Ralph:
Cops are on their way.
Now! We've got to go!
Come on!
Where's Dosan?
Dosan's dead.
So is Jake.
Wasn't supposed to go down like this.
We were told this guy
is a goddamn goon.
A low-level nobody.
A nightclub bouncer.
We got soft on the idea
and it's our fault.
Whatever this thing is worth,
it's already cost us two lives.
Let's sharpen it up
and get that package.
Ralph, circle back.
He went to that gas station.
We'll get him.
What the hell?
l've chased Taliban
insurgents in Kabul,
hunted war criminals
in Serbia,
and here l am
in a rotten old gas station
in the middle of Hicksville,
Washington, US of A,
chasing an ex-nightclub bouncer-
turned-errand boy.
Who else has seen this footage?
The police.
The police were here.
l told them
the same thing l told you.
Well, that doesn't help me at all.
- Yes?
- Devon: We lost him.
- Come again?
- l said we lost him.
- Meaning?
- Meaning this guy,
we were misinformed
as to his capabilities.
How do you want us
to proceed?
Proceed how you see fit.
Your fee, however,
is now up for grabs.
Look, you can't just turn things
around on me now
- and start--
- Yes, l can.
l'm now offering the bounty up
to anyone in my crew.
- Anthony, l lost--
- Screwed up!
Say it.
Yeah, l screwed up.
Let me put it to you
as simply as l can.
We are at war
with the German.
The German
has paid a serious
amount of money
for this package.
lf l can get to it
before it gets to him,
then l'll have
negotiating power.
Power is everything.
Do l make myself clear?
Yes, sir.
Now go do whatever it takes
to get that goddamn package.
Ex-military contractors,
my ass.
Next time, l hire Sal
and his union enforcers.
You still got that picture
of the courier?
- Yes, sir.
- You don't cross me either.
You better be right about this.
Whatever it is,
it's serious enough
to clear this guy's whole tab
just for delivering.
lt's something big, boss.
l know it.
Get it out there.
Send it out on the street.
On the street, boss?
l want every informant,
stool pigeon, rat fink,
lowlife, ex-con, crackhead
looking for him.
And when they find him,
which they will,
- l want you there.
- Yes, sir.
What is this?
lt's his whole life.
Military records,
DMV information.
Every parking ticket citation
and credit card
this guy ever applied for.
l got you everything on him.
You don't cross Luis Ramirez.
Tough guy, huh?
- You got this?
- Yes, sir.
Well, that's good to hear.
The funds have been processed
and will be wired upon receipt.
And, Doug?
Thank you.
Oh, as l was saying,
mangos are the most popular
fruit on the planet
and chock full of
vitamins A and C,
alongside a healthy dose
of antioxidants
in the form of alpha-carotene,
beta-carotene,
and beta-cryptoxanthin.
The blueberries provide
damn near the same.
Not to mention,
the little bastards
are tasty as hell.
Cucumbers for
magnesium, potassium.
Bananas for protease inhibitors.
Please, l'm dying.
Grapes for resveratrol
and papayas
for the folate.
Please, man.
l'm dying here.
Now the vertebral column,
or spine as it were,
is a column made out
of 24 articulated vertebrae.
Three of which are crushed,
meaning you'll
never walk again.
Which isn't necessarily
a problem
since l also ruptured
your spleen
and tore into your liver.
ln essence, l gutted you...
like a freshly caught mackerel.
lt's a fish l quite enjoy, in fact.
Pickled with butter on toast.
Please.
Rye toast.
So...
Please.
Tell me who sent you.
Or what?
You gonna save me?
You're gonna kill me anyway.
No. There ain't
no saving you, son.
That's in the hands
of the Almighty alone.
But if you don't tell me
who sent you,
well, l'm just gonna have to--
l'm gonna have to drive
myself over to...
1825 Del Cashan Street.
With a blowtorch,
five pounds of lye,
and some bolt cutters.
And just--
just do whatever l want to
to the inhabitants therein.
And believe me,
l'm both patient
and creative.
Anthony!
lt was Anthony!
Well--
well, that's disappointing.
Yes, Mr. Topasana.
Of course, we're gonna get you covered.
1.4 in the Swiss account.
The offshore account.
lt works every single time.
- You gotta trust me.
- Boss.
- What now?
- lt's the German.
l'll call you back.
He's still alive.
- And the men?
- He sent us a movie.
- A movie movie?
- A home movie.
This guy's got
some kind of crazy skills
for someone
who's supposed to be sick.
lt never troubles the wolf
how many the sheep may be.
The time for negotiating is over.
You need that package badly,
but l'm gonna get to it first.
And when
the time comes, German...
l'm gonna cut your throat
and watch you bleed.
The history of the martini
is an interesting one.
One part vermouth,
four parts gin.
A twist of lemon
or an olive.
For garnish.
Thank you.
Mm.
Delicious.
Thank you.
Well, shall we?
And the package?
lt's en route.
This will do very nicely.
Excellent.
l'll also be adding
a 5% monthly retainer.
You can keep the man
in black at bay
for only so long.
Hey, Doug, this is bull
and you know it.
Doug: Everything we do carries with it
a little bit of excrement, Tommy.
You know that.
Tommy: Hey, man.
l don't like the feel of it.
Send someone else.
Doug:
l can't do that, Tommy.
Tommy:
Man, l'll wait here and hand it off.
Tommy.
Look, it ain't like
l'm quitting on you, Doug.
- lt's just--
- Tommy.
Son,
outside of me,
for a man like you,
there is no other work.
l can send someone else,
Tommy.
l can, but you forfeit your pay.
Yeah, no problem.
But here's the way of it.
Things have got so bad
for all of us,
that over the course
of the next few weeks,
your take-home pay
will probably be halved.
There's no way around it.
And that being the case,
your brother's debt,
his payment plan,
remains the same.
l can't change that.
So that being said...
do you want me
to send someone else?
Still with me on this, Tommy?
Yeah, yeah, l guess.
You guess or do you know?
- l ain't got no choice.
- Well, that's one way of putting it.
Tread lightly, Tommy.
Take care of yourself.
Thanks, Doug.
Hello?
Hey, babe.
Hi, honey. Are you okay?
You sound tired.
Yeah, l am.
Long day.
l'll tell you
about it tomorrow.
Just wanted to call
and check in.
That's about it really.
My mind's just a little fried.
l know the feeling.
Today's been crazy.
- Any plans tonight?
- No, l'm gonna crash.
Put in a pizza, glass of wine,
maybe watch a movie.
- Take it easy.
- Sounds good.
Hey, when are we gonna spend
that day in bed together?
We'd just get up to eat.
Are you okay?
Yeah, l'm good.
l just wanted to hear your voice.
l love you, Tommy.
Be careful.
You hear me?
Yeah.
Hey, l wonder if you might
help me get down the road?
- Yeah, l'm heading north.
- Yeah, let me give you some money.
We don't need your money.
Hop in. l'm going that way anyway.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Tommy: This is good.
l'll walk from here.
Hey, thanks for the ride.
You get out
while the gettin's good.
l'm workin' on it,
l'm workin' on it.
- l got him.
- Man: Are you sure it's him?
Yeah, l'm sure.
He's not too goddamn hard to spot.
Man:
He's heading to the German.
Just keep him in sight.
l'll be there in 20 minutes.
Yeah, Devon, it's Carl.
We got him.
lf you're lucky,
l'll leave you some crumbs.
There's a reputation
to be made here.
There you are,
you big bastard.
l know you're
back there, Tommy!
l need that package
and you're going to give it to me.
l don't think so.
One of us is gonna be
disappointed.
An address.
613 Low Arch Drive.
Yes, Tommy.
l know where you live,
where Darla lives.
But don't worry,
that's not my style.
l just wanted you to know
that l could have if l wanted to.
You see,
l work for Anthony.
l fix things for him.
You run collections
for Big Doug.
You got a reputation, man.
A good one.
You know, why don't we just
skip all this and walk away?
Would you walk away, Tommy?
No.
Well, l hear you've been
a hardcase.
Well, l specialize in
hardcases, Tommy.
Whoa, yeah!
Come on, just give me
the package, Tommy.
l could do this all day, Tommy.
No, man, please, no!
No!
You better forget that address.
Devon:
How you doing, Tommy?
You just keep running,
but you don't know well enough
to stay hidden, do you?
You know, l took it easy
on you last time.
l ain't gonna take it
easy on you this time.
Are you sure he's out?
For now.
Devon: Yeah, yeah.
lt's the first door on the south side.
We left it open for you.
He's here.
We're in business.
Here comes the man.
What do you think
you're doing?
Just a little payback
for Dosan and Jake.
Anthony:
Sorry, love.
Trust me when l say
l understand
the importance
of retribution,
but l can't let that happen.
The German's agreed to terms.
Which means your crew
has earned its fee.
But part of the deal is
the German wants to see him.
lt's business, Monique.
That's all any of this is.
lt's only ever been
about business.
What is it that he wants
with you, big man?
'Cause he sure reacted
strangely to your name.
Huh?
l've got a feeling that whatever
the German has planned for you,
it ain't gonna--
Killed him with one hit.
l've never seen
anything like it, Chief.
Yeah, it sucks to be him.
Get him out of here.
l'm gonna kill you next, sunshine.
What are we gonna do now?
We renegotiate the terms
of our deal with the German.
And until then?
What about him?
Just make sure he's got a pulse
when you're done with him.
Oh, you're good.
l could use a man like you
on the team.
l don't soldier for money.
No? What axe did you
have to grind?
l'm an American, son.
l fought for my country.
Oh, they sure don't make 'em
like you anymore.
No, Russian Spetsnaz are close,
but not quite.
lt takes selection.
What were you?
Force Recon? Ranger school?
Chechnya, Mogadishu, Somalia?
You see, names like that
don't mean much
to normal people,
but to us, they do.
Where did you learn
your trade?
l took an online course.
lt's good that you got
a sense of humor.
This is Monique.
She was Army Counterintelligence.
You know what that means.
lt means she conducted
the interrogation
of countless captured
al-Qaeda suspects.
lt means
she's a sadistic,
soulless bitch.
She sounds like
one of my ex-wives.
For five years,
work meant making men scream
and beg for mercy,
but it didn't affect her
'cause she was good
at what she did.
Very good.
l'd clap, but l'm a little
tied up right now.
She did what she did
for minimum
warrant officer wage, Tommy.
Just think what she's gonna do
to the man who killed her fiancé.
Just don't kill him.
We need some new wheels.
l'm taking this.
l'll phone back in 20 minutes.
Have fun.
What Devon said
was not quite accurate.
When it comes to
advanced interrogation techniques
or "the alternative
set of procedures,"
as the administration
referred to it--
"torture,"
as you would call it,
l never did it for money.
l did it for fun.
Let me see.
Good.
You don't care
about the package, do you?
l'm the definition of
a consummate professional,
but when you killed Dosan,
you crossed an invisible line.
Left or right?
He screamed like a bitch,
you know.
- What?
- Your fiancé.
He died like a bitch.
ls this your clumsy attempt
to incite a reaction?
No, l'm just letting you know
he died like a bitch.
Died screaming.
Like a whiny, little--
bitch.
ls that all you got, lady?
Hm.
l know what
you're trying to do.
You're trying to provoke me
into an emotional response.
You think?
l think you just about did it.
Something's wrong.
You are really starting
to piss me off.
Shit!
Well, well, Tommy, old son.
Looks like you just increased
my take full share.
Sir?
The subject is conscious.
Hello, Tommy.
Hey, the German.
But seriously, do you really
want me to call you that?
l do.
What can l say?
l like it.
Besides, one never picks
one's own nickname.
Which makes for tall men
named Shorty
and fat men named Slim.
So...
what have you been up to
since we last met?
You mean, since you
sold my ass down the river?
Aw, but you had that coming.
How do you figure?
Well, you didn't follow through
with my request.
But, l must admit,
l may have overreacted a bit.
So do you know
why you're here, Thomas?
No.
l do have one
hellacious headache, though.
Well, that's because we
took a couple of pints
of your blood, Thomas.
My blood?
Well, l've taken all l can
from my father.
That's-- that's pleasant.
That is...
reality.
What was in the wallet?
Season tickets.
Good seats, too.
Hard to come by.
But football tickets
do not a package make, Thomas,
but you do.
What's that got to do with me?
You, Thomas.
You are the package.
You see,
you and l, we--
we share a common curse.
An extremely rare
blood group.
Most people have
A, B, AB, O,
or one of
the assorted subsets.
But the two of you
are designated HH.
Sometimes known
as Bombay Blood.
Sadly, the only compatible match
for an HH is another HH.
And in the United States,
.004% of the population
share this affliction.
Big Doug had us all in
for physicals.
Hemolytic anemia is--
well, it's when the red blood cells
rupture and become dysfunctional.
Extremely painful condition.
Well, you see,
l need clean blood, Thomas.
But to find a compatible donor,
it's highly unlikely.
lt's almost impossible, in fact.
lmagine my surprise
at finding one in my own stable.
Doug know he was
sending me into this?
Yeah, of course he did.
Yeah.
He sold you to me.
l liked you, Thomas.
You had potential.
But when it comes to a man's
sheer willingness to survive,
you'd be surprised
what one's willing to do.
You're plumb unlucky,
you know that, right?
Excuse me?
We ain't compatible.
You goddamn Kraut.
What do you mean?
Our blood may be the same,
but there's the issue
of my condition.
He's a dead man.
What condition?
Stop the drip.
What-- what condition?
l-- l can't.
What? Tell me, Thomas.
What-- what are you saying?
- l can't.
- Tell me what you mean.
Guards! Guards!
Guards!
No! Don't shoot!
Don't kill him! Don't!
God damn, Tommy.
You just don't know
when to quit, do you?
Had yourself
one hell of a day, huh?
lt ain't over yet.
There's a lot of money out there.
The kind of money a man
could have a lifetime on.
could get lost with.
l'm not greedy.
l could just as easily
split it 50/50.
l'll even give you the Merc.
l'll walk.
Tommy, think about it.
Think about it.
You don't need to kill me.
l'm just a man doing his job.
On the job or no job,
you killed my partner.
Yeah, now,
l'm gonna kill you.
Drop the guns, Tommy.
Your blood's no good to me
if you're dead.
Turn around.
Well, you have what l need,
Thomas.
And l'm gonna take it
with or without your consent.
l heard you killed Anthony
with one strike.
l've only seen a man
kill like that once.
l was holding
a roll of quarters at the time.
l don't suppose it would
make a difference
if l said we could just
walk away from this, does it?
Not this time, Tommy.
The stakes are too high.
Ain't no rules
in this game, Tommy.
You got that right, jackass.
Still here.
No need for that.
Let's go.
lt's good to see you, Tommy.
You mean that?
Yes, yes l do.
l know you do.
lt was business,
Tommy, just business.
Just one man following
a bigger man's orders.
Tommy, if l tried to keep you
hidden from the German,
he would have taken
everything from me.
- Everything.
- l figured as much.
- Did he pay you up front?
- He did.
And that clears
your brother's debt.
With him dead,
what does that make you?
An older man
having grown tired
of this game.
l hear ya.
What now?
Well, the way l see it,
we either proceed as before
and file this little incident away,
or we go our separate ways,
leave the baggage behind
and wish each other
a hearty Godspeed.
A hearty Godspeed.
Godspeed, Big D.
Godspeed, Tommy.
Godspeed.
Thank you, Tommy.
Thank you.
Hey, man, you'd have done
the same thing for me.
Look, l'm gonna
get out of here soon.
And this time,
l ain't ever coming back.
l'm gonna set
things right, Tommy.
l'm gonna do that for you.
l know you will, bro.
l know you will.
Man: Mercedes for the pickup
straight across? Deal.
Here are the keys.
Pink slip's
in the glove compartment.
Well, it was a pleasure
doing business with you, Tommy.
Thanks, Gary.
l'll be seeing you around, brother.
Hey, l'm back.
Yeah, one piece mainly.
- Hey, Tommy.
- Hang on.
You forgot this.
Sorry, Gary,
been a long day.
They all are, huh?
Hey, yeah, we can talk
about it over dinner.
Hang on.
Hey, remember when you asked me
what l'd do if a miracle happened?
l got a surprise for you.
Hey, l love you.