Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Don't tell me your kung fu is good
that your master is amazing
that your style is profound
Kung fu
two characters
one horizontal, one vertical
Those who are wrong...
fall down.
Only the one left standing in the end is right.
Isn't that right?
I'm from Foshan in Guangdong close to the South China Sea.
My father was Yip Oido.
He operated a North-South trade company on Bonham Strand West in Hong Kong.
When the Yip clan was in Foshan, people called us the Peide Village Yips.
They also said
all of Peide Village was ours.
Before I was 40 years old, I never worried about making a living.
I depended on the wealth that my forefathers passed on to me.
My only passion was...
When I was 7 years old, I studied martial arts.
My teacher was Chan Wah Shun.
Foshan Wing Chun was started by Master Leung Jan.
I suppose that makes me part of the 3rd generation.
When my master took me in, he was already 70 years old.
The day I formally became his student
he personally gave me my sash.
This sash represents your school and your master.
One's sash is one's honor.
Wearing this sash signifies someone who trains in the martial arts.
From now on, you will rely on this honor to conduct yourself.
Ready stance!
One's sash, one's honor.
I lived through the Guangxu Emperor (1875-1908)
The Last Emperor (1909-1911), the Republican Government, the Northern Expedition (1926-1928)
The Resistance against the Japanese, and the Chinese Civil War.
In the end, I arrived in Hong Kong.
I was able to endure all of this
by relying on those words.
My wife is Cheung Wing Sing.
She is a descendant of the former Qing Foreign Affairs Minister Zhang Yinhuan.
In general, she doesn't speak much.
She says that words can sometimes hurt people.
As for our relationship, the silent defeat the loud.
She likes listening to music.
Whenever there was a social event, I took her to the Golden Pavilion.
In those days, things were still pretty conservative.
It was very rare for ladies from respectable families to go to the brothels to listen to music.
She went anyway and didn't care what anybody said.
Whenever I went out at night
she would light the lamp by the front door
and wait for me to come back, and only then put it out.
If my life had four seasons
everything before 40 years old would be spring.
Foshan, Guangdong
The Chen Jitang period.
It was supposed to be a time of peace.
In those days, men would often come to the brothels to have fun.
The most famous playground in Guangzhou was Chen Tang's "Forgotten Goblet."
The most popular one in Foshan was Ying Shazui's "Republican Pavilion."
The inside was completely covered in gold.
So everybody called it the "Golden Pavilion."
It was the first brothel in all of Guangdong to have an elevator.
It became known as the place where princes enter but only beggars leave.
You could easily end up blowing a thousand gold pieces there.
It was where my kung fu brothers would often hang out.
In that world, there are always ordinary men.
But among them, there are many martial arts experts who don't reveal themselves.
Normal people see the Golden Pavilion as a place of ecstasy.
But in fact, it is a place of heroes.
In this life
I've only accomplished three things:
I merged the Xingyi and Bagua school
took in my big kung fu brother's students
and headed the affairs of the Chinese Martial Artists Association
which unified the Tongbei, Paochui, Tai Chi
Yanqing, and scores of other schools.
Finally
I gathered the skills of the Northern styles and passed them down in the South.
In 1930
the Two Factories National Skills School was established.
The Five Tigers will come down to Jiangnan
just as Master Li Renchao and I have decided
while sitting here in the Golden Pavilion.
I'm old now.
It's time for a new person to come forward.
I already had a retirement party in the North.
This time, I'm having another one here for the Mengjing Martial Arts Association.
This was so I could say farewell to my old Southern brothers and comrades.
In the Northeast, my best student Ma San is my heir in the North.
He has taken in my students.
Ladies and gentlemen, please look after him.
Originally
I still wanted to do one more thing
and that was to spread the Southern styles into the North.
Unfortunately, I don't have any more time.
Here at my retirement party
with my heir from the North
I am looking for a Southern style martial artist to be my Southern heir.
Of course, that person has to win everyone's approval first.
Choose someone.
Is that all you got?
And yet you dare say you can challenge the Old Man?
Let's finish this.
Attack me all at once!
Take him out!
At the Old Man's retirement party in the North
I was chosen to be his heir.
"If you want to pray to Buddha in the temple"
"you have to first pass through the front gate."
If you want to see the true Buddha
You'll have to get by me, Ma San.
I think I'm qualified to represent Guangdong martial arts.
As for the different schools
the Southern style has the Hung, Lau, Choi, Lei, and Mok.
As for seniority
all those sitting here are the elder generation.
They aren't the heads of their lineages but just the head of their schools.
I haven't even gotten around to me.
This is a matter of honor for the Two Factories National Skills Association.
We are men from Guangdong.
Although people say that all we do is play with our abacuses all day
when we really act, who hasn't been afraid?
Yeah, who are we afraid of?
Today someone has come here to challenge us.
We can't pretend to be helpless!
Do you agree or no?
Brother Shou is right!
You are the chosen one!
Tomorrow I will take our children to my parent's home.
So you don't have to worry.
When men pass the age of 40
they want to do things they are confident in.
I will wait. And when this is all over
come get me.
Do you know why
a sword has a scabbard?
Because a sword's true purpose
is not to kill
but to be hidden.
Your sword is too sharp.
Keep it well-hidden in your scabbard.
My scabbard
is you my master.
When you are around
I cannot start trouble.
I will not be that for you.
Make a name for yourself again after 10 years.
Leave Foshan now.
If you miss the train,
I will cut off your legs!
Stop the carriage!
Please friends, let us through.
Sorry, the Foshan Jingwu Association has rules.
Anyone carrying weapons
cannot enter the street.
Do you have any idea who is sitting in this carriage?
Call out the disciples of the Gong family!
Lady Er, please come in.
We must put a stop to this immediately.
Win or lose, this isn't good for us.
Father has never lost his whole life.
How can you speak of losing?
If we wins then what?
It will make people say he bullies the weak.
What about the difference in seniority?
Where's my father?
Kung fu Brother!
I, Baosen, have come to see you.
The Northeast is so large
but yet it cannot accommodate you.
You had to come to Foshan?
Get up!
I have come to take you back.
Go back?
Can I go back?
The Northeast
is part of Japan now
under the banner of the rising sun.
Can they accommodate me, this ghost?
It is not time yet.
This much stew
must be exhausting.
This isn't stew.
This is snake soup.
Isn't snake soup a winter dish?
It is a decades-long dish.
How many decades?
Year of the Snake
That's when you left the Northeast.
When making soup
you have to pay pay attention to the fire.
If you take something off the fire before it's ready
nobody wants it.
If you keep it in the fire too long
things get burnt.
How we conduct ourselves is the same.
Go back!
I'm waiting for this furnace
to accept this piece of firewood
only then will I go back.
Things done quietly get done well.
Things that attract attention are difficult to complete.
We are both getting old.
It hasn't been easy for you being so famous.
Swinging your fists and waving your arms with the younger generation is not a good idea.
If you force things
it ruins the flavor.
I don't want to be a hero.
I just want to create the circumstances for one to emerge.
This furnace now
needs this new piece of firewood.
When you were with our Northern brothers
they all disapproved of this competition.
To bring how much honor to the heir?
This Yip guy doesn't appreciate the honor bestowed on him.
We also cannot break our own rules.
Don't think so superficially like them.
Old men would die to protect those rules.
New men must step forward.
Yip Man has the right stuff.
I will see if he can rise to the occasion.
The Gong family has never lost.
You are here again.
What does he have to rely on to rise to the occasion?
Your temperament
is just like mine when I was young.
In my eyes there was only victory or defeat.
There was no room for feelings or human relations.
If people want to see far into the distance
they climb a mountain
to broaden their perspective.
But if a person cannot see
the goodness in people.
Nor see the wisdom of people
there can be no kindness in his or her heart.
Our family's skills are high.
But we do not produce immoral people.
Father!
You brought your daughter to roam around in a brothel. What kind of Buddhist teaching is this?
This is a worldly matter.
If you don't look at him, he will disappear.
Take a look. There's no harm in doing so.
When I first came to the Golden Pavilion
you weren't even born.
In a flash
20 years have passed.
People live this life
and their skills carry on into the next.
Some come out into the spotlight and become famous
while some remain in the background and perfect their inner nature.
They are both a product of their times.
This time I am forced come down.
I want to seek the end.
I want you to see
how your father will step down.
Ever since you were little
you grew up watching me fight others.
This is the last time.
You have chosen who you are close with.
The affairs of the martial arts world
no longer concern you anymore.
Find a good husband.
Live a peaceful life.
That is the ultimate filial piety.
Master Yip!
In this world, there are many ordinary men.
Today is the day you rise to the top!
We and the employees of this fine establishment
have all come to wish you luck!
This is all too much, Uncle Deng
Don't mention it.
And you don't have to be so damn polite!
After you!
Brother Yip
A few of us juniors representing all the ladies have come to congratulate you.
My what an impressive lineup.
Sister San
is the head of the Jing and Renli schools.
She knows a little Bagua.
She wants to give you a few pointers.
After you!
Bagua techniques come from swordplay.
Single-turning palm is a single sword.
Double-turning palm is a pair of swords.
As for footwork, one step opens, the next closes.
There are 64 transformations.
To master this art, you need to attack quickly.
Sister San, you're going easy on me.
You haven't used the "Temple Breaking" technique.
I've done it countless times.
It's nothing special.
Mr. Yip
Bagua can be brutal.
Be careful.
Thank you!
Mr. Yip
Today is a happy day.
We, representing the accountant, congratulate you.
Xingyi was bestowed upon General Yue Fei who became its founder.
The so-called "stripped spear" became a fist.
Drill!
Chop!
Wipe!
Cannon!
Destruction!
Wing Chun's "Listening Bridge"? Now that's good kung fu!
Your "Half-step Destruction Punch" is also pretty amazing.
Mr. Yip
Exchanging hands is like climbing a mountain
one step at a time; day by day.
Xingyi is powerful.
Never underestimate your enemy.
I want to experience a high mountain.
Sounds like fun!
Master Yip
It should be my turn now.
Brother Yong. How are you going to congratulate me?
With a bunch of firecrackers.
The Fendingcun technique?
Hung Gar right?
I'm a jack of all trades!
You really are a jack of all trades.
So how is my mixed style?
As long as it works, right?
The Gong family has 64 Hands, 1000 Changes, 10,000 Transformations.
Your Wing Chun only has 3 techniques:
Tan, Bong, Fuk
How can you hit anything?
Three techniques were enough to deal with you.
Brother Yong
Your firecrackers weren't so loud.
You think? I'm getting too old for this.
Fighting, I fear is for the young and strong.
It doesn't matter if he is a respected master or not
Be swift like the wind, shoot for the moon, and have no mercy!
You must win.
Thank you all, my elders, for leading the way.
We wish you success!
Good luck!
In every generation, a man of talent comes forth.
I am pleased to have Mr. Yip here.
Today is my final battle.
Today we will not be battling with our fists
but with our minds.
How about it?
You are all guests.
Your wish is our command.
In the year
the Chinese Martial Arts Association was established
came a man from the south.
He didn't speak much.
In his hand, he held a piece of cake.
He asked my great kung fu brother Li Cunyi to take it from his hands.
My great kung fu brother Li Cunyi didn't say anything.
Instead, he had him become the first chairman of the Martial Arts Association.
He didn't rely on his martial arts skills.
In other words
Does martial arts have a North and a South?
Does the country have a North and a South?
That gentleman was a man from Foshan just like all of you.
His name was Yip Wanbiu.
He was an outstanding person.
I never thought that after 25 years
I would meet another Mr. Yip in Foshan.
I would like to ask the same question from before.
Mr. Yip
Can you take this cake out of my hand?
Yang-style Tai Chi has a technique called "Making the Bird Not Fly."
A sparrow in one's hand cannot fly away
because it has no place to borrow power and lift off.
The Old Man's kung fu is still strong.
Mr. Yip is like a sparrow.
I think this cake
cannot be taken away.
Actually it is the vastness of the world.
Why stop with just the North and the South.
Struggling to see the whole is the same as being stuck in one place.
In your eyes
this cake is a single martial arts community.
For me it is an entire world.
It is this so-called idea of "what is most perfect seems somehow defective."
Only by having flaws can we improve.
A truly useful expression.
As for teaching the Southern Style
why stop in the North?
Don't you agree?
Well-spoken!
In my whole life, I have always won.
I have never lost with martial arts.
I never imagined
I would lose in a battle of wits.
Mr. Yip
Today, I give you my honor.
In the future
when you step into the ring
I hope you will be like me
relying on your honor to light the lantern.
If you know to bear this in mind, it will reflect on you.
Where there is a lantern, there will always be people.
Gong Er, we cannot let this happen.
The Gong family has never lost.
If we lose
there is always another member of the Gong family to step in.
Take this letter to this Mr. Yip.
He will understand.
In this lifetime
I failed to become an undisputed hero like my father.
Unfortunately, I never made plans for my life.
I've only lived for the moment.
Go quickly!
Tonight's gathering must be in accordance to the rules of the North.
The winning party must host it.
If Yip Man won't go
I won't go.
Go in my place.
Don't worry.
Someone from the Gong family will take care of it.
We have nothing to be ashamed of.
Let's go.
Gong Baosen personifies skilled martial arts.
Ma San inherited his hard power.
His daughter inherited his soft power
and is the only heir to the 64 Hands.
The "Hidden Flower Among the Leaves" technique
is impossible to defend against
One girl
in the Golden Pavilion can ruin the king's evening party.
She's trying to force you to come out with this challenge.
Don't underestimate her because she's a girl.
Remember the Four Great Prohibitions:
Buddhist monks, Taoist priests, women, and children.
There is nothing good about going.
"When crossing the bridge, one should not be afraid of the soldiers."
Everyone has put a great deal of effort in setting the scene.
How can I not go?
Three days ago
my father sat there.
Today
we become the followers.
After you.
What a pity... to ruin this beautiful room.
Kung fu is a contest of detail.
If I break anything
I will declare you the winner.
Mr. Yip
Let me show you the 64 Hands.
I hope this will help you understand:
"Beyond people are people, beyond mountains are mountains."
The fist cannot only have the path in front of one's eyes.
There is no one behind one's self.
I hope you can figure it out.
For the longest time it has had no equal.
Is the bottom of the leaves enough to conceal the flower?
If we have the chance, I would like to try it again myself.
If you come
I will wait for you.
Take care.
"Hidden flower under the leaves just once",
"Leaves snowy track in my dreams again and again."
"A promise that has been made"
"Ten thousand mountains cannot keep us apart."
Does it fit?
Is Foshan that cold?
It looks beautiful on you.
Let's take a photograph of the entire family the day after tomorrow.
October, Foshan falls.
October 1938
Foshan fall to the Japanese.
The Japanese military police took over the Yip family mansion.
If my life had four seasons
for my family, we went from spring straight to winter.
I'll be right back.
Wait for me. I'll bring something back to eat.
Teach me how to make a living.
Help me get out of poverty.
I've never been poor in my life.
Our country is under hard times.
People are suffering.
Giving just a little won't hurt you that much.
I now drink water from the Pearl River.
As for Japanese rice
I can't get used to eating it.
I truly have nothing to eat.
But I still have friends.
If each person invited me to a meal
I can hold out for around a year and a half.
Enjoy your meal.
In times like these, it isn't water that flows.
Who comes to drink Chinese wine anyway?
Just now there was a customer that took a girl and had a banquet.
There was some food left over.
If you don't want it go to waste
take it home and feed your children.
You are too kind.
In any case, all their money is dirty money.
Whether your take it or not
these are all people you know.
You don't have to be polite.
It has never been worn.
I originally planned to go to the Northeast.
I'm afraid that's not going to happen now.
If the price is right
help me sell it.
Hey, there is a button missing.
Really?
It must've fallen off.
When I was 7 years old, I learned martial arts.
Forty years ago
I never saw a tall mountain.
The first time I saw one
I realized the most difficult thing to overcome was just staying alive.
In the 8th year of the War of Resistance
I lost everything.
Income
Friends
Go to hell you Jap bastards!
Sister Yao heard from the brothel madam
that the masses want to follow a new leader.
His name is Sun Yatsen.
Everything he says goes.
The rage of the young is out of control.
All they know is glory and humiliation.
But Sun Yatsen won't dare to attack these Japanese devils.
Kill them all!
Uncle Deng was killed in a Japanese air raid.
The Golden Pavilion was taken over by a Chinese traitor.
The only thing I have left is my family.
During 8 years of war, Lady Si and Lady Liu died one after another in the Great Famine.
Sit down! Don't move!
Where are you going? Show us your ID.
Hurry!
Take it out!
Where are you going? Show us your ID now!
Freeze!
Ma San joined the Japanese and became the president of the Shenyang Cooperation Association.
Do you know why I called you Ma San?
I know.
"Words must spoken in accordance to the Three Divisions, hands must be perfected into fists."
It's an old martial arts saying.
It means that there will always be someone better coming up behind you.
All things divide people into three.
You changed my name
to remind me
to be humble
to know my place.
You grew up following me.
You consider yourself a person
who fights for the honor of this house.
Today I want to talk to you
about my supreme skill.
"The Old Monkey Hangs the Seal"
Have you practiced it?
Yes
Do you know what it means?
I've never heard you speak of it.
"The Old Monkey Hangs the Seal" is about looking back.
The essence is not in the hanging the seal
but in the looking back.
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
"An army does not have a constant position, water does not have a constant shape."
If
the head doesn't turn properly...
The Gong legacy
cannot be entrusted to you.
Master!
Who dares?
Let him go.
He's not allowed to enter my gate forever.
Get lost!
Old Man!
I heard that you came back.
All our supporters from the Northeast have all arrived.
San Ye and Wu Ye are on their way from Guannei.
What about Old Man Jiang?
Uncle Jiang is inside with everybody else.
My lady!
All of us have been waiting for you to come up with a plan.
The elders are on their way from Guannei.
What you want is not what I want I'm afraid.
Did my father have any last words or not?
He did not ask for revenge.
My lady!
The Old Man did not request revenge.
If you ask me, I also think we should kill him.
My hatred is boiling over.
He deceived our master and killed our founder.
Is there anything in the world that can compare to this?
But after some consideration
to be able to hit your father this time...
Bagua and Xingyi have been merged into one school.
Your kung fu brother's Xingyi kung fu is strong.
Your 64 Hands
is also what the Old Man taught you.
If the both of you each perfect your father's ultimate techniques
your skills will be complete.
Then your family's kung fu will will also be complete.
In addition
If you go out personally to deal with this
no matter who wins or loses
this will make us look like fools.
From within your family
a student kills his teacher
a kung fu sister wants to kill her kung fu brother
wouldn't this whole thing make us all cruel and unjust monsters?
As for your kung fu brother
even your father could not do anything about him.
What have you got?
Lady Er
We are all getting too old for this.
The elders are on their way from Guannei.
What they say is for your own good.
You should feel grateful.
Get married quickly.
Those were your father's final words.
Not to ask for revenge.
If you kill Ma San
isn't that against his wishes?
What my father said
breaks my heart.
He wants to make me live a happy life
but as long as his death is not avenged
I can never have a happy life.
Gentlemen, I understand what you are all saying.
My elders.
But you old men
who have fought together with my father, worked with my father, swore a pact with my father, and are closer than brothers...
My father is deads
Logically you are supposed to be the ones to go find Ma San.
But instead you come here and twist his words and talk utter nonsense.
You have all benefited from the Gong family for many years.
I know
Ma San depends on the Japanese.
He is strong-willed.
But the Gong family does not lack people.
Whether he comes today or not...
What does it matter if he comes or not?
He comes. You go.
What's the difference?
Can't you find forgiveness in your heart Lady Er?
Many things are beyond our control.
It is the will of heaven!
Perhaps I am an instrument of the will of heaven.
The Road to Paradise!
All the spirits are waiting for you!
Stop!
You can't stop! You can't stop!
Go around!
The main road is big enough for us to each go on one side.
It is the order of Ma San, the master of the Feng family
to accompany him part of the way.
Miss Er
Ma San's men
are blocking the road.
They say they are here to deliver a letter of mourning.
Is this not asking for trouble?
Miss Er!
People wait for the right time.
The right time does not wait for them.
Old Man Jiang!
Make Ma San clean his neck (so we can cut it) and wait at home for us.
Go!
Someone's coming!
Keep her from coming!
Stop her!
Everyone except Ma San get out of the way!
As a kung fu brother I respect you.
So I won't break into your house.
But you need to have a clear head.
You can't hide behind those curtains for the rest of your life.
Today I'm going to take back the Gong family's things.
Come out!
"You must think of your opponent's move first, before you decide your own move."
That is a fighting principle that the Old Man taught me.
It is also the basis for personal conduct.
It is unfortunate
that he was not so open-minded.
The Gong family's things bring money and precious things.
If you want to take them
someone from the Gong family must come get them.
If you allow anyone else
it's not going to happen.
Don't ask about my affairs
Having no news is news.
Find somebody else.
My lady
You pushed away a good potential husband
Was it worth it?
You had better think clearly
if you want to follow this path.
You will never be able to marry for the rest of your life.
You will never be able to pass on your martial arts, nor have children.
You cannot turn back.
Father
Do you know what women think inside their hearts?
If you can understand me as a woman
give me a sign.
"You must think of your opponent's move first"
"before you decide your own move."
He took advantage of our family.
I can only go forward.
I cannot be held back.
Hong Kong, Tai Nan Street
Master Yip, you've taught martial arts, right?
I had to in order to eat.
But that was just one time.
How can you only do that kind of thing just once?
To survive.
You brought in all the luggage by yourself.
You're pretty strong.
Saved me a round trip.
You know there aren't many Wing Chun practitioners in Hong Kong.
Does it have any special techniques?
No special techniques.
Only three basic ones:
Tan, bong, fuk
How many forms?
Siu lim tao
Chum Kiu
and there is also Biu Jee.
Weapons?
The Bat Jam Do butterfly knives
and the Six and a Half Pole.
Anything else?
Nothing else.
As for bone-breaking
neigong, lethal pressure points
it can do none of those things
As for smashing roof tiles with your head
or doing dragon or tiger dances
it doesn't teach any of that either.
Why not?
Teaching kung fu is not for putting on a show in the street.
So we don't teach breaking roof tiles with your head.
Lion dances and setting off fireworks
is only good for things like New Year's celebrations.
Furthermore, in that situation why would you need to fight so fiercely?
Just for a red envelope of New Year's money?
It is undignified.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Have you been in a real right before?
This whole street is made up of martial arts schools.
Whether or not something happens, people get challenged all the time.
Master Yip.
Do you think you can handle it?
If I said yes
would you believe me?
They're gonna fight! They're gonna fight!
We've been practicing for a few years now.
We would like you to show you our stuff.
Have you had lunch yet?
I just ate a bowl of fried rice.
I urge you to rest a bit.
So it won't go to waste.
Go to waste?
Brother Xiong!
Brother Xiong! Are you okay?
Not yet ready enough to go pour tea.
Pour tea?
To give respects to the master and be his student!
This bed is only temporary.
Master, make do with this first.
Please forgive the mess.
Do you have a hammer?
Master Yip
My gang want to study special two-handed techniques from you.
8 cents per person not too expensive, yeah?
However, you'll only get the full amount when you earn our respect.
Don't try and sell us any bullshit!
Are you cool with those two conditions?
Close the door.
You bastard!
Closing the door means you're gonna fight us!
You only got two hands and two legs. How many people do you think you can take out?
You're wrong!
I have two hands
but 8 legs.
As for how many people I can take out, that's hard to say.
But just hitting you sufficiently is more than enough.
"More than enough?"
I'm giving you that leg for free.
One leg!
Four legs!
One more leg left!
Do you still remember
our oath?
What oath?
"I sincerely swear"
"to be loyal to our leader"
"to obey the organization"
"and in order to carry out my missions"
"to take charge of difficult and thankless tasks"
"and always be ready to sacrifice myself."
What kind of punishment should does who violate the oath
get?
Fuck.
Babaojie, Chaotiangung's stuff
can still be used in Hong Kong.
Yes but our rules still apply:
The living can enter
but only the dead can leave.
I'm leaving now.
What are you gonna do about it?
See for yourself!
New Year's Eve - Hong Kong
Mr. Yip you didn't come here just to see a doctor.
I came to see the Gong family's 64 Hands
one more time.
Surely you must be joking.
But... since you lost to me.
Have a seat.
If you want to pass through the door, you have to say this:
"I'm afraid"
"you will have to sing 'Killing the Four Gates' before I do"
"only then can you eat this dumpling."
Thank you!
Did you know
in 1937
I had planned to go to the Northeast
because there is a tall mountain there.
I even got an overcoat.
But because of the war
I couldn't make it happen.
I couldn't keep the overcoat.
The only thing I have left is a single button
that I kept as a souvenir.
The 64 Hands of the Gong family is a tall mountain.
You shouldn't let it vanish in a puff of smoke like this.
The study of martial arts has gone on for a thousand years.
As for things vanishing in a puff of smoke
we haven't seen many cases have we?
The Gong family will always be depending on something to keep it going.
Mr. Yip
Martial arts can be tall but never taller than heaven.
Our natural gifts can be deep, but never deeper than the earth.
Life is never constant
so there is no need to regret.
As for this button, take it and go back.
If we want to see something
we end up not seeing it.
Say it again slowly later.
Mr. Yip
On New Year's Eve 10 years ago
did you know where I was?
Mr. Yip
A moment.
The Gong family
is not a river without direction or a tree without roots.
The 64 Hands is also not what you think it is.
The Gong family still has people.
I know the Gong family's "Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon"
If anyone wants to come and show me
I will be here any time respectfully waiting.
People!
Times have changed.
Go past that whatever river, take off those whatever shoes.
There are a lot of butts wearing a lot of underwear.
When I came to Hong Kong.
I could only smoke this brand of cigarettes.
The past resides in one's hometown.
Oh to have a puff of some genuine Guandong tobacco leaf...
Exquisite!
You need to study "warmth", "goodness", "respect", frugality", and "consideration."
Especially "consideration."
For example, I'm smoking right now.
A person I don't know is sitting across from me.
Out of consideration, I'll ask "would you like a smoke?"
It doesn't matter if the other person smokes or not
everyone still wants to be asked.
Otherwise, it's just plain rude.
Mr. Yip
Would you like a smoke?
Thank you.
You're welcome
What fantastic talent!
Twenty years ago
we could've had an exchange.
Too bad.
In a martial arts school
some people are ruled by their honor
others by their inner feelings.
Honor cannot be allowed to be tarnished by even a speck of dust.
So when you spill blood, your inner feelings take it in.
When it can't take in anymore, it leaks all over your honor.
This is a big reason why schools get destroyed.
Honor invites people to smoke cigarettes.
Inner feelings, however, can lead to murder.
Mr. Yip
you arrived too late.
Don't speak of the 64 Hands ever again.
You won't see a single hand of it.
New Year's Eve - The Northeast
Killing people is hard you say?
My lady.
Things now are different from before.
The price for killing is your own life.
In Ma San's case,
I'm not sure he is worth it.
The Way is the path that people walk on.
Should they go back home?
Or keep moving on?
Tonight is New Year's Eve.
He will certainly come.
We must wait.
Alright.
We wait.
Today my lady and Ma San
have a score to settle.
No one else
can interfere!
Anytime.
But there's still a monkey doing tricks here.
Take him out!
You are more relentless than a debt collector.
It's the last day of the year. And you still can't forgive me after all this time?
The dumplings are in the pot.
I'm afraid you won't be able to have any.
For the last time
I'm telling you that I had no intention of taking over your family or its honor.
Know when enough is enough.
We should burn the incense
eat the food
and do what we have to do.
Heaven will rain down thunder and lightning to finish this.
The Gong family's possessions
must be returned today.
Alright.
The possessions you speak of
are here.
If you want them
come take them!
Master!
Don't go near him!
Ma San
Talk!
That day
the Old Man
spoke with me alone
about his supreme technique
"Old Monkey Hanging the Seal"
He said "hanging the seal"
meant looking back.
At the time
I didn't understand.
I also thought
he was slow.
As for the Gong family's possessions
I return them.
You said it clearly before.
They aren't yours to return.
They are mine to take myself.
My lady!
Hong Kong - Yixiantian opens the White Rosebush Barber Shop.
I'm sorry!
I was thinking of my mother.
As for the package I sent out... did the boss get it?
He got it.
There are traditions when you open a business.
It's the same everywhere.
The card I sent to Sanjiangshui.
You should have known how much it weighed.
Enough money for the total weight.
My brothers
You've got your money down here
and your life.
Think about which is more important
and choose.
Your eyes... there's no mistaking it!
They're just like my mother's.
Should I cut out both or just give you one?
Wait!
Don't you want them?
Sorry, my bad!
You really are
like an elder.
Today is the anniversary of my mother's death.
I gave two lamps to the boss to light the road.
The waters that flow around Qing mountain go on forever.
Anyway, I think I'll be going now.
Wait!
You also said something about tradition.
Nobody said anything about tradition.
What do you want?
I stab you 3 times, you stab me three times.
That's lame.
Lame? That wasn't lame!
Do you see that chair over there?
In a few seconds, I'm going to tell you to go sit there.
If I can't make you do it
I'll give you back all your money.
You're joking
right?
Brothers
I'm going to let this go just this one time.
But the next time you cross the line...
Just try it.
I'm telling you this from the bottom of my heart
the fire in your eyes is just like my father's.
Please! Take me as your student!
Teach you?
That would insult our founder's honor.
This is also coming from the bottom of my heart.
Fine. I'll teach you a little bit.
That year, Yixiantian accepted students.
Baji Quan entered Hong Kong.
The winter of 1952.
Gong Er stopped meeting people.
Some people said that it was because her old injuries
that she started to smoke opium.
Some people said that she become obsessed with perfecting her kung fu.
The last time I saw her
was in the Great South.
Do you understand this play?
I think I heard this before in Foshan.
It called the Dream of something-something.
"The Dream of the Flowing Wind."
A flowing wind's essence is the same as a dream.
Some people say
"bamboo is better than silk"
"and meat is better than bamboo."
Singing something
is far better than saying it out loud.
Did you ever learn acting?
Just superficially.
In those days
Those who were stubborn
would study drama.
I took the corner of the stage.
There were a lot of ups and downs.
When I get sick of singing "Lady General Yangmen"
I would switch to "The Peony Pavilion."
At that time
I imagined you were in front of the stage.
I sang so you would look at me.
I thought meeting that way
would be fun.
I imagine getting tickets for a play that good would be hard.
You are a true fan.
If you want to see the play
I'll send you a ticket.
Actually, life is like a play.
For the past few years, it seems you have performed in many different plays.
Yet you have always kept the beat and brought honor to yourself and your family.
It's unfortunate
that we didn't spend more time together.
I never expected you to take me to see a play.
As for my drama
it doesn't matter if people applaud or not
just as long as we can stay in this moment.
Tonight I invited you to come out
to finish the things I should have finished
and to say the things I should have said.
Do you want to leave?
In the North we have an old saying
"People don't leave the road"
"tigers don't leave the mountain."
These past few years
we've all been living away from our real homes.
I am really tired
and I want to go back to my real home.
Before I go
there is something I want to return to you.
As for the Sixty-four Hands Technique
I've already forgotten it.
I met you in the best time of my life.
I was lucky.
Unfortunately, I don't have any more time.
Remember when I told you
that there is nothing to regret in life?
It's all bullshit.
If life had no regrets
it would be really boring.
Mr. Yip
I want to be honest with you.
You are in my heart of hearts.
Telling you this shouldn't be a big deal.
Liking someone is not a crime.
But I can only go so far as liking you.
I've never told anybody this.
When I saw you tonight
I didn't know why I should say it.
I dragged you through the good and bad in my life
and like a chess game, it is always going back and forth.
Please take care of yourself.
Life is like a chess game. The loser has nothing to regret.
Originally there was no good or bad between us.
And if there were
it would be fate.
Your father said
"If you know to bear this in mind, it will reflect on you."
"Where there is a lantern, there will be people."
I hope one day
I will be able to see the Gong family's Sixty-four Hands Technique again.
My father would always say
People who practice martial arts go through three stages:
Seeing yourself
Seeing the world
Seeing all living beings
I learned to see myself.
And I think I learned to see the world.
Unfortunately, I was never able to see all living things.
I wasn't able to finish
walking down this road.
I hope you can keep walking on it.
At first glance
does it not look like a martial arts place?
During the so-called Great Age
there was only one question:
To go or to stay.
I chose to stay in my time.
Those were the happiest times of my life.
Gong Er died of illness in Hong Kong and kept her oath until her death.
She never married, never had children, and didn't pass on her art.
Tomorrow we're going to send Miss Er's coffin back to her hometown.
She left this for you.
Before I joined the Gong family
I was a head-chopping executioner.
When the Republic was formed, there was need for us, so we thought we would starve.
During that time
if the Old Man hadn't taken me in
I would still be in Chengnan getting pissed on by pigs.
The Old Man never mistreated me.
Instead he asked me to always follow Miss Er around and stay by her side.
He said I was full of hate, but I could keep it under control.
Later, he changed my name to
Lucky Star
He had hoped Miss Er
would always have a lucky star following her around forever.
For women
cutting off their hair is like cutting off their head.
When she was going to avenge the Old Man
she cut her hair off
and followed the path of never marrying and never passing on her art.
She was on her own.
Now her work is done.
This is from before her vow.
She burned the hair she cut
completely into ashes.
The lady said
she and you knew each other for half her life
But in actuality, you didn't know her
and she didn't know you
but if you saw this
you will understand her.
Mr. Yip
The Gong family has nobody left.
I give Miss Er
to you.
The Gong Family has never lost.
Gong Er also never lost to anyone her whole life.
If she had to lose
she would rather lose to herself.
On the day I left Foshan
there was something I wanted to tell her
but I didn't say it with words.
A young man's heart has a pair of legs.
Even if divided by a river or an ocean, he always comes back.
When I took that first step forward
I wrongly thought that there would be a day I would return.
I never suspected that it would be the last time.
From then on, I only looked ahead
for there was nothing behind me.
Looking back there is no shore.
Cheung Wing Sing died of illness.
Yip Man never stepped foot in Foshan again for the rest of his life.
Alright! Ready stance!
Left fist! Punch!
Tan sao!
Rotate your wrist!
Bring it in!
Right fist! Punch!
Tan!
Twist the wrist!
Bring it in!
Mr. Yip
All the people we meet in the world
we will eventually meet again, even after a long time.
Some people say became popular because of me
and because of me became accepted.
I just hope they are right.
My whole life I had never put out a signboard.
In my opinion, martial arts is universal.
A thousand styles returning on a single road.
In the end, it is just two characters:
One horizontal
one vertical.
Yip Man died of illness in Hong Kong. He passed the lantern on to countless others.
Thanks to him, Wing Chun flourished
and spread all over the world.
Thank you for watching. These subtitles aren't perfect, so please feel free to improve them!
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player