My mother made me promise
to be an artist.
She taught me that imagination
could take a person anywhere.
Mine took me from Indiana...
...to Broadway to Hollywood.
She was right.
- Hello, Lou.
- Mr. Kazan, how are you?
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you, sir.
- Otto. How are you?
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning, Mr. Kazan.
- Good morning, Miss Harris.
You look beautiful, Julie.
Thank you.
- Perfect, Anna.
- Thank you, Mr. Kazan.
- Let's film this, Mike.
- Yes, sir.
What else do we have?
- Raymond. Where is he?
- Let's clear.
Good morning. Hello!
It's nice to see you again.
Elia, good heavens,
they're shooting.
It's okay.
We're not shooting with sound.
Good. How are you?
Good morning, Anna.
Julie, you look marvelous.
Thank you. Good morning, Raymond.
- Good morning, Mr. Massey.
- Good morning.
Good morning. Lovely day.
This is what he'll wear
in the birthday scene.
I like the cloth.
Just for you, Raymond.
Do you think I'm back playing
Abe Lincoln in this get-up?
Not at all.
It seems right to me.
All right. It feels good.
Thank you.
Let's shoot Mr. Massey next.
Can I have one that works?
Absolutely. We'll get Props on that.
Props, Mr. Massey needs you!
I am so looking
forward to this.
- So am I, Raymond. So am I.
- Good.
- Do you want this smiling or natural?
- Natural.
I wanted to call you last night.
I wanted to tell you how wonderful
you were in rehearsals.
Just so beautifully...
Just very pleased.
- I think we've broken through.
- Oh, yes. I do too.
James Dean is here.
Send him in.
Be right back.
Raymond, let's stop this for a moment.
Sorry, everybody.
The boy I've cast as Cal is coming in
and I'd like you to meet him.
Well, I'd be happy to.
He's never done a feature before.
He's done some first-rate stage
and TV work. He's a natural.
He may strike you as odd,
but he's enormously talented.
Well, let's take a look.
Jimmy.
Jimmy, come meet Raymond Massey.
- Oh, he's probably shy.
- Come on.
All right.
This man can't play my father.
He's too old.
Get somebody else.
- I'll talk to him. I'll talk to him.
- What-
What the hell
were you thinking in there?
Raymond Massey is a highly respected
actor and you've offended him.
- He said I offended him?
- Of course you deeply offended him.
Good.
Why good?
Because I need him to hate me.
Yeah, we're still a little hot.
Mark, you up there?
Hey, Al!
Al, pan that lamp around.
All right, who isn't ready?
Good. Let's shoot this one.
Okay, we're going, people.
Let's all settle down.
- And... roll camera.
- Rolling.
Scene 163 Apple, take three.
Okay, marker!
And action!
Cal, you'll have to give it back.
No, I- I made it for you, Dad.
You'll have to give it back.
- To who? I can't give it back-
- To the people you got it from.
The British Purchasing Agency?
I can't give it back to them.
Then to the farmers you robbed.
We didn't rob anybody, Dad.
We paid two cents a pound...
- Two cents over market for that stuff.
- Cal.
I sign my name...
...and boys go out
and some of them die.
And some live helpless
without arms or legs.
Not one will come back untorn.
Do you think I could take
a profit from that?
I don't want the money, Cal.
I couldn't take it!
But thank you for the thought.
I'll keep it for you.
I'll wrap it up and-
I can't take it! I won't take it!
Son...
...I'd be happy if
you gave me something...
Well, something like your brother.
Something honest and...
...and human and good.
Now, don't be angry, son.
If you want to give me a present,
give me a good life.
That's something I can value.
No, Cal.
No. Damn it!
I'm sorry, IKaz. I'm...
Cut it!
IKaz, may I speak to you
a moment? Privately!
Let's not everybody fall apart.
- What's up?
- Why is he trying to hug me?
It's infuriating! What he's supposed
to do is turn from me and exit.
That is what-
The last moment is mine.
- I understand.
- He's humiliating my character.
- I'll talk to him and take care of it.
- Please do.
He'll be fine.
He's right where we want him.
But I need one more.
You got another one in you?
You just let me know
when you're ready, okay?
This time, try to kiss him.
Raymond.
- I've talked to him. He's very sorry.
- I should think.
I don't know what to do either.
I need your help.
- If you could do me one favor...
- What?
If you could stay in the scene
and react in character.
No matter what he does, wait
for me to yell, "Cut. "
You have no idea how difficult it is.
- He's so unprofessional.
- He's a young man.
- Yes, he is.
- You're a brilliant actor. Help him.
Help him. Help me because
I don't know what else to do.
All right, all right, all right.
Thank you. Everybody, let's take it
from Adam's line "I sign my name"...
...right through Cal's exit
and no stops, no matter what!
Okay, everyone,
back to one, back to one!
- "I sign my name" right to the end.
- All right.
- Let's go. Quickly.
- Roll camera.
Scene 163 Apple, take four.
- Slate it.
- Marker!
And action.
Cal, I sign my name...
...and boys go out and some die.
And some live helpless
without arms or legs.
Not one will come back untorn. Do you
think I could take a profit from that?
I don't want the money, Cal!
I couldn't take it!
Well, thank you for the thought.
I'll keep it.
I'll wrap it up-
I'll never take it!
Son...
...I'd be happy
if you'd given me something...
...like your brother's given me.
Something honest and human and good.
Oh, don't be angry, son.
If you want to give me a present,
give me a good life.
That's something I could value.
Cal.
Cal, I-
Cal!
Cut!
Print that one, please.
Gets no better than that.
Did you see that?
I did. It was brilliant.
Thank you, Raymond.
Okay, that's it.
Let's print three and four.
"O the raggedy man
He works for Pa
And he's the goodest man you ever saw
He comes to our house every day
Waters the horses and feeds them hay
And he opens the shed
And we just all laugh
When he just drives out
Our little wobbly calf"
What is he saying?
It's a poem, Daddy.
He's memorized three entire verses...
...of James Whitcomb Riley's
"Raggedy Man. "
I am trying to read my paper.
It's a lovely poem, Win.
Fine, you two take the front room.
It's not you, honey.
Daddy's upset with me.
Now, he loves you.
Come on, come here.
It's not your fault, Jimmy.
- It was a long time ago.
- I need a place by myself.
- But I'll be lonely.
- A place where I'm being respected.
Please don't leave me, Win. Please!
You asleep, Jimmy?
No.
- Jimmy, I have to go away for a while.
- Where, Mama?
I have to go to the hospital.
Why?
Because I'm not well.
The doctors, they need to...
They need to do some things
to make me get better.
Can I go with you?
I wish you could.
Who's gonna get me up for school?
Who's staying with me?
Daddy.
Daddy doesn't like me anymore.
No, of course he does.
He loves you.
He won't hug me.
Listen, Daddy's not mad at you, Jimmy.
Just keep showing Daddy
your love and he'll love you back.
It's not Daddy's fault, Jimmy.
Now go to sleep.
I love you.
I was nine years old
when my mother died.
My grandmother Emma
came out to Los Angeles...
...to bring my mother's body
back to Indiana for the funeral.
I think it would be better
if you came with us now-
I can't do that, Mother.
- The boy is so upset.
- I can't leave work just now.
I really can't.
I'll be there at the funeral.
All aboard!
Take good care of your grandma, Jim.
Winton, you shouldn't
take this out on the boy.
Now, for God's sake, give him a kiss.
Say something encouraging.
I'll be coming out to Indiana
in a couple of days, Jim.
All aboard!
You gotta go, Jim.
All aboard, please.
Jimmy?
Jimmy.
No, thanks, Grandma.
I'll go sit with her.
I'm right here with you...
...so don't worry about nothing, okay?
Can you hear me?
Mama, can you hear me?
My father never came
to my mother's funeral.
In fact, he never came
to Indiana at all.
I moved in with my Aunt Hortense
and Uncle Marcus.
Son, you can't stay here.
You almost got me
that time, Mr. Walther.
Yeah, one of these days, James.
You got anything for me from California?
No, just the usual.
Want ads, circulars.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Our next graduate holds
the Grant County record...
...for the pole vault.
He is a four-letter man...
...an outstanding dramatic speaker...
...and as everybody knows,
a fine actor.
And he will soon be off
to study Business Administration...
...at Santa Monica
Community College in California.
James Byron Dean!
Jim, is that you?
Come on in.
Thank you for letting me
stay here with you.
You can stay here
a month or so, till you're on your feet.
It's fine with us.
This is Ethel.
Oh, hi.
Your dad's told me so much about
you. I'm glad to meet you.
Ethel's my wife, Jim. We're married.
You're married.
That- That's great.
Let me show you the guest room.
I mean, your room.
I hated business school.
Felt like I was wasting my time.
I'd done some acting in high school
and I loved it.
And more than anything,
I wanted to study acting.
Oh, Winnie. Oh, Winnie.
Acting?
Like in plays and movies?
Yes, sir.
How you planning on making a living?
Acting.
You are a dreamer.
Just like your mama.
That wasn't our understanding.
You stay in business school...
...and you can stay here.
But you study acting...
...you're on your own.
Next in is...
...Byron and/or James Dean?
Over here, kid.
Which is your real name?
Byron or James?
Well...
What do you think is better
for an actor?
Go with your real name. Less confusing.
What can I do for you?
I want to study here...
...in your professional acting class,
Mr. Whitmore.
Are you any good?
Well, I did a couple plays
in high school...
...and people said
I was pretty good, but I...
Sir, I don't want to be just good.
I want to be great.
Got any money?
No.
I sure don't.
Great ones never do.
All right, kid. You're in.
It's 12 a week, man. Cash, no checks.
I'll take it.
So how come you got a card
up at Whitmore's studio?
You an actor?
Next to Brando,
I'm the world's greatest actor.
Who's Brando?
Jimmy, Billy, up front.
Billy owns a watch repair shop.
Jimmy's picking up a watch
that he cleaned.
Billy, come here. Come here.
You know it's stolen,
you called the cops.
You gotta keep Jimmy here till they
arrive so you can collect the reward.
Don't let him go. Okay?
All right.
You have an appointment
in 15 minutes...
...to deliver this watch
across town to a buyer...
...for $2000 cash.
You want to get the watch fast.
You need the money, Jimmy.
- All right. You both got the setup?
- Yeah.
Whenever you're ready.
Hi.
I'm here to pick up that watch
right there in the case.
It's not ready yet.
Just give me a minute.
No, that's fine.
No, no, no. Stay cool.
Give me the watch, man!
Okay, give me a minute.
Hey!
- Hey! IKnock it off!
- Come on, you stinking black!
Jimmy, knock it off!
- IKnock it off, Jimmy!
- I'm gonna kill you!
Jimmy, knock it off. Jimmy!
Hey. Enough, enough.
Enough.
Stanislavski, you're next. Come on in.
You get into a lot of fights?
No, not a lot.
You will...
...if you let yourself go
over the edge like you just did.
Jimmy, acting is acting.
You can't get confused.
You gotta know where to draw the line.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I mean, it was good, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, it was good.
Wait, Mr. Whitmore.
I want to ask you something.
Do you think I got the goods
to be a real actor?
Yes, I do, Jimmy.
Yes, I do.
I decided to move to New York.
Every actor I cared about,
Brando, Clift, even Whitmore...
...all worked in New York.
New York was big and lonely...
...and I loved it.
Being a struggling actor in New York
in the 1950s was the best.
The right place at the right time.
I stopped worrying about
my mother and father for a while.
I was dead broke.
It didn't matter.
I was home.
Off the stage! Off the stage!
Let's go!
Next five numbers. 120 through 124.
Shut up!
Shut up! I want to see those numbers!
I want to see them today!
123, 120, 124!
Today, today! Thank you.
Smoke?
Yeah.
- Thanks, man.
- No problem.
What's your name?
I can't decide.
What are your choices?
Well, I got James Dean, Jimmy Dean...
...or Byron Dean.
Which one's your real name?
James. Byron's my middle name.
Go with your real name.
- You think?
- I know.
Jimmy's an 8-year-old boy
and Byron's a dead poet with a clubfoot.
And James is king.
What's your name?
Martin Landau.
Where you from?
Why? You wanna come home
and meet my mom?
Yeah, can she cook?
- You like matzo ball soup?
- My favorite.
You're invited.
Where you living?
Some dirt-hole rented room.
Let's go, fellas.
125 through 129, you're up!
What number you got?
231.
I'm 216.
Let's cut out, man.
Cattle calls are for losers.
Yeah?
Unless you got an agent sending you in,
you're kidding yourself.
All right.
Thanks.
You got an agent?
If I had an agent...
...would I be blowing my time
with a goof like you?
Come on.
Hey, who was Brando's agent
in New York?
Louis.
What?
I'll take him on.
I have a hunch I can sell him.
To who? To The Ringling Brothers?
Jane, he's too strange!
It's a "strange" people
won't get out of their minds.
I think he's a star.
Let me see what I can do with him.
All right. You do it on your own time,
not on my time.
What am I gonna do with you?
Bring your chair over.
You put "Leads only. "
You can't just audition for leads.
Why not?
For one thing, you've got to eat.
No, Miss Deacy...
Look, I only want to audition
for important parts.
I mean, parts that I care about.
Even if I have to starve.
Fine.
Thank you, Miss Deacy.
I'm a...
I'm a really lucky guy.
I've got the best agent in the world.
Get me those 8 x 10s.
Hi.
You work here?
I don't work here.
So...
...you're a writer or something?
You're an actor?
Jane Deacy just signed me.
Well, congratulations.
Are you an actor?
Actress. I'm an actress.
What are you writing,
Miss Actress?
Audition scene.
Yeah? Who wrote it?
That's what I'm trying to do.
Can I see it?
Yeah.
Well, this is the first page.
- So?
- Yeah, this is good.
What are you auditioning for?
The Studio.
Actors Studio?
Yeah.
Wow.
Brando's like some kind
of lifetime member there, right?
Yeah.
What's your name?
No, wait, don't, don't, don't.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
How about...
How about I take you out tonight?
I'll give you a ride on my motorcycle.
And then after I take you home
after the movie...
...when I lean in to kiss,
you can tell me then.
You got a scene partner?
I did.
Come on!
- I can't...
- Come on!
- Let's do it!
Let's go!
Oh, this is great.
What's the matter?
White.
Christine White.
My name.
Good to meet you.
Okay, I need Morty Chase
and Stanley Rushton.
Yes, gentlemen, please. Thank you.
Ah, excuse me. Excuse me.
Who's watching the auditions?
Kazan, Lee Strasberg,
and Cheryl Crawford.
- They're all here.
- Who?
Strasberg, Elia Kazan
and Cheryl Crawford.
- Oh, my God.
- Good.
Hey, that's my prop! Don't drink it!
Jimmy. Jimmy, stop! Come on.
You just drank my prop, Jimmy.
Okay, Christine White and James Dean?
Yes, that's us.
- You're on next. Are you ready?
- We're ready. Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Where are your glasses?
No, they're wrong for my character.
Wait, can you see anything
without your glasses?
Yeah, I see fine.
What do you think, man? How-
Yeah, very, very funny.
Put on your glasses.
I can't, Chris.
They're back at my place.
Why'd you leave them at your place?
They're wrong for my character.
I don't want to be tempted to use them.
Dean, White, let's go!
Oh, sorry. I didn't-
That's a chair.
You're apologizing to a chair.
I'm telling you, Jimmy, you never know.
Look at me when I auditioned
for Tennessee Williams.
I thought I was terrible.
You were terrible.
You didn't get the part.
It's just a detail.
Hi.
I'm Rogers Brackett.
Oh, God. The director?
A mutual friend tells me that
you're enormously talented.
Yeah, I guess.
I know of something that
you just might be right for.
A TV drama. It's a very good role.
So... would you like to audition?
Yeah, sure.
There's a party at my place tonight.
How would you feel about stopping by?
We could chat about the project.
There'll be some interesting men there.
Yeah, that sounds like a ball.
Here's my card.
Why don't you come by late?
Say midnight?
Yeah, midnight. That...
Perfect.
Good. See you later.
Right on.
That man's a class-A faygalah,
you know that, right?
Yeah, the man's a class-A faygalah
with a paying job.
Oh, Lord, you look like Hamlet!
Come in.
I'm drumming. Go to hell!
Come on, Jimmy. It's important!
Open up, open up! Come on!
Come on!
You want to break my door down?
- What's that?
- Actors Studio.
- Let me see.
- No.
Chris, let me see.
- Chris!
- Wait, wait!
- I'm gonna pour water on you.
- Wait, wait, wait!
You want to open it?
Or should I?
Here, you do it.
Oh, God.
Come on!
What?
We're in.
Both of us?
Both of us. We are in!
Give me that Actors Studio butt!
Dear Father...
...I hope you're well.
I think of you often.
My life in New York is a happy one.
I'm finding work as an actor.
I'm in a TVplay
that will be broadcast live...
...all over the country
in two weeks' time.
I hope you can watch.
And he'd yell up to me:
"Yo, Joey.
Come on down and play, Joey.
Joey. "
I hate to be wrong, but you were right.
Thank you, Louie.
Jimmy, you were fantastic!
I'm so proud. We all watched.
Saw it, saw it.
Here, here, here. Double Black Label,
the nectar of the gods.
- Jerry, give me two more of these.
- Thank you.
That's for me, man.
I was just on national TV.
So you're on TV,
and too cheap to buy me a drink.
Raise your glasses, everybody.
Raise your glasses.
I'd like to make a toast to James Dean...
...who's just achieved
what we all aspire to. Paid work!
Father, it's James.
Did you get a chance
to watch the play on TV?
It was tonight.
It was the one I wrote you about.
No. No, I don't mind.
I understand.
Yes, sir.
Okay, James Dean is next. James Dean!
Yeah.
That's James Dean.
Mr. Dean, you're reading
for an Arab, not a cowboy.
Would you mind removing your hat?
Sure.
Can you read
with broken glasses?
No, not so well, but...
I'd like to give it a shot, if you
don't mind, Mr. Rose and Mr. Mann.
It's okay with me. Let's start from...
...act two, scene one,
Bachir's entrance.
Okay, page 36. We're gonna
pick it up in the middle of the page.
Right there.
"Sir, did that doctor tell you
anything about me, sir?"
"Why? Is there something to tell?"
"Uh, no, sir. "
"He's a- He's a good doctor. "
"Are you hungry?"
"No. "
Okay.
I'm sorry, I...
I'm having trouble
seeing through the tape on my glasses.
How long will it take to fix them?
It's not the time, it's...
It's the 10 bucks.
Hang on.
Come here, kid.
Get your glasses fixed.
Come back this afternoon. Around 4:30?
Yeah, okay, 4:30's great.
- All right, thank you.
- Don't forget your hat.
All right.
That's a nice rose there.
Nice kid.
- You think?
- He's adorable.
Now, let's try it again, okay?
Let's do one more.
We can get it this time.
Okay.
Sir, did the doctor tell you
anything about me?
No, no, no, no. That doctor.
There's another "sir" at the end.
See it?
Let's try it again.
Sir, did that doctor tell you
anything about me, sir?
Perfect!
All right, here.
You got change for a 10?
Sir...
...did that doctor tell you
anything about me, sir?
"Why? Is there something to tell?"
Oh, no, sir. He's a good doctor.
Are you hungry?
"No. "
I brought it too soon.
What a shame.
That's enough.
- Thank you, Jimmy.
- Wait, wait, wait.
I really like him, Danny.
He's good.
- A little too weird, though.
- I'd like to hear him read with Geri.
I'll try it.
Can you stick around
for a half-hour?
We'd like you to read
with Geraldine Page.
Yeah, sure, I'll...
I'm open. I'll be over there.
You took my 10 bucks
and didn't get your glasses fixed!
Yeah, I used it to eat.
But I memorized it
so I didn't have to read it.
Do you...
...forgive me?
Sure.
We're very interested in you
for this part.
Thanks.
Biskra is a confusing place.
Don't you think so, Michel?
No.
Well, perhaps not.
Perhaps I think so because
you've been in that awful hospital.
Jimmy, come on, that's your cue.
Come on, get up.
Ah, sorry.
Madame, I'm...
...so happy that my gentleman
came home that...
...I was too lively.
Hold it! Hold it!
Everybody, take 10.
We're on 10, but let's stay close!
Jimmy, come over here. Over here!
Come on! Clear the set,
but don't go too far.
Sit.
Now, I've been saying this
40 ways to Christmas...
...but you don't seem to want
to get it through your head.
- Thick head.
- What?
The expression is
"get it through your thick head. "
I'm breaking my ass trying
to get this turkey off the ground.
I have no time for your games.
Now, the name of the play
is The Immoralist.
It's not
"Let's Hear James Dean Mumble. "
When will I have the privilege...
...of hearing you clearly?
I have been extremely patient thus far.
But frankly, you cut my part down
so much, I don't even know...
...who I am playing anymore.
And this upsets me.
If that means mumbling
through rehearsals...
...then you'll have
to be patient too.
Okay?
How'd you like that acting?
Could you hear me okay?
It's very convincing.
While we were rehearsing
The Immoralist...
...I got a call from Jane Deacy
to audition for Elia Kazan...
...for East of Eden.
Kazan had directed Brando
in Streetcar...
...and On the Waterfront.
Morning, Jimmy.
Have a seat.
Tell us about yourself, Jimmy.
Well...
You know, there's not much to tell.
I was born in Indiana...
...and moved out to California
when I was about 5...
...till I was 9...
...when my mother died.
And then...
...I was sent back to Indiana to live
with my aunt and uncle on a farm.
What was it like living on a farm?
I wasn't much of a farmer.
I rode my motorcycle.
I used to...
...chase the cows.
They'd run and their udders
would swing from side to side.
How about your father?
Well, we don't...
We don't really talk much.
We don't like each other.
In fact, we hate each other.
See, I'm an actor because...
...it's how I express myself.
I'm not very good with talking.
I think you can tell.
When do you open in the Gide play?
Next Thursday.
Mr. Steinbeck and I
will be coming on-
If you're coming, don't tell me when.
It's better if I don't know.
You think you can handle Cal?
Yes, I do, sir.
Good.
We'll contact your agent.
Jane Deacy, right?
Right. Yeah.
Is that it?
That's it.
Thanks.
That's the kid I want
to go with for Cal.
What do you think?
Mr. Kazan, that young man is Cal.
Five minutes, Miss Page.
Five minutes, Mr. Jourdan.
- Where the hell is he?
- I don't know, Mr. Rose.
Geri. Geri.
Oh, my heart. Oh, my God.
- Can't catch my breath.
- You're the greatest actress.
Go enjoy yourself.
Louis! How are you?
Look how handsome you are.
- Merde!
Look, five minutes. Five minutes!
I want that understudy dressed.
We're going up in 10.
It's already done.
We looked everywhere!
Get this kid on a leash.
Put him on a leash!
How is this happening?
Are you crazy? You're on
in three minutes! Get dressed!
Good job, Jimmy!
Jimmy! Come over here.
I'm so proud of you.
So proud of you.
You're gonna be a star!
I'll be right back.
You were better than I ever imagined.
- Thanks, beautiful.
- Ever!
Louis, you're improving.
You raised both hands upstage.
IKid, kid. You stole the show!
We can run a year on your reviews.
Congratulations!
Congratulations. What's this?
My two-week notice. I'm quitting.
- Oh, very funny. Very funny!
- I'm not joking.
I've got a movie.
I'm going to California in two weeks.
You're not kidding?
No.
Good luck to you, kid.
Why'd I do it like that, Marty?
He was nice to me. Why must I
make people reject me? Why?
You're an ambitious,
selfish son of a bitch.
Mr. Kazan.
Can we make a stop near here?
There's somebody I want you to meet.
An actor?
No, sir, it's my father.
I'd love to, but another time.
We really have to keep moving.
Please, sir?
It's important.
- Driver.
- We can go?
Sure.
Take a right, the next right.
Father.
Hello.
This is Mr. Elia Kazan.
He's directing the film that I'm doing.
- Happy to meet you, sir.
- Same here.
And you two will have to tell me when
this moving picture of yours comes out...
...so Ethel and I can go see it.
Yeah, you'll be
the first person I tell.
Well, that's good.
I'm sorry, but I can't invite you in.
Ethel and I are expecting guests.
Thank you, sir, for taking Jim
into your moving picture.
- Nice to see you, Father.
- Thanks for the time, Mr. Dean.
Yes, sir.
Winnie.
That must have hurt.
We'll use it.
All your boy has to do is sign it.
Jane Deacy hooked me up
with Dick Clayton...
...an agent to look
after me in Hollywood.
Here we go.
We're all signed, Mr. Warner.
Before we start shooting Eden,
I think I'm gonna send your boy off...
...to Palm Springs
for a couple of weeks.
Have you lying out in the sun,
get a tan.
Maybe we should
fatten him up a bit too.
You're too skinny. Way too skinny.
You look like a refugee.
You're never gonna get rich
unless you look rich.
Jack.
IKid's been seen around town
riding a motorcycle.
How much am I getting paid for this?
Thousand a week,
10 weeks guaranteed.
This true?
You ride a motorcycle?
Oh, yeah. I...
I just bought a Triumph 110.
You know, like they used
in The Wild Ones?
Get rid of it.
The studio backs stars, not corpses.
You understand me, don't you?
Say yes.
Yeah.
Attaboy.
Thank you, Dick.
What's wonderful about Massey
is that he's easy to get off guard.
He's so stiff and he's so wooden that...
...those quick moments are
the moments that I'm gonna use.
Those are the wonderful moments.
What I want you to do when
we're dealing with the Bible scene...
...just on his close-ups, is to swear
like never before...
...because he hates that stuff.
He hates it. He's so wooden,
but it works for us. It's wonderful.
Who's that?
That's Caesar and that's Brutus.
No.
The girl.
It's Pier Angeli. She's working
opposite Newman in Silver Chalice.
Do me a favor.
Bring the guy in the skirt over here.
Come on, he looks more like your type.
Can I have a word with you?
- Hello. What is your name?
- Stephan.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Oh, my God, I have to ask.
Where did you find that dress?
I've been looking everywhere
for something like this.
You may try it on
if you want.
I hear he's up against Paul Newman
for the big fight movie MGM's doing.
Well, I'm sure he'd trade in
the movie for the girl.
- What girl?
- That girl.
He's gonna have a problem there.
What do you mean?
And who is this?
Mama, this is James Dean.
He's an actor.
This is my mother, Mrs. Pierangeli.
So, what do you want
with my daughter?
Nothing.
Good. You won't be disappointed.
Hands up.
Go, go, go, go!
Her real name was
Anna Maria Pierangeli.
I loved her like
I'd never loved anyone.
She was my reason for being alive.
I used to wish that if she died...
...that I would die
in the very same moment.
I borrowed a beach house in Malibu
where we could be totally alone.
Higher, higher, higher, higher.
One, two, three.
Come on in here, kid.
I got an actress' mother telling me
that you're molesting her daughter.
It's lucky I've been watching your
dailies or you'd be out on your ass.
It's walnut.
You scratch that, it costs me $2000.
That's more polite.
You got anything else?
Yes, there's plenty else, wise guy.
If you're thinking
of marrying her, forget it.
You think 14- and 15-year-old girls
want their heartthrob married?
On the other hand,
you want to marry Miss Ravioli?
Go ahead.
Find yourself another studio.
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
You got two weeks left on Eden.
I know Nick Ray's been talking to you
about Rebel Without a Cause.
And he wants you for it.
But you know what I told him?
I told him I gotta think about it.
Is there anything else?
Don't play it smart with me, Jimmy.
I'm tougher than you.
A lot tougher.
Now get out of my car, please.
Drive on.
Put your chin right there. That's good.
You know, because she's Catholic.
So she's not going to break us up
once we're married.
Jimmy, we just need to be married.
Put the cig in your mouth.
Eyes here.
- Can you understand me?
- Yes.
Yes?
You do?
Get over here.
I understand you.
We've gone over it cinquanta times.
Go over there. Get right.
Why do we have to wait?
Oh, that's perfect.
That's perfect.
Why do we have to wait?
I'm making a movie right now.
Oh, God, you look great.
You look like...
You look like the Madonna.
We can elope.
Yes!
Sure, that's crazy.
Hey, hey, look at me. All right.
Come here. Look, look, look.
Just let me finish making this movie...
...and then we'll get married.
- Yes.
- I promise.
Well, maybe my mother's right.
Maybe you're just using me
to get into the papers.
How can you think that?
That's what my mother thinks.
That's your mother, not you.
Okay? Can we just have
one night here, alone...
...without your mother in bed with us?
She wants me to marry Vic Damone.
She what?
You know, he's Catholic.
She likes him a lot.
So is the Pope.
Why don't you marry him?
I can't fight her!
Why not? Don't you have
a will of your own?
- It's not about will!
- What is it?
It's a matter of family
and being Catholic!
- Listen.
- What?
You tell Vic Damone
and your crazy mother...
...to stay out of our lives,
all right?
- You don't understand!
- I understand!
- You're not listening!
- Stop yelling at me!
Open it.
I love Aron, I do.
Really, I do.
I do, I do.
Cut.
Jimmy, wonderful.
It was just wonderful.
- Julie, you're beautiful. Beautiful.
- Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, that's a print,
a wrap, and we are finished!
Have you seen Jimmy?
He's not in his trailer.
Jimmy?
Come on up.
You okay?
It's over.
I know, Jimmy.
It's so sad.
You know, this is like my family.
I can't just let that go.
Always knew I would get
an actor like you for Rebel.
I think...
...divine fate calls the shots
for a director like me.
You know what I mean? Brando.
What, are they kidding?
Brando is too old, man.
You are fresh.
You are perfect for this part. Perfect!
We just gotta...
We gotta find somebody...
...somebody great for the girl.
What about Natalie Wood?
No, really, what do you think of her?
I want to know.
I really want to know.
Because, Jimmy, it's just you and I.
We are on this quest together, baby.
All the way down the line.
What do you think?
She's a child star, man.
Child star, huh?
Jimmy, this girl is 17 years old...
...and she is built like the Pieta.
I know. She doesn't look it, right?
But I'm telling you that
underneath those simple childish...
...cotton frocks, she is built
like a marble masterpiece.
Jimmy.
- Jimmy, listen to me.
- What?
You're young.
You're wonderful and you're young...
...but if you'd been there
for the start of Helen Hayes' career...
...you would know
what I see in this girl.
Genius. Pure genius.
That's what I see in you, Jimmy.
Genius!
Man, Rebel Without a Cause...
...is gonna be the first
visionary movie ever made...
...about teenagers.
You mark my word. Mark my word!
- You like jazz?
- Yeah, I like jazz.
Chet Baker mean anything to you?
Yeah.
He's playing down on the beach
tonight. You want to go?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Solid, baby.
Solid.
Pier!
Pier, listen, I have to go to New York.
I have to go to New York,
all right? Come here, look.
What?
Look, come to New York
with me, all right?
I can't go to New York!
I can't leave my mother.
Why?
You wouldn't understand.
- Look.
- What?
It'll be two weeks, okay?
Two weeks.
I have to be back to do Rebel.
I may not be here
when you come back.
- What?
- You heard me.
I may not be here when you come back.
What is that supposed to mean?
I don't want to stay here anymore!
I want to go!
James, I'm gone!
Fine, go!
I'm leaving! I'm gone!
Hey, Pier!
You're breaking my heart
Cause you're leaving
Hi, is my father here?
I want to talk to him.
He's away for a while.
Is there something that
I can help you with, James?
No, no. I need to talk to him.
I'll tell him that.
Are you all right, James?
Yeah.
We follow you in the newspapers.
Your father's very proud
of your success.
He is?
Of course he is, James.
Thanks.
Nice to see you, James.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
Can't you even talk
to the boy, Winnie?
I can't.
Her mother wants her
to marry Vic Damone.
Why?
Can't she just buy one of his records?
- She's driving me bananas, Marty.
- For you, bananas is not a long drive.
Jimmy.
You guys are meant for each other.
It's perfect casting.
Pick up the phone, tell her
you love her, tell her you're sorry.
Tell her anything.
Go, call her. You got the nickels.
Pronto. Hello.
Is Pier there?
Who is this?
It's James Dean.
She does not want to talk.
Just put her on the phone, please!
No, no, no. She's out there
choosing the flowers for her wedding.
Goodbye.
I don't know where he is.
He'll show, Jack. It's a benefit
for the studio. He'll show.
I'll tell you something.
He doesn't show,
I'm gonna ruin the bastard.
Even if I have to pull
the plug on Rebel.
- Jack, you look great!
- Nice to see you.
We should get going, guys.
We'll be late.
All right, let me do it.
God!
- We're not going.
- What do you mean?
I'm not even interested
in this glitzy glamour crap, all right?
They want to wear monkey suits, fine!
Not me.
Jimmy, I spent $174 on this dress.
Come on.
This is my first tuxedo.
Jerry, why don't you give
a round to everybody on me?
We're spending the night.
Maybe he's laying dead somewhere.
That's no excuse.
Jack, congratulations. Fantastic.
What did I tell you, Hedda?
What did I tell you?
Oh, God.
It's an Academy Award performance.
He is a great actor. God!
I'm going to write that, Jack.
I'm so pleased, Hedda.
I'm so truly pleased.
Now, is he really as difficult...
...as everyone says he is?
- Difficult? Jimmy?
- Yes, everyone says it.
Hedda, he's like a son to me.
Oh, come on, Jack.
Come on.
He is a teensy bit difficult.
But you mustn't write that.
You have to promise me
that you will not write that.
Please.
All right.
You'll owe me one.
Nothing for nothing, huh?
- Yeah.
- It's a deal.
- Great. You know what I'm gonna write?
- What?
I'm going to write
that he is America's...
...new...
...free spirit.
Hedda, Hedda, listen.
Write he's America's newest rebel.
- Rebel?
- Yes, he's a rebel.
Like us.
I don't care about reviews
or about grosses.
There's gonna be no more crap
like you pulled on me in New York.
Shut up!
Bernie Plotkin gave me this.
"Question:
Are you a homosexual, Mr. Dean?
Answer: No, I'm not a homosexual...
...but I won't go through life
with one hand tied behind my back. "
Did you say that?
You said that to a fan magazine?
It's true.
"It's true. " What are you,
a crazy person?
You think homosexuals
sell tickets to teenagers?
I don't want you saying
any more crazy things to magazines.
You say,
because I'm making you a star...
...you say, "Thank you, Mr. Warner.
Thank you. "
You sided with Pier's mother against me.
You should kiss my ass for that.
You'd be miserable with Pier Angeli.
Her mother would cut your balls off
and plant them on Mussolini's grave.
Let me tell you something.
Pier Angeli's gone.
She is really gone.
She's married. Forget her!
You got such a wonderful talent...
...and a wonderful career
ahead of you.
You should learn to trust me.
You're like a son to me.
What's funny?
You just gotta trust me too.
Of course I trust you.
Oh, you gonna light my cigar?
Smells good, huh?
You want to try it?
All right, everybody, he's coming.
Roll sound!
76, take one.
Shh! We're rolling!
All right, Jimmy.
Stop! You're killing him!
You want to kill your own father?
And cut!
Jimmy.
Jimmy, it's over. It's over, Jimmy!
How you doing, son?
It's got 200 horsepower...
...1300cc engine.
Right here, dual Solex carbs.
Whole body's made of aluminum
so it weighs about 1100 pounds.
- Watch it, man.
- Oh, sorry.
You know that
car racing is for idiots.
Well, you're working for me.
And I say no racing cars.
You find that funny, huh?
We're signing a deal that
will pay you a million dollars.
And for a million dollars,
I'm telling you, no more racing cars.
- While I'm shooting.
- I beg your pardon?
When I'm not shooting,
I'm on my own, Jack.
If you don't like that,
you can take your million bucks-
You're gonna say something
you're gonna regret.
Smile, Jack.
Why?
Get rid of it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
could I have your attention please?
Please gather round.
Everybody, come on in.
We're here today to celebrate
a great new Warner's movie star...
...James Dean.
Jimmy, come on up.
James Dean, who drives me crazy...
...and a million-dollar contract
which proves me crazy.
When the cork pops, the deal is done.
All right, but no deal
unless I get the cork out.
Right. Watch out,
everybody, you know he's crazy.
Oh, you're crazy.
You are nuts.
Oh, you sweetheart.
I love you and I hate you.
I hate you and I hate you.
When I started shooting Giant...
...nothing went right between
the director, George Stevens, and me.
Maybe it was because I missed Pier.
Or maybe it was because
Stevens reminded me of my father.
Where the hell is he?
I'm sorry, Mr. Stevens,
but he won't come to the set.
He said you kept him
waiting too long between takes.
- What?
- He says he's done for the day.
Come on, we'll take care of it.
Jim, we're ready to shoot.
Not me.
Not today.
Come on, son, let's go.
The well's rigged, we're losing the light.
Let's get out on the set.
You keep me waiting hours
preparing for a scene...
...you never get around to shooting.
I ain't working today.
And you do it again, I'm gonna
take two days. And then three.
All right. Put Dean's clothes on
his stand-in. We'll shoot it without him.
Come on!
You can push that mug Rock Hudson
around, but not me!
You don't know what acting is,
you stupid son of a bitch!
Come on, old man!
I guess that's a wrap for today.
Is that you?
- I need to talk to you.
- Ethel's waiting for me.
Why don't you let her wait?
Hold on, young man.
Don't take that attitude with me.
- I need to talk to you!
- I don't have to talk to you-
Everybody thinks I'm great except you!
- Fine, listen to them.
- Don't you read the papers?
I'm in the papers! Everybody wants
to meet me except you. Why?
- every stupid mistake
you've ever made.
Shut up! Listen to me!
Why don't you talk to me?
You're my father!
- Please!
- I deserve some damn respect.
Dad, I was 9 years old!
9 years old! Now open
your mouth and talk to me!
You talk to me! Dad, please. Please!
- Hey, Winton.
- Talk to me, please!
What's going on here?
This is my father.
Now get in your house!
- Is this your son?
- Yeah, this is my boy.
- You two all right?
- We'll be fine. We'll be fine.
Winton, you shouldn't be fighting
with him out here in public.
I understand.
Now, where do you want to go?
We gotta go somewhere else.
- Okay?
- All right.
Beautiful view.
This is where my house is gonna be.
And I own that land over there too.
Nice car.
Yeah, it's aluminum.
They only made 30.
That must have cost a lot.
I got a lot.
Yeah, this town is yours, isn't it?
I'm doing pretty good.
You like L.A., Father?
Do I like L.A.?
Well, I'll tell you something,
young man.
If I could find the edge
of this town...
...I'd leave it.
But you're the edge of this town now.
And you are everywhere.
Why'd you do it, Father? Why-
Why'd you send me away?
Why didn't you come
to Mother's funeral?
- Just talk to me.
- But I don't have to talk to you.
You're my father.
No, I'm not. I'm not your father.
And your mother told me that.
Your mother, my wife,
told me that I'm not-
Well, I might not be your dad.
Told me just before she died.
She wanted to set
things straight, I guess.
When she was 18,
she started seeing this other guy.
He was married with kids...
...and she just couldn't
break it off, I guess.
A couple of weeks
after we were married...
...she found out that
she was pregnant with you.
And not knowing, I was
the happiest man alive...
...for about nine years.
But then, she just had
to tell me the truth.
And I just couldn't live with that.
Yeah, you know,
your mother was brave.
Telling me the truth like she did.
And I was...
...too prideful.
I couldn't find the damn courage...
...to forgive her.
And so I got cheated
out of my wife...
...and I cheated myself...
...out of having you as my son.
And I'm proud of you, Jim.
And I'm sorry that I acted so bad
to you all these years.
Mr. Stevens?
Ready to go to work, sir.
Good, son.
Good.
Ready? Let's go!
Let's go for picture, everybody!
Now, that's picture.
Here we go. Make it happen.
Effects, ready?
Ready!
Sound, ready?
- Camera, ready?
- Ready!
Let's roll!
Speed!
Scene 253, take one!
And action!
Blow!
Looks good.
Weird thing to name a car, man.
I don't know.
Maybe.
My mechanic, Rolf Wutherich,
and I decided...
...to drive my car
to a race in Salinas.
It was a beautiful, clear day.
The road seemed almost deserted.
You got it.
See that piece on you
in the L.A. Times?
No, why? I get hammered?
Opposite. They said you're gonna get
bigger than Brando and Clift together.
Can you believe it?
Watch that Ford.
He's turning left.
He's gotta see us.
There's been a terrible accident.
I took the train ride
back to Indiana again.
This time my father came with me.