Have you ever dreamed of a
before you met him?
As you invented it but did not.
These things really happen.
Weird, incredible things.
I can swear that happen all
the time.
Wake up.
Get up.
Is it raining?
Sort of.
I thought this park.
But at night, looks like
a park.
And we were in Italy,
we would be Italian?
A could be the French who
live in Italy.
We enjoy the food and way
of life.
Yes, but now we're in someone's backyard
and I'm starving, so, hurry up.
We are French women who die
of hunger.
Shit.
You parked on my lawn.
Yes, it's really nice.
It is better to remove.
No problem.
It is better to immediately
remove.
I told you, all right!
I'm sorry for your lawn.
What did you say?
I've always loved to travel.
Manny & Lo
- Meninas de Ninguém -
The day when our mother died,
Lo hid behind ðubrišta car,
just in case.
That summer, she ran away
from her adoptive
and somehow I was kidnapped
from my own.
She said it was her job to
save me from
such families as the Gordons.
I did not think it was so bad,
except that I was forced
to sleep in the garage.
But I'd still rather be with Lo.
She's my sister, but a good man.
Will?
Do You Know What's this for?
Thank you.
It seems that is not the owner.
That's what I thought.
Lo, this is true of horses.
Really? Really.
Go check milk.
Lo says that there are familial types
of people, and those who are not.
It's no good to you if
you're wrong.
She said that since our mother
had was majèinski type,
it means that she and I are
naturally independent.
Therefore, it is planned to
become a flight attendant.
And how are you today? - Good.
Would you like something
to drink, gentlemen? Of course.
Luckily she had a natural gift
for turbulence.
How about you girls?
- Move.
What? - I have cramps.
Have already? - Lo, down.
All right.
Can I ask you something, I?
When are you going to grows out this?
We're out. We need to get some
more tomorrow.
In the car we Rajkar.
She did not smell of Rajkar.
Yes, you're right, it's not, and you
know why, because it smelled like.
What's wrong with you?
Will you take my side?
Really? - Just tonight.
Some things, or you notice it
or not.
As eyelashes, Lo tried without
anyone noticing.
What are you looking at?
It's nothing.
So we have persisted for so long.
We were just two girls passing by.
If you have a car that no one knows,
and you know to borrow petrol
with the help of hose, you
quite some time to travel.
Hey, Joey.
We just stuck with one rule.
Always on the move and will
not get caught.
Thank you.
I did not do it for you.
I know, but thank you anyway.
I got something for you.
What's this? It's a gift
for you.
Seriously?
Open.
What's this?
That's the blues. Try it.
Why?
I do not know, I wanted to see
how it looks.
And how do you think it fits?
Probably different.
I mean, it's nice.
Fuck you, Joey.
Why?
I did not mean anything by it.
Let me, let's go.
Wait, where are you going, I'll buy
you another one, with a different pattern,
drugaèe blouse, where are
you going? I love you.
Hurry up, I want you to practice.
We have a new tray.
I did not do that tonight. Why?
I do not know. Why?
Because you're too...
- Too what?
Are you saying I'm fat?
Lo're not fat, but...
Okay, I'm fat, ok, I admit,
It's not so much a surprise.
Read this.
What? - This.
Mix eggs, sugar, oil, corn syrup...
- This is eating every day.
The thing is, you can lose
weight whenever I want,
You just need the will, right?
And who has more will than me?
No Lo. That's right.
Shit.
Susie. - Yes.
You have not been here by now,
right?
No, this is my first time.
So how is it?
Brilliant. - Good.
You do not need to test my urine.
I know what it is.
Deal.
- I am pregnant.
Are.
That's why I'm here, to take
care of it.
What do you think?
If sin will come to know when I die,
but now I do not have a choice.
As I said, I'm pregnant.
And you are long gone when you
could have something to do.
You can give birth tomorrow.
Will you do what I ask or not?
Sit down to talk.
You and he have a lot to
catch up on.
I'm not here to talk.
You know what we need? What?
Something in the countryside.
Where can we keep before us
the hope.
And not only so we wander, we
need some stability, is not it?
Sure.
While not complete, and then
continue.
In which direction to go?
I think that way.
Sounds good.
What if your mom here and tell
her about the baby?
Since we, as a ghost?
No, I think she's still alive.
To sit in the back seat.
I normally talk to us.
What would you do? Depends
whether drunk or high.
Come on, Lo.
How would I know what to do, Me.
Why do you always ask stupid
questions.
You probably would have had
a bath.
Yeah, probably.
How We've been on this trip?
Thirteen minutes and 40 seconds.
And when we passed the last
house?
That time. - Surely you see the
mailbox for the mail?
Sure.
Some people privacy seriously.
Wait a minute.
What if there's anyone?
- What are we going to tell them?
To sell biscuits.
What? Èokoladne?
Just go.
Is there anyone?
It is not locked.
You know, I think people live
here.
But do not currently live.
This is the second homes.
There will be vraæati some time.
How do you know?
See skis? - Yes.
Can you see the snow?
There is no food in the fridge.
And a bunch of cans. Food for
the winter.
Go check it out beds.
Tomorrow we have to get some
things that we need.
- What?
As the book. We must begin
to impart.
I saw the cat work on. Nine maèiæa
for eight and a half minutes.
Not hard to guess. Compared
with the other things we do.
They could at least introduce cable
here. See the tapes that they have.
"Orphan". - I was watching.
"In the service of love."
And that I saw.
A "Welcome Tiffany?"
- "Welcome Tiffany." I've never heard of.
I guess it's not bad.
This is Tiffany.
Look. See?
Lo? Lo?
Ugasiæu it.
This looks good.
There are a lot of pictures.
And drawings.
Check it out. Can you hear the baby
crying in the distance of 200 meters.
Try it.
Say something, will you?
There are three choices for each
Use of, or ordinary cloth diapers.
Of course, disposable ones are
most convenient,
but it breaks down, the canvas is
much better for the baby...
Come on. I said, let's go.
Just a second.
So if you want ordinary
diapers, we have,
and there is a kind of...
It's beautiful, is not it?
Unfortunately babies love to swing
right and not to the side.
I do not know why they were so right,
because if you make sure you can roll over the baby.
Honestly, if you like it buy
a rocking chair rocker.
Thank you.
Hello. - Hi. That's all? - Yes.
This is for your baby?
- Yes.
I think you'll also want a pink
pedal travel.
It's okay, it's better
this way.
Well, I never made a mistake.
Did you see someone that knows
so much about babies?
Excuse me, I'm Connie, this
is my store.
Alison. Hi Alison.
This is my Aunt Elaine,
who helps me when he can
and we are very grateful
to her.
Elaine, I think that Alison
wanted yellow.
How are you?
I'll be back in the morning,
Elaine.
You might ask her, right?
You think you can just take her?
So, always take things from
the store.
It's not funny. Do you want to go to
the hospital to arrest me or I die?
I do not want to get arrested
or to perish.
Okay, with that we have
already taken.
I'm sorry we're closed, you need to
you to come tomorrow. I can not.
Do you know what you need?
Yes. - All right then, come on.
How can I help? - Others need
my cradle.
We have two types of cribs, there
she was with stuffed animals
and here we have...
- Whoa, this is a rifle.
Put your hands in the air.
I'm serious, hands in the air.
Me, is greater.
Stop mumbling hell.
I mean it, do not spray it.
And legs.
Take the card.
Any.
Write to the sick and went to France...
No, do not write it.
Can... Dear friends I need
a break, like you Elaine.
Okay, come on.
If you think you'll take this
money, terribly wrong.
I do not need your money.
What do you need?
Let me, let's go.
Go see what he's doing,
I'll be careful.
Elaine...
I hope you slept well.
I'll let you music.
Some people like music while
you are sleeping.
Or when they are awake when they
are bored or neraspoložni.
My sister wanted to know if
you're okay.
Please tell your sister that I have
a lot of relatives and friends
with every day views.
No one will understand
my absence for granted.
I'm the one for you should
be worried.
Please pass on this.
Okay. - Thank you.
She is...
- I heard what she said.
Lo.
Elaine, hello. View Elaine.
I'm an alien.
Let Elaine, smile.
I still do not eat.
Take a spoon and feed it.
I've already tried that.
I think that the hunger strike.
What? Hunger-strike.
Lo? Lo.
There you go.
Do not discount the criminals,
regardless of whether a drug
or religious rituals, or whatever,
do not give up criminals.
Okay, then die.
I'm not going on holiday, ever.
It is generally known.
You have to sleep sometimes.
I can not believe I listened
to the rest.
I said I was sorry.
I did not know.
Go check the bathroom has
already been there.
Still she needs in 15 seconds.
How does that leaves
combination?
Around 22000
OK, check the twice daily.
All right.
That's your responsibility.
All right. - I'll tell me when it
is time to change the locks.
When it comes to the 15-20 may.
And do not let her see that
checking.
Let's not think that will work.
Give her the feeling that something
is achieved. It's okay.
So, are you going to relax
a bit.
Maybe he'll relax if you
talk to her.
You explain her situation.
First, let it cool down and
then I'll talk to her?
When you understand who's
the boss.
I think we should immediately
talk to her.
Well, you're the boss, right?
Is this yours?
Thank you.
You live here?
Yes, this is my room, this
is my fortress,
This is my bike there next room.
What is your name?
Do you?
Ben, but you can call me Even.
And why not Ben?
Nothing, I like it Even.
Take one.
Was signed.
I'm Tiffany.
Where do you live, Tiffany?
This is your mom? - Yes.
The real juice laid.
I said I was in that mood and
makes me such a shock.
It was weird.
What? Well I am currently so
in the mood.
Really? - Yes.
It was weird.
Maybe I can stay. They're coming
my relatives. - I like cousins.
Probably not enough.
I need to add some more things.
Will you come over tomorrow?
No it's fine. - Are you sure?
- Yes.
Whatever. Take care.
Where have you been? - Nowhere.
You did not talk to anybody,
right? - No.
You did not do anything stupid?
- No.
It is better not.
Let's get some food but I'll be
back sooner than you think,
so do not try anything.
There are no houses in the vicinity and
the road has at least five miles, is it me?
Four and a half.
And broken glass everywhere around
the house, I show her what you got.
There are all shoes that are in
the house. What else?
You also have things that can serve
as the shoes if you're really desperate.
Bucket on the floor if you need it.
Come on.
Now, if you want to stop a
hunger strike.
And if you want to listen
to music, and...
I do not know it seems like
a bad idea to me.
You're not gonna to keep the baby.
There's no way to keep the baby.
Then you have to choose
someone.
And that family on the ground?
They look ok.
Do you think they are ok.
I think you're sick.
What about them is wrong?
See how mother rocked her ass
every time the ball is hit.
Do you think these people you
can trust?
There are two or three mothers
out there that are not so bad
and if you will not already
choose to pick a bad one.
Shit.
Here Connie.
Is Elaine there?
Who is this? Barbara.
Who? Barbara, her friend.
Sorry Barbara, Elaine is not
here.
Really? Do you know where
it is?
She is on vacation.
Hello?
Do you know when will you
be back?
I do not know if you're her
new friend?
No. - Lf you were not in church?
- No.
Do you think you can hear her?
I do not know.
If you hear give her a message
from me, will you? Of course.
Tell her that this job has a
lot of financial cost
and that I am personally
responsible for them.
I can not afford to tell
people do unpredictable,
even relatives, not that I do not
have to understand it, and I have...
Get in the car.
How do you know that ozvuèen?
I know, because I was screwed, I know that.
Do not drive so zgnjeèiæeš baby.
Why we parked here?
Be quiet until you get to safety.
Shit.
Stop it.
God, you're pregnant.
Jesus, the porodiæeš.
Why do you think you're here?
Rodiæeš boy.
What?
I said it was a boy.
I have never made a mistake.
Why smoke when you're pregnant?
What do you think it is?
I have no idea.
It's called a hot meal and eating
it. Not for touching.
I think that kidnapping victims are
entitled to a meal like everyone else.
And if I'm not mistaken, the same
is true for the innocent babies.
If you two do not agree with it,
I can not help you.
It's good.
You know Connie?
My niece?
Yes. Why is not she wearing that
uniform for nurses like you?
Connie is a good woman, but
there is no such experience.
Are you there? It's a nursing
home.
I worked many medical tests
while my father was there.
Why not wear the same uniform
as the other sisters?
I was not formal.
What?
I got in the house other
photos and I hope
you'll respect my right
to privacy.
Even if you hold me against
my will.
Can I get this file?
Pardon?
Can I get this file? Please.
Well, you can. For now.
- Thank you.
Amanda, two things I want
to tell you.
The first is that crime
does not pay.
And second, I can'd feel good
about this kidnapping
as many people have suffered
because of it not just me.
But I think you're a beautiful
young lady.
Really? Thank you.
Who is it? - Loreal...
and Amanda.
Come.
Like I can not breathe,
and has shot more.
No, he turned.
Maybe hiccup. - Shut up,
I talk to Elaine.
Vida've done it before.
Is that bad?
Could be. - What do I do?
Put your head. Come on.
Put your elbows on your knees.
Like that?
That's it. Okay, Amanda tell me
when you sell exactly twelve minutes.
It's going to be ten and
thirty four.
I'll put the water for tea.
So, how is Lo?
I think it's working.
I'll be in the next room
if you need me.
Hey, thank you Elaine.
You're welcome, Loreal.
So, when will it happen?
- I'll have some more to cook.
I hope they come out earlier.
Loreal, there's nothing worse and
more dangerous than prevremenske pregnancy.
A woman should be Porada while
he can.
And how is it done?
Well, first he wants to stop it.
What else?
To avoid certain things that
cause. - What things?
Zaèinjenu food, long showers,
soda, closely underwear,
dancing...
No dancing?
Especially do not play rock
and roll.
Damn, and I was just in the
mood to play.
Go get your sister a glass
of water.
Did you hear me? She stopped
at 14-39 since Saturday.
You probably did something
wrong.
No, I swear.
Listen just because this lately
does not mean we should discount.
Maybe you prefer to stay with us.
Did you ever think of that?
To stay with us? You mean
that crazy?
No. Then we specify a reason
why someone like her
wanted to stay with us?
It is better to check the
numbers again.
You have no family, Elaine?
Some people have a gift but are
unable to use it. Sometimes
should not wait until their body
becomes used up to the present.
Do you understand?
No, not really.
When I was younger, I could not
physically have a baby,
my emotional side, how to say...
It was hard. It's hard?
I was like everyone else, but now
I feel much better.
This is good.
There are many ways to give
a gift, not just one.
And not just the obvious.
Does that make sense?
Yes. There is.
Amanda, can you nurse to add
water? Of course.
I do not want her back legs
swell. Fill to me. Thank you.
Have you checked the numbers
again?
Administration are still
trying to escape. I told you.
Have you noticed how some crazy
not believe someone
who does not wear a chain of
Articles?
There has been such. Elaine,
I knew that.
Whatever, but I did not care,
why should they?
Elaine. Sister-sleep.
I brought you something.
Hypnotized him. Eight minutes.
It was very thoughtful.
Go and wash.
Lo, get up.
Lo.
Okay, what is it?
What the hell?
Out of 475
00:54:29,360... > 00:54:31,120
It's nothing.
He's a good feeling, is not it?
What?
A nice long shower.
That's right.
It is better to obuèeš.
I let my sister to sleep,
we'll have dinner later.
Carefully Amanda, that's hot.
With mushrooms.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right, Elaine?
I'm fine.
What is it?
Just thinking. - About what?
Well, if you ever thought of
how all this might take?
How can we stay in this house?
No, not really.
Well, that explains it.
What explains?
It's nothing.
What explains this?
Well, it seems that people in
your position,
would prefer that they move,
instead of sitting in the same
place for weeks as ducks.
As targets. Thank you, Amanda.
As there is no process of
elimination.
You say we should go from
here?
Well, I do not make the decisions.
It's your show, right?
You know, I think that's right.
I think I should go from here.
Wait a minute. Did a lot of
people asking, Elaine?
It's a silly question.
Do you? Of course.
My group from the church, I was in
charge of the coffee, you know?
Remember, one reason why you
have not found?
I'll tell you why, because this
is the hiding place for the killer.
Do not I know you? You think
I'm stupid?
Yes, healing very nicely.
Clear.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, of course.
She is interested in the true
nature of your visit here.
Well, this is my house.
Yes, I'm just curious,
if you are going to join
someone else?
I came here to be alone for
a while. Really?
I need space from time to time.
My family knows that.
Well, I think we need to
concentrate on each other,
in order to survive.
Have you seen these guys?
They do not. You odvlaèiš
attention to them until the run.
I'll go to a pay phone and call
the sheriff,
will come soon, my acquaintance.
He will come soon, I promise.
So?
I think it's a very
interesting plan.
I razmisliæu about him.
What are you doing? Why do not
you untie?
No, what you do, what do
you do?
I do not understand why you were
not able to stay home with your family?
What?
Hello.
You know it's all a lot of glass?
Yeah, I know.
What can you play?
Hide, have you heard of
that game?
It looks like he's angry.
Or just weird.
It seems odd, but it has that
special gift.
What a gift? - Designate a gift
that certain people have.
You want it?
No, thank you.
Tonight we have a weird juice
if you want to drop by.
That's okay, we have a hot
meal.
You will not tell anyone
about him?
I still have my picture? - Yes.
Maybe I'll drop by tomorrow.
Yes, you may.
Take care.
Are you going to Elaine?
Loreal thought we'd stop
smoking.
We will. I'm sorry.
I wish I did not sit in that
chair.
Why?
I would not sit.
Lo, do not sit in that chair.
Are we going to sing?
No, we'll talk.
We'll talk about serious things,
about the future.
You know Elaine certain before we
lived a life that does not tolerate baby
even that we want and do not
want it.
I do not mind. - I do not start.
I've been thinking a lot...
What's this? - I'm talking about.
I thought it was stupid to give
her child hostage,
but you're like most people,
Elaine, I see it now.
You are overcome frown.
You have the knowledge, medical
experience and not only that, you're right.
Who the hell is this?
You're supposed to take his
shoes Elaine.
Can I ask you a question,
Elaine?
Have you ever heard of the
hostage taken hostage?
She was only trying to help.
What kind of crazy person would
do that? Well, we just did it.
It's not the same to me,
Do not you see that it should
be different than us.
You probably never had children.
I do not understand, just helped.
- I guarantee it's not a nurse.
Out of the car-what?
I mean it out of the car.
Lo stop, stop.
Damn, Lo. - What did you say?
I said, damn.
Do you want you to go out,
do you want?
Who are you with me, with
me or her?
Do not you want to sit
in front?
No, thank you.
Let me stop, you can not
sleep here.
Listen I'm sorry that it turned
out like that, but it is.
And better for what I have
now realized,
so we have time to come up
with something. - Stop playing.
What? I told you to stop
that play.
Who's playing, I'm freezing.
Play and looks like a rock, and
You'll get contractions and so cut.
Who told you that to me?
No one has said that.
And who is out asshole?
But it should not stop
you playing.
Stop Lo. I mean it, stop
it please.
You'll get contractions,
please stop.
Stop it.
Get up, come on.
I told you to stand up.
It's still early. So?
What is it? Nothing.
You look like you've swallowed
a fly. - Well, I'm not.
Give me five minutes, then come
in... - I will not go into.
What? I said I will not go
in to. Crime does not pay.
Damn me and you gave her
our food.
Okay, sit here and act like
an ass, but watch out for the cops.
Lo, where are you?
What are you doing?
- Did you see the cops? - Yes.
Did he see you?
- Yes. - Shit.
On what are you standing?
- On the crates. - Are there others?
A few. - Line them up.
You want to eat? Why do you
keep looking at your stomach?
You have cramps, right? Got
them from last night?
No ovako. -Did not I tell you
not to play like that last night.
Did not I say...
- Shut up, please.
What are you doing?
Look I do not want to get
arrested because of me,
But the cops know medicine
will die if I do not.
We're not going until they come.
Lo, we can not stay.
Now will come.
It was already half an hour.
The policeman saw me. He saw,
too. - I know.
Do you think that we are
now not after?
No.
No?
I think no one is chasing,
never.
What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking
about.
Will die in the middle of
the damn time in this damn car.
You're not. I do not want
to die to me.
Elaine, I am.
I thought you were never
going to come.
Neither do we. - Do you know
how dangerous these roads?
A radio does not work on more
than two hundred meters.
I did not deserve what your
sister did.
It was a terrible thing and
I did not deserve it.
We know. We're sorry.
We?
Yeah, me and Lo. We're sorry.
You'll be fine, look who's
here.
Tell her you're sorry.
I'm sorry.
She said.
Can you help?
Excuse me for a moment.
I'll give my best.
It should not take much,
does it?
Okay, I'm going to stop, and
falsehoods will leave prestaæu right?
Lo, look at me. Look at me.
You're not going anywhere,
do you understand me?
and I, I'll stay here and rodiæeš this baby.
Do you believe me?
Do you trust me?
Then stop resisting.
Push.
I think you should pick it up.
Elaine Damn, he's really
a boy.
Well, Amanda, we have a
long road
Your sister will certainly be
busy,
but I would like it uèiniš
something.
What's this?
I'd like to write a story of
500 words or more
about certain lessons that
are learned.
Lessons? - O hostages.
How?
As soon as we set up, and I
intend to write one.
Well, if you're gonna be'd
feel better about that, Elaine.
I believe I will.
Okay, fasten all.
You sure know how to drive,
Elaine?
Loreal, what kind of question
is that?
Have you ever thought someone
before you met him?
These things really happen.
Weird, incredible things.
I swear to constantly happens.
Original Serbian Translation by (c): Alexander
Adjustment by (c): Nemanja