- Danevang Presents --
- Mega Shark Vs.
Giant Octopus --
Aviation and Missile Command.
Sonar Test.
Height 3-4-0-3.
Win 3-2-2 to 1-0.
- Continue to report.
- Roger. Speedbird swings to the left --
- And continues close to the ground,
heading 9
Okay, Speedbird.
Wait a second part
of an iceberg dropped.
Hello.
- Half of the continent is ...
- Vince, it is okay.
Why are you so nervous?
- I know not.
- Just relax and enjoy it.
It is like a poem.
Speedbird, Alpha Tango here.
Can you see anything?
Can not see anything and radar
detects nothing
It is a wasteland.
It is no miles in circumference.
Remember lieutenant,
This is a confidential mission.
Get problems
the government will not be known by you.
Turn off the engine.
Lieutenant, hold your position
and wait for signal.
There you are.
Diving 20 degrees down.
Got it. Changing course.
Turn left. 3-0-0.
She is beautiful.
- Huge.
- Absolutely.
There are a whole bunch.
There are many.
Speedbird for April.
Is in position --
- And ready for
sending LFAS leave.
On my signal:
3, 2, 1 and leave ..
LFAS sent off
and works.
I want to receive
signals of 5, 4, 3, 2, 1 ..
Are the signals
emerged switches?
- It's incredible.
- Records we here?
Camera 2 and 3 are active.
Hold on.
- What ...
- There is something with sonar.
Lieutenant, what is the status of LFAS?
It is in level
1-20 and rising.
1-30, 1-40, 1-50.
Ladders, sir.
Is 1-60 ...
- What happened?
- I know not.
- What is that noise?
- It's Dawry she hates us.
The noise? We need to
to leave the area.
- It's whales.
- No, it is not.
Something bothers whales.
- Music?
- No, something stronger.
Man, what I thought of?
Whales are not the ...
The framework iceberg.
They kill themselves.
Think. Think.
This is it!
It's a transmitter.
Son of a bitch, this is a LFAS!
What?
Low Frequency Active Sonar.
They should not be used.
The iceberg is different.
Got a napkin?
Here in Japan, Mr. Harvey
we have certain customs.
Yes, we also practice in the United States.
So as to urinate
on a colleague?
I take it
too seriously.
- He feels you demean him.
- I can understand that.
There are many crazy things.
Listen.
Things are happening
is --
- Larger than our
own small problems.
And one has only the fun,
even doing.
The point is as long as we retain
our good mood --
- Everything will be okay,
I promise.
- Thank you Vince.
- Hey. I am a driver.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
That I do not know.
Nightmare.
It was also the worst,
I have been exposed.
- Yes, even ...
- What?
That I do not know. I think
I saw something out there.
- What?
- Whatever.
What are they
Drop guys here?
FBI agents.
Perhaps "Sad Mou" a spy.
- Do you?
- Not talking about.
After our little stunt,
my job is in jeopardy.
- I'll stay here.
- You are a coward.
- Okay.
- Did you know?
- You are late, McNeill.
- Yes, I know.
- It's the third time this week.
- It is enough, Dick.
Get some pills, ik!
What a mess.
Is that your official opinion?
It is a propeller.
It is the only explanation
on such a large wound.
It looks like the same type of injury
we were on the other whale.
- What did I miss?
- A promotion!.
Poor animals.
Hey, can I borrow it?
- Strange. He ever seen it?
- What's on?
The damage of this wound
does not come from something mechanical.
This wound is organic.
Organic, crosses.
Do you know how it sounds, Emma?
Mention one thing in the sea
can do this.
I stole not Dawry,
I borrowed it.
There is damage to
half a million dollars.
The Board is furious.
There were over 50 of them
and they went berserk.
- Whales are not behaving itself.
- You of course.
You are in places
where you should not have!
Yes, and thank God I was so.
Otherwise, we had not discovered
effect of ...
Shut up!
Listen to me!.
I am at risk.
I suggest that you go home
and think about what you have done.
- There is a meeting tomorrow morning.
- You know I'm right, Dick!
There is something big out there.
Something very big.
Perhaps I should gather
some samples.
Pak!. We already have the answer!.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just allergic
against the men in suits.
- Yes, I am too.
- What happened?
Nothing.
Let's have a drink.
It irritates me.
It's just about Dawry.
- About the damage.
- Fuck them.
They are only interested in money.
- They can not see what is happening
- Of course not.
They are not a
mermaid like you.
Yes, but this mermaid
being fired.
- They will not decide anything tonight.
- No, they will fire me tomorrow.
- So it gives me very little time.
- For what?
It is the same face,
as when we stole the submarine.
Borrowed.
Hello, I came here
to see the body.
Nobody has given me
about this.
Typical! I was also
at home and then television.
We should get the payment
for these guards, right?
That, I agree!
Thank you.
Just hurry,
with whatever you're doing.
The boys will move it
on the high seas in the evening.
You know, before it explodes.
Mr. Orry, I'm Dr. Shimada
from the oceanic Institute.
- I am here to ...
- Liar!.
- Who is lying?
- All.
They say that it was
a design error.
I saw it on TV,
before they arrested me.
I know.
They say that all were killed!
No survivors.
How the hell can they say what
when I sit right here?
- Do not worry.
- Quiet?
My family think I'm dead
and I can not call them.
We'll contact your family soon.
But you must
to cooperate with us.
These people can be unpleasant,
if they do not get their way.
Believe me, I know.
Are you not for them?
As I said,
I am a scientist.
And you have seen
I would like to talk to you about.
I saw it.
I saw its eyes.
How they looked?
Please show me that.
Take your back, sir.
Right up your seat, miss.
Right up your seat, sir.
Change your seat up.
Please sit down.
It's just turbulence.
- We need to marry for 2 days.
- You'll handle it.
This is the captain.
Fasten your seatbelts.
Holy shit!
- Emma, wait.
- You are not my boss more, Dick.
Emma, you're a good employee,
you just need a little discipline.
- Want some advice?
- No.
Love is not the ocean too much
it will not be returned.
Professor Sanders?
Emma McNeill!
- When we last seen?
- For 5 years ago.
5 years. It is too long to
be away from my favorite pupil.
What is wrong with the teacher.
You got me away from the gutter.
So it makes us almost to the family.
- It's all a bit messy at the moment.
- Tell me everything.
Are you sure you're okay?
You look tired.
I have just been
fired from the Foundation.
And I am sure,
that no shadows me.
- Who?
- FBI.
Bloody FBI.
Du hunter you until you bleed.
Do not worry, Emma.
I will not let
them touch you.
I see you have taken
laboratory with you.
Is there anything you want
I should look at?
Funny you should ask.
You stole it
from the scene?
Work calls.
- A tooth?
- It has a big smile.
Very big!
- 11
- Inches? Oh God!
- Feet.
- Feet?
Crazy.
Who do you think it belongs?
That I do not know.
You are past palæontolog.
I would say the strains
from a very old guy.
A dinosaur?
You must be crazy.
- Why are you unsure?
- Did not I always taught you ...
Good to doubt,
but better to investigate.
Yes, I am proud of it.
Say hello to Megalodon.
It means "Big teeth."
Lived for 8 million years ago
and was the largest røvdyr in his time.
- The extinct order ..
- 1.5 million years ago.
The biggest fish
ever existed.
And possibly the largest shark,
who have ever lived.
Previous studies
have shown --
- That Megalodon ate larger animals
including whales.
Are you trying to tell me that a
extinct prehistoric shark --
- Ate my whale?
Clearly not extinct.
- It is impossible.
- Are you sure?
I can not turn on the TV
without hearing about --
- Unexplained
disasters at sea.
But inexplicably does not
re prehistoric monster.
Why not? Observations
of havmonstre --
- Has existed for many years.
- I have written articles about it.
- It has never told me.
Students may be
a bit skeptical.
I was fired from the FBI, could not
risk was fired from the university.
And besides it would
no, believe me.
Yes?
Dr. Shimada, nice final
to hear your voice.
Dr. Shimada, I have heard everything
wild about your diving adventure.
They are amazing.
To steal a nuclear submarine
so it does not hit a dolphin --
- I would say
is more than game.
Indeed, it was a youth.
So you were thrown out
of the fleet.
May I introduce my
former pupil, Emma McNeill.
Brilliant havfotograf and pilot.
Miss, a pleasure
to meet you.
Should we?
I was surprised when I heard
that your government needs help.
Well, technically Dr. Sanders ...
- Lamar.
- So, Lamar.
Technically speaking, it is not my government,
who have asked for help.
- It's me.
- This makes it only better.
Diplomatic seen
I am not here.
Despite many reports no
appears with the root cause.
This is probably
lack of physical evidence --
- Or pictures or anything else.
And if there was evidence
they would not come forward.
The government would hide them
To avoid panic.
They are afraid. They are not ready
to a catastrophe of enormous scope.
And when they realize the situation
gravity will be too late.
That is exactly why I came --
- So we can determine what we are facing
and what we can do about it.
It was not what I expected
not from the attack characterization.
How accurate are your attack look like?
The injuries we can not be compared
with a Megalodons physiology.
However, I got talking to one of
the only survivors of the attack --
- Before my government took him away.
Look at these sketches.
Note the eye.
Enormously with a large vertical pupil.
I agree. It is not
one eye from a shark.
No, it looks like more ...
It is for you.
For me?
Who knows, I am here?
It has no sender.
The mini-submarine's camera.
- Vince must have delivered it.
- Who?
My friend Vince was present
when it happened.
Given what happened?
Oh God! Thought it was a nightmare!
Definitely a shark.
A Megalodon.
And its friend ...
The same as in the diagram.
- The expected ...
- What. A giant squid?
- Octopus.
- Chips?
- I am on diet.
Wise to deliver video to you
instead of to the authorities.
He knew I went to you.
I spoke often about you.
One thing is certain
now we have half the equation.
The photographic evidence.
A good starting point
as possible to give an answer.
Amazing.
Two prehistoric creatures
is mysteriously --
- Released in this world.
Maybe not so mysterious.
All icebergs melt
because of the ozone layer.
Perhaps it is our fault.
We are at 1-5-0-6.
We are ready, sir.
We have not seen anything yet.
Give my president
personal word --
- To arrive we find the monster,
we send it to hell.
Shark! 1000 yards
and coming closer.
Ready for battle!
- Time to move forward!
- Start Operation Delta.
Start the Delta.
I repeat: Start the Delta.
500 yards and
comes ever closer!
The target is fixed.
Fire!
I repeat: Fire!
Stop no. Send the big monster
back to hell.
- The target disappeared, sir.
- The target is hit!
We can not
confirm yet, sir.
Washington dialing up
the target is hit.
But, sir?
The target is returned.
The resurrected.
No.
No!
Stand up sleeper snouts.
- Seiji, you will have coffee?
- Yes!
- Sugar?
- Yes.
Good morning.
What can I help you?
It is not a
particularly nice place, do you?
It has the same illumination
as in Guantanamo.
I am pretty sure.
See not so scared off Dr. Shimada.
You will not be sent to Mansanar.
No, Mansanar were Americans.
Very well, Miss McNeill.
I amazes me safely over,
why we disturbed your sleep.
Let me guess
our country needs us.
One point for Irish.
Actually I am amazed at the fact
why it took so long!
We exhausted all opportunities
before we called the reserve team.
Your plan did not work.
We are facing a threat --
- Which no one had imagine.
Like Hurricane Katrina.
Very good,
and fun, Dr. Shimada.
Do you know that your Japanese Government,
has given us full control over your destiny?
Your life in my hands.
Unless you want to
commit ritual suicide.
It is wrong.
And it comes from someone
whose career is in ruins.
Sleeping on your
previously learned sofa.
What now? Will i have some
money for rent?
- Hey!
- Do not worry!
You should be happy.
This country would like to hear
what you have to say.
For 20 years were
my ideas ignored --
- Why should it
have changed?
To be honest --
- In the losers
that everyone on line.
You said the shark --
- Since all spoke
of seismic disturbances.
- What you want from us?
- Solutions.
If we do not find a way
to stop it --
- Will Sharkzilla
dominate the oceans.
If you dominate the seas,
dominate your world.
I hope i is aware.
What? With many more
opportunities is that?
The red dots show where
Military ships have been attacked.
These show attacks on civilians.
Megalodon does not discriminate.
But yes, he is a
Fair killing machine.
And he is not alone.
- What the hell ...
- A squid.
- They were frozen together.
- But now 2 individuals.
Unless you believe that the shark
Téléport from place to place --
- I think you'll see it fits
Timeline of the disaster.
A giant squid.
It is crazy.
We have talked about
how we can contain them.
- Do not destroy them?
- No, we believe containment.
Yes, these monsters are a threat --
- But they represent also the main
scientific discovery of our time.
You can not just wipe.
And we want your words
that you do everything in your power --
- To catch these monsters.
Believe in it?
And what do I get?
You get our full support.
Professor Sanders and I
Both agree --
- To isolate them in areas --
- Where it is possible to
contain and catch them.
Could I?
Bay in San Francisco
and Tokyo --
- Are the best opportunities
in this scenario.
Look at it as a coral.
And how would we get them going
ideal for these places?
By sending
them an invitation?
- We are working on!
- Work quickly!
Naval intelligence indicates
that they will continue their attacks.
They are not
they kill only.
Then find a solution
as soon as possible!.
See here.
- Thank you.
- It was so little.
Do you?
It is not easy to work
where there are armed guards.
As far as I know it is not
new to you to be under pressure.
To sail a submarine at night
seems to be exciting.
Yes, I have always been
attracted by water.
- Has always felt myself a part of it.
- I have too.
No matter how large or
strong waves were.
- They never scared me.
- You scared even me.
Everyone in my family
were fishermen.
Lived on the water.
Were alive because of the water.
Everyone wanted me to
follow in their footsteps.
- Why did you not?
- Death was everywhere.
I saw a dolphin being caught,
when I was a child.
I could not liberate it.
The panic in its eyes.
Despair is.
That was it.
I never got over
"worm on the hook".
I would go for a walk.
You know a trip.
- You smell good.
- To do well.
Fragrances are a powerful thing.
They can form
basis for relations.
Scents can even explain --
- Why is chemistry
between any people.
- You say the most romantic thing.
- Really.
They say that physical attraction
literally based on the scents.
- What?
- Pheromones.
- Oh, my God do you think that ...
It means we can use
to attract them.
Yes!
- Emma is brilliant.
- I agree.
I've taught her,
everything she knows.
Before ordering
cake and balloons --
- Is there anyone who will tell me
what the hell is happening?
The smell!. Scent
biological effect.
Pheromones are the means
linking all species.
It is the source of procreation.
The ultimate magnet.
We use San Fransico's and
Tokyo's bay as bait --
- With pheromones from both monsters.
Shark and octopus captures
smell and are drawn to --
- And think ahead
a partner in them.
A tragic decision.
How are we sure
they bite the bait?
They have been
frozen for millions of years.
Would you not be horny?
These pheromones
released into the water --
- And attracts our friend
San Francisco's bay.
We can use technology UAB
to place the feeding strategy --
- To lure them directly
into the trap.
And if I may ask
what is your case exactly?
You may well ask.
And may the people of
San Francisco to ask questions!
What they do not know ...
- If you need assistance please call.
- I will do.
Lucky for us, my
Government produced the substance --
- Is necessary
to catch squid.
- They had hidden it.
- But it is not destroyed.
And we've only just learned
to know each other.
I know. In this darkness,
you were my only light.
- I only hope ...
- If the fate will be our turn.
- Are you sure you want to clear you?
- Sure.
It is always best to fight on
one's own home which says.
Yes.
- I am waiting for you in Tokyo.
- Good luck.
Sayonara.
Well Julia, back to work.
Sparkling 7, this is Tango-Delta-9.
I have seen something.
1-7. The Tango-Delta-9.
We have seen something.
It could be the guys.
Shark or octopus?
Octopus.
It is hard to say.
They have almost the
same size.
The image disappears.
Tango-Delta reduce
delay your account.
Sir, we are flying in height 3-0, a lower
height could put the mission in jeopardy.
When you say put the mission in jeopardy
do you think yourself.
- But, sir ...
- Go down and keep an eye on the monster --
- Or I'll get your wings involved.
- Roger.
What is the point?
If he flies lower ...
Is it possible to make it work
as having been paid for.
Black Bird flying down to
height 6-5-0.
Understood.
See?
How low-flying the aircraft?
- Approximately 100 feet above the surface.
- Soft enough to take pictures.
- Stig!
- What?
Get him to grow now!
Mayday! Mayday!
I crash!
- Pin his last position.
- No!
Get ready to fire.
- Fire!
- Firing!. The missiles are on their way!
- The goal is gone, sir.
- Yes, along with the aircraft.
Now when we have placed the bait,
how long does it?
With the current rate
and speed --
- I would say he frames
The first goal of 5 hours.
- And where is it?
- It is located there.
Far from civil activity.
The place is like a big cave.
If you push it against the wall,
it has nowhere to go.
And what about delivery?
We put them
these guys must not destroy it.
You put me in a difficult situation.
Last time he was behind the helm,
he hit a sandbank.
A violation is
costing several million dollars.
At least, rescued
your submarine.
I get us into.
I just heard from Seiji.
Squid are on their way to Tokyo
and our sharks are on the way to do so.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, and you?
We have to be very
careful out there, Lassie.
I know.
We are entering into their world now.
Your backyard. They have the advantage.
It is strange, I have always
perceived me as an observer --
- A scientist
not a soldier.
Well, in a perfect world
it would be the case.
But every scientist faces
for something like this sooner or later --
- When to intervene,
for humanity's sake.
I am thinking of Einstein and Oppenheimer.
The extent of it. Devastation.
Yes, it is a great one.
But ta 'no mistake, Emma.
What we are doing here is necessary
and true.
I am just so happy,
you could be with me.
I do not know how I would
do it without you.
Of course you know it.
I am proud of you, Emma.
I have always been.
But never again,
yet I am now.
- Ready.
- Roger.
Heather makes clear.
On my signal.
3, 2, 1
Frakobel Heather.
Quietly.
How does it feel to be
behind the helm again?
Nervous?
We were sitting Megalodon.
Are you nervous?
I love it sgu!
- We are about 100 meters.
- Okay.
I take my arm.
- 50 meters.
- Roger.
In position.
Understood.
- Is on the starboard side.
- Roger.
Quiet now.
- Prepare for frigøring.
- Are ready!.
Okay.
Unlock it.
I said freeing it.
I know. I heard you.
- What are you doing?
- It stuck.
Stop the Christmas game
and release it!
Have you not heard of genius?
Armen stuck.
- Sir?
- What?
The goal came because the first two
and maintains the expected rate.
How long does it
before it reaches the bay?
Its speed has increased to
almost threefold.
In two, listen up!.
The shark will be with you
in about 5 minutes.
Find a way that frees it
or leave the submarine!
The submarine has no anchor. If we leave the
it can operate in a net fisherman.
Or enter the Bay.
To unlock it,
it had to be here.
Find out!
We run out of time!
I have always loved the dodgems!
- Quiet. You are destroying it.
- It will not happen.
The goal has increased the speed
to 500 knots, sir.
Jesus, he is quicker
than a jet.
Try to come out of here.
I try, we are stuck!
Expected arrival: 2 minutes.
Admiral Scott, expected arrival
about 2 minutes. Make you ready.
- Get us in position.
- Yes, sir.
Nemo!. I repeat: Nemo!
Drop the chain of command!.
When I give the order,
slider in order to kill!
We have lost his arm!
So what. Get away!
- The goal is within reach.
- Within reach, sir.
Wait for the order!
Hey!
Are you okay?
- Fire!
We are firing!
I repeat: we are firing!
Reports!
- Too much dust, sir.
- Impossible to see, sir.
- Fire again.
- Anything to see?
Still nothing new on the target.
The target is destroyed!
The goal is ruined!
I repeat: the goal is ruined!.
Who will have hajstøvler?
Sir, I get a signal.
Some orders, sir!
Sir!
- Oh, dear!
- Hold on!
Turn off the autopilot.
Turn left! Now!
Sir, the target is moving towards
Golden Gate Bridge.
Sir?
The goal is gone, sir.
It can not be seen on radar.
Call Shimada in Tokyo.
I sincerely hope that i had more
successful than we had here in Tokyo.
Shimada, what happens?
As can see, we've tricked
squid to the bay.
But our military has only
supposed to make it sour.
Like a rabid dog, the
more aggressive than ever.
- It's crazy.
- The change course, sir.
Wait a moment.
It seems that the monster flees.
Oh, my God, what have we done?
Tell me, had success
with the shark?
Very little I fear.
Sir, cephalopods is
disappeared from radar.
Then we have much more to watch.
Did Dr. Sanders
and Mrs.. McNeill it okay?
- Yes, we have it good.
- Yes, but the city is in ruins.
Thousands have died.
What the hell happened?
Watch your tone
or if you smoke in arresten!
She not going anywhere
and do you know!
Her idea is the only one who
could be used on this mission.
Seiji what happened?
We got problems. Bait
worked as you said Emma.
- But when he came to the Bay ...
- You are a failure.
Cephalopods were affected by
many shots, but no effect.
The same here.
It seems that our weapons
almost no effect.
- Conventional Weapons.
- What do you suggest?
Perhaps it is time
to use something more powerful.
- What nuclear weapons?
- Yes.
- I can not believe you are saying!
- I can not.
I can. It is a
Standard military solution.
There are many deaths,
on both sides of the globe.
And you want to add more?
Nuclear weapons may be our
only realistic solution.
And that is what
I would recommend to Washington --
- Before we have
a global disaster.
- Do you think he will really do it?
- He speaks with the Pentagon at the moment.
We can not allow
that this happens.
Efficacy of an underwater nuclear explosion
would be catastrophic.
The destruction of marine life;
unthinkable.
And the sea will be polluted
of radioactive fallout.
Potential damage to coastlines
and loss of life --
- Will be extremely high.
- And many tidal waves.
- We need to think of something fast.
I propose that we get some sleep,
and think about it.
We can not reach something,
so tired we are.
destruction of marine life;
unthinkable.
- Jesus! What?
- "Trilla in Manila".
- Say it again.
- We get them to kill each other.
That I do not care about.
Same battle as they were frozen in
for millions of years ago --
- Will be the battle as
kill them.
It is brilliant, Emma.
Just a moment.
Can I interrupt this for a moment?
How to propose in
we bring the two together?
We use the same pheromones
process which we used earlier.
It was the only
worked perfectly.
Okay.
Let's say they meet --
- How are we sure,
that they will fight to death?
It is in their nature.
They are natural enemies.
The fact that they were frozen
midst of battle, makes it clear.
Since isalderen came nearer
the animals were panicked and fled.
But not these two. They chose to be
and fight to death.
Only hatred stronger than
their instinct for survival --
- May have led to this.
Your hatred is our last chance.
Precisely. Physics laws take effect.
Both possess a force
as our military has not.
But do they spend their
forces on each other.
- Bang.
- They kill each other.
Secure. But we have a small problem.
What we see there?
No answer?
- Nothing.
- 1 point for you.
They move in silence
and low depth.
SR 75 spionflyvene
have no signal.
And if we get a signal --
- They move so quickly
that we can not detect them.
They are adjusting.
Uro. All marine life accelerates
under stress.
And they can increase their speed by up to
three times when they are tense.
Yes, we make them sure.
Yes, they make me and all
world leaders acidic.
They control the oceans completely.
All the boats are in port.
- I can not carry anything.
- There is only one solution.
Place the bait in the ocean
and room them.
They will continue where they left off.
Everything we do is to get them in the ring.
- What insurance?
- A place far from civilization.
A place where anything they can do
are harming each other.
I assume you have submarines
to patrol out there now.
Yes, all are in full alert.
The Japanese do the same.
So get us into a submarine with our
with pheromones, and get us out there.
The release of pheromones
is crucial.
It is important that the system
pumps every 15 minutes.
Understood.
The system works 100%.
Thank you captain.
You are a little green.
Going to sygelukafen?
No, the pills will work.
There are several buttons on it now.
- You used to sit behind the helm?
- Yes but it was in the past.
Well, from the old school.
The release of Dr. Sanders
pheromones works perfectly.
Brilliant.
I have some questions
about our current course.
Why?
Because the further north we sail,
Despite tougher is the sea.
You are surely not afraid
Sunday captain too?
You have to
forgive my old pupil.
But she can li '
to use his leisure to drown.
Latest position on the shark,
was to the north.
How do you know it will keep the price?
I know. Intuition.
It must be good to be so inaccurate,
reach you at work.
It frightens me,
but you start with what you know.
Instinct, followed by track
and a solution.
Hopefully.
- What kind of solution that we hope?
- A bloodbath.
Full speed ahead.
Everything seems to go according to plan.
We continue
to follow them north.
It seems that our friends
prefer the cold climate.
It looks like this.
Unusual, but none of them
has followed a certain pattern.
Yes but in a way or duck
it makes sense.
- What do you think?
They are programmed to
to cross each other.
The point,
random, or intended --
- Is what that creates
life and destruction.
The universe was created
of such an intersection point.
The events in our daily lives,
is also created by them.
- Or destroyed them.
- True.
Still, whatever
Ahead --
- I am pleased that our
paths have crossed each other.
Yes, it has been a pleasure.
Julio Cesar said: "In today's
end, which came on --
- But the battle will end.
- Also will the end be known.
But if we meet again,
why we should smile.
- But if not.
- Then there was this battle a success.
I need to talk
with navigator.
- I think much of the night.
- So do I.
Every time I get up.
- We talk to you later.
- Okay.
Every man on the bridge!
- Put it on medhør.
- Yes.
What happens?
- Sounds like Russian.
- They say they are being attacked.
Who is under attack?
I thought there were no ships out.
Captain, I have confirmed that
Petrox from a tanker has been hijacked --
- By the Finnish coast
three days ago.
Petrox would not pay ransom,
As the crew was killed.
They shout søuhyre.
It sounds to monster
got them up and running.
Captain, I suggest you
change course immediately.
If we are lucky, the rest
after his meal --
- And we could
overtake it.
Maybe we can get it to
to hunt us.
Hunt us?
Pin transmission.
We change course there.
- Ready for battle!
- Pirates?
They have been hit hard.
- What kind of monster did this?
- Impossible to say.
- Released in still the bait?
- Every 15 minutes as ordered.
- Good.
- And if he turns out?
So are we ready for him!
Maybe he escaped!
Shark!
- What the hell is happening?
- Shark attack.
He is just above us, Captain.
- Time to move forward!
- Roger. Time to move forward!
Callback Jack up.
Say they have to do torpedo are ready!
We have full speed on
Devil with the heels!
Jesus!
How in the liver to such an?
Torpedo 1 and 2 are ready, sir.
Get ready for firing!
Fire torpedo 1!
Fire torpedo 2!
Move!
Torpedo will stay on course.
Frames of 5, 4, 3, 2 ..
Torpedo are missed!
Oh, God!
He tails at us!
Wolf Pack Fleet is ready for service.
Good shot, boys
but is delayed.
Sorry boss.
We did what we could.
This is unacceptable.
This command must be reported!
This command saved your ass!
Should have timed it better!
Send another team torpedoes away.
Let's keep him at a distance.
I thought you would have him
to follow us.
I will. But I will not
have him so close!
Yes, sir.
- Sonar: Reports!
- Pack away, sir.
- What do you mean gone?
- All 5 ships.
Destruction of an octopus.
Squid?
How ...
See if you can get them.
All communication is dead, sir.
- Try one more time.
- Yes.
Captain, octopus approaching.
300 meters at the port.
- Time to move forward!
- Full speed ahead. Yes!
- Captain?
- Not now Dr.
Captain, I know these waters well.
There is a massive passage
15 miles away.
- Passage?
- I've been there.
It is risky, but we can
escape from them.
He is right. We do not slip away
from those in the high seas.
The goal we seek, 100 meters.
Enable nødturbo now!
But sir, it will
overheat ...
It was an order!
Enable nødturbo now!
Nødturboen is now activated.
Enabled.
If we do not have the speed of
we are dying here, guys.
Speed increases, sir.
The engine keeps.
- Roger.
- The speed increases, captain.
- Take us to the path he said!.
- Yes, Captain.
Dr. We have discovered some
disruption on our radar.
There are several intercepted signals
near the arctic circle.
That must be them.
There are many disorders,
it could be explosions.
Explosions?
My last message
shows only one submarine.
Only one.
Trying to communicate with the submarine.
I tried to make contact with
all ships. No response.
It is perhaps only
a communications error --
- Disorders due to depth,
or errors in the system itself.
- What about the submarine?
- It is impossible to say now.
We must be optimistic,
and help the survivors.
Navigator. Take their
rate. Leave.
We are approaching.
100 meters again.
- Should I reduce the speed, sir?
- Negative. Keep the current pace.
The goal is gone.
No traces of squid.
- Should we stay on course?
- Yes.
We have an estimate sir.
The width is less than 25 meters.
Sir, the target is returned
It seems to be the shark.
- How are we?
- 22.8 meters wide!
- Distance to target?
- 75 meters and comes closer.
- Captain?
- 20 meters.
Keep her calm now.
Captain?
- We do not!
- Quiet.
Captain, he ...
Quiet.
Reduce speed now!
- Improve speed now!
- We frames wall!
- Negative. You are insane!
- Will you kill us all?
- Drop your weapon!
10 meters again.
The aim is approaching continue.
- Drop your weapon!
- Go back!
Gåå back!
You are insane!
- The speed is restored.
- We are in favor.
Hold the hat and glasses!
- Isvæg straightforward.
- Turn right!
How many torpedoes
is left?
- Only 1
- Prepare torpedo 3
- Ready.
- Shoot!
You got it!
- Captain?
- Speak up!
The goal comes ever closer.
3, 2 ..
Captain, I pick up a lot
underwater disturbance.
Two animals.
Hard to say what they do.
It works.
They are together. They are struggling.
What happens?
Who has taken over!
It is impossible to say.
There are many sounds.
Sir, the targets are separated.
They just lick their wounds.
It is not over yet.
Captain, the animals were separated.
But is still active.
Can we not get away from here,
we need to see what happens?
- Take us periscopes height.
- Yes, sir.
Good work, sir.
Can you handle it?
It is like to ride, sir.
- Americans are still not equal.
- Are you sure?
There is nothing here, sir.
If the submarine has survived, it could
not have come this far.
- Are there any signals at all?
- No.
- Maybe it sunk.
- No, never!
There are intercepted
activities in the water.
To the north by
a passage.
Of course. That is where
we are going.
Are you crazy.
It is impossible to navigate there.
And the radar shows that
may have been an avalanche.
Or something else.
Changing course, Captain.
- Sir, both targets disappeared.
- What?
They were on screen for a
moment ago and now they are gone.
Perhaps the dead
of their injuries.
Dead?
It would be good.
Real communication?
Barely online.
Only short range.
See if you can get in cash
with the Japanese submarine.
Yes.
- I know these waters.
- How?
I have been together
some whales here.
- Captain, may I look?
- Yes.
Just when you think
there is no logic --
- Life is just a
random mess.
- Something hit us!
- We have multiple damage sites.
- Get us to the surface now!
- I try, but do not respond!
- Make clear the missiles!
- Yes, sir!
- With this speed, you'll kill us.
- Step down!
We need to come
to mini-submarine.
Get us up!
- I try.
- Get in!
Sir, it comes straight at us.
- Captain, we need a mini-submarine.
- Go! Move!
You can not beat it.
You have to leave the ship!
Move!
- Get away from here now!
- Back!
- Disconnect us now!
- Isolated.
Sir, it is just against us.
Fire torpedo s!
- There!
- Hang on!
- Emma, move up!
- We will not handle it!
Got you!
- What happened?
- MORE!
Oh God!
It is Seiji.
Yes!
Seiji. No!
What are you doing?
- I take there.
- To do what?
- To save my friend.
- You can not. You kill us all.
- Lamar.
- It's too late.
I knew they could not
stay away from each other.
It appears,
they finally finish it --
- As they began to
for millions of years ago.
Can anyone hear me?
- There are Shimada.
- There.
The Shimada.
Can anyone hear me?
- Emma!
- It was incredible.
You could have been,
slightly longer.
I am thinking, maybe I could
be a little longer.
What do you think?
Now there are several
great secrets --
- I could be as long
you want me to be.
I am not the type who
stands in the kitchen and cook food.
- I am a mermaid.
- My home is there.
The sea, like you.
Do you know that only 8% of the oceans
has been studied?
It sounds like a challenge.
Have you ever seen a herd of whales
swim to Mozart?
I think
I soon will.
- Emma! Seiji!
- Lamar!
Oh, no!
You have the facial expressions!.
- Well, I thought ...
- Oh no, teacher.
To find these monsters were
a unique event.
- What is it?
- A new unique event.
A volcano.
A type of volcanic life?
Protected?
- Where are they taken?
- In the North Sea.
- Are you ready?
- Oh, yes.
- And you?
- Let's go!