( Orchestral music playing )
( Distant chatter )
So how is this guy? Nice guy
or is he going to be trouble?
He's a real sweetheart, Manny.
Just like you.
( Sighs )
Man: Who the fuck are you, huh?
You got my clothes?
Where's my clothes, huh?
Where is this? Is this some kind of joke?
Don't keep that door locked.
You guys are lucky I didn't
break that door down.
Okay listen, I didn't do
anything to that girl.
That was my friend, it was
stupid and I didn't touch her.
So I don't know
why the fuck I'm here, okay?
Wherever the fuck here is.
Where... where am I?
Emilio Manrique, you are in
South Miami mental hospital
and I am here to help you out.
Mental hospital? I'm not crazy.
I'm not the...
will you keep me here forever
with the crazy people?
I'm not the one that's crazy, okay?
Don't look at me like that!
Because I'm fine!
Okay, I'm fine!
Look at me... I'm fine.
I'm not... I'm not crazy, okay?
And I'm a good person. You've got
to believe me, what I tell you,
- I'm fine!
- Go ahead.
- I've never felt better.
( Weeping )
That's it, go ahead.
I'm here to help.
Go ahead and let it all out.
Don't fucking tell me
to let it all out!
Because I will! I'll
fucking sacrifice it all.
Ahh!
( Indistinct screaming )
- Don't you... hey!
- Hold it.
Ah!
You motherfuckers!
Fuck you!
No!
- ( Music playing )
- Man: My name's Emilio.
This is where my story begins.
I was born and raised in Miami,
the city that's known
for its tropical beaches,
clear blue skies...
the playground
for the rich and famous.
You know, all that stuff
you see on TV.
Well, I'm not
from around there.
I'm from that part of Miami
that nobody even knows exists.
( Man singing )
♪ ever since I was a young'un ♪
♪ I been in these streets,
hustling ♪
♪ grindin' and bustin',
tryin' to make somethin' ♪
♪ started out with nothin',
now I gotta have it all ♪
♪ never made the team,
but every day I ball ♪
♪ from the bottom of the mat
to the day I get the call ♪
♪ followin' my dreams
till that mother... calls... ♪
( Laughing )
( Grunts )
Hey, be careful.
Don't break Beto's house.
Yeah, right, I'm a millionaire.
Nigga, you so broke you can't
even afford to pay attention.
Come on, serge.
Do I have to do it?
You lost, E.
You know the rules.
Damn, it's hot as hell
today, you know?
I need some water. I'm fuckin'
dehydrating over here.
That's 'cause
you're 50 lbs overweight.
- Hurry up, E. Let's do this.
- How does paper beat rock?
Am I the first person
to think about that?
I mean, scissors beats paper,
'cause you can just cut the paper.
But paper doesn't beat rock
'cause you can't cut a rock.
What you mean
you can't cut a rock?
Your mama be doing that
every night.
( Grunts )
E, if you're scared,
I'll do it.
I ain't scared of shit!
Then let's do this.
Almost ready, mi Amor.
Mama, you don't have to cook
me breakfast every morning.
Mi Amor, it's the most
important meal of the day.
Okay? I want to make sure that
you start your day off right.
You're not eating?
Sit down.
I know.
I don't eat breakfast.
- I don't have time.
- ( Shower running )
Yeah, did they turn the water
off in her apartment again?
( Sighs ) I don't know.
Mami, don't give her
any more money.
Mami, Mami, Mami, you know what
she's going to do with it.
Do you want more Platanos?
She doesn't appreciate a goddamn
thing you do for her or for Emilio.
Frank, God's last name
is not "damn."
I'm sorry.
I worry about Emilio.
I do too.
Oye, hey.
When you're done there,
can you give me a ride home?
- Okay. That looks really good.
- Sure.
Mi Vida, por favor, you're
getting the carpet all wet.
Why don't you go and dry
off in the bathroom?
Relax, Daisy.
It's just water.
It'll dry.
Okay okay!
Iesta bien!
God!
If it's not one thing,
it's the other!
If not, it's something else!
Imia!
It's just water!
My God!
( Sighs )
So can you take me home?
I got this job-interview thing.
I said sure.
Where's Emilio?
( Brakes squeal )
Woman: Oh my God, the
kid's in the road!
Man: Hold on, hold on, stay here.
Hold on.
- Oh my God!
- Stay here, stay here.
Hey, kid, are you okay?
( Grunting )
( Woman shouting ) Robert!
Shut up
or I'll crack your skull!
You're lucky to get jacked
by the Jack boys.
- ( Laughs )
- Robert!
Hey, little mama,
don't worry about Robert.
- What are you doing? Robert!
- He's gonna be fine.
- We're the Jack boys!
- You got a wallet?
Woman:
Let me out!
Damn, bro, it's dangerous to be carrying
this much money around with you.
- Robert!
- Hey hey, sit back.
- Let...
- Don't touch me.
I'm gonna hang on to this,
keep it safe for you.
A lot of thugs
in this neighborhood.
- He's gonna get the shit kicked out of him.
- Get off my car!
All right, Mr. white man.
Pleasure doing business with you.
All right, little mama. Keep it
nice and tight. I'll call you later.
- Ha ha!
- ( Distant siren wailing )
Robert!
Frank: You know, if you want,
you could stay with me
- for a couple of weeks.
- ( Laughs ) Frank, with you?
Please. You live
in a boxing gym.
Thanks, Pero no thank you.
Boxing is all about discipline.
Maybe he could use a little...
maybe he could what?
Become a boxer like you?
I don't think so. I'd rather him
flip burgers than become a boxer.
- Boxing is a waste of time.
- Okay okay okay, I understand.
( Sighs )
Besides, we can take care
of him just fine, all right?
"We"?
Excuse me?
- You just said we.
- Yeah.
Don't tell me tomas
is staying with you again.
No.
Well, he...
he just comes over
once in a while, all right?
We're trying
to work things out.
Lydia, do you realize what
you're doing to your son's life?
You're just jealous!
You are not his father, Frank.
Okay? You're just
an old, lonely man.
- That's what you are.
- Yeah yeah, I'm jealous.
You're jealous of what
me and tomas have. Yeah!
Yeah, I'm jealous.
You know what? You're crazy.
- Oh, I'm crazy?
- Yeah, you're crazy.
- I'm the crazy one.
- You're crazy. You're crazy.
Si, Loca. Yeah, don't forget
about what you did, okay?
Okay, you have
no right to judge me.
Mami, I'm sorry.
( Whispering )
It's okay.
( Mocking kissing ) Mami, mami.
- What about my ride?
- ( Door slams )
( Boys singing ) ♪ Jack boys,
Jack boys, what you gonna do? ♪
♪ what you gonna do
when we come for you? ♪
♪ oh, you know a lot
of folk got a dream ♪
- ♪ and you know that I am so very mean... ♪
- Y-yeah!
♪ Oh, you know
that I show my power ♪
♪ every day
and every fuckin' hour. ♪
Yeah yeah!
Beto: Hey, I think that
lady liked me, you know?
I could tell by the way
she was looking at me.
That was bad.
You see how I pulled up?
- Mm-hmm.
- He was so scared!
- Yeah.
- I could have took his girl too, right there...
- right in front of him.
- That's what I'm talkin' about.
Whoo hoo!
Wallet!
Yo, how much did we make?
"We"?
What you mean, we?
Nigga, you must be crazy.
I just bought all these beers.
And I'm the one that always
brings the weed and shit.
And I'm the one that makes sure
that nothing happens
to you little motherfuckers
while you out here.
Yo, E, it's all you, big dog.
Nah, I just need some water or something.
It's hot out here.
Hey, I'll take it.
What the hell is that?
This?
Take it...
Just in case anything
happened to you.
I'll show you.
You just push this lever
in and out
when you're ready
to stick someone.
- Trust me.
- All right, serge.
You bet.
What the fuck is this?
- You eating dog food now?
- ( Laughing )
Is that why your breath
always smell like shit?
Give me that fuckin' thing.
Yo, we got company.
I told you dirty Haitians,
don't you come around here.
- This is my bridge.
- Fuck you! We go wherever the fuck we wanna go.
Why don't you take your
fuckin' ass back to Haiti?
- I was born here, stupid ass.
- Who the fuck you callin' stupid ass?
You think we scared?
- ( Grunting )
- Fuck!
Do it, E!
Do it! Kill him!
( Stick clatters )
( Dog barking )
- Lydia: How was school?
- Emilio: Fine, mom.
- So do you have homework?
- No.
No? Wow. Emilio,
you never have homework.
- Man: Lydia?
- ¿Que?
( Man speaking Spanish )
( Both speaking Spanish )
Oh shit.
What are you looking at?
What are you, a little pervert?
Don't you believe in knocking?
( Speaks Spanish )
Stop it.
There's no water.
What do you mean,
there's no water?
Well, I paid the bill.
I sent it.
It must have gotten lost.
I'll call tomorrow.
Okay? ¿Esta bien?
What's wrong?
Huh?
¿que Paso...?
Shit!
You been fighting again,
Emilio?
Icono! What have I told
you about that, huh?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?! What happened?
- Nada. Nothing.
- ( Speaks Spanish )
I cannot afford another
emergency-room visit.
- ¿Me entiende?
- Oye, Lydia.
Okay, stop babying
the boy, okay?
What he needs is
a fucking ass-whipping.
- All right.
- ( Lydia speaks Spanish )
- I'm not talking to you.
- Don't fucking yell at me.
( Shouts in Spanish )
Go to the bathroom
and wash up, okay?
Can I go to grandma's?
You can go to Daisy's
manana, okay?
- Just stop it!
- Why do you call her Daisy and not mom?
Because she's a better
grandmother than she is a mom.
Okay.
Well, good night...
Lydia.
Good night.
- Tomas: Lydia!
- ¿Que?
Get your ass in here!
( Barking, whimpering )
Boy.
There you are, T.
Okay. No no, boy.
No, boy.
It's in there, okay?
Had enough, T?
( Sighs )
( Laughs )
You've got doggie breath.
( Distant music,
woman shouting )
( Glass breaks, footsteps )
( Coughing )
Psst, T, wake up.
Shh shh shh.
Quiet down, quiet down.
Shh. Stay here, boy.
I'll be right back.
Okay?
( Whimpering )
( Choking )
- ( Blow falls )
- Ahh!
( Lydia coughing )
( Breathing hard )
Ah!
Fuck you!
Ihijo de puta!
Oh God.
( Sobbing )
Get in the car.
I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry.
( Crying ) I love you,
mi hijo, and I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Tell me what happened.
Frank, they're not
taking my baby.
Give me a minute, please.
Emilio.
Uncle Frank.
Give me a hug.
- I need you to do me a favor.
- Okay.
- Can you go with this gentleman?
- Frank, don't you dare.
- Lydia, Lydia, Lydia...
- Frank! No! No!
- Lydia, Lydia.
- Lydia...
- No, you fuckin' piece of shit.
You're letting them
take my baby.
- Lydia!
- You're not his father.
You have no right!
Lydia, Lydia!
- ( All chattering )
- Step away from the wall.
Lydia: No no!
( Muffled shouting )
( Muffled )
Adult Emilio:
I'll never forget that night.
I completely lost myself.
I was just trying
to protect my mom.
The judge didn't believe me
and sentenced me
to seven months in jail.
I was convicted with a second-degree
assault with a deadly weapon.
Yep.
My mom lost custody.
That night
changed my whole life.
So how do you feel?
I feel like I can't breathe.
I feel like my heart
is going to explode.
I feel like I'm going
to swallow my fuckin' tongue.
I feel like thoughts are
going 1,000 Miles an hour.
How do I feel?
How do I...
I don't know, man.
Can you get
this thing off me, please?
( Laughs ) I can't.
I'll get fired.
But, uh, here you go.
Oh.
I knew your last name
sounded familiar.
You're Frank Manrique's
nephew, right?
Yeah.
He wanted me to give you this.
So are you a boxer too?
( Orchestral music playing )
Hey, kid, what the hell
are you doing?
You gotta be mopping.
Come on.
Again. You set?
( Talking continues )
Okay, I want you to...
hey, Emilio,
back to work, buddy.
Back to work.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- One more.
- Enough, come on.
Come on, come on,
let me catch my breath.
Let's go, let's go.
It's the last round.
It's the last round, T.
What you got?
Give me some more.
( Chains rattling )
Frank:
Whoo! Emilio!
Meet me at the ring, T.
Emilio!
What?
You're gonna burn yourself out.
Come on.
Mr. T's tired.
Let's go.
Burn myself out? You been telling
me that since I was a little kid.
True.
I feel good.
- I look good.
- All right.
- All right, all right.
- I feel good.
♪ I don't know
what you been told ♪
- ♪ Uncle Frank... ♪
- Nice and easy. Nice and easy.
You got a fight tonight.
Nice and easy.
Pace yourself.
That's right.
What time did you get in
this morning?
Around 5:00.
Couldn't sleep again?
Um, nah, man.
I just want to be ready.
I got energy. I want to be
ready for tonight, baby.
You'll never be ready, kid.
Oh, Ben, what's up, man?
When are you gonna
start promoting me?
Hey.
I cannot promote anybody
from jail.
I don't even have that pull.
( Both speaking Spanish )
- Hi.
- I'm Emilio.
- I'm Kristina.
- Kristina?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Ben: I heard you're
sleeping here now.
I'm saving money on gas.
You need some money.
No no no, I'm good.
I'm good.
Okay, Frankie.
Talk to me. What's up?
I need a favor.
Sure.
You're like my brother.
- It's about Emilio.
- No.
You just said that
I'm like your brother,
that just ask,
that whatever I need...
- no, I can't.
- Why not?
Because of that.
He just has a lot of energy.
He's unfocused. He's all over the place.
He's like a wild horse.
Is that why your fighters
are afraid of fighting him?
I am not going
to promote Emilio.
I'm not asking you
to promote him.
Then what?
( Exhaling )
You know what your problem is?
What's my problem
this time, Talia?
You need to stop copying
every boxer you know
and start making
your own style.
Look, if you're going
to do Ali's jab,
at least do it right, okay?
He would twist his wrists
as he would make contact.
Also you need to stop
leading with your head, okay?
You're not Arturo Gatti.
He had a jaw made of granite.
And you have a pretty face,
so try and protect it.
Anything else?
Not at the moment,
but I see some improvement.
Tell that to your pops.
Yeah, he's focused on Teddy.
Hey, Talia,
what are you doing here?
- Dad, I'm working.
- Working?
- Yeah.
- You need a ride home?
- No.
- All right.
Let's go shopping then, girl.
- Okay, so you got that?
- Yeah. Yeah.
So I was going to ask you,
what are you doing Friday night?
'Cause I... I, um...
I like your fa...
your fashion now.
It changes...
I knew it. Nope.
I didn't mean it.
( Sighs ) That was so dumb.
What?
What are you looking at?
Don't do all that. Don't look
at me all like that, okay?
I got game.
You know how I get.
Come... come on, T.
Manny: You mean the big black
guy with all the chains?
No no no,
Mr. T is my dog.
He's a pit bull.
I had him since I was a little kid.
He's like my best friend.
Damn, Manny,
I trust him with my life.
Why's that?
Because I can relate to him.
I hate how people
look down at pit bulls
just 'cause of the way
they look.
You know what I mean?
I hate that shit.
I want to start an organization
called peace for pit bulls,
like, whenever I start
getting money and shit.
You know, helping out pits.
And, uh, I just hate it
that every time someone looks
at a pit bull, they judge them.
You know what I mean?
( Laughs )
How do you think I feel?
You should start an
organization: Peace for Manny.
( Both laugh )
I try to keep a smile all day.
And by the end of the day,
my face hurts.
Sometimes it's hard
to smile, huh, Manny?
Oh, fuck.
Hey, Manny, I'm not feeling
so good right now again.
I'm feeling a little...
I'm feeling a little shaky.
What can I do for you?
Can we get a TV up in here
or something like that?
Anything to just
take my mind off this.
I can make that happen.
( Birds singing )
( Sighs )
It's not that easy.
You could just walk up
to any bitch and hump her.
It's not like that in real life...
you gotta wine and dine 'em.
And then when you go up
to a girl, what do you say?
You know, and then you
have to have pick-up lines.
T, are you listening?
This is human world.
Do you know what I mean?
You just don't walk up
to girls and pick...
hey.
Hi.
You come here often?
It's the bus stop.
Oh, yeah.
- Cute dog.
- Oh, yeah.
What's his name?
Mr. T.
He's my little brother.
Yeah, he's...
I'm... I'm...
I'm the fighter.
He's actually the lover.
He's cute.
( Laughs )
- I'm cute? Oh, he's cute!
- He's cute.
- Yeah.
Born and raised in Dade county.
( Laughs )
( Stammering ) You know the
difference between a dog and a wife?
If... if you lock up,
um, your dog
and your wife in a trunk
and you let 'em out
an hour later,
guess who's happy to see you?
- Is that the bus?
- Yeah.
Hey, there she is,
all bright-eyed and bushy-tailed,
ready to take on the world.
Morning, dad.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You've been like a busy bee lately.
What are you up to?
I... I've had a couple
of meetings lately.
You know, if I'm going
to be a female boxing promoter,
I've got to work twice as hard.
Benjamin, you said you were
taking me shopping today.
Okay, honey, go get ready.
I'd like to buy that dress
I've been telling you about.
It's awesome.
Can I, like, talk to my dad
for, like, one second?
Maybe, like someday?
I don't know.
Okay.
Talia: Dad, when are you
going to get rid of her?
I don't know.
I like her.
What about you?
When are you going
to get rid of him?
Who?
Emilio.
- What?
- Are you banging him?
- Dad!
- Eh, it's all good.
He's a good-looking kid.
You know I don't
give you too much shit
about the guys you go out with.
Just don't keep him around
too long, that's all.
Have your fun and then move on.
I'm not interested
in him like that.
Then what?
That's what I want
to talk to you about.
I'm not going to promote him.
I know that.
So you had a meeting
with Frank.
Yes, I did.
Great.
What did he say?
He said you were going
to help him,
try to get Emilio
into golden gloves.
- Yeah.
- So what happened?
The boxing commissioner wants
nothing to do with him.
They say maybe next year.
So you're telling me
one of the most well-connected
boxing promoters in South
Florida couldn't get him in?
- Sweetie, stop stop stop.
- Come on.
Emilio is not my priority.
- I tried.
- Did you? Did you really?
Because, I don't know, I feel
like maybe you're scared
that if Emilio qualifies,
he's going to take
the spotlight away from Teddy.
Are you comparing Teddy
now with Emilio?
I don't feel safe having that kid
in the same ring with Teddy.
He will kill him.
I guess we're just going
to have to find out.
Because I'm promoting Emilio and I'm
getting him into golden gloves.
Love you.
( Man on TV speaking Spanish )
( TV continues playing )
Can I ask you something,
grandma?
Of course.
( Speaks Spanish )
Do you think God exists?
Of course I do.
How do you know?
He gave me you.
God gave me you.
Huh?
( Cellphone vibrating )
What?
Lydia: Oh my God, you sound
like such a grown man.
Finally!
You haven't called.
I've been busy.
I gotta go.
Call me later
or something, okay?
Oh, okay.
I miss you, mi Amor.
That's all.
I just want to see you.
I got a fight tonight, mom.
I don't want to...
you have a fight?
Can I come see you?
You want to come to my fight?
Yeah!
I want to come see you.
Okay.
All right.
You can come at 7:30. You
gotta be there early though.
I can... I can get you
a good seat if you come.
Okay.
Okay okay, perfect.
All right, so I'll see you
tonight at 7:30.
Okay, 7:30.
I'll be there.
I promise I'll be there.
I'll be the first one there.
- Okay.
- I love you.
Be nice to your mom.
Okay?
She's trying.
And nobody's perfect.
Mr. T is.
( Chuckles )
She says she's going
to come to my fight.
Good.
Muy bien.
So what do you want to eat?
Huh? I have congri,
tasajo, ropa vieja...
grandma, I have a fight tonight.
I can't eat.
- We go over this every time.
- You're too skinny.
- I can't eat.
You have to eat
before the fight.
All right, you just got
to come to my fight
then I'll eat
whatever you want.
Okay.
( Both laugh )
You got it.
( Crowd cheering )
Come on, Jimmy!
Kick his ass!
What the hell is wrong
with your brother?
The Spanish kid is pretty fast.
Fuck him. Come on, Jimmy.
Beat his ass.
Will you please
be quiet already?
Shut up before that old lady gets
her cane and beats your ass.
Come on, Jimmy!
Cocky little fucker, isn't he?
Damn, dude, your brother sucks.
He's getting his ass beat.
Thank you.
Shut up, lady.
Come on, Jimmy! Cut him
off like we talked about!
Come on, Jimmy!
Frank: Stay on him, stay
on him, stay on him!
That's it,
that's it, that's it.
Stay on him!
Get back on him!
( Bell dings )
( Crowd cheering, shouting )
All right, you made your point.
( Spits ) This is the
guy Benjamin said
was supposed to knock me
out in the first round?
- Fight's not over.
- I know, I know.
Just trying to put on
a good show, you know?
- All right, Emilio?
- Yeah.
- You need to pay attention.
- I got you.
Listen... Emilio?
- Emilio? Emilio?
- Yeah?
The fight's not out there.
It's in here.
- All right.
- You need to focus.
This guy's gonna be
looking for a knockout.
I need you to keep
your hands up, all right?
- Yeah. You got it.
- Keep your hands up.
- What did I just say?
- You said win the fight!
- Win the fight, win the fight.
- I said keep...
let's go! You got it.
( All cheering )
( Bell dings )
Frank: That's it,
that's it, that's it.
Yeah.
( Crowd cheering )
Come on, Jimmy!
Man:
That was a good fight, man.
Not really, dude.
Whatever.
I really don't care.
All good.
Damn.
Those are some nice shoes, man.
How much you pay for those?
I don't know, dude.
My sponsors pay for everything
for me and my brother.
Sponsors?
Well, I'll catch you later.
All right.
Hey, what happened?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you stick to the
game plan we talked about?
- Dude, I tried.
- Don't call me dude.
Hey, good fight.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'm Teddy.
I'm Jimmy's bigger,
faster, stronger brother.
( Laughs )
Okay.
I'm... I'm Emilio.
Yeah.
It was a good fight.
No.
No, it wasn't.
Yo, back up, man.
- Hey!
- Bro, bro, come on.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go home. Come on.
Grandma, we're playing around.
Come on.
Sinverguenza.
( Muttering Spanish )
( Doorbell ringing )
What?
( Laughs ) I brought you these.
I'm allergic
to flowers, remember?
Oh yeah, that's right.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't make it
to your fight last night.
I really tried.
I'm sure you did.
I did, papito.
I tried.
Can I come in?
You can you give these
to your grandma.
Where is she?
Where do you think she's at?
Working.
Yeah, working.
She got two jobs.
Doctor says she can't do it,
but you know how she is...
- hard-headed.
- Mmm.
Runs in the family.
( Sighs ) Yeah.
I've been doing really good.
I'm not drinking...
That much.
You know, when I get nervous,
I have a beer.
( Laughs )
But... oh yeah,
I... I got a job.
- You got a job?
- Yeah.
I had one.
I got fired
for being late 30 minutes.
The guy was really stupid.
It wasn't even my fault.
( Speaks Spanish )
Wow.
It's never your fault.
How is it ever your fault?
It's always somebody else.
You know that?
You know you can't hold a job
for more than two months.
You're 40 years old.
What do you want from me?
( Laughs )
Great to see you too.
- Don't do all that.
- No no no no! It's fine.
It's fine.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry that I am not
perfect like your grandmother.
There we go.
You're gonna start that?
Like your tito...
like your perfect Uncle.
I'm not going
to bother you anymore, okay?
- Good.
- No no, I'm not.
I'm not going
to bother you anymore.
But you know what?
No matter how much you hate me,
I am still your mother.
( Shouting Spanish )
( Sighs )
( Grunts )
- ( Doorbell rings )
- What?!
Oh!
Wo... wow.
Is that the way everybody answers
their door in your neighborhood?
No, I thought
you were someone...
I thought you were
somebody else.
Yeah. Who was that woman
that just came out of here?
Uh, it was a jehovah witness.
Oh.
- So you...
- I wanted to...
- sorry, you go first.
- Um... okay, I just...
I wanted to know if you wanted
to hang out or something.
Okay.
I mean, 'cause I was
bored and I thought...
oh no, I'm... I'm always bored.
You know.
My Uncle said that
I can't go to the boxing gym,
'cause he's going to beat me
with a broomstick.
You know, I'm down to do
whatever you want to do.
Whatever I want to do?
Okay, go get ready.
All right. I'm gonna go put
on a condom real quick...
I'm... I'm gonna go
put on a shirt real quick.
I meant... I meant
to say shirt.
- You're crazy. You know that?
- Yeah.
Um, I'll meet you in the car.
I'll see you there.
Um, okay.
God. God.
Emilio:
What does this do?
Oh, that one just turns...
oh no, turn it off.
Okay, close that.
Why do you always carry
a backpack around?
Stop.
What about this one?
That one actually
warms your butt.
Yeah right.
Can you imagine if
they made a car that
could warm up your butt?
Oh my God, you're not kidding.
I know.
- I feel kind of violated.
- You should.
It's like a spaceship in here.
We should go to the moon.
You know, I was thinking something
a little bit more challenging.
This feels kind of weird.
What does?
Um, the whole heated car seat.
Oh, hold on...
okay here.
It actually cools
the whole seat down.
Feels good?
Yeah.
( Cellphone ringing )
Okay okay, I hear you.
I hear you.
Uh, hello?
- Hello?
- Frank: Mami, mami, oye,
how many times
you gonna say hello?
M'ijo, how are you?
Good good. Oye, I'm calling
you 'cause Emilio and I
are gonna go have dinner
to celebrate his win
and I want to know
if you want to come with us.
Uh, I would love to,
but I have to work
until late tonight.
Maybe next week
we can all go, eh?
I thought today
was your day off?
It is, at my other job.
What?
You got two jobs, mami?
Frankie, you know,
I don't want to talk
about this right now.
- I don't have the time to have an argument...
- ( Thumps )
Vieja, remember, the doctor
said that you shouldn't...
Frankie, I gotta go, okay?
Bye bye, I love you.
I love you too.
( Upbeat music playing )
Emilio:
So where are we going?
We are actually going shopping.
- Shopping?
- Yeah.
I want to get you
an outfit for tonight.
- Tonight?
- It's nothing.
It's just a small party
I put together.
Okay.
Trust me. You're going
to have fun, Emilio.
I'm having fun.
Okay.
( Vibrating )
( Instrumental music playing )
D.J.: Excellent, yes.
I'm D.J. Scottie C.
With dream team entertainment.
And I've just been informed
that our queen of the evening
has arrived.
So please put
your hands together
as she makes her way
on up to the stage...
the beautiful, the talented,
the absolutely lovely
and always timely
miss Talia Portillo.
( All applauding )
Hi, everybody. Thank you so
much for coming out here.
Most of you know me as
Benjamin Portillo's daughter,
the head
of Portillo promotions.
But tonight I'm happy
to announce the formation
of a new promotional
boxing company
headed by its first
female boxing promoter.
( Cheering )
Whoo!
Thank you.
Um, T promotions
is happy to announce
its first fighter...
Emilio Manrique.
Come on up here. Everybody
give him a round of applause.
Come on, everybody.
- Come on!
- Man: Emilio!
- Woman: Yeah!
- Man: Speech!
- Yeah!
- Man: Come on, Emilio.
( Whispers ) What are we doing?
You needed a boxing promoter,
so I got you one.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna promote you.
Yeah, I thought
that we were on a...
- what's...
- I have to go.
Wait, Emilio...
- ( all jeering )
- Man: Where are you going?
I'm sorry, everybody.
Emilio is a little bit shy.
Have fun. Enjoy. Thank you
so much for coming out here.
Scottie, keep it going.
Have fun!
No more of that awkward moment.
Let's dance, everybody.
( Music playing within )
Emilio, what's wrong?
You told me
this was a small party.
This is insane, okay?
What's going on?
It was supposed to be
a surprise, okay?
- I'm putting all my money on you.
- Oh, money!
Money... there it is.
Money?
This was about money?
'Cause I don't have any
and I can't pay you back.
Stop. I don't want you
to pay me back, okay?
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm not your dancing little monkey.
Okay? I'm not.
Go ahead, be straight up.
What do you want from me?
Nothing.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
before about the party.
I thought you would be excited.
I don't feel good
in these kind of places
with these kind of people.
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm just not used to it.
That's it.
Well, you're just going to have
to start getting used to it.
'Cause you're with
T promotions now.
( Music playing )
- Ready to dance?
- Mm-hmm.
You sure?
You been training?
Have I been training?
Are you sure about that?
Are you gonna be ready?
So who's your inspiration?
Do you fight
for the golden gloves?
I want to, yeah. I want to
fight for the golden gloves.
- How many days a week do you train?
- Where are you training?
Um, I train at Frank's boxing gym.
That's my Uncle.
Oh, Frank's! Yeah.
We're trying to get him
into golden gloves.
But you know what?
Let's not talk about business.
- Let's have fun.
- Okay.
- We'll go back you up.
- Oh, thank you.
Hey, looking good, you two.
Purple and purple
like a couple of bruises.
- How you doin'?
- Teddy.
Great to finally
get to meet you.
I saw you fight last year
at golden glove.
Thank you very much.
How you doin'?
You gonna take it again
this year or what?
Oh, definitely.
There's no competition.
- Cheers, guys.
- Good luck.
So, Talia,
you want to jump head first
into the boxing world
and this is who you're
banking your future on?
Teddy, what is your problem?
I don't like him
hanging around you
'cause I don't trust
the piece of shit, okay?
- Damn it...
- Hey hey hey!
- Talia: Stop! Emilio, stop.
- Sorry, Teddy.
Bobby, he didn't do anything.
No, stop.
Emilio, just wait for me
outside, please.
- You're such an asshole!
- ( Laughs )
And what are you doing here?
Where's my dad?
He went out of town
for a meeting.
I'm chaperone, making sure
Teddy stays out of trouble.
Who's going to make sure
he stays out of you?
- Huh?
- ( Teddy laughing )
I don't get you, Talia.
You didn't have to go
through all this trouble
if all you want to do if fuck a
piece of Miami street trash.
- ( Grunting )
- Shh shh shh.
Calm down. Shh. I'd be
careful if I were you.
I don't want to have to tell
my promoter that his daughter
just gave his future
meal ticket a fat lip.
Off you go.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
( Both speaking Spanish )
Manny:
Oh, man.
I... I watch a lot of this
with my grandma.
It's kind of awkward
when the girls get naked.
- ( Laughs ) Yeah.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Your grandma sounds cool.
My mom used to love these, man.
She'd watch them all the time.
( Man crying on TV )
My mom is kind of the opposite.
She's... she's the one
that should be up in here.
I think the reason why I'm
in here is 'cause of her.
You know, she... she has
these mood swings
and she can go from zero to 100.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. Well, you know, that's
most of the female population.
You know what I mean?
She's still... that's the one
that gave you life, man.
That's mom.
You know,
when we hold on to stuff
that we have nothing
to do with...
you know, it's like
you can't choose your parents.
You hold on to stuff, it
doesn't hurt anybody but you.
- It doesn't work.
- But, Manny,
it's still affecting me right now.
That's the issue.
- Oh yeah, no no, I understand.
- You know what I mean?
Yeah, I understand.
But it's kind of like,
"what can I do about it
right now?"
You know, hey, so you...
you just gotta, like,
take it with a grain of salt.
Move on.
Where were you last night?
You left me hanging.
- Last night?
- Yeah.
What happened last night?
Shit.
I forgot.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
This is for you.
What you got over here, man?
What you got? Ooh!
- Thank you.
- No no no.
Don't thank me.
I didn't get you that shit.
- Grandma?
- No.
- My mom?
- Don't make a big deal about it.
Just say thank you
when you see her.
Emilio:
You see, moments like this
makes me feel that I can
accomplish anything.
My dream has been to move to
California just like my Uncle did,
fight the best fighters
from all over the world.
These shoes make me feel
like I'm floating on the air.
They make me feel
stronger, faster.
I love my mom.
Or at least I try to.
I try to enjoy these times.
Lydia:
Is that you?
Hey! Aah!
( Speaking Spanish )
Ahhh!
Mi Amor, I missed you so much.
( Speaking Spanish )
Look at you.
Wow. Wow, let me see.
Let me see.
( Speaks Spanish )
My God.
Wow, baby, you're not
a baby anymore.
( Speaking Spanish )
Uh, yeah, is everything okay?
Sí, mira, everything's good.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Do I look good?
Okay, I'm gonna serve you.
Ahem. Ahem.
( Laughing )
( Speaking Spanish )
Your favorite.
I like the shoes you got me.
They look really good.
- Yeah?
- Showing them off to everyone.
That's awesome!
Que bueno.
I saved up for them.
I saw them, I'm like,
"those are for my baby."
I knew you were
going to love them.
( Phone ringing )
Hello?
Yes.
What?
Yes, that's... that's me.
What... okay.
Okay, what...
what room is she in?
What... what room?
4712. 47...
okay.
Okay, thank you.
( P.A. Announcements )
Excuse me, 4712?
Down the hall, on the left.
He said "left," right?
Yeah, I think so.
Woman: Let's go, guys.
We gotta go.
Yeah, definitely.
Yeah, I just had
a minor setback, so...
Sure. You know what?
Let me call you back.
Hi, I'm Angela.
I don't believe we've met.
- Frank.
- Nice to meet you, Frank.
You must be Emilio. Your grandmother
has told me an awful lot about you.
- You're the baseball player.
- Mom, who are these people?
You know what, guys? Go grab some
candy over there, would you?
I'll be right back. I'm sorry
we had to meet like this,
but she's going
to be just fine.
Frank:
What happened to her?
She fainted when she was
playing with the kids.
The doctor said she had
a slight heart attack.
- A what?
- A heart attack.
I heard you,
but I thought you said it was...
mom, Julian just punched me
in the arm.
- No, I didn't, liar.
- ( Cellphone ringing )
- Yes, you did!
- When is Daisy gonna be home?
Soon, honey.
Okay, we gotta go.
Can you have her contact me as
soon as she's feeling better?
Thanks.
Hello?
Hi there.
¿Mami?
Mmm.
Frankie.
- ¿Donde esta Emilio?
- He's right here.
- Did you eat something, hmm?
- Yeah.
Please don't worry about us.
We're fine.
Mmm.
Hey, you gotta
take care of yourself, okay?
We need you to get better.
( Whispers )
( Crying )
Emilio: You know how you
try and prepare yourself
for things like this?
Well, it never works.
I can't even imagine
living life without my grandma.
I thought she was
the strongest woman alive
till I saw her
on that hospital bed.
It made me so angry.
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't know who to blame.
When we get to the gym,
grab Mr. T
and take him
to your mom's house.
I want it to be nice and
peaceful when grandma gets home.
He's been eating all her pillows.
He's stressing me out.
Grab the bags.
All of 'em?
I guess that means yes.
Good stroke.
( Grunts )
What's the matter, baby boy?
Come on with it.
That's it.
One, two, three.
- Oh, that's...
- This is stupid. I'm good.
What the fuck is
the point of this, huh?
- What are you talking about?
- You know what I'm talking about.
You've been telling me
to bust my ass.
Every single year, he's been
telling me to bust my ass.
- "Do this, do that."
- Then quit.
I never said
it was going to be easy.
If you don't want to work for it,
there's nothing I can do about it.
Quit.
Go ahead, quit.
Okay.
"This year we're gonna go
to the golden gloves.
This year we're going
to go to the golden gloves."
Fuck that!
( Glass smashes )
I remember that. I fucked up a
guy over there the other day.
- ( Laughing )
- Remember that shit?
- That shit over there?
- Oh, fuck that.
Oh my God, dude.
I always forget
about that fuckin'...
what the fuck?
Hey, yo, you got a fuckin' death
wish or something, Nigga?
- Yeah, bitch.
- What? You mother...
- oh shit!
- Cono.
- Fuck, E!
- Look at this fuckin' guy.
- Oh, E, you got big as fuck.
- Fuck, man.
- What's up, man?
- God damn.
Hey, but don't fuckin'
get it twisted, bro.
I'll still knock your shit out.
You okay, bro?
What you been up to?
- Working with my Uncle and shit.
- Yeah, boxing bullshit?
Yeah, I thought you
were locked up, Nigga.
Shit, I was, bro.
But you know me, Nigga.
Out and free like a bird, bro.
Going to a party tonight,
that pinga.
Yo, you coming?
Take a sip, man.
Let's go, man.
Bro, easy Cuban girls.
Bro, let's go.
Talkin'? Walk. Go go, these
fucking girls are easy, man.
- Come on, man.
- Bro, even Beto's gonna fuckin' get laid, bro.
I always get laid. Yo, I fucked
Suzy right by that little tree.
Oh my God, the same
Suzy bullshit, bro.
That shit was over
fuckin' 10 years ago.
- I had her right there. What are you talkin' about?
- Open your eye, Nigga.
Brother is getting down with
these fuckin' Haitian Niggas.
Go, yo.
Watch... watch how...
( Speaks Spanish )
Watch...
oh, we got wasted!
- ( Music pounding )
- Serge: Chug chug chug.
Ahh!
Ahhh!
That's what
I'm talking about, baby.
Yo, finish that shit.
Come on now!
Come on, beto.
- Come on now, yeah!
- Drink it, drink it!
( Drunken singing )
- ( Music stops )
- Man: Esta Bien, esta Bien.
- ( Plastic cup clatters )
- Emilio: Chill the fuck out, Homie.
- What the fuck you doin', Nigga?
- Shut the fuck up.
( Music resumes )
Hey, dog, yo! Chill out, man.
Fuck, dog!
Serge: That's what I'm
talking about, baby...
fucking bitches
and getting high.
Here, take that shit.
- Yeah, I'll take this shit.
- Hit it, hit it. Hell yeah.
Hold it, hold it.
Yeah, dog, you're fuckin'
wasting your time
with that boxing bullshit, dog.
Hey, slow that shit down.
My Uncle's been trying...
fuck you
and fuck your Uncle, dog.
This is your fuckin'
family here.
Emilio, I just want
to tell you...
( crying ) I want to tell you
that I love you.
You're my family.
And you're my family.
And I will fuckin'...
I will fuckin' die for you.
I fuckin' don't care anymore.
Is this Nigga crying?
I don't cry.
I get high.
- Let me see that blunt, man.
- Serge: Hell yeah, beto.
That's what I'm talking
about, baby.
- We are back.
- I don't feel good right now, man.
Holy shit, dog.
Check that shit out.
What?
Oh shit.
Oh, that is some porno shit
right there, man.
Fuck that bitch hard.
That would be some gangster shit if we
fuckin' run the train on that bitch
right in front
of her fuckin' boyfriend.
Fuck yeah, man, I'll make that
bitch suck my fuckin' dick.
Hey, beto, you're drunk.
Sergio, let's ride, man.
- What, are you fucking scared?
- I ain't scared of shit, dog.
Yo, man, I'm down for whatever.
I don't give a fuck right now.
That's what's up, beto. We're about to
go fuckin' fuck that bitch nasty style.
- Serge, this is crazy.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Be the lookout, bitch.
- Serge.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Beto.
Beto.
Ique pinga, maricon!
- Ique pinga, chinga!
- What the fuck?
Beto...
you fucking chinga.
Huh?
¿huh, maricon?
Beto, fuck him up.
Come here, you fucking whore.
- No, don't! Stop it!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Stop it!
- Turn around.
- Woman: No!
- Shut the fuck up.
- No!
- You want a fuck in an alley?
- Huh?
- No, stop it! Jeffrey!
- No! Jeffrey!
Shut up, bitch.
You like that shit?
Huh?
- You fucking like that?
- ( Girl crying )
You scream one more time,
I'm gonna fuck you up.
Say something now,
you fuckin' stupid bitch.
Emilio?
Emilio, what the fuck, man?
Sergio? What the fuck
are you doin', bro?
- Emilio, man.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- No, we gotta get Emilio.
- Hey, fuck Emilio. Let's go.
We gotta get Emilio.
( Panting )
( Grunting, crying )
Manny!
( Knocking on door )
( Door opens )
Woman:
Hello? We're home.
- Mami.
- Ay, mi Amor.
- Mamita.
- ¿Como estas?
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Come on up.
You sit down and relax.
Okay okay.
What are you making?
Arroz con pollo?
Remember not to...
( Inhales )
- Overheat the sofrito...
- Si si.
This is what I got
to put up with.
Well, if you don't want her,
we'll keep her.
No no no, you kept her
for a week, okay?
Now she's all mine.
Okay. Well bye, Daisy.
Take care.
- Bye bye.
- Bye now.
Thank you.
I didn't know you could cook.
It's my specialty, vieja.
Are you hungry?
Yeah, I'm hungry after all
that food in the hospital.
It's so bad.
Ay dios...
Where's Emilio?
Frank?
Frankie?
What happened?
¿Que Paso?
Mami, Emilio tried
to commit suicide.
¿Que? No.
Mi Emilio, no.
- Mami, please.
- No. Where is he? Where is he?
- Tell me where he is right now.
- Mami.
He's at the South Miami
psychiatric hospital.
Take me there right now.
- Take me there right now.
- Mami, mami, we can't go.
We can't go. They're holding
him for 14 days, okay?
- We'll go get him on Friday.
- Ay, dios mío...
It's gonna be okay, mami.
Mami, it's going to be okay.
All right, so you want...
all right, how do we do...
paper, rock, scissors.
Okay, so you do it three?
Paper, rock, scissor.
Damn.
Oh, I got you.
- Hey, what's that? Bam!
- Oh!
Come on, man, you're a boxer.
You're a boxer
and you go for that?
That's a cheap shot, man.
My Uncle does
the same thing, Manny.
( Laughing )
Wait up, have you ever
wondered about this?
How does...
how does paper beat rock?
- You could just...
- Well, it covers it.
Paper covers it.
You know what I mean?
It's kind of like boxing.
You swarm over somebody.
You clinch them up,
they can't really hit you.
You told me
you used to box, right?
Yeah yeah, a long time.
Yeah.
- How was it?
- It was tough.
A tough way to make a living.
You know what I mean? But
sometimes that's all you got.
Doctor: Everybody
just take your seats.
Is the mother here?
We are his mother...
his family.
Okay, well,
thank you for coming.
It's important that everyone
who's close to Emilio
and part of his life
be part of his treatment.
Treatment?
Emilio has been diagnosed
with bipolar ii,
with suicidal ideation.
But the good news is
it's treatable.
And Emilio's a good kid.
He'll just need your love and
support to get through it.
Now I'm going to up
the dosage of lithium
and that'll help
control the mood swings.
And Manny here will
continue his counseling
and monitor his progress.
Him?
Si, senora.
( P.A. Beeps )
( Indistinct talking
over p.A. )
And just so you're aware,
bipolar ii is a disorder
that manifests itself
with periods of insomnia,
anxiety, high stress,
manic states.
Be very sure he doesn't miss any
of his scheduled medications.
And I'll keep an eye on him,
check back in with you
guys every 30 days.
Woman over p.A.: Mr. Portillo,
your 1:00 is here.
Grace, who's my 1:00?
A rep from T promotions?
They have a fighter
they want you to see.
I don'T know anyone from T promotions.
Send them away.
She's a female.
Is she attractive?
Yes.
Send her in.
Hello, Mr. Portillo.
I'm Talia Portillo.
I'm the president
of T promotions.
What can I do for you,
miss Portillo?
Well, I have the best boxer
in Miami Dade,
and I want him to fight
the golden gloves champion
in an exhibition to help raise
money for Frank's boxing gym.
Well, miss Portillo,
your proposition
is very interesting.
But we're not interested
in saving a fledgling boxing gym
or fighting a boxer
with suicidal tendencies.
I could have beat that guy
that fought Teddy, okay?
That doesn't matter.
Golden gloves
says he's the best
and now we're moving
to junior Olympics.
- I can't believe you're...
- The answer is no.
- You're not even letting me finish.
- Talia.
You are irritating me.
I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
There's no way Teddy
is going to fight Emilio.
So for now,
have a good day.
Frank:
Ah, there he is!
¿Que pasa?
It's great to have you here.
So how do you feel?
( Subdued ) Great.
What have you been up to?
Uh, sleeping.
Hey, you want to train?
Tio, where's, um...
where's... ( Kisses )
Where's Mr. T?
Oh, Mr. T?
Talia took him.
Why?
'Cause he wouldn't
stop crying since, you know,
and he ate my shoes. And he was
barking at the people in the gym.
Uh, you didn't tell him
anything, right? About...
nah, I didn't tell him.
I didn't tell him.
He also ate some
of my new equipment,
- so Talia came by and took him.
- Probably didn't feel good.
He did once he saw Talia.
I don't know,
but I think he's in love.
He might be trying
to steal your girl.
Well, she's not my girl.
That's not what I heard.
He said that if you don't
make your move fast,
he's gonna take her.
Ah!
Did I see a smile?
- Oh! Hey, T!
- Hey.
Hey, bud!
Hi!
( Making playful sounds )
Good boy!
Go over there.
- Hey.
- That's all I get? "Hey"?
Guys, let's...
You look good.
Yeah.
Where's my bag?
What's going on?
( Sighs )
Just, uh, packing up my stuff.
Why?
'Cause I'm done, okay?
You're quitting?
Yeah, I'm quitting. I'm quitting,
if that's what you want to call it.
I'm quitting.
Okay, what do you want to do?
I don't know.
I think I'm gonna get a job,
help my grandma out.
I'm tired of being broke.
What kind of job
do you want to get?
Something legit,
like a real job.
I was thinking like Wendy's
or burger king.
Burger king has a good
pension plan, so that's...
yeah no, yeah.
If those don't work out,
you could sell girl scout
cookies or something.
You could, like, wear the outfit,
like a beret and badges.
Do you want me to help you?
No.
No, I don't need
your help. I'm good.
I'm gonna take, um, Mr. T to my
mom's house for a couple days
so I can figure things out,
you know?
Do you need a ride?
No. I'm good.
I'm gonna walk.
I wanted to thank you
for taking care of Mr. T.
I just wanted to let you know
that I appreciate that.
Oh yeah, it was...
it was no problem.
Actually, he was the one
that was taking care of me.
He told me to tell you
that he knows things
are really tough right now,
but that they're going
to get better.
That was just something
that he said to me.
Okay well, come on, T.
Come on.
( Glasses clanging )
( Tomas speaking Spanish )
Un poquito de whiskey.
Just like old times.
Whoa. What...
wow.
Wait, don't tell me.
You're Emilio.
Wow, you're big, man.
Don'T tell me that's T.
Mr. T.
Wow, you both are big.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Where's my mom?
She went to the store
to get some groceries.
She'll be right back.
Get out.
What?
I'm sorry?
T, go to your room.
All right, all right,
listen listen,
I don't want any trouble, okay?
You don't have to come in here
and disrespect me, really.
You're a fucking piece of shit.
I want you to stay away
from my mom, you hear me?
All right, all right.
You know what?
Okay.
( Speaks Spanish )
I'm gonna be the big man
and I'm gonna walk away.
Smart move.
Just you remember something.
I was young then
and I wasn't perfect,
so I fucked up.
But you know what?
You fucked up too,
you little punk.
I don't give a fuck. If you
come anywhere near my mom
- and I will fucking kill you.
- You're gonna kill me?
- Oh my God!
- Wow, he's gonna kill me.
Tomas, he just came to say hi.
Yeah, I just came by to say hi.
- Keep your fucking mouth shut.
- No problem, chief.
No problem.
I'm gone.
Adios.
You're not staying for dinner?
No, he's leaving right now.
Lydia, it was nice to see you.
Um, I gotta go.
Okay.
Nice to see you too.
Hey hey, you don't still
have that little knife
- that you used...
- No, I don't have that little knife.
- I don't need it no more.
- Tomas!
Papi, I'm sorry.
He just came to say hi.
What does he do?
His mom is dying
- and his sister's in the hospital.
- I don't care.
- I don't... I don't.
- Okay.
I just want to know
if it's okay if Mr. T
can stay here
for a couple of days.
Of course.
Whatever you want.
I've been praying for you.
I'm just really glad
that you're okay.
Well, I'm very far
from being okay,
but we're going to keep T here.
I'll come back tomorrow and
everything is going to be okay.
Okay. Okay, no no,
I'll take care of him, okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
( Speaks Spanish ) Mi Vida.
Okay.
( Water splashing )
Dad?
( Panting ) Shit.
Oh fuck.
Talia, wait.
It's not what it...
listen, I'm sorry
you had to see that.
No, you're sorry
you got caught.
Talia, please.
Let her call daddy
and break his heart.
She won't do it.
Bitch, you think you mean
anything to him?
Benjamin worships me.
Your expiration date
is long past due.
Talia, hey, look at me.
I'll do anything.
( Ringing )
Hey, Ben, how you doin'?
Emilio:
I don't know what she did,
but she got me
a fight with Teddy.
Talk about bad timing.
I'm terrified of getting
inside that ring with Teddy.
All I could think about
was getting knocked out.
I had this feeling
that he was going to kill me.
My Uncle said
this is my moment.
It's either now or never.
( Orchestral music playing )
I know that.
I already know that.
Emilio:
I do that on purpose.
I'm a counterpuncher. That's what I do.
I let the guy
throw one punch and I throw
four or five right after it.
- I use it as bait.
- Teddy's different, okay?
He hits hard, maybe even
harder than you do.
So just try to keep
that pretty face pretty.
What... what is this?
Are you...
are you my girlfriend?
I just want to know
'cause I never had a girlfriend,
so I just want to know.
This is so corny.
Okay, look, just relax.
Calm down.
( Exhales )
I'm with you.
That's all you need to know.
Okay.
- No.
- Where are you going?
- No!
- Get back here, Emilio.
Stop.
Where are you going?
Talia: Do you want
me to wait for you?
No no, I'm good. I'm gonna
go see how T is doing
- and check up on my mom.
- Okay.
- Night.
- Good night.
Good night.
Really?
What? You have
a fight tomorrow.
( Laughs )
I had a good night though.
- I did too.
- Thank you.
Good night.
( Distant siren wailing )
- What happened?
- ( Lydia moaning )
Nada.
What happened to your face?
I, uh, I...
- tomas came. He...
- To...
no se.
He... he wanted money
and he went crazy.
And he hit me by accident.
And... and Mr. T...
- he wanted to protect me.
- What?
Mr. T wanted
to protect me, papi.
And he got in the way
and I'm sorry.
T?
- Lydia?
- Frank,
- I'm taking Mr. T to a hospital.
- What?
- Emilio's going to kill tomas.
- Slow down. What?
- I'm gonna call the cops.
- No no, don't call the cops. Let me handle it.
- I gotta go.
- Then why the hell did you call me for?
- Hurry up.
- Fuck!
You know we always
need ears to help us out.
Montes?
Hey, Frank.
What are you doing here?
Lydia called me.
Where's Emilio?
Hopefully training.
He's not here?
No.
Frank, is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
What happened?
Tomas finally got
what was coming to him.
There was an argument
over a dime bag.
Only this time he got stabbed
in the face and neck.
Frank, is everything
all right with Emilio?
Yeah, everything's great.
( Frank sighs )
Hey, champ.
What's going on?
( Groans )
Mr. T's going
to be okay.
He's a tough boy.
I went there to kill him.
But you didn't.
Right after I won the title,
I had everything...
money, fame.
On your grandmother's birthday,
we were going to take her
out to celebrate.
So I went by your mom's
house to pick her up.
And I see a bunch
of people standing outside.
And I hear her screaming.
So I rushed in.
And I find your mama
all bloodied up
and her boyfriend
just standing there.
And I went at him.
I started hitting him
and hitting him.
All my training,
all my dedication
went out the window.
I lost myself that night.
And everything I had
was taken away from me.
Look, I can't tell you
what to do.
But whatever you do
decide to do,
you do it for yourself.
You don't do it for your mom
or for your grandma
or even for me,
but for yourself.
You're gonna be okay.
( Crowd chattering )
( Overlapping conversations )
Hey, can you take this?
Where do you want me
to take it to?
Aren't you a coat check?
What's a coat check look like?
Well, just like you.
Emilio: You told me you
used to box, right, Manny?
- Manny: Yeah yeah, long time.
- How was it?
It was tough. It was a tough
way to make a living.
You know what I mean? But
sometimes that's all you got.
You know, boxing is a lot
like a chess game.
You've gotta be two
or three moves ahead.
'Cause any time
you throw a punch,
boom... here comes
the counterpunch.
You're gonna jab
with this punch, okay?
All right. And then I'm going
to slip that jab, right?
Now what? Now what?
Now they...
boom!
It's just bang bang!
And it's like...
it's a real quick punch.
But a lot of people can't do it
'cause it's a hard
punch to hit.
( Indistinct conversation )
Gentlemen.
I'm looking
for a good clean fight.
No hitting below the belt,
no hitting behind the head.
In case of a knockdown, you're
gonna go to your neutral corner
and wait
for further instructions.
Any questions?
Touch gloves,
come out fighting, gentlemen.
I'm gonna fuck you up.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
( Applauding )
Spit it out.
Now I want you to stop
moving around
and make him feel your power.
Okay? He's got nothing on you.
This guy's nothing.
He's got nobody.
Talia: The only thing he
has is that left hook.
That's it.
That's the only thing he's got.
- You've gotta counter that.
- That's how he does it.
He leaves himself open,
so nail the fuckin' guy.
- Come on, let's go. You can do it.
- You can do it.
( Bell dings )
Punk, I'm gonna nail ya.
( Crowd shouting, jeering )
Come on, ref!
Come on.
Get up! Get up, Emilio!
Get up right now.
( All shouting )
Come on, get up!
Get up.
You can do it.
Get up!
( Bell dings )
Emilio?
Emilio, look at me.
You've been working your
whole life for this moment.
This is it, right now.
I want you to take
all that pain,
all that hurt you got
inside of yourself,
and make him feel it.
Hey, you're a warrior.
Remember that.
Be calm.
Focus.
( Bell dings )
Frank:
Keep your hands up!
( Frank shouting )
Are you kidding me?
Ref, you didn't see that?
Get up, get up!
Ref:
...Three, four, five,
six, seven.
Take your time, Emilio.
Take your time.
( Crowd cheering )
Ref:
Ready? Fight.
( Muffled yelling )
( Yelling continues )
( All cheering )
( Soft music playing )
Daisy: Are they feeding
you over there?
Eh? Because you know
those people... they don't eat.
And when they eat then they throw
up after so they can stay skinny.
So you be careful.
You eat after you train
- and before you train, okay?
- Emilio: No, I ate already.
Maybe I can send you something
over the mail. Some food over the mail?
No, you can't...
you can't mail food.
They'll arrest you
over here. It's illegal.
Okay okay okay, here's
your Uncle Frankie, okay?
Okay, bye, mi Amor.
Bye bye.
Frank:
Hey champ!
How's training coming along?
Oye oye oye,
have you met any celebrities?
No no, I haven't met any celebrities yet.
( Laughs )
Well, I should be there
in a couple months,
so I'll be seeing you soon,
God willing.
Hey, I love you, man.
Call me.
Emilio: I'm so grateful for
the people I have in my life.
- Thank you for not giving up on me.
- Come on, T, come on!
I have no idea what to expect,
but for the first time
in my life,
I'm excited about the future.
( Instrumental music playing )