Sold to the gentleman
in the aisle for $25,000.
Thank you.
And now showing Lot 151,
another beautiful piece...
...from our Imperial Russian collection.
A very rare Fabergé ruby
and diamond-encrusted egg...
...given to the Empress Maria Alexandrovna
circa 1865.
Thirty seconds.
That job was a fucking joke.
They were begging us
to nick those diamonds.
What was with the countdown?
We had another two minutes.
The hotel stops serving breakfast at 11.
Look out.
Where are my diamonds?
I'm sorry, Mr. Groznyi.
It wasn't my fault.
Everything was going perfect.
This dog came...
That is not what I asked you.
Where are my diamonds?
Right.
Look, it was an accident.
We were driving along...
Do you or do you not
have my diamonds?
And if you mention a dog one more time,
I swear I will fucking kill you.
No. I don't have your diamonds.
Oh, Ritchie.
What are we going to do with you?
I help your mother get out of Russia
and start a new life in America.
I treat you like the family.
You, almost like a son.
No, no, this cannot be.
It was on the understanding
that I would get paid back in full.
That was 20 years ago
and still the bill has not been settled.
This job was for you
to square your family debt to me away.
I know, Mr. Groznyi, and I'm sorry.
I mean, I've never let you down.
So, uh...
...when's my flight back to L.A.?
Shut up about Los Angeles, Ritchie,
you're not going back to L.A.
I've decided to give you one more chance.
Open, please.
This priceless artifact...
...once belonged to the first czar of Russia,
Ivan IV.
And soon, thanks to you,
it will belong to me.
You see, the family who have it now,
they also own Eurals...
...which is probably the biggest...
...international multimedia company
in the world.
They live on the penthouse floor
of the company headquarters.
That is where the cross is.
I want that cross, Ritchie.
This job is very important to me,
you understand?
So don't fuck it up,
for your own sake. Okay?
I understand.
So good, it is agreed.
You will meet my men
and you'll be in and out...
...in one day.
That wasn't so bad.
- In and out of where?
- Moscow.
Hello, my name is Peter.
This is my brother, Yuri.
- Hey, how are you?
- Open the door. Open the door.
- I'm doing.
- Thanks.
You got that, didn't you?
Get down and shut the fuck up!
Yuri, Yuri, hurry up!
Yuri!
Hey, Ritchie, too easy, eh? Ha-ha-ha.
Fucking crybaby.
I cannot believe you are my brother.
Get him up.
Oh, ladies, ladies, please, this lift is full.
Get the next lift, please?
Did you not hear what I said?
This lift is full. Please take...
Take the next lift, please.
Am I still here? Am I still here?
Hello, can anybody see me?
- Leave it alone.
- No, no, no.
Ladies, please. Get off the fucking lift!
- Please, this way.
Thank you.
- No, no, no.
- That was lucky.
Where did everybody come from?
Please get the fuck out of the lift.
Please. Please.
Hey, it's you. You, you fucking old bitch.
- Hey, leave it alone, all right?
- You're...
- Oh, God.
- Blasphemy is a sin.
You've got a walkie-talkie.
Why don't you call someone?
Let them know
there's been a breakdown.
Attention all security.
A female member of staff has been killed
during a robbery on the penthouse.
Report to central security
on the ground floor.
- Hey, Yuri.
- Extreme caution is required.
- I repeat. They have killed once already.
- It's my brother, he's okay.
He killed...
Nobody fucking move!
Everybody stand still. Come on.
- Hey, just get them all out! Get them out!
- Okay, okay, everybody nice and easy.
Line up against the wall. And you, big guy.
Come on. Come on.
Stand there
and don't make a fucking squeak.
Who's the fucking big shot?
Anyone else?
Hey.
You run again and I'll hurt you.
Come on.
Drop it.
Stamp on it.
Fucking hell!
So if any of you fuckers
tries anything...
...I will stamp on your heads
until your brains come out of your nose!
Let me make this perfectly clear.
This is not Christmas,
I am not Santa Claus...
...but on the other hand, if you are
looking for a bloodbath, ha-ha-ha...
...then I am your man!
Get over there.
You took your time.
Did you see anyone else?
No, I didn't. This floor looks like
it's still under construction.
Just our luck, eh?
The fucking lift, it breaks down.
It didn't break down. Security's onto us.
Where's your brother?
Get out of the damned lift, Yuri!
Yuri, you gotta get up.
We can't stay here.
Yuri.
He didn't have to kill her.
Look, I'm not too happy about that
either, okay?
We gotta keep our heads
so we can get out.
You'll tell them I had nothing to do with it
if we get caught?
- We're not gonna get caught.
- Peter will blame me. He always does.
Let's just try to forget about him
right now.
Okay. Can I have my sandwich now?
What sandwich?
- I don't have any fucking sandwiches.
- I brought my own.
Just get up.
Yuri, don't stand there, you idiot,
you're one of...
We gotta get the hell away from here.
Come on, let's go.
Ah-ah-ah. I'll take that.
- Come on. Keep moving.
- Aah!
What the fuck you looking at?
No running away, okay?
All right, everybody just wait.
All right, everybody, in here. Come on.
Let's go.
Just sit down and shut up.
Let us get this straight.
You are saying that the security,
the building security stopped the lift?
We don't have time for this.
You wanna get out of here, move fast.
The cops will be here any minute.
No, no, no. Answer the question.
Did you or did you not say
that security stopped the lift?
Who else could it have been?
And it was your job to make sure
that the cameras were switched off.
What are you trying to say to me?
I am saying that if security stopped the lift,
it means that they saw us.
If they saw us, it means the cameras
were up and running.
If the cameras were up and running,
it means you fucked up!
I didn't fuck anything up.
The cameras were down.
- How did they know to stop the lift?
- I don't know. Maybe somebody saw us.
- Maybe we missed something.
- Yes, yes, yes, very convenient.
Maybe they heard the screaming
from the woman that you killed.
Why did you do it anyway?
That wasn't part of the goddamn plan.
So what? I changed the plan.
One less middle-aged bitch in this world.
Big wow.
- Where's Yuri?
- What?
Ah...
You are a fucking embarrassment.
Stay there. Hmm?
Officer
Bogdanovich, are you receiving me?
- Hey, give it to me.
- Ah-ah-ah.
- Peter.
- No, he isn't here...
...you fucking pig scum!
- Hey.
- Who is this?
- I am one of the men you are looking for.
And don't try any funny stuff.
We have hostages,
and if I see even one of you pigs...
...more bitches will get it
like the one upstairs.
- This is not Christmas. I am not Santa...
- That was my sandwich.
Yuri, Yuri, Yu...
Listen to me. You stay where you are
and nobody will get hurt.
- What happened to the other man?
Not the hair.
He's indisposed.
From now on, you're talking to me.
If you give up the hostages,
we will make a deal with you.
You think I'm an idiot?
I give you the hostages...
...and you'll come with a SWAT team.
Stay down. Stay down.
- No.
This is what we're gonna do.
I'll give you one hostage, you guarantee
not to make a move on the floor.
- Say you're sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- And you will not do it again.
- I promise. I promise, just get off.
- You'll leave the hostage at the elevator.
- Okay.
It was only a fucking sandwich, Yuri.
All right, enough.
If any of you fuckers touch him,
you're dead.
So okay, what's happening?
We're gonna give up a hostage.
It will buy us time to think.
Okay. Maybe we should do some work
on them first?
- Let them know we mean business.
- They know we're serious.
- You killed that woman, remember?
- Oh, yes.
Just talked to the police.
We're gonna let one of you go.
Who's it gonna be?
You, come on. Let's go.
Ritchie, Ritchie, let me take him.
Peter, you're just taking him
to the elevator, that's it.
Don't talk to him, don't touch him.
Deliver him and come right back.
Yes, I know. I know, but if I see pigs,
I shoot them, yes?
No. Don't shoot anybody, all right?
- Just drop him off and come straight back.
- Yes, I know.
If pigs come out the elevator and are
looking for trouble, I shoot them, yes?
You stay here, I'll take him.
No, no, no. It's okay. It's okay.
I've got him. I've got him.
Go.
Now you go.
But remember, if anything goes wrong,
you will be the first to die, hmm?
Press the fucking button, you idiot.
Lucky bastard.
You know, I was going to volunteer
before he did.
I swear to God, he was like
a split-second ahead of me.
They should have let me out first.
If there's anyone here more of a liability
than I am, I'd like to see it.
- I am this close to cracking.
- Why are you telling me this?
Are you trying to make me feel better?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sure it's going to be okay.
Try to relax.
- I'm Dmitry.
- Anna.
So, what do you do?
- I work for CKL.
- Oh, a secretary.
Junior vice president.
- I meant did you have secretary?
- I have two.
That is nice.
- Do you work here?
- No, I had a meeting with Eurals.
I am journalist.
You know those funny stories
at the end of the news?
Really? What channel?
- Well, it's mostly radio so far.
- What station?
Hospitals. Voluntary.
Those three were ahead of me.
Apparently, there is not enough
religious programs on television.
Continue with your prayers.
My name is Sonya. What's your name?
Yuri.
What's wrong, Yuri?
It's Peter. He stole my sandwich.
And he's always calling me
a fucking idiot.
He's the idiot, he can't even read.
Whose blood is that?
It wasn't me.
Peter killed her, but I'll get the blame.
- I don't want to go to prison.
- It's okay, Yuri. I believe you.
God knows it wasn't you.
But that woman, she died for a reason...
...in the same way that we've been
brought together for a reason.
If you let God into your life,
he will take away all your fears.
- Do you want to be free?
- Yes.
- Where's the rest of him, Peter?
- It is back there where we came in.
And don't fucking look at me like that.
I did not do it.
- Who did?
- It's obvious.
Fucking pigs. Ha.
- They must not have liked your demands.
- I didn't make any demands, all right?
Do you think I'm fucking stupid?
The police don't kill hostages, you idiot.
- Why? Why did you do it?
- Have you lost your mind?
Listen, I take him to the lift.
The doors open.
Big scissors. Head comes off. Here it is.
Hey... Hey, hey, hey. That is my gun.
You killed that woman upstairs
and now you turn up with a head.
You tell me the truth now.
Look at me. Eh? Look at my hands.
If I'd have cut his head off,
I would have been covered in blood.
If you cut one little nose off, trust me,
there is a hell of a mess.
Ask them. Ask them!
And then I want an apology
and my gun back.
You'll get your gun
when we make it out of here.
- Can you hear me? Hello.
Yes.
Sorry about what happened
to the man you sent. That was a mistake.
See? Huh. See?
What do you mean a mistake?
You cut his fucking head off.
I know, it was a tragedy.
Still, you do have other hostages,
don't you?
- Yeah.
- Send another one along.
This time a woman.
I'll give you 10 minutes.
So, what they say? Eh?
They want another hostage.
They want a woman.
- Well, you take her.
- No.
No. Nobody's taking anyone anywhere.
I wanna check something.
Don't do anything until I come back.
Sit here with my head.
Ah...
Hey. Ha-ha-ha.
- You calmed down?
- As if you care.
Fucking coward.
When are you going to let
the rest of us go?
I would not be in such a hurry to leave
if I was you.
- What do you mean?
- Why shouldn't we be in a hurry?
What is this? Fucking quiz show?
- What happened, happened.
- What happened?
Peter, we got a big problem.
- What did you do to him?
- What?
I'd like to volunteer as the next one
to get out.
Just shut up.
Everybody just shut up, okay?
- Hey, Ritchie, get a grip of yourself.
- Is he all right?
Okay, this is my fault.
You want to know what happened
to the young man.
The police, they picked him up.
His last words to me were,
"Tell all of my new friends. "
That's all of you.
"I will meet you in the bar
for a drink later. "
Peter, Peter, outside. Now.
Was it just me or did anyone else
see the head?
I've seen heads.
Christ.
I've seen hundreds of them.
Let me introduce myself.
Bogdanovich, Boris.
Serial number 881967.
Ex-Spetsnaz Special Forces.
Combat experience:
Afghanistan, Kosovo, Chechnya.
I am what psychologists would call
alpha male.
I know how these people think.
I am a trained killer myself.
- What?
- I'm a trained killer.
No, seriously, I am. Don't worry.
I know what I am talking about.
Combat Weekly?
I will get us all out of here.
- So this is what, a mummy?
- No, it is not a mummy.
The skin's practically still warm.
Oh.
- So who do you think did this?
- Whoever cut the kid's head off, obviously.
God only knows who we been
talking to, but it wasn't the police.
Listen. You hear anything?
There's no sirens.
In a normal hostage situation...
...the whole block would be packed
with emergency services.
It would sound like the Fourth of July
out there.
I don't think this robbery's
even been reported.
So according to you,
the police, the real police...
...they do not know we're here?
No. Maybe. I don't know.
What kind of floor is this anyway?
So things are looking up.
- Look at it, Peter.
- So?
Jesus Christ.
Okay, okay, okay. I understand...
...but things could be a lot worse.
If the police don't know we're here,
all we do is grab Yuri and leave.
- It's that simple, is it?
- What could go wrong? Ha-ha.
What are they going to do?
Are you ready for war?
Dmitry, they're harmless.
Anna, it's possible you have anything
we can use as weapon?
- You best keep hold of that for yourself.
- I will.
The only other thing we could use
is that.
That is enough.
In trained hands...
...a filing cabinet...
...can be more effective than a tank.
- What?
- Wait, Dmitry. Help me, beside door.
On two, up.
Up, Dmitry, up. Good.
Turn round. Turn round, comrade.
Be strong. Be strong.
Yes.
This is plan.
Anna, you bang the door:
Bang, bang, bang.
When they open the door, Dmitry and me,
we push filing cabinet on top of leader.
He goes down, we jump second man.
You, you take gun from leader.
If you want, kick him in head.
- This is suicide.
- Suicide?
It's better than being murdered, no?
- Yeah.
- The army taught me that.
Good luck.
No!
What are you doing, man?
You make a big mistake trying
to bite me, pal.
Now it's time to pay the price.
Aah...
That's it.
Don't, Peter, don't.
- Why not?
- Just don't.
What, Ritchie, you're animal lover?
- Get that thing away from me, all right?
- Ha-ha-ha.
Aah! Bastard.
Help.
- Yuri's in there.
Open the door!
- Help. Help us.
- Dmitry, don't worry. This is good plan.
We'll probably get away
with 50 percent casualties.
- Open the door.
- But there are three of us.
Help! Please!
Please help us! Help!
Let us out of here, please.
No more Mr. Nice Guy.
Yuri, Yuri, what is all that banging?
I thought you were being cut up.
- What the fuck are you up to?
- It was a trap.
They were going to push that on you
when you came in.
You, come here.
Yuri, take this. Change of plan.
We're leaving.
Goodbye, everybody. It's been fun.
- Come on.
Hey, we can't do this.
- What?
- We can't leave.
- Why the fuck not?
- You know why.
What do you care
about these fucking idiots?
What idiots?
We're gonna figure something out,
all right?
I'm a thief. I'm not a murderer.
- Listen, you stay, I'm going.
- Can I see that?
You're not going
until we figure this out.
- You going to stop me, Ritchie? Huh?
- Lf I have to, yeah.
Come on, come...
What the fuck are you looking at?
Fucking idiot, Yuri.
Drop it.
Katerina, get the gun.
Helena, get the bag and the shotgun.
Do not be afraid.
This is all part of the Almighty's plan.
- I'll call the police.
- Get back.
- The Almighty's in charge now.
- But...
- Get back in here, you whore.
- Okay, lady, listen...
Speak again
and I'll shoot you in the head.
Yuri, get that walkie-talkie.
Let us thank the Almighty
for delivering us from this evil.
On your knees.
YURl:
What was that?
That's what I was trying to tell...
Jesus Christ.
I told you to be quiet.
Let's go.
Try anything
and you will be slaughtered.
Can't believe this. Fucking Russia.
- Sonya.
- Do not be afraid.
- But it came from down there.
- Stay here.
Don't go.
You don't know what's down there.
I have no fear.
The Almighty will protect me.
I was really impressed with the way
you performed our operation.
Unlike some,
you acted with great courage.
If we make it out of here...
...I'd really like to take you for drink.
What?
No, I was just saying...
...if we don't all end up dead...
...maybe we could go for drink.
- As a group?
- Just you and me.
No.
No, don't.
From now on, I don't want nothing
to do with you, Dmitry.
- You... You deserter, you.
- I'm sorry, okay?
I was scared.
I know you'll think I'm not a real man
for saying this...
...but I don't like violence. I never have.
I can't say I understand you.
Fear, being frightened, afraidness...
...these words are not part
of Boris' vocabulary.
I am an alpha male,
but then I can't blame you.
I suppose I did spend 15 years in army.
It was the time of my life.
It's not like you journalists say,
that it's just bullying...
...cannibalism and homosexual rape.
The sense of camaraderie
is unbelievable.
Imagine being a part of the biggest family
in the whole world.
That's what being in the army was like.
I'm not ashamed to say that I loved every
single man in my regiment.
And why did you leave?
I was accused of bullying, cannibalism
and homosexual rape.
I did not do it, of course, Dmitry.
Them bastards in my regiment
set me up.
Not so tough now, are we?
What?
One more step and I'll break you in two.
He knows who's boss.
- What was making that noise?
- There is nothing to fear.
This is a sacred place.
I know what the Almighty
wants us to do.
- And that would be...?
- It's time to make a sacrifice.
Well...
...looks like we're all
in the same boat here.
And if we wanna make it out of here,
we better make a truce.
For what it's worth, it was never
part of the plan to take hostages.
- I'm sorry.
- We know what you did.
- Why did you cut his head off?
- I didn't cut anybody's head off.
Neither did he.
There's someone else here, guys, all right?
We're not alone here.
I don't know who it is, but he's the guy
who cut the kid's head off.
My advice is get good lawyer.
Because when the police come...
The police aren't coming.
The police don't even know we're here.
Frankly, I wish they did.
Now, whoever killed that kid,
he stopped the lift as well.
He pretended to be the police
so we'd send a hostage.
And, well, you know what happened.
You're a security guard, right?
- Yes.
- You've seen this floor before?
Who wants to be saved first?
What exactly do you mean
by being saved?
You, get up.
Mm-mm.
Katerina, get the chair.
Sit.
- Please. You don't have to do this.
- Yuri, tie him up.
Get away from the door.
There's only one of them.
She's scared, just talk to her.
Look, I don't know what's going on
but I just want to go home.
- Why don't you open the door?
- I can't.
Sonya told me to stay here
and not let you escape.
But you know I've not done
anything wrong.
This whole thing is a job for the police.
Let us out
and we can call them together.
But I'm just so scared.
I'm scared too,
but this can all be over soon.
Open the door.
You promise to call the police?
I promise.
Everything's going to be okay.
What?
You know how to use a shotgun?
Take it.
No.
The reason I've got it
is because I'm the only one who does.
I know how to use it.
Yeah. Come on.
Dmitry, don't move.
I get the ropes off you.
One, two...
Dmitry?
- What is it?
- There are no buttons.
What was that?
We can't call the lift.
There are no buttons.
We're stuck here? Jesus Christ.
If we can't call the lift...
...we're as good as dead.
- Just relax, relax.
I can still get us out of here.
I gotta get this panel off.
I'll short the system
and it will call the lift.
That's it. We're all going to die.
We're going to be hunted down like animals
and killed one by one.
I mean, think about it.
What if he's a sex criminal?
Dmitry, you are becoming hysterical.
I am now going to slap you.
That's enough.
Nobody's getting slapped.
We're all going to die
and he wants to slap me.
- That's not fair.
- Where are you going?
I'm gonna find a way to raise that thing
and get out of here.
You coming?
- Sonya?
- I didn't give you permission to speak.
I need to see Helena.
Room cleared and secured.
No, Katerina. Stay.
Helena, what happened?
- Answer me. What happened?
- I'm sorry. I was going to let them out.
Please.
- I'm sorry.
- Come.
Yuri. Aah...
Get away from the door.
Aah!
Come on.
He's been shot. We've got to leave him.
I haven't been shot, you idiot.
It's a cramp.
- I'll stay.
- To hell with you.
Boris, you have made fool of yourself.
Never leave man down.
I can't believe you forgot that.
Shh.
Do you have anything for a weapon?
I have a nail file.
Great.
Don't worry. Boris is back.
Shh. Shut up.
- No, no, no. I'm ready to fight.
- Point me in dire... Mm...
Just shut it.
Yeah. It's a dud. Shit.
- There's one round between us all.
- Where's Dmitry?
Can anybody hear me?
Greetings, comrade.
- Oh, thank God.
You have to get the police.
Various people are trying to kill me.
What is your handle?
Huh?
- I said, what is your handle?
- I don't have a handle.
- Oh, you've got to have handle.
- Mine is...
- I don't want to know your handle.
Just listen.
I got on this lift,
and you're probably thinking:
"Normal passengers.
Ground floor, please. " No.
Three of them had done a robbery
and the rest of us were hostages.
Things have changed since then.
Some of the hostages have taken over.
Yeah, they tried to sacrifice me.
Come back, robbers, all is forgiven.
And before I forget, there's also this
psycho, definite-sex-criminal nut job...
...running around
cutting people's heads off.
I haven't had the chance to talk to him yet,
but I'm sure I will later.
- Do you want to know what my handle is?
- What?
Didn't you hear a word I just said?
Oh, if you don't want to know,
I'll tell you anyway.
- My handle is "Ferret. "
- Oh...
Listen, you weirdo.
Just phone the police.
Hello?
Ferret?
Are you okay?
- Dmitry, where are your trousers?
- Where I left them.
That was me.
Just give me a second.
Anna, you look closely,
you see blood on hook.
I'm really glad you told me that.
Dmitry, you hungry?
Look at that.
Is that what I think it is?
Dmitry, give me hand, please.
"Chosen by God...
...first czar of all the Russias,
defender of the one true faith...
...and scourge of nonbelievers.
Ivan the Terrible. "
- And the Almighty can do anything?
- Yes. The Almighty is all-powerful.
- And he can't die?
- Yes, Yuri, the Almighty is immortal.
So that means he can't kill himself.
Because if he can't kill himself...
...then that means he's not all-powerful,
doesn't it?
- Why don't we go and ask him?
- Oh.
- I suppose we could.
- Yes. Let's do it now.
- You stay and pray.
- But I want to meet the Almighty too.
Be patient. Your time will come.
Bye-bye.
Look.
"This cross is a symbol
of Ivan's almighty power...
...and it will pass down
through the generations...
...until there comes a time
when he will be made flesh again...
...and save the souls of all.
That time has come. "
Hey.
Remind you of anyone?
Are you God?
No.
I am the devil!
Peter!
So let me get this straight.
That witch with the Bible
is related to a wannabe Ivan the Terrible?
- Yes.
- And they chop people up on this floor?
You saw the fridge, right?
They got a system here rigged above
and beyond what the normal security is.
I mean, they must control the elevators,
the cameras, everything.
- But how can they do this?
- Because they own the building.
- They're the ones I ripped off.
- What did you steal?
The cross.
Ha-ha-ha. That's perfect.
You stole a sacred relic from the insane
descendants of Ivan the Terrible.
Give me the bag.
Give me the bag, I make drop-off.
- What drop-off?
- It's simple.
I return the cross, they let us go.
Therefore, the bag.
Are you not hearing what we said?
They're psycho twins.
They're not gonna let any of us leave...
...with or without the cross.
- But I have negotiation skills.
Now give me the bag.
- It's beautiful.
- It's not the cross, you idiot.
Peter, you stupid bastard.
Bullshit. Bullshit. That's it.
Enough is enough is enough.
I'm bloody sick of it.
That fucker tried to put a 6-foot spear
through my scrotum...
...and that is not something
I'm gonna forget in a hurry.
Now come on, everybody.
- Let's go do the bastard!
- You are right, Dmitry.
It is time to make a stand and fight.
We are Russian.
That's it. Quickly.
Put him on the altar.
Not like that. The other way.
Almighty, accept this sacrifice
from your humble servant.
Forgive my younger brother's foolishness.
He knows not what he does.
What are you doing?
To think I was speaking to the Almighty
on your behalf!
You do too much speaking. I killed him.
I should be able to do whatever I like.
If it was not for me,
you would be nothing.
- But I skin...
- But nothing.
- Apologize now!
- But I...
Say you're sorry!
Sorry.
It doesn't matter anymore.
You ruined this one.
Get me another one.
So, Dmitry, you ever thought about
career in army?
I don't know. Is there an accelerated
promotion scheme for graduates?
Are we leaving?
- Yeah. I gotta get that cross.
- Ritchie...
Look. I'm not gonna argue with you
about it. I'm sorry.
Are you coming?
- It's better if we stick together.
- Me and Dmitry have our own plans.
Time to make our declaration of war.
And we shall start here with this room.
Good luck, guys.
Good luck, Anna.
Wait.
Just gotta figure out
which is the right way.
- Oh, it's not cramp, then.
- No.
Thanks for staying with me.
What was I going to do?
Run away with Boris?
Look, I'm sorry I got you involved
in all this.
Since I came back to Russia,
things haven't gone exactly to plan.
It's time for a new plan.
We stick together...
...we get out of here alive. Deal?
Deal.
- This way.
- No, it's that way.
No, we're going back
to where Peter was shot.
I know, that's why we should
go this way.
Are you sure?
I think that's doubling back around.
No, it's not.
Look, you've made enough
bad choices for one day.
Okay.
Ritchie.
- It's stuck.
- All right. Hold on. Hold on.
I can't pull it out.
That son of a bitch. Okay.
All right, it's gone through your ear
and it's opened up inside the wall.
I'm not gonna be able to pull it out.
What can we do?
Okay, everything's gonna be okay.
I'm not going anywhere,
but we can't stay here.
You're gonna need to move your head
as quick as you can.
- Get it over and done as fast as possible.
- What?
- Do you understand me?
- You want me to tear half my ear off?
- Oh, I can't.
- Yes, you can.
Try for me.
- I can't do it. I can't do it.
- Okay, fine. Shh, shh, shh.
All right. Hey. Hey. Hey. Relax.
Tell me about your favorite vacation.
- What?
- Talk to me, okay?
I don't know.
- I suppose it would have to be Sochi.
- Sochi, yeah?
- What's so good about that place?
- It's just really perfect.
- I'm sorry.
- Aah!
This will do.
We didn't have much time.
Considering everything, we did very well.
- Think it will work?
- Of course, Dmitry.
I mean...
Do you think so?
One hundred percent positive.
Me too.
Bastards!
We're never going to get out of here.
Nobody ever gets out of here.
Why should we be any different?
Because we're different now.
Because we're together, we're a team.
Come on, I need you to be as strong as
you already proved you were back there.
Look, Anna, you gotta trust me.
There's no way in hell
I'm letting either one of us die.
We made a deal
to get out of here alive, right?
I'm not in the business
of breaking my word.
Did your mama never tell you
to keep your room tidy?
I had him. Goddamn it.
Fuck.
He's been watching us the whole time.
Hold this.
Dmitry.
Come on.
Oh, no.
Boris?
Oh, fuck.
I should have been an accountant.
- My head.
- On your feet.
Can't you do this any faster?
Here we go.
Yes.
- What are we waiting for?
- Just give me one sec.
Now we get the cross
and get the hell out of here.
That's it. It's gone.
It's time to go.
- I can't.
- It's gone, Ritchie.
- It's time to go.
- I'm not leaving without it.
If you stay here, you're going to die.
And if I leave without the cross,
I'm dead anyway.
Anna, you gotta understand
there's people outside waiting for me.
If I don't give them what they want,
they're gonna kill me. I need that cross.
So, what now?
We go and we find it.
Come on.
Where the fuck
do you think you're going?
Get back in here now.
I said get the fuck back in here now!
Tie him up.
What's that for?
This will freeze the muscles on your face.
It'll make it easier to skin you.
I must warn you I have allergies.
No one will be spared
for the glory of the Almighty.
- This one's mine.
- No.
That's not the way we do it. I kill them.
I always kill them.
Stay where you are. I told you, he's mine.
Stay and watch if you want.
You can have the next one,
just let me kill him.
- No.
- But I did this for you.
- Please, let me kill him.
- I don't want that. You disgust me.
- Aah!
- Get out!
- But I want...
You are an animal! That is all you are.
I am the eldest. You do what I say.
Now go!
Ten seconds. That's all.
If I was born 10 seconds before you,
then I'd be in charge.
Well, you weren't, were you? I was.
Now get out!
Ooh!
- Sonya, what's going on?
- What?
- Do you know him?
- Oh, shut up.
You're fucking dead!
Get up. Get up.
Pussy. Get up!
You're fucking dead!
Shh.
- Huh...
- Shh.
Let's go.
Where is it?
You son of a bitch. If you weren't dead,
I'd fucking kill you myself.
- This isn't helping.
- Fucking stabbed me.
Jesus.
Ritchie, what are you doing down there?
I've been looking for that.
Where's Yuri?
- I said, where's Yuri?
- He's over there behind the curtain.
- What's he doing behind there?
- He's dead.
It's okay.
Ritchie, keep still.
Don't... Put pressure on this.
It's okay.
- Who did this?
Ivan the Terrible killed him.
- And where is he?
- I don't know. He just left.
Okay.
Where are you taking us?
You're lost, aren't you?
You realize you will die here,
you stupid im...
You.
Please, listen to me.
I don't know what's going on.
I was lonely
and she said she would help me...
...and I don't want to die here.
Please. Please.
Close the door.
There's a draft. Close the door.
Please.
Come back here
with my fucking hand, you bitch!
You bastards.
Spetsnaz.
I'm a reasonable man,
but this is getting out of hand.
I'm gonna get my cross...
...I'm gonna get the hell out of this damn
country, and I'm never coming back.
Where the hell are you?
I'm alpha male.
Alpha male. Alpha male.
Hey. Ha-ha-ha.
Over here. Come on.
Yes, I'm talking to you.
- You motherfucker!
Hey.
Give me the cross and I may let you live.
You cut my friend in half, bast...
- Come on. Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Come on. Come here. Come here.
Come on.
Oh...
Just wait. Just wait.
All right, give me a second.
- Aah! Jesus Christ.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, it's an electric shock.
Well, then.
Come on.
Come on. Yes.
It'll be here any second.
Die, bitch.
Tell me, what should I do?
No!
I'm going to kill you.
Boris Bogdanovich.
But please, don't call me B.B.
Are you okay?
You look terrible.
There is bodies all over the shop.
This is one sick bastard.
Wait, Ritchie.
- Mr. Groznyi, I have him.
- Bring him to me.
Come.
Ritchie.
Looking...
...shit.
Yeah.
Oh, Ritchie.
You have made me a very happy man.
Shake. We can be friends again. Shake.
What did you know about the people
we robbed anyway?
You tell me.
- You got one hell of a family, Mr. Groznyi.
- Ha.
I...
...haven't seen my family
for the last 20 years.
They make my life a misery
when I was growing up.
You have any idea what they've
been getting up to?
Who cares? You see, Ritchie,
I have now what I need.
So you don't know anything?
- No. Nothing.
- Nothing?
- Didn't know a thing? Okay.
- Nothing.
Forget it.
Your whole family's pretty fucked up,
Mr. Groznyi.
Hey, wait.
You actually have met my family?
Oh, yeah. I killed them.
Good boy.
Here.
Good boy. You take that beautiful girl,
you go on holiday.
When you relax, you come back, you give
me a call and you work for me again.
No. My debt's paid now.
That's it for me. I'm out.
Hey, Ritchie.
You are never out.
What now?
Do you think I'd like L.A.?