Subtitles riped by BuddyO 2007
>>
www.cesketitulky.com
Spike Lee Joint
www.spikeleedvd.com
On your mark!
Get set!
Go!
Grandma, Grandma, sick In bed
Called the doctor, the doctor said
Let's get the rhythm of her head
Let's get the rhythm of her hands
Let's get the rhythm of her feet
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Wow, look at that one!
- Look at it!
Red light, green light,
one, two, three.
You.
Top of the inning. Billy Bruton is up.
Home run. One-ten.
Home run! It's out of there,
out of the park!
One-ten.
Hey, Number Three!
Mister Number Three!
I told you, I run
a respectable rooming house over here.
You ain't paid your rent in two months.
What gives?
I pay, OK? No se apure. I pay.
No más. Bastal
That's a disgrace!
- Shut up!
- Come on, Troy the Boy.
Hit it, Troy the Boy.
You ain't hit nothin'.
Look at that. You hit air.
- I told you so.
- Lucky shot.
Dinner!
Oh, Daddy! Dang!
- Dang! Dang!
- Clinton, Wendell.
- Come on. And bring Joseph.
- come on, Dad, I'm...
I don't want to hear it. Let's go.
I'm tired of that Strat-o-Matic.
Bring your brother in.
- I'll beat you.
- I was in the lead.
He just hit a home run.
- These plates are heavy.
- This thing hurts.
Tell Clinton and Wendell
to come and eat.
Clinton, Wendell, time to eat!
I could have done that.
- Woody, that's enough sugar.
- Come on, everybody, let's eat.
Can I have a piece of lemon, Daddy?
- Can't I eat somethin' else?
- Won't get better.
- Black-eyed peas are nasty.
- Let's bow our heads.
- Take your elbows off the table.
- Clinton's in my chair.
- Clinton, let's go.
- Eat already.
- Food's getting cold.
- Be quiet, move.
- I'm not really hungry.
- Come on, Boogie.
- Food's getting cold.
- Be quiet!
All right, everybody,
let's bow our heads.
Lord, thank you for this food. Amen.
Heavenly Father... We thank thee
for the food we're about to receive
for the nourishment of our bodies,
for Christ's sake. Amen.
Amen.
- Pass the butter.
- Move over.
Shucks, now. Every time
we sit down to eat, there he goes.
I just want white meat
and a little more potatoes.
That's all he eats.
Eat vegetables.
- Stop biting your nails.
- My peas are touching my chicken.
Baby. Just move it over.
That looks so good.
Get out of here, you Possoms!
- Mashed potato!
- Lemonade!
- String beans.
- Look at that chicken!
- What's she doing?
- Troy the Boy!
- And stay out!
- They should eat their dinner.
That was rude, my girl.
Wendell! Please close your mouth
when you chew.
- Can I eat in peace?
- You're disturbing the peace.
You eat like a pig and chew like a cow.
Come on, it's a compliment
to your good cooking.
My butt. That boy is just plain greedy.
- I'm done.
- You didn't eat nothin'.
- I did. I ate three peas.
- Mom, I'm full too.
- May I please be excused?
- No, you may not.
You sit there until you eat
every pea on your plate.
When I come home,
I want this kitchen clean.
- See what you started?
- I hate black-eyed peas.
- Here we go.
- That's right.
There is no reason why your father and I
should have to clean up after you.
- Daddy likes to clean.
- Leave me out of this.
Your daddy may not mind, but I do.
I'm going to your father's gig
and the house better be cleaned.
I be godammned if I should do anything
after work but sleep and relax.
Ew!
Daddy!
Excuse me.
It's the dinner table!
We're trying to eat!
Excuse me!
Oh, brother,
there he goes again!
Tony Eyes can't even sing.
Not tonight!
_ If I ever find
that you've changed at any time
_ It's not unusual
to find that I'm In love with you
It's not unusual
Son of a bitch. Can't even enjoy my meal
without that funky faggot ruining it.
- Woodrow.
- It's true, Gem.
Put the salt down, Wendell,
before I pull your head off.
He got blowed up!
- See his hands?
- What are you laughing for?
He don't even know what's going on.
- They're gonna get him.
- They stopped him with the tank!
Troy.
Troy, what are you doing?
This isn't the bathroom,
get out of here.
That's disgusting.
You better clean that mess up, too.
Sorry.
Clinton. Have you lost your mind?
- What?
- I wanted the kitchen cleaned.
Get up, get up now. Come on.
It's four o'clock. Get up.
Get your butt in there.
Get in there
and do what I told you to do.
Hey, you, get up!
All you peanuts at attention,
before I... Now!
Hey, little one, everybody up!
Get your butt out of bed.
I'm sick of it.
I don't want to get up, Mommy!
Wendell! Don't play with me, boy.
Get up now.
Get your...
You'll get your butt up. Get up now!
What did I tell you to do?
What did I say?
- Get downstairs.
- Where's Daddy?
Your Daddy ain't here.
Get up. Come on.
- Can we do it in the morning?
- Up against the wall.
From now on, everybody's gonna start
pulling their weight, understand me?
- You're crazy.
- You make me crazy.
I'll slap the black off you.
This is no hotel.
I'll knock them teeth into tomorrow.
Get downstairs now.
Go. Get out of my face now.
Get out of my face right now.
- Do not wake your father.
- You're waking everybody up.
Shh! You know why I'm screaming,
don't you?
I am not crazy. You'll be crazy once
I beat your brains out of your head.
I'm crazy cos I got five of you
running me stark raving mad.
This ain't no plantation.
I'm not a slave.
And I tell you one damned thing,
I am not a plaything, understand me?
- What can I do?
- What I told you.
Clinton only washed one plate,
one fork and one knife.
- Heifer.
- Don't be a tattletale.
Don't call her a heifer.
You are gonna wash every fork,
plate, spoon, pot, pan,
our drawers and Mutley for a month.
- Wendell and Nate never do nothin'.
- I empty the garbage.
- Worry about your own shiftless self.
- I'm hungry.
Too bad, kitchen's closed.
Should have ate more than three peas.
- "I ate three peas!"
- Shut up.
Clinton, what kind of example
are you setting, being the oldest?
Can you hear me? You are so immature.
When you finish mashing peas, mop.
I'd rather have a father
than a mother any day.
- Yeah. Any day.
- What did you say?
What did you say?
He said, I'd rather
have a father than a mother.
Take your father. Take your father.
Let's see how your hungry asses eat.
I'm not playing. Come here.
Mornin', Ladybug. How are you today?
Fine.
How are you?
I'm good.
- Are you gonna eat some breakfast?
- No, thank you.
Troy, I was wondering,
Would you like to spend a few weeks
with Cousin Viola in Virginia
after school's out?
- They asked if you'd like to come.
- No, thank you.
- What are you gonna do this summer?
- I don't know.
I'm teaching summer school. You can't
run after your brothers all day long.
- Would I miss my birthday?
- You'd spend it with them.
That'd be good. That'd be great.
Would you please eat some breakfast?
I have to go to work.
[TV] Heavens to Mergatrold.
Exit for child welfare, stage right.
Don't you know better than
to stand under a loose boulder?
Heavens to vegetables,
I've been squashed.
The question Is, how does one baby-slt
a Western-type baby?
- Can I have some Trix?
- No.
- Please?
- I said no, you idiot!
- I'm telling Mom.
...a Western TV star.
Mommy! Troy's eating a box of Trix
and she won't share any with me!
Mommy's not here,
you silly, stupid rabbit.
Stupid.
...low-down, mangy coyote
of a wild steer.
Get out!
Do you get the picture?
Exit, stampeding all the way,
stage left.
Wendell!
Look at your eyes
popping out of your head.
Let's not hit people!
Snuff, you know
we stole that tube together.
You better share that, man.
- Ah, yeah!
- Ah!
- My best friend, babe.
- Nice glue.
All right.
- To the brothers that ain't here.
- Drain it out, baby.
All right.
All right. Shake it.
If I could, I'd like to be
A great big movie star
Overnight sensation
Drive a big expensive car...
Don't throw bottles!
We always get blamed for it.
He should clean his stinking house.
Hey! Hey! You stinkin' faggot!
Hey! Olean up
after your friggin' dogs, man!
- That ain't funny.
- Puerto Rican chink spic.
You friggin' nigger moron!
- Hey, what you say that for?
- Don't let him talk about me like that.
- I never say nothin' bad about you.
- Your mama.
- Play your music.
- I'm emotional. I can't sing now.
You can't sing anyway.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my man Vic.
- How you doin', Vic?
- Tommy LaLa.
I'm all right. Like that do.
Your mama know you're out here?
- What's up, Vic?
- How you feelin', kid?
All right.
- Vic, my number one soul brother.
- All right.
Great God!
- Bye, Vic.
- That's the bigs.
- It looks funny.
- Stupid.
- So? Look at yours.
- Mine don't look funny like yours.
Mine isn't standin' on my head
stickin' straight out like Topsy.
I don't know who Topsy is, but it looks
stupid and I can't stand you.
I can't stand you either.
- Sit down your black self.
- I'm black and proud.
- She got good hair.
- Peter Rican hair.
- Stop touching me, ugly.
- Don't call my sister ugly.
- I'll slap you.
- You ain't slappin' nobody, stupid.
- Get lost. You think you're pretty.
- I can't stand you either, Minnie.
Later for you. You think you're cute.
- Come on, who wants to jump rope?
- Me, I wanna play.
Brenda and Cathy, you're turning.
- You always tell us what to do.
- I'm older. Don't give me no lip.
Minnie and Troy get in the middle.
Shut up and get in the rope.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Come here.
You better not throw that cat!
She looks like a gorilla.
Shut up, your welfare self
has been left behind how many times?
Stupid ass dummy!
- So?
- So your mother's a ho!
- Who's got money for us?
- Give it up.
- What happened to your shoe?
- Damn kids broke my shoe, man.
Snuff, man.
Got to get some bread, nigger.
I've got all night, Nate.
Come on, Mommy. Why do I gotta eat this?
Peas have calcium.
All the calcium can't make up for
this nasty taste.
It might have made up for
your broke arm.
I broke my arm because I just got hurt.
Besides, this is gross. Nasty.
It is not nasty.
Everybody else likes it.
They're all crazy.
You're sitting here to eat.
Desserts anybody?
I got ice-cream and cake.
- Who wants some?
- I do.
- Bring some spoons and plates.
- All right!
- I don't want them having junk.
- It's just a little sand cake.
Get rid of this.
You get nothin'
till you finish your peas.
- How come these fools get to have it?
- You know what?
Finish your food,
I'll save you a piece, OK?
- Yum, yum.
- It looks good.
It tastes good, too.
- Scrumptiadilious.
- Scrumptiadelicious.
Hits the spot.
Take a bite, it's so moist.
Sweet. Come on, Red.
- Clinton called me Red.
- Red, Red, pees in the bed.
- Shut up.
- Ugly monkey.
He ate my cake! Mommy, he ate my cake!
Hey, Boogie.
You got a brand new piece, OK?
- Daddy, that's my piece!
- All right, here.
Half for him and half for you.
Nate. I'm tired of
standing here waiting.
Pick up the fork and eat the peas.
Now!
Now.
Eat the peas!
Do like your mother tell you.
Do I have to finish my peas?
That's OK, Doc.
Let's get you to the bathroom.
That's disgusting!
OK, all right, little mister.
I saw you.
Did you think you were a secret
commando with no-one watching?
I am always watching and you are going
to stop throwing garbage in my area way.
You're imagining things.
Oh, OK, smarty-pants.
I'm gonna call the police.
Let the cops see how you live,
you filthy, stinkin' pig.
- Who's a pig?
- You're a pig.
You come from a whole family of pigs.
I see you and your friend throwing that
garbage in my area way and my backyard.
Just shut the hell up. How dare you
talk about my family like that?
- You should be shot.
- Wendell, what's wrong?
This man accused me
of things I didn't do.
You'll see. Look, look.
Look at him,
picking up his own garbage.
I caught him throwing this trash
on my property.
He's the ringleader,
makes his friends do the same.
How dare you? He does no such thing.
- Yes, it's him and this other one.
- We don't do nothin'.
My kids can't sit on our stoop
or play in our backyard
without having to smell that disgusting
odour of dog shit from your house.
- How can you live in filth?
- My house is not filthy.
- Yours is.
- You know nothin' about my house.
You are a menace
and a disgrace to this entire block.
The board of health
ought to shut you down.
High waters!
Pull down your pants
or pull up your ankles!
You're disturbing the peace around here.
I never had trouble till you moved in.
Listen, you better be glad
we moved in here.
If you call my kids names
or accuse them of anything,
you'll have to deal with me.
- Call yourself a mother?
- Get your finger out my face.
Keep them inside. You killed my mother!
- What?!
- You killed my mother!
All right, all right.
Be quiet!
- You can't!
- Tony!
- My mother was a good person!
- Get you ass into your dog-house.
- You can't tell...
- I'm tired of listening to you.
- I'll call the cops!
- Get in the house!
Call the police!
I'm gonna sue you! I'm gonna sue you!
You can't do this!
You know what happened, look at this.
I'll tell you
what's gonna happen to you.
_ I'll never go back to Georgia
_ I'll never go back to Georgia...
What you talkin' 'bout?
I ain't no puta.
I'm Connie. I keeps my panty clean.
- Oh, come on, Connie.
- No, no, no, Tito.
You're crazy.
- Mira, ten cents.
- Hold your horses.
Give me two liquorice sticks,
ten Bazookas,
some lemonheads, some fireballs,
and some Boston baked beans.
- Está muy callente.
- Is that right?
You ain't nothin'
but a damned Puerto Rican.
I give you something good.
Oh, yeah, that's
what you say to all the fine things!
- Come on.
- No, no.
No, no, no puta.
No tickee, no tockee, Tito.
Why don't you arrest that
stinkin' Tony in that stinkin' house?
Don't worry baby,
I'm gonna get you out tomorrow, OK?
- Go home.
- Don't push me.
- Don't yell at me, either.
Come on,
he wasn't doing anything.
Vic, don't worry.
I'll come and visit you tomorrow.
I'll get you out.
You and that stinking house!
Shut up, you prostitute!
I am not a prostitute!
[TV] I don't wanna think about lt.
Hey, what are you all doing in here?
Get off my bed.
- The cops took Vic away.
- I know.
- What's in that bag?
- Want some candy?
- Psych your mind.
- Eggies. Thumbs up.
- I called no eggies first.
- When?
- When I bought it.
- That don't count.
- Eggies.
- You never give me nothin'.
- Shut up, evil flat-chested wench.
- For that, you're not getting any.
- I'm telling Ma you called me that.
- Go ahead.
You are an evil wench.
I'll tell her you went to the store.
- Nigger.
- Pop-eyed heifer.
I want the lemonheads.
I throwed you the red one.
- Can you chew with your mouth closed?
- Yeah!
Don't start with me.
I don't need you to fight my battles.
Quiet, it's the good part.
They even know the words.
Y'all turnin' so white.
They want to be white.
_ Went to sleep with you on my mind
_ Nate woke up In pee this morning
_ I woke up In love this morning
_ Went to sleep with you on my mind
Is the TV on?!
- I said, is the TV on?!
- No!
Be quiet.
- Don't turn it off.
-  I'm just turning it down.
_ I woke up In love this morning
- This show is stupid.
- Let's watch the Knicks.
Joseph, please change your vote.
- I'm watching The Partridge Family.
- He won't change his vote.
- We win.
- We watch the Knicks.
Hey, hey. Come on, get out.
Out! Out! Let's go.
- Out!
- We ain't buyin' nothin'.
- It smells funny.
- It stinks.
- I'll tell your mother.
- Tell her.
Hey!
What are you doing? Huh?
I'm talking to you. What are you doing?
Huh?
You think you can
come into my store and steal? Huh?
- Do I go to your house and take things?
- No.
No. Ten cents.
- Ten cents.
- I don't have any money.
What? No money?
Send her to jail.
No money, huh?
OK. Then get outta here and don't
come back until you got some money. OK?
What took you so long?
- You let him catch you?
- What was I supposed to do?
You should have said,
"I don't have to steal from you."
- "I forgot my money."
- Oh.
Steal something easier.
Yeah, my main man, Walt Frazier.
We better win tonight.
Stupid.
Don't pass the ball to him.
Jackson ain't nothin'.
He can't even dribble.
Pass it to Frazier
if you're gonna pass it to anybody.
Come on.
Pass it to him,
pass it to Frazier, come on!
Frazier! Yeah, tough shot!
It went in!
I knew he'd make it.
That's number one, right there.
Only one way to find out.
Damn it, Woody,
you bounced another cheque.
Thought we had it covered.
I'll get some money.
When?
When? What do you think
I'm doing right here?
Gem, let me just finish this music.
That's what I've always done.
Your music's not bringing
anything into the house.
The money will come.
I'm waiting.
I'm back teaching school
again and I am waiting.
Just keep doing what you're doing.
You know I made money before,
I'll make money again.
I trust you but you have got to realise
we are on a limited budget.
I am trying to balance everything.
If you write cheques and don't tell me,
it makes it extremely difficult.
As God is my witness, I want the best
for you and the children.
But I've got to do it in my own way.
Cool?
Cool. I opened a separate bank account.
That supposed to get
some kind of reaction from me?
- What is that supposed to prove?
- I don't know.
I'm interested in food on the table
and a roof over our heads.
Boy!
You know, you... you really kill me.
On the one hand, you come down here
telling me about yet another mistake
Woody done made.
But when I'm sitting at that piano,
trying to work, concentrate,
you won't let me do that either.
You got a beef with that?
I don't know what to do.
You can get up off my chair.
I don't want to talk about
your mistakes, I don't have time.
All I ask you to do is to write down
when you spend the money I am making.
I done told you,
it was a legitimate mistake.
You've made that mistake
five times this month.
I want you to change the pattern.
I don't need no lecture from you
on how to conduct myself in this house.
I'm asking you to help me conduct
the business affairs of this family.
What the hell am I trying to do?!
I don't know what you're doing.
I know you don't.
Well, let me tell you.
I got to be like a thief in the night,
every time I want privacy to do my work.
Selfish child!
Don't tell me about privacy!
Selfish, nothin'!
I can't take a piss
without six people on my tits.
You're the big saint and I ain't shit?
Call yourself what you want to.
Just write down the cheque.
I will note the cheque, right there.
I think you can do two things at once.
Make music and write.
"Woody...
...wrote...
...a bum cheque."
- Here.
- That's very cute.
Remember to write it down
before it bounces next time.
You seem to forget, I'm the one
who used to pay for you and the children
to go to Bloomingdale's and get
what you wanted, when you wanted.
- You ain't the only one...
It's a foul! What a referee!
Clinton! Clinton!
- What?!
- Don't answer me "what"!
- Turn the TV off.
- I'm watching the Knicks.
I don't care. No TV on a school night.
Let her scream. I'm watching this game.
Hey! No TV! Turn it off!
- It's just a game!
- Who is that?
- That was Nate.
- It wasn't me!
If the TV's not off,
I'll whop everybody.
Troy, I have to go to the bathroom!
Open up before I pee on myself!
Come on, Troy.
Troy, what are you doing?!
Open the door!
You better chastise your boys.
Hey! Clinton,
don't make me come up there!
-  Clinton!
-  Troy!
In a minute!
- Walt Frazier doesn't pay my bills.
- It ain't about no Walt Frazier!
Surprise, boys.
- I'm watching the Knicks!
- What's the big deal?
The big deal is,
I said no TV on a school night.
The Knicks got a job.
You need education.
I'll throw this idiot box
out the window.
- Let Boogie in the bathroom.
- She won't let me watch the game.
- How dare you go to your father?
- Let him watch the game. Let's go.
- Woody, please, don't touch me now.
- Come on.
- Get your hands off me.
- I want the bathroom!
I own this house.
I pay Con Ed for the electricity.
When you start paying bills, you can
decide when the TV's on and when not.
- I'm watching this game.
- I'm gonna knock you out!
Shut up! Shut up!
What I want...
...is some respect...
...for my work in this house.
You get out of my house.
You call your brother,
and you tell him
to come and get your shit.
That's just fine.
If that's what you want,
that's what you get.
See what you did?
See what you started?
-  It wasn't my fault.
- Wanna go to your room?
Want some ice?
- Hey, Miss Coomish Mimmish.
- Hi, Uncle Brown.
Here's the other bag, man.
- Ready to go?
- Yep.
- Get down.
- Where's Clinton and Nate?
Nate's with Mommy
and Clinton's in his room.
OK, Boogie, I'm gonna see you soon.
No, come on, now.
No, we talked about this.
You're gonna be a big man,
I'll put you in a big chair.
Like that?
- Bye bye, Daddy.
- Bye bye.
All right, Miss Coomish Mimmish.
Don't go, Daddy.
You're too grown to give me a hug, huh?
Come on.
Now...
I'll be over at Uncle Brown's.
You have his number.
Call me if you need me, OK?
- OK.
- Wendell?
Come on, Wendell. Don't be like that.
Wendell.
- OK, Troy?
- Yes, Daddy.
All right.
Bye, Dad.
Good morning, Mommy.
How are you today?
I'm fine. Thank you, Ladybug.
- I made you some breakfast.
- I see.
Thanks.
- Are all of you mad at me?
- Yeah.
I'll get it.
Hi, Daddy.
- Hey, where's Mommy?
- In her room.
I want to talk to you.
Guess what? I cleaned the kitchen
and I made Mommy breakfast.
That's great.
- I think she's feeling better now.
- That's good.
- Your father's sorry about last night.
- It's not your fault, Daddy.
You know, Daddy doesn't want to fight
or yell or scream or holler.
All Daddy wants to do...
...is play his music. That's all.
Maybe if you played other people's music
Mommy wouldn't scream and yell at you.
I can't do that any more, Troy.
I got to work on my music now.
Well, maybe you should just go for
taking her out on a date.
- You think so, huh?
- I do.
Hey, listen.
This is for you and your brothers.
- You don't like candy no more?
- No, I do.
I want you to take and give this
to your mother from me.
- OK?
- Sure.
- Everybody else doing all right?
- Yeah, I think.
All right, Miss Coomish Mimmish.
Come here.
Hey.
Your father loves you, Troy.
I love you too, Daddy.
These are from Daddy.
You can at least open this.
He said to tell you
he wants to take you on a date.
Hmm!
Candy from Dad.
Can I have a quarter?
Thank you.
- I still say you're rich.
- No, we aren't.
You are. I can tell by these fancy
antiques and that foreign car.
It's not fancy, just rare.
- Agh!
- My God!
I gotta go.
Thanks for the ice cream.
Yeah!
Happy you drove my company away?
;Stupid! I hate you!
Idiot!
Hey, Wendell. You seen my tickets?
- It wasn't me.
- You can't find the tickets?
- I know man, I can't find 'em.
- Keep looking.
Troy!
Troy, I know
you can hear me calling you.
- Troy! Have you seen my Knicks tickets?
- Who cares...
- Did you see my tickets?
- I haven't...
- I'll break your neck.
- Break it then.
- Ow! Get off me!
- Shut up. Give me my tickets.
Why? You started the fight
between Mommy and Daddy.
- You're hurting me!
- Where are my tickets?
Gimme my tickets and I'll let you go.
All right, nigger. I hate your guts.
I hate your guts.
Who told you you could go in my room
in the first place?
Next time I'll punch you in your face.
- Heifer.
- I spent them funny-looking nickels.
Mom!
H-E-L-L-N-O and you are not it.
There's a German
In the grass, a bottle up his ass
Stick It In, stick It out
Do you wanna be a scout?
N-O spells no and you are not it.
Hot peas and butter!
Come and get your supper!
Come on, you can run faster than that.
I know you can find it.
Look at you, you can't even get it.
- Get outta here!
- Come on!
Miss Carmichael, I see you.
- Oh, be quiet.
- I heard that.
Better keep trying. You're cold.
Oh, you're hot.
Oh, you're boiling hot.
I beg your pardon. I beg your pardon.
- Bye, Troy.
- Bye, Minnie. See you tomorrow.
Where are you going, Troy?
- Stop following me, Greg.
- I ain't following you, Troy the Boy.
Troy!
Huh?
I need to ask you something.
Clinton claims you stole his
prize collection of buffalo nickels.
They're very valuable
and they mean a lot to him.
- Did you take them?
- No.
- You look cute Mrs. Carmichael.
- Thank you, Greg.
- How's your mother?
- She's OK.
- What's wrong?
- Troy.
She's always picking on me,
she teases me about school.
She calls my mother names.
She treats me mean.
Makes fun of me in front of our friends.
I wanna be her friend
but she doesn't like me.
-  I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
Troy!
Somebody left the toilet seat up.
I almost fell in again.
Never mind that.
I do not believe what I just heard.
Are you calling people's mothers names?
- I didn't!
- Don't lie to me.
Why is that child standing outside
with tears in his eyes?
You go back outside and apologise.
- But I didn't do anything!
- Go.
- Sorry, Greg.
- Sorry why?
Sorry I called your mother a ho.
Are you sorry about teasing me
about being left back?
About welfare and my brothers
having different fathers?
- All right, already. I said sorry.
- You better be.
- Thank you, Mrs. Carmichael.
- That's OK, baby.
- Stupid!
- Hey! Hey!
Hey, come here.
Go to the supermarket,
get things for dinner.
I hate food stamps.
Besides, we ain't on welfare.
Stop saying "ain't". You better be glad
we got food stamps. Go on.
Mommy, everyone's gonna laugh at me.
Nobody gonna laugh
that ain't on welfare their self.
How come I have to go?
Do you want to have
dinner tonight, Troy? Go.
Where are you going? Come back.
I've been watching you, you know.
If you don't put it down,
I'll call your mother.
- Call her, I haven't got a phone.
- Come on. Let's see.
Aha, what is this? Is this your hips?
- All right!
- Is this your other hip?
- Coconut West Indian monkey.
- Listen, you little pick ninny.
Get out of my store
and don't come back here no more!
Oh, God, these children. They don't know
how to act, they have no manners.
Miss, I'm sorry for the disturbance.
I'll get you, you ugly bitch!
- I didn't do nothin' to you. Get off!
- I saw you!
Hey! No fighting in front of the store.
- Get out of here, pick ninny!
- You shut up!
If your parents would teach you respect
you wouldn't be here.
You got your things?
Don't pay her no mind.
- You all right?
- I'm gonna punch you in your face.
You know where you live? OK, go ahead.
God! Back to work!
- Here, I told you not to send me.
- What on earth happened to you?
- She took the change too.
- Who?
- Peanut.
- What were you doing?
- Getting beat up.
- A boy beat you up?
- Peanut's a girl.
- How big is she?
Six-two, 200 pounds.
You wrestle your brothers all the time,
and you let some girl
take my groceries and my food stamps?
I should whup you myself.
Get your brother and go get my things.
That's all right. I hate liver anyway.
I'm glad Troy got her butt kicked.
She thinks she's so cute.
Shut up, you ugly black baboon.
- You ain't talking to me?
- Shut your moustachie self.
Ain't nobody gonna do nothin' about it.
- Agh!
- And stay off my stoop!
- Troy!
- You glue sniffers! Leave me alone!
- Where's our money?
- I ain't got money, only food stamps.
You know we take those too.
Leave me alone! Shut up!
Yeah, you like that, don't you?
Breathe in.
One more time, one more time.
Breathe out.
Get it, girl. Get it, girl, hey.
Bye, Troy!
Hey, Miss Coomish Mimmish.
I'm flying.
Snuffy and Right Hand Man
are chasing me.
No, Snuffy and Right Hand Man
are not here.
But Poppa's here.
Daddy, I'm glad you came back home.
Did you take Mom out yet?
Not yet, but I will.
Take her out now, Daddy.
Take her out now.
Young lady, I want you to get some rest.
Yeah?
It's for later.
They're spirited. But I don't know why
our kids are ostracized by your family.
- Welcome back, Daddy.
- Thanks, man.
Clinton, did you go to the game?
- Yeah, the Knicks won.
- Oh, yeah?
Daddy, you burnt the toast.
That ain't burnt, just a little dark.
Give it here.
Poor kids in the Delta would love
to have that to eat.
- And a father nice enough to burn it.
- OK.
You'll give us all heart attacks, Woody.
- Daddy, these eggs are runny.
- Eat those eggs!
The food was prepared by your pops
with loving care so you will eat it,
am I right?
Celeste has had Joan, Sam and Viola
out to St Lucia and none of our kids.
I ain't studying Celeste.
The woman is mean and evil.
- That's your sister.
- Yeah.
- I don't want to visit Aunt Celeste.
- We don't need to visit nobody.
We got the car. We can go for a drive.
Can we leave Brooklyn?
- Can we please leave Brooklyn?
- Yes, we can.
Hey, Miss Coomish Mimmish. Come here.
- How's my girl?
- Good.
- Feeling better? Want some breakfast?
- Mm-hm.
- Ready for a drive after breakfast?
- After we clean up.
- What do we have to clean up for?
- I got an ailment.
Hey, hey, hey. After you all clean up.
- Can Mutley come, Daddy?
- Yeah, Mutley can come.
We're gettin' ready to get in the car,
and... Roll on, roll on...
- Here we go.
- Jinx! You owe me a Coke!
Roll on, little Citroen,
Roll on, roll on down the road _
- This is 7 Arlington Place, right?
- Yeah.
- I have to shut off your electricity.
- What?
- You gotta pay your bill.
- It's paid.
The bill is unpaid. "7 Arlington Place.
Unpaid bill. Service to be shut off."
Did you pay it?
Yes, I paid it. This is the second time
they made this mistake.
- Go back in the house.
- Oh, Daddy!
- You can call them.
- I'm gonna talk to these people.
- Just doin' my job.
- OK, you do what you gotta do.
All right.
Come on.
- It's so pretty.
- What are the candles here for?
- Santeria.
- It's like church. Turn the lights on.
- Ain't working.
- What do you mean?
- Hey, how you all doin'?
- Hi, Mr. Carmichael.
- You blow a fuse?
- What happened?
- Been waiting for you.
- What's with the candles?
- There's enough candles in here.
- Yeah, we, uh...
We're having some
financial problems right now.
We understand. I was hoping
the food stamps would help.
Um, anyway, like I was saying...
Here you go, Vic. We, uh...
We didn't blow no fuse.
- Damned electricity been cut off.
- What?
- Yeah. Drag, man.
- Come again?
We ain't got no electricity,
and neither do you.
You know I need my damned lights.
Can't sleep, can't think, can't read.
- It won't be long...
- How can I cook?
- A couple of days till we get straight.
- A couple of days?
Ain't that a bitch? Payin' good money
for rent and I ain't got no lights?
That's what I'm saying.
I can give you some candles.
- Forget candles.
- You don't understand.
My disability
requires that I have light.
I know it's an inconvenience
to you, Vic, to everybody.
I'm gonna go in the morning
and talk to the people, OK?
I hope you don't expect us
to pay rent, because
si no hay luz, no hay renta.
No lights, no rent.
Miss Jessica, I don't know about "us"
cos you don't even live here,
but I do expect you to pay, Vic.
Now I don't live here?
Did you hear? Are you gonna
let him say that to me?
I don't live here now?
I paid enough. I got enough shrapnel
in my back, I'm afraid to get wet.
I think I paid enough,
I paid far too damn much.
Well, hold up, hold up, there.
I don't want no hollerin' or screamin'.
I don't mean no disrespect
to you or your kids,
but my rent puts as much food
on your baby's table as you do.
Well, now...
I did not have to give your wife
those food stamps.
Vic, let's go. Forget about it.
I can't live like this no more.
At least you all still got
gas and hot water. Hey, Vic?
It's good, baby.
I like eating by candlelight.
It's kinda romantic.
- Are you wooing me?
- It wouldn't do me much good, would it?
- This is fun.
- Does it mean we can't watch TV?
That's right, no cartoons.
No Brady Bunch or Partridge Family
for Troy and Nate.
- Hey, nigger, I don't watch that show.
- You do so.
- Liar.
- Nigger.
- Stop calling each other nigger.
- You can't watch the Knicks.
Come on, let's just eat in peace.
Daddy's got some good news.
They've given me a solo concert.
Wow, great, Daddy.
This is the one, Gem.
It's gonna be real special.
Clinton, Wendell, Nate,
I need you all to get out
and put up some posters for Daddy.
- Will you do that?
- Fine with me.
Don't you worry.
I'll take care of the house, I promise.
- Thank you. Call if you need us.
- OK.
If you see anybody acting suspiciously
around the house,
you stand on that top step
and you sing, OK?
You'll scare the whole neighbourhood.
- You drive safe. OK, take care. Bye.
- Let's go!
No-one's gonna step on this stoop!
- You didn't say bye to Tony.
- Tommy LaLa can't sing a lick.
Why did you tell him that?
_ Roll on, roll on down the road
- What did you hit me for?
- Out that out.
- Hey, hey.
I'll tell Mommy.
_ Troy's gonna be with Cousin Viola
_ Nate's gonna be with Cousin Sam
Can't wait. Finally,
some peace and quiet.
_... roll on,
Roll on, Citroen, roll on
_ Roll on down the road _
How many times are you
gonna sing that song?
- You don't like my song?
- No!
I'm glad the kids
are coming south. I'm tired.
Woody, we need to make some changes.
The money I bring in
is not making ends meet.
I need your help.
You want me to... pick up a guitar
and play some rock'n'roll?
Yes.
If it'll help pay Con Ed, yes.
This concert's gonna change
a lot of things for us.
Plus, it'll bring in
a nice piece of change.
Who's gonna come but us, Uncle
Brown, Aunt Maxine and our friends?
People are gonna come to this concert.
People still wanna hear good music.
I don't care how much rock'n'roll sells.
People know the difference
between that and pure music.
- I need you to support me in this.
- What?
Look here.
Who gets up at the crack of dawn,
Monday through Friday,
cooking breakfast, go to school,
teach school, come home, cook dinner,
grade papers, make lesson plans,
keep our kids from killing each other,
so you can be a pure musician,
playing pure music.
If that ain't support,
I don't know what is.
Thank you.
You woke up Troy. Are you satisfied?
What's the matter? Can't you sleep?
No.
- Want to come up here with us?
- Yeah.
- Oh...
- Your long legs.
Whoa, Miss Coomish Mimmish.
Troy, aren't you the lucky one?
Aunt Song said Viola is beside herself
that you're coming down here.
When am I coming home?
In a few weeks.
- Will the lights be back on?
- Oh, yeah, baby.
All the lights will be back on.
- I don't wanna go.
- Troy, come on, come on.
You're gonna have a wonderful time.
Please, just this once.
Lord have mercy,
would you look at this!
- I didn't think you'd ever get here.
-  I didn't either, Song.
You look tired. Lord have mercy,
you brought your dog, too!
Viola, why don't you put Queenie
in the family room?
- Family room?
- You sure got a clean house.
Oh, isn't that cute?
Clem, did you hear what Clinton said?
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm Wendell.
- I'm Clinton.
- Well, shut my mouth wide open!
Oh, Carolyn, I just love yours and
Troy's hair. Would you look at that?
Those tiny braids.
What do you all call that?
Braids.
No, sugar. We don't let the dogs
in here. This carpet's too nice.
Take that dog outside.
Put him in the car.
- Nate.
- Come on, Mutley.
Viola, ain't you gonna say hello
to your Cousin Troy?
Troy, are you gonna say hi?
- Hi.
She's just a little shy.
- Off the couch!
-  Got any coffee?
I don't mind, we are all family.
Who's hungry? I got fried chicken and
potato salad in the kitchen right there.
Wait! Come here!
- You have not changed.
- Come on, Troy.
- Aunt Song, you sure can cook.
- Why, thank you, sugar.
Lord, Troy, you don't know how happy
we are to have you here with us.
We're gonna have us some fun.
Troy can stay as long as she wants.
Oh, Song, that's so nice.
Troy, isn't that nice?
- Yeah, thank you.
- You're welcome.
We need to get on the road. We have
to drop Nate off at Trudy and Boo's.
Come on, finish your plates.
We got about two hours to go.
How soon are you
getting back to New York?
Day after tomorrow.
Will you please try and cooperate
and get along with everybody?
- I don't wanna stay here.
- You're gonna have a great time.
Sweetie, I wish I was staying.
Just don't leave me here.
- I hardly know these people.
- They're your relatives.
I'm the one to feel sorry for,
I have to go back with those boys.
Troy, I love you baby.
- Bye! See you!
-  Take care of yourself.
Bye, little Joe.
- Don't leave me.
- Let's go inside.
- Mommy, don't leave me.
- Let's go inside, baby.
When you're getting dressed for bed,
I have often heard It said,
Before you go to sleep,
You have to put away your clothes...
...if you do things,
Do things right.
Queenie, is mama's baby
gonna be nice to Troy?
Troy, where are your pyjamas?
May I be excused?
And they'll say "Yes" to you...
Lord have mercy, honey,
you can't wear these!
Viola, give Troy one of your nighties.
I'm gonna throw these in the garbage.
Yes, Mama.
Get up, wake up,
get there on time for school,
Don't you be late,
Find your place
Win the race.
- Here, Troy.
- Go change in the bathroom.
Sugar, you ain't got a thing to hide
with your skinny self.
Thinner than a blade of grass.
- Viola, you got your bra on?
- Yes.
Come on.
All right, you rascals. Let's say
our prayers. Put Queenie on the floor.
Now I lay me down to sleep,
I pray the Lord my soul to keep,
If I should die before I wake,
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
Amen.
All right, now.
I want you two right to sleep.
All right, sleep tight,
don't let the bed bugs bite.
So glad you're here.
We're gonna have lots of fun.
- Goodnight, honey.
- Goodnight, Daddy.
- Goodnight, Troy.
- 'Night, Uncle Clem.
Night, night.
I ain't no puta.
I keep my pyjamas clean.
- I keep my pyjamas clean.
- What's that noise in there?
Nothing! Stop jumping
on the bed before she comes in.
I don't care. I hate this place anyway.
Besides, my dog could kill
your rat dog anyway.
I don't care either.
And it ain't my dog, it's Mama's dog.
- You like living in Brooklyn?
- A lot better than here.
- You should visit me.
- I like Aunt Carolyn.
It's OK if you don't like Song.
She ain't my real mother, I was adopted.
You were?
What's that funny noise outside?
- You ain't never heard crickets before?
- Goodnight.
Lord have mercy, child,
you sure got one thick head of hair.
You need a hot comb on these.
You ain't got good hair like my baby.
Ow!
Don't tell me you've got the nerve
to be tender-headed with these naps?
What's those things
you and your mother have?
- Beads and braids.
- Beads and braids. Lord have mercy.
Troy's having a birthday party
Pizza, pizza, daddy-o
I hit it!
- Want me to go over the bump?
- No!
- Hold on.
- I am.
I'm gonna go faster.
The bump's coming'.
- Hey!
- Hi!
Daddy-o!
Inny, Minny, siss a linny
Oshie, koshie, Liberace, I love you
Take a peach, take a plum
Take a bubble-gum
No peach, no plum
Just a stick of bubble-gum
I like coffee, I like tea
I like the colored boy and he likes me
Step back white boy
You don't shine
I'll get the colored boy
to kick your behind
All, all, all In together now
How you like the weather now?
January, February, March, April
May, June, July, August...
Queenie!
[TV]... our Savior
was a kid just like you.
Stay there.
[TV] Sling this song nice and loud
so he can hear you up In heaven.
Here we go.
_ One, two, three
The Devils after me...
I like this song.
_... he's always throwing sticks
_ Seven, eight, nine
He misses every time
_ Hallelujah, Hallelujah,
Hallelujah, Amen
_ One, two, three
The Devils after me
_ Four, five, six
He's always throwing sticks
Come on, sing. It's real easy.
_ Hallelujah, Hallelujah,
Hallelujah, Amen
_ Amen
_ Amen _
Praise the Lord!
Did you all wash your hands
when you came in from playing outside?
Viola? Girl, I am speaking to you.
I don't have to listen to you.
All right, Missy. Don't show off
in front of your company.
I am going to speak
to your father about this.
Don't let me have to go get my switch.
Jesus help me.
- Clem! Clem!
- She ain't my real mother.
But we know a secret, don't we?
- Did you wash your hands?
- Yes.
Don't tell me a fib.
You know it's sinful to lie.
Yes, Aunt Song. I washed them.
Good, run back to bed.
Uncle Clem and I
have a surprise for you.
- Come on, Clem!
- Happy birthday, Troy!
Happy birthday, Troy.
Say "Happy birthday, Troy."
- Thank you.
- Isn't this nice?
I'm gonna make you a birthday cake.
What kind of cake shall it be?
- Chocolate!
- Oh, no, sugar, I can't do chocolate.
Last time I did,
Viola broke out in hives.
- No, I didn't. You did.
- Don't argue with your mother.
You see, Clem? I say it's white,
she says it's black.
If the girl says she didn't get hives,
she didn't.
- I told you.
- Always taking her side.
For Christs sake, let Troy
open up her presents, please, honey.
Goddamn!
- Ooh!
- It's a dress.
It's from me and your uncle Clem.
Ain't that pretty?
- You are going to wear that today.
- Oh, thank you.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- It's a training bra.
- You won't need that for quite a while.
Oh... This came in the morning mail.
It's for you.
- It's from my Mommy.
- Oh, yeah. What'd she say?
I hope she don't mind
me taking out those braids.
I didn't know what else to do.
Let's let her read her letter in peace.
Come on, let's make breakfast.
Viola, let's go.
- Jade!
- Dear Ladybug, happy birthday!
The mailman just tapped on the window
and I got your letter. Hooray!
I'm glad you're having such
a wonderful time. Could this be true?
You've been gone a month,
but It feels like an eternity.
- Minnie asked:
- When is Troy back from down south?
All the boys are still on the stoop
playing Strat-o-Matic baseball.
What a waste of time
And Tommy still can't sing
_... yes to you
_ Listen to me
_ La, la, la, la, la means
_ I love you _
Last night,
we had yet another run-in with Tony.
Vic didnt slap him this time,
your father was there, thank God.
Wendell told me
that every morning,
Tony throws trash from his yard
onto our stoop.
Well, we finally caught him red-handed.
What are you doing?
Throwing this trash
back where it came from.
- Why did you throw it here?
- Was it us?
- Get into your house!
- Don't tell me. I know...
- You're the one...
- No...
You know how It Is.
Before you know it,
you got a big crowd wanting a big show.
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
We caught him throwing trash over there.
I expect more from a grown man.
What are you doing?
Your children are constantly
throwing trash on my property.
- True.
- And they throw rocks on my dogs.
- Untrue.
- Machine gun! Machine gun!
- Are you doing this?
- Do you believe him?
You gonna believe this stinky over us?
My children are doing no such thing.
You ought to be ashamed.
Act like an adult.
Out this foolishness out.
I hate to say this,
but your house stinks.
That's the truth.
Why your house stink, man?
- Hey, you up there.
Mister Number Four. Where's my rent?
When are you going to pay my rent?
Hey, Tony.
If you want me to,
I'll come and help you straighten up.
This situation's got to stop.
I can smell your animals in my house.
You understand me?
OK.
Here.
Aren't you glad to be away from
the crazy people In Crooklyn, New York?
And now, about your father.
It started with Clinton.
You're the eldest
and I expect more from you.
You make your own decision.
Why did Daddy have to
have his concert tonight?
The same night
of the NBA Championships! Dang!
Which is more important?
- Was that some new stuff tonight?
- Yeah, man.
-  You ought to record it.
- I plan to.
I also started working on a folk opera.
Folk opera? About what, Woody?
- What are you laughing at?
- Jessica, she's from the city.
My folk opera
is about growing up in Alabama.
- You got the material.
- That's right.
You're right!
We were all trying very hard
to lift your father's spirits.
And it was working, until...
The Knicks are world champs.
We got some ice cream
and cake right here.
- Clinton.
-  I'm not hungry.
The Knicks won. How about that?
I've enclosed some gifts
for you and Viola.
Ladybug, we all miss you dreadfully.
I miss you. Love, Mommy.
P.S. We got the lights turned back on
thanks to Uncle Brown,
who is buying you a plane ticket home.
Please write...
"...and thank him immediately."
Queenie!
I don't know where she's run off to.
- Here she is, the birthday girl.
- These are for you.
- Thank you.
- Did your mother send those?
- They're jade.
- Aren't they pretty!
What are they? Elephants?
Look, Aunt Carolyn sent me some also.
You don't have pierced ears.
You know how I feel about that.
But Troy has pierced ears.
Troy was also wearing them funny braids
and beads and shells and things.
You don't let me do what I wanna do.
- I wanna go home.
- Beg pardon?
- I'm going home.
- No need to get upset.
Everybody has a little argument
now and then.
Aunt Song didn't mean nothing about
your hair and your earrings, did you?
- I don't care.
- See what you did?
Lord have mercy, Troy.
How would it look if you left now?
Aunt Song has a big mouth sometimes.
Do you want your folks to think
we done scared you back up north?
If she goes, I go.
Troy, Aunt Song
loves you and your family.
- Clem, do something.
- Now, look, folks.
Troy wants to go home, Troy's
going home, that's all there is to it.
Troy, at least stay for
the birthday party I've prepared.
- Song.
- All right.
Fix us some breakfast.
Queenie!
Baby, where are you?!
- Come back in here.
- Where's my baby?!
Queenie! Where are you?!
She done lost her way, has my child.
Queenie!
Queenie, where are you?
Queenie, where are you, baby?
Stop that, please!
- Did you find her?
- I don't understand where she is.
It's not like Queenie just to up
and disappear. Why, Lord, why?
- She'll be back.
- Don't worry. Queenie'll show up.
It's late.
You had enough ice cream and cake?
- Yes.
- Brushed your teeth and washed?
- Help me pull this bed out, then.
Come on, move! Move!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Pick up the pillow.
Viola, help them with the pillows.
Get out of here, Judy, Jody,
whatever your names are.
Oh, dear God!
Oh, God, take me right now!
I don't want to live without my baby.
Queenie!
Oh, God, Queenie!
Looks like it's gonna rain.
That means my baby's in heaven.
Troy, I'll go get your bags.
Bye, Aunt Song.
I'm sorry about Queenie.
Maybe you can come
and stay with me some time?
I'd like that.
Bye, Queenie.
Sorry you got squashed in the sofa,
even though I hated your guts.
Let her go, Viola.
We're off and running. Let's go.
- Bye, Viola.
- Bye, Troy.
You're going back to bad oi' Brooklyn.
Hey, little Ladybug.
- Hi, Uncle Brown.
- Welcome home.
- Hi.
- How are you? How was your flight?
- Good. Where's Daddy?
At rehearsal so your mother
asked us to pick you up.
- Here's a gift.
- She didn't want a ride?
- No, she's just busy.
- Hmm.
What happened to your hair?
Aunt Song didn't like my braids
so she took 'em out.
Goodness, gracious. Carolyn's gonna
have a fit when she sees this, huh?
- Are you ready to go?
- Mm-hm.
- Woody been there all day?
- Since this morning.
You were ready to come home? Had enough
of the south? I don't blame you.
Mm-hm. It's too slow.
- Don't know what you're missing.
- I'm glad I missed it.
- When was your birthday?
- Yesterday.
- How old are you now? Eight?
- Ten.
No! How's my brother Clem
and Song and Viola?
Good. Thanks for the tickets.
I didn't get a chance to write.
- You're welcome.
- Family's gotta stick together.
- Right.
- You're right.
We're gonna make a quick stop
before we take you home.
- Who's sick?
- It's nothing serious.
It's Mommy, isn't it?
Well, she hasn't been
feeling too well lately.
- What's wrong with her?
- We don't know.
- The doctors are running tests.
- Why didn't she tell me?
How come nobody told me?
No one wanted you
to worry yourself silly.
Your mother didn't think
there was cause for alarm.
Where's Daddy?
He's in there with your mother.
- Hey!
- Hi, Dad!
Miss Coomish Mimmish!
Hey, baby. Troy's back.
Mm? Oh... Oh, Ladybug.
- Hi.
Mommy, how are you feeling?
- Who did that to your hair?
- Aunt Song.
Aunt Song... Oh, shit, I knew she would.
Come and give me a big hug.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too. You and my brothers.
You must have been lonesome
if you missed them.
Mommy, you work too hard.
I can start helping you cook and clean.
I don't even care
if nobody else helps me.
- You have to get your rest.
- That's very kind of you.
Come here.
You know, I need you...
...to watch out for Joseph,
your little brother.
He's the youngest.
He's your responsibility.
You promise me?
Come here.
I promise.
Woody, get the car.
I'm ready to go home.
You're coming home now?
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Let's go, Troy.
- Get the car.
- OK.
Your car.
Aunt Song's kinda weird, huh?
Yeah, they talk funny down there.
What do you mean?
"Aw, yeah" funny.
Hey, where did those trees come from?
Your mother.
She got the block association
to put some life on this street.
- Hey! Clinton, Wendell, look here.
- It's Troy.
- Doesn't she look good?
- Look at her hair!
- Tommy, turn that junk off now.
- Oh, come on.
I'm tired of hearing that garbage
on my stoop.
- But it's the Ohi-Lites.
- Ohi-Nothin'.
- Want some help?
- Quit it.
- Didn't expect you for two weeks.
- Get off. Stop it.
- Clinton, grab this bag.
- I'm busy.
Boy, you'd better come get these bags.
She should carry her own bags.
Come on, Mutley.
[TV] So great was the beauty of this
black woman, It has become legendary.
And now, out of the mist of 3,000 years,
emerges today's beautiful black queen.
Naturally beautiful,
radiant, she Is black essence.
And her beautiful natural hair
Is her crowning glory.
Afro Sheen, beautiful products
for beautiful people.
_ Beautiful people use Afro Sheen _
Soul...
Train.
- Change the channel.
- Shut up. You can't give orders.
Yeah, crabby, Mommy ain't home.
- What do you care?
- Be quiet.
- You be quiet or go back down south.
- Soul Train line!
My favourite part of the show.
- Somebody could get hurt.
- You can't dance.
- You got no soul.
- He's on his butt.
- Clinton, turn the TV off.
- Oh, Dad, we're watching the...
Soul Train!
I got some news about your mother.
I want everybody
to listen to me real good.
The doctors told me that
your mother's sicker than we thought.
- What?
- They found...
- They found cancer.
- What's cancer?
It means your mother's gonna be
in the hospital for a while.
No need to be afraid,
your mother's gonna be fine.
But she'll have to stay there
for a while.
It's not fair.
I know it ain't fair,
but it's gonna be all right.
Now, listen to me.
You all listen to me.
Come on, shh! Y'all ain't listening
to me. Now, listen.
They got to run some tests
on your mother.
It's gonna be fine.
Don't be like that.
- It wasn't my fault.
- I know it wasn't.
I know it wasn't your fault.
Ain't nobody's fault.
She'll be out soon,
she's just got to stay in there,
and they're gonna run some tests.
_ One, two, three,
The Devils after me
_ Four, five six
He's always throwing sticks
_ Seven, eight, nine
He misses every time
_ Hallelujah, Hallelujah,
Hallelujah, Amen
_ One, two, three,
The Devils after me
_ Four, five, six
He's always throwing sticks
_ Seven, eight, nine
He misses every time
_ Hallelujah, Hallelujah,
Hallelujah, Amen
_ One, two, three,
The Devils after me
_ Four, five, six
He's always throwing sticks
_ Seven, eight, nine
He misses every time
_ Hallelujah, Hallelujah, Hallelujah...
Hope we don't have to dress
up for Mommy's funeral.
It won't be so bad.
Hey, Sam. How come you're not playing'?
- Cos I'm a girl, Daddy.
- Aw, come on.
[TV: Pepsi jingle]
Troy.
Look, here are your new clothes.
Aren't they pretty?
I picked them out myself.
Wait...
Wait till you see these shoes.
Aren't they just adorable?
Troy, why don't you
at least try it on, OK?
Please, Ladybug.
Don't be difficult, OK?
I know this is hard,
it's hard for everybody,
but you have to wear something nice.
Don't you want to look all pretty
like Aunt Maxine?
Carolyn would be so proud of you.
Listen, my mother hates polyester.
She would never let me
wear anything like that.
Right, Troy.
[Cheerios jingle on TV]
- _ Let yourself go _
- Get Cheerios
- Troy?
- What?!
- Let's go!
- I'm not goin'!
Shit.
- Troy, baby, what are you doing?
- I'm sick.
- You got everybody waiting on you.
- So?
Please don't make this
any more difficult than it has to be.
I hate funerals. I'm not going.
Troy, you're not the only one
who's in pain.
We're all hurtin'.
We gotta think about Mommy
and what would make Mommy happy.
- You wanna make Mommy happy?
- No use trying right now.
Yes, there is. Your mother
would want everybody to be...
...at the church together.
- Will you do that for me?
- Yeah.
I want you to get yourself together.
I'm gonna wait for you downstairs.
- OK?
- All right.
I hate funerals too.
- I'll be downstairs.
- OK.
I'm proud of you, Troy.
Hey, there, little bit.
Want Vic to get you anything,
little sister?
No, thanks.
All right. OK.
Who are these people anyway,
coming out of the woodwork?
- Mommy sure had a lot of friends.
- I guess she did.
Troy, they keep laughing
and pointing at me,
saying, "His momma's dead,
his momma's dead"!
- They took my money!
- Who?
The Possoms! Right Hand and Snuffy!
Come on, Joseph.
There they are!
- Who took your money?
- There! Snuffy and Right Hand Man!
Snuffy, that's what you get.
- Troy, what you do that for?
- Tired of being terrorised.
Go sniff on your own block.
Mother, stop it!
Mommy, I don't like it when you fight!
Daddy, get her to stop!
Get her to stop!
Mommy! Daddy!
- Mommy!
-  Damn rat!
- Stop!
- No, get... Huh?
Mommy?
No, Troy...
Mommy's... gone.
Mommy's gone, Troy.
Troy, you can cry.
It's all right to cry.
Mommy's gone.
Are you sick?
- Are you sick, baby?
- You should have told me.
Stand up, baby.
Here.
Oh, baby.
Let me wipe that.
Come here, let me wipe that.
OK...
Damn, Troy...
Everybody was wondering
when you was gonna break.
Even Clinton cried.
Daddy, please don't make me move away.
I know Aunt Maxine
wants me to go and live with her.
Nobody's goin' anywhere.
Mommy was in a lot of pain, wasn't she?
Yes, she was.
Then it's good she died.
So she wouldn't have to suffer.
That's a nice way of putting it, baby.
Yeah, that's real nice.
Ow! You're hurting me!
Be quiet. It doesn't hurt.
If you combed it more often,
it wouldn't look like a sheep's behind.
It never hurt when Mommy combed it.
I'm sorry, Joseph, but I'm not Mommy.
Dear Ladybug, how are you?
I miss you so very much.
I can't believe you just turned ten.
All of you kids
are growing up so rapidly.
You turned out pretty good,
considering you're raising
a house full of ashy...
- Ow!
...rusty butt boys.
- Can Joseph play?
- Can he come out?
All right. Don't go too far,
cos dinner's almost ready.
Wait for me! Wait for me!
Joseph! Don't go too far!
That ought to hold you
for a little while.
We thank our guest stars,
Curtis Mayfield, The Honeycombs,
and of course the Soul Train gang.
Be right where you are
next week when we return,
and you can bet your last money
itll be a stone gas, honey.
I'm Don Cornelius,
and as always we wish you love,
peace, and soul
Here comes the pitch,
and It comes In wide.
And the count now,
1 and 1 to Jackie Robinson...