My father told me if I was hard enough,
I wouldn’t break.
He lied.
Everything breaks.
Set!
Hey Roy,
are you okay ?
Yeah, hey!
29 36 60 All right.
Turn around. Touch the ground.
Get up. Everything gonna be ok.
What the hell’s that ?
My uncle.
I’m here.
What’s that accident?
Didn’t Peyton tell you?
An accident?
What are you saying?
Roy,
you-you look like the first time I saw Nelson.
He died. He got all smashed up, dead.
It was a train.
He was walking, 'cross the track.
We don't have all the details yet.
My boys.
My little bunnies.
Pink squirrel?
No, thank you.
I can't drink.
I could make you a virgin one.
It's just, um, I'm in training.
I see.
We all gotta get through these things somehow.
I can't believe it's an open casket.
I mean it's awful how he died.
Do you know, Mr. Chutney very well at all?
No, not really.
I gotta…
Sorry.
He used to call me his little king.
I'm his son.
Come on, babies.
He's on the risin'.
You ain't got none,
you might as well pull your hands out of there.
What the hell's going on?
Hard-on contest.
Bucks riding on the winner.
Hey, Chutney.
Why don't you come on over here and, uh,
drop trou.
Oh! No thanks, Russ.
I don't need to cir the jerk to long dick you.
Just ask your girlfriend!
Just ask you mom's pussy!
Pussy is right!
Your red neck daddy's pussy to vote!
They won't pay for your schoolin',
let alone your football!
You know, I would rather cut off my own damn arm,
then cut any of you boys.
But I’ve got to work.
There's no J.V. this year.
It's gone.
Now, some of you, will be varsity.
And some of you.
I posted the list outside.
See your name on that list,
be a good soldier,
and walk away.
Coach?
I think there might be a little problem with the list.
The list ?
Chutney, look at you.
You-you-you got no gumption.
You ain't angry enough.
And I-I ain't got room, for "ain't angry enough ".
Yeah, hey!
Roy Chutney.
Come on, dammit.
Football’s not where your life belongs.
Think of it as a blessing, it free's you up now.
You know, it's time to, to knuckle down, rebuild the corral,
get this ranch back in working order.
This ranch, mom?
This place is nothing like a ranch.
This "nothing"  is everything Nelson left me with.
This "nothing" and you.
This “nothing” and me, well...
I'm sorry you got stuck with me, mom.
That's not what I meant.
You didn't even come to the funeral, mom.
Well, our divorce was funeral enough for me.
Took you limp dicks long enough.
You call this a wood pile?
You call this tight?
It's a god damn health hazard!
It's loose!
It's all loose!
But, we spent all day on that!
Well, now you gonna spend all night doing it right.
Yeah, like hell, you gonna pay us.
Then we're gonna go downtown.
You're not going anywhere.
Lem!
Tracy!
Stop it!
So, what you gonna do?
Kill me?
Who'd feed ya?
Who'd buy ya Levi's?
Lem!
Somebody says they call me
Swinging the world by a tail
Bouncin' all over the white cloud
Killin' the blues
Hey, bro!
Are you okay?
What are you grinning at?
You, white boy,
getting all Paul Bunyan back at Lem's.
I'll tell you what was funny
was you and your dad doing the Appalachian boogie.
Hey. Lem's not my dad.
Neither was mine.
Yeah, I hear ya.
I only ever saw him at the football games.
It doesn't really matter.
Hard cheese about your father.
Hard fuckin' cheese.
My real pop,
he went after smoking some day.
And never came back.
Least he's still alive.
I hope to think he is.
I'll see him around somewhere.
I'll walk up and say "pop"
Can I hold a cig?
You know, all nonchalant like.
Then I'll kick his ass!
Do you ever tell yourself a story, Tracy?
You start seeing the future as it's gonna happen. And…
…everything just gets broken.
Whoa! Down boy, coming at ya!
Down boy, coming at ya!
Laugh it up!
Come on!
Chuckle butt!
Chut, chut, chut, chut, buddy! Hey!
No man, varsity only.
That shines are, uh, with our team spirit.
Give me a break, Russ, okay?
Sorry, Chutney.
Hey, it's nothing personal, you know?
It's just a ritual.
Personal? It's not even human.
Think I'm kidding, weak tit?
That's enough!
Does the baby want his bottle?
Yeah, fuck you.
Oh, yeah?
You got a bottle for me?
Are you okay, man?
You burned my fuckin' jacket!
What the shit?
Come on, fucker! Get up!
Whoa! What happened to the moonshine?
Fuckin' pussy.
Are you okay?
Hey, Roy!
Where’re you going, Roy?
Ladies and gentlemen it's Keno time.
So let's go.
Hey paper Blue Springs gazette.
Tomorrow's news today.
24!
Oh no, what did I drag my sleeves through this time?
I've only been here two hours, and look at how dirty I am.
Oh, shoot, Gretch' you're dirty long before you came in tonight.
Oh, Gid.
Hey, you ought to, uh,
get you some brains.
Excuse me?
Cow brains, bub.
Scrambled on up, with eggs.
Yeah, man's meal.
He needs them in eggs, Gretch', for my boy, Roy here.
Chutney, right? You are Roy Chutney?
Yeah. How'd you know that?
Uh, my name's Gideon Ferguson.
Gid to my friends.
Oh. And everybody's my friend.
I sell the paper, right man.
We get the paper at home.
Oh, we get the paper at home.
Now, Gid's not here trying to increase the circulation.
No.
I’ve seen you practice.
Uh, watch your football.
A long time.
Well, not long enough.
I got cut.
I know you did.
That's why Gid wants to jaw at ya.
Barn's throwing up a football team.
He wants gamers, from all over town.
Boys like you.
Well, boys… with touch.
Yeah.
Well, we're talking full on tackle football.
We're talking six-man.
Six-man, isn't like a ranch kid game?
Well, isn't that what you is, a ranch kid?
That's the last thing I am.
Oh, no, it ain't a thing to be shameful of.
Well, ranch kids are tough.
You have to be.
You raise a pet pig, then you kill it.
We-we don’t raise pigs.
Oh, well the point is,
town kids don't know if they're tough.
In six-man, in six-man, you got no place to hide.
No, you miss a tackle. And boom!
Yeah, scary to some kids, bub, it's scary!
Long night, that’s all.
No-no, that's all right. Shh, shh, shh.
This offer,
it ain't open to every swinging dick.
Come on.
Roy? You wanna shine?
You wanna watch motlow's pretty boys, from the stands?
Or you wanna be my quarterback?
What you got to loose?
See ya.
You all right, Ms. Bowser?
Yeah.
Just your ordinary everyday heartbreak.
Oh, is that all?
Well, I thought it might be something serious.
Now, we have 64 and that looks good.
This ain't my first rodeo, Chunt.
I hail from west Texas.
Six-man's a religion down there.
I speak it's tongues.
That's good.
Why me?
You got your daddy's blood.
And that's good blood.
You know-knew my dad?
I told you, Gid knows everybody.
Your daddy was a mighty fine ball player.
All state three years running.
He was a real…
sledgehammer, sledgehammer, yeah.
I've heard that before.
Course you only knew smash my arm.
He was just a…
tackle…
grunt…
like me.
But you,
Roy,
You're better than that.
Six-man, it takes smarts.
You get to run a gun, you get to think on your feet.
What do you get?
Oh, I get to coach again, bub.
Yeah. I get to be bull-goose.
Now I'll run my boys against any action in the state.
And if you sign, you got a cannon,
right there.
Boom, boom, boom.
Roy.
You can own this game.
You can have somethin'
that nobody ever gonna take away from you.
You're my lynchpin.
Without ya, I got no team.
You in?
Hey, Skyla.
Gid
Please bud,
will you stick me in?
Floyd! Come on, sit down.
5, we have a winner.
You look awful ragged.
Ragged, did you say?
“Ragged but right”, Riley Puckett, 1934.
Don't mind, Floyd.
His…his diabetes and his drinking
just disagree.
Folks call me Studebaker,
'cause I live in one.
But, my name's Floyd.
What do you go by, mister?
Roy.
He's Roy Chutney.
My new quarterback, right champ?
You know that's trouble sure and true kid.
Nothing but trouble.
Oh, “nothing but trouble”, Floyd, Lonnie Johnson, 1949.
So, how 'bout it, son? You in?
Yeah!
Atta boy!
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir.
All right, listen up.
In six-man,
you never stop moving.
It's high-octane, hardscrabble.
You got to be,
outlaw, out there.
You got to be Renegade.
Let's get friendly.
Over there, this is, uh,
Quirky Lovoy.
He'll put you on the back of your helmet.
This is Josh Coudrow.
He's our special teams.
Now this is, uh,
Jeremy Areala.
Got
Dave Bishop here.
A hard time, getting a helmet over that hat.
Down there,
Warren Hudson.
We got us,
Benton Toranjos.
Mr. wrong way, Toranjo.
And Lester and Earl Bucket.
Now they're new to football,
but their old man owns this field.
So be nice.
Now, Gibbs, he played six-man,
right? At Valley Christian.
Yeah.
'til he left the team for, um,
well religious reasons.
What's that?
I called the coach a cock sucker.
And hidden over here, this is Roy Chutney.
He's our big boss with the hot sauce.
He's our bull-roar, our deepback.
Gid, uh.
This helmets are ancient.
Oh, be broadminded, boy.
It's not the helmet, it's what fits inside.
All right, where's that ball?
Okay, now deepback.
He's just a, he's just a quarterback but don't get the hike.
He gets the ball through a-a hand off or a pitch.
That way he's always got the option to throw or to run.
That's it, Roy.
Run it again. Run it again, keep it going.
Now, all of you.
You're always eligible to receive a pass.
So always be on your ready.
Now remember chums.
In six-man, a broken play may just be your best bet.
Go, go, go, that's it!
Yeah, you got it!
Let's play some football.
What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing?
Now, get down there.
Now, hike, stand back.
Come on, come on.
Strip it away, strip it away. Strip it away.
Oh! Now it's play it.
That's it.
Hey Roy, take your office. I’m uh…
I got some business needs tending too.
All right, Gid.
All right, let's run it again!
Hey, Jute.
Been a long time.
You got that buying money?
Yes indeedy, you got me some games?
Oh, we got you some games, Gid.
Scheduled your team in all the off slots.
All the by-weeks, huh?
Yeah, that's what I reckoned. Here you go.
'Course we still have another problem.
Oh yeah, what’s it?
Yeah, I'll be blunt, Gid.
That trouble you got into up at Hishem.
That boy that died.
You know that wasn't my fault.
Yeah, now don't get your jaws…
Jute, it's blasphemy.
I did my best.
Yeah, hell I know you did!
But, it’s just it…
Yeah they're asking for some insurance.
Some insurance?
Yeah. You mean, cash?
Every game?
Every game.
Cash on the barrelhead.
Louvin Brothers, 1954.
What?
Nothing but a song in my head.
We're gonna whop you up in geralee.
Well, I don't know about that,
but you're more than welcome to try.
We got us some games.
We got us some games!
Come in here, everybody in. Everybody in!
And one last thing!
The slaughter rule!
If either team gets ahead by 45 points, they call the game.
But, Gideon Ferguson, he never been slaughter ruled.
And I aim to keep it that way.
Okay?
Today, I was in uh, I was in ceramics class.
And up comes Motlow.
“So what have we made today, Mr. Two Dogs”
And I said “ma-many things for flowers”
“Mr. Two Dogs, that-that's not a vase.”
“It’s a water pipe.”
"Nuh-huh, that-that's not a water pipe."
“Today, Mr. Motlow,
we had made a bung.”
No, you didn’t!
Yeah, he went ape shit.
“Two Dogs ! Your piece of reservation! Trash!”
“Get out of my room. Pronto tonto”
Yeah. That racist fuck.
So I decked him.
You hit him?
You'll see I left a big old clay mark on his face.
Oh, then he, then he kicked me out of the team.
Perfect!
Now you can go play six-man with me.
Yeah?
Does your old lady go for younger men?
Shut up.
Hi, Mrs. Chutney.
Hi, guys.
Smells good.
Thanks.
Okay, if I stay for dinner?
Oh, of course.
Mind you this isn't all for tonight
this is two weeks worth.
Can I stay for two weeks then?
Two weeks! You just got here.
Roy, look
I’ve got to come back to Montreal.
So, you know
a three day layover in Montreal.
And Francis got tickets for the hockey game and…
Francis?
Which one is he?
He's the rancher one? The professor one?
He's the pilot one, honey.
The pilot one.
Mind you, you better fix that corral by the time I get back, or else.
Or else what?
Or else they'll be spankings.
Oh. Count me in.
I got it.
Hello.
Hey, champ’, you got a minute?
Hey.
How you doing?
Yeah, I wanted to jaw jack with you 'bout the game.
Okay.
Yeah, we got leave 10:00 a.m. sharp.
We're going up to Augusta, weather gets kind of squirrelly, so, uh...
you come prepared, eh?
You got it.
Okay.
What?
It's uh, it's about your rent.
By, Tuesday the government check get in.
Nothing doing 'til Tuesday.
Just asking.
Just telling.
One more thing, Roy.
Can I count on you for a ride?
Yeah, for Saturday sure.
No, I mean every game. Can I, uh,
can I, uh, can I depend on you for that? Can I trust you?
Yeah, sure.
10:00 A.m. sharp.
See you then.
That’s our football coach?
Yep.
Big Gid. Big  Gid. Big Gid.
Man I heard that guy's some kind of a pre-vert.
A pre-vert?
Yeah.
Well, Lem said he's a funny.
Well, Lem don't know his ass from his elbow.
Right.
Come on.
Is he? Is he kind of funny?
Sure wanna welcome all you folks.
For being here today, we're sure lookin' forward to this football game.
Um, if you noticed over there, the cheerleaders having a cupcake sale today.
I wanted to congratulate the Anderson's on the birth of their new son.
It's nice to have another boy in town.
Six man-football, we need all the boys we can get.
We're really looking forward to this game, between the Elks and the Renegades.
No that ain't a hike.
That ain't a hike, that's a pass.
He's gonna pull a reverse!
It's a reverse!
It's alrigh’. We're okay.
We just gotta buck up now.
We’ve got to … play real.
West Texas pig iron, wing set.
We'll spread it wide in the flats, cross screen.
And we're gonna lead block.
You get me, huh?
Now, Roy,
you jack like that,
out of the pocket too soon.
I need you to take a hit one time, okay?
I need you to be my, alpha wolf out there.
Yeah, that's it.
Hey, Benton?
Don't just look pretty, you gotta bust me a seam, okay?
Trayce
Coudrow.
You're my wings out there, so fly, all right?
Right.
Let's double up on two. Ready?
Let's do this!
Get him!
Yeah, here we go.
So close!
Go, Tracy!
All right?
Come on- come on- come on.
All right, is his mama or papa around?
Okay, he's okay, he's all right.
He's a tough boy. He's a tough boy.
Come on.
Yeah, don't let your head get too swelled, huh?
Too late!
Go! Go, Two Dogs! Move outta the way!
Yeah, how do you like the Renegades now?
That’s it! That’s it!
That’s it!
That’s my sneaky sneaky boys.
Yes, sir! Yeah!
What are you doing?
having a spaz attack?
I'm warming up the old larynx.
Singing tomorrow, genuine juke joint music.
What? You sing?
Is a frog's ass water tight?
Yeah, me and Floyd we gotta gig Saturday night.
Why don't you come on out?
Uh, tomorrow?
I don't know.
You know that gal you was making eyes at the other night.
Ms Skyla?
What the girl? The girl at the diner?
Well, you bet your sweet cherry pie she'll be there.
Yeah?
Howdy, partner.
Hey.
What can I give for you?
Whisky
with some water and some ice.
A ditch?
What?
The drink you ordered is called a ditch.
Is it a ditch water irrigation…?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah I didn't know if you knew…
What are you ? A rancher or something?
I'd say you're the cowpoke.
Don't I know you?
Uh, Pink squirrel?
Right, the funeral thing.
Sorry.
I keep forgetting Mr. Chutney was your father.
He kept forgetting too.
So, how you holding up?
I-i-i could, I could really
use that Ditch.
'kay.
Are you, um,
breaking training tonight?
Hey!
I’ve just finished my shift.
And I gotta close you out.
Oh, it’s okay.
Come on!
Check out in my ass.
Where did you learn all that?
It’s just uh
it’s just I've always been my mom's dancing dummy.
Oh, you are no dummy.
You're more of a sweetie.
I’m sorry.
I just mean
just that your eyes aren't hard.
They’re more serious,
just like they're hurt.
That's just the smoke, that's all.
Gid can sing!
Oh, you know Gideon?
Oh, yeah.
I came here to see him.
Really want to see you, but.
Do you wanna dance?
No, um
Slow songs are
Like whisky in milk?
Uh, that drink’s called the Cowboy.
Oh, it is?
Who drinks Cowboys?
Old-timers mostly.
Guys like, Floyd over there?
Yeah.
Poor Floyd has a hard time keeping his cowboys in line.
You can't just come up here. Come on, come on, okay?
You can't abandon me. You…
You can't ignore me…
‘cause of this…
this boy!
Floyd, will you just god damn sit down!
Floyd, you're drunk.
Just sit your butt down and shut up.
Sit down. Sit down.
Floyd, just…
Whoa, you're getting your money's worth tonight, folks!
Let's do something a little quicker.
Go on.
Go help Gid out.
Give me a call some time.
It’s 5, 6, 9 …
It tickles?
Yeah.
Call me.
Okay.
Good-bye.
Hey, Floyd!
Floyd you in here?
No?
Floyd?
Mr. Studebaker?
Hey!
They're worried about ya.
You kind of ran off back there.
Come on.
Oh, officer I didn't, I didn't see how fast I was going.
Gid, send you after me?
You his errand boy?
I'm not Gid's anything.
It's football boys like you what shrunk him down.
When I met him, he was tiny.
Only yay-big.
He's been getting back to full size.
But he still got inside troubles.
I don't, I don't know what you're talking about.
He likes to think he looks after me, but it's the other way around.
“Rank strangers”, Albert E. Brumley, 1954.
That's a good song.
Yeah.
Will you take me to my Maybelle.
She's parked up here a ways.
Oh. Oh.
Maybelle's your car?
Maybelle's my everything.
The police are always trying to move me along.
The hardest part is trying to stay clean.
Folks stare when I change clothes.
Free show. Free show.
I'm just trying to square things a-okay with the lord.
That sounds like a good plan.
Will you stick me?
Mister.
Please?
I can't do me, myself.
Yeah, okay, sure.
Aim away from the blood.
Shoot, give me a heart attack.
Blood you say?
That's easy!
“Will Jesus wash he bloodstains from your hands”, remember?
Oh, of course I remember.
Crazy monkey.
Hazel Dickens, 1964.
Go on, Roy.
Just ease her on in.
Floyd,
you are your own worst enemy.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
My weakness is stronger than I am.
Sorry to drag you away from your gal.
That's okay.
I got her number.
Yeah, good for you.
Right here.
No, you didn't.
Damn it!
Ain't that just kiss my ass?
I lost my gig,
you lost your girl.
You can still make a mark on the night.
You know, my dad used to do this all the time?
He used to tell me stories about rabid freights and
going out to Canada, each spring,
or, out to winachi for apple harvest.
Lord knows I know that circuit.
Yeah?
Yes.
He said it's how he first came to Blue Springs.
He just sort of, just got off to stretch his legs and never left.
You know, maybe he wasn't trying
to kill himself.
Maybe, he was just
leaving.
Just trying to go back the way he came.
Just
Just judged the timing wrong.
Yeah.
Only Hanks I know live in the jukebox.
Well you got, Hank Williams, of course.
And, uh, Hank Thompson
F 1 and F 2, and
Hank Snow
E
I mean he's the-he's the ultimate ranger.
Do you know him?
Oh, gosh.
I'll make you a deal.
You tell me what the problem is,
and I'll tell you how to fix it.
I guess the only thing you could do is lie to me.
You could
tell me a story.
that you
are not from here.
Okay.
And um,
and you're gonna take me far, far away.
I'm not from around here.
And, uh
my truck’s parked out back.
And I think I got enough gas to get us to Moose Jaw.
Oh, that boy.
Have you boys seen your coach today?
That's it, forfeit, red!
Forfeit, red!
Victory lap, gentlemen.
Yeah, you better run you chicken shits!
Smear the queer- smear the queer!
Cannonball comin' at you.
You, lovebirds, get a room.
Hey, hey, hey, Bison!
Give it up, ya'll!
Bison, more like Buffalo chips.
Yeah.
Paper, Blue Springs gazette! Get your paper.
Paper, Blue Springs gazette!
Yeah.
Tomorrow's news tonight.
I'm gonna go see a man about a horse.
Hey, paper, paper!
Look at this tomorrow's new tonight.
Bison win divisional’s.
That’s right.
Give me the damn paper.
What's the idea?
Hi, Gid.
Yeah, hey!
You gettin' all hoity-toity on me?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about you god damn supposed to pick me up, before the game!
Yeah.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I wanted to talk to you about that, I just…
I was running late and my-my rig she.
Oh.
You a liar, Roy?
You connin' old Gid?
Okay.
I don't know what… I was, I was with Skyla.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, girls got no truck with me.
You and me, we had a deal.
Yeah, Gid, but,
I'm your quarterback, not your taxi.
You cost us that game.
And that game cost me plenty.
And I'm really sorry.
It won't happen again, I promise.
Okay?
I'm gonna get back.
What?
You're having yourself quite a time, right?
Yeah.
I guess you could say that.
Say it. I can smell it.
Yeah.
You got the thirst, and soon it's got you.
I've seen it happen to my mama.
And I seen it happen to Floyd.
And there won't be no one what's a stranger to you.
And there won't be no one who can trust you, either!
Cause you are poisoned in your gut!
And you're poisoned in your liver, and you're poisoned in your heart.
And you're poisoned in your brain.
Hell, Gid. It's a couple of beers, that's all.
Come here. Wait.
Gid's got something he wants to show you.
Here.
Gid, what the fuck?
No wait a minute, Roy. God damn it.
Roy, just, would you just quit squirming!
What?!
Look, I just wanted to show you my scar.
There!
Now, ain't it a beaut', huh?
Yeah, I was born with a large heart.
Rittled up veins.
Yeah, my mama, she pickled me.
She pickled me up good,
when I was still a pup, up inside her.
And there’s a few beers for you.
Now, what about you, huh, Roy?
You committed?
Are you trustworthy, Roy?
Yes.
It's not possible to live in this world without trust, Roy.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Mr. Ferguson, can I get a paper?
What?
Can I get a paper?
A paper,
yep.
Yo, Chutney!
You see the game tonight?
No when we won.
It was a bitch though man we lost Devo and Tulliver.
It's too bad. It's a rough game.
I'm telling you there's a spot on the team for you.
For divisionals.
I mean, it's not backfield, but it's varsity.
I've something better going on.
Hey, come on, Roy.
We need you.
No, thank you.
Nothing personal.
You'd rather play for him?
Oh, I think it's very personal, Roy.
Russ, don't.
You hear that, boys?
Chutney, here, would rather play for his fuck buddy.
What's the name of your team again?
Was it
the blow jobbers, huh?
Pole smokers, wasn't it?
Uh-huh, no, not this time chief.
Fuck off!
Leave him alone, fuckin’ asshole!
Come on!
Roy!
Get my boys outta! I said, get out!
You stay out of this, Gid.
This isn't your concern anymore!
Get out of here.
Go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Kiss it better.
Women get all wet, for a black eye!
Yeah?
Yep.
You bet your ass that
Skyla's got some wild in her.
Is she your girl, Roy?
I don’t know.
I can't really tell ya.
Ohhhh. You can tell old Gid.
You got ya some, didn't ya?
Oh yeah.
You got you some, sweet gherkin.
Yeah, some pop tart.
What happened to that paw of yours?
I didn't see you land no punches.
Oh, yeah and why's that, Gid?
Hey!
That was my fight!
I didn't need you to butt in.
No? What’s this?
I was just looking out for the team.
Fine.
But, I can take care of myself, all right?
Oh, sure you can bub.
Yeah, guess I'm just a mother hen, sometimes.
Come upstairs we're gonna retape this before the game.
But we gotta, um, meet Tracy.
Well, it won't take but a jiffy.
Yeah, sorry things ain't balmy.
Didn't think it'd get this cold, this early.
Cold, it…
It don't bother me much but…
well, Floyd he don't got the skin for it.
Oh, hell,
I got manners enough to fed grits to a grizzly.
You, uh, you
want some mud?
Some what?
Some hot pip before the game?
Sure, yeah.
Hey, Hank Snow.
Yeah, what?
Oh! Those are my chums, Roy.
What all I come home to.
Yeah, a song you love will never let you down.
Okay.
Let's see about that hand, come on.
Sit down over here.
So, tell me.
Two Dogs, how do you figure?
He had nine stitches, in his neck.
Russ had on his class ring.
Yeah , Russ,
that punk's crying to mama now.
Put the fear of Gid into him!
Just shake it off.
Hey, I know…
what Russ said about you, the way what he called you.
That's not the first time I've heard that.
Well, listen, Chutney,
get this clear.
I ain't a man who wants other men.
I just like being around men,
in their company.
It's what I know.
It's all I've ever known.
But you go for women, right?
Just 'cause, just 'cause Tracy and all them think…
Well, let them think it!
You and me, we know better ?
Yeah.
Would you have come here, if
if you thought that?
Why did you come here, Roy?
Well, 'cause we gotta game, remember?
We got a game, 'member!
Listen.
You don't trust me.
And you never will,
Unless I give you my trust first.
So, I'm giving you it.
Just don’t let me down!
Again.
I won't.
Thank you.
Well, the only truth is
I’ve never been with a woman.
And I ain't paid straight up for her.
And whores don't count.
Now/or, do they?
Oh I’m a man.
But
I ain’t never been
kissed.
I ain't ever been with nobody.
Oh, Russ, he thinks he knows something about being a man.
He doesn't!
No child knows what a man is.
No child can say a damn thing about me.
No child, no man has that right.
Do you think Tracy will know that we're up here?
Roy,
you know much about roughnecking?
Roughnecking?
Ever know anybody that worked the oil fields?
You know the hits I took?
You know the miles, the, uh,
the hours, the hours of my life?
Tell me something, you remember-you remember what, uh,
that first, uh,
that first, uh, good hit.
First good stick, come here!
What are ou talking about? ‘bout this !
What'd that feel like, bud?
It wakes you up!
Hell yes, it wakes you up!
Good morning!
Gets you all fired up, eh?
Feels good!
Yeah.
It puts blood in mouth!
It puts blood in your mouth.
That's right!
It tastes good, don't it?
Sure it do.
In my life,
I can't put it back the way it was.
Mingus, Marathon, and whore in Odessa.
Odessa, god damn, Odessa was the worst.
Moxy Ferguson, have you ever heard of her?
My mother.
Yep, my old lady.
She's a crooner.
Couple of her records around here.
She put me in an orphanage, Roy.
She was a god damn tramp!
Alcohol ruined her!
And something else,
I don't know what it was.
Something,
something,
money,
maybe,
pride, I won't know what it was,
ruined your father.
But you, Roy,
you aren't ruined.
You can hold on to that taste, that blood in your mouth.
You can use it, to hit back, Roy.
You can hit back.
Hit back harder!
That’s the way you do it, Roy!
You hit back, harder, Roy like that. You see that!
Hit back harder! Like that!
That's how you do it!
All right?
You’re gonna
You’re gonna hear
some stories
about me.
Stories about a boy
who had got killed.
Only he didn't get killed.
He died.
He just died.
He's still with me. He’s…
Where's your father, Roy?
He's dead, Gid.
Yeah, well sure he is but, where is he?
He's dead, Gid, he's buried.
Roy, no, he's here, Roy.
He's your fear.
Now you can use that fear, Roy.
Or you can let it eat your heart.
You comprende amigo?
Yeah, okay.
Then, prove it.
Good.
Get by me.
I don't wanna do this, Gid.
Come on! Get by me!
Gid, I don’t wanna do this.
I'll stick you. No, no, no, no, I'll stick ya.
This is stupid.
It is not stupid!
Come on, use your fear now!
Oh, you want it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, shake yourself loose. Come on.
Hut, hut, hut, hut!
No, now don't throw your legs out like a little girl!
Use your hips, Roy!
Use your hips!
Now is that it ?
Is that your best go?
Yep.
You win, okay?
Okay.
No, no, no.
You can let me go now.
Why did they kill my, my beautiful boy?
Will you stop touching me, please?
Please, get off of me!
Just get the fuck, off of me!
Damn it!
What I just…
Oh, Jesus, I don’t…
I didn't mean nothing by it! I just,
I just thought maybe you’re someone to
to hold you.
Oh I don’t know what God did to me. I just…
hold, see…
What’s that ?
Roy, come on.
Okay?
What you're afraid of ?
'fraid of a little rough housing?
Men do that, you know?
Athletes!
Yes they do. They hug each other!
And they hi-five!
You know! They slap asses.
It's different Gid!
No!
It's different and you know it is!
No, it ain't different!
And you know it is!
It ain’t different.
It ain't different! Roy!
If you just trusted me!
If you trusted me, Roy!
Hey.
If you just…
What's going on in here?
A little game of wild hared grab ass.
Up yours, Two Dogs.
You're fuckin' late, you fuckin' drive.
Roy.
Oh, it's okay, Two Dogs. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
This place has seen better days.
No, it hasn’t.
How would you know?
Duh Chutney,
I grew up here.
Let's go Trace.
Oh, come on, let’s get this game going.
Hey, fellas, you know what, this ain't Texas.
All right, all right, come in here.
Come in here. All right.
Clean slate now.
Uh, forget it ever happened.
So, uh, I'm uh, I'm soft on you.
You're soft on them.
Our new games, gonna be, uh, smash mouth.
Anvil formation, you drive a fish down their throat!
Two Dogs, you with us?
100%, rock and roll!
They're too proud.
Keep them in the hole,
they'll give up.
Fuck with their heads,
and you'll fuck with their hearts.
All right.
Go for their heart.
Go for their heart, let's have some pride.
Let's have some pride!
Let’s have some pride!
You got that renegade pride? Yes, woo!
You got that renegade pride! Good god, yes, woo!
When I say renegade you say pride!
Renegade! Pride! Renegade! Pride !
Renegade! Pride! Renegade! Pride!
You got that renegade pride!  Good god, yes, woo!
When I say renegade you say pride!
Renegade! Pride! Renegade! Pride !
Renegade, renegade! Pride! Pride!
You got that renegade pride!
Yes!
No you can't take nothing away from my boy.
No you can't put a shadow on his side.
Oh, that's right! A barrel of laughs!
Barrel of monkeys!
Yeah, well my boys might get awful proud tonight!
So awful god damn happy!
You’re dinner’s on me !
Get out here, when you're ready!
Good game fellas.
Hey. Tracy,
good war cuz.
You know, you should stay here tonight.
Tell us your tales of living among the of- of living among the napequans.
Don’t…
Don't make me drive home alone with him.
Why? Afraid he might try to get lucky!
Oh, very funny, fuck you.
No.
It's just…he's different, when you're alone with him.
He’s just like uh uh…
He's so vulnerable and stuff.
I just don't really feel like hearing his life story again, okay?
All right.
Thanks, Waylin, no I can’t do it.
I gotta chauffeur that old, funny boy on home.
Weiner boy, you mean.
Yeah.
Weiner, boy? Why-why you guys call him that, huh?
Uh…
We caught him lookin' at our wieners.
Let's go!
Get in.
Get your ass in gear, let's go.
It's a long ride home, Gid. You'll freeze.
Get your ass in gear boy.
It's okay.
It's so embarrassing.
It's not embarrassing.
It's sexy to me.
Hold still, okay?
Hey?
Are you still here?
What?
I want some pancakes.
Careful. Make sure it's still on.
God, I hate these things.
Can you shut the door, please?
Why?
It's really intimate. I don't think I know you that well.
You know me well enough to fuck me,
but not enough to watch me pee?
Haven't spent much time around women, that's all.
Well, that's for sure.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means I'm frustrated, Roy.
Well, look it, I know I was fast, but we can try.
No, Roy, no, I'm not frustrated with sex, okay?
I'm just…
I’m just frustrated with boys who think sex isn't intimate.
And how many boys is that?
You know, Roy, I think I liked you better
when I thought you were someone else.
Who'd you think I was?
Someone a little older.
Well, I'm working on that, as fast as I can.
You can’t…
Don't rush it, Roy.
I mean I would love to see who you grow into,
but I'm just afraid he's turning into out
to be someone I'd hate myself for falling for,
you know, someone hard,
someone who acts all cocksure.
I don't even know what that means.
What are you saying?
Are you saying that what we just did didn't even feel good?
I felt good, Roy.
It’s just it didn’t…
It didn't feel right.
I suppose it felt right with, uh…
what's his bucket?
Zander.
And yes,
yes it did.
It must of.
I can't take another winter here.
I think you should go.
What can I get you, hon?
Double portion de red eye.
Isn't, Skyla supposed to work this shift?
Not this shift or any shift.
What?
Listen kid, what she means is,
she bought a bus ticket from me,
for Seattle, for tomorrow.
Hey Floyd, come on!
Come on.
Ha ha sexy !
Hurry up, Roy!
Lem says we can clear 300 bucks easy.
Are you sure we're not gonna get caught?
Sure, I'm sure.
Come on, now three at a time weak tit.
Come on, come on, come on, some time today would be good.
Chutney, get your head outta your ass.
Come on, baby.
Come on, bab.
Come on,  girl. You can do it, come on.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm gonna find you a room at the mission.
You outta straighten things on up.
“Straighten up and fly right”, Nat King Cole trio, 1949.
That's right.
Sleep tight.
Ever since we played up in hardview,
I've been thinking and, uh,
it's not worth it.
Tracy,
You and I are supposed to be together.
Yeah, hey!
You can't just quit on me.
You know quit, leave, what the fuck ever.
The team really needs you.
I need you.
Look, I've out grown this little six-man scrub league.
What?
Yeah, then there's that whole thing with you and Gid.
What thing?
You know how Gid's always, creaming his shorts over us?
Gid's weird man.
Yeah.
Okay.
But, he's harmless.   He's just all…
He’s just all bruised up inside, you know?
Lem says Gid's dangerous.
You know, he got some kid killed up in Hishem.
Lem doesn't know a jack shit about jack shit!
Yeah, he knows about you cozying up in those freight cars with, Gid.
Man, I can explain it now.
I don't even wanna hear it man.
Shut your pie hole!
Let's get these god damn, trees outta here!
Like father, like son.
Look,
I told you
Lem's not my father.
Least I can trust him, not to bend me
over some of the fuck ass.
No, but you can trust him to give you
your nightly smack down.
No wonder you quitting you coward.
You don't know a damn thing about my life! Napequan!
Get up, Roy!
You, kids hold it right there!
God damn snowplow!
Damn!
Francis?
It's, Roy, ma.
Roy?
You get home, right this minute.
I can't.
You're not going to believe this.
I don't wanna hear about it!
Zumack, well she's gone.
She got out where you jerry-rigged that corral!
And Francis, is so mad, he won't- he won't even speak to me!
He-he left. He just…
He just up and left.
My pregnant horse is somewhere up there in that blizzard.
And…
And now god! God damn you Roy Chutney,
you get on home!
Hi. It’s Skyla, leave me a message.
I'll call you back.
Sky, it’s me, pick up the phone.
Would you pick up the phone?
Damn it! Sky, I know you're there.
I really need to talk.
Go grab your mother.
Taking those trees to Pocatello tonight.
No, fuck that noise.
I'm going to see about, Roy.
You go down there, and they'll throw your stupid ass in jail!
And then they'll come after me.
Yeah, I hope to hell they would!
Tracy, stop it.
Let him be.
Let him go!
Tracy, Tracy please baby!
Lem! Lemmy.
What,
Lemmy ?
Just go!
Are you his father or his guardian?
I ain’t exactly his mother.
Uh, he's my coach, madam.
Open.
Thank you, Gid.
I'll pay you back, I promise.
Okay Roy.
Me and Floyd were hoping to…
go up to Georgetown lake.
Catch us some fish before the game.
You’ll drive us up there?
We'll call things even-steven.
Sure.
Yeah?
Yeah. It's a deal.
Hey, Floyd!
Hey.
Floyd!
You monkey, wake up.
We got us a fishing partner!
Sleeping beauty, wake up!
Come on, Floyd, wake up!
Floyd, gee.
Go get us a hot meal.
Hey!
Gid!
What?
I don't think he is…
Oh, no, no, no, look out, look out, look out.
Floyd come on!
Come on!
Is he breathing?
Okay, I got him.
Oh, just breathe.
Oh, Floyd.
Stupid.
Oh, Floyd don't go.
Good morning, Saint Regis, Cordinlaine, Kellogg,
Spokane, Walla Walla.
All points west.
Let’s go.
All points west. This for both of you?
Yep.
Yeah, okay.
All points west, huh?
Sounds optimistic.
Going anywhere in particular, or you just going?
Island, it's supposed to be beautiful.
You're not okay, are you?
Just lie to me ‘cause I…
Tell me you're not going far.
Tell me you're gonna come back.
I did lie to you.
In a way, I guess.
I was home last night, when you called me.
I’m sorry. I'm…
not much help to you, am I?
You're such a help, that I want.
I'm gonna go.
I know.
Mom are you alone?
Mom are you okay?
Oh Floyd!
That’s what Floyd… He
He caught a 11 pound squaw fish out here.
I'm hardly strong enough to reel her in.
Christ, he was so happy.
Didn’t have the heart to tell him squaw fish is trash fish.
No, it's no good for eating.
Oh, it’s all…
All grease and bones, that's all.
Are you a wayfaring, Floyd?
Oh, yeah, Gid.
“Wayfaring pilgrim”, Almeda Riddle, 1932.
Are you drifting, Floyd?
Not “drifting too far from the shore” [Bill Monroe].
Where are you going?
“I’m going back to Jericho” [Doc Watson and Clarence Ashley].
Thank you.
Hehere.
Hey why don't you have some of this.
No.
Come on, come on, come on.
Roy, you still don't trust me son.
After all of everything.
I think it's time you told me about, Hishem.
Hishem?
Yep.
The boy in the picture on your wall.
What happened to him?
Oh, Roy, he's just…
He’s just some scrawny, toe-headed
kid.
Come on. Look at this.
Tackle packed.  We got a big game.
Gid, Gid!
Don't lie to me.
All right.
His name's Jody.
He was a real sweet fullback.
Yeah, he looked me straight in the eye,
just like you.
He had wide shoulders
and softest hands.
I ain't ever known
natural grace myself with that boy
Well, he'd catch that ball
with half the field.
We had a team picnic,
up on, uh, Kicking Horse lake.
And maybe on this old boat.
Way out there.
That’s it
And this shittin' boat,
it sunk.
It just sunk.
My rough boy
My boy,
My beautiful boy
he,
he kept hold of the boat.
He went
down with it.
Yeah, reached down after him.
I should have kept going.
I should have just died,
trying to save that boy.
Then you'd both be dead, Gid.
Well.
It's be better than, uh,
living with him gone.
If he hadn't died, he'd still have left ya.
What were you doing with him?
What were you doing with him, out there on that boat, Gid ?
What was I doing?
We were boating, Roy.
Roy, we were on a damn boat, across the damn lake.
How 'bout that? Is that so bad?
It wasn't so good for Jody, was it?
Don’t you understand?
You remind me of him.
You’re both alive.
Spring water is
something better than
what it moves through.
Well, I'm not him!
And he's not me!
And he should have learned to swim, he should have known that much!
And so should you!
Let's get outta here.
I'm freezing my ass off.
Go!
Set!
Hike!
Oh, Roy.
What the hell you thinkin' huh?
Throwin' a widow maker out there, where's you head?
My head's just about ripped off out there.
Without Tracy…
Well, welcome to the world!
Get the hell back out there!
And stop your whining!
Stick 'em good, saw 'em off!
Hey! You get yours you little, puke!
Come on!
Let's go! I want it! I want it!
You little punk!
Oh, lord.
These poor
pissants.
They ain't so tough.
We gotta break them down.
Kill them.
They'll slaughter rules us.
In Texas, they’ll that
mercy rule.
Same thing, either way.
Yeah, hey !
Right!
Let's go with twin sweep, right!
GJS
Well, call them then.
Pitch after pass.
Yeah, but don't give it up too late.
Or, you're one to talk.
I'm here ! Ain't I?
Yeah, hey!
All right.
Twin sweep right on one, on one.
Ready?
Break.
Whoa, all right!
Go, Tracy!
Good job, buddy, good job.
That's it. That’s it! Don't get hurt, give hurt.
Keep giving Two Dogs the ball.
They won't know what from what!
What the hell is Tracy doing, man?
Counting coo.
That’s it. Just break yourself where you are.
All right, big daddy!
Are you okay?
My neck.
Hey! Get an ambulance over here!
Okay, all right, easy bud.
Take it easy, all right?
Don’t move, okay ?
Get over here!
One, two, three!
What they say, Gid?
Oh, well they said thatTrace took a bad shot to the neck.
And they said strong kid can survive it.
Tracy's strong as they come.
Sure took it like a man.
Oh, it got so god dang, dark.
They a hack away from the slaughter rule, anyways.
How 'bout we just, uh,
well we call it a night, huh?
We just all go on home, and get warm huh?
Hey.
Those fuckers, took Tracy out on purpose.
It wasn't on purpose. It's football.
And so what? We should lay down and die?
No, I don't want anybody else getting hurt.
But we don't get hurt.
We give hurt. 'member?
No, not tonight we don't. We ain't go the man power for it.
Yes, we do.
If we stop playing like children,
and we start playing like men, we do.
Easy champer, look we did our best.
There ain't no shame in getting beat.
What ever happened to hit back harder?
No, no it doesn't always work that way.
Yes, it does, work that way!
Cannon ball, coming at you.
Cannon ball! Cannon ball! Comin’ at you!
Roy. Roy.
You got that Renegade pride? Yes, woo!
You got hat renegade pride? Good god, yes!
Roy!
When I say renegade you say pride.
Renegade, pride!  Renegade, pride!
When I say renegade,  you say pride.
Come on!
Get him outta here!
Renegade- pride!
Roy!
You see?
It works that way!
Unless you're a coward?
Men know when to walk away. Just quit acting like a punk.
You're the punk, Gid.
I've seen you cry.
I know what you are.
Oh.
What's that you said to Gid?
I said you’re a coward.
Little pussy!
Now, is that what you think of Gid?
That's what I think of you.
I bet you was better than that, Roy.
I thought,
me and you
had some trust.
I can see right through you, Roy.
You ain't tough.
I'll show you tough.
Everyone knows
that you're a sugar tit!
You see!
There's bastards enough in this world, Roy.
Bastards
and they'll shit all over a mama's boy like you.
You gotta show 'em Roy!
Gid!
I trusted you. I trusted you, Roy!
Show me you have the balls to get fucked in this life.
Show me, Roy!
That's it.
That's it, Roy.
Help me up.
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay, oh I'm sorry.
You are sorry.
You're a sorry-ass queer.
Roy.
And I'm sick of it.
Roy
Did you hear that?
Roy.
He's a sorry-ass queer!  And I'm sick of his
bullshit!
Roy, don't quit on me.
Roy
don't leave me out here all alone.
Fuckin' pathetic!
Don't leave me alone.
Roy.
Don't leave me here.
Don’t!
What?
Fuckin' touch me.
I won't touch you. I won't touch ya.
No, I won't hurt ya.
Gid ain't never hurt nobody, okay?
This
Roy
This ain't you.
You ain't hard.
Roy.
I'm hard enough!
Roy. I…
I know you're joshing old Gid, huh?
You see, I'm laughing.
Roy, I'm laughing.
You see this. I'm laughing.
I thought we had us a deal, Roy!
Roy!
I thought we had a deal!
I'm sorry.
My dad used to call me his little king.
Dad wasn't trying to leave, was he?
He wasn't trying to hop that freight.
No.
He was just
ending.
But, a king wouldn't leave.
Would he?
Gid!
Everything breaks down.
Everything gets against to me.
Gid.
Hey !
Get up!
Come on!
Time to get up.
Get up!
Gid?
Is that you, Studebaker?
No, no, no.
It’s me.
Roy.
My old buddy.
You came back for old, Gid.
But why?
Why?
I know.
I know, I did.
Come on.
Okay.
Here we go.
That's it.
Yeah, hey?
Yeah, hey!
My boy.
My friend, Roy.