[ SKATEBOARDING ]
[ BIRDS CAWING ]
[ TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
>> [ SINGING IN SPANISH ]
>> HEY.
>> I CLOCKED YOU IN ALREADY.
>> COOL.
>> GET ANY SLEEP? [ CHUCKLES ]
>> BARELY.
>> YEAH. ME, TOO.
YEAH, THAT PLACE SO WASN'T WORTH
IT.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
>> THERE WAS ONLY THAT ONE CUTE
ONE.
>> [ SIGHS ] TELL ME ABOUT IT.
$33 DOWN THE DRAIN.
>> [ Chuckling ] YEAH.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY I TALK
TO WOMEN IN THIS TOWN.
>> COME ON, MAN.
>> I'M SERIOUS. IT'S POINTLESS.
AW, SHIT.
[ GROANS ]
[ ENGINE SPUTTERS ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> GOOD MORNING, LOS ANGELES.
IT'S 68 DEGREES OUT, 6:37 IN
THE A.M., AND LOOKING
BEAUTIFUL, AS ALWAYS, OUT
THERE.
SUNSHINE, CLEAR SKIES, AND
PERFECT POOL WEATHER ALL WEEK
LONG IN THE ENTERTAINMENT
CAPITAL OF THE WORLD.
GOT TO LOVE IT.
BREAKING NEWS THIS MORNING -- A
TOURIST LAID DOWN HIS OWN
HANDPRINTS AMONG THE BIGGEST
CELEBRITIES AT THE
HOLLYWOOD WALK OF FAME.
WE'LL HAVE HIM ON OUR SHOW
LATER THIS WEEK AND ASK HIM WHY
HE'S A LITTLE BIT CRAZY.
COMING UP, WE'RE GONNA...
>> WHOA.
MARK WAHLBERG SOLD HIS HOUSE.
>> FOR HOW MUCH?
>> NOT MUCH. 6.4.
HEY, HOW BIG DID YOU SAY HIS LOT
WAS?
>> UH, I THINK I SAID IT WAS A
HALF ACRE.
>> I SAID THREE-QUARTERS OF AN
ACRE.
LET'S SEE.
YEAH. 0.7 ACRES.
I TOLD YOU.
>> MAN, IT JUST DOESN'T LOOK
THAT BIG.
REMEMBER THAT, UH, BASKETBALL
HOOP HE THREW AWAY, LIKE, FIVE
YEARS AGO?
>> IT'S THE ONE I HAVE AT MY
HOUSE.
>> THAT'S THE SAME ONE?
>> YEAH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
[ HYDRAULICS HISS ]
>> HEY!
>> COME ON, MAN! LET'S GO!
>> JUST COME HERE!
CHECK IT OUT.
THIGHMASTER.
>> I'M SURE IT'S BROKEN.
>> ISN'T THIS THE ONE THAT
SUZANNE SOMERS INVENTED?
YOU WANT IT?
>> NOT REALLY.
>> I'M GONNA TAKE IT.
>> GREAT.
>> CAN YOU PUT IT IN THE CAB?
>> YES.
>> HEY, DID YOU SEE
"GOOD MORNING, L.A." THIS
MORNING?
THEY DID A SPECIAL ON
DARYL HANNAH.
SHE'S SMOKING HOT.
I DARE YOU TO SAY SOMETHING TO
HER.
>> [ SCOFFS ] LIKE WHAT?
YOU ALWAYS DARE ME TO SAY STUPID
CRAP TO PEOPLE, AND THEN I END
UP LOOKING LIKE AN IDIOT.
WHAT IF SHE'S NOT EVEN MY TYPE?
>> AHH.
WHEN DID HE GET THIS?
BASTARD.
WICKED.
>> NOT BAD.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> I HATE COMING UP MULHOLLAND.
>> OKAY.
FIRST OF ALL, THANKS TO ME,
YOU'RE ON A FIRST-NAME BASIS
WITH DEBRA WINGER BEFORE SHE
MOVED TO MALIBU.
SECOND OF ALL, DARYL HANNAH IS
EVERYBODY'S TYPE...
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> ...AND IF WE SEE HER TODAY, I
THINK YOU SHOULD SAY SOMETHING
TO HER.
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> OI!
OI!
WATCH THE PORSCHE!
>> YEAH, IT'S FINE. WE KNOW.
>> I KNOW YOU KNOW, BUT YOU'RE
TOO CLOSE.
THAT IS A 1955
PORSCHE SPEEDSTER 356.
THIS AUTOMOBILE IS ONE OF THE
SEVERAL PORSCHES OWNED AND
DRIVEN BY JAMES DEAN.
IT'S PRETTY MUCH PRICELESS, AND
MR. STILLER SPECIFICALLY ASKED
ME TO REMIND YOU TO STAY CLEAR
OF ALL OF HIS VEHICLES,
ESPECIALLY THE PORSCHE.
AND MR. STILLER ALSO REQUESTS,
YET AGAIN, THAT YOU PLACE THE
TRASH BINS SIX INCHES APART.
>> OKAY.
>> MARVELOUS.
>> HAVE A NICE DAY.
>> YOU, TOO.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I FEEL LIKE,
SOMETIMES?
>> WHAT?
>> I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE ALL MY
LITTLE CHILDREN, AND THEY'RE
DIRTY, AND I HAVE TO CLEAN UP
AFTER THEM.
AND IF IT WASN'T FOR ME AND YOU,
THEN THEY WOULD BE LIVING IN A
WORLD OF FILTH.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
I CAN SEE THAT.
>> WE'RE SO LUCKY TO BE
SERVICING BEV HILLS, HUH?
IMAGINE IF WE HAD TO DO THE
VALLEY.
>> YEAH.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
OH, MAN. [ GROANS ]
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO WITH THIS?
SHOCK AND AWE.
>> NO SHOCK AND AWE.
>> COME ON.
SHOCK AND AWE.
>> HI, GUYS.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THIS.
WE TRIED TO CALL GOODWILL, AND
THEN WE THOUGHT MAYBE SOMEBODY
WOULD TAKE IT, BUT...
>> IT'S FINE, UH, DARYL.
WE'LL, UH -- WE'LL MAKE IT FIT.
>> [ Chuckling ] THANKS.
OH, WE COULD CALL ONE OF
THOSE BIG DUMPSTER-THINGY
COMPANIES OR --
>> HI.
>> WE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
>> OKAY. [ CHUCKLES ] THANKS.
BYE.
>> BYE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
I MEAN -- WHAT AM I SUP-- IT'S
NOT LIKE I HAVE A SHOT WITH
DARYL HANNAH.
>> BUT YOU NEVER KNOW, AND THAT
IS THE POINT.
>> OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
WITH THIS?
>> WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE IT COMES
APART IN PIECES.
>> SHOCK AND AWE.
>> NO SHOCK AND AWE.
>> COME ON. SHOCK AND AWE.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> PLEASE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ HYDRAULICS HISS ]
SHOCK AND AWE!
>> GOOD STUFF.
>> YEAH, MAN.
WE'RE IN THE INDUSTRY, BY THE
WAY -- BOTH OF US.
UH, BEHIND THE SCENES, MOSTLY.
>> COOL.
>> I BET YOU THINK THAT WE'RE
WRITERS, HUH?
CLOSE. NO.
WE DEAL WITH A-LISTERS ALL THE
TIME.
I SHOULDN'T BE SAYING THIS, BUT
JUST THIS MORNING, WE WERE AT
BEN STILLER'S HOUSE, AND THEN,
UH, WE WENT TO JEN ANISTON'S AND
NICK CAGE'S, AND, UH, WAHLBERG.
HE'S MOVING, ACTUALLY.
WAHLBERG.
>> THAT'S COOL.
>> I-I-I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T CATCH YOUR NAME.
>> IT'S JESSICA.
SO, IS THAT IT?
JUST A TONIC AND LIME AND A
CORONA?
>> PLEASE.
>> YES. THANK YOU.
>> OKAY.
[ SIGHS ]
>> SHE SEEMED NICE.
[ WATER RUNNING ]
THERE YOU GO, PETER.
[ BIRD CHIRPS ]
[ SMOOCHES ]
>> ...IN FRONT OF WORLD'S FAMOUS
HOLLYWOOD BOULEVARD, WHERE JUST
A FEW HOURS AGO, A FRENCH
TOURIST BROUGHT SEVERAL GALLONS
OF WATERPROOFING MATERIAL
CALLED PENETRON.
IT IS THE SAME SUBSTANCE USED
BY HOLLYWOOD STARS TO LAY DOWN
PRINTS ON THE WALK OF FAME.
APPARENTLY, THE OBSESSED
TOURIST USED PENETRON TO LAY
DOWN HIS OWN HAND- AND
FOOTPRINTS NEXT TO
TOM CRUISE'S.
>> STAY TUNED, AND WE TAKE YOU
BEHIND THE SCENES AND COUNT
DOWN TO HOLLYWOOD'S BIGGEST
CELEBRITIES AND THEIR
EXTRAVAGANT LIFESTYLES.
"HOLLYWOOD INSIDER EDITION"
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[ THEME MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ SINGING IN SPANISH ]
>> HEY. BERNARDO.
>> HEY, HOW WE DOING?
>> ¿QUé PASA?
>> HEY.
>> LENNY AND ABBOTT TO
MR. TORRES' OFFICE.
LENNY AND ABBOTT TO
>> HEY.
MR. TORRES' OFFICE.
>> HEY!
>> HEY.
WHERE'S MY US WEEKLY MAGAZINE?
>> HEY!
>> WHAT MAGAZINE?
WHERE'S MY US WEEKLY MAGAZINE?
>> THE SAME MAGAZINE YOU KEEP
>> WHAT MAGAZINE?
TAKING OFF MY DESK.
>> THE SAME MAGAZINE YOU KEEP
>> OH. I -- IT'S IN THE TRUCK.
TAKING OFF MY DESK.
YOU WANT ME TO GO GET IT?
>> OH. I -- IT'S IN THE TRUCK.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU WANT ME TO GO GET IT?
>> WHAT'S UP, DYNAMIC DUOS?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> WHAT'S UP, DYNAMIC DUOS?
>> HEY, CHECK IT OUT, MAN.
>> HEY, MAN.
MR. TORRES -- HE WANTS TO TALK
>> HEY, CHECK IT OUT, MAN.
TO YOU.
MR. TORRES -- HE WANTS TO TALK
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
TO YOU.
>> HEY, MR. TORRES.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
YOU WANTED TO SEE US?
>> HEY, MR. TORRES.
>> YEAH. HAVE A SEAT.
YOU WANTED TO SEE US?
>> I CAN'T AFFORD ANOTHER BREAK
>> YEAH. HAVE A SEAT.
DOWN.
>> I CAN'T AFFORD ANOTHER BREAK
YOUR COLLECTION TIMES ARE
DOWN.
ALREADY THE SLOWEST IN THE
YOUR COLLECTION TIMES ARE
COMPANY.
ALREADY THE SLOWEST IN THE
THE NEW MACKS HAVE THE BETTER
COMPANY.
TECHNOLOGY.
THE NEW MACKS HAVE THE BETTER
THEY'VE GOT PACK-ON-THE-GO WITH
TECHNOLOGY.
THE FASTER HYDRAULICS.
THEY'VE GOT PACK-ON-THE-GO WITH
>> WE EMPTY OUT JUST AS MUCH AS
THE FASTER HYDRAULICS.
WILLIAMS AND MORALES, AND THEY
>> WE EMPTY OUT JUST AS MUCH AS
DUMP THE MOST IN THE WHOLE
WILLIAMS AND MORALES, AND THEY
COMPANY.
DUMP THE MOST IN THE WHOLE
>> THAT'S TRUE, MR. TORRES, AND
COMPANY.
THE ONLY TIME ROSIE'S BEEN OFF
>> THAT'S TRUE, MR. TORRES, AND
THE STREET THIS YEAR IS FOR
THE ONLY TIME ROSIE'S BEEN OFF
BIO-DIESEL CONVERSION.
THE STREET THIS YEAR IS FOR
>> SHE'S GOT TO GO, GUYS.
BIO-DIESEL CONVERSION.
IT'S EITHER THE MACK OR THE
>> SHE'S GOT TO GO, GUYS.
NEW TERRAPRO, AND I WANT AN
IT'S EITHER THE MACK OR THE
ANSWER BY NEXT WEEK.
>> ALL THAT TANNING MUST HAVE
FRIED HIS BRAIN.
FASTER HYDRAULICS -- WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN?
GAIN A TENTH OF A SECOND?
>> I HEAR YA.
>> I HATE MACKS.
I'D WAY RATHER GET A VOLVO.
SWEDISH PEOPLE MAKE THE BEST
REFUSE VEHICLES.
>> IT'S NOT FAIR, MAN.
>> DAMN RIGHT, IT'S NOT.
YOU KNOW, YOU AND I, COMBINED,
HAVE BEEN DRIVING ROSIE FOR,
LIKE, 20 YEARS, NOW.
SHE'S LIKE FAMILY.
LOVE THIS TRUCK.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
HEY, CAN I DRIVE HER TOMORROW?
COME ON.
>> IF MR. TORRES FOUND OUT, HE'D
KILL US BOTH.
>> FIRST OF ALL, HE WON'T FIND
OUT.
SECOND OF ALL, EVEN IF HE DOES
FIND OUT, WHICH HE WON'T,
TICKET'S OFF MY RECORD.
>> FINE.
JUST DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
>> HEY!
IMAGINE IF WE WERE ON THAT
CRAB-CATCHING SHOW, AND ALL THIS
GARBAGE WAS ALASKAN CRAB.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MONEY WE'D
MAKE?
>> I DON'T KNOW. A LOT?
>> YEAH.
>> YO, LENNY!
YOU STILL DRIVING THAT OLD-ASS
DUST CART?
>> YO, LIL' JAY, YOU STILL
WORKING THE VALLEY?
>> [ CHUCKLES ] YEAH.
>> I'M GONNA HAUL YOUR ASS --
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING!
BETTER WATCH YOUR DAMN SELF!
I LIKE YOU, LENNY!
>> [ WHISTLES ]
>> WHAT?
>> AN OSCAR!
>> WHAT?!
I THINK I FOUND AN OSCAR!
"1996 -- BEST SUPPORTING
ACTOR -- CUBA GOODING JR.,
'JERRY MAGUIRE.'"
>> LET ME SEE THAT.
THAT'S HEAVY.
[ Chuckling ] THAT'S JUST GOT
TO BE FAKE, THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> WHAT IF IT'S REAL?
>> YOU THINK?
>> HERE.
HERE, PUT IT IN HERE JUST IN
CASE THE VALLEY HOMEY COMES
BACK.
I'M JUST SAYING, YOU KNOW --
WHAT IF IT'S REAL?
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH.
I'M KEEPING THIS THING FOR SURE.
YEAH, CHECK IT OUT.
[ BIRDS CAWING ]
THANK YOU!
FIRST, I WOULD LIKE TO THANK MY
DERMATOLOGIST.
THEN, I WOULD LIKE TO THANK MY
TAE BO INSTRUCTOR AND MY
PHARMACIST.
BUT MOST OF ALL, I WOULD LIKE TO
THANK MY BEST FRIEND,
ABBOTT SMITH.
YOU COMPLETE ME.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> CUBA GOODING JR.,
BEST SUPPORTING ACTOR OSCAR,
"JERRY MAGUIRE."
>> DO YOU HAVE IT?
>> IT'S IN A SECURE PLACE.
>> ALL I'M SAYING IS, IF YOU HAD
AN OSCAR, AND IT WENT MISSING,
YOU'D WANT IT BACK, RIGHT?
>> "JERRY MAGUIRE" -- IS THIS A
GOOD MOVIE?
>> IT'S A GREAT MOVIE, ESTEBAN.
>> LOOK, GUYS. I REALLY --
>> MR. TORRES.
I CAN CALL TELEMUNDO ABOUT THEIR
OSCAR.
>> YOU GUYS, I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOUR BRINGING THIS UP, OKAY, BUT
IT'S A DISPOSED ITEM.
IT'S NO LONGER A COMPANY MATTER.
SO, JUST DO WHAT YOU WANT.
>> GREAT.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
DIDN'T YOU SAY HE'S ON YOUR
COLLECTING ROUTE?
>> YEAH, HE'S ON THE SAME BLOCK
AS ERIC ROBERTS AND
STEVE GUTTENBERG.
>> LISTEN, IF IT'S THAT
IMPORTANT TO YOU, TALK TO THE
ACTOR, WORK SOMETHING OUT, AND
THEN YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
>> SEE?
WE CAN DRIVE BY TOMORROW AND
CHECK IT OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT. FINE.
BUT WE'RE GONNA KEEP IT AT MY
HOUSE TONIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> "JERRY MAGUIRE" IS ONE OF MY
FAVORITE MOVIES OF ALL TIME.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO MEET
CUBA GOODING JR. IN PERSON.
HE'S A GREAT ACTOR.
YOU EVER SEE HIS OSCAR SPEECH?
IT'S ONE OF THE BEST OF ALL
TIME.
>> I NEVER SAW IT.
>> IT'S OUR CHANCE TO OWN A
PIECE OF HISTORY.
>> YEAH, WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
IT'S THE OSCAR FOR "TITANIC," OR
ANYTHING.
>> THAT'S TOTALLY YOUR OPINION,
MAN.
YOU CAN'T COMPARE THEM.
THEY'RE TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
PLUS, I BET YOU A LOT OF PEOPLE
WOULD RATHER WATCH
"JERRY MAGUIRE" THAN "TITANIC."
>> "TITANIC" IS THE NUMBER-ONE
GROSSING MOVIE OF ALL TIME.
>> YOU EVER HEARD OF A LITTLE
FILM CALLED "AVATAR"?
IT'S JUST ALL ABOUT MONEY AND
FAME TO YOU, ISN'T IT?
YOU'RE A SHALLOW MAN.
>> YOU'RE BEING RIDICULOUS, MAN.
I'M JUST STATING THE FACTS.
>> WHO CARES WHOSE OSCAR IT IS?
AN OSCAR IS AN OSCAR.
>> IS IT THE YELLOW ONE?
>> I THINK IT'S THE BRICK ONE.
>> BRICK ONE.
>> OH, NO.
>> WHAT?
>> COPS ARE HERE.
I'M NOT STOPPING.
SEE?
I TOLD YOU WE SHOULDN'T COME
BACK HERE TODAY.
>> WE DIDN'T STEAL ANYTHING.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO GIVE
THAT THING UP.
>> GREAT. WE HAVE A TAIL.
>> HUH?
WELL, PULL OVER.
SEE WHAT HE WANTS.
>> I'M NOT STOPPING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SLOW DOWN!
>> NO.
>> PULL OVER, MAN!
DAMN IT!
LENNY! PULL OVER!
>> I GOT IT.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
>> HI.
>> HELLO.
>> I'M CASEY SIEGEL.
>> THAT'S AN OSCAR IN THAT BOX?
>> OBVIOUSLY NOT.
>> CAN WE TALK?
>> OKAY.
>> FOLLOW ME.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
[ CAR DOOR SHUTS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT A MUFFIN
OR CAPPUCCINO OR --
>> NO, THANKS.
>> NO, THANK YOU.
>> OKAY. HERE'S THE DEAL.
I RUN A BOUTIQUE MANAGEMENT
MEDIA-ADVISEMENT COMPANY.
I REPRESENT TV PERSONALITIES,
REALITY STARS, SOME ACTORS.
THE POINT IS YOUR STORY IS SUPER
HOT, AND -- AND I'D -- I'D
REALLY LIKE TO GUIDE YOU AND
HELP YOU MAKE THE MOST OF IT.
ON YOUR OWN, YOU MIGHT MAKE SOME
KIND OF HEADLINES, BUT THAT'S
ABOUT IT.
BUT WITH MY HELP, I CAN PUT YOU
ON "LENO."
I CAN PUT YOU ON E!,
"ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT," TMZ,
AND MUCH MORE.
>> WE DIDN'T STEAL IT.
>> OH, I DON'T CARE.
>> CASEY, I HAVE A QUESTION.
>> HOW DID I KNOW THAT YOU HAD
THE OSCAR?
>> YEAH.
>> SOMEONE FROM YOUR WORK CALLED
TELEMUNDO NEWS, AND THAT'S HOW
THE TRASH FIND LEAKED OUT, AND
THEY DESCRIBE YOUR COLLECTION
ROUTE, AND, UH, HERE WE ARE.
OH. THANK YOU.
CUBA'S REPS HAVEN'T MADE ANY
STATEMENTS YET, SO NO ONE REALLY
KNOWS WHAT HAPPENED, BUT THE
POINT IS I HAVE THE RIGHT
CONNECTIONS.
I CAN HOOK YOU UP WITH PEOPLE
WHO WOULD POTENTIALLY DO A
SEGMENT ON YOUR STORY AND PUT
YOU ON ALL THE RIGHT NETWORKS...
FOR 15% OF EVERYTHING YOU MAKE.
SO, I AM GONNA GIVE YOU MY CARD,
AND I WANT YOU TO THINK ABOUT
IT, AND, UH, CALL ME IF YOU WANT
MY HELP, BUT DON'T TAKE TOO LONG
BECAUSE YOU'RE HOT ONE DAY --
YOU'RE NOT THE NEXT.
MAY I MAKE A SUGGESTION?
IF YOU GET APPROACHED BY
REPORTERS, SIMPLY SAY, "NO
COMMENT."
OKAY?
SAVE THE STORY FOR WHEN IT
MATTERS.
>> "NO COMMENT"?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> "AND THE OSCAR GOES TO...
AND THE WINNER IS...
LENNY EATON!"
YEAH.
YEAH, THERE'S DEFINITELY
SOMETHING FISHY ABOUT THIS WHOLE
THING.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> A HOTTIE LIKE THAT FINDS US
AND TELLS US THE ENTIRE NEWS
WORLD IS AFTER US, AND SHE WANTS
TO REPRESENT US?
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
>> I KNOW.
>> MAYBE IT'S ONE OF THOSE
"PUNK'D" SHOWS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
WHO IN THE WORLD WOULD WANT TO
PUNK YOU?
>> DID YOU PLANT THE OSCAR?
>> NO.
>> SWEAR.
>> I SWEAR ON MY FUTURE CHILDREN
I DIDN'T PLANT IT.
DID    YPLANT IT?
>> I SWEAR ON MY FUTURE CHILDREN
I DIDN'T PLANT IT.
>> OKAY.
>> WELL, ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
THAT CHICK DEFINITELY IS A
HOTTIE.
>> YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
>> I BET YOU I CAN GET HER IN
THE SACK.
>> OOH, I BET YOU CAN'T.
>> HOW MUCH YOU WANT TO MAKE THE
BET?
>> UH, LET'S SEE.
IS A BAJILLION A NUMBER?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH THAT
IS.
>> I DON'T, EITHER, BUT I'M SURE
I'LL WIN.
>> HUH.
THERE'S PAPARAZZI.
THAT'S PAPARAZZI.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
>> WHERE'D YOU FIND THE OSCAR?
>> DID YOU KNOW THE OSCAR WAS
REAL WHEN YOU FOUND IT?
>> WHAT'D YOU DO WITH THE OSCAR?
>> WE'RE FROM TMZ.
SHOW US THE MONEY.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
>> WHERE'S THE OSCAR NOW?
>> WHERE DID YOU FIND THE OSCAR?
>> WHAT WERE YOU DOING WHEN YOU
FOUND THE OSCAR?
>> I -- WELL, WE -- WE WERE AT
THE DUMP.
WE WERE WORKING.
>> ABBOTT. ABBOTT.
DON'T SAY ANYTHING TO THEM.
NO COMMENT.
>> ARE YOU WILLING TO SELL THE
OSCAR BACK TO THE ACADEMY?
>> LENNY, SHOW ME THE MONEY.
THIS IS TMZ.
>> NO COMMENT.
>> ROLL YOUR WINDOW UP, MAN.
>> DID YOU KNOW IT WAS REAL WHEN
YOU FOUND IT?
>> SIR, PLEASE.
[ HORN HONKING ]
>> LENNY, DID YOU HAVE LUNCH
WITH CUBA?
>> JUST A QUICK WORD.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
>> [ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
HOLY SHIT.
I'M GONNA CALL CASEY.
>> ESTEBAN, LINE ONE.
PICK UP LINE ONE.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
>> CASEY, HI.
IT'S LENNY AND ABBOTT.
IT'S A DEAL.
WE'RE IN.
>> GREAT.
DON'T DISCUSS ANYTHING WITH
ANYONE.
CAN YOU, UH, COME TO MY OFFICE
TOMORROW?
>> YEAH!
YEAH, WE -- YEAH, OF COURSE.
WE'LL COME RIGHT AFTER OUR
SHIFT.
>> EXCELLENT.
YOU GUYS SHOULD CONSIDER, UH,
GETTING SOME NICE CLOTHES
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE ON TV A LOT.
>> REALLY? WOW, OKAY.
SO, WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
THANK YOU!
[ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
THIS IS FOR REALS, MAN.
[ DING! ]
[ WINDOW SQUEAKS ]
>> WATER?
SODA?
>> Together: WATER, PLEASE.
>> IT'S A NICE OFFICE.
>> THANKS. THERE YOU GO.
YEAH, I WAS THINKING ABOUT
MOVING TO THE WEST SIDE, AND
THEN I THOUGHT TARZANA IS JUST
MUCH MORE CONVENIENT.
IT'S CLOSER TO EVERYTHING.
OH, HERE ARE YOUR CONTRACTS, AND
I NEED THEM SIGNED BEFORE YOU
GUYS LEAVE.
OKAY?
OKAY. HERE'S THE DEAL.
EVERY STATION IN TOWN WANTS AN
INTERVIEW.
[ CHUCKLES ]
MY SOURCES TELL ME THAT CUBA
WANTS IT BACK, BUT HE'D LIKE TO
COMPENSATE YOU FOR YOUR
TROUBLES.
SO, HERE'S WHAT I SUGGEST.
SINCE YOU GUYS DIDN'T STEAL IT,
NO ONE CAN TAKE IT AWAY FROM
YOU OR FORCE YOU TO GIVE IT
BACK.
WHAT I SUGGEST IS I SHOULD CALL
UP CUBA'S PEOPLE AND SET UP THE
HANDOVER LIVE ON NATIONAL TV.
BIG BUCKS THERE.
SEE, HERE'S WHAT YOU HAVE TODAY.
LATER ON, "GOOD MORNING, L.A.,"
ON THE FOX LOT, AND IN A COUPLE
OF HOURS, CBS'
"EARLY MORNING SHOW."
OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S A SMALL SEGMENT.
THEY WANT TO FILM IT AWAY FROM
THE STAGES, IN YOUR NATURAL
ENVIRONMENT, RIGHT IN FRONT OF
YOUR GARBAGE TRUCK.
>> HEY, DO YOU THINK THERE'S A
WAY FOR US TO BE IN US WEEKLY
MAGAZINE?
YOU KNOW, THE SECTION WHERE THEY
DO "CELEBS ARE JUST LIKE US --
THEY WALK, THEY TALK,
THEY EAT, THEY DO THINGS"?
MAYBE WE COULD JUST BE WORKING
OR SOMETHING.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
>>   US WEEKLY.
>> HI.
CASEY SIEGEL FOR, UH,
LORI HICKS, PLEASE?
>> HOLD, PLEASE.
>> CASEY!
>> HEY, STRANGER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW'S MY LORI-WORI DOING?
HEY, LISTEN.
I AM REPPING THE GARBAGE GUYS
THAT FOUND CUBA'S OSCAR.
UH-HUH.
[ LAUGHING ]
THAT'S SO FUNNY.
[ SIGHS ] ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. GOOD FOR YOU.
OKAY.
OKAY. WE'LL TALK SOON.
OKAY. BYE.
THEY'RE INTERESTED.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> THEY'RE INTERESTED.
I GUESS WHAT I'LL DO IS I'LL
SEND THEM OVER THERE DURING THE
HANDOVER FOR A Q&A AND SOME
STILLS.
>> THAT IS GREAT!
CASEY, YOU ARE SO GREAT!
HEY, UM, I THINK I'M SPEAKING
FOR THE BOTH OF US -- YOU KNOW,
INSTEAD OF "GARBAGEMEN," COULD
YOU REFER TO US AS
WASTE-MANAGEMENT ENGINEERS OR
PERSONNEL?
>> [ GASPS ] OH.
OH, SURE. SURE.
I'M SORRY.
I-I JUST THOUGHT THAT
"GARBAGEMEN" HAD A BETTER RING
TO IT, BUT OF COURSE.
OF COURSE.
WHY NOT?
>> SURE.
>> NO, YOU KNOW.
IT'S -- IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> OKAY, QUIET EVERYONE, PLEASE.
>> ROLLING SOUND.
[ CLAPPERBOARD SNAPS ]
>> LET'S DO IT.
ROLL CAMERA, PLEASE.
>> ROLLING, ROLLING.
>> TAKE A HALF STEP TO YOUR
LEFT.
>> STAND BY.
>> BACK A LITTLE.
>> OKAY, CAMERA IS SET.
>> GOOD.
I'M READY.
>> AND ACTION.
>> READY, GENTLEMEN?
>> YES.
>> OKAY. HERE WE GO.
DESCRIBE TO US AN AVERAGE DAY
FOR A GARBAGEMAN.
>> UM, WELL, YOU KNOW, WE WAKE
UP IN THE MORNING, UH, YOU KNOW,
GET A CUP OF COFFEE, GO TO WORK.
AND THEN WE UPDATE OUR SERVICE
LOG AND COLLECTION ROUTES FOR
THE DAY.
WE, UH, CLIMB INTO OUR, UH,
REFUSE VEHICLE, AND, UH -- WELL,
YOU KNOW -- AND THEN, SOMETIMES,
WE KNOW WE COME UPON ITEMS THAT
ARE TOO BIG TO FIT, AND WE HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO WITH
THEM -- LIKE LARGE PIECES OF
FURNITURE, FOR EXAMPLE.
>> THAT'S EXCELLENT.
ABBOTT, HOW LONG HAVE YOU TWO
BEEN PARTNERS?
>> UH, LENNY AND I HAVE KNOWN
EACH OTHER FOR 13 YEARS.
UM, UH, HE WAS A TRUCK MECHANIC
BEFORE HE STARTED, AND I WAS
ALREADY WORKING AT L.A. RUBBISH.
AND WHEN HE STARTED, WE JUST
BECAME FRIENDS.
>> WE'VE BEEN IN THE SAME TRUCK
FOR OVER 10 YEARS, NOW.
HER NAME'S ROSIE.
>> GREAT NAME.
OVER THE YEARS, HOW MANY OTHER
FINDS HAVE YOU HAD ON THE JOB?
>> WELL, STEVE, UH, YOU CAN TELL
EVERYTHING ABOUT A PERSON BASED
ON THEIR REFUSE -- YOU KNOW,
WHAT THEY EAT, WHAT THEY LIKE,
WHAT THEY BUY, WHAT THEY THROW
AWAY.
I MEAN, WE HAVE HAD SOME AMAZING
FINDS OVER THE YEARS.
LIKE, THIS ONE TIME, I REMEMBER
WE FOUND AN AUTHENTIC, UH,
GERMAN HELMET FROM WORLD WAR I.
>> ABBOTT, HOW DID YOU NOTICE
THE STATUETTE?
>> WELL, STEVE, UH, WE WERE AT
THE LANDFILL, DISPOSING OF OUR
DAILY CATCH WHEN JUST, YOU KNOW,
OUT OF THE CORNER OF MY EYE, I
SAW SOMETHING, AND IT WAS SHINY.
AND OF COURSE, YOU KNOW, WE
DIDN'T THINK IT WAS REAL AT
FIRST, BUT THEN...
>> WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO RETURN
THE OSCAR TO ITS RIGHTFUL OWNER?
>> CAN WE SKIP TO THE NEXT
QUESTION, PLEASE?
>> SURE.
>> I'M STILL ROLLING.
>> WHAT PLANS DO YOU HAVE FOR
THE FUTURE, AND WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO FIND NEXT?
>> UH...
SKY'S THE LIMIT.
Put your thumb up.
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ]
REALLY?
GREAT. THANK YOU.
OKAY. OKAY.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
BYE.
OH, MY GOD.
WE ARE GONNA BE COVERED BY
SEVERAL NETWORKS DURING THE
HANDOFF, INCLUDING E!
AND GET THIS -- OPRAH, WHO IS
GOOD FRIENDS WITH CUBA, IS
JUMPING ON THE BANDWAGON WITH A
TV SPECIAL.
WE'RE GONNA BE ON "OPRAH," MAN.
>> NO WAY.
>> YEAH.
SHE'S GONNA COVER US LIVE.
THIS IS CRAZY.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE THIS, MAN.
>> NOW, LISTEN TO ME.
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE ON TV, YOU
GOT TO LOOSEN UP.
YOU'RE REALLY STIFF.
YOU KIND OF SUCKED.
>> YEAH?
AND YOU WERE POUTING YOUR LIPS.
>> WELL, AT LEAST I WASN'T
TILTING MY HEAD LIKE
GEORGE CLOONEY.
THAT'S WHAT CASEY SAID.
>> WHAT?
WHY DOES SHE EVEN HAVE TO BE
THERE?
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> YOU HAVE A CRUSH ON HER,
DON'T YOU?
>> [ SCOFFS ]
WHATEVER, MAN.
LOOK, WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT HOW
WE'RE GONNA GET TIME OFF WORK.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S THE LAST THING I'M
THINKING ABOUT.
WE'RE LIVING THE LIFE NOW.
>> WHAT LIFE?
>> THIS IS OUR SHOT.
THIS IS A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY, ALL RIGHT?
SO, JUST FORGET ABOUT WORK.
CHEERS.
SKY'S THE LIMIT.
>> HEY! [ GIGGLES ]
>> I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> WATCH THIS.
>> IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> HEY.
JESSICA.
HI.
UH, WE GOT A REAL OSCAR BACK AT
THE PAD.
YOU GIRLS WANT TO COME AND CHECK
IT OUT?
>> IS IT YOURS?
>> CUBA GOODING JR.'s.
BEST SUPPORTING ACTOR,
"JERRY MAGUIRE," 1996.
>> SURE.
>> SO, HOW'S NICOLAS CAGE IN
REAL LIFE?
>> OH, UH...
YEAH, NICK CAGE -- HE'S A --
HE'S A GOOD GUY.
UM, WE KNOW HIM, UM...
JEN ANISTON,
UH, DEBRA WINGER...
>> MM.
>> ...UH, WAHLBERG.
YEAH, JUST -- JUST -- WE SEE
THEM ALL THE TIME 'CAUSE WE'RE
IN MANAGEMENT.
[ BIRD CHIRPS ]
>> [ GIGGLES ]
GUYS, THAT WAS SO AMAZING --
HOLDING A REAL OSCAR IN MY
HANDS.
I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD.
>> [ CHUCKLES ] CHEERS!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> CHEERS.
>> AND IT WAS GREAT BECAUSE
"JERRY MAGUIRE" IS, LIKE, ONE OF
MY FAVORITE MOVIES.
JESSICA.
[ As Forrest Gump ] "SO,
THERE'S, LIKE, BARBECUED SHRIMP
AND PAN-FRIED SHRIMP AND SHRIMP
GUMBO."
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> YEAH, LIKE,
"LIFE IS LIKE A BOX OF
CHOCOLATES.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GONNA
GET."
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> UH, ISN'T THAT
"FORREST GUMP"?
>> [ Chuckling ] OH, MY GOD.
IT IS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> OOPS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> EVER HAD A HAND JOB BY A HAND
MODEL?
>> IT -- IT'S USUALLY A LOT
BIGGER WHEN IT'S EXCITED.
>> I DON'T EXCITE YOU?
>> OH. NO, YOU DO.
I-IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S, UM...
[ SIGHS ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
>> LENNY! IT'S LENNY!
>> OH, MY GOD! WHOO! LENNY!
HEY, LENNY!
OH, MY GOD, IT'S REALLY HIM!
LENNY! OH, MY GOD!
>> LENNY!
>> WHOO!
>> L.A. RUBBISH.
THEY'RE NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO CALL BACK
LATER.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
>> L.A. RUBBISH.
[ SIGHS ]
THEY'RE NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO CALL BACK
LATER.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
>> HEY.
>> HOLD ON, PLEASE.
[ TELEPHONE RECEIVER CLICKS ]
HEY, HOT STUFF.
>> HEY.
I HEARD YOU'RE ON
"THE EARLY SHOW."
>> YOU DID?
>> YEAH.
>> [ GRUNTS ]
I WAS ON "GOOD MORNING, L.A.,"
TOO.
DID YOU SEE THAT ONE?
I WAS BETTER.
>> NO, BUT MY HOMEGIRL IS
TiVoing IT RIGHT NOW, SO...
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
HOLD ON.
>> HEY, WE'RE GONNA BE IN THE
NEXT ISSUE OF US WEEKLY.
>> YOU KNOW YOU HAVE TO SIGN
THIS FOR ME, RIGHT?
>> FOR YOU, I WILL SIGN TWO.
AND WE'RE ALSO GONNA BE ON E!
AND "OPRAH."
IT'S CRAZY.
WE'RE, LIKE, BLOWING UP.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN I GO WITH YOU GUYS TO SEE
OPRAH?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT'S UP, DYNAMIC DUOS?
>> HEY.
>> HEY. HEY.
[ SLURPS ]
CHECK IT OUT.
MR. TORRES -- HE WANTS TO TALK
TO YOU.
>> HEY, MR. TORRES.
UH, WE HAVEN'T DECIDED ON THE
TRUCK, YET.
>> LOOK -- I CAN'T HAVE YOUR
INTERVIEWS OR WHATEVER ELSE
YOU'RE DOING INTERFERING WITH
YOUR WORK.
THIS PLACE IS BECOMING LIKE A
CIRCUS.
I'VE GOT MONKEYS WITH CAMERAS
HANGING AROUND THE GATE.
>> MR. TORRES.
>> I GOT PRESS REQUESTS.
I'VE GOT PEOPLE HAVING TO ANSWER
PHONE CALLS ABOUT --
>> BUT MR. TORRES, THIS IS GREAT
EXPOSURE AND PUBLICITY FOR
L.A. RUBBISH, INCORPORATED.
>> LENNY, I'M IN THE GARBAGE
BUSINESS.
I MEAN, COME ON.
>> UNDERSTANDABLE, BUT WE
PROMISE THAT ONCE WE RETURN THE
OSCAR, EVERYTHING'S GONNA GO
BACK TO NORMAL.
RIGHT, LENNY?
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
>> RIGHT.
>> L.A. RUBBISH.
>> YOU KNOW, MR. TORRES IS
RIGHT.
HE'S GOT A BUSINESS TO RUN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SLACKING OFF
ANYMORE.
>> YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
HEY, DURING INTERVIEWS --
HAT, NO HAT?
>> YEAH, I DON'T CARE.
>> YEAH, I THINK I'M GONNA
RETURN IT.
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
HEY, CASEY.
>> HEY.
UH, I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU
GUYS TO SOME IMPORTANT INDUSTRY
PEOPLE.
CAN YOU MAKE IT TO A PARTY IN
THE HILLS TONIGHT?
>> YEAH. DEFINITELY.
>> GREAT.
IS ABBOTT NEXT TO YOU?
>> YES, HE IS.
>> LENNY, I WANT YOU TO MEET ME
BEFORE THE PARTY FOR DINNER, BUT
YOU HAVE TO COME ALONE, AND
DON'T TELL ABBOTT.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
>> UH...
YEAH.
UM...SOUNDS GOOD.
>> GOOD. GOOD.
TONIGHT AT 8:00, AND I'LL, UH --
I'LL TEXT YOU THE ADDRESS OF THE
RESTAURANT.
>> OKAY.
THANKS. BYE.
>> BYE.
>> WHAT'D SHE SAY?
>> WE'RE GOING TO A PARTY IN THE
HILLS TONIGHT.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> COOL.
[ THEME MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> WE'RE BACK WITH
COLIN ROLLINS, A LONGTIME
MEMBER OF THE ACADEMY.
NOW, COLIN, IT'S BEEN PUBLICLY
ANNOUNCED THAT THE GARBAGEMEN
WILL BE RETURNING THE OSCAR
LIVE ON NATIONAL TV.
WHAT ARE YOU THOUGHTS ON THAT?
>> THANK YOU, WARREN.
THE ACADEMY IS PAYING CLOSE
ATTENTION TO THESE EVENTS, SO
IT WILL BE VERY INTERESTING TO
SEE HOW THE SITUATION UNFOLDS,
AS WELL AS FIND OUT HOW THE
OSCAR STATUETTE...
[ HORN HONKING ]
...LEFT THE PREMISES IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
>> LENNY! LENNY!
>> THE MEDIA'S HAD A FIELD DAY
WITH THIS STORY...
>> RIGHT HERE, BROTHER!
>> ...EVER SINCE IT BROKE.
>> LOOK AT THIS.
DON'T THESE PEOPLE HAVE ANYTHING
BETTER TO DO?
>> LOOK AT MY CAMERA!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
>> MAN, THE OSCAR IS THE BEST
THING THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
I COULD TOTALLY GET USED TO THIS
LIFESTYLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> WHAT LIFESTYLE?
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE A CELEBRITY --
WOMEN, PARTIES, MOVIE PREMIERES,
FREE STUFF.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
MAYBE I COULD BUY A HOUSE AROUND
HERE.
HEY, LOOK.
THAT ONE'S FOR SALE.
I BET YOU THAT'S 5,000 SQUARE
FEET ON A THIRD OF AN ACRE.
IS THIS L.A. OR BEV HILLS?
I THINK THE BORDER'S, LIKE, TWO
BLOCKS WEST.
AH, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'LL TAKE ANY ONE OF THESE
CRIBS, AS LONG AS I'M NOT LIVING
NEXT TO BEN STILLER.
>> WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, MAN?
>> HI.
>> THERE HE IS.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, YOUR SERVER WILL BE
RIGHT WITH YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ENJOY.
>> SO, UH, THERE'S A -- A
PAPARAZZO OUT FRONT.
SHOULD WE LET HIM KNOW THAT I'M
HERE?
>> THEY'RE HERE FOR
JOHN MALKOVICH.
>> OH.
OH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD. GOOD.
>> YOU LOOK GREAT.
>> THANK YOU.
THANKS.
>> I --
>> OH, BEFORE I FORGET, THE E!
PRODUCERS WANT YOU TO PULL UP IN
FRONT OF CUBA'S HOUSE IN YOUR
TRUCK.
>> YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
OH, BUT, CASEY, UM, WHEN IT
COMES TO CAMERAS AND PUBLICITY,
COULD YOU REFER TO IT AS A
WCV, OR WASTE-COLLECTION
VEHICLE?
>> SURE. ABSOLUTELY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> SO, WHAT DO WE TELL CUBA?
AND BY THE WAY, I CAN'T WAIT TO
MEET HIM.
>> AT 3:00 P.M. ON MONDAY, YOU
DRIVE UP, YOU RING THE DOORBELL,
YOU JUST BE YOURSELVES.
THAT'S THE WAY TO BE.
PURE, UNSCRIPTED, NATURAL HUMAN
EMOTION -- PEOPLE REALLY
REMEMBER STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND MAY I ALSO SUGGEST THAT YOU
NOT ACCEPT CUBA'S REWARD?
IT'LL JUST -- IT'LL RESONATE
BETTER WITH THE PUBLIC THAT WAY.
>>   YOARE GOOD.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> YOU'RE VERY GOOD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO, UH, HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
DOING THIS, UH, IF YOU DON'T
MIND ME ASKING?
>> TWO YEARS.
I INITIALLY CAME OUT HERE TO
ACT.
YOU?
>> WELL, I MOVED OUT HERE ABOUT
15 YEARS AGO FOR A GIRL, BUT
THAT DIDN'T REALLY WORK OUT.
SHE, UH, WANTED TO BE AN ACTRESS
IN SOAPS, AND -- AND I JUST
ALWAYS WANTED TO MOVE TO
HOLLYWOOD.
AND SO HERE I AM.
>> HI, GUYS.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING TO
DRINK?
>> I'LL HAVE A, UH, A GLASS OF,
UH, CABERNET.
>> A COURVOISIER FOR ME, PLEASE.
>> GREAT.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH YOUR
DRINKS.
>> THANK YOU.
OKAY. ENOUGH SMALL TALK.
A MAJOR, MAJOR HOLLYWOOD PLAYER
WANTS TO BUY THE RIGHTS TO YOUR
LIFE STORY FOR A TV MOVIE OF THE
WEEK.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> POTENTIALLY COULD BE A
SIX-FIGURE DEAL.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
I MEAN, NOT TO MENTION JUST
THE -- THE POSSIBILITIES IN THE
FUTURE -- THEY'RE ENDLESS, FOR,
LIKE, MINISERIES AND SPIN-OFFS,
I MEAN, THE WHOLE ENCHILADA.
>> YEAH.
>> AND A MAJOR NETWORK IS TOYING
WITH THE IDEA OF A REALITY
SHOW -- "GARBAGEMEN."
>> WOW.
I-I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THE TITLE,
BUT...
>> OH, WHATEVER.
"WASTE SOLDIERS"?
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> IT'S FINE.
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
YEAH, I'M ONLY KIDDING.
YEAH, SURE. THAT'S GREAT.
YEAH. LET'S DO IT.
AW, MAN, I'M SUPER EXCITED.
>> AHH.
>> TO MAKING IT.
>> YOU'RE SEXY.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU HEARD ME.
SO, UH, WHEN DO WE SIGN UP, AND,
UH, WHAT STUDIO?
>> NO STUDIO.
>> OKAY.
>> BEN STILLER.
>> BEN STILLER?
>> WHAT -- WHY, IS THERE A
PROBLEM?
>> OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
I-IS HE GONNA PLAY ME?
>> OH, NO -- HE WANTS TO PRODUCE
IT THROUGH A SHINGLE.
>> OH, A SHINGLE.
OKAY.
SO, WELL, WHO'S GONNA PLAY US?
>> LENNY, THEY WANT THE RIGHTS
TO YOUR STORY, ONLY.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THEY -- THEY DON'T WANT ABBOTT
IN THE PICTURE, FIGURATIVELY
AND -- AND PHYSICALLY SPEAKING.
>> WHY NOT?
>> WELL, BEN'S DEVELOPMENT
PEOPLE JUST FEEL IT'S -- IT'S A
MUCH MORE COMPELLING STORY THAT
A DOWN-ON-HIS-LUCK, LONELY
GARBAGEMAN FINDS AN OSCAR, AND
HIS ENTIRE LIFE GETS TURNED
AROUND.
THERE'S NO ROOM FOR A BUDDY.
PLUS, THEY WANT YOU TO BE THE
ON-CAMERA NARRATOR FOR A
TRUE-STORY TYPE OF DEAL, AND
ABBOTT JUST DOESN'T HAVE THE,
UH, CHARISMA TO BE ON CAMERA
LIKE YOU DO.
>> OKAY.
SO, ON-CAMERA NARRATOR -- THEY
WOULD ACTUALLY WANT ME TO BE IN
THE MOVIE?
>> YES.
I'LL BE STRAIGHTFORWARD WITH
YOU.
YOU HAVE A MUCH BETTER CHANCE OF
MOVING FORWARD ON YOUR OWN.
PEOPLE LOVE A RAGS-TO-RICHES
STORY, AND ABBOTT, QUITE
FRANKLY, JUST ISN'T INTERESTING.
HE DOESN'T CARE TO MAKE IT BIG,
BUT YOU DO.
HMM?
SURE, HE'LL END UP ON "OPRAH,"
AND HE'LL GET SMALLER VENUES.
HE'LL HAVE HIS 15 MINUTES, BUT
YOU AND I CAN MILK THIS COW FOR
A LONG TIME.
YOU HAVE PERSONALITY.
YOU HAVE CHARISMA.
YOU HAVE STAR QUALITY.
TRUST ME, I HAVE AN EYE FOR
TALENT.
I KNOW THESE THINGS.
DON'T BLOW IT.
OKAY?
CHANCES LIKE THIS DON'T COME
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
YOU GOT TO SHED THE DEAD WEIGHT,
LENNY.
AFTER ALL, IT WAS YOU, NOT
ABBOTT, WHO FOUND THE -- WHO
FOUND THE OSCAR, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> THEN YOU'D BE DOING THE RIGHT
THING.
WE NEED TO GIVE HIM AN ANSWER BY
TOMORROW.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> MMM. YUMMY.
THANKS.
>> MM-HMM.
[ TECHNO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ] BILLY.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> [ SMOOCHES ]
NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> YOU, TOO. YOU, TOO.
>> YES.
THESE ARE MY NEW CLIENTS.
THEY FOUND THE OSCAR.
>> HOW YOU DOING, OSCAR?
>> HI. UH...
>> MY -- MY NAME'S LENNY.
>> THEY FOUND THE OSCAR.
>> OH, RIGHT.
THESE ARE THE GUYS...
>> OUR GUYS, YES, YES.
>> ...THAT I'VE BEEN HEARING
ABOUT.
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS WHOSE OSCAR?
>> CUBA GOODING JR.'s.
>> CUBA GOODING?
>> YES, YES.
>> OH, GREAT.
>> I'M A BIG FAN.
>> YEAH. OH, THANKS.
HOW'S THAT WHOLE THING WORKING
OUT FOR YOU?
>> OH, GREAT.
>> GOOD.
>> YEAH?
>> YOU HAVE A BEAUTIFUL VIEW.
>> GREAT. TERRIFIC. WELL --
>> I'M ACTUALLY REALLY FAMILIAR
WITH THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> HOW SO?
>> WELL, OUR RUN IS -- IS IN
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> OH. OH. OF COURSE.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> THE GARBAGE -- THE GARBAGE
FELLAS, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
YOU EAT A LOT OF FISH STICKS.
>> YEAH, SO, UH...
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, LET ME LET
YOU GO.
>> YEAH. IT'S GREAT.
THANKS -- THANKS FOR HAVING US
HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> PLEASURE.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> YOU GUYS ENJOY THE HOUSE.
>> OKAY. THANKS.
>> HAVE A DRINK.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
YEAH, SO, THAT HAPPENED.
>> THIS IS VINCE HOLLOWAY.
HE MANAGES MICHAEL MADSEN.
>> HI. PLEASURE IS MINE.
>> AND THESE ARE THE GUYS
THAT FOUND -- THEY FOUND CUBA'S
OSCAR.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> LENNY. ABBOTT.
ABBOTT. LENNY.
>> SO, YOU GENTLEMEN LOOKING FOR
REPRESENTATION?
>> UNH-UNH. NO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I OWN THEM.
THIS IS A VERY GOOD FRIEND OF
MINE -- ALSO THE ASSOCIATE
PRODUCER ON THE NEXT
"SPIDER-MAN."
>> OH, NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> LENNY.
>> GREAT.
YOU DO ANY BACKGROUND WORK?
>> NOT YET.
>> YOU'RE IN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOUR PARTNER?
>> THIS IS MILA FROM
HOLLYWOOD CASTING.
MILA, LENNY. LENNY, MILA.
>> THIS IS DAN, A VERY PROMINENT
DEEJAY IN THE MUSIC WORLD --
ALSO A CLIENT OF MINE.
DAN, LENNY. LENNY, DAN.
>> HEY.
>> BONJOUR.
>> HE FOUND CUBA'S OSCAR.
>> OH.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT KIND OF MUSIC DO YOU
LISTEN TO?
>> OH, YOU KNOW, LIKE CLASSIC,
UH...ROCK AND --
>> NEXT WEEK I'M SPINNING IN
PRAGUE, SO IF YOU CAN SWING BY.
>> OH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
HE JUST MIGHT.
>> PRAGUE?
>> OKAY.
>> DO YOU KNOW PRAGUE?
YEAH?
>> WHERE -- IS THAT A CLUB?
[ TECHNO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> HI.
>> HELLO.
HI. I SAW YOU EARLIER.
>> OH.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> GOOD. GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
>> I-I'M REALLY GOOD.
UM...SO HOW DO YOU -- HOW DO YOU
KNOW BILLY?
>> UH...ACTUALLY, UH, I KNOW MY
FRIEND LENNY.
I KNOW LENNY, AND HE KNOWS, UH,
CASEY.
SHE'S A MANAGER OR AGENT.
AND    SACTUALLY KNOWS BILLY.
THAT'S HOW I'M HERE, SO...
>> THAT'S COOL.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I GUESS, THEN, I'LL SEE
YOU LATER.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH?
>> OKAY. I'LL BE HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> GREAT.
>> OKAY. I'LL BE HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> GREAT.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NICE SHIRT.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> THANK YOU.
>> NICE SHIRT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
HI.
>> DIDN'T YOU USED TO PLAY FOR
THE DOLPHINS?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN I HAVE YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
>> YEAH. SURE.
SURE. NO PROBLEM.
[ BILLIARD BALLS CLACK ]
>> HOW DO YOU LIKE ME NOW?
>> NICE SHOT.
HEY, DO YOU KNOW WHERE THE
BATHROOM IS?
>> DO YOU WANT A BUMP?
>> NAH. NAH, I'M GOOD. THANKS.
JUST THE BATHROOM.
>> YEAH, MAN, THERE'S ONE BACK
THERE.
THERE'S ALSO ONE UP THERE.
>> GREAT. THANKS.
SORRY.
HEY.
>> OH, HEY.
WHERE YOU BEEN?
>> MICHAEL MADSEN IS OFFICIALLY
THE COOLEST DUDE ON THE PLANET.
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH, HE'S THE SHIT.
>> I WANT TO BE THAT GUY.
[ Laughing ] DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
UNREAL.
>> YOU GUYS HAVING A GOOD TIME?
>> HEY.
>> HUH?
>> YEAH.
THIS -- I CAN DEFINITELY DIG
THIS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, CASEY.
>> ABSOLUTELY. NO PROBLEM.
NO PROBLEM.
BILLY'S PARTIES ARE USUALLY THE
BOMB.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, YEAH.
OH, BY THE WAY, I HEAR
ANDY SAMBERG AND
JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE MIGHT BE HERE
LATER ON.
>> WOW.
>> HELLO! HELLO!
>> THAT'S GREAT. YEAH.
WE GOT TO BE UP IN LIKE FOUR
HOURS, BUT THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE
LEAVING, RIGHT, LENNY?
>> THAT -- THAT'S RIGHT.
HEY, BUT I-I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
INTO THIS WHOLE HOLLYWOOD THING.
>> SAYS WHO?
>> I-I DON'T KNOW.
JUST SAYING.
>> NAH, FORGET THAT.
>> PERFECT NIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> MM-HMM.
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
>> LENNY! LENNY!
>> LENNY! LENNY! OVER HERE!
LENNY, PLEASE, CAN I GET A
PICTURE OF YOU?
>> I LOVE YOU, LENNY!
I LOVE YOU!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
>> OH, MY GOD! LENNY! LENNY!
LENNY! LENNY! OH, MY GOD!
WHOO! LENNY!
>> I LOVE YOU, LENNY!
AAH!
LENNY!
>> I LOVE YA, MAN!
>> LENNY!
[ CRICKETS CHIRP ]
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
[ ALARM STOPS ]
>> IT'S 68 DEGREES ON A GLOOMY
MORNING IN THE ENTERTAINMENT
CAPITAL OF THE WORLD, BUT WHO
CARES?
HOW ABOUT THAT OSCAR STORY?
WOULD LOVE TO HEAR YOUR
THOUGHTS.
FIRST 10 CALLERS GET TWO
BLEACHER SEATS WITH A VIEW OF
THE RED CARPET AT THE NEXT
ACADEMY AWARDS...
>> HEY, UH, DID THAT HAND MODEL
GIRL EVER CALL YOU?
>> OH, YEAH, SHE DID.
YEAH, SHE WANTED TO PICK MY
BRAIN ABOUT I.T.A. OR U.B.M. OR
SOME TALENT AGENCY.
DID JESSICA CALL YOU?
>> NOPE.
SENT HER AN E-MAIL, TOLD HER THE
TRUTH ABOUT WHAT I DO.
SHE NEVER GOT BACK TO ME.
>> WELL, THAT SUCKS.
>> YOU THINK A GUY LIKE ME WOULD
EVER HAVE A SHOT WITH SOMEONE
LIKE CASEY?
I MEAN, WOULD THAT BE SOMETHING
WORTH PURSUING, OR...
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
>> THAT'S HARD TO SAY, MAN.
SPEAKING OF CASEY, UH, SHE SAID
THAT BEN STILLER WANTS TO DO A
TV MOVIE OF THE WEEK ON OUR
OSCAR STORY.
>> WHAT?
BEN STILLER?!
[ LAUGHS ]
SMALL WORLD.
>> YEAH.
BUT THEY JUST, UH -- YOU KNOW,
THEY WANT TO ADJUST THE PLOT A
LITTLE BIT.
MAKE IT MORE DRAMATIC.
>> SO WHAT? LET THEM.
>> YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
YEAH, BUT THEY SAID THEY JUST
WANT TO, UH, FOCUS ON ONE
CHARACTER.
[ CLANK ]
[ ENGINE SPUTTERS ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ RATCHET CLICKING ]
>> BEN STILLER DOESN'T WANT ME
IN THE TV MOVIE OF THE WEEK, AND
YOU AGREED TO THAT?
>> I MEAN, I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
INTO ALL THAT STUFF.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE'LL STILL SPLIT ALL THE MONEY.
>> I'M NOT CHARISMATIC ENOUGH?
I DON'T LOOK GOOD ON CAMERA?
SAYS WHO? BEN STILLER?
>> WHY ARE YOU SO UPSET?
>> LOOK, JUST 'CAUSE I DON'T
DRESS LIKE A CLOWN AND ACT LIKE
PARIS HILTON DOESN'T MEAN I
DON'T CARE ABOUT BEING IN THE
TV MOVIE OF THE WEEK.
>> YOU AND I ARE JUST ON
DIFFERENT PAGES, MAN,
'CAUSE I'M LOOKING INTO THE
FUTURE AND SEIZING OPPORTUNITY.
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT IS SHOWING UP
TO WORK ON TIME AND NOT MISSING
SHIFTS OR WHATEVER.
[ SIGHS ]
SHE'S GONNA NEED AN OVERHAUL
SOON.
>> I DON'T GIVE A SHIT.
MR. TORRES WAS RIGHT.
WE SHOULD'VE GOTTEN A NEW TRUCK
YEARS AGO.
>> YEAH.
WELL, YOU AND TORRES ARE GONNA
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I'M GONNA GIVE MY TWO WEEKS'
NOTICE SOON.
>> OH, YEAH?
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S THE RIGHT
THING FOR YOU TO DO,
MR. MOVIE STAR.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE A
GARBAGEMAN MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> A GARBAGEMAN LIKE ME?
I STARTED YOU IN THIS BUSINESS.
>> THE POINT IS, IS THAT, YOU'RE
FINE DIGGING IN PEOPLE'S TRASH
ALL DAY.
I JUST SEE SOMETHING MORE TO
LIFE THAN JUST HAVING A CRAP
JOB.
>> OH, SO NOW YOU'RE
MR. BIG SHOT.
OSCAR WINNER!
YOU THINK YOU'RE BETTER THAN ME.
>> I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
GARBAGEMAN?
YOU'RE A GARBAGEMAN, TOO, MAN.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE IS YOU HAVE
AN OSCAR, BUT YOU'RE NOTHING
WITHOUT IT.
>> I AM GOING TO BE IN
US WEEKLY MAGAZINE.
AND I AM GOING TO BE A
CELEBRITY, AND YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY?
BECAUSE I HAVE CHARISMA AND
PERSONALITY, AND I HAVE STAR
QUALITY.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE DICK!
I DON'T NEED THIS CRAP.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THIS
BULLSHIT, 'CAUSE THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT IT IS.
SO YOU CAN GO MAKE YOUR STUPID
TV MOVIE OF THE WEEK WITH YOUR
NEW BFF BEN STILLER, AND YOU CAN
GO ON E!, AND YOU CAN GO ON
"OPRAH," AND YOU CAN DO IT ALL
BY YOURSELF, 'CAUSE YOU'RE A BAG
OF SHIT AND A BAD FRIEND.
YOU THINK YOU'RE ALL THAT?
YOU'RE A LOSER.
>> YEAH?
WELL, I'M GONNA GIVE MY
TWO WEEKS' NOTICE TODAY, AND
YOU'LL SEE HOW MUCH OF A LOSER I
AM WHEN I'M LIVING IN 90210 AND
YOU HAVE TO PICK UP MY GARBAGE!
>> GOOD!
>> FINE!
[ HIP-HOP MUSIC BLARES ]
>> GOOD!
GOOD!
[ HIP-HOP MUSIC BLARES ]
>> FINE!
GOOD!
[ HORN HONKING ]
>> HI.
I SAW NEWS YOU HAVE OSCAR.
HOW MUCH?
>> OH. NO, IT'S NOT FOR SALE.
>> PLEASE.
"BRAVEHEART" IS MY FAVORITE
MOVIE.
I GIVE $10,000.
>> OURS IS FOR "JERRY MAGUIRE."
>> WHO?
>> IT'S A DIFFERENT MOVIE.
NO "BRAVEHEART."
>> AWW. SHOOT.
>> I'VE GOT ENOUGH PEOPLE TO
MAKE THE SWITCHES.
WE CAN ROTATE THINGS AROUND.
WE'LL HAVE TRUCKS SHOWING UP ON
THURSDAYS STARTING IN TWO WEEKS.
OKAY. THANK YOU.
>> MR. TORRES, I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT I HAVE TO RESIGN.
MY LAST SHIFT IS GONNA BE TWO
WEEKS FROM NOW.
>> AND I WOULD LIKE TO REQUEST A
DIFFERENT PARTNER IMMEDIATELY.
>> I CAN'T HAVE CERTAIN...
ELEMENTS DRAGGING ME DOWN
ANYMORE.
>> ALSO, I'D LIKE TO BE ON A
DIFFERENT SHIFT SO I DON'T HAVE
TO SEE THIS PRETENTIOUS LOSER
ANYMORE.
>> WILLIAMS AND MORALES TO
MR. TORRES' OFFICE.
WILLIAMS AND MORALES TO
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> HEY, LENNY! YO!
>> I'LL BE AT LADUTCH TONIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, LENNY!
>> IN LIGHT OF A VERY SPECIAL
TRASH FIND BY TWO BEVERLY HILLS
GARBAGEMEN, DOZENS OF
ANGELENOS HAVE BEEN OUT
SCOURING BEVERLY HILLS
DUMPSTERS FOR VALUABLES.
STAY TUNED FOR MORE ON THE
OSCAR STORY.
>> LENNY, WE'RE SO EXCITED FOR
YOU.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> LENNY, CAN I SEE THE OSCAR?
>> HEY, THIS IS THE NEW GUY,
GREG.
HE'S GONNA BE DRIVING WITH YOU
TILL YOUR LAST DAY.
>> LENNY.
>> WHAT'S UP, LENNY?
CONGRATULATIONS ON ALL YOUR
SUCCESS, MAN.
>> YEAH, MAN.
>> LENNY, I WANT TO THROW YOU A
GOING-AWAY PARTY AT MY HOUSE.
>> THAT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU,
MR. TORRES.
>> ESTEBAN, WE HAVE A SCHEDULE.
LET'S GO.
>> SORRY, MAN.
>> YOU BEEN TO THE
PLAYBOY MANSION YET?
WELL, TELL WHEN YOU ROLL, ALL
RIGHT?
MAYBE YOU CAN HOOK ME UP, PUT ME
ON THE GUEST LIST OR SOMETHING.
HOOK A BROTHER UP -- SOMETHING.
MAN, MATTER OF FACT, YOU CAN
EVEN SAY I'M WITH YOU.
I WATCHED THAT GIRL'S SHOW LAST
WEEK.
WHEW, IT WAS OFF THE CHAIN.
THEY EVEN GOT BUNNIES IN THE
POOL AND SHIT.
SHIT. I NEED TO BE THERE.
YOU NEED TO HOOK GREG UP.
>> YO, MAN, JUST CHILL, OKAY?
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
>> COOL.
LET'S GO PICK UP SOME GARBAGE.
>> [ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
GOOD LUCK TO YOU, MAN.
TAKE CARE.
>> YEAH. YOU, TOO.
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> HEY, LENNY, HOW'S IT GOING?
>> OH, HEY, GOOD.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> HEY, LENNY!
>> YO.
>> I MADE YOU A LITTLE
SOMETHING-SOMETHING.
>> OH, HEY.
AH, THANKS, MAN.
>> OH, MAN.
GREAT INTERVIEW, BRO.
DON'T FORGET TO HOOK GREG UP,
THOUGH.
>> NO, I WON'T.
>> ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
>> THERE HE IS. MAN OF THE HOUR.
>> AH, LENNY.
>> OH, WOW. THANK YOU.
>> OH, YOU WANT SOME KETCHUP?
>> NO, THANKS.
>> UH, SOMETHING TO DRINK?
>> OH, I'M -- I'M GOOD.
THANKS, MRS. TORRES.
>> OH, OKAY.
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
AND TELL ME, HOW WAS THE
INTERVIEW?
>> IT WENT GREAT.
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH. THANKS.
>> YO, LENNY!
>> HEY, LENNY.
>> HEY.
>> CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A
SECOND?
>> OF COURSE.
>> THIS IS KIND OF EMBARRASSING,
BUT SOMETHING I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT FOR A REALLY LONG TIME.
>> ME, TOO, YVETTE.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY LIKE YOU.
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT ABOUT CALLING
YOU A COUPLE OF DAYS AGO.
BUT BEFORE YOU SAY ANYTHING
ELSE, I JUST NEED TO WARN YOU
THAT I'VE GOT A LOT OF STUFF
GOING ON FOR ME RIGHT NOW, AND
I, UH -- I DON'T WANT TO HURT
YOU IN THE LONG RUN.
>> I JUST WANTED TO GIVE YOU MY
HEAD SHOT.
I WAS THINKING SINCE, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE GONNA BE OUT THERE, YOU
COULD PASS IT AROUND.
YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER KNOW.
>> YEAH. DEFINITELY.
>> I'M SORRY, LENNY.
I'M JUST NOT INTERESTED IN YOU
IN THAT WAY.
>> OH, IT'S FINE. NO WORRIES.
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> GREAT.
>> YOU GO GET THEM.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> OKAY.
>> HEY.
>> WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
>> COUPLE MINUTES AGO.
>> OH.
COOL.
>> YEAH.
SO, UH, WHEN'S YOUR LAST DAY?
>> WEDNESDAY.
LOOK, UH, BY THE WAY, I-I TOLD
CASEY THAT IF BEN STILLER WANTS
TO DO THE MOVIE OF THE WEEK,
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING IN
IT FOR YOU, 'CAUSE WE FOUND THE
OSCAR TOGETHER, SO WE SHOULD
BOTH BE IN THE MOVIE.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I'LL PROBABLY WORK FOR
MR. TORRES UNTIL I RETIRE, AND
YOU'LL GO ON TO DO BIG,
BEAUTIFUL THINGS, AND
THAT'S TOTALLY OKAY WITH ME.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
THIS HOLLYWOOD STUFF'S NOT FOR
ME, SO GO AHEAD WITH YOUR MOVIE,
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
REALLY.
>> WELL, WILL YOU STILL RETURN
THE OSCAR WITH ME?
>> YEAH, I CAN DO THAT.
>> GREAT.
HEY, MR. TORRES, I'D LIKE TO
RIDE WITH ABBOTT UNTIL MY LAST
SHIFT.
>> YEAH, SURE.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> CALL ME SENTIMENTAL OR
STUPID, BUT I'D LIKE TO PAY FOR
A COMPLETE OVERHAUL AND REFURB
ON ROSIE SO MY BUDDY HERE CAN
PUT ANOTHER 10, 20 YEARS ON HER.
>> WE'LL WORK SOMETHING OUT.
LISTEN, I WANT EVERYONE TO COME
OVER HERE.
I GOT TO SAY SOMETHING.
COME ON DOWN.
YEAH. COME ON.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS 13 YEARS AGO
WHEN LENNY BEGAN WORKING FOR OUR
COMPANY.
IN A FEW DAYS, IT'S GONNA BE HIS
LAST DAY.
[ CROWD GROANS ]
LENNY'S BEEN -- YOU'VE BEEN LIKE
A SON TO ME, LENNY.
YOU REALLY HAVE.
AND YOU'RE WELCOME TO COME BACK
HERE ANY -- ANY TIME, NO MATTER
WHAT.
OKAY?
LOOK, AS YOU ALL KNOW, LENNY IS
GONNA BE AIRING ON NATIONAL TV
TOMORROW WITH CUBAN JR.
THIS IS A MOMENT WE'VE ALL BEEN
WAITING FOR.
WE'RE REALLY HAPPY FOR LENNY.
CHEERS!
[ APPLAUSE ]
LENNY, COME HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> WHOO!
>> YEAH!
>> PROUD OF YOU!
>> YEAH, LENNY!
>> YOU THE MAN!
>> AH.
THANK YOU.
WOW. UH...
WELL, FIRST I WOULD LIKE TO
EXTEND A SPECIAL THANKS TO
MRS. TORRES, WHO MADE THIS
BEAUTIFUL PARTY POSSIBLE.
NEXT, I WOULD LIKE TO THANK
MR. TORRES FOR A WONDERFUL
13 YEARS AT
L.A. RUBBISH, INCORPORATED.
I WOULD ALSO LIKE TO THANK MY
BEST FRIEND, ABBOTT SMITH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND ALSO, MY FRIENDS ESTEBAN AND
YVETTE AND BERNARDO.
YEAH, I SEE YOU BACK THERE,
BERNARDO.
HEY!
AND WILLIAMS AND MORALES AND
EDITH IN ACCOUNTING.
[ CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING ]
UH, THEY'VE ALL BEEN REALLY
AMAZING.
UM, THEY'VE SUPPORTED ME
RELENTLESSLY AND UNYIELDING OVER
THE YEARS.
AND, LASTLY, I WOULD LIKE TO
THANK MY MANAGER, CASEY SIEGEL,
WHO COULDN'T BE WITH US TODAY,
BUT SHE HAS MADE IT POSSIBLE FOR
ME TO BE A SOMEBODY.
>> AND DON'T FORGET THE LITTLE
PEOPLES, MAN!
>> I'LL BE COMING BY TO SAY
HELLO.
YOU CAN COUNT ON THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> LET'S HAVE SOME FUN AND
MUSIC.
>> OH. NO, THANK YOU.
I ACTUALLY ALREADY HAVE A BEER,
BUT I APPRECIATE IT.
I AM. I AM.
>> LEONARD EATON.
HI. HI, I'M LEONARD EATON.
YOU CAN CALL ME LENNY.
[ BIRD CHIRPS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
>> WHERE ARE ALL THE CAMERAS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE THEY'RE INSIDE THE HOUSE.
>> YOU THINK?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T HAVE A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT THIS, MAN.
>> WELL...
[ DOORBELL RINGING ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> NOTHING?
>> NAH.
[ FEEDBACK ]
>> HEY, FELLAS.
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> COME ON OVER.
HOW YOU DOING?
>> GOOD. ABBOTT.
>> LEONARD.
I'M CUBA.
JUST JOKING. MICHAEL MADSEN.
IS THAT THE, UH, GOLDEN BOY?
LET ME SEE IT.
AH, IT SURE IS.
THAT'S HEAVY.
YOU COULD CLUB SOMEONE IN THE
HEAD WITH THAT.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU CAN USE THAT AS A WEAPON.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> MICHAEL?
>> YEAH?
>> IS CUBA HERE?
>> NO.
HE'S REALLY SORRY, BUT HE HAD TO
GO.
I'M HIS NEIGHBOR, AND HE SAID I
COULD COME OVER AND GET THE
OSCAR.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
I KNOW HE WILL, TOO.
HE'S GONNA THANK YOU PROFUSELY.
IF YOU GUYS STILL WANT THE
REWARD, YOU SHOULD GO HIT HIM UP
FOR IT, ALL RIGHT?
I'LL MAKE SURE HE GETS IT.
YOU GUYS WANT A DRINK?
>> UH, NO, THANK YOU.
MICHAEL, WHAT ABOUT THE, UH,
CAMERAS AND STUFF?
ARE THEY --
>> OH, THAT'S ALL BEEN
CANCELLED.
HE LEFT RIGHT AFTER HE GOT THE
CALL.
>> SO NO ONE'S HERE?
>> I'M HERE.
>> LIKE, I KNOW THAT, BUT
US WEEKLY AND OTHERS WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
>> I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA, ALL
RIGHT?
>> [ SIGHS ]
OKAY.
>> I JUST KNOW THEY'RE NOT HERE.
>> OKAY, UH, CAN YOU TELL ME WHY
IT GOT CANCELLED?
>> TO BE HONEST, I DON'T EVEN
KNOW.
ALL RIGHT?
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS HAVE A DRINK?
>> UH, THAT'S OKAY.
>> COME ON.
YOU CAME ALL THE WAY DOWN HERE.
GO AHEAD AND HAVE ONE.
>> UM, MR. MADSEN, CAN I ASK A
QUESTION?
>> SURE.
>> HOW DID THE OSCAR END UP IN
THE TRASH?
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
SPECULATION IN THE MEDIA.
>> WELL, IT'S MY THEORY THAT IT
WAS PROBABLY SOME ENVIOUS PRICK
AT A PARTY -- SOME PISSED-OFF
A-LISTER, SOMEBODY WHO'S
JEALOUS.
AND THEY PICKED IT UP AND THREW
IT IN THE TRASH.
>> I MEAN, CUBA, HE FELL APART
WHEN HE HEARD ABOUT IT.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE
A DRINK?
HAVE SOME SANGRIA.
IT'S CUT-UP FRUIT IN WINE.
IT'S REALLY GOOD.
GOOD FOR YOU, TOO.
I THINK THIS BATCH HAS A LITTLE
BIT TOO MUCH BRANDY IN IT,
THOUGH.
>> I'M GOOD. I'M DRIVING.
>> YOU'RE DRIVING?
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M NOT.
>> SO, MICHAEL MADSEN SEEMS
PRETTY COOL.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
[ SIGHS ]
[ GATE CLOSES ]
>> NOW WHAT?
[ SPEED-DIALING ]
[ RINGING ]
>> SIEGEL MANAGEMENT GROUP.
>> CASEY SIEGEL, PLEASE.
>> SHE'S NOT IN, MR. EATON.
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
[ SPEED-DIALING ]
[ RINGING ]
>> YOU'VE REACHED CASEY SIEGEL.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESS--
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
>> GIVE ME THE KEYS.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
>> HOW DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHERE
SHE LIVES?
>> I DROPPED HER OFF ONCE.
CASEY!
[ CAR DOOR CLOSES ]
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I WAS GONNA CALL YOU FROM THE
CAR.
IT'S BEEN A VERY EVENTFUL
MORNING.
HI, ABBOTT.
>> HELLO.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> EVERYONE CANCELLED.
>> W-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> BEN STILLER'S EMMY WAS STOLEN
FROM HIS HOUSE LAST NIGHT.
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> SOMEONE STOLE BEN STILLER'S
EMMY FROM HIS HOUSE.
>> YEAH, SO? WHO CARES?
>> EVERYONE CARES.
I MEAN, THEY CAUGHT THE THIEF.
IT'S THE HOTTEST STORY IN TOWN.
OPRAH'S AND E!'s PEOPLE
CANCELLED ON US, FLEW ON OVER
TO THE WEST HOLLYWOOD JAIL TO
COVER THE STORY -- US WEEKLY,
TOO.
IN FACT, I'M -- I'M ON MY OVER
THERE, UH, RIGHT NOW.
CAN WE -- CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS
A LITTLE LATER, GUYS?
>> THAT'S A BUNCH OF CRAP!
YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT NOBODY
WANTS OUR STORY?
>> YOU STILL HAVE THE CALIFORNIA
SECTION OF THE L.A. TIMES.
YOU HAVE THE -- THE
DAILY BREEZE.
I'M SORRY, BUT EVERYONE'S LOST
INTEREST AT THIS POINT.
>> UH...
UH, W-WHAT ABOUT THE, UH -- THE
TV MOVIE OF THE WEEK?
OKAY, TELL THEM THAT THEY CAN
HAVE THE RIGHTS ANY WAY THEY
WANT.
>> YOU KNOW, I SPOKE TO
BEN STILLER'S PEOPLE WHEN THE
STORY BROKE OUT, AND YOUR OSCAR
STORY'S TOO SIMILAR TO THE EMMY
STORY.
THEY WANT TO GO WITH THE NEWER
ONE.
IT'S MORE FRESH.
>> BUT THAT'S JUST AN EMMY!
I HAVE AN OSCAR!
AND THAT GUY IS A THIEF!
WE ARE THE GOOD GUYS HERE!
H-HOW CAN THIS BE HAPPENING,
CASEY?
I-I DON'T GET IT.
YOU.
YOU SCREWED EVERYTHING UP.
>> I SCREWED EVERYTHING UP?
>> YES.
>> YES, YOU DID.
>> I SCREWED EVERYTHING UP?
>> CONSIDER US NO LONGER IN
>> YES, YOU DID.
BUSINESS TOGETHER.
>> CONSIDER US NO LONGER IN
OKAY?
BUSINESS TOGETHER.
[ CAR DOOR OPENS ]
[ CAR DOOR CLOSES ]
>> WE HAVE A CONTRACT.
>> DID YOU EVEN READ IT?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> EVERYTHING'S FINE,
SWEETHEART.
THESE ARE JUST, UH, THE
GARBAGEMEN I USED TO REPRESENT.
>> OKAY.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> YOU'RE MARRIED TO
STEVEN BAUER?
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT, SIR.
>> IT'S OKAY.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU GUYS.
>> WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE ON TV BY
NOW.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE'S
MARRIED.
WHO'S STEVEN BAUER?
>> MANOLO FROM "SCARFACE."
>> HUH.
AND WHEN DID YOU DROP HER OFF
HERE?
>> W-WE WENT TO A-A RESTAURANT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
>> JUST THE TWO OF YOU?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I BET YOU THIS EMMY BUSINESS IS
A PUBLICITY STUNT BY BEN STILLER
SO HE CAN MAKE HIS OWN
TV MOVIE OF THE WEEK.
>> I SERIOUSLY DOUBT THAT,
LENNY.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
WHY WOULD HE NEED TO GO THROUGH
ALL THAT TROUBLE?
>> WELL, LET'S FIND OUT.
>> LENNY.
[ HORNS HONKING ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
LENNY!
LENNY, COME ON, MAN!
DO YOU REALLY THINK BEN STILLER
HAS NOTHING BETTER TO DO
THAN TO HIJACK YOUR STUPID
TV SPECIAL?
LENNY, SERIOUSLY!
>> BEN STILLER!
>> LENNY, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING?
GET OFF HIS PROPERTY, MAN!
>> BEN STILLER!
GET DOWN HERE NOW!
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU ARE?
YOU'RE A COCK BLOCKER!
>> WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
NO, NO, NO. OH, NO.
>> HEY!
OPEN UP!
COME ON!
>> LENNY, IT'S OVER. LET'S GO.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE,
STILLER!
COME DOWN HERE AND FACE ME
MANO Y MANO!
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE IN
US WEEKLY MAGAZINE!
THIS IS MY STORY!
THOSE PEOPLE WANTED TO HEAR MY
STORY, AND THEN YOU PULL THIS
EMMY CRAP!
>> DID IT EVER OCCUR TO YOU THAT
HIS EMMY WAS ACTUALLY STOLEN?
>> THAT'S BULLSHIT.
>> EMMY, MY FUCKING ASS!
STILLER! STILLER!
STILLER!
[ PANTING ]
>> IT'S OKAY, MAN.
LET'S JUST GO BACK TO WORK.
>> AS A MATTER OF FACT, LET'S
JUST DO THAT.
YOU WANT TO PICK UP SOME
GARBAGE?
LET'S PICK UP SOME GARBAGE!
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
>> LENNY!
WHATEVER YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
DOING, DON'T DO!
COME ON, LENNY!
STOP THE TRUCK!
AH, NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
LENNY! DAMN IT, LENNY!
STOP!
LENNY!
BEING IN US WEEKLY IS NOT THAT
BIG A DEAL, MAN.
>> SHOCK AND AWE, ZOOLANDER!
>> LENNY, STOP!
[ BEEPING ]
>> COME ON, ROSIE.
DROP IT!
>> OPEN THE DOOR BEFORE YOU
MAKE THINGS WORSE!
>> DAMN IT!
>> OPEN IT NOW!
DAMN IT, LENNY! STOP!
OPEN THE GODDAMN DOOR! NOW!
>> HYDRAULIC MALFUNCTION.
>> WHAT'S YOUR MALFUNCTION?
YOU NEED HELP, MAN.
GO DOWN.
[ WHIRRING ]
[ SIGHS ]
HYDRAULICS ARE OUT.
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
WE'RE FINISHED.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT.
I'LL TAKE IT TO THE LANDFILL.
WE'LL DEAL WITH IT THERE.
IT'LL BE JUST LIKE IT WAS
STOLEN -- JUST LIKE HIS
STUPID-ASS EMMY.
>> JUST LET IT GO, MAN!
>> NO WAY, MAN.
I'M NOT GOING DOWN LIKE THIS.
[ TRUCK BEEPING ]
>> STOP THE TRUCK.
ARE YOU INSANE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I DON'T CARE.
[ HORNS HONKING ]
>> [ WHISTLES ]
>> WHOO!
>> SHOULD'VE TAKEN SIDE STREETS.
>> THIS IS THE FASTEST WAY.
[ RATTLING ]
[ ENGINE SPUTTERING ]
TRANNY BURNED OUT.
[ HORN HONKS ]
>> ASSHOLE!
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
NOW YOU'LL MAKE YOUR HEADLINES.
[ SIREN WAILS ]
>> HEY.
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> YEAH, I UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE
WCVs HERE.
>> WHAT?
>> WASTE-COLLECTION VEHICLES.
>> OH. WHAT'S THE PLATE NUMBER?
>> IT'S, UH, 3PCI140.
IT'S A '93 VOLVO WX64.
IT'S A BIG, GREEN GARBAGE TRUCK.
>> YEAH, TOMORROW, IT'S
DEPARTING OUT TO BE RECYCLED.
>> YEAH. I, UH -- I CALLED IN.
I WANTED TO GET SOME PERSONAL
BELONGINGS.
>> SIGN IN. LEAVE YOUR I.D.
DOWN THE MAIN AISLE, THIRD LEFT,
AND A RIGHT.
>> THANKS.
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ CREAKING ]
I'M SORRY ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> ESPECIALLY FOR GOING OUT WITH
CASEY BEHIND YOUR BACK.
>> IT'S OKAY, MAN.
IT'S NOT LIKE I REALLY HAD A
SHOT WITH HER ANYWAY, RIGHT?
>> WELL.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO?
>> WELL, SINCE THEY DROPPED THE
CHARGES, I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR A
NEW JOB.
BUT I THOUGHT I'D FIND ONE FOR
YOU FIRST, YOU KNOW, TO SORT OF
MAKE UP FOR THINGS, SO...
HEY, LISTEN.
UH...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT CAME OVER ME.
I -- I WASN'T MYSELF ANYMORE,
AND --
>> IT'S OKAY, MAN.
I ACTUALLY ALREADY HAVE ANOTHER
JOB.
>> YOU DO?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
UM...WELL, I GUESS I'LL -- I'LL
SEE YOU AROUND.
>> TAKE IT EASY.
>> OKAY.
>> HEY!
THEY'RE ACTUALLY LOOKING FOR
ANOTHER GUY DOWN WHERE I WORK
NOW.
SO IF YOU'RE INTERESTED, WE CAN
GO TALK TO THE BOSS.
I THINK HE'S THERE FOR ABOUT
ANOTHER HALF-HOUR.
CHECK IT OUT.
>> SURE.
WHAT KIND OF JOB DID YOU GET?
>> HOP IN.
>> NO WAY.
YOU'RE DRIVING A STINGER?
YOU'RE WORKING IN THE VALLEY.
>> YEP!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> PAYS THE BILLS.
>> AND WE'RE GONNA TALK TO THE
PAPARAZZI FOLLOWING A CERTAIN
CELEBRITY'S BACKYARD...
>> ROSIE SOUNDED BETTER.
>> YEAH.
>> AND YOU GOT TO GET AN iPOD
ADAPTER.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
I GOT A GUY I WORK WITH NOW.
HE SELLS HIGH-END STEREO
EQUIPMENT.
HE SAID HE COULD HOOK ME UP FOR
CHEAP.
I GUESS HE JUST SOLD SOMETHING
TO SOME REALITY STAR.
>> OH, THAT'S COOL.
SO, WHAT PART OF THE VALLEY YOU
GOT?
PLEASE TELL ME IT'S SOUTH OF
VENTURA.
>> IT'S BASICALLY MOST OF THE
91416 AND THE 91335.
>> YEAH, THAT'S NOT BAD.
ENCINO'S A DECENT ENOUGH AREA.
I READ BRITNEY SPEARS MOVED TO
ENCINO RECENTLY.
I SAW A PIC OF HER HOUSE IN
US WEEKLY.
THE LOT IS AT LEAST A HALF AN
ACRE, WITH A 7,000-SQUARE-FOOT
HOUSE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE GONNA
SPEND THAT MONEY, WHY NOT BUY IN
BEV HILLS, YOU KNOW?
>> I SUPPOSE.
>> HEY, HOW MANY GRAMMYS DOES
BRITNEY SPEARS HAVE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
A FEW, I WOULD IMAGINE. WHY?
>> WELL, I'D SAY THE CHANCES ARE
ONE OF THEM ENDS UP IN THE
GARBAGE SOMEHOW.
>> OH, YOU THINK, HUH?
>> OH, YEAH.
YOU WANT TO SWING BY AND CHECK
IT OUT?