Um, subject: King,
just out of County,
participation mandatory
and details to follow.
All right, turn it off.
I'm not saying shit
till you turn the damn thing on.
So, um, what's your name?
King.
- How'd you get that name?
- It's always been.
Is that your real name
or your street name or...?
- Just my name.
- So how was--?
- Can I have a smoke?
- Sure.
Thanks.
- So how was jail?
- Oh, fuck.
- Can I--? Can I say "fuck"?
- Yeah.
It says here, "assault,
possession, loitering."
- That's pretty petty stuff.
- Yeah, right.
It's just survival.
A lot of kids tell you that they party
all night with Axl Rose,
or that their girlfriend
just got banged by the Crips,
or they've seen five guys
get murdered or something,
but the truth is, it's not hard.
It's not easy.
It just is.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
How long have you been
on the street?
Six or seven years.
How old are you?
Uh, 20, might be 21 .
I'm not exactly sure.
That's a good question, though.
Did you have any brothers
or sisters growing up?
Yeah, I got a sister,
but, uh, she's gone
from home too.
Maybe she'll show up here
in Hollywood sometime, you know.
I'll take care of her
or something.
I hope she's not into drugs
or anything. She probably is.
Might be dead.
What about your mom,
your dad?
- What about them?
- Do you, um--?
Not very comfortable
talking about them.
Yeah.
Hey, what the hell? Hey, you with
the camera, up here, I'm talking.
Drugs?
What kind you got?
Ha-ha, just kidding.
- What kind you do?
- Don't do them.
Hey, look, nobody's
gonna see this tape.
I'm not shitting you.
- I just want you to be straight with me.
- I'm being straight with you.
You do realise that your
participation in this program
is one of the terms of your parole.
Yeah, I also realise that
you're giving me 10 bucks
a pop for these sessions.
Thank you very much.
Is that why you decided
to participate in this program?
Because of the money?
Hell, it's better than
picking up trash on the freeway.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, are you--? Are you done?
Is that it? Can I go?
Just a minute. Um, where--?
Where are you gonna go?
Well, I've been in lockup
for two months, where the fuck
do you think I'm gonna go?
You going back out
on the street?
Yeah.
(MICKEY THOMAS'
"FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH" PLAYING)
INTERVIEWER: What--?
What do you do for fun?
KING (CHUCKLING):
Fun?
Anything we can.
Just kick back or hassle tourists.
Hell, we'd watch ice melt if it was free.
To hell with the devil!
(CROWD CHEERING)
I thank the Lord
you're all here tonight.
I pray that you find
what the Lord wants for you.
He has a purpose
for each and every one of you.
And us!
And remember,
God does not create trash!
(BAND PLAYING
"NO SURFING IN HELL")
(SINGING)
INTERVIEWER:
Do you have friends?
No. I got a family.
It says here you haven't
been with a family for--
My friends are my family.
Of course you can't trust them
for shit, but, you know,
once you know that, it's cool.
Greg! Little J!
(BAND PLAYING LOUDLY)
Hey, Greg! Shut up!
- Who threw that?!
- CROWD: He did!
- Hey, it's King!
- King, man, shit.
Hey, did you miss me?
Why'd you do that, brother?
Because you got terrible extensions
in your hair, and because you're just--
You're shitty.
- That's not funny!
- Why don't you jump, King?
INTERVIEWER:
What's a typical King day?
KING: A typical King day?
INTERVIEWER: Mm.
(KING COUGHS)
KING: Well, hit the streets,
hook up with my friends.
You know.
Kick back, hang out.
Stay out of trouble.
(CHEERING)
That's it. That's it.
That's it.
J: Hey! Let him go,
you fucking pigs!
Little J!
No! I'm not fucking around, man! Now!
Put that thing down!
You fucking heard me, man! Now!
You heard me!
Come on, come on. Let's go.
KING:
They're good people.
You'd like Little J.
He's a little shit, man, I'm telling you.
Skinny little fuck.
He's growing, though. It's wild.
He's hard to keep fed.
That's a tough habit.
J:
Hey, yo, wait up.
When'd you get out, man?
Just a couple short hours ago.
You on the streets,
or are you at home?
Fuck them, man.
I haven't been home
since you got busted.
What the fuck were you doing
back there, Little J?
What do you mean?
I was saving your fucking ass.
Don't ever pull a gun
on somebody again.
Get the fuck off of me.
lt's stupid.
It wasn't even loaded.
Well, that's even stupider.
Give it to me.
No.
Yes.
Where'd you find
this sissy piece of shit, anyway?
In the trash, man.
It don't even work.
Ah, it figures.
What the fuck
did you do that for, man?
Your own good.
Fuck you!
I'm out of here.
GREG:
I think you pissed him off, man.
Hey, Little J?
What?
You want that tat still?
What do you think, man?
I've been waiting two months
for the fucking thing.
Come on, then.
GREG: So how was jail, man?
KING: Boring. Easy.
Did you suck any cocks?
Just your dad's.
And they're going into the stretch.
Manny goes for the whip,
makes a bid for the outside! Whoo!
(WHISPERS)
Go ahead.
MANNY:
Run, motherfucker! Come on!
INTERVIEWER:
How do you get by on the street?
(KING COUGHS)
KING: Excuse me, I thought
we just went all over that stuff
with the assault and the possession and
the loitering and all that petty stuff.
Give it up, motherfucker!
You guys have turkey potpie?
This is, uh, vegetable beef, and I'm allergic
to anything with lard in it, or, um...
Do they cook the turkey
with lard?
Let me through!
Watch out! Watch out!
Pardon me, excuse me, pardon me!
(YELLS)
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Come on! Come on! Whoo!
Going into the stretch! Whoo!
I did bust your ass, boy.
I told you, you can't fuck
with this boy in this wheelchair.
See, man, that's one of
the advantages to being crippled.
Oh, get the fuck out of here.
Hey, fucking--
You've been in County
too long, King.
How you doing?
Hey, what's up, baby?
Hey, you're looking good.
Staying out of trouble, man?
Oh, I'm trying.
Let's get off
this street corner.
(COUGHING) Hey, you got a smoke?
Yeah, you need one.
MANNY:
So how was it up in County, man?
What, did you read a couple of books?
Yeah.
Did you lift some weights?
Yeah, a little bit.
You suck some dicks?
Now, come on.
It's great having you back
though, man.
Yeah, you're looking good.
You still a ugly
motherfucker, though.
KING:
Drugs is the toughest habit.
And friends.
Friends are tough to k eep too.
Hmm.
I don't know.
What do you think?
Do you want
to tell me something?
You want to tell me
some kind of little...
A little something about your day?
A little titbit?
A little titbit about you.
About your day.
Well, I'm just--
I'm looking to get out of here
and hook up.
You all right?
Yeah.
Don't be a puss.
Fuck you.
Okay, man. You gonna crash
with us in the hole tonight?
We saved your clothes and shit.
KING: No, I was gonna look
for Devon, maybe get some.
Has anybody seen her?
No, man, I ain't seen her.
What do you mean?
I mean, I ain't seen her, man.
Well, what in the fuck,
you guys?! Goddamn!
I told you to watch out
for my lady.
And-- So, what, is that
too much to ask, or what?
All right, look, King, man,
last time we seen her,
she was with that kid, Tommy Ray.
I think she's in his stable.
You've seen Devon
with Tommy Ray?
Yeah, she started swinging with him
when you got locked up.
Just out of curiosity,
were you gonna tell me?
Yeah.
Yeah? When?
I don't know.
Thank God you're back.
Hey, Brenda.
Who are you?
Heather.
KING: You just get here?
Two days ago.
BRENDA: She's from Chicago.
Trip out. Me too.
Bullshit, you're from Phoenix.
Brenda, you know, the next time
I want you to open your mouth,
I'll point at you.
Why don't you sit down.
You're making me nervous.
I'm King.
King? As in what,
Burger?
He's the one I told you about.
Yeah, I bet you did.
Hey, y'all, I was thinking
of maybe going and doing
a little train hopping.
Yeah.
How'd that be?
Cool.
Greg's got some speed, don't you?
I was thinking maybe we'd get
some pot and some mushrooms.
Let's get all fucked up.
Yeah, later. Hey, Crasher, come here.
Come here, man.
INTERVIEWER: So why do you think
so many kids come out here?
KING: Most kids come out to L.A.
looking for Hollywood.
BRENDA: Told you everything
would be cool, didn't I?
Usually, it's not what they expect.
You're from Chicago?
Yeah.
Crasher, I went in lockup
for two months, I get out,
and everything turns to shit.
I took a zip gun off
of Little J tonight.
And Greg is off,
tweaking his brains out.
And where the hell is my girlfriend?
I don't know.
Huh?
Well, what the fuck
do you know about?
Well, don't look at me
like it's my fault.
Crasher, man, you fucked me.
I asked you to look out
for everyone.
Well, you shouldn't
have done that.
That was a mistake.
I mean, shit, man,
nobody listens to me.
You're the only one
they listen to.
Shit, I'm older than you,
and I don't get that kind of respect.
Before you start pointing fingers,
you take a look in that fucking mirror.
That's the guy
you wanna blame.
You know, it's pretty lame
how you got busted that way.
You know, and then you
just, like, disappear
and figure, well, I'm just gonna,
like, keep tabs on everybody?
Well, guess again, pal.
On Devon?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, man...
but it's not my fault.
I didn't have anyone else
I could ask.
What are you doing?
You stink.
That's you, man.
It's not me.
It's you.
Someone could be dying
in the fucking streets,
and they won't do a thing.
But if you just so happen
to jaywalk,
10 of them will come out
of the woodwork.
Shit, I got busted last week
for jaywalking.
J: You got busted for being too fat.
Shut up, dickhead!
Oh, King. King, the trolls
are partying tonight
at the Western squat.
King?
Why doesn't anybody
fucking listen to me around here?
Hey, Mouse. How old are you?
Almost 18.
How come you moved to Holly-weird?
Just wanted to.
You wanna be a movie star, don't you?
No.
Yeah, you do.
No, I don't.
Why not?
I'm gonna be one.
Yeah, after you lose
about 1 00 pounds.
Brenda, I think you have star quality.
Yeah. Julia Roberts,
eat your heart out, baby.
Yeah, Sleeping With the Fat Girl.
BRENDA: Fuck you!
Fuck you, you stupid bitch.
KING: Hey, J.
J: Why don't you sit the fuck down.
BRENDA: Don't touch me.
KING: Hey, I had to sleep with
somebody for this big fucking joint.
No, I didn't.
Crasher. Have you seen Devon?
Is she here?
No, I ain't seen her,
but Tommy Ray is over there.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Tommy.
TOMMY:
Holy shit.
Well, well, well. lf it ain't the King
and his little band of butt pirates.
J: Hey, fuck you, man.
Fuck me? That's what I got in mind.
Who is this guy right here?
You know, for a kid,
you got a great ass.
I could make some money
with this kid.
I'm looking for Devon.
Yeah?
Well, who isn't?
Well, I ain't seen
the little cunt.
That's not quite how
I heard it, Tommy.
Yeah, well, don't believe
everything you hear.
Because that little fucking bitch
was stealing from me.
She stole my radio,
she stole my rock.
So naturally, I kicked
the fucking bitch out.
I mean, the last I heard is that
she got her face cut up real bad
and just...
No, no. I know her.
She's not robbing or stealing
or thieving. Nothing.
So, what are you doing?
You calling me a liar?
Hey, Tommy Ray, you got
your whole life to be an asshole.
Why don't you take tonight off?
Why don't you go
fuck yourself, huh?
J: All right, all right. Get the fuck off
of him, man. Get the fuck off of him.
CRASHER:
Be cool, be cool.
KING: Come on, where is she?
Why don't you do me a favour.
Why don't you bring back your friend
as soon as he gets some pubic hair.
J: Fuck you, man!
Pubic hair, that's good.
Come on, Greg. Don't be needy.
Check me.
Come on. No, fuck that.
Man, fuck Tommy Ray!
You shouldn't have tossed
my fucking gun.
I'm glad I did too.
I feel like killing somebody.
INTERVIEWER: Does your family live
in the hole which is under
the bridge of the--?
KING:
Under the freeway, yeah.
But not always there.
It depends on the weather,
and who's with us or who's already
there, but that's basically our home.
BRENDA: I'll sleep with you, King.
KING: Oh, Brenda, now that's sweet.
I'm just not sure
I'm up to the challenge.
BRENDA: And why not, baby?
J: Because you're too fat is why not.
BRENDA: Shut up, fool!
J: Fuck you, bitch. I ain't no fool.
BRENDA: Yeah, you are.
You're a scrawny little piece of shit.
I'm sick of hearing your trap.
If I wanna sleep with King,
I'll sleep with King.
You know.
Keep your butt out of it.
Just shut the fuck up!
No!
Hey, J, stay out of her hair,
or she's gonna keep us up all night.
I know. I know.
Here. Here.
KING: Hey, where you guys staying?
BRENDA: We been at the Bowl Motel.
Shit, who's paying for that?
HEATHER: I paid for it.
Well, I ain't whoring.
J: Yeah, sure you ain't.
Listen, you save your money.
This one here will take you
for a ride.
I'm gonna get a job.
You know shit, dick-for-brains.
It's, "You know dick, shit-for-brains."
So get one.
I think either is correct.
It's a declarative sentence,
so the juxtaposition of the adjective
is appropriate in either case.
Hey! Nobody here take
any of Heather's money.
I'd take that personal.
J: Oh, okay, King.
I won't take it from her.
KING: I don't think that would be right.
J: Okay, I won't.
BRENDA: She's my buddy.
I'm taking care of her.
She's my buddy. Right?
Little J, what's the aerosol du jour?
I don't know, just something
I picked up in Nam.
When I was down in County,
Greg came down, but...
Like he was gonna get 500 bucks
to bail me out?
It's nice, though,
to have somebody that...
wanted to.
KING: Hey.
Hey, what's up?
You want some?
You should try and get some sleep.
Nah.
You gonna sleep
with Heather tonight?
Not tonight.
When I went in lockup,
I couldn't sleep for the first week.
I was used to the fucking freeway.
Have to get used to it again.
You having fun?
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm totally fucking tweaked.
Can I scratch that for you?
Can we do something
tomorrow night?
Yeah.
Can we?
I'd like that.
All right, I'm out of here, man.
King...
it's good to have you back, man.
Thanks.
It makes me feel better,
you know?
Can I have one?
Morning.
Hi.
That's the best I can do.
That's good.
HEATHER:
Where'd you learn that?
KING: I don't know.
I've been doing it forever.
How long you been picking
at your nails?
People can come into your life,
and you can become very close.
And then they're gone in a week,
and you never see them again.
INTERVIEWER:
How do you feel about that?
There's nothing I can do about it.
What were you
locked up for?
Assault with
a deadly weapon.
This bum was trying to rob me,
so I hit him with a bottle.
He got three stitches,
and I got three months.
One month suspended.
Brenda said you killed him.
Yeah, well, Brenda,
she says a lot of things.
I'd believe about...none of them.
Could I ask you a favour?
What kind of favour?
Oh, just a simple favour.
Maybe.
INTERVIEWER: So within
your family, do you have
some kind of code of honour?
KING: Yeah.
INTERVIEWER: What is it?
KING: Let's just say
we look out for each other.
MAN (OVER SPEAKERS): Attention,
please, now arriving, Gate 5,
bus number 3 7 1
from San Francisco.
Excuse me.
You, um, got a light on you?
Got a cigarette?
Absolutely.
Thought I was gonna
go fucking nuts.
They don't let you smoke
on the bus.
Yeah? Long trip, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, Tommy.
(YELLING)
You fucking bastards!
Shit!
J: You look good, Tommy!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Shit!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Goddamn it!
Hey, Sleeping Beauty.
Can you fix this fucker?
What is it?
It's a piece of shit!
I don't know, man. I could try.
Well, if you can fix it,
you got a quarter of meth.
Move over.
Shit, I can do it for that.
Put on a goddamn shirt.
Oh, why don't you?
Where's the milk? Goddamn! Fuck!
I just fucking bought this yesterday.
You know, I'm sick of this!
Nobody should be allowed
in this refrigerator except us.
Climb in and shut the fucking door.
No, fuck you! Fucking--I
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
Fuck.
Come here, man.
You wanna slam a speedball?
No, man.
My treat.
No, fuck that, man.
No needles.
Good boy. Just say no.
I say yeah.
KING: When's the last time you ate?
Yesterday.
J:
Fuck.
I can't get this
stupid fucking thing.
J, now, give it up, man.
You're never gonna get it.
Yeah.
You want another burger?
I'll take one too, buddy.
Fuck you, little buddy.
So you gonna spend
the night with me, baby?
He likes you.
Oh, yeah?
Definitely.
How can you tell?
I can tell by the way he's acting.
He's trying to be all cool.
J: Bitch is right.
Besides, you're
a dead ringer for Devon.
Who's that?
His ex-old lady.
He killed her.
Really?
Yeah, just fucking stabbed her
right in the gut and cut her up
into little pieces.
But don't tell him I told you that.
It could get a little messy.
I won't.
He's very touchy about it.
And, you know, who knows
when he might strike again.
He's lethal.
Shh!
KING: Here you go.
Thanks.
KING:
Fucking Brenda, I bought that for her.
Don't you share?
INTERVIEWER: So...
what's the first thing you learn
on the street?
KING: You try not to get
too high or too low.
You just learn to watch your back.
Oh, shit. Oh, fuck.
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S
"ROYAL STATION 4I16" PLAYING)
HEATHER:
I'm telling you, this is crazy.
What happens if you miss?
GREG: Then you die, baby.
KING: You're not gonna die.
J: Well, I mean, you might.
J.
CRUSHER: Guys, here it comes.
KING: You guys go ahead.
I'll wait for her.
Let's go! Let's go!
(YELLS)
J.
Oh, yeah! Little J, all right!
Come on!
Okay, it's our turn.
You can do it.
HEATHER: I can't!
KING: Yes, you can!
If you can't, then you got to anyway.
If we're gonna go, we gotta go now.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
All right!
Hey, Little J!
Where's the beer?
Um, they were--
They were all out.
HEATHER:
What do we do now?
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
INTERVIEWER: So when you don't
stay in shelters and you don't
have a curfew,
that's the kind of thing
that you do at night?
Yeah, you know...
just kicking back, fucking around.
Just trying to--
Trying to have fun.
Like kids do, you know, like kids.
These kids are kids.
Come on, man. Fuck.
Fucking will you come on?
Hold on.
Fuck. Oh, goddamn it.
Fuck, come on, bro.
I'm coming! Yeah.
Fuck. Come on, come on.
It's about fucking time, man.
You got a light?
KING: I got high the first time
when I was 8.
INTERVIEWER: Ever tak e heroin?
KING: No, I never shot heroin.
INTERVIEWER:
But you did other drugs?
KING:
Well, pot, alcohol,
meth, mushrooms, acid.
I had a great trip
on Hollywood Boulevard one time.
I was, like, trying to scrape
the stars off the sidewalk.
It was totally wild.
You do this?
A couple years ago.
It's beautiful.
So, what, you've been here
about seven years?
Yeah.
In L.A. Three or four
here in the hole. On and off.
You wanna go sit over here?
Why?
Why not?
You're a little edgy, aren't you?
Well, maybe I am.
I mean, what's this I hear
about you killing your girlfriend?
It's a joke.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Well, I think we're gonna
go back to my van.
We gotta get something
straight between us.
Why don't you come over here
and sit by me.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I just don't
wanna do any more.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to scare you.
What the hell
do you wanna do?
Sleep.
Come to think of it,
I'm kind of tired myself, I guess.
Here. Take my sleeping bag.
Make yourself comfortable.
It's okay.
No, it's okay. I got an extra one.
It's gonna be real cold.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I got 98.6 over here, baby.
Body temperature.
(GIGGLING)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
Slow down, bro. Take this.
Fuck.
Oh, shit, man.
That's the new BMW.
No, don't fuck with that, man.
That one got alarms.
Yeah, man.
Yo, fuck, let's get out
of here, man!
Little J's kind of an artist,
though. Graffiti artist.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You probably seen his tag
all over town. It's like a--
You know, L with a wide bottom
that goes into a J.
L.J. It's all up and down
Cahuenga. Every block.
One night he said he was gonna
get every block up to the freeway.
And he did.
Fuck!
Fuck! Oh, you little fucker!
Hey, you little fucker!
Come here. Come here.
Problems?
Yeah, one named Little J.
Hey!
Fucking asshole!
What'd he do?
He almost got us busted, man,
and then he dropped
the fucking stereos
that we already fucking had!
Come here!
Leave him alone!
You're stronger than him!
Fuck you!
I'm out of here!
Where you going?
What the fuck do you care, man?
I give you guys everything.
My money, my fucking drugs,
and all you do is stick up
for this little faggot!
Forget about it!
Fuck you, I'm out of here.
J: Fucking speed freak.
Shut up, J.
Shut up.
Go to bed.
Is she staying
with us too?
Just go to bed.
Excuse me, can you spare
some change? A penny?
Anything, please?
CRUSHER:
Do you know what time it is?
Spare some change
so me and my sister
can get something to eat.
Excuse me, sir. Could you spare
a little change so my father here
and I could get a little something eat.
Hey, man, fuck you, your father,
you Axl Rose-looking motherfucker!
I ain't your fucking father, man.
Got any spare coins, bitch?
Please, give me some money!
Excuse me, sir. Sir.
Spare some change so I can
give my horse some feed.
Just a little something, sir.
Thank you very much.
He's got an
unfair advantage.
(SINGS)
That's fucked up.
Hello, officers.
Why don't you cut the bullshit.
Were you down
at the bus station yesterday?
No, I wasn't at the station.
No, I wasn't.
You're on parole,
aren't you?
Yes, sir. And I'm obeying
all the terms of my parole,
I assure you.
Let's hope so.
Why don't you get
your butt off my car.
Yes, sir.
Get out of here.
What's your name, miss?
Heather.
My mother would die
if she knew I was being
harassed by cops.
She says you have
to contribute to society.
Your mother talks a lot of shit.
Yeah.
I'm sure she's
a very nice lady.
She's gotta be real pretty.
KING:
What's one of my lines?
INTERVIEWER:
Yeah, what's one of your lines?
KING:
Buddy, can you spare a dime?
(INTERVIEWER CHUCKLES)
That one doesn't usually work.
But, no, you can say
pretty much anything.
People, you know, they can tell
when you need money.
And when I get money,
I give it to somebody that's
less fortunate than me,
so I figure it goes around.
(LOUD GUITAR PLAYING
INSIDE APARTMENT)
Is Ted here?
Ted.
TED: Who is it?
VICKI: It's Greg.
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
Aspirin?
No, man. I'm trying to quit.
So, what do you need, huh?
More meth?
Yeah, man.
That shit will drive you crazy
after a while.
Sure you don't wanna slam
one of these?
No, man.
Suit yourself.
Just say no.
(MOANS)
Here you go, man.
Hey.
Where's the cash you owe me?
Man, I'll get it.
Come back when you do.
I was thinking maybe
you could just front me a little bit?
No. No can do, bro.
I can't do that no more.
Times are changing.
Maybe I could make
another run for you
like I did that one time?
Just get the cash you owe me and
take a shower. You really stink.
Now, out of here. Come on.
(DOOR OPENS)
INTERVIEWER: You do spare
changing, stuff like that,
but you don't walk the streets.
What does
"walk the streets" mean?
It means I never had
to fuck anybody for money.
INTERVIEWER:
But you've seen lots of kids do it.
KING:
Yeah, you see lots of kids do it.
Boys and girls.
You know, when they're growing up,
they never think that that's
how it's gonna turn out,
and they wak e up one morning,
and there they are doing it. You know?
J: Hey, Kimmy!
Hey, Little J.
Where you staying?
The Hills Motel.
How many people you got?
Five.
Who?
Some of Rob's asshole friends.
How much you paying?
Seven bucks. Unless
a trick buys it for us.
Can I use your shower?
Yeah. Hello? Hi, is Dave there?
Yeah, go ahead. Go for it. Go.
Thank you.
Hi, yeah, Dave. Hi, it's Kimmy.
Do you wanna have a date tonight?
It's that first time that's--
Gets them. I've seen them.
I've just never had a first time.
HEATHER:
Where are all the hookers at?
KING: Well, most of the scuzzy ones
work downtown or in the Valley,
but a lot of them go through
those escort services.
Excuse me, sir?
Me and my sister haven't had
anything to eat in a couple days.
Could you help us out?
Thanks.
King?
Hm?
Have you ever?
No. No.
Not unless you count
sleeping with some girl
just to have a place
to lay your head down...
shut your eyes,
you know what I mean?
No.
Good.
Oh, my goodness,
what's that?
INTERVIEWER: So, what happens
when the cops bust a squat?
Well, usually they're pretty cool,
but I have to get the kids out of there
because they'll run them through
Missing Person or Runaway, you know,
and they'll just send them on home.
I wouldn't let any of my friends
go home. It's worse there.
I swear.
And the hardwood floors
were redone about a year ago.
Can I call you back?
Someone's at my back door.
Okay, thanks, bye-bye.
Well, look who we have here.
You've been gone what,
two months?
Greg, can I ask you
how long you plan on staying?
Greg, talk to me!
Shut up!
Greg! I'm calling your father.
Fuck you!
KING: Man, I wouldn't let any
of my friends go home.
J: Hey, thanks
for the shower, man.
MAN: You look like
a drowned fucking rat.
J: Rob, how old are you?
ROB: What's it to you?
J: I don't know.
Just asking.
ROB: I'm 22, but I could
pass for 1 7. Why?
J: I need to buy some bullets,
but they won't sell them to me.
What do you need them for?
Ah. Let me see that.
See with your eyes,
not with your hands.
You're an asshole.
Will you buy them?
I mean, I got the money.
Well, maybe.
If you do something for me.
Like what?
I got this trick later, but I don't
wanna see him. I'm busy.
Maybe you can go
in my place.
No way, man. I'm not down
for that shit.
He's a cool old guy.
He won't even touch you.
You don't need to touch him
or nothing.
No.
Okay.
Sure is a sweet gun.
I mean, what's the use of a gun
if you ain't got no bullets?
It's pretty fresh.
Okay, it's your loss.
I mean,
it sure is a shame you don't got
any ammo for that fresh gun.
Fucking dick.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
Cheap piece of shit.
(PAPERS CRINKLING)
(KNOCKING)
MAN:
Greg?
Greg? Can you open
the door?
Greg, open the door, son.
What do you want, Dad?
Your stepmom and I
wanna talk with you downstairs.
Dad, we got nothing
to say, man.
Just open the door.
I want to speak with you
downstairs.
Open the door!
What do you fucking want?
We wanna talk with you downst--
I don't see what there is
to talk about. I'm 17 years old--
What the fuck is he doing here?
You're under arrest for grand theft.
I didn't steal a fucking thing.
You took the jewellery.
You get what you deserve, Greg!
You fucking bitch!
You put him up to this!
FATHER: You need help.
GREG: Goddamn it!
You're quite young,
aren't you?
Yeah.
I, uh, sell those.
If you ever need one,
just let me know.
Okay.
Well, uh, could I get you something?
Maybe a Coke or some juice?
An ashtray would
be nice, thanks.
No, look, nobody smokes
in this house.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Look, I gotta get going.
Why don't we take care
of business, all right?
Business?
Yeah, you know...
a jerk-off...
or whatever turns you on.
Could I ask you
a question?
Yeah.
When was the first time you had sex?
I was about...
About 1 2.
Who was it with?
This chick at school.
When was the first time
you had sex with a man?
About 10 or 11 , I guess.
So you had sex with a guy
before you had sex with a girl.
Yeah.
Who was it with?
My uncle.
Oh.
Look, I know you're paying me,
but what is this crap?
Did you enjoy it?
Do you wanna talk, or what?
What if I were to ask you
if I could touch your face?
Would that be all right?
Would you mind?
No.
Whatever.
This is a good place to know about.
You can come in the afternoon,
get something to eat.
Some nights you can get a bed
if it's not too crowded.
They got a lot of rules, though.
I think I broke most of them.
You gotta sign in.
I can't stay.
I gotta go to this interview.
They got me being
this community service
guinea pig.
Can I be your Habitrail?
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Hey, bro.
Hi, sorry I'm late.
INTERVIEWER: That's okay.
So, what's the topic today?
Well, what do you want to talk about?
What, are you out
of questions already?
Mm.
Have you seen this one?
Yeah, I saw that.
You did. How about this one?
Heads or tails?
Heads.
Cheating.
Yeah, we got that one.
I know, I'll show you my tattoo.
Wow.
You like that?
I got one on my right arm too.
That's great.
I did that myself, left-handed.
Mm-hm. Wow.
My dad did this one
when I was 14.
Really?
Do you still keep
in touch with him?
What happened?
I don't know. Um...
I don't know. He's probably
dead or something.
See, tattoos weren't
his only thing.
He had a taste for
all kinds of needles.
INTERVIEWER:
You feeling pretty good
these days?
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty
good these days.
Got a little cough,
though.
Some days I feel good,
some days I don't,
like everybody else.
Yeah, actually, I get along
with them really well.
I needed a short break
or something.
Okay, you ready to go?
Yeah.
I see you met Stephanie.
Come on.
Thanks.
See you later.
Faggot.
Fucking fag. Fuck.
(GUNSHOT)
So, what are your drugs
of choice?
Um...
Crystal.
Mm.
Pot sometimes.
Coke if I can get it.
Mm.
When did you,
uh, start using?
When I was about 10 or 11 .
Well, it says here the first time
you ran away, you were 9.
You ran to your mother's.
Why the hell did you do that?
I wanted to live with her.
But her and I don't get along so good.
Mm.
What about your father?
You, uh--? You like him?
Yeah, he's all right.
But he got you arrested.
Yeah, well, life goes on.
Yeah, life goes on.
You know, I gotta tell you,
you're a very lucky guy.
You know that?
See, you've been given
a second chance here.
You could've just gone straight
to a lockup, but you're in a rehab.
I gotta be honest with you.
I'm a little hesitant to take you in.
You see, you have this habit
of running away.
I mean, what's my guarantee
that you're not gonna run
from us, huh?
Well, I need help with my problem.
Excuse me, miss?
Can you spare some change?
All I want is a little something to eat.
Skank!
How you doing, cripple?
Hey, Tommy, get your
stinking-ass breath out of my face.
Let's take a little ride.
Hey, Tommy, get the fuck off me.
You gonna wiggle out of this thing?
Get off me!
You're infringing on
my fucking civil rights, man.
Get off! Fucking bitch,
get off of me, man.
Sit the fuck down.
Why don't you leave me the fuck alone!
I didn't do shit to you, man!
Tommy, leave me the fuck alone!
Get off me!
Relax, asshole.
I'm just looking for King.
Have you seen him?
I think I did see King.
I think he went down
to the corner.
You know, your grandmama's
down there spit-shining dicks again.
Dealing balls today.
Two for the price of one.
Hey, man, get the fuck off me!
I asked you a question.
Didn't you hear me?
Yeah, I fucking heard you.
"Yes, sir."
Suck my fucking dick!
"Yes, sir," asshole.
Yes, sir, asshole.
No!
Just "yes, sir."
Yes, sir.
That's better.
Where do I find King?
Down at the hole.
The hole.
Nice hat.
You know, Tommy,
you're a punk bitch!
Oh, yeah, I almost
forgot something.
(CRASHES)
Hello, family.
PATIENTS (IN UNISON):
Hello, Cynthia.
We're taking away radio privileges
until you can learn what being
a family is.
Also, welcome a new family member.
Say hello to Greg.
PATIENTS (IN UNISON): Hello, Greg.
What's up?
Hey, where's King?
He's up there, man.
(WHISPERING)
King.
King, get up.
(SCREAMING)
Hey! Help! Somebody, help!
Help!
BRENDA: King!
HEATHER:
Leave him alone!
(SCREAMING)
(KIDS YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
BRENDA:
Little J.
(GUNSHOT)
(KIDS YELLING)
(WHISPERS)
Oh, fuck.
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S
"PRECIOUS PAIN" PLAYING)
J.
BRENDA: King.
HEATHER: King.
BRENDA:
Are you okay?
CRASHER:
Come on, come on. Let's go!
HEATHER:
Oh, fuck!
CRASHER:
Shit!
BRENDA:
Oh, shit.
KING:
Shit.
HEATHER:
You okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
What are you doing?
I gotta see what's keeping
Crasher so long.
It's okay. I'll do it, okay?
Stay here.
Oh, God.
Come on.
What? What is it?
We gotta get out of here, okay?
Give me your arm.
Crasher's in trouble.
INTERVIEWER:
You have trouble with the cops?
KING:
You gotta always watch the cops.
They're gonna bust you for loitering
just so they can find out
who you are.
I always tell the kids
to stay off the streets
until after school's out. It's easier.
What do you really feel
about me coming in here
and asking you questions,
putting it on tape?
Well, I feel like I have to, but...
I feel better about it
than I thought I was going to.
You know that runaway shelter?
They got this thing...
this program where they
contact kids' parents,
and they arrange it so that
they can go back home.
So?
So you can go back to Chicago.
I think you should.
I don't wanna go back.
Do you want me to go back?
I think it might be a good idea.
You don't seem to realize
we're in a lot of trouble.
I know that!
Then why are you acting
like such a jerk?
Because you're an asshole,
that's why.
I'm not trying to be an asshole.
I'm just trying to live my life
the way I fucking want to.
Everything is fucked up.
This world's fucked up. It's fucked up.
And everybody's miserable,
and they're only happy
if you're miserable too.
Lady, will you kindly get out
of my motherfucking face?!
Shit.
Did you have to be so rude to her?
Rude? Who's rude?
You are! Can you blame
the little lady for looking at you?
I'm looking at you.
You look like a fucking fool.
You got spit coming out of your mouth.
Can you yell a little louder?
Yell a little louder.
Come on, come on.
Sorry.
Shit.
It's okay.
But I'm not leaving town
unless you're coming with.
Sorry, lady.
You're mad.
You're embarrassing.
Get away from me.
What the fuck are you doing here?
He's staying with us, I told you that.
You told me fucking shit.
I did fucking tell you three times.
He's staying with us.
He's helping out with the rent.
Oh, yeah?
Chill out, man. Chill.
Shut the fuck up!
You're a little fucking slut!
You're a little slut.
Seven bucks, you got it?
No, not yet.
Well, then go get it.
Did you smoke my pot?
No.
You fucking better not have.
Hey, get the fuck off of me!
Hey, come here.
KIMMY: Shut up!
ROB:
Shut up!
What the fuck
are you looking at?
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S
"OCCASIONALLY" PLAYING)
Excuse me, sir,
do you have any change?
Hi, little girl.
Do you have
any money on you?
Some change
or a dollar or something?
Do you have any spare change?
Nothing? I just wanna get
some money together.
Any change so I can
get some food?
Sir, I hate to bother you,
I'm just trying to get some change.
Mom, I can't, not with him there.
No, Mom, I gotta go, all right?
I just wanted to call you
and tell you I'm fine.
Bye, Mom.
How do you feel?
I slept.
How'd you do?
No shit.
That's, like, 30 bucks.
We should've been down here
the whole time.
Pretty good, huh?
I'll say. It's incredible.
Now we can eat. I'm starving.
We can get a motel room.
Oh, shit, that's
a waste of money.
Well, I earned it,
so end of discussion.
Well, I guess you're the boss.
Yeah.
Is that right?
Come on.
You okay?
Ow! Ow.
Whoo!
Oh, my goodness.
This is great!
Nine-point-two.
Listen, I can wash all my stuff,
I can watch TV,
I'm in a bed, I can watch
Laverne & Shirley.
What?
Nothing. It's nice to see you so happy.
Well?
Nothing. It's nice.
You're--
What?
Nothing.
Well, I'm gonna go take a shower.
Yeah, me too.
You go first.
No, go ahead.
No, go.
After you.
No, go. You smell.
No, you--
Come on, you had
to have known.
You stink.
OFFICER:
Take off the hat.
A pimp named
Tommy Ray White
was killed last night.
Oh, that's terrible.
No, not really.
But we do need
some information.
I don't know anything
about it.
I'm not saying you do.
But we hope your friend
King might.
We just want to talk to him.
Just talk, that's all.
Think you might be able
to tell him that next time
you see him?
Yeah, sure,
I can tell him that.
I mean, if I see him, you know.
OFFICER: You'll see him.
HEATHER:
What's wrong?
Where the fuck did Little J
get a gun? I told him
not to fuck with guns.
Oh, man. Fuck.
Here, let me help.
Yeah.
Jesus.
Yeah, he got me.
The bastard.
What do you think happened?
Do you think he died?
Maybe.
It's gonna be okay.
No, it's not okay! It's not okay.
We're sitting in this motel
like nothing's wrong,
and Crasher's in fucking jail
for all I know.
Where's Little J?
It's not okay.
It's not supposed to be
like this at all.
(CRYING)
I'm sorry.
(WHISPERS)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
CHARLES:
Have a seat up here.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I was just, uh--
What do you need?
Nothing.
You know...
I do have a spare bedroom
if I thought I could trust you.
Well, I suppose you could
stay here a few days.
Would you like that?
That'd be great.
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S
"PRECIOUS PAIN" PLAYING)
(KNOCKS)
Hey, man.
What do you need?
I thought maybe I could
get a little taste, man.
You got money?
Not on me, man.
What are you doing here, man?
I thought--
No.
Why don't you ever ask me
anything about myself?
Like what? I just met you.
I don't know. Like, anything.
Like why I left home,
what my family's like,
how I got here.
I know why you left home.
Think you're pretty clever, huh?
No.
No, really.
I bet you've known
a lot of girls like me.
No, I haven't.
So tell me,
why did I leave home?
Man, forget about it.
No, really, I'd like to know.
Well, one or two reasons.
Either your father molested you
or your stepfather did.
You're a jerk.
Why else would you
be here?
That painting's really spooky.
Yeah, it's freaky.
It looks like the devil.
It looks like the Grim Reaper.
My father didn't fuck me,
my brother did, so a lot you know.
I'm sorry.
I am.
Open the fucking register!
Get out of here! Fuck you!
Motherfucker, sit down!
Back off! Stay the fuck down!
Fuck you! I call the police
on you, motherfucker!
Checkout time was half-hour ago.
Oh, shit.
I think we should get up and go
and get some more money
like we did yesterday.
It was so good on the pier.
Listen.
We could get something to eat.
That money? That's some of
the money I had with me
from Chicago.
Oh.
I didn't make anything
on the pier.
Why'd you lie to me?
I don't know,
maybe I just thought I had to.
(MUMBLES) I can't stand it.
What are you mumbling about?
I don't want you to be me.
What are you talking about?
I don't want you
to be me, Mouse.
I see people on the street
every day and I just see myself,
and I don't wanna see you--
I don't wanna see that happen to you.
It won't happen to me.
Won't happen to us.
I promise.
Collect call from Greg.
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
WOMAN:
Hello?
Hi, Mom.
Greg?
Greg, where are you?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Greg, are you all right?
I love you.
Greg? Greg?
CHARLES: Do you skateboard?
J: Yeah.
Well, I used to
when I lived in Boston.
CHARLES: How long you live there?
J: About 1 3 years...
then I moved to New York
for a while, and then
I came here.
Did you like New York?
Nah.
Well, you're a long way from Boston.
Yeah.
Why'd you leave?
I broke my probation.
Yeah? What'd you do?
Assault and battery.
But that's bullshit.
I never should have gotten it.
All I did was hit this teacher
after she tried to hit me,
and she never got
in trouble for it.
Fat bitch.
If I saw her again,
I swear to God, I'd hit her.
(GRUNTS)
Jesus Christ, man.
You look like shit.
So...
your old man got you busted, huh?
Yeah.
Man, life is a real bitch.
How long since you slept, anyway?
I don't know, four days.
You gotta sleep, man.
It's too hard, man.
It's too hard.
You want some vodka?
No, fuck that.
I could do that all night,
that ain't gonna help.
So, what do you want me
to do about it?
You want some help?
Huh?
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, I do.
All right.
I'm only doing this
so you can sleep.
Starting tomorrow,
I want you to cut down
on your speed.
Cheap-ass drug, man.
Is it gonna hurt?
Man, is it gonna hurt?
No.
Lights out, boy.
You got the law after you.
What?
Yeah, they think you
killed Tommy Ray.
Me?
I didn't kill him.
I didn't touch anybody.
I know you didn't.
He didn't do anything.
I know he didn't!
I'm gonna kill Little J.
Oh, man, I can't
go back to jail. I can't.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Well, I'm leaving.
KING:
Where are you going?
Dallas.
Dallas?
Yeah, Dallas. Y'all ought to come
with me too.
Shit. It's great there.
We should, huh?
You wanna go
to Dallas?
I'm gonna get myself
a big old lady with
some fucking gnarly--
You know what I mean?
Maybe a couple pit bulls.
How'd that be, huh?
Sounds good, doesn't it?
I don't know.
Yeah, well, don't think
about it too long, King.
Because as soon as I score
some speed, like I need it,
I'm off like a bride's nightie.
What's that smell?
That's you, motherfucker.
That is you.
That's you.
You smell very bad.
It's you.
You're handsome, but you stink.
You stink.
No, seriously, though, man,
y'all ought to come with me.
Fuck, I tell you what.
Why don't you meet me back here
in, say, like, a half-hour?
Come on, man, let's go.
Yeah. No, you're right.
Fuck this place.
You're right. I gotta get out too.
We'll get Little J and Greg,
and maybe we'll come.
Yeah. Anyway, if I don't see you,
it's good knowing you.
Yeah, you too.
Yeah. Have a good life.
It's nice to meet you, Heather.
Take care.
Later days
and better lays, y'all.
You didn't do shit.
Yeah, well, that doesn't matter.
(TV PLAYING)
I want you out of here.
I want you out of here now!
I heard you the first time!
No, don't hurt me. Don't hurt me.
Don't hurt me.
(GROANING)
Oh, fuck.
Oh, you gave me shit, man.
TED: What the fuck
you talking about?
Oh, you tried to cheat me,
motherfucker!
You gave me shit!
Take this, man!
I don't cheat nobody!
You wanna buy from
somebody else, kid, you do it.
I don't wanna sell to you no more.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Ted.
You just can't handle it, man.
I can.
Sit down.
I'm sorry, man.
I didn't mean it, man.
I'm sorry.
You're practically
my brother, man.
If I would've known
you couldn't handle the smack,
I never would've given it to you.
I can handle it.
The fuck you can!
Look at you.
You stink, man. What the hell
is wrong with you?
Nothing.
Nothing! Fuck that!
I'll tell you what's wrong
with you.
You're a spoiled little shit who's
ended up on the streets and thinks
he's a bad man with an attitude.
You're nothing but a punk,
man, that's it. A punk
who can't handle his drugs!
Fucking pathetic.
All right. From now on,
it's cash only.
Maybe that'll help you
slow down a little.
You still got cash,
don't you?
Well, all right.
What do you want?
A quarter?
No.
I'll give you a 20 piece.
That's it.
Okay.
Show me your cash.
Have you seen him?
You just missed him.
And too bad for you.
He had a bunch of money
and bought me all this food.
Where'd he go?
Hey, hey.
To score some speed from Ted.
Shit. Thanks.
Young love. Sheesh.
You just do like we said, all right?
Okay.
Just leave it to me.
You stay in the hall.
You got your money?
Right here.
Is he here?
Ted.
Look out, Vikki.
What the fuck?!
Ted!
Where's Greg?
Ted, where's Greg?
Greg's here, I know he is.
What can I do for you, man?
Just stay the fuck out of my face.
Sure.
Greg!
Shit.
What?
What the hell are you doing?
King.
What are you doing?
What's up, bro?
What?
Look at yourself.
Look at yourself. How do you feel?
Well, it's cool, man.
It's not cool, Greg.
(METAL CLANGS)
We're in big trouble,
all right?
Little J and Heather and I
are leaving on a bus tomorrow.
What happened?
Somebody got shot, all right?
You're coming with us.
Where are we gonna go?
I don't know. Someplace cheap.
We'll just get on a bus
and go where it's going, okay?
What do you say?
We'll be together?
Yeah, all of us. All right?
Okay.
All right. Get the hell up.
Get your shirt on.
I can't-- Wait. I'm too high
for the street, man.
Listen, you'll do what I tell you
to do when I tell you to do it.
I'm too high, man.
Listen!
Look, no more drugs.
Here, take my money.
This doesn't mean
anything to me.
I can't believe a word you're saying.
On my honour.
I just need to know
you're gonna be there.
On my honour,
I'll be there.
I'm trusting you.
I promise.
Noon. Noon.
What? What are we--?
What's wrong?
I tell Greg in there--
Where are we gonna go?
What city?
Are we just gonna pick a city?
What's gonna change?
Maybe we'll find
a freeway underpass...
or a nice squat.
Or maybe I'll just get
my shit together
and get a job.
I told Greg that everything
would be fine.
I have no right. I have no right.
I can't promise anything.
No, you can't.
You can't promise
anything to anybody.
You mean the world
to them.
I just want them to see
how to look out
for themselves better.
They love you.
I...
Little J, are you home?
Little J.
Where you been?
You okay?
Yeah.
No, man.
What are--?
Fuck!
Man, I didn't mean to shoot him.
I fucked everything up for us.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm fucking sorry. Fuck!
Fuck!
Fuck.
Man, I'm fucking sorry.
I didn't mean to fucking shoot him.
I know, J.
He tried to kill me.
You saved my life.
Man, where the fuck--?
What are we gonna do?
J, cool it. Cool it.
J, what?!
We're leaving. We're splitting town.
You're gonna come with us, okay?
Where the fuck are we going, King?
Now, listen to me.
What the fuck do we have. No!
J!
I'll take care of you, J.
Listen. Listen.
What?
I'll take care of you.
Will you come with us?
Come on, J. Come on.
Come with us.
Yeah.
Good. Come on.
Fuck. Fuck.
Hey, hold up there.
Fuck.
Police officers.
Wanna ask you a couple of questions.
Why?
Just got a couple questions for you.
I didn't do anything.
That's all right.
(TIRES SCREECH)
Oh, shit.
Goddamn it!
Get up! Get up!
I didn't do anything!
Fuck are you running for? Shut up!
Jesus-fucking-Christ.
You okay?
Yeah. Look, we're not
gonna take you in.
We just wanna ask you
a couple of questions, that's all.
Where the fuck is King?
I don't know King.
You're a fucking liar.
I never heard of a--
I don't know who King is.
You're a fucking liar!
He's your friend of yours.
You're lying. Where's King?
I ain't seen him.
Oh, yeah? What were you running for?
What do you got on you?
I ain't seen him.
I swear to God.
I ain't seen him since
he been in jail.
What's that? Huh?
You're a lowlife scumbag,
you know that?
All you had to do was share
a little information with me.
Where King was.
Now you got a real problem.
What do you want from me?
You're going to jail.
You have the right
to remain silent.
If you give up that right, anything
you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S
"ROYAL STATION 4I16" PLAYING)
You did the right thing,
talking to the cops.
You save yourself.
Save yourself.
Fuck King, man.
Fuck him.
You did the right thing,
little bro.
Come to me, okay?
Good. Good.
KING:
What do you got?
No, J. You gotta roll it
over your knuckles.
You'll get it when you
get a little older.
MAN (OVER SPEAKERS):
Bus number 4 20...
Shit, we can't wait.
We gotta go.
What about Greg?
We can't wait. Let's go.
--now boarding at Gate G.
Which way to departures?
KING:
Shit.
Where the hell is Greg?
You guys, wait here.
I'm gonna check again.
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S "YOU CAN
SLEEP WHlLE I DRlVE" PLAYING)
MAN (ON SPEAKERS): This is
the final call for bus number 420.
Service to Riverside, Indio...
Fuck, Greg.
Oh, shit.
I fucking did it.
Hey, King, I did it.
Hey, freeze! Don't move.
Put the gun down, son.
Come on, put it down.
Little J, put down the gun.
Don't make a mistake,
son. Don't--
OFFICER:
Come on, son, put it down.
Put it down. What are you doing?
Fuck them!
Don't, man!
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
INTERVIEWER:
How do you see your future
on the street?
What do you mean?
Do you see yourself always
on the street? Or do you
see yourself getting off--
Look, if you got a plan,
I'm willing to listen.
I'm just trying to--
You know, it's like--
What about love?
What about it?
Well, what if you fell in love
with something?
Wouldn't that make
a difference?
Yeah.
In fact, I got somebody now.
His name's Waldo. Big, cute black guy.
I met him on the cellblock.
Really?
Yeah, sure.
No, just some chick I met.
Tell me about her.
No.
Why not?
Because what's mine is mine.
And if I share it with you,
then it becomes less mine.
You understand?
Her name's Heather.
She's very beautiful.
So you got it out of me.
You're such a character, King.
Fuck that.
Look, can I get my 10 bucks
and get the hell out of here, please?
Sure.
I think it was
a really good
session today.
Good.
INTERVIEWER:
You okay?
I'm fine.
You got a cigarette?
INTERVIEWER: Um, yeah.
Thanks.
Are you sure you're okay?
It's been a long time.
Look, I know you just turned 18.
I don't know your history...
but maybe you wanna think
about giving home a try.
My home's here.
Okay.
He's ready.
(BUFFALO SPRlNGFlELD'S
"FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH" PLAYING)
So, what's up?
You always been
such a pain in the ass?
Yeah.
Excuse me, you got
a dime? Nickel?
Hey, how was it?
Suck any cocks?
Just your dad's.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Could you spare some change for me
and my little brother?
INTERVIEWER:
If you could put out one thing,
put one thing out there
about King's philosophy,
what would it be?
KING: If you keep
everything simple,
you'll do okay.
You just go where the day takes you.
(MELISSA ETHERIDGE'S
"TESTIFY" PLAYING)