Selling love will make you rich.
That's what my mother taught me.
Just don't put your heart in it.
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Happy New Year!
Happy fucking New Year!
You know, this is the greatest
country in the world.
And I'm the luckiest guy in the world
.
Sit your asses down and I'll tell you why.
What is this great country shit?
You know, hafalong Bontempo,
fresh off the Jersey prairie.
Get up here, Alana.
Come here!
This here is the greatest revenue generator
machine in the world.
Is better than gold!
You don't get your nails
dirty digging for it.
And the Good Lord just keeps
making more and more of it.
There's no business like
whore business!
I say, you've shown them enough.
Let's have some fun,
back in the swing...
Jay, put that music on, come on!
Wait a minute! Hold on!
I wanna make a toast!
Charlie, come back up here!
Charlie don't get mad,
but everybody knows...
That you ain't nothing
without your better half.
Now, she sprained her knee...
Bad, and she's kind of shy,
but if we ask real nice...
I'm staying right here!
Grace, it's New Year for crying out loud!
Come on up here!
You heard me.
I'm doing orientation, okay?
Someone's got to work around here.
- Hey, hold this.
- Ok.
My third leg!
You think I'd forgive you, Charlie?
Happy New Year!
The first kiss of the New Year!
Grace!
Samantha.
Ok, baby, I got to go.
Warren.
Happy New Year everybody!
Hi, happy New Year! Let's see that music!
Hope everybody have a good time!
Come on!
OK, soldier! At ease!
This bitch won't give
me what I want!
He said that he wanted it
just like in Saigon!
Yeah, just like in Saigon!!
OK, put your clothes on,
I'll buy you a drink. Come on!
- I ain't leaving till I get what I paid for.
- You didn’t paid for a shit!
- Well, I'm taking it anyway.
- Warren!
Pay attention Warren,
he's got a knife!
He's got a knife!
Get out, bastard!
Get out! Get out!
Get back, you!
- You're Okay?
- I'm fine!
Get back!
- I'll cut you!
- Hey. Calm. Easy.
- Take it easy, take it easy. Hold up.
Get back!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine Charlie, I'm sorry.
He fucking cut you, he?
I ruined my fucking guitar, Willie Nelson
gave me that fucking guitar!
Charlie... you're okay?
I'm fine honey, how are you,
you all right, you okay?
- Oh shit!
- What a way to start the new year!
Johnny boy, get him out of here,
will you please?
Come on folks! Don't let this
hold up the party. We got a lot...
Will! Will! Drinks from the house!
You hear that? Drinks from the house!
Happy New Year!
What a way to start the fucking new year.
- Oh, Charlie, I'm exhausted.
- I'm fucking tired too.
- I'm going to bed.
- That sounds like a good idea.
But...
I do have to go have a drink
with the fucking manager of the Eldorado.
Shit! Maybe I could...
No, I gotta go. I gotta go.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Rio? Pay the band.
Hey, honey bun!
I waited all night for this honey...
I'm falling apart, like this stupid town.
More tests, a second opinion?
I could be wrong.
You are not wrong.
You have options,
it's not a death sentence.
There are breakthroughs in
cancer research every day.
I'm not telling Charlie.
He doesn't like bad news,
not before dinner.
Speak of the devil...
My chariot.
So, what are you sick or some?
Why did you go to the fucking doctor for?
- Yearly check up.
- Uh!
Where are we going? Charlie I want
to go home, I got a headache.
No, no, no! We're going to see
that fighter I told you about.
What fighter?
The fighter!
Don't you fucking listen to me?
I must have told you
nine times!
You remember that fighter
Armando Bruza I told you about?
Who?
Armando Bruza, the Argentinian fighter,
I saw him gambling.
He was loosing,
I bailed him out.
Oh, not again!
What is this place?
It's where the fighters train.
- I'm staying in the car.
- No you're not. This is not just any fighter,
This is our fighter, we own him!
Get your ass out of the car, Grace.
Well. I'm not going anywhere
if you wear that hat.
This hat cost me 300, baby.
Who do you think you're,
Clint Eastwood?
the Queen of fucking England?
Flesh!
I'm a sucker for it, honey.
How come everyone of this places smells
like they got a body floating in the pool?
Ah, I love this shit, baby.
Charlie, you don't need me here.
Hey, Grace!
You are my wife, ain't you?
Ah? Listen to me.
This here Bruza is not a nobo.
He fought Joe Frazier
and Muhammad Ali.
And he gave them full time,
And he is ranked fifth in the world
in the heavyweight division.
And I got a two night fight for him
coming at the Auditorium.
And after that, I'm gonna give him
a rematch with Muhammad Ali.
Oh, Charlie, not again.
Hey Grace! Don't give me that
"Charlie not again" bullshit!
You know, come on honey,
you know what this means?
This is gonna be reporters here
from all over the country.
And you know me baby,
I get my fucking hands on those guys.
Then it ain't gonna be anybody in whole
world didn’t hear about the Love Ranch.
The Love Ranch.
Sugar, come on baby, we're gonna be famous.
Come on, you can do this..
Hey Prado!
Good you could came down.
- Ms. Bontempo, Hernan Prado.
- Hi.
So glad to meet you.
How does he look?
This guy Colter, he
don't punch much.
Armando beat him easy.
Had better.
I'm talking to Ali's people,
they're interested.
Bruza! Hey!
- My man!
- Hey!
Charlie!
Charlie Good Time!
Looking good!
You bringing any of those
chiquitas with you, he?
Those smoking hot putas?
- Calma te.
- She's my wife.
- What?
- My wife is here.
- Su esposa
- Oh, your wife...
Quite a head of hair
you got there...
Mucho caveza, si!
Like the Beatles.
But you know...
In my country...
I'm more famous than
any fucking Beatle.
I am more loved than Perón
and his bitch wife, eh?
Come on in here, honey bun.
Come on, Grace.
He ain’t gonna bite you.
I am Bruza...
The Wild Bull of the Pampas.
Fantastic to meet you,
Ms. Good Time.
Pleasure is all mine.
Okay, come on out, girls.
Samantha Snow...
Irene...
Alana...
Christina.
You.
Yes ma’am.
That one there.
Okay.
That, you know...
Thank you very much!
Have a wonderful time!
Oh, go on, oh!
Oh, why are you stopping?
Quiet!
So last night, I had this guy...
So we had this straight kind of set up
and halfway through he says...
He wants the back door.
You know me, I'm like: "Sure!"
"But... we need to renegotiate."
They always want
something for nothing.
They think we gonna forget all
of that in the heat of passion.
You were in my room!
You're blocking the TV.
Could you move?
You went into my room,
and you stole my Quaaludes.
I know it was you.
I went into your room!
My God, I didn’t take your
fucking Quaaludes, Ok?
You probably took them,
and you don't remember...
Give them back...
Or I may tell Charlie.
Oh no!
She is gonna tell Charlie!
What shall I do?
You're fucking kidding me,
are you not?
Yesterday was New Year, Georgia girl.
See, Charlie he got a real short
attention span.
Short dick span too.
Has he made you do
that dog thing yet?
Kind of like get up
like this and you bark...
Hey, when I did, he was real nice.
He let me keep the collar!
Shut up!
I still get it and I wear it
sometimes, it's cute.
All right, you fucking cunts!
Charlie and I are together,
he says he loves me.
He loves you...
So sweet!
You're a fucking moron,
get the fuck out of the way.
- Bitch!
- What?
Fuck! You ruined my dress!
Don't you, don't you ever...
ever lay your hands on me!
Hey, do you hear me?
Break it up, ladies.
She started it!
Don't you ever touch me again!
Get up, come on!
Fucking old witch!
I'm fining you 500 dollars.
500?
What the fuck about her?
I'll tell Charlie!
Go ahead, you go tell Charlie.
But I'm the boss around here,
and don't you forget, Ok?
I make the rules.
You want to stay here, you obey them
or you get out, you understand?
She, she ripped my dress.
Oh, boo hoo!
You know what? The next time
I'm in KMart, I'll buy you a new one.
Come on, go to your room.
OK.
The show is over.
It's okay, Warren?
Good, Grace.
Hey honey bunch!
Where've you been sugar?
I've been looking all over for you.
Listen, dickhead.
The next time you steal my mink...
So your sweet little screws
can wear it around Reno...
At least take the Quaaludes out of the pocket
before you flip it back into my closet.
Oh sugar, come on, darling,
you know better...
Oh, don't give me that cowboy shit!
It hurts me, Charlie.
It hurts me and it pisses me off when
you do it right in front of my nose.
Honey, there's something
else bothering you. Now what is it?
Come on, is it something
to do with the ranch?
- Nothing to do with the Ranch.
- If it ain't about the Ranch, what the fuck...
The Ranch is the only thing
in the goddamn word, okay!
Grace...
I know you.
Tell me what it is.
Charlie!
Remember that buddy of mine
who works for the election commission?
He says those church people
have called to file a petition.
We need to talk.
- Hello, Grace.
- Hey.
Hey, honey, we'll have a drink later
and talk about this, uh?
I'm sorry, honey.
Hey!
Mrs. Charlie!
Mrs. Good Time!
It's me, Bruza!
You remember? The fighter!
Oh, yes, yeah, I remember.
- The wild bull, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
Listen, you got someone
to help me with my stuff?
Your stuff? What stuff?
- Charlie didn't tell you?
- No.
No, Charlie didn't tell me.
I'm moving in.
You what?
Bruza, mi campeon!
Hey Charlie! Charlie Good Time!
Charlie, what's this shit
about he moving in?
Yes, that's right, he's gonna train
here at the Ranch!
- What?
- It'll be good for business!
What the hell do you get off,
telling me what's good for business?
Oh, come on, baby...
Look, look!
- If there's a problem...
- There's no problem!
There's no problem,
right, Grace?
She looks pretty mad, eh?
No, she's not mad...
I always got a bunch of friends about,
you know how women are like.
Get over here, I wanna show you something.
Stand right here, boy.
Warren, bring up
his bags for him.
- What's up?
- Stay there.
Girls, come on out.
This here's Samantha,
and this is Angel.
This is our champion.
You take him back to the leopard room....
Show him the leopard room,
you know what I mean?
- The leopard room?
- The leopard room.
Come on tiger, get back there.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, Grace!
Why do you have to talk to me
like that before that fucking fighter?
How much did you give that guy?
What?
You mean to his contract?
You paid off his gambling debts,
how much?
Practically nothing.
I gave him maybe 15,000 dollars.
Oh, 15 means 50 with you!
You gave that lad
25 grand my money?
We're fifty-fifty, Charlie!
You gave that fighter
25 grand out of my pocket.
No, that's not right.
- Oh, I got it wrong!
- Yeah.
I can sure see it all now...
"Come to the Ranch.
Bang your way into shape..."
"Fuck all the girls,
don't pay a dime..."
- Party!" That's how it was, wasn't it?
- No.
Now listen to me.
You can act how you like out there.
You can prance around like a little king,
with your cigar stuck in your face...
But in here it's different!
Don't take what's mine!
If it wasn't for me, you'd be
sticking in shit to this damn day.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, really.
- Really? That's what you think?
- Yes, that's what I think..
- You really think that?
- What the fuck!
Through the fucking...!
No, not the phone! Not the phone!
I need the phone, okay?
Listen, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
- How the fuck could you say that?
- I'm sorry.
Hey...
Maybe you're right
about the fighter.
Well, I know, I am not
a great visionary like you.
I'm just here with
the nuts and bolts,
Trying to keep the ship
from sinking, okay?
Gracie, Gracie.
Am I not always right
about this kind of things?
Yeah, you're, you are right.
You are.
Okay, look.
You want a new toy?
You got a new toy.
Just don't have him
stay at the ranch.
Can't he stay
at the trailer park?
I told the press.
It's gonna be out in print, I mean all the papers,
You wanna look stupid, is that what you want?
No, I don't want that, I know
Grace, I don't know
if you know...
What this means to me,
what it means to us.
To go to Vegas...
And have all those
fucking scumbags...
Say...
"Charlie, can you get me tickets
to the fight?"
"Charlie, come to my restaurant,
bring your beautiful wife..."
And then...
Welcome to the heavyweight
championship of the world!
Promoted by...
Charlie Bontempo!
And...
Sitting ringside,
is his gorgeous wife...
Gracie!
I dreamed of this shit
my whole life, my whole life.
Oh, you're fucking crazy, Charlie.
I try to be... more every day.
Oh listen, one more thing...
That guy Prado...
Prado? Who is Prado?
Prado, that trainer, manager,
whatever the fuck.
We met him at the gym
the other day.
I don't trust this guy, so...
I told the commission
you'd be his new manager.
What?
- Yeah.
- Are you out of your mind?
Honey, I've told you, it's
a business asset...
And we got to protect him.
Why don't you do it!
I can't do it!
They wont let me manage him.
I can't get a license,
I'm a convicted felon!
What am I supposed to do?
Carry his spit bucket?
No...
You don't have to carry
his spit bucket.
All you have to do
is sign some papers...
You go to the fights...
You sit near his corner...
That's it!
You don't carry
his spit bucket...
Oh you're unbelievable!
No, we're unbelievable, baby.
I got to go to Carson City.
Sorry it ain't much.
- Charlie own this place?
- Yeah.
Yeah. He keeps rents low as long as
this people vote right at election time.
Smart.
American democracy at work.
Charlie had a Ranch maid
come over and spruce the place up.
Charlie wanted you to have this.
Use that to pay
for a hotel in Reno...
Or stay here...
And put it in your pocket.
I stay here.
The world-famous Love Ranch,
where your wildest fantasies come true.
How can I help you?
Pink handcuffs.
15.
Close?
Honey, we never close.
Grace!
What's this?
I found it on the window,
this morning.
Mrs. Good Time...
It's crazy to work out here in the snow.
Do you want a rematch with Ali or not?
Charlie really wants me here.
There's a perfectly good gym in Reno.
I took Charlie's money.
We're going to do this.
This is bullshit.
I need to straighten things out with his wife.
Go on... We need to eat, don't we?
Mrs. Bontempo.
Hello, Beautiful!
I haven't been out here
since we built the Ranch!
You're sure that old tree
is gonna hold that bag?
Hey, I thought you wanted
to talk to me.
Yeah.
Sorry about yesterday.
I didn't know that you
didn't know that I was coming.
That's okay.
Charlie and me worked it out, but...
You're okay in the trailer park?
I know it's not the Hilton.
I sleep good anywhere.
Hey, hey...
You don't have to work out here.
You can go inside if you want.
I prefer to be here.
I don't like to be inside,
no offence.
Here I feel free.
Yeah!
Well, don't get too free.
I don't care what Charlie said.
These are working girls.
That means they're
supposed to be working.
You just keep your wild bull
pecker in your pants, okay?
Hey!
Mrs. Charlie...
You gonna help me?
Help you do what?
You're my manager.
You're going to get me ready
for the fight.
No, no, no, no, I told Charlie.
No, that's crazy.
A manager is supposed
to help the fighter, you know?
Listen, I got 25 psychotic whores to
manage, that's a full dance card.
Yeah, I know!
I don't like to work out alone!
I feel lonely.
A big boy like you?
Yeah, a big boy like me!
I need people to talk to.
Come on, it's easy.
I show you.
I hit like this.
You say: "Good." Then...
Come on, say it.
Say "Good"!
Good.
Nice!
Hey!
Now I hit like this.
- And you say: "Way to work..."
- Oh this is stupid!
No... not stupid!
Come on, say it.
Say...
"Way to work!"
- Way to work.
- There you go!
See!
Now you train me.
That's all Hernan ever do.
And I give him...
30%...
One last thing
you ought to know.
Now you say: "Don't loaf!"
"Don't loaf!"
Come on, say it! Say it!
Don't loaf!
Come on, say it!
Say don't loaf!
Don't loaf!
There you go!
Right so!
You see how easy?
You watch me and you learn
everything in 10 minutes.
- Hey.
- Hey, hey, hey!
One last thing.
Hold the bag.
What?
Go on the other side
and hold the bag!
Are you're kidding,
that's, that's sweaty!
No, it's not sweaty, it's good!
Come on! Please!
Please.
Give me that cane.
There you go!
Okay.
You feel that?
You're nuts.
You really think so?
Hey!
Your cane.
I go to work.
You just keep...
Banging away, okay?
Bruza...
In Argentina,
you are a king, a champion.
You don't belong here.
Friend...
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Surviving...
Don't worry, we'll be back on top.
These people can't
make you a champion...
This old lady and her pimp.
Let's go home, Bruza.
God forgives. Forgive thyself.
What God?
I spoke to Carmela's sister.
Nobody blames you.
Nobody!
Get this through your head.
Carmela's gone!
I am not going back, understand?
My job is to worry about you.
I'll worry about my own life!
Don't talk to me like that.
Fuck you all!
Is this Fench peckerhead
ever going to give up?
These fucking morons, eh?
Disgusting.
Our customers are gonna read this smut.
Warren, take them down, all.
It ain't against the law
to put up posters, Charlie.
Oh yeah?
What law is that you talking
about Johnny boy?
Do you forget who you work for?
Help him.
And hurry up, I got to get out to the
development to deal with that prick Tom Macy.
All right folks.
Now it's only fair to let you know that we
only have two of these babies left.
This one is totally custom...
Avocado appliances
and picturized on the inside.
You got cabinet tree to match.
One of a kind!!
I like it.
- It's 37,500, right?
- No.
This one is 41,500, because of the custom kitchen,
you get the double garage, lots of extras.
I think there is
someone in there.
Oh no, there's no one in there.
Let mommy and daddy
talk to Mr. Macy.
But I tell you what, folks...
If you make a decision today...
I might be able to do
a little better with the price.
There is someone in there.
Iti's the master bedroom.
Could be a critter guard in there or something, you know?
It's still pretty wild out here.
I'll go to take a look.
You folks make yourself at home,
look around, snoop. Okay?
I fell for the avocado.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, you got to get the...
Let him go, let him go.
Tommy boy, my super salesman!
Listen to me, you fucking idiot!
Did you think I was gonna let your bible
banging sister put me out of business?
Did you think I was gonna do that?
Is that what you thought, uh?
Does Mary Fench know where her little brother
spends the commission I pay him, uh?
On whores!
And she wants to shut me down?
That will never happen, it will never
fucking happen, you hear me?
You get that wretched bitch
to stop this referendum
Or you gonna loose your fucking job!
You got it?
You got it? Did you?
You're okay boy. You're okay.
You're all right.
You're okay.
You got 45 days.
I'm gonna debate
your sister on TV.
It'll be good for business.
But you... better... stop her,
do you understand?
- Yes Charlie I understand.
- Here you go..
You look good.
Now go out there and make those
poor people give you their life-savings...
For this piece of shit.
Shit!
Please, folks!!
5... 4... 3... 2...
A referendum on Comstock County's controversial
law of legalizing prostitution...
Is coming up.
We've invited two local interested parties
to join us to discuss the matter.
Miss Mary Fench, of the
Nevada Families Association...
and Charles Bontempo, of
Love Ranch, a legal brothel.
You must be proud of yourself.
Trading on weakness of the flesh.
If somebody somewhere is having a
good time, does that wreak your day?
The contaminated anti-God
moral of our society...
Exploited by vermin like you, Mr Bontempo,
that's what wreaks my day.
They always have to bring
God into it, I hate that.
I was an altar boy in the church of Rome.
Not like this voodoo shit
they got here.
If I go to hell,
I go to hell, honey.
I don't need to hear about this
from that voodoo witch bitch.
Although I have to admit she was kind of cute
in her own librarian sort of way, you know?
I was actually thinking of sticking my hand up
her dress at one point and tickling her ass.
Oh, that would have changed
her mind all right!
You think so?
Listen Charlie, we got
another letter from the IRS.
They want to look at the books.
The good ones or the bad ones?
That was easier in the old days, Grace,
when we were illegal.
We just used to shaft
the money in our pocket.
Yeah, but don't let those secret deals
of yours get us into trouble.
Hey Grace, do me a favor....
Don't act like you never
stole anything, okay?
This guys will just keep coming...
I don't wanna to be the one
stuck holding the bag.
Hey.
Hey!
Don't worry so much,
you're gonna give yourself a heart attack.
Got to go to Reno...
Meet some fight people for lunch.
Oh!
Hey, Charlie!
What the fuck
are you doing up here?
This is private.
Ah! I didn't know, sorry.
I didn't know, really.
It's great up here, uh?
Yeah!
It's where I come to relax.
Yeah. I can see why.
I got the idea when I was in Folsom.
Folsom?
Yeah, a prison.
You see the whole joint from up here.
You see everything.
Yes, the whole empire... from here.
My empire.
Yeah.
What?
I said sorry!
Yeah, come on.
I want to show you inside.
I'm gonna show you something.
You see this trailers?
We are not gonna have trailers
anymore, you know.
Stand over here, watch this.
I wanna you to have a good look.
How's that!
Wow!
It came to me in a dream.
A star.
A fucking nova.
Bricks and mortar.
Ah? See this here?
I'm gonna have a bunch
of little lights over here.
And no matter like, how far away you are, like
planes coming by hundreds of miles away...
They'll be able to see the Love Ranch.
- Is that thing...
- Don't touch, don't touch.
The trees look like this little
broccoli, I like it.
They might get down.
Yes, that's it, it's gonna be
a new Love Ranch.
Nothing like it!
It's great, Charlie.
Thank you.
You know...
I don't got nothing like this.
No place to call my own.
You're a champion,
you'll make money.
Oh money... I made it, I lost it.
You have a great life, Charlie.
Really.
Yeah...
It depends how you
look at it, you know?
I mean, some guys like to leave
something behind.
You got any children?
No.
It's a bitch, eh?
Six brothers and four sisters.
Bontempos go back
to fucking Nero.
And I have never once been
to a football game...
And said, "See that kid
out there kicking ass?"
"He's my son."
Have you seen a doctor?
We saw a million doctors.
Grace took it hard.
What about you?
Do you have kids?
Yes, in Argentina.
Ah, yes.
But I don't see them.
Not for a long time.
How come?
Because it's like...
Complicado.
Oh, oh!
Hey, honey bunch!
The champ and I are just doing
a little male-bond in here.
I go back on in 20.
Oh!
Hey!
Seen Charlie?
No. I didn't
see him all day.
Not much of a liar, are you?
Just not so,
I am a very good liar.
The little bitch has
my mink coat on?
Don't fret.
I am used to this shit.
Ms. Good Time...
I've been watching...
And you and Charlie...
You're a great team, eh?
- Oh yes, we are the best.
- Yeah!
You know...
I could run a whorehouse.
I know I could.
Some day maybe...
I'll have a place like this.
That's your life ambition?
Great!
I go all over the world
fighting, you know.
Half the time,
I don't know where I am.
But here, I feel great.
It's like a family.
You and Charlie are like
the mom and dad...
The girls, they are...
Not like sisters, but...
So nice!
How did you and Charlie do it?
I mean, start everything up?
You mean you wanna know what a girl
like me is doing in a place like this?
Give me a break.
- Please I'm serious, I really wanna know.
- It's easy.
My mom was a whore.
- Your mom?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- That bother you?
- No.
Maybe.
Guys!
You're so predictable.
How much is Charlie
with that girl...
Like... in a week?
Well, that ain't none of your
fucking business now, is it?
I’m something like awed by it.
You are quite a piece of work,
aren't you?
Maybe.
The girl I took along, she had a pussy
like the Grand Canyon.
Hey, aren't you supposed
to be training?
So, go train.
Long before Las Vegas
was ever heard of, or even invented...
Reno...
was one hell of a fight town.
This is where the great Jack Johnson
defeated Jim Jeffries...
In the great "Wild Hope" movie.
Now Bruza here is gonna bring us
back on top where we belong.
Word is that Muhammad Ali
is coming up to the fight.
That's a long way to travel,
he must be a little scared of Bruza.
I figure.
Well Charlie, personally
I hope Ali do come.
And then he'll see who he is
really supposed to be fighting...
Me, not that washed-up clown.
Bruza, what's your response to that?
I wanna tell everybody to bring
some flowers next month at the fight.
What do you mean?
It's gonna be a funeral, you know?
Leroy Colter's funeral!
I'm gonna slap you silly. I'm gonna slap you
like Jack Johnson did that other ugly white boy.
I'm not a white, I am Argentinian.
Why, olé! You look white to me!
Fish belly white.
Ok, I'm gonna show you the difference
next month in the ring.
Why, you don't even know when
you get chumped, damn wet bag.
Mr. Colter, Mr. Colter...
You know, in my business
guys are always coming in talking big...
But when it comes down to it...
They are kind of little...
That's his manager, boys!
She got you good, uh?
Who is this old lady?
Is it your mama?
But you got some nasty mouth,
own that to your mother...
No la puta che te paria...
I'll smash you so bad
granny won't recognize you!
Show her some respect, eh!
So, Bruza went out to this guy
to defend your honor?
That's hot.
Nobody ever did that for me.
Wrong!
Once my ex...
Put a coat over a puddle for me.
Except he was drunk
and it was my coat.
Who is it?
Here's Janelle.
Yeah, come on in baby.
You see the kind of degenerate behavior
I have to put up with here?
I just got a offered an
accounting job in Tahoe.
- Oh baby, that's fantastic.
- Wow!
It pays shit.
An assistant...
Starts at 13,5, with only
partial medical benefit.
How am I gonna take care
of the twins?
You gone to school for three years
trying to give you kids a better life...
The first job you get
you turn chicken?
I like it here, Grace.
I feel safe.
Out there...
In the square world...
I don't trust those people.
I'll make it easy for you.
Here.
What's this?
Severance pay. You're fired.
What?
Take it.
Come on. Pack up your trunk, put your
kids into a decent school, take the job.
If in six months, it doesn't work out, you can
always come back here, I'll be happy to have you.
But for now...
Pack up and get out of here.
Come on!
Thank you, Grace.
No problem.
Nicely done.
Wow...
What?
I just had a flash.
I just saw...
You and Bruza...
Floating up on a cloud.
And there was froggy Charlie there,
jumping up and down in his little boots...
Waving his magic pecker...
- You're stoned.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna ask you something, Grace...
Have you ever been unfaithful to Charlie?
I don't know if you
noticed or not...
But, the big Neanderthal out there, dear...
Is fucking sexy.
Just a hassle, like all the rest.
You know he has already
taken Charlie some thousands.
Good for him!
I like him already.
Hey, excuse me,
it's my money too.
Moneysh money, Grace.
My God, you have to have a little fun.
You ain't gonna live forever.
Duty calls.
Yes, Pavlov!
The old dog is coming.
You know...
You got to admit it, Grace.
Since he's been here...
You got a little more...
Spring in your step...
A little more... rhythm in your bum!
A little bit more yin... to your yang.
I am telling you!
And then...
Come on!
Do you really need
that cane anymore?
Think about it.
Don't loaf!
I should never teach
you that word.
These are real eye catching
clothes money can buy.
This is a Japanese cherry blossom corset.
Is all original design.
Girls, this a plain song!
Money in the bank.
Glad you like it.
This is a sheer merry
feathered baby doll...
It comes with matching....
Are you tired?
How far I went?
Oh, from the road,
about a mile and a half.
Oh, well!
Tomorrow, I do more.
You're okay?
Yes!
I'm tired.
You ought to lay off those candy bars.
What's over there?
On the other side?
I don't know, more of
the same. Nothing.
Maybe a couple of coyotes.
Maybe you haven't seen it
with the right person.
Oh, really? And who is that?
Mr. Wild Bullshit of the Pampers?
The Pampers?
You mean like diapers?
You make me laugh, Grace.
Yeah, well, I'm keeping you loose,
like a manager does, so I...
I just got to stay loose, no?
Yeah, but don't get too loose!
Get off of my car.
Respect, please.
I see the tire tracks...
And I wonder if the driver wanted
to miss the animal...
Or to hit it.
Tell me about you and your mother.
Finally! The 64,000 dollars question.
Was I a whore like my mom?
Well, the answer is no.
My mom said there was more money
in running whores than in being one.
So I had my first house
by the time I was 20.
I ran joints all over the state.
It wasn't legal then, just,
you know, tolerated.
So one day, I am running this three girls
dump down in Fallon.
A guy pulls up driving a Reno cab.
Fallon is 75 miles out of Reno.
It was Charlie.
Yeah, it was Charlie.
He wasn't interested in girls,
he said it was me he came to see.
He'd heard I ran a good house.
He had this plan, you know.
A dream really, to make it legal.
He said if we were legal there wouldn't be
any cops around with their hands out..
Would be citizens.
Would make a lot of money.
He was right.
Yeah, he was right.
You know, I've been thinking
about the Ranch.
And many changes need to be made.
Immediately.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah, yeah, for example, I don't know
why you let your girls curse?
It's not sexy.
They call themselves cunts!
I hear that, and my thing
just... goes down.
Remind me to wash everybody's mouth
out with soap when I get back.
Well, you know, I got
plenty of good ideas.
To make the Ranch better.
Or maybe you wish to
call it Bruza's Love Ranch.
No, no way.
No, it should be
Grace and Bruza's.
Oh, boy! Charlie is not
gonna like that!
Charlie?
And who needs Charlie?
All right!
Who needs Charlie?
You see, Grace...
We think alike.
We are a good team.
You know...
I don't know why you stay with
that little man.
He wanders around
with that skinny girl.
It makes me... sick...
How he treats you.
You don't love him, Grace.
A woman like you can not
love someone like him.
It could be just you and me.
Get out!
What?
Get the fuck out of the car!
Get out! Out!
Go! Get out!
Do you think I'm that stupid?
- Okay, I'll get out!
- Yeah!
Then I'll get back in.
Come on, Grace...
Come on, Grace! Grace!
Come on!
Grace! I didn't mean it!
I'm sorry!
Grace!
I'm sorry.
I'm a fucking idiot!
Shit!
Lorazepam. In case of insomnia.
Don't exceed 3 tablets in 24 hours.
Hey!
Hi.
Oh, it's you.
You gave me a start!
How're you doing?
Good!
These are nice!
You made them?
I learned in jail.
They put me in
the welding shop.
You just use old cars?
Whatever shit
people throw away.
You sleep there?
They own the shop.
Grace lets me stay out here.
I can't stand being cooped up.
It was Grace that got
me sculpturing.
She saved my life.
She's good people,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, I know.
Rio, get me Tom Macy on the phone.
I'm gonna kill that little fuck.
Grace!
What are you doing, I've been
looking all over for you.
That fucking Fench lady
is on her way over here.
Who?
Fench, the church lady from the fucking
TV show I did the other day.
She's coming, she got
Armored Christian soldiers,
They're marching up to
the fucking front gate now,
They got television crews
and everything.
Charlie, when you look at me,
what do you see?
What?
What do I look like to you?
Grace, what is this,
I got a fucking secret, now?
Charlie...
I'm serious.
Do you love me?
Do you?
Grace...
22 years we're married.
Do I love you?
Are you okay, honey?
Is it something wrong?
22 years...
It sounds like a stretch
in Quentin to me.
I want to take a vacation.
You wanna what?
I want to take a vacation...
You know, just you and me.
You mean like that cruise we took
to Mexico, just me and you?
Yeah.
Wasn't that nice?
Yes, it was nice.
- Okay, we'll do it. Let's do it!
- Good.
Good, let's go today.
Grace, are you on fucking LSD?
In the middle of this
fucking shit, that one?
Don't pull this fucking stuff!
Charlie, I need to be with you.
You're with me!
Just reach out and fucking touch me,
I'm here, honey.
Why do you have to make
everything so cheap?
Okay.
Okay, I'll break it down for you.
- Do.
- When I went to the doctor...
For your check-up!
Hold on!
Hello?
Hey Tom, your sister's over here
with the all fucking church!
It wasn't just a check up.
I thought you were
gonna stop her.
What?
Her husband?
What do I give a shit!
Lean on!
Do what you got to do!
Hey, you better stop this bitch,
or you're fucking done!
Grace...
Honey...
Look at me.
I may not always act like it...
Or show it...
But I love you.
I fucking love you.
I could have never found a woman
as loyal and sure to take my side.
I know that.
I fucking know, look what we did
together, look what we built.
Isn't that beautiful?
I do fucking love you.
I fucking love you.
I love you.
And I need you.
I need you, I know I do.
I can't go out there
and fight that bitch,
They got television cameras,
it would look terrible if I do it.
I need you to do it.
I'm sorry, Grace, I know you...
Okay, I'll be there Charlie,
I'll be there. Okay.
Grace! Grace!
Thank you, honey. Ok.
Ok, ok, let's go!!
Prostitution out of
Comstock County now!
Prostitution...
Legal or not...
Is evil.
Why do you think there's a fence
around the place?
These women are in bondage.
Mrs. Fench...
You're on my property...
I could have you removed...
But, in my America I happen to think
that freedom of speech...
Is a lot more important
than private property.
So I'm going to invite
you people in...
And let's start talk it over.
This may be hard for you
to understand, Mr. Bontempo...
But God-fearing people aren't interested
in your perversions.
That's right!
You are a woman!
How can you sell
their bodies like this?
Oh, Mrs. Fench...
Would you do me a favor and
just take a look at these girls?
I don't need to.
Oh, come on, just look at them.
I mean, don't look at their
make-up or their clothes, but...
But look at them,
the people they are...
I mean, do you think they dreamed of being
hookers when they were little girls?
No, they've taken what life
has thrown at them...
And they're making
the best of it, okay?
Yeah!
And maybe being a whore
ain't so great...
But it beats serving burgers
in Winnemucca.
God will win!
Down legal sin!
Legal sex!
Hi.
How the hell
did you get in here?
I picked the lock.
You what?
I picked your lock!
I learned it when I was a boy
in the streets in Buenos Aires.
Any lock. No problem
Well, you can just
get the hell out!
Grace...
I just...
Wanted to make an apology.
What I said on the road....
It was wrong.
I just never met anyone like you.
And I don't know how to ask.
What do you want?
- Want?
- Yeah, what do you want?
I want you to be my manager...
I want you to be with me and...
Bullshit!
I just...
I just like you...
What do you mean you like me?
I mean, look at me...
Look at me, I'm old.
I am not like those girls...
Sorry.
Oh, yeah!
- Easy.
- Yes.
Girls, If you want something,
get it now, come on!
I don't wanna be in there!
Hey Warren...
Take care of it.
- Hey Tommy!
- Hey, Charlie!
Did you hear they canceled
that referendum?
Nice work, boy.
I see you found your little price
at the bottom of a crackerjack box...
Is that all right?
- It's a swell thing you did.
- All right, Tommy gun.
Johnny boy... ringside for Mr. Macy
and his lovely date.
Charlie!
Grace, you are as beautiful as
the first time I busted you 20 years ago.
Can I have that box, please. Thank you.
Asshole.
And... just as sweet!
You know how women are,
Mr. Prosecutor.
They can't all be as
forgiving as me, Jim.
This is a big night for you, uh?
Comme ci, comme ça.
Look, Charlie, I been thinking...
You known, we go way back.
And guys like us, we shouldn't be...
Butting heads...
You know what I mean?
I mean you got some
big things coming...
I can give you a little boost.
You want to give me
a little boost, Jim?
I don't like anybody's
hand in my pockets.
Especially your.
Don't get too sure of yourself,
Charlie Good Time.
It just makes it harder
when you fall.
- Hey! Salaam alaikum
- Alaikum salaam
Charlie Bontempo,
I pray life is good.
Same shit, different flies.
Say hi to our State's Senator and former
District Attorney James Pettis.
Meet Naasih Mohammad.
Welcome to Comstock County.
Now, is there any truth to this rumor
that I have heard that...
Ali himself is coming here... soon?
Inshallah!
That means "God willing."
Right! Right, right,
God willing.
Yes, well, It would be economically
wonderful for Reno.
I mean, and spiritually too,
of course.
The spiritual is always permanent.
Why, yes it is!
Yes it is!
It certainly is!
I want you to know that you can call your new
friend Jimmy anytime you need something.
Will you do that?
Good luck tonight, Charlie.
Good luck to you too, Jim.
Politicians...
They can be useful.
Yeah, in small doses.
So. How is Bruza?
I mean, he's got to look good,
or the network wont pay.
The kid is champing at
the bit, he's ready.
I'm telling you, he can be good.
I'll knock him out.
Of course.
- Hi.
- Come in, come in.
Hi!
Beautiful!
Oh, my God!
You look completely different
without your beard.
Look! Look what I've made for you.
- It's mi lingo! Bruza!
- Si!
Beautiful!
And look, Charlie wanted you to wear this,
advertise the Ranch...
He wants to advertise the Ranch...
- And that...
- Shh!
Yeeh!
- Bruza!
- Yeah!
You know what?
I'm gonna knock him out
in the first round.
Jab, jab at the body
and a big right, and...
Your boy's catchin'.
A slow starter, will wring rust.
Hold buddy, he'll be there!
He's gone, he's gone!
Yeah!
You seen that?
I told you he was ready!
You see that fucking right?
He almost took his head off.
Come on, Bruza!
How about that, honey?
Uh? Uh?
This is great.
Seven... Eight...
Break!
Break it up!
Let them fight!
Colter, fake it!
That's the way to go, Bruza!
It is going just like
I dreamed, honey.
You let that bum get away.
We should be home by now.
Please welcome our first
Love Ranch beauty... Mallory!
Hey! Hey!
This guy is on fire!
Maybe we should go, like,
close circuit...
Then network.
And a 5% of course, of course!
You know, the fight ain't over yet.
Maybe after the fight,
I'm gonna ask you for 60%.
Stay away from him!
Keep that left in his face!
Think. Breathe through your nose.
Calm down.
I'm gonna rip his balls off.
That's it!
That's knock-down number two!
No knock-down, no knock-down!
It's not knock-down man, he was pushed!
That's not regular.
That's because he was hanging on him!
It's not his fault.
The referee got to break them up!
See, your boy lost this round.
I'm telling you, because of the ref.
Opened his eye!
He opened his eye.
C'mon! C'mon!
Charlie he got a little cut here.
It's a wonder it's all he's got, the
way he's fighting. I don't get it.
Ok, folks! Welcome...
Alana!
Are you cut motherfucker?
Hearing me?***
Come on!
Stop!
Time out!
Charlie! This guy's trained
on blow-jobs or what?
I've been saying,
work on his left eye.
If you go over the cut above the eye,
they'll stop fight.
Show him the heavy,
brother, move it!
All right, let's welcome Angel!
It's over, Bruza fall, Bruza fall!
Charlie...
It's over.
Neutral corner!
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
Okay?
Go! Go!
Hey you!
I got you, damn fool!
Come on, doctor!
Doctor come on here!
Hey Charlie!
Charlie, maybe you should take me up
on my offer for a boost!
He's to die, but
don't worry about it!
- No! Excuse me madam.
- I'm his manager.
Get out of my way!!
Please, give me
one more round, please.
- One more round!
- No!
I can do it!
One more round!
One more round! Please!
One more round!, and that's it.
One more.
- Please, stop!
- I want one more round!
Trust me!
Trust me! One more round!
You can't let him do this,
it's crazy.
He don't listen to me!
Do something this round
or it's over.
Work on that eye!
Oh, shit!
You put blood on me!
Who's gonna clean it?
I'll tell you, you are!
I think is you!
It's you!
All right?
That's all now?
Why, when I'm done with you...
Your granny over there
wont be able to...
Bruza! Bruza!
You are okay?
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner...
By way of knock-out...
Armando...
The Wild Bull...
Bruza!
Bruza! Bruza! Bruza! Bruza!
Get me out of here.
I'm gonna take him away, okay?
I'm gonna go to Naasih!
Bruza! Bruza! Bruza! Bruza!
- Ooh!
- Bruza, what is it?
Take me to the hospital.
- Prado!
- Si!
No, no, I want you to
take me to the hospital.
Come on!
Hey, Naasih!
What are you doing?
Come on up here,
We're celebrating and
then we're gonna go to some to eat.
With the girls.
Come on!
No, I'll call you later.
We're gonna have dinner
over at the Ranch...
We can talk about
the Ali contract.
Charles Bontempo?
Can I have a word with you?
Robert Bellner,
Internal Revenue Service.
We tried to reach you
at the Ranch many times...
But we haven't been able
to get a hold of you.
What's your name again?
That little fag has messed
me up good, eh?
Sure did.
I look like...
A monster.
Yeah!
Frankenstein.
I'm come to suck your blood...
- It's Dracula.
- What?
Dracula sucks blood,
not Frankenstein.
I'm sorry.
Wrong monster.
Wrong monster...
What?
What is it?
My head!
Hell, my head!
Your head?
Okay, I'll get you there.
We're near now.
Intensive Care Unit
What are you doing in here?
I'm here to see Armando Bruza.
I'm afraid ICU is off limits,
Mrs. Bruza.
No...
Bontempo, Mrs. Bontempo.
Your relationship to the patient?
I'm his manager.
Is he going to be all right?
His manager.
You ought to be in jail.
Why?
This man had a craniotomy.
A cra...
A brain operation.
Mr. Bruza has a
metal plate in his head.
He has a 6 inches scar in his
skull, did you not know this?
No, no, I didn't.
No.
He never said anything
about any operation.
Mr. Bruza has no business
being in a prizefight ring.
He has no business
wearing a tight hat.
Please don't lecture me!
Just tell me,
is he going to be all right?
With brain injuries,
it's hard to tell.
Oh my God...
Oh, my God...
We've put Mr. Bruza in a
medically induced coma.
We'll wake him up tomorrow morning
and do tests, observe him.
Look, Mrs. Bontempo...
Go home...
Get some sleep, and...
Call me tomorrow.
Thank you.
I drove his car here.
What shall I...
Can I...
Call you a taxi?
Yes!
Thank you.
I'll let the nurse tell you
when the taxi arrives.
Where the fuck were you?
I was in the hospital.
I've been looking
for you all fucking night.
Somebody had to
take him to the hospital...
Why the fuck did you have to take him?
Why not fucking Prado take him?
Because he wanted
me to take him!
You are the one who wanted
me to be his manager.
What did you fucking do, operate him?
You've blood all over your face.
- I have?
- Yeah!
Grace I've been fucking
looking up for you!
You don't know the fuck I
went through all night.
I was looking for you...
How's the fucking loser anyway?
He's bad!
Bad, Charlie, he's really bad.
Did you know... he had a plate
in his head?
No, I mean what did they do, operate
and put in a plate, you mean?
No, no! He had an
operation some time ago.
You know he could
have died fighting?
Did you know that?
You mean before the fight
he had a plate?
Yeah, yeah, some time ago.
What the fuck is going on?
They sold us damaged goods!
I mean they hadn't noticed
before the fight, Grace!
This is like they sold us
damaged goods!
This fucking spick!
His fucking head should blow up
in that fucking hospital.
It should explode!
Listen to me! He nearly died
and he fought a great fight.
What the fuck...
Hey I'm fucking talking to you!
Where the fuck are you going?
What's wrong with you?
You listening to what
I'm telling you?
I mean this fucking
fellow up hard on me tonight...
Everything that I fucking
worked for, for us!
All my fucking dreams!
You worry about a fucking spick head
blowing up, who was looking to fuck us?
What's wrong with you?
Fucking Naasih said we'll not
even get the Ali fight...
Because even though he won,
the fighter looks bad!
So we are not getting that!
Everything!
On top of everything else,
in the middle of fucking the ring,
A guy walks up to me
and hands me a paper....
The IRS has summoned me...
In my... In my fucking fight!
Why don't they just take a broom so
they can shove it up my fucking ass!
And everybody says "Where's Grace?"
"Where's Grace?"
What's going on... I am looking around...
What the fuck is going on?
Charlie, let's...
Charlie, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you.
I'm sorry.
Right now, I'm really cold...
I'm really tired, and I want
to go to bed.
We'll talk about it later.
Not your fault, Grace.
Is that it?
My problem, uh?
Fucking whores, do you ever think about
cleaning up after yourselves in here?
It stinks!
Is it not why we pay you
50% of our salaries?
Excuse me, what did you say?
I said, is it not what we pay you 50% for?
No, it is not that you pay me 50% for it.
As a matter of fact I do purchase a lot
of things like soap and water...
Which I don't think you use too much,
because you got some...
Smelly pussies around here
the guys don't want to pay for!
Fuck you!
Fuck me? No, fuck you,
you little fuck you!
Fuck me, after all the shit
I do around here?
You talk to me that way?
You better get your fucking priorities
straight, who the fuck you're talking to!
Fuck me? Fuck you!
Get your shit, pack off, out!
Out! Get the fuck out of here!
Are you serious?
Yes I'm fucking serious!
I'm tired of your fucking
smart mouth, shit!
What kind of shit is that after all
I fucking do for you, girls?
You'd better fucking clean this fucking
place up a little bit, it fucking stinks!
Five minutes.
I new dress?
I'll fucking teach you to motherfucking
blame my head 'cause I said it.
I'm fucking saying I can smell a shit.
Fucking stinking motherfuckers!
It fucking stinks around here!
Fuck him!
Don't worry about him,
I'll talk to Grace.
Grace!
It's me!
You scared the shit out of me!
How the hell
did you get in here?
Through the window.
You're supposed to be
in the hospital.
Yes but...
They woke me up this morning
and they wanted to...
Drill holes inside my brain.
I said fuck you!
I'm leaving now.
Look what they did to me.
Your hair.
This is terrible, uh?
No more Wild Bull.
Look at that!
My God!
You had that scar all along!
Yeah!
I had.
That doctor said you could have
died fighting in that ring...
Why did you do that?
Grace, I'm a fighter,
so I fight.
Don't give me that macho shit!
He said you could
die at any time.
But I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you.
I don't give a shit, I die, I die.
What?
Oh my God, it's a joke,
it's the biggest joke in the...
Fucking history of the world.
What is a joke,
what do you mean?
I'm dying too.
What?
Yes... I've got...
I don't know...
Six months, maybe less, maybe more.
- That's not true.
- Yes, I had all the tests.
Cancer...
Yeah, nobody knows, not even Charlie.
You gonna tell him Grace...
You know when I found out?
I found out the day that I met you.
Remember?
In the gym.
You took off your headgear
and all that...
Beautiful hair came out.
Remember?
Get it?
We're both dying, Grace!
Some punch-line, uh?
Grace?
You in there?
Yeah?
Charlie has just fired Mallory.
You got to get out here...
I...
Well, I can't come right now.
Grace, you don't want
to lose Mallory...
Charlie is going insane.
You really have to come out here now..
Okay, I'll be there in
five minutes, okay?
Listen, you better hurry...
I don't know where Charlie is.
My God, you'd better get out of here.
You know, if Charlie...
I'm not afraid of Charlie.
Please, please, you got to go,
you got to go now...
Go out the window.
But I go with you.
What do you mean with me?
- Where?
- With you, yeah!
Anywhere!
Out of here!
Please, please, out of here.
Oh no, no, no,
I can't do that, I can't...
I am afraid, I...
Grace, Grace, look at me!
Look at me, please.
You're not afraid of nothing.
Okay?
Okay!
Look ahead!
Hey, hey, don't...
So!
It's not like this is not...
troubled this night, you know?
All of a sudden, walking down
the aisle comes this IRS guy.
He's walking down the aisle like death! The
fucking Grim Reaper, you know, I'm no....
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yeah!
- Is that Grace?
- Forget her.
Looks like Grace.
Where the fuck is she going?
Come on, Charlie!
But... Wait! Wait up!
Charlie baby!
Fucking asshole!
Hey, Grace!
Shit!
What shall I do?
No, come on, I drove my car
from the hospital.
Ok, give me the keys.
Grace, what's going on?
Hurry!
Grace!
What the hell is going on?
Shit!
Where are we?
California.
Not way!
Yeah! Reno is just half an hour
from the border.
Where are the girls in bikinis?
My mom used to bring me up here,
when she wasn't drinking.
I had forgotten how
beautiful it is.
A good place to think.
You want to think?
Listen to this.
Well, you seem to be
feeling better.
You make me feel better.
It's beautiful, uh?
Who is that?
Carlos Gardel.
- Who?
- Carlos Gardel.
Cardo... Carder...
Cardo Gardel!
Carlos Gardel!
Cardo Garvel!
He is God!
- He is God?
- Yeah!
No, no, Elvis is God.
No, Carlos Gardel.
No, Elvis.
Carlos Gardel is God.
You know? Here is God, here is Elvis,
and here is Carlos Gardel.
- No!
- Yeah!
Grace?
Grace, you in here?
Looking for Grace?
Charlie!
She's not here.
Why don't you sit down? We'll have
a drink and wait for her together.
That's Ok, Charlie.
I'll come back later.
You knew about
this thing, Irene?
What?
You knew about her fucking this spick.
I don't know what you're
talking about, Charlie.
You didn't know that she was fucking around
with this fighter, with this fucking spick?
Charlie, I have just found
out about it this afternoon.
But I got to tell you something.
I'm happy for her.
I hope she's banging the shit out of him. I
hope she's having a thunder of fucking life.
How can you be fucking happy?
How can you be that, uh?
You know what she meant to me?
- It doesn't feel so good, does it!
- Get out!
Get the fuck out!
Listen little man, it doesn't
feel so good, does it?
Warren!
Get hold of Johnny boy.
Get him over, we're going
to take care of something.
Mom and I used to come up here
and tent in the summertime.
"Two little girl scouts," she called it.
I loved it!
What's this?
That's for emergencies.
You know, it gets
snowed out, here.
This is the Donner Path,
famous in American history.
There was cannibalism here.
- Canibalismo?
- Yeah!
- Here?
Yeah!
You know, there was this
wagon train...
They came through here and they got
snowed in. They run out of...
Food.
There was this Indian tribe living around here
and they'd never seen white people before.
They peeked through the trees at them...
And they saw them
cooking bodies.
And one of the Indians
turned to the other one and said:
"They eat of each other."
- They ate each other, uh?
- Yeah.
You know?
- I kind of like it.
- I like it.
I could get used to it.
- To what?
- To your hair!
No, no!
It's horrible.
Have you read the book
about Samson, in the Bible?
Do you believe in this stuff?
Yes, every word!
I know I'm going to hell.
And I'm not going to be alone!
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Who's going with you?
You.
Charlie.
That's for sure.
Almost everybody.
You know, what you
said before is right.
We still eat each other.
We still eat each other....
I hurt people who loved me.
Grace...
My family...
I saw, I saw that picture on the wall,
in your trailer, I know.
That was...
That was the most
happy time for me.
I loved my wife.
We had our son.
I said to myself...
"Finally, I've put up something real."
I think: "Maybe I fight..."
"One, two more times, and then..."
"And then we move to the
countryside, you know?"
"Away from everything."
But I'm stupid, Grace.
In Argentina, I am a hero.
Money, women...
Everything is free.
Then one day I met
a movie star in Buenos Aires...
She is very beautiful...
I am the champion...
My wife read about it
in the papers, and...
She jumps out of the window...
With my boy.
I know, I know...
You know, I read about it
in a fight magazine.
So you know why
I fight with this...
Thing in my head.
I don't know... Maybe...
- I deserve the pain.
- No.
I don't care what happens to me.
I only care about...
Being here...
With you.
Now I been thinking and...
I don't know....
How much time we got.
Two months, two weeks...
Two minutes...
I don't know and...
I don't care neither.
Bruza...
Bruza, wake up.
Bruza, wake up!
Wake up!
Bruza! Armando!
What?
What happens?
Listen, I got to go
back to the ranch.
To the Ranch?
Yes, now.
No, no!
For what?
We got to go away from there!
I know, I want to,
I will, but...
No, no, it's a mistake!
The Ranch, it's over for you.
Whatever we need, we can get!
I have to go back.
I have to make my peace with Charlie.
I owe him that.
Do you understand?
- Ok, then I'm going with you.
- No!
- Yes.
You have no idea
what he is capable of.
I can handle Charlie.
Don't worry!
Ok, what do you want
me to do, stay here?
No, no, I know
somewhere to take you.
Okay!
Listen, you'll be safe here.
These people hate Charlie.
He used to have a suite at the hotel here and
then he screwed them on a business deal..
But he got spies everywhere,
so, do not leave your room...
- Promise me. You will not leave your room!
- I promise, I promise.
- Okay.
- Ah... take this.
You know, when I came
to the US...
I only knew two words in English...
So maybe this is not so good,
but I wrote it for you.
A poem... you...
- You wrote me a poem?
- Yeah!
I am Argentinian.
I couldn't be only a fighter...
I must be a poet, you know?
You can read it now,
it's not so long.
You're a caress to my brain...
You are the refuge
from my pain...
- You're my beauty.
Is it okay?
It's is beautiful.
I know.
Heyhey!
- I'll be here.
- Ok. Ok.
Taxi!
Grace's back here, Charlie.
Really?
When did she get in?
45 minutes ago.
- Well, thank you.
- I work at the bar, Charlie.
I remember that luggage.
You're packing, uh?
Did I ever tell you what Prado
told me about Bruza's wife?
I don't know, it's
not very nice that...
You know, Bruza
jilted his wife...
And she was so upset
that she took a...
Plunge off a
20-storey building...
With one of his kids
in her arms.
Imagine that,
one of your own kids.
He never even made the funeral, 'cause he
was too high on coke and stuff, I heard...
It doesn't matter, Charlie.
None of it does.
It doesn't matter, uh?
None of that matters.
I wonder what matters.
Do you think something like...
You fucking him in our bed,
would matter?
Who's bed are we talking about Charlie? When was
the last time you ever spent the night here?
Oh God, dear Grace!
All this girls I ever fucked around
mean nothing to me, and you know it.
You're my wife, I never touched
anybody in our bed.
I'm your business partner,
that's all I have ever really been.
That's not true
and you know that.
What about family?
We were going to have kids, you forgot?
We wanted them...
We tried.
Here.
You give me a ledger?
That's the one you want
the IRS to see.
The other one...
You know, the real one...
I got stashed.
The one that could send you to Lompoc
and me to Phoenix for a very long time.
Gracie, Gracie, Gracie...
Now I know why...
Years ago, the first time I saw you
in that joint in Fallon, I said...
"This girl is for me."
You're fucking just like me!
You are!
Great move!
You backed up everything, uh?
Grace, listen to me.
I can understand...
A big, good-looking guy
comes along...
Makes you feel good...
Sweeps you off your feet...
I understand.
I really do!
And I promise you...
I'll never...
Ever bring it up or mention it.
Never!
Oh, Charlie...
I'm dying.
You mean because of this
conversation, you're dying?
It's cancer.
I got six months.
No, less.
Grace...
You're talking to me!
What kind of fucking
bullshit story is that?
It's true. You remember the
doctor Smathers I went to?
He did all the tests in San Francisco...
Came up positive.
If all this is true, how come
I never heard about it before?
I tried to tell you
a thousand times!
Charlie... Charlie!
You see, I am not good to you.
Not good to the Ranch.
So take it.
Take the Ranch, because that's
all you have really wanted.
There's no Ranch without you,
and you're not fucking dying.
That's a bunch of shit!
I've been dead for years.
You just never noticed.
I will check with Smathers...
Find out about this bullshit.
Goodbye, Charlie.
It ain't over, Grace!
By a fucking long shot!
Reba?
Reba, this is Bruza.
Is Grace there yet?
I need to talk to her.
Bruza, do not come down.
Charlie is on the warpath.
Bruza?
Charlie!
Charlie Good Time!
Don't give me that Good Time Charlie
shit, you motherfucker...
You want to see fucking Grace again?
You get your fucking ass down here.
That's right, me and you pal...
Face to face, man to man!
Get your fucking ass down here!
I need my car, now.
Bruza?
Damn!
- How can I help?
- Tell Charlie Bruza is here.
Grace?
Where is Grace?
I didn't think you had
the balls to show up!
I thought this was between
you and me, Charlie.
A man don't bring his boys.
Hey, you want to talk!
I treat you like my flesh and blood,
and you wanna steal my wife!
Why, steal your wife!
I never stole your wife...
Listen, you lost your wife.
- I lost my wife?
- Yes!
Grace, I'm here!
Grace!
Bruza,
you think I'm to let you win?
Come on, I can't let you win!
You better jiggle that fucking plate in
your head if you think I'm to let you win.
Why, you can't take my wife.
Grace?
Bruza!
Why did you come back here?
You're a fucking liar!
Come on! Come away!
What are you doing here?
Charlie...
Come on!
Come on! Come on, come on Armando!
Come on! Come on!
Grace!
I love you, what are you doing?
Come here!
Charlie, we have been
through all this!
There's nothing left
to be said, okay?
I talked to Smathers.
I can't believe this!
I can't believe it!
You think I'd lie to you
about that?
Let's go!
Come on!
- Goodbye, Charlie.
- Hey, Grace!
26 years we've been married...
Can't you even talk to me
for one minute?
Charlie, we go now, okay?
We go!
One minute... One minute...
One minute!
Grace... let me
take care of you...
I didn't know you were dying...
- It's too late Charlie.
- Grace...
- No... Shh...
- Come on!
Charlie, it's too late...
I don't want any more of this!
I don't want the Ranch.
I don't want your dreams.
I don't want this life,
I don't want...
What the fuck we'll go away,
I'll take you somewhere...
We will give it away,
I don't care.
Let me take care of you.
- Charlie, listen... I have such a little time...
- I know.
Okay?
I want to spend with him.
- No, no, Grace.
- Please!
Please, Grace!
Shut up!
- Charlie!
- Fuck!
- No!
- What have you done?
No!
Oh, my God!
Bruza!
Warren, get him inside!
I'll take care of it!
Oh no!
No!
Grace stand back.
We'll call an ambulance.
Oh, no!
What the hell is going on?
- What's going on?
- What happened?
He had a gun!
Warren had to shoot him
in self-defense.
You liar! Liar!
- Liar.
- Grace, I saw it all!
Call someone!
Liar!
You are a liar!
Get some blankets!
I'm so sorry.
They called it self-defense,
justifiable homicide,
On account of the gun
Bruza was supposed to have had.
I told the cops what happened,
testified before the Grand Jury...
But it was Charlie's word against mine, and
of course Warren and Johnny backed him up.
Poor Warren...
He took the rap.
They shipped Bruza's body
back to Argentina, on a military plane...
His funeral was almost as big
as the one for Carlos Gardel.
He would have loved that!
The IRS did shut
the Ranch down.
What a party those bloodsuckers
had with the other ledger...
The real one, the one I sent them.
You should have seen
the look on Charlie's face...
When they took away his car,
his golf clubs, his cigars...
I knew I'd fall down too,
but it was worth it.
Just to see him fall.
I did two years in a Federal pen
in Phoenix...
But before the fuss of a single day,
he jumped bail and escaped the country
He went to Brazil, where they
don't extradite tax cheats.
Charlie tried to phone me,
but I wouldn't take his call...
Like I could ever
forgive him what he did.
About the only thing I couldn't predict,
it was still being alive...
In prison I signed out
for radiation treatment...
What did I have to lose...
Surprise!
Remission!
No one knows
how long it will last.
But I take it
one day at the time.
When I got out...
I remembered what my mother
had always told me.
"If you're good at something, stick to it."
So, I built our dream house.
The legal brothel business
was bigger than ever.
Today people come
from all over the world...
Just to party at the new
Love Ranch!
And some of my old girls
even came back.
You know, when you're family,
you stick together.
I don't make apologies
for my life...
Selling what passes for love
in this sad little world...
With so many lonely people.
What keeps me going,
is that through all the lies...
I know the truth.
We had it...
Him and me for a moment.
Love and truth, together.
Finally...
And forever.
Hey, how many people can say that?