What are you looking at?
I am looking at bucket, thinking...
I like you.
I like you because I can
say what's on my mind.
What?
Why haven't you ever kiss me?
I am scare.
Scare that when...
When Tip ask me if I ever
kiss you, I'll have to say yeap.
That scares you?
Tip is my best friend.
I don't want to mess with that.
I don't want to be with somebody
who is scare to be with me.
Mostly, I don't want to be like,
like when I kiss other girl.
Why don't you kiss me right there?
I don't have to be
like the other girls.
- Okay. Where?
- Right there.
Here.
...not to let it hurt you or anything.
Called the Butterfly Principle
which is basically a bird...
Flaps its wings and it cost a fall,
Cause a chain reaction of a
painting to be made of the apple.
Somebody looks at the painting,
Forgets they got to pick
their mama at church and...
Runs the red light and get
for 80 bucks.
Now, all because the bird flaps its
wings which is 6 million miles away.
- Gotten into the car accident
- Yeah, crack its ass from the stairwell
Are you kidding me?
Snap his whole goddamn neck.
They say he is paralysed and
put him in wheelchair.
We never know anybody
in a wheelchair before.
That kid is a dumb ass.
He's not a good driver.
Hey, Mary Margaret.
Check her out, dude.
Look at that. On the street.
I like to hang out her for a few
afternoon, man and make some pizza...
That's gross.
You should pick it up and spin it.
The other way. The other way.
The other way.
Hurry up, so we can go eat.
You can tell stuff that is useful.
I am not Spanish.
I've been to school but
they're not supposed...
To know all the words
in the dictionary.
- You got a Spanish cousin?
- I know that...
A blondie girl is meatball soup,
- I don't think so.
- M.U.J.E.R.
- Think Seniorita is a woman.
- That's right.
Tip, I saw that your sister
is back in town.
It's pretty cool.
She looks a lot different than
the last time I saw her, she...
- She's gotten older.
- Yeah, you're the same.
Don't talk about his sister, man.
That was purely just wondering
what was happening.
He has more friends than his relatives,
I would care about if they...
I want something greasy.
- How is it going?
- Fine.
There is a pubic hair by the ashtray.
- Kind of gross.
- I am sorry.
- Got to clean that up.
- I can get Pat to clean up for you.
What do you get with a mouse fat?
With the mouse's fat?
- Bacon.
- Then bacon it is.
- What do you guys want?
- Some black coffee. Straight-up.
- I want medium with bacon.
- Okay.
I just want to get a hamburger.
And cheese.
- How do you know it was that one?
- I don't.
It's so dark in there. I don't even
know how you guys even make...
Why don't you drop some
mothballs in this tank?
You boys think you got all answers.
Don't do anything weird to my truck.
He's here.
What's up, Bo?
Nice ball.
Come on, we're going to bother somebody
- Bother who?
- A boy.
- How are you doing?
- You got a problem?
- Yeah. I do.
We'll take a look at it.
- What're you doing?
- I was dumping whatever in the bucket
Dumping the dirty water
out of this bucket.
How are you doing?
- That's a great shirt you got.
- Thanks.
Well, I got to go. My dad is
over there waiting for us.
Don't work too hard.
Okay. Take it easy, you guys.
I will see you later.
I want you to do what you
say you're going to do.
- Can I have by 4:00 this afternoon?
- Absolutely.
Geoff, you bringing this
cart in here again?
What was that all about?
I told you're my number
one best friend.
- Good for you.
- Something smells.
You find my cutter?
Your tools are in your own same bag.
This is what you're talking about?
- No.
- Would you need this?
Yes.
Have you ever thought about
a normal past time?
Cooking, make a pie.
You're just jealous
because I do lunch.
What should I do with that?
Looks like you ain't fixing, Elvira.
I am working on it.
I will slap you naked
and hide your clothes.
Hey brother, hie.
Come here.
- Hey, how you're doing?
- I'm good.
- You okay?
- I am fine, I am fine.
You guys are working
out there or what?
No, we are just wrestling.
And then I hit my tooth...
Earlier this morning when I was
working on Joe's car break...
And I fell and it looked like...
- What happened to it? What you do?
- I don't know.
Hey, Leland. You tell your
child to stop biting my dog.
He got red marks all over
his body from her fangs.
Fangs, we call.
Dogs have bacteria, sweetie.
I don't want to be like my brother.
Which one?
Well, neither of them.
Tip spent all day drunkard, lazy.
He's not like my father who really
work, study for everything he has.
What did they think of you?
I think that they're afraid
I'm going to end up like Tip.
Living at home 4 years from now,
working at the mill.
I worked at the mill one summer.
They wrap blankets and plastic and...
We're working a cake, it's like
dust and stuff in the air and...
There is this sprinkling system
that turns on every hour...
To keep the fibres down and
you get rain on.
At least you have that experience.
I have never even been inside.
You know, I never have a real job.
Never been paid for anything normal.
I just don't want to go
to college and...
Have to be like, you know,
4 years and...
Writing bad poetry.
Listening to drums.
I think there is probably just as much
bad poetry in the breakroom at the mill
Yeah.
What?
I got a secret.
But you have to come here.
Come over there?
Hey Bo, if Cliver saw
race this weekend...
I might need you to ride along
with me if you don't mind.
I'm not kidding either.
When the hell I get angry?
Like that short trees race track that
I did with Robin on the back of them.
And Cliver saw him
got out of his car,
He climbed the tree and
kicked that dude's ass.
The dude up the tree was saying,
"Get out, go. Go down. Go out of
this tree. Get out. Stop climbing."
You remember that?
Hey, let's get some mothballs and
make my truck go faster.
Why are you all so quiet?
Marshall...
Says you hang out
with my little sister.
Saw you all hanging out.
Did he?
So what?
I hope there is no more talk
about that kind of stuff,
I get uncomfortable, you know.
We've been asked about things,
Margaret came down here
with her sweater earlier.
So what, you're a lover now?
What do you care, man?
Not like she's your sister.
Damn.
"You keep getting older
and you don't ever die."
God.
You know there're a few things
about me that you don't know.
There are a few things about me
that you don't know.
- Oh, really?
- Oh really.
I'll like to play you a song about it
- Okay.
Here we go, 2, 3 and...
Snake eyes, going to win or lose.
That's great. I don't know
you play instruments.
You didn't say much about that.
- Well, he doesn't really talk to me.
- Watch the retractor there.
I'll watch my own instrument.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you stupid or just blind, Noel?
I'm neither one.
You clearly don't know him.
What are you talking about?
He fucked every girl in this town.
- That is not true.
- It is true. I asked him.
- Did you asked him?
- Did you sleep with her or not?
And he walks away.
- I think I hate you.
- He won't walk away from me.
All right, because you are different.
Tip, could you put that down, please?
What makes you so special?
What makes you so special
besides the fact...
That you're new back in town and you
don't know what kind of guy he is.
I think I hate you.
I hate you.
If he is so horrible,
why are you his best friend?
Put that down!
Get out!
No, get a girl to do,
I'm not doing that.
But you've such a funny face.
- Excuse me.
- Look...
No, mom.
I need a hand. Just a little help.
- I don't want to do that crap.
- It is a couple of hours, please?
Don't touch me with
that clown costume.
Hello?
Awesome, mom.
Awesome.
With you, it taste different.
I like hanging out with you coz...
You look around and listen.
You know...
you follow.
When we're little,
I was too dumb to notice.
Did you just fart?
And here you are.
You always be happy.
- Did I say something stupid?
- No.
I pretend that...
I only have 10 seconds left to live.
One, two, three...
I like the mountains.
All right.
That's good.
What's wrong now?
Last night, I had a bad dream,
and you're in the river.
And you aren't moving,
and you were freezing,
And I was watching and cry.
Will you stay here with me?
Oh yeah, I will stay, be your friend.
Always be your daddy.
Can I go play now?
It's like this.
"Strong as a bird. Fast as a...
You know what I mean?
Hey, what's going on?
Do you want a pretzel?
Strong as a eagle,
fast as T.
You know what I mean?
It's like lndian talk.
We're going to start a band.
What do you play?
You hear that before?
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah, I am into it big time.
With my dream, you know.
I tell a lot of people, you know,
that I am into...
They look like me like
I am an alien or something.
Fast as a cob.
What I want to do? I'll sit there...
By myself in the dirt
with nobody around.
Start all over and put new ones down.
Make a wish.
That's really cool.
I love music.
Music makes me happy.
- I play the trombone.
- Do you?
- How long?
- About 4 years.
I can play
for longer than that.
Like ten.
Since you are like 12?
You want to see my teeth?
Tall as a bear.
...no, bird.
Tricky, it's tricky.
Pretzels are carbohydrate and they
expand in your stomach and turn to fat
Well,
- Eat it up. Eat more.
- I will.
Pancakes expand in your stomach too.
- Did they really?
- They do.
I didn't know that.
Don't you think about, you know,
When you order a pancakes
in the restaurant...
And just like sit in your
stomach like a brick?
- Usually I don't go for pancakes.
- What do you go for?
- Eggs?
- Really?
You know, what about waffles
or stuff like that?
No, the place that I go are
usually not that fancy.
So you two going out?
We hang out a lot.
It's different when it's a family.
I won't know that.
But Tip see you exactly
what he hates himself.
You think he'll just forgive and
forget about it?
Go up, tell it's all right.
"Go ahead, get my sister.
I've seen what you done...
With every other
girl in town. It's okay."
What you want me to do?
Turn the things off?
What do you want Tip to do?
I want him to calm down, I guess.
That's not going to happen.
Maybe if you didn't go down on...
Every girl's history book
as the asshole's ex-boyfriend.
But you have.
I have a dream that...
You grow a garden on
a trampoline and...
I was so happy that
I invent a peanut butter.
I saw them together today.
He's going to fuck your sister
like you fuck me...
And everybody else in this town.
Are you fucking my sister?
You didn't even feel anything.
I am just another girl.
But still kept going.
I thought I love him,
I thought he is in love with me.
I thought one day he'll wake up and...
I don't even know who
have you been talking to.
Tip, stop!
What the hell are you talking about?
I don't even know who
have you been talking to.
What do you got to give, Tip?
What do you got to give?
He is just jealous, man.
He want to fuck his own sister.
Tip.
We ain't friends no more.
You're on my top 10.
Who is that girl at the river?
Tammy Clinard.
She is this girl...
Did you date her?
Did you sleep with her?
You have too much shit on this bed.
I got a long time ago.
I was drunk.
Wait. Can I say something?
- I am sorry.
- No, don't be sorry.
I just want to say that...
I never have sex with anyone before.
But I trust you.
You trust me?
Do you trust me?
I make some ugly mistakes.
With girls?
There are most really ugly.
And anything...
That will make you feel
more comfortable for you to know...
I want to tell you that stuff...
Because I care about...
because I care about you.
A lot.
And when...
You know when people
from before come up...
And I want you to understand...
What they hate when they see me.
I think that...
I feel like...
If everything that you
have done before...
Makes you who you are now, then...
No matter how...
Ugly it is, I'm just going to learn
and deal with it because...
Right now, it's...
You and me.
You're the best boyfriend for me,
and I know that...
I am the best girl for you.
So...
If you don't choose to say
those things, I won't ask.
The first time I had sex,
I was 13 years old...
And it was in a basement, with
this older girl that I didn't know.
And then when we're,
when we are finished...
I was nervous...
I try to be cool and I told a joke.
It was stupid.
She never spoke to me again.
I just want to make sure that
in a million years from now...
I can still see you up-close and we'll
still have amazing things to say.
I am going to go now.
Okay.
How am I suppose to think
this girl is enough for you?
You'll meet her and then you'll know.
What if you ain't good for her?
Crazy.
Educated or honest or strong.
You don't have any faith.
You're my man that's
ever been in my life.
I am pretty strong.
You are funny.
But you know, maybe...
I get hurt, and I'm worry about others
like me that don't mean any harm.
I've stood where she stand.
I've seen the look you have.
I am just happy.
Look at me and say that.
I am happy.
I don't believe you.
Are you in love now or something?
What do you mean?
When you finish being in love,
you should come over to my house.
I got a water bed.
What is that suppose to mean?
What's up? When you're hooked with
your friend. I've been working out.
Check out this pipes. Look at this.
Noel, wait up.
Who is number two?
Who is back up for you?
- What?
- Who'll be the 2nd one you go with?
First choice is not available.
Who is number two?
I don't want to choose number two.
You don't have to act or anything but,
just if you had to, who'll it be?
It won't be anybody.
If you had to choose a
certain back up, if you...
Why would I have to choose?
You have to, everyone else is gone.
What if I want to be alone?
Okay, you can't choose alone or
number one. Who is number 2?
This is a ridiculous question.
Who you'll have sex with more?
Me or a preacher?
All those people that
pass through your life...
And they come and go find that
they're all gone and there is no...
There is no second best,
and she's the one...
Who talks to you,
with all you need to be...
And she laugh at the
funny thing that you say...
Like she was, she is in on a joke,
and then she whispers in your ear.
You know, when she first died...
I won't even shaken...
Because I could see myself
in her eyes before they close.
I was naked, looking over her.
The good stuff that
you've felt with Elise...
- Was that worth it?
- I think about that...
But how I felt if
something happen to you.
Or your mama...
Your Feng-Shui or
love another woman again?
I never want to feel that close.
Ever again.
- Are you still seeing Eric?
- Yes.
My brother can do that. My brother've
listened to me and he pumped his...
That's really disgusting.
- Did he ever get jealous?
- Yeah.
- He does.
- He is jealous.
You talk to another guy?
Yeah but he, I mean
he understand sometimes...
He will sit there and he'll watch.
But you know, just joke. It's not that
he's not worry about me or anything.
He's worry about the other man.
That's true.
I have learn that in a hard way.
You cannot trust man.
Have you ever had any
bad run in with man?
I've been to boarding school with
all girls since I was 1 2, so...
Not much experience.
You got something on your hair.
I like it when you smile at me.
You want to spend the night together?
You mean like a summer party?
A sleep over?
I think that's a good idea.
It smells like
is in here.
Two rooms.
What do you want to do?
What do you mean?
I don't know. Did you want
to get drunk or something?
Not really. Do you want to get drunk?
No. I don't.
I didn't know.
Do you want me to give up my pillow?
I still have my pillow.
I realise this.
I want to show you something.
I used to go fishing a lot...
My dad.
One summer when I was 12...
We went to Lake Sturtsum together.
I was a good fisherman so I used
to get to real fishing, you know.
My dad would take them and
cut them up and he cooked them.
And we get to eat them.
One day, I was...
I was driving the boat.
I wasn't suppose to coz,
But my dad let me take the
wheel because he was drunk.
There was these kids
out in the middle...
Swimming.
I guess I let the boat
get away from me.
I ran over this little boy.
We almost have killed him.
He wasn't coming out when everybody
was screaming hysterically.
My dad...
Push me down at the bottom of the
boat and he told me not to look.
I grabbed the fish hook from the
bottom and I just started scratching.
Then when I came home,
I was...
...mom and Tip that it was
an accident. But it wasn't.
You're the first person that
I want to tell that to.
Because you're the first person I want
to talk to for more than 5 minutes...
Ever.
Baby, I like,
I like that you trust me.
Does it hurt still?
It hurts because...
I know what was going through
my head when I did that...
It was like a release, you know.
I was glad, I was glad
that I have the pain.
You are so nice.
Sometimes, I am scare of myself.
But I am not scare with you.
Get undress.
Get into the water.
Are you okay?
I thought I was wearing my boxers.
It's cool.
Two seconds.
You are a baby.
Excuse me?
You see that right there? You
see that. It's tough skin, girl.
I don't know if you know
anything about Celtiques...
That is our symbol for fit size.
Are you okay?
I tore my nuts.
No more cannon-balls.
And no more pulling pants games.
Only what?
It hurts.
I like it when it hurts.
Kiss me on the neck.
You want me to kiss you on your neck?
Right there.
- Right there?
- Right there.
You sure right there?
Where again?
I don't want to have sex with you.
Are you attracted to somebody?
You're the best.
Will you just sleep here with me?
Sometimes I can't tell...
I can read your mind.
I don't want to be like what
it was like everything else.
You fuck her yet?
Did you?
Is it top secret?
Is it I am not suppose to know?
Special delivery?
I don't know if I can go out
with her for this long...
I probably at least
have feel her boobs.
I meant to tell you that.
She have nice boobs.
Sometimes your...
Friends aren't good to you or you
might not be good to your friends?
I talked to Beth last night. She and
the girls think I'm avoiding them.
You mean you were?
I guess I just lost track.
So we decide to go to
Vicki's house next weekend.
Would you want to go?
And pine needles and cone and sand.
Fun like in the lake
in the winter time.
I like the sound of water.
It makes me pee.
I guess that...
I will just go and...
Learn how to miss you...
You can do the same thing here.
I want to dance.
But I don't want you to watch.
Mom?
What are you doing?
Mother.
Where have you been with my car?
I forgot about your thing.
You're suppose to be here, oh God,
4 hours ago or something like that.
Did you know that it was Levante's
birthday party, I told you that actually
I remembered you saying
something, yeah, Levante.
- The kid that couldn't walk.
- I waited for an hour.
Then I rode my bicycle.
By the time I got there, the party
was over and he was back in bed.
Sorry.
That's all you have to say?
I am really sorry.
Listen, I'm sorry I forgot about it.
I don't even remember you
telling me about it...
But I believe that you did,
I've been a little occupied
lately and I understand.
I miss it.
Where were you?
I was just off.
Doing what?
Hanging out with...
- This girl?
- Yes, with this girl.
Mom, I'm not a kid anymore.
I got to go with how I feel.
I just do what else
am I suppose to do. Stop feeling?
Your selfishness, I pay the price.
I live here because I love you and
I don't want to see you alone.
I'm sorry if you're just jealous or
sad or you just want to shelter me.
I am very happy actually.
God jerk...
Don't call me a fucking jerk.
He's gotten up behind you.
Come on!
Hey, Tip.
I missed you at the race.
We didn't do real well.
Of course I will.
She changed a lot.
I know.
This is hard for me because
I know what you're. You're like me.
We are partner in crime.
She makes me decent.
You banged a lot of chicks, huh?
You took them down and
left by the way home.
Man, look at us.
We're getting old.
Not me, man.
I still sleep with my light on,
wet my bed or suck my fucking thumb.
All the girls I've been with, I never
spent a night away from home.
I afraid I will have bad dreams.
Last summer, I have this collection.
It was real special to me.
One day, I get home
from work and Justin...
He let them all go, you know.
I know he was just a kid but...
Hurtful things is bad.
You have a collection?
You want to hear something funny?
What's that?
I will be daddy.
You're going to be what?
Rachel came and find
her buddy yesterday.
The truth is...
I don't want to lose her.
Last night, I've decided...
Can you believe that I cried?
I cried because I was happy.
A pussy, huh?
Yeah, you're a pussy.
When I get this morning,
I cry myself back to sleep again.
Do you love her?
I guess.
There you go.
Come here.
Sit.
Good boy.
This ain't exactly a sport,
Tip is not much of an athlete.
He says he think I am a victim.
- He thinks you're a victim?
- Yeah.
What do you think?
Do you miss my sister?
Why, do you?
Yeah.
Yeah, me too.
She's nice, ain't she?
Teach you how to play what?
Teach me how to play piano.
- Teach you how to play piano?
- Yeah.
Sure I can.
- For 50 bucks.
- Huh?
Give me a five, dude.
My hand.
Hello.
What's up?
What's going on?
Where are you?
I'm at Vicki's lakehouse.
We're having a party at the deck.
You're having a party?
It's just a bunch of drunk people.
I got a suprise for you.
What suprise?
It's kind of drastic.
I don't know if you'll like it.
What is it?
It is a suprise.
Why don't you just give it to me
when you get back here, I guess.
I was hanging out with Justin.
He wants me to play...
teach him how to play the piano.
I don't know, not sure what to do,
I don't know the right...
Like a lesson, coz I don't really know
how to play the piano that well.
Hello?
Yeah?
Are you having a good time?
There was this guy,
he keeps looking at me,
He was such a dolt.
I hope he'll leave.
- I miss you.
- Yeah, I miss you too.
So, is this guy a friend
of Vicky or whatever?
He is just a friend.
It's kind of raining here.
- Is it really?
- Yeah.
Really raining actually.
That was perfect.
What's wrong?
I think your hair looks great.
It makes you look
completely different.
- You think?
- Yeah.
It's great.
Where did it all go?
It makes your eyes look
bigger in a really good way.
It's so short.
- It's not that short.
- It's pretty short.
- It looks really good though.
- Thank you.
I am really happy you're here.
I miss you a little bit.
I am sorry.
I am a little hangover.
I hear you.
Big weekend.
There's this guy, Patrick, who's there
and he was going around and he was...
He was moaning everyone, you know...
You'll be like talking and there'll
be like this big butt around you.
And there's like this house
of elderly people and he...
He pull down his pants, he shot a
firecracker through his leg at them.
It was funny. You'll have thought
it was cool if you were there.
Do you...
Let's go somewhere.
I mean I have a place for us...
I have a suprise for you.
- You do?
- I do.
Come on.
It's not far, I promised.
Could we talk for a second?
Sit down.
I have such a funny weekend.
Funny how?
There was this guy that I met at the
lake. He is a friend of a friend.
What about him?
Baby?
Baby, what did he do to you?
What?
We fucked.
I didn't mean for it...
I don't know how it happened.
I didn't plan...
I tried so hard not to make it hurt.
Did he hurt you?
- He raped you?
- No...
Not to make it hurt you.
I don't want to hurt you.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about...what,
I don't know what, I don't know...
I don't know what I am talking about.
I am trying to be open with you.
Why?
Just don't say anything.
Just shut up.
I'm just trying to figure out,
I'm just trying...
To figure out what
I'm going to do here.
Wait a second.
What am I going to do?
How am I supposed
to just get past this?
What do you...
What do you telling me that
you had sex with some guy?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
That's what you just said.
- You just said that to me.
- I know I said it. I know I said it.
I didn't mean it...
I mean I didn't...
Listen, if you just tell me
what you want me to do here...
I mean tell me what I did to you...
That's what I'm trying to say here.
I need to figure out what I need here,
okay?
And I feel sick, I feel sick.
I feel sick.
Who is this guy?
You had sex with some guy?
Do I know who he is?
Just tell me I know who he is.
Tell me I know who he is.
- Where does he live?
- I love you.
I love you.
- What?
- I love you.
- You what?
Why would you said that?
What is wrong with you?
What did I do to you?
It's just that I love you...
Because I want you to love me,
Don't try to correct something that
you fucked up by saying I love you.
Why would you said that to me?
What's wrong with you?
- What did I do to you?
- Did you hear me?
I said, "l love you" because how
else, how else am I suppose to...
How else am I suppose
to explain to you...
That this isn't
something that you did?
This is not something that you did.
I love you.
That's how I feel.
I'm looking at you right now
and I hear you talking...
And all the words
that are coming out of...
Your mouth are like
coming out of a stranger.
Why don't you put your fucking
hair back and come back.
Just come back.
The worst part is,
I don't even know this guy.
He is just some guy that she met at the
lake, and they hang out at the lake,
And then, he just
fucks her brain out.
I mean you don't understand, she...
I've been through 26 woman in my life.
You know all of a sudden, I stop and
this girl breaks to the surface...
This virgin breaks to the surface and
she did the exact same thing to me.
- She is a virgin?
- Yeah.
You mean you never did...
Damn.
If anybody smile at me ever again,
I'm going to freak out.
And he say one little thing...
Girls are smart.
They figured this out.
Woman make you act like monkey.
They become monkey and
they get vulnerable.
They let your guard down...
They identify your weakness...Bam!
They're in control.
This is creative thinking, kind
of like when you're dating Kelly.
I mean if you want to bust a nut,
that's your business.
But you're about to have a baby.
You can't even afford your braces.
Mary Margaret, I see you.
Where have you been?
I haven't been anywhere.
I've been right here.
Nowhere.
Let me get that for you.
You put that back on.
I'll put that on for you.
You have a great ear-rings.
My dad
for the baby.
Congratulations to your...
Happy Birthday.
Baby, when baby get borned,
it's like a woman's time.
It's only girls in there,
You know, you try to pop your head in
and they don't want you around.
I don't know.
Listen, I want to talk about
when we're dating...
I wanted to say to you that,
if I hurt your feelings...
If I hurt your feelings,
- Then I'm sorry.
- Shut up.
- I'm sorry I hurt your feelings.
I'm really sorry. I'm trying to
apologise to you in a real way.
You're not sorry.
You know how I know that?
Because you're not
smart enough to be sorry.
Guys like you,
They don't quit...
And they never leave.
You're going to be here forever.
How does it make you
feel knowing that?
Hey, what's happening, Sattler?
Hey Bust-Ass, nice outfit.
Your mama get that for you?
You let me borrow them?
Hey, do you want to know a secret
that I didn't tell anybody ever?
No.
When I was walking in the dark
I had before Dwayne...
This dog named Mr T...
When he was a puppy, he had a, his
hair was sticking out like a mohawk.
And you know how ducks fly home
in a V? It's like a V shape.
And they get home...
And I was walking my dog and...
I looked up and there
is a big V above me,
And l, there is all these ducks
flying back to their home.
- Can I please get a beer?
- And right when they flew above me...
I saw them and they're crashing
to a big house, the whole V.
And then they hit the ground,
and they just kind of curl up.
You ever fucking see that?
Have you ever seen a mistaken nature?
Have you ever see an
animal make a mistake?
What kind of pleasure
you having here?
Really?
What kind of gas you put in here?
87.
We thought it'll go faster.
- I might have one.
- Where do you keep it?
Hey.
Where are you going?
What?
Come for a ride with me.
Why?
Coz I want to talk to you.
You car break down?
Leland got it started.
I am in a truck.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about how we
sit in this car right now.
I wish we could talk.
It sounds to me like you
got Bust-Ass to talk to.
We're just friends and you know it.
Oh, you guys are friend?
That's awesome.
Actually, I didn't know that.
I thought he was my friend.
But it's great that you guys
are tight like that.
We just started talking.
He's really fun. We went bowling when
Blake and those guys are there.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's cool this is so easy for you.
At least I am trying.
You see this is why you
don't know anything about me.
I mean, you know a lot.
And that's yours.
You can keep it.
I'm just the guy who thought...
He was finally on the right track
and making the right moves.
Bust-Ass said that...
Don't tell me what Bust-Ass said.
That's not even his name.
His name is Tracy.
I don't care what that
fucking dick said.
- I can't even talk to you.
- Listen to me,
Every single girl I've ever touched,
I regret every night.
What is that mean?
Are you saying that...
You think that we should just
forget about each other?
That's the saddest thing
in the whole world.
I'm just saying that...in the future,
don't come crying to me coz...
Coz I'm not feeling anymore your
midnight phone calls coz you fuck up.
Wait, wait,
please stop.
Would you come over one last time?
Because I am sorry, I am sorry.
And I want to make sure that the
words in my head come across to you.
I want you to see the feelings
I have for you.
You can touch me.
Are you okay?
I don't know what to
say to you anymore.
Don't say anything.
Don't smoke in my room.
When you sit around crying,
it ain't going to do you any good.
I got news for you.
You got to grow up and balance your
personal life with responsibility.
What am I suppose to do, dress up
like a clown and change bedpans?
I don't understand why I've to
listen to this crap when you're...
Fucking standing here
with a broken heart about...
That's good.
That's a good one.
Do you know what this is?
Clown's clothes.
That's what.
This is what I get for
living through hard times.
These are the clothes I wear.
This is my face now.
Do you want to look like me?
Do you want to look like this?
I was fucking beautiful.
Look at me.
I got my own battle to attend to.
I didn't mean that I don't love you.
I don't.
It is just that I can see the future
and you got other opportunity...
Opportunity I didn't have.
I don't know the kind of
moment that have got...
Where is that going to get you?
I just want to be like
she never existed.
No, you don't.
I can tell you that right now.
Justin, it's good to see you, pal.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Stop the world.
You came to the door.
I did.
And I got some stuff to say,
if you don't mind.
You got paper-towels?
Yeah.
We're making macaroni and cheese,
do you want some?
No.
It's all over.
No, I am sorry.
I am sorry.
Take it easy, buddy.
Be strong.
What did you do?
I got to fire my truck.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
I'm not the smartest guy in the world.
I guess what I was trying to do
is become a better person.
You know what I think?
My problem is not anything
that you did.
It's between me and...
Me.
Well, I did what I did.
It felt...
So...
Wrong.
And that's when I realised
that I love you.
You can't understand it but
that's what I have found out.
It is an emotional thing.
Nobody tells you that part.
It's true.
I miss your face.
You know what?
You're not allowed to hate me.
Because I am not going to let you.
Nobody said we
have to be perfect.
I wish it didn't hurt with
every thought of you.
You have my heart.
Can you close your eyes?
Pretend you can see the ocean.
Pretend you standing over the ocean.
You are a millionaire.
Pretend we're running under the ocean.
You jumping across mountains.
I used to be the richest
man in the world.
Now, I'm sitting here
looking out at the state...
Happier than I have ever been.
With next to nothing.
I thinking about growing a beard.
You know when you hit me,
It hurt.
I mean it hurts.
But it help me.
Have you ever held a baby?
Are we always going to be this old?
I don't want to do it alone.
I mean...
...I brought you all the way out here.
It's not like I'm the one
who need swimming lessons.
And the fact that you're not even
trying, that baffles me, really.
What are you afraid of?
There is no sharks in here.
Suppose the water all
comes walking down...
The tracks and sees you,
what is he going to say about you?
If there is a time in the world,
there is time to take a chance...
...it's time right now to take a
chance. What's this? Water. Get in it.
It is water. Listen.
This river goes two ways.
That way and that way.
You know what I am saying?
It's like a puzzle with pants,
if you think about it.
Are you happy now?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org