WOMAN:  7-3-4-7.
4-9-3-1.
4-3-1-9.
0-7-7-4.
7-3-4-1.
7-4-4.
7-5-7-5.
GREY: Did you
get that?
EMERSON: Yeah,
I got it.
GREY: So I'm listening
to the radio the other day,
Radio 2, NPR Radio
or something...
Uh-huh.
There's some fucking guy,
scientist or something.
(SIGHS)
Real sick bastard.
You listening?
Avidly.
Says he measured
out the remains,
the cremated
remains of a dead man.
Measured out the,
uh, minerals left
behind, you know?
The iron phosphates,
the... Whatever it is
we're made up of.
Says he added
it all up to the
cost of $4.40.
You believe that?
Yeah, I guess so.
$4.40.
Burnt down man's
worth less than
a fucking Big Mac,
all you can say
is "I guess so"?
Says give this poor
bastard what he's
got coming.
Authentic?
Yeah.
Ten minutes.
Start the count.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
MAN: (ON TV)
All eyes are on the
newcomer, Rainer...
BARTENDER:
Can I get you something?
Two shots. Scotch.
EMERSON: Got money
on the game?
Nah, spread's terrible.
Here. One
for the road.
No, thanks. Been
sober for three years.
Interesting career.
You do something
long enough.
(SCOFFS)
You close your eyes,
you just can't think of
doing something else.
(CLATTERING)
They found
your accounts.
Where'd you spend it?
(CHUCKLES)
Look, man, I just
wanted to start over.
Quit the Agency.
Have your drink.
It could have been
anybody walk
through your door.
Yeah. But
it was you.
(SCREAMS)
(CLANKING)
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Go clean up
your mess.
Three minutes.
Start the count.
MAN: No,
please, God.
(GRUNTS)
Why did you
do that?
Why? Why did
you do that?
(SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
Why did you do that?
(GUNSHOT)
(EXHALES)
(GASPS)
GREY: What a shame.
(GUNSHOT)
Have you lost
your fucking mind?
(SIGHS)
She's just a kid.
Jesus Christ.
The fuck,
Emerson?
(PANTING)
No loose ends.
(COCKS GUN)
(GUNSHOT)
DOCTOR:  How long
have you been out
in the field?
It should say
there, in the file.
I want to hear
what you say.
A long time.
I didn't know
you smoked.
When did you start?
Right after
I quit drinking.
Why did you
stop drinking?
I was a drunk.
What would you say is
your current disposition?
How do I feel?
How do you feel
about the girl?
She asked a very
good question.
Which was?
Why?
Well, that's a question
that needs to be asked.
We are not sociopaths.
We're vulnerable
to qualms of conscience
like anyone else.
We face these
decisions every day,
and we vote up or down.
Like everything else,
it has all been
distilled down to
zeros and ones.
They have asked for me
to describe your
emotional state
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
in as detailed
a manner as possible.
To determine
whether you are fit
to remain in the field.
I hate that it had
to turn out this way.
(SIREN WAILING)
Me taking care
of the girl, me taking
care of the police.
What you need, what
we're willing to offer,
is a change of pace.
We have a station
for you to look after.
Blackleg Miner.
One of the
smaller terminals.
England?
Yeah.
Far the fuck out,
middle of nowhere.
Old American Army base.
Officially it doesn't exist.
Unofficially, it's
used to broadcast numbers
to our European field agents.
How long?
Until your
head is right.
You'll be babysitting
a broadcaster.
Civilian, right?
Yeah, cryptology specialist.
And one of the very few
people who can process
code at this level.
You and another team,
alternating shifts.
Three days each.
You keep the station safe,
you keep the code safe.
Whatever it takes.
Okay.
Do the job, Emerson.
I don't wanna look like
an ass for sticking my
neck out on this one.
'Cause I've got nothing
left, nothing to keep
you from the wolves.
0-7-3.
4-5-5.
8-1-7.
6-9-0-1-0.
KATHERINE: Sorry.
Little last-minute
broadcast come through.
EMERSON:
I'll inform
the authorities.
You do that.
Wanna hear my
latest theory?
Sure.
We're coordinating
troop movements
in Afghanistan.
Long-term
tactical formations.
Yeah.
Illegal missions unsanctioned
by the UN, that's why
it's all hush-hush.
EMERSON: Could be.
It's good, right?
Yeah.
KATHERINE: Maybe it's all just
some sort of awful experiment.
Stuff two people in
a box, see how long
it takes for one of
us to kill the other.
EMERSON: That's nice.
Ah, give me something.
We're up two hours
early next shift.
You guys been
waiting long?
No, you're good.
Good shift?
Yeah.
Got to catch up on
sitting alone for 70 hours.
It was nice.
You know, my contract's
up pretty soon. I was
thinking of re-upping.
Nothing else
you'd rather do?
No.
I was recruited
by a software
company in college.
The kind that
makes apps for phones.
What's wrong?
Pay is no good?
No, it was great,
actually. Obscene,
to be honest with you.
Why didn't you
do it, then?
I don't know. I don't
know, I guess I just
felt like it was silly,
it wasn't really that
important, you know?
I guess I like the idea
of serving my country.
Even if I don't know
exactly what it is I do.
What about you?
You never wanted
to do anything else?
There comes
a time when you
do a thing long enough,
you can't really
imagine doing
anything else, you know?
So, if I stay here,
I'm stuck with
you forever?
Yes. Be careful
what you wish for.
(LAUGHING)
KATHERINE:
You're doing it again,
aren't you?
What?
You have that
look that you get.
What look?
You're squinting one
eye as if you're
taking aim with a gun.
You're gonna be late.
It's horrifying.
I'm sure you're
great fun at parties.
Seriously, you don't
have to think about
killing everyone
that you ever meet.
I don't.
Okay.
So, just for fun,
what would happen
if I wasn't here on Monday?
EMERSON: Has there
been a horrible
train accident?
No. Train's here.
I'm just not on it.
It wouldn't be fun.
Come on, what
would happen?
I'd have to make
a phone call.
You'd have to
make a phone call?
I would make
a phone call.
No fun.
Company man.
(GUNSHOT)
Hi.
How you doing?
Good.
You should have seen
your face back there.
What?
When I didn't get off
the train right away,
you looked like
you were about to
have a heart attack.
How was your weekend?
Good.
I had a great weekend,
thanks for asking.
So you got that text?
Confirming the...
What I already knew.
Yeah, I got it.
Did you get mine?
I was trying to
make a joke about
the White House
Correspondents' dinner,
but my phone spell-checked
it into whorehouse
correspondents' dinner.
Spell-checks are
usually pretty accurate.
Right. I'm sure there's
a whorehouse
correspondents'
dinner somewhere.
Somewhere, yeah.
(LAUGHS)
(PHONE RINGING)
I know, I know, I got it.
No phones inside.
Hey, if it were up
to me, I couldn't
care less.
Gone. Done.
Okay?
Should be out by now.
Yeah.
Probably just got
a last-minute broadcast.
What?
Nothing.
One sec.
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(COCKS GUN)
(GUNSHOT)
(CAR ALARM BEEPING)
KATHERINE: Ah!
(COUGHING)
(KATHERINE GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
No... Ah!
I can't hear.
Shh.
(WHISPERS) Okay.
Eardrums.
(GUNSHOT)
Stay quiet, okay?
Okay.
Stay quiet.
(KATHERINE GRUNTING)
Stay here.
Be quiet, okay?
(KATHERINE GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
(SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
Katherine.
We're clear.
Are you sure?
We'd know by now
if somebody else
were in here.
Whose hand is that?
I don't know.
Can you hear?
Yeah.
If they know the code
from before, they're
gonna come back in.
They're gonna
use it again.
No, the codes
change every shift.
They could have had
David and Meredith's
code but not ours.
Where are they?
Take a deep breath.
(INHALES)
(BOTH EXHALE)
We're gonna walk.
We're gonna call
for help. Okay?
"Cardiff, Aberdeen,
Glasgow, Belfast,
Oxford, Slough."
"Cardiff, Aberdeen,
Glasgow, Belfast,
Oxford, Slough."
OPERATOR:  Operator.
Blackleg Miner Station.
Go ahead.
The station's
been compromised.
Requesting
immediate evacuation.
One moment.
Evac authorized.
ETA?
Four hours. For now,
standard protocol.
Secure location. Retire asset.
Repeat.
The code has
been compromised.
Retire your broadcaster.
Did you copy that?
Got it.
What? What'd
they say?
EMERSON: Four hours.
Sit tight.
(THUDDING)
Shh.
Did you hear that?
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(BANGING)
They're drilling through.
EMERSON: Let's go
check the security cameras.
Find out what happened
to David and Meredith.
Shit.
All the cameras are down.
Audio's on a separate file.
Yeah.
Pull it up.
KATHERINE: Here.
(STATIC)
Nothing.
What time was that?
One hour ago.
Earlier.
(PEOPLE FIGHTING)
DAVID:  Fuck you!
MAN:  Do you wanna
be a fucking hero?
Go back further.
DAVID:  We just gotta hold
out a couple of hours
till Emerson gets
here and then I hope...
(SOUNDS OF FIGHTING)
MAN:  Quiet!
DAVID:  Get off of me!
MAN:  Where is she?
DAVID:  Fuck you!
MAN:  You go get her. Tell her
to come out. Tell her
to come out right now!
Take a fucking seat!
We know you have
to open the door
from the inside.
Can you get her
to do that for us?
It'll be a lot easier.
Fuck you.
I need to get inside
the broadcast room.
I need the girl
to open the door.
I need her to take care
of some numbers for me.
Now this is something
only she can do.
And I'm kinda on
a tight schedule.
KATHERINE: They didn't
know about the
change in schedule.
We got here early.
I know about
you and the girl.
We know, okay?
Now we can offer
you two a way out,
a way through.
And if you do what
we say, if you help us,
we won't have to hurt her.
There's no need
for violence.
Violence is what got
us all in this place
to begin with.
This is the end
of violence for us.
This is a new beginning.
It's a partnership.
And it starts by
you getting her
to open that door.
DAVID:  Fuck you.
EMERSON: Oh, shit.
Your leg.
Oh, my God.
I don't even
feel anything.
That's usually a bad sign.
You always know
what to say to a girl.
Up.
You have training
in this kind of a thing,
right?
What?
Field surgery?
Dressing wounds?
Yeah.
I mean, it's not my
area of expertise
but I know a little bit.
Okay.
Is all this blood normal?
Well, you have a piece
of truck in your leg.
No way is a joke
gonna make me feel
more comfortable
in your ability to
not kill me right now.
Grit your teeth.
(GRUNTS)
Looks like we
missed the artery.
But it's gonna
be okay, right?
You could
still bleed out.
Emerson, lie
to a girl, will you?
Bite down.
I think it's
starting to hurt.
Bite.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
That was bizarre.
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES)
Emerson!
Yeah.
I thought you left me.
(SIGHS)
How long was I out?
Little while. Not long.
We were ambushed.
Yeah.
So, what? What?
They wanted to
stop the broadcasts?
You know as
much as I do.
Yeah, but we didn't
do anything wrong.
Right? We were ambushed.
Sit back down.
All the audio files are
there. We had nothing
to do with it. So...
They can't blame
us for anything.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
We're fine.
We were ambushed.
Calm down.
I am calm. But what
are we gonna do next?
Stop walking
around on your leg.
I'm fine. What
do we do next?
Just tell me
what we do now.
(PHONE RINGING)
OPERATOR:  Timetable updated.
Mmm-hmm.
We'll have you out
of there in less
than two hours.
Has everything been
taken care of at your end?
I can't confirm that.
Is there a problem?
No.
Get it done, immediately.
What?
Two hours.
Ugh, this drilling
is driving me nuts.
I wanna find
David and Meredith.
(TAPPING THE GUN)
You sure no one
else could be in here?
What?
Nothing.
I was just
thinking they wanted
something in
the broadcast room.
Gotta get over there.
Think they got
what they came for?
Let's find out.
It's pretty
standard activity.
Two broadcasts yesterday.
Three last night.
There's gotta
be something.
What? What
do you got?
Fifteen broadcasts
this afternoon.
What?
Just 20 minutes apart.
Whoever broke in
here didn't do it to
stop the broadcasts.
Well, that's a good
thing, right?
Katherine, when you
send a broadcast
you're sending
out these numbers
to the agents in the field
to deliver specific
assignments they cannot
trust to normal
communication lines.
Do you know
what that means?
Fifteen broadcasts.
Fifteen assignments.
Unauthorized.
Assassinations, bombings.
Could be anything.
Murders?
Gonna fix it.
Here, what does it say?
Can't read that.
Agents in the field carry,
like, one-time notebooks,
like pads.
Each page is
a new cypher.
When you broadcast something,
the agent matches
up the first set
of numbers to
the page in the notebook.
Now he knows he's
using this page,
and this page only,
to decode the message.
When he's done,
he destroys the page.
So we send another broadcast
to cancel this one.
Every cypher's
a one-time deal.
Totally random.
Completely impossible
to crack the code
unless you have
the original cypher.
That changes
with every shift.
So we need the cypher?
Yes, we need
that cypher.
(CRASHING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
MAN:  As much as it
seems like we're here
to hurt you,
to kill you, I assure you,
both of you,
that's the
worst-case scenario.
Must have left
the computer running.
It doesn't scare me.
Shut the fuck up!
Back off!
Please. Let me
rephrase that.
You think someone
like me is afraid
of being shot?
Back off!
Meredith. This is
between you and I.
The rest of these guys,
they don't matter.
This is just you and me.
And a choice.
You're shaking now.
You're getting angry.
You're letting your
emotions get the better
of the situation.
The adrenaline is
really kicking in.
But what I know,
the reason that
I'm not shaking
is because this is a choice
not dictated by emotion.
This is logic.
Pure, simple.
My boy over there is
rated 4th in the world
on the Glock 30.
You know what
that means?
What's it mean?
It means I could
shoot you from Texas.
(CHUCKLES)
Now, that's, of course,
an exaggeration
but the point stands.
He knows what he's doing.
He's a professional.
And you're you.
You've already
dropped the gun.
Because this is
a choice within a very
strict set of parameters.
Right now you're in control.
What you don't wanna do
is put him in control.
Don't give him the choice.
That way is death.
That way is
the unconditional end
to future choice.
That's it.
Good girl.
I know, I know.
It's always a tough
lesson to learn,
to realize that you
don't have the stomach
to do what's needed.
Don't kill her.
MAN: Of course not.
But you, on the
other hand...
MEREDITH: No!
Don't! Please, please.
No! Please, please.
(DAVID GRUNTING)
(BELCHES)
(MEREDITH SCREAMS)
(DAVID GRUNTS)
(SOBBING)
David!
Please!
No!
You'll do exactly
what we want.
You'll broadcast my
numbers because now
you know every
choice has a consequence.
(DAVID AND MEREDITH SCREAM)
MEREDITH:  Stop it!
Stop it!
KATHERINE: My God.
Try the other zones.
(POUNDING)
Who's in the basement?
EMERSON: Let's see
what's down there.
(FOOTSTEPS CLANGING)
We're clear.
My God.
He only fired two shots.
Oh, my God,
it's David.
(MUTTERS) Oh, my God!
EMERSON:
They must have thought
he was dead. Bled out.
He knew there was
a gun hidden down here.
You still with me?
Yeah, feel nauseous.
Yeah, well, puke
if you have to.
I haven't puked
since college.
Keep talking.
Where did you go?
Brown.
Yeah, how long?
Two years.
Before you dropped
out, huh?
MAN: There you are.
(DAVID YELLS)
They're looking for this.
Mainframe's connected
to the computer.
So whatever's on this...
You said the codes
were impossible to crack.
Unless you have
the original cypher.
But whatever
they're looking for,
it's on this, so can you?
Yeah, I'm on it,
I'm on it.
Who's this?
Oh, it's the Director
of Clandestine
Operations Overseas.
Somebody's boss's boss's
boss. Somebody high up
in the company.
Director Atwater.
Director Collins.
Templeman.
Keep going.
Yeah, these are
people being groomed
for top slots in
the corporation.
Go back, go back.
I know that man.
That's my fucking boss.
Fifteen dossiers.
Fifteen broadcasts.
There it is.
If I wanted to
cripple the system
in one fell swoop,
these would be
the 15 I'd start with.
You kill these men today,
you won't recognize the
world when you wake
up in the morning.
But they've already
sent the broadcasts.
I mean, what the hell
do they want with us?
They wanna kill us.
Make sure you don't
cancel the broadcasts.
Grab that.
Let's go.
Here.
That's all the information
from the laptop,
in case, uh...
I don't know, in case
we don't get out of here.
Drink that.
"Of course we'll get
out of here, Katherine.
"Don't you worry
about a thing."
You ever get
used to it?
Used to what?
Bodies. Dead people.
Seeing them.
No.
They never seem
to stay dead. How's it
going over there?
There's stuff on here,
but it's password protected.
I know, but can
you open it?
I don't know.
I'm trying.
(SIGHS) How do we
know all this mayhem
hasn't already happened?
We don't.
Good. Just keep working.
Fuck.
(SIGHS)
Can you just
talk to me?
Yeah, what do you
wanna talk about?
Anything. Just regular stuff.
Like what normal
people talk about.
Not really my
strong suit, Katherine.
I'll start.
(SIGHS)
How do you know I
dropped out of college?
Oh, that was just
a lucky guess.
Grabbed my file
or something?
You fit a profile.
Of what?
Civilian broadcasters
have a certain, you know,
personality trait.
Keep working.
Well, I can't work in silence,
so you might as
well just entertain me.
Okay.
A troubled childhood
with an emphasis
on extreme emotional
loss or fatigue.
Death of a parent.
Sometimes sexual abuse.
Lack of a strong
authority figure
in adolescence.
Low self-esteem resulting in
few permanent relationships.
Defensive.
Rebellious.
Highly intelligent.
Susceptible to being
stuck in one position,
environment or occupation
for long periods of time.
Wow... Yeah,
you're terrible at this.
How about your profile?
Indifferent and
emotionally detached
from reality.
Inability to communicate
with any other
human being on
the face of this Earth.
Willing to sit
silently in one place
for hours at a time.
Make sure that you have a plan
to kill every person
that you ever meet.
No. Close.
No, I had a stable childhood
but with an underlying desire
to break free from
control or authority.
Restless.
Sense of self-entitlement.
Striking lack of empathy
or compassion
for other people.
Bordering between autism...
Stop.
You know, I, um,
didn't always do this.
This is my first
station assignment.
I was on the other
end of the numbers.
Looking at nine million
black-book tax dollars.
Recruited me
straight out of college.
Said it was the best
opportunity I'd ever have.
Told me I'd do special
things, important things.
Well, you're worth
more than
what some
bureaucrat wrote down
on a piece of
paper 20 years ago.
Hmm...
All they're really
talking about is
what's real. Reality.
They know how to use it.
They're good at it.
Why not quit?
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. Yeah.
I knew a guy once,
and he decided
he wanted to quit.
He squirreled away money for
about 20 years and
he opened up a bar
and wanted to
create a new life,
and he survived
about 37 months.
They killed him?
No, I did.
See if you can get
into those files.
DAVID:  ...Emerson gets here.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(GUNSHOTS)
DAVID:  Get off me!
Get the fuck off!
Get it off me!
(DAVID GRUNTS)
How much longer?
Little while still.
MAN:  Go on, David,
tell her to come out.
Tell her to
come out right now!
DAVID:  Fuck you!
MAN:  Get up there.
(GUNSHOTS)
MAN:  Do you wanna
be a fucking hero?
DAVID:  Get off!
Get the fuck off me!
(REWINDING)
(GUNSHOTS)
DAVID:  I don't know
how they got in.
I mean, how can
they have gotten
the door code?
It changes every shift.
Unless someone...
They knew the code
and I told Mere...
I told Meredith to
lock herself inside
the broadcast room
to broadcast over
the emergency channel.
(POUNDING)
Fuck.
If anyone's even listening,
if it's even
still on the air...
They've cut into all our
other secure lines
of communication.
I don't know how.
I mean, who could
know that much?
Even the one-way
operator line,
I didn't even think
that was possible.
Wait.
What did he just say?
(REWINDING)
Even the one-way
operator line,
I didn't even think
that was possible.
KATHERINE: They cut
into the operator line?
You did speak to
someone on the phone.
You spoke to the operator.
Yes.
I swear to God,
if you were pretending
to talk to someone...
Katherine,
I gave him the code.
He verified the code.
Yeah, but did you
verify him?
"Cardiff, Aberdeen,
Glasgow, Belfast,
Liverpool, Slough."
Operator.
That wasn't
the right code.
What?
What I just called in.
It wasn't the
right code.
Tell me you killed the girl
before you figured that out.
What?
Fuck! They got to
the emergency phones.
Just let me think.
No one even knows
we're in trouble, do they?
No, they don't.
There has to be
a safety measure, right?
No.
Something or someone?
There's nothing.
Someone who
cancels the broadcast
when something
like this happens.
There's no one.
There has to be
some kind of back-up,
like an emergency back-up...
Something like
this doesn't happen.
Seventy years,
the code's
never been breached.
Somebody has to be
out there who can...
Katherine, there's nothing
but the goddamn numbers!
(PHONE RINGING)
If we do our job,
we get out of here
alive. I promise.
OPERATOR:  You kill her
for me, I let you live.
(SIGHS)
No.
We've gone to
a lot of trouble here
with these broadcasts.
We can't leave
anything to chance.
We can't let the girl
cancel the broadcasts.
She's the only one
who can undo what's been done.
You understand that,
you're not a fool.
Go fuck yourself.
Look, your bosses
won't let her live.
She knows too much.
Either you or me
or the Agency
pulls the trigger.
No matter what, she
doesn't make it out alive.
You know a lot
about this business.
What's the problem?
What do you care?
Like you haven't done it
a hundred times before.
We've almost drilled
through your door anyways.
Might as well
save your own life.
What's she worth
to you? She's nobody.
DAVID:  Fuck.
If anyone's even listening,
if it's even
still on the air...
(DAVID PANTING)
I couldn't take the shot.
I couldn't do it.
How could I do it?
KATHERINE: He said
he couldn't take the shot.
No, he couldn't.
What does that
mean, Emerson?
What do you
think it means?
It means that there are
no other safety measures.
That David was
the safety measure.
Yeah.
Means that you're
the safety measure.
And all this time
I thought you
were protecting me.
I knew you looked at me
funny. I knew you fucking
looked at me funny.
(SIGHS)
Liar.
I should have
listened to myself.
Where are
you going?
Nowhere! Where
am I gonna go?
I'm stuck here
with you.
Yeah.
And what have
you got, huh?
What have you got
outside of this?
Do you have a life?
How could that
possibly matter?
What do you mean
"how does it matter"?
It means everything.
What is...
What have you got?
You've got nothing to
live for except for this!
Mmm-hmm...
This is all you've got.
You've got your protocol.
You've got your numbers.
You're on the other side
of the fucking numbers.
And you read them and
you take their money.
You think you're not
a part of this, huh?
Do you think you
can fuck around
with these people?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing here?
You're in it.
You asked for it
and you're in it.
Here, locked
and loaded.
Safety's off.
It's good to go.
I don't want
your fucking gun.
If I was gonna kill you,
I would have done
it a long time ago.
(SOBBING)
MAN:  You'll do
exactly what we want.
You'll broadcast my
numbers because now
you know every
choice has a consequence.
(REWINDING)
You'll do exactly
what we want.
You'll broadcast my
numbers because now
you know every
choice has a consequence.
My cell phone.
My cell phone's
in your glove-box.
We can use it
to call for help.
Doesn't help much
with the guys waiting
outside that door.
Yeah, but there are
three voices on
the recording, right?
The one who attacked us,
the one who was
dead in the basement.
And one guy who will
watch outside. Maybe.
Yeah.
Lock yourself in.
It's the only secure
room we got left.
(LOCKING DOOR)
OPERATOR:  Is she dead?
Yes, it's done.
Come upstairs.
Leave the door
open and drive away.
Welcome to early retirement.
God, Meredith.
Please.
(SIGHS)
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
these are them.
(UNLOCKS DOOR)
Meredith.
0-1-6-6
4-4-3-1-7-8-7-0.
8-8-2-8-4-5-7-7
6-6-8-9.
(GUNSHOT)
(GUNSHOTS)
Fuck, no!
7-7.
Okay.
(DOOR OPENING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GUNSHOT)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
(COUGHS)
(GROANING)
KATHERINE:
I unlocked the cypher.
(GRUNTING)
I got the cypher.
It was just one...
One more, one
more broadcast.
Forget the broadcast.
Ow, oh...
(GRUNTS) No, no...
Come here, come here.
(BOTH PANTING)
It's seven.
It doesn't matter.
Please...
What?
It's 7-4-6-3.
Can you remember?
Everything's all right.
It's all right. It's okay.
Go, go...
Okay.
Can you keep your
pressure on it? Okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Did we do it?
I think so.
Will I die?
No, you can live
a long time like this.
I need a doctor.
(GRUNTING)
Can you take
the bullet out?
It's a lot different
than taking a piece of
scrap out of your leg.
Oh!
Here.
This is gonna take
the pain away for a while.
Wait.
I'm gonna wake up, right?
I've seen four guys
get shot in the gut.
Every one of them lived.
Not the bullet. You.
You wouldn't...
What?
You wouldn't do
that to me, would you?
No.
(DIALING)
MAN:  Somerset Textiles.
Blackleg Miner.
Under duress.
Please hold.
Blackleg Miner,
what's going on?
Terminal was compromised.
What's your status?
Terminal secure.
I knew you
wouldn't let me down.
Numbers secure?
Of course.
That's all that matters.
Yeah.
GREY:  And the girl?
All assets retired.
She's dead?
Yes.
All right, then.
(GRUNTS)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(GUNSHOTS)
Get out! Get out of the car!
Hey, don't shoot,
don't shoot.
I got money.
I don't want
your fucking money.
Help me get her
in the car.
We gotta get
into town.
We need to get
to a hospital.
What happened to her?
She's shot?
Shot? Out here?
Help me! Help me
get her in.
Okay, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
What happened?
Is she dead?
She will be if you
don't hurry the fuck up.
I understand that.
I'm not a fool.
You understand that,
you're not a fool.
Who are you working for?
(BREATHING LOUDLY)
I used to work for
the same righteous pricks
who twisted your life.
Now I work for the other side.
Just as twisted but
they pay a lot more.
They break us, you know.
Turn us into
these awful things.
Broken pieces.
They push us.
Make us into
men we're not.
And then complain
when we no longer function.
They think we should
live like this is normal.
Like this is how
we should behave,
how we should think.
And our reward
for this life?
We try to run away
and they kill us because
of what they
forced inside our heads.
You think men like
that deserve to live?
They deserve
everything they
got coming.
Maybe.
Did you stop
the broadcasts?
Yeah.
Why?
Some fleeting
virtue in not being
a mass murderer.
I take it you're
not a religious man?
You don't believe
in a guiding light?
No.
You're like me, then.
Floundering in wet shit.
Yeah.
How long do you think
we can go on like this?
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
(ENGINE STARTING)
(EKG BEEPING)
(SNEEZES)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Still at this,
are we?
So, you told me
she was dead.
Look, tell me.
Burnt down,
a man's worth $4.40.
Excuse me?
That's what you said.
When?
In the car.
When all's said
and done, you know,
carbon and minerals.
A human being's worth
less than five bucks.
I said that?
Uh-huh.
Well, you know me,
I talk a lot of shit.
But if you say I
said it, then I suppose
I should believe you.
What about it?
Hmm...
We walk.
Both of us.
Well, you might
walk but her...
That's impossible.
She knows too much.
She's got the codes.
She's got the cypher.
She's compromised.
It's gotta stop.
I'll get you
a prescription for Ativan.
That will stop your
conscience bothering you.
Yeah. Well, take
a look at that.
It's a copy of
the broadcasts.
The ones she stopped.
Number 14 might be
of interest. It's you.
She took a bullet for you.
Gotta be worth
more than five bucks.
What do you want?
Give me a week.
Ten days.
And I'll find your
bodies at the station?
You'll find enough.
(LAUGHS)
(TAPPING IMPATIENTLY)
Start the count.
We were never here.
(EKG BEEPING)
(BREATHES LOUDLY)