[ ominous music ]
[ wind blowing ]
[ wind whistling ]
[ tears packaging ]
]
[ breathing nervously
MIKE: Emma?
[ object clatters ]
.
Hold on.
One second
Can I come in?
Hold on one sec.
One minute.
Everything cool?
.
Yeah, fine
Well, we're all packed,
so we're ready
to leave when you are.
Okay, I'll be read
y in a second.
As much
as I like this look,
you might want to put
on something warmer.
I'll be
out in a minute.
Cool.
[ music ]
?
You doing okay
Yeah.
[ music playing
on radio ]
You're gonna love
it, I promise.
Yeah.
I still don't
get what's so fun
about freezing your as
s off in the snow.
[ laughs ]
Oh, I got you
something.
It's called
a vacation I.O.U.
I know this isn't exactly
what you had in mind,
so for our next big trip,
I'm promising you
a tropical paradise.
So when
we go back home,
I'm, uh, thinking abou
t going over to Henry's.
.
I'm gonna ask him
if I could bartend
a few nights again
Yeah, sure, up to you.
Thank you for coming
out here with me.
I love you.
ou.
Love y
Okay, we're head
ed nine or ten mile
s that way.
We're just gonna
take the truck
right through there?
No, we're gonna
leave it here.
Just need to get
the snowmobile
to the snow
n.
and hitch the tent o
You know how to do that?
Yeah, the guys
at the rental sh
op showed me.
It's easy.
Sure you don't
just want to set up
shop right here?
No way.
We just head nine,
ten miles that way,
we can see
the whole valley
from there.
Be awesome. Come on.
[ music ]
[ engine stops ]
?
Is this it
No, we still have
to go a ways that way.
Just gonna mark our path
with these guys
so we can find
our way back to the truck.
?
Do you have plans
on getting us lost
[ laughs ] Stop it.
Just marking our path
like Hansel and Gretel
and the breadcrumbs.
Please tell me
we're not taking
.
survival notes
from a children's book
[ flies buzzing ]
Oh!
Shit!
What the hell is this?
MIKE:
It's fine. It's probably
just a hunting area.
Oh, my God,
this is seriously sick.
It's not sick.
You've just never
been hunting before.
It's what people do.
Okay. Well, can we get
the hell out of here?
Yeah.
Eww.
[ wind whistling ]
[ sighs ]
I thought you said
you've done this before.
Everyone's built
a tent before.
I've never built
Well, why
don't you help me?
Can you grab that?
Think
I'm just gonna get
the instruction manual,
okay, city boy?
.
City boy?
Yeah, city boy
I'll have you know
I can be quite handy.
y.
Hand
Can you move it back?
e--
What are w
[ laughs ]
Watch where you're going.
I have never seen
you do anything handy
in my entire life,
except maybe
put something
in the microwave.
But you're gonna
build this tent.
Yeah, I am.
Okay, Davy Crockett.
Where's the thermos?
In the black bag there.
I'm gonna put th
is down now.
Okay, do it, 'cause
you're not really helping.
?
We're not near
those dead animals, are we
No, a couple
of miles back.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
Just don't go
near the tent.
Anywhere else you like.
Oh, wait.
In case you need
to go number two.
n.
MIKE:
All right, come on i
EMMA: Okay.
Watch your head.
Welcome home.
k?
What do you thin
Is this gonna collapse?
No, of course
it's not gonna collapse.
Well, we got the kitchen
right there behind you,
e,
living room out ther
and, uh, two bedrooms.
You're here,
and I'm there.
This gonna be warm enough?
ne.
Oh, yeah.
These things are
like top of the li
And now
I'll make a fire.
Cool. Well, it's gonna
get dark soon.
...
Do you want to check o
ut some scenery before we
Yeah, let's go.
It's your thing.
You call the shots.
All right, let's go.
Me first.
ol.
Co
It's tent-living.
t.
You have
to get used to i
Oh, boy.
[ snowmobile buzzing ]
Come on, can't beat
this view, right?
Wow.
It's so quiet.
g.
MIKE: Amazin
It is amazing.
[ music ]
[ loud crash ]
[ Emma breathing slowly ]
[ muffled ] Em!
Em! You okay?
[ panting ]
[ sound grows clearer ]
Em! Em, are you okay?
ay?
You ok
I think I hit my head.
ck.
Let me che
.
Let me see
d.
I don't see any bloo
You're not bleeding.
it.
Sh
I'm okay.
?
You don't hurt
s?
Nothing hurt
I'm okay.
I think I'm okay.
Just--I just
need one moment.
I just--
Let me catch my breath.
.
Stay there, stay there
Take your time.
Emma, I'm--
I'm so sorry.
I don't even k
now what we hit.
I didn't
see anything.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
up.
Okay,
let's get you
Ready? Here.
ay?
You ok
it.
Sh
Aw, sh
What are we gonna do?
Just let me see.
[ pulling starter cord ]
it!
Sh
What are we gonna do?
?
Just give me
a second, okay
Okay.
op
It's okay. The g
uy at the rental sh
.
gave me a tool kit
,
Let's just get y
ou back to the tent
and I'll come back
here and see if I
can fix it, okay?
I mean,
the tent's just over
that ridge there.
It's not far.
I want to go.
re,
Come on,
it's right over he
just over the ridge.
?
You got me
Be careful
, it's deep.
Oh!
You okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
.
Just give me a sec
Okay.
.
Thanks
You okay?
Yes.
It's just over there.
Ohh!
What? What's wrong?
I think
I just saw somebody.
Where?
Over there, near
that bunch of trees.
I don't see anything.
That's wei
rd. I just...
--
Maybe I--I..
. Maybe I just
Em, you hit your head
pretty hard.
ah.
Ye
We're almost there.
d.
MIKE:
Just a secon
You okay?
How do you feel?
Dizzy?
ay.
No, I think I'm ok
I think I'm okay.
Okay, just don't lay down.
You might
have a concussion.
.
Mike, I'm fine.
I just need to sit
Okay, okay.
do?
What are we gonna
Okay, um, I'll go back
to the snowmobile.
Worst case scenario,
we walk back to the truck.
It would be a pain
in the ass,
but we could do it, right?
I don't know!
!
I don't even know
where we are, Mike
I know, I know.
We'll be fine, okay?
We didn't tell anybo
dy where we were going.
That's not true.
I told my parents.
You know my mom.
As soon as she doesn't
get me to pick up
a few phone calls,
she'll freak out.
Then what?
Call the town,
us,
say she can't
get a hold of
then what?
I don't know.
it.
Oh, sh
Look, just stay here.
Just stay upright
in case you have a concussion.
Don't sleep
or anything.
I'll go check
on the snowmobile
and see if I can get
some reception
on my cell phone, okay?
.
Okay, fine
Okay.
[ sighs ]
[ ominous music ]
[ fire crackling ]
Still no signal.
?
You hungry
Well,
there's a bright s
ide to all of this.
.
We're here, we're warm
May not be
how it's supposed to go,
but at least
we're safe...
and...
and we've got
the coldest bo
oze known to man.
ry.
Emma, I said I was sor
I don't know what el
se you want me to say.
I mean, I take
full responsibilit
y for this, okay?
I'm sorry.
Emma?
I'm pregnant.
at?
Wh
I'm pregnant.
I took two tests yesterday,
and I took two tests
this morning.
I don't know
what to say.
You don't have
to say anything.
I'm not keeping it, so...
an?
What's that
supposed to me
It means
exactly what it means.
I'm not having the baby.
I'm not--I'm not gonna
keep the baby, so...
we don't really have
to talk about it anymore.
.
Yeah, um..
fine.
.
It's your decision
Good night, Mike.
[ Mike snoring ]
[ footsteps outside ]
[ clink ]
[ footsteps ]
Mike?
[ branches cracking ]
Oh!
ck?
Any lu
No.
.
I think we should just
walk back to the truck
Can you just let me see
what I can do here?
[ wrench clanging ]
,
This is the first time
you've ever ridden one
so what makes you thin
k you could fix one?
Well, thank you
for that vote of confidence.
Shouldn't you be keeping
yourself warm or something?
[ scoffs ]
I'll be at the tent.
[ shivering ]
Hey!
Um, we need help!
Uh, our snowmobile
wrecked.
My boyfriend,
he's right over there.
He's trying to fix it
right now,
but I feel like
if we could just have...
Mike! Mike!
Mike, I saw him!
What?
?
The guy--The guy that
I thought I saw before
He was right over there.
And I yelled and I sai
d that we needed help,
.
and he just walked off
Seriously?
He was looki
ng right at me.
Of course,
it's snowing again.
ay.
Ok
So which direction
did he go?
I didn't see,
'cause I turned arou
nd and he was gone.
You're sure
he was here?
Yes!
I don't see
any footprints.
I swear I saw him.
He was right over ther
e by those trees.
Is your head
feeling okay?
Are you serious?
What? I'm just
asking a question.
.
No, you think I'm
hallucinating or something
.
I saw a man over there
Okay,
I believe you, okay?
Look, I'm gonna go back
to the snowmobile.
Just let me know
if you see him again.
He might have
a vehicle
or a place where
we can call for help.
Do you think
it's the guy
s?
that killed
those animal
No, that's too far away.
He'd have no reason
to be out here.
Besides, we'd hear
a snowmobile or something.
I don't want to be
out here any longer.
k?
Could we just wa
lk back to the truc
Just let me go
see what I can do
with the snowmobile.
Mike, you don't
know anything
about snowmobiles.
,
This is the first time
you've ever driven one
without much luc
k, by the way.
Can you just adm
it you have no idea
how to fix it,
re?
and we can just ge
t the hell out of he
ke.
I'm not asking, Mi
Let's get the hell
out of here
and walk back
to the truck.
Fine, done.
We'll go
back to the truck.
[ music ]
.
There should b
e another marker
Where is it?
.
I don't know.
That's what I'm saying
.
We should have com
e across another one
So we're lost.
.
No, we're not lost
We've been following
the markers.
We just should hav
e found another one.
Let's just keep going
this way then.
.
I don't know
if this is the way
All right,
well, what about
the tracks
from yesterday?
em.
I don't see th
Okay, well, that should
have been a good indication
that we're going
the wrong way.
We're not going
the wrong way!
e.
The markers were her
Okay, well,
what about the map?
Where are we
on the map?
Well, we should be here,
but if we were here,
we would see the marker.
Well, let's just keep
going that way.
ay,
If this is the wrong w
we could end up
seriously lost.
So what
are you saying?
on,
I'm saying
it's gonna get dark so
s
and we should probab
ly follow our footprint
back to the tent.
Back to the tent?
The markers.
..
Mike, are you serious?
[ sighs ]
Okay, well, what about
a campsite or a ranger station?
There must be something
like that around here.
I mean, this is
a camping area, right?
.
No
What do you mean, no?
?
Not here, okay
What does that mean,
not here?
[ sighs ]
e
We're not gonna
run into anyone up her
s.
because this isn't
where the campsite i
Oh, my God.
Are you serious, Mike?
When I talked
to Cowboy Jeff,
he said that this
was the place to come.
Who the hell
is Cowboy Jeff?
re.
He's the guy
at the general sto
s,
I told him
what our plan wa
me.
and--and he sa
id that the camps
ite was kind of la
Lame?
us.
Just not
very adventuro
We're camping
in the snow
in the middle
of the winter.
Is there really a need
to be more adventurous?
I just mean
that a campground
.
is for kids
and families and stuff
So I asked what would be
more exciting.
And he said out
in the middle of nowhere.
No, he said a local secr
et that's tourist-free.
Wearethe tourists!
You got to be
kidding me.
We're stuck out here.
No. We'll just
go back to the ten
t and figure it out.
Mike...
d.
Just give me a secon
Mike!
ey!
Hey! H
!
We crashed
our snowmobile
p!
We need some hel
Can you help us?
Why is he just looking
at us like that?
Hey, do you have
a snowmobile nearby?
Stay here.
Did you find him?
.
No
What if he took
the ribbons off the trees?
What if he's messing with us?
t?
Who would do tha
I don't
like this, Mike.
Let's just head back
to the tent, okay?
[ fire crackling outside ]
ce,
Still no servi
.
all over this hi
ll and the next one
This was suppo
sed to be special.
s.
I wanted us to have all
of this just to ourselve
s
I didn't want a bu
nch of screaming babie
ten feet away
from our tent.
I didn't want to sha
re a pissing tree
with a weird
hippie couple
.
we'd have to listen to
having sex every night
This was supposed to b
e just you and me.
It was suppose
d to be special.
ne
I mean,
you're the o
who broke some
pretty big new
s last night.
s ]
[ sigh
g
Look, this is somethin
we're gonna tell
our grandkids
about one day.
Remember when gran
dma and grandpa
e
busted their snowmobil
and had to hike
the whole way
back to town?
Why are you always
so fucking optimistic?
.
I didn't know that was
such a bad quality to have
I'm sorry.
And stop apologizing!
Maybe for once,
tell me I'm wrong!
Tell me
I'm a bitch!
You always play this martyr
with these big plans
that never quite work out,
and then you'll blame it
on something like,
"Oh, everything happens
for a reason," or something.
Like this!
What made you think
you could just drive
into the middle of nowhere,
pitch a tent,
and it would just
all magically work out?
This just isn't
how I thought it would be.
.
Emma, this isn't
how I planned this
Not just this.
Everything.
Us.
It just doesn't feel
like I thought it would feel.
ng,
Emma, if this is
about the baby thi
we can figure it out
together.
[ crash ]
What is that?
Is it that guy?
ng.
I don't see anythi
Let's just go to bed
ay?
and figure this ou
t in the morning, ok
ed,
We're both tir
ys.
and it's been
a weird two da
[ branch snaps ]
Mike, Mike.
Mike, wake up.
There's somebody out there.
[ footsteps ]
Is it that guy?
mn!
Da
He's totally
screwing with us.
What are you doing?
.
I'm gonna go see
what his problem..
.
See, he's gone
k.
I'll go chec
Mike,
what are you bringing?
Just taking a knife.
Why are you
taking a knife?
.
Just stay here.
I'll be right back
Hey! Hey,
what's your problem?
[ distant pop ]
[ noise outside ]
Mike? Mike?
Mike?
Mike!
[ panting ]
[ gasps ]
[ crying ]
[ music ]
Okay.
Come on.
[ straining ]
Come--come--
[ mutters ]
[ crying ]
[ thump outside ]
[ footsteps ]
[ heavy panting ]
Hello?
[ panting continues ]
Stay away from me!
I have a gun!
I'll shoot you
if you come near me!
[ wind whistling ]
[ sighs ]
[ music ]
Shit!
[ distant howling ]
[ howling ]
WOMAN'S VOICE: [ whispering ]
It's not enough. No fun.
[ distant howling ]
Shit.
[ tearing ]
[ nearby rustling ]
[ wings flapping,
crow cawing ]
[ distant
mechanized thrumming ]
[ whispers ] What?
[ helicopter approaching ]
Hello!
I'm here!
Help!
[ fire crackling ]
EMMA: I don't know
if you can hear me, but...
I'm sorry.
I didn't think
this would happen.
I don't--I don't think
I'm ready for this.
We can't stay here
very much longer.
You know, we don't have
a lot of food,
and I don't even know
where to start looking.
I wasn't planning
on any of this.
I'm not really
the best person
to be stuck with
in this situation,
so I'm sorry about that.
We got to find
the truck tomorrow.
[ owl hoots ]
If you were a boy,
I would name you Eric.
You know, like Prince Eric.
I always really liked
that name.
And if you were a girl,
I would name you...
Sophie.
Definitely.
You're definitely Sophie.
I like that.
Oh, my God,
Look at me.
I'm a mess.
I'm such a mess.
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get us both
out of here.
I'm gonna--I'm gonna keep
the fire going,
and in the morning,
I'll pick a new route...
and we'll go and get help.
Everything's gonna be okay
because I promise.
Promise.
[ gasps ]
[ exhaled breath echoing ]
[ creature growling ]
[ growling ]
EMMA: Hello?
Wait!
Wait a second.
Hey, wait.
Are you okay?
[ growling ]
[ low panting ]
[ growl ]
[ fire crackling ]
[ howling, loud crash ]
[ screaming ]
[ Emma's breathing ]
[ baby crying ]
[ baby continues crying ]
]
[ thumping noises
g ]
[ noises continuin
[ wheels squeaking ]
[ music box playing ]
]
[ growling breath
[ click, music stops ]
[ chair creaks ]
s ]
[ gasp
Oh!
[ panting ]
[ gasps ]
[ music ]
Oh!
[ flies buzzing ]
[ whimpering ]
[ muffled crying ]
[ stamping foot ]
[ wind whistling ]
[ flies buzzing ]
[ gasping ]
[ groans ]
Hello? Hey!
Excuse me!
I need help.
If you can please help me?
I'm stuck here in the woods,
and there's a man
coming...after me.
Hello? Excuse me!
I need help!
Excuse me, please!
I need help.
Excuse me, miss. I...
Aah!
[ pounding on door ]
[ thump ]
[ thud, man laughing ]
[ laughter ]
[ Emma whimpering ]
[ knocking ]
Aah!
]
[ pounding
grows louder
Leave me alone!
[ light bulb buzzes ]
e ]
[ man screams
in the distanc
]
[ buzzing
[ buzzing ]
[ wind whistling ]
[ crow cawing ]
[ music ]
Help me!
Please, somebody!
Can somebody
please help me?
My boyfriend is...
[ crying ] My boyfriend
is dead,
and there's a man,
and he's coming,
and he's gonna kill me.
[ patrons conversing ]
Sir? Sir,
can you please help?
Why--Why--
Why is nobody
listening to me?
Please!
Can you please help me?
I need some help.
I've been lost in the...
woods for so long.
[ crying ]
Please, why are you
doing this?
Please, can somebody
please help me?
.
They can't see you
er.
They can't
hear you, eith
I don't--
I don't understand.
,
When I explained
everything to Mike
.
he came
with me right away
,
He wanted to tell
you what was happening
but it doesn't
quite work that way.
I don't...
me.
I'm not offended
that you ran from
Every person
on the planet
.
spends every waking
moment running from me
ou.
But I am glad
that I found y
When you crashed
on the snowmobile...
p.
you never woke u
I'm here to take you
to the next place.
This...
This isn't real.
Actually,
it's quite real.
In fact,
most people here,
they'd say
you aren't real.
u.
That's why they
can't see or hear yo
re
You're stuck
between where they a
.
and where you're going
No, I'm not dead.
I would have been
bleeding.
I would have been hurt.
You both died on impact.
No, I would have
seen blood.
I would have seen something.
You did see blood.
wn.
Just wasn't your o
Sometimes when the truth
is hard to accept,
we only see
what we want to see.
It makes it hard
to move on.
No! I'm not dead!
I heard people
looking for me.
I heard them.
.
Yeah, they were
looking for you,
and they found you
.
They found the truck..
found the bodies..
...
found the tent
..
found your
personal belongings.
and kept them to g
ive to your families.
Emma, it's okay.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
.
But I am glad
that I finally
caught up with you
There's something
else out there
looking for you,
something very bad.
You've seen it.
[ growling ]
[ screams ]
I don't force people
to come with me.
.
They have to go
on their own free will
Folks that
don't come with me,
they're lost...
forever.
.
Well..
s ]
[ sigh
There's no need
to stay here any longer.
Come on,
I'll explain everything.
..
Sophie's
waiting for you.
your daughter.
You named her Soph
ie, didn't you?
[ laughs ]
How?
She was
only three weeks old.
.
Well,
she was with you..
is.
and she still
.
She always will be
Come with me,
and I'll tell
you all about it.
e.
I can't take you
unless you let m
[ music ]