Musa!
I've told you before,
you can honor your mother
by doing your chores,
not sitting by her grave.
Musa!
Come and help me with your father.
Yes, Grandmother
Khalazome, you are so funny.
Musa! Come now!
At least I have you girl.
Is the Sangoma here to heal father?
If she can.
Musa go and see if your father is thirsty,
maybe he will eat.
The witchcraft plaguing
Ayize is getting worse.
I have told you, the family is cursed.
Majola's wife,
then Bheki and his wife,
Ayize's wife and their baby, all have died.
Now Ayize suffers.
But Ayize respected his ancestors
and followed tradition.
He took his brother's wife
when Bheki passed on.
It is a curse.
I beg you, give me strong muthi for Ayize
and bring an end to this evil.
Praise to the ancestors.
Under the blanket.
I made it for you, my son.
I saved it for when we are happy,
for a time when we celebrate our ancestors,
but I want you to have it now.
Guide us ancestors.
Praise to the spirits.
Ayize has neglected an ancestor,
a female ancestor, his grandmother.
She demands a sacrifice.
Quickly, while there is still time.
Musa my son, you are now a man.
What can I do, father?
You must be strong now...
in the way of a man, Musa.
I will do that, Father.
Majola... if only he were here,
he would help you.
Musa, go find your cousin,
she's late coming home from school.
Yes, grandmother.
Get away, your family is bewitched!
No, that's not true!
You're cursed. Everyone knows it!
No, that's not true.
The elders must drive you out!
You're bringing a bad plague!
Go away!
Get away!
What do you want?
I came to look for my cousin, Thandi.
At the school you will speak English.
She had to stay after school.
Musa, why were you not in school today?
My grandmother needs help with my father,
he is very sick.
Why so many people
in the village getting sick?
Is it really a curse?
A disease, a curse, who knows?
It is the same in other villages.
We should not talk about it,
it only makes it worst.
Thandi, you did much better today,
your grade will improve.
Thandi, what happened?
Why did you have to stay after school?
Is something wrong?
I want my father.
You know is working.
I don't care! I want my father.
He'll come home one day.
Come on, grandmother is waiting.
The boy will be back soon.
If the sacrifice is necessary,
we must do it now.
There is no choice.
It may already be too late
to appease Ayize's ancestors.
Then do it now.
Why are you killing
your children with illness?
When they are all dead,
who will look after you?
Here... Take what we are giving,
and in return give us luck... and life!
Khalazome!
I see you, boy. What is it now?
Grandmother,
father said that I am to act as a man now,
And so you should.
I've been thinking of going to the city
to find work.
To earn money so we can buy another cow.
The city is very far,
too far for a boy to go.
I could find Uncle Majola.
Father said he would help us.
Do you know where it is?
He went to Johannesburg.
He went in the big truck.
I'll go to Jo'burg then.
I will find Uncle Majola.
Grandmother may I have
your permission and blessings?
Yes you have my blessings.
Find your uncle.
Get us money for a cow.
If you keep this
on until it falls off by itself,
something good will happen.
Musa, please find my father.
I will Thandi. I promise.
With this may my journey bring success.
Hello baby!
Ah look at this, what have we got here?
Little kid
Boohoo little kid.
Hey baby where do you come from?
No man, they scored three goals
in the last five minutes.
Another beer?
No man, I'm going to drive.
I'm hitting the road, I cannot drink.
You must be safe these days heeein!
Mister, could you please
take me to Johannesburg?
I won't be any trouble.
What are you up to?
Don't bother my customers!
Did you hear me?
I said get out of here! Ham ba!
Hey watch it!
Why not?
Darling, you're just going to love it...
Thank you baby!
You!
What do you think you're doing in my truck?
You could get killed there man.
Come on get off my truck.
Mfan ngithe phumala. Manje. Come on
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Hey! What now!
My drum, I left it in your truck.
Here!
Get in.
Have you ever been
outside your village boy?
I bet you've never been
inside a truck before.
What's your name? What's your name?
Musa.
Me namo Nobe, Nobe Lebese.
Why in the world do you want
to be in Johannesburg?
Hey I'm talking to you!
To find my uncle,
and to earn some money
to buy gogo a new cow.
To buy your grandmother a cow, hahahaha...
Where is your uncle?
Gogo said he works in the city.
What's his name?
Uncle Majola. Majola Mkhize
from our umuzy, in KwaZulu-Natal.
Musa, I want you to listen to me,
you're going to see many things
in the city
things that could catch your attention,
things that could get you killed,
things that could bewitch you.
Things that you should stay away from.
You hear me?
Yeah well, I just wanted you to be careful.
Go Ahead!
Jo'burg?
Yeah.
Big, hey?
Mr. Botha?
I need to speak with you about Suzanne.
- Yeah?
- In accounting,
Yeah?
Her car was hijacked
in the back parking lot, last night.
Don't tell me! Not again!
And one of our guards, the Major,
he was shot, he's critical.
These street gangs are out of control man.
I'd like to send them all straight to hell.
Botha!
Matlin look I'm trying to run
a transport business here man!
I need these trailers back on the road
by Monday, hein!
Okay great.
Sorry I'm late.
Here are your contracts.
Stefan I need you here man.
Dad, we've been over this so many times.
I know, I know, but it is important
to have you here in the business,
we had another hijacking yesterday.
Yeah one of the security guard was shot,
these street kids are out of control man.
There is nowhere safe anymore
It's not the street kids.
They may do the petty crimes
but don't hijack cars.
Look! I didn't pay for your legal studies
so you can waste your time
on all these sob stories man.
I got a whole load of work
for you to do here, you know,
I mean, I got all these claim forms
that I need you to handle.
I can't dad,
I've got a filling deadline
on a zoning case.
I can't understand why you get yourself so
involved with this charity case non-sense.
This is your business too, you know.
Look at you man!
You look tired.
Looks like we have another
slow puncture over here?
Hey?
I don't think he is going to be
with us much longer!
Dad, I have to go.
Nobe!
Yes, sir.
I see you brought your son with you today.
No. He is not actually my son sir;
he is a boy from the village sir,
looking for work.
Get him out of here now!
- Maybe you could...
- Now! Run man, run...
Street kids, they are all criminals,
I don't want any around here.
Hi baby, how are you?
Do you know Majola Mkhize?
Have you seen Majola Mkhize?
- Do you know Majola Mkhize?
- Narrr,
mfana you need big magic boy,
I have, have the best herbs and potions,
cure anything.
You cure nothing; you just kill cows!
Papa, papa, papa.
Girls, yeyeya, How do you do?
Ahaha my little one.
So Emily, have you been helping
your mother to look after your sisters.
Of course I have,
but they don't want to listen to me.
Heyeyey girls, you must listen to your
big sister and your mother right!
- Yes father.
- Right.
I thought you were not due 'til tomorrow.
Are you not happy to see me? Come on...
Hey, what do we have here?
Yaya lana, this is our spot.
Get going if you know
what's good for you.
Where you from?
You aren't from Jozi.
I said where you from?
Ukhalamba Valley, KwaZulu.
A real life Zulu,
so you think you're tough.
You're going to fight all of us hein?
He doesn't have anything.
You can sleep here;
will find you when we need you.
But... you owe us! Uyaskolota mpinshi!
I'm the local Sangoma,
what are you telling these women?
The truth about the sickness.
Our people are suffering because
they don't follow our traditional ways.
Mmmmm, some of them say
that if a man with AIDS
has sex with a virgin
he will be cured.
That's not true.
That's why so many
young girls are being raped.
We have to stop the lies and the rumors.
Tell the people the truth.
Many Sangomas are helping us
educate the people.
I'm a sorry lady, I have to go.
Better keep a close
watch on your daughters.
What was all that about?
A health worker,
more talk about the sickness.
These people,
I'm tired of hearing about it man.
Tell me about your new route.
Why do you care?
I care, tell me.
Well, I picked up
a little Zulu boy yesterday.
A Zulu boy?
Yeah. He hid in the back of my truck,
said he was coming to Johannesburg
to look for work, and to buy a cow.
A cow?
You know there are a thousand like him
on the streets.
It would be nice to have a son,
you know.
Nobe, I think we have tried enough.
Our children are our treasures.
Yes they are,
and it takes one to feed them,
you know that better than anyone!
What?
Nobe, you're on the road a lot.
Please don't bring this disease
into our family.
Well I'm not using any of those.
And I'm not explaining myself to you
or to any government worker.
All this talk about condoms,
it is not natural,
maybe these condoms are the ones
that brings the sickness.
You know that's not true.
You see, once I take my trousers off,
why do I have to put them on again?
Besides, you can tell when one is it.
No you can't.
Your sister looked fine a few months ago.
Now look at her.
Nobe promise me you aren't messing around,
promise me!
That's enough;
I'm not talking about it anymore.
Nobe. Please don't bring this dis...
That's enough!
Why do you care after all these years?
Hey stop pushing, stop pushing...
Careful, careful now!
Hey that little one here.
Would you like some bred?
Thank you.
I haven't seen you before.
I'm Francis, what's your name?
Musa.
I'm looking for my uncle, Majola Mkhize.
Do you know him?
Sorry I don't.
Yhea what's your name?
Are you scared of me, what's your name?
Musa. What's your name?
Me I'm Letti. But my friends call me "T".
And then this popo what's up with that?
My father gave it to me, before he left us.
Oh so why did you come to Jozi then?
To find ajob, and to find my uncle.
You know what, watch this I'm going to
show you something, quick!
This is the muthi market.
The place where herbs and other ingredients
are sold for traditional medicine,
for magic and for potions...
Musa? Do you want to learn
how to make some money?
Enough for a cow?
No! But enough to eat. Watch this out!
It's okay to take pictures,
but please stay close to the vehicle.
Don't try to wonder off on your...
- She's got my purse; she's got my purse.
- Hey come back here.
You stupid girl!
I'll bite you for AIDS! I'll bite you!
Augh! Get away!
You've got to be fast,
before they have time to check you out.
Here take this.
No, you stole it!
Ah Musa don't be stupid man,
you have to steal to survive,
the sooner you learn that the better.
One Rand rinse and wipe!
Thank you my brother.
Thanks, thanks...
Hey! Move man this is my spot.
Yes!
Thanks, good job!
See, you don't have to steal.
You're not going to get much
to eat with that.
I will eat.
And I'm looking for my uncle,
through every window.
Musa do you really think
you're going to find your uncle in this
humengus city and even if you do?
Are you going to know him?
Hey of course, he is my uncle.
Ahhhh, leave me alone man.
Well it's official,
approval from the council.
At last, thank god,
thank you Stefan.
Hey, I just got the permit;
you've got the tough job,
helping these kids.
I'd just wish you
would reconsider and stay.
You can use this office
for as long as you like.
Thanks, but you're going to have kids
coming out of your ears,
you're going to need
all the space you can get.
We're going to miss you being underfoot.
Is that what you call it?
If you like.
Without you,
I wouldn't have known what to do
or have the strength to do it.
Yes, you would.
I just whish my father would understand.
He used to be first to lend a hand.
What happened?
I don't know exactly.
All he cares about now is its business.
It's his whole life.
He is a lonely bitter old man.
You have a fever, are you okay?
It's just a bit stuffy in here.
I'm sorry to interrupt Francis,
but there is a lot of people
waiting to see Stefan.
Go ahead,
I've got things to do in the kitchen.
A wash sir?
No!
Okay... A wash for a Rand, a wash sir?
A wash for a Rand. I'm your man.
A wash for a Rand. A wash for a Rand sir?
A wash for a Rand Mam?
I give up, I give up...
Thank you sir.
Uncle Majola? Is that you?
Come here, you know you want it.
Stop it Tyro!
Stop it Tyro! Leave me alone!
Stop it Tyro man leave me alone!
Stop!
Leave her alone!
Musa?
I'm getting tired of you little Zulu.
Get the glue, get the glue. He is shocking.
Take a sit anywhere.
We're safe here, for now.
I hate living under a bridge.
It's better than being dead.
How long have you lived here anyway?
Since my mother died.
My parents and my baby brother all died.
Why did you tell that man you had AIDS?
I just did that's all.
What does it mean?
Musa, don't be stupid,
it's a disease that killing our people.
The doctor told me about it
when my mom was sick.
Do you have it?
No, I just say it
so that men will leave me alone.
I get scared when they look at me
in the streets.
Let me show you something.
See this bracelet?
It's my most special thing.
The white stands for purity
and the red stands for love.
My mother made it for me when,
when she was sick.
She made me promise that
I would stay a virgin,
until I get married.
I'd rather die than let any
of those sick man touch me.
I'll protect you.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Before my mother got sick,
she taught me how to pray.
I'll pray for a new home
for the both of us.
It will have as much food as we can eat,
and it will be safe,
so we won't have to hide.
Hum, that will be good.
And it will have a place to play,
like in the park, with swing.
Yeah Musa,
it will have all these wonderful things.
It'll be a new day.
It will be a brand new day...
Stefan? Stefan? Stefan? Stefan!
Excuse-me, where is the men's ward?
Down there.
Mr. Botha?
I'm Francis Siswana.
Stefan is been helping me at the orphanage.
What's wrong? It must be exhaustion.
Ek's hier Stefan, ek's hier,
What is it? What's wrong?
When I finished U.C.T.,
I found out I was HIV positive.
But, but how?
Does it matter?
Nobody needs to know about this.
You're better than all this,
we, we're better than all this.
I'm tired...
Hello Stefan, I'm doctor Trube,
are you Stefan's father?
Yeah.
Can I have a word?
Has anyone told you
what's wrong with your son?
He says he's HIV positive.
It's progressed further than that.
He has AIDS.
At the moment he's suffering
from a bacterial infection,
and the next 24 hours
are going to be critical.
Letti?
Have you seen Letti?
Have you seen T?
No.
Letti!
Tyro, stop! What are you doing?
Letti is missing, I found her bracelet.
Keep it! She's not going to need it again.
What have you done to her?
I told you, he owes us.
Hey Musa! Is that you?
Nobe!
Would you like to take
a ride up the road with me.
I could use your help.
Come on son, we'll get something to eat.
Did you find your uncle?
No.
Are you hurt? What happened?
I see, you still have your drum.
Are you getting enough to eat?
What's bothering you boy?
My friend, Letti, she is missing.
You never can tell about woman.
How about the money for your cow?
I've been washing car windows.
I had more, but it was stolen.
Hi baby, hi...
Tell me about your family.
They all died except my grandmother
and some of my cousins.
Sorry.
People say our family is cursed,
but I think it was the AIDS.
Have you ever heard of it?
It's all I hear these days.
Okay hold still.
Bull!
Snake!
Lion! No, no, no, no, no, Elephant!
Yeah.
Hey who's there?
They can steal you blind,
you've got to watch every second.
Nobe, thanks for warning me,
and for letting me come with you.
Nobe! I thought I heard your voice.
Hello, Joe.
How have you been?
Okay, so where you headed?
Back to Jo'burg,
if I don't get sidetracked.
Oh! This is Musa
Fresh. Hey,
one of those women wants to barter,
you know, carry a load of crafts to Jozi,
and then she'll give me a good time.
That sounds like a good deal?
I don't know Joe.
Huun?
They say it could kill you.
Arrg, we're all going to die,
what difference does it make?
Besides,
if some bitch gives me that disease,
I'll give it to every woman that I know,
they'll die with me.
That's a fact.
Guys, I've got some business;
see you later.
Musa...
Yeah, Nobe.
Thanks for coming with me.
Mr. Botha, come and look
They're here for Stefan.
He's helped so many, your son.
He told me that's
what you taught him to do.
Wake-up sleepy!
I cut, you choose!
You took the smaller piece.
I'm the smaller man.
Ahh! Good boy!
Good work, it's empty hein!
Let's see,
we've got one more stop.
One more?
Let's go.
Mr. Botha, I'm sorry
but Stefan is not responding in the way
that we'd hoped.
Hey, stop!
What?
I know where we are.
Are you taking me home?
I can't go home,
I haven't found my uncle,
and I don't have a cow.
You can go for a visit,
you don't have to stay.
Okay, I visit.
This is isivane, to show respect.
Okay.
Let's go
Musa I didn't know what happened to you.
Grandmother, this man, a good friend
of mine, has the name Nobe Lebese.
You are welcome in this house.
We will prepare food and drink.
Please sit down.
Ngiyabonga mama, you don't have to go
to the trouble for me.
Water will be fine.
BaNobe gave me a ride to the city
with his truck.
Siyabonga for watching out for him.
Where is your uncle? Did you find Majola?
Not yet Gogo.
But I've been working
and earned money
This is for you, towards a new cow,
like Khalazome
You've done a great thing.
Mama, you've dropped some.
You should get a good cow.
Your grandson has done well.
How is school Thandi.
The teacher had to go to the hospital.
They say he's going to die.
The curse is killing us all.
Grandmother, may I go see the chief Elder?
The chief Elder,
you know you can't see him.
But I want to try, may I go.
Does a man ask permission for such things?
Go!
Do you have sons?
Four daughters.
I thought I would be taken care
of my old age,
but my children are gone.
The burden has fallen on me
to take care of the little ones.
I understand, I'm sorry.
There is no work, no cattle,
no hope for a little boy like Musa.
Your grandson is a good boy.
I think he'll make his way in the world.
I see you.
Yes, I see you, Father.
Who is this who wishes to speak to me?
It is me, Musa, son of Ayize,
whom you see.
May I enter and speak, Father?
Go away boy, you shouldn't be here.
Son of Ayize, why are you such a nuisance?
My Lord, my teacher wouldn't speak
of the thing that is hurting our people.
Now I come to you.
What is it you speak about?
I've been to the city.
I've learned what is making
our people sick.
You are brave to travel to the city.
Braver still to come back.
What is this witchcraft of which you speak?
It's called AIDS.
There are ways to prevent it.
We must tell the people.
The people have heard about this,
but they won't speak of it.
They fear it
It's a disease, my Lord, not magic.
We have followed our tradition
and sacrificed for the ancestors.
What more can we do?
Tell our people the truth, my lord.
Leave me my boy. Leave me.
The boy would make a fine son.
But he is your grandson, mama.
His grandmother past away
before he was born.
Just as it is custom
that you call me mama,
the boy calls me grandmother.
But all these children?
Some his cousins,
some grandchildren of my own.
I can no longer bear the burden
of raising one more child.
Please, take him.
Grandmother, it is time for us to go now.
Nobe and I have to go back
to work in the city.
A man must do his work.
Musa, when we will see you again?
Some day soon,
when I find your father.
Stefan...
hey man, help me!
Stefan, Stefan?
Doctor, doctor!
Just for tonight Okay. Let' go.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, baby,
your sister died in Sebokeng,
and her two little ones showed up here
early this morning.
What? What are you going to do?
Is this the boy?
Why did you bring him?
Look, I didn't ask
for those children to be brought here,
I didn't ask for any of this!
Just do as you please.
Get out of my way!
Nobe? Nobe Lebese? Is that you?
Pastor Gophe! I'm sorry sir,
I didn't see you, very sorry.
Come, come, help me to church.
Sure pastor, sure.
Nobe? Why were you in such a panic?
It's nothing pastor.
No Nobe, it's not nothing, I know you.
It's this disease, there is no escape.
I'd just heard that
my sister has died from it.
I see. I'm sorry.
What can we do? We must stop this.
The People don't want to talk about it.
If they admit they have it they're shunned.
They feel shame.
I haven't even preached
an AIDS funeral yet.
How could that be?
The death certificate lists
only the disease that killed them,
it never tells if AIDS was involved.
Maybe it's easier
for the families that way.
We've spent too long fooling ourselves
because it's easier that way.
People must face this killer
and you've got to tell them.
The people don't want to hear it.
Only God knows what to do.
There is a meeting,
there is a killer in the township.
Hey, come to church,
hurry to church, there is a meeting.
There is a killer in the township
Can I come in?
Of course.
All are welcome into this house.
What's this about a killer?
What's going on?
Please, please settle down.
Nobe!
There is a killer among us.
It is killing our wives,
our neighbors and our children.
It is HIV/AIDS.
Not this again,
we are sick of hearing about this.
What can we do about it? It's hopeless.
You're killing yourselves
and your loved ones out of fear and shame.
I did not see it for what it was.
Now, I do.
Ignoring this disease is a sin.
We are the children of light,
and only the light of truth can save us.
It must starts here and now.
Yes there is wisdom in what he says.
God grant us that wisdom.
They say my daughter has it,
but she looks very healthy.
How could it be?
My sister and her husband have it,
they don't want to talk about it,
we're all scared.
Show them compassion.
Do not shun them.
Help them in any way you can.
Do not judged.
How can we fight it? We have no medicine.
We will fight it with the truth.
Truth? What's my daughter
suppose to do with truth?
The truth can unite us,
and let us draw courage from each other.
Together we can
have the strength to go on.
It was a good thing you did last night.
It was good to speak the truth.
Musa, there are shelters,
places for street kids.
It's not much,
but it's better than the streets.
No, I haven't found uncle Majola.
Musa, you have to get off the streets.
I'm going to take you to the shelter.
Musa! Musa! Musa!
Hey! Hey Musa
Nobe, you're in very early.
Yebo, Laurain.
Did you hear?
Majola Mkhize died.
Who?
The Major, Majola Mkhinze, the guard
that was shot when Sue was hijacked.
Remember?
Good guy.
Hey have you seen Musa
the boy who caries a drum.
Is there anything I can do for you?
No, thanks.
I'm sorry if I'm disturbing you.
No, please come in.
I brought some of Stefan's things
from the house.
Personal items, I thought you'd want.
Thanks
It's not much, some old pictures,
his diploma.
It's very kind of you.
Mr. Botha,
even though
Stefan knew he was dying,
he fought to make something of his life.
I know.
Actually Tumisho, I do need your help.
Of course, what is it?
Thanks you everybody.
I'm very happy that you manage
to get here so quickly. Thank you.
Some of you just heard that
my son Stefan
died unexpectedly.
What you don't know
is that he had AIDS.
That is why, from today,
we are offering free
testing and counseling
for all of you and your families.
We have a nurse here
to take blood samples,
but I want to stress,
it's all voluntary. It's up to you!
And if any of you do tests positive,
you're not going to loose yourjobs,
and will do our very best to help you.
Thank you.
I'll be the first one to be tested.
Anyone will join me?
- Nobe!
- Sir,
Yes sir?
Thanks for what you did there.
No problem sir...
Sir...
Yeah?
It's about the Major, and a little boy.
Check over there man.
Thank you sir.
Hey Musa,
Musa,
we want to talk to you.
This is Mr. Botha.
Hello Musa.
Sorry son, we have news about your uncle.
You found him?
Musa it's bad news.
Your uncle Majola has been shot and killed.
He was a guard at the depot.
He was a brave man Musa, like you.
What am I going to do?
That's why we here.
My uncle did what need to be done.
I will do so too.
You have Musa.
What do you mean?
You've worked hard.
You've worked honestly like a man should.
Yeah I did. I earned money
so grandmother could replace Khalazome.
What does that mean?
She was my old cow.
Her name means
"cry, then her tears will dry up",
like mine, tears are over.
Musa how would you like
to go to a new home?
Safe place to sleep nice place to play.
Go to school? A good school.
Can Thandi come too?
We'll ask grandmother.
The God sent you mister.
No,
I think it's the other way around.
Good afternoon!
Good afternoon.
I remember you.
You the one who brought us bread.
Welcome to our home, Musa.
If I had a son,
I'd want him to be just like you.
Thanks Nobe,
thanks for everything.
T. It's you.
I knew you would find me.
Poor little thing.
She was beaten, left for dead.
She's safe now.
I saved it for you.
Musa, you found my bracelet.
I, I really missed you Musa.
I missed you too.
T. Iook, there is even a swing
just like I prayed.
Yes, Musa, even a swing,
just like you prayed.
Don't cry T.
It's a brand new day...
Come...
AIDS has already orphaned more than
12 million African children.
30 million people
in sub-Saharan Africa
carry the HIV/AIDS virus.