(Rockets roaring)
Man:
Eva, we've got to go now!
Now, now!
- Come on, Eva!
(people screaming)
Come on, hurry!
Come on, run!
Eva, come on!
Come on, Eva.
We don't have time.
- Come on, Eva!
- Get out the door!
- Run!
- Eva!
(Screaming)
- GO, go. Go. 90!
Mommy!
Get back!
Go on, go!
(Shouting)
Woman:
Hold on to me.
(screaming)
(coughing)
(shivering)
(rumbling)
(panting)
(buzzing)
(electricity crackling)
Let there be light.
(clanking)
Yeah.
Not exactly the Garden of Eden.
After a blast,
everything gets vaporized
and sucked up
into the atmosphere.
And it rains back down to earth...
as radioactive dust.
Number one rule:
No one opens that door
till the radiation clears.
You understand me?
You want to survive,
you listen to me.
(Rumbling)
(crashing, metal screeching)
Jesus!
Woman:
Someone get the lights!
- You okay? You okay?
(coughing)
- Someone get the lights!
- Calm down. Calm down.
Don't touch that.
(Crackles) (girl screams)
(coughing)
Holy shit, it's the dust!
It's the dust!
That dust is from the inside.
The bitch is sealed tight.
What was that?
Another bomb?
That was our building
coming down.
How the fuck do you know that?
I don't want to be down here.
I want to go now.
I know, sweetie.
But Uncle Mickey says
we have to stay.
- Why?
- Because your face will melt off
and your hair will fall out.
She's a little girl.
I was just fucking around.
- So that was a nuke?
- Definitely.
Fucking rag-heads.
- We got to stay down here?
- Bet your ass we do.
That door stays sealed
until the radiation clears.
And how long's that gonna take?
When I say.
What's the plan, Mickey?
Well, my plan was to build
a fallout shelter
and take it easy
while my pain-in-the-ass tenants
barbecued above me.
Does anybody's cell phones work?
No, there's no signal.
- I fucking lost mine.
- You lost it?
Is that a radio?
Give it a try.
Cocksucking jack-off.
- Hello?
(static hissing)
Hello? Hello?
Hello, do you copy?
What's down here?
Mickey: As you see, just a bunch
of storage cells full of junk.
Hey, uh...
uh, it's Mickey, right?
Yeah.
Why do you have
so many mattresses?
Because I'm the super
of a goddamn apartment building.
So why do you have
so many mattresses?
What the fuck do you care?
I sell them on the Internet.
(Man coughs)
Turkish bath in here.
Sorry, ladies, no running water
to wash your panties.
Toilet's on the left.
It's septic,
so after you finish,
throw some lime on top of it.
That's fucking disgusting.
It's called saving water.
Sure, whatever.
I've got to take a dump.
What's in here?
That's my room.
Nobody goes in there but me.
Mama, I'm hungry.
Uh, Mickey...
do you have anything to eat?
Mickey:
The food is adequate, I hope.
Don't thank me all at once.
No, the food's good.
Thanks, Mickey.
(ball bouncing)
- Hello?
(static hissing)
Hello? Hello?
Anybody there?
Hello?
(Crashes)
- Shut up back there.
Hello?
We have survivors
in a building
on the northwest corner
of 29th and 5th.
I repeat, the northwest corner
Do you copy?
Woman: Do you really
have to smoke that thing?
I mean, there's already
so much dust in here.
So when can we go up?
When I say so.
Fuck it.
Ade, come on, let's go.
Adrien, come on.
Bobby, let's go. We're out of here.
Let's go. Fuck it.
Mickey:
What do you think you're doing?
Get away from the door.
I won't tell you again.
- I told you!
- Josh!
- Adrien: Look out!
- Get away from the fucking door!
- Get away from the goddamn door!
- Come on!
Go ahead.
Shit!
What the fuck, Mickey?
God damn it.
- Fucking...
(girl screams)
Fucking big man with that ax, huh?
Keep pushing me, Mickey.
Keep fucking pushing me,
you're gonna see what happens.
(Spits)
Ever see what happened
to those poor Japanese bastards...
after we dropped
Little Boy on Nagasaki?
The skin melting off their bones.
Faces like roadkill.
Lucky ones died in the blast.
And those kids in Chernobyl...
eyes and... ears.
Shit growing all over 'em.
Tumors the size of grapefruits
popping out of their necks.
Enough, Mickey.
We get it.
What you need to get
is if that dust gets in here,
we're all fucked.
(Rumbling)
Hope not.
(metal clanking)
(door opens)
(water splashes)
Come here, honey.
Let me braid your hair.
Can I borrow that, please?
Of course.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
You kept it.
Of course I did.
Eva.
I'm sorry if I've been acting
a little bit nuts.
I'm just trying, you know,
to keep it together.
I guess that's what survival is,
just trying to keep it together.
But I love you.
And you love me.
And that's what's going
to pull us through this nightmare.
It'll make us better parents.
(lighter clicking)
Eva.
- Eva.
- What?
Come on, honey.
Just one more bite.
Girl:
I want to go home.
Woman: Do you want me to try
and warm them up for you?
Girl:
We are going to die, aren't we?
Woman: No, honey,
we're not going to die.
We're going to live.
Let's just do our meditation, okay?
Shut your eyes.
Really picture the beautiful light
and how good it makes us feel.
Let's do that right now, okay?
Come on.
- Shut your eyes.
- It doesn't work.
- It does work.
- I want to go home.
Wendy, you just have
to be patient, okay?
And then it'll get better outside.
And then somebody'll come down
and they'll help us.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Thank you.
Gonna have to eat this shit
every day?
What'd you say?
What?
I give you food.
Shelter, and that's what you say?
Fuckers come down here,
expect me to take care of you.
What do you contribute?
What'd you bring to the fucking party?
Take it easy, Mickey.
All my family and friends
are probably dead,
and all you can talk about
are fucking beans?
Come on, Mick!
Are we really supposed
to rely on this guy?
- Sam.
- No, no, no, no, really, really.
How long can you keep us
alive in this... in this...
- Shit hole.
- Yes, exactly.
You know what?
This is a fucking shit hole, man.
Eva:
Calm down. Sam...
No. No, I'm sorry.
I won't stop.
- Stop.
- I won't stop because I want someone
to do something, that's all.
- I need someone to do something.
- Sam, calm down.
- No, I won't calm down because I...
- Sam.
Woman: Sam, please stop.
Stop!
- Do something, man. Come on!
- Sam, please stop.
Instead of just sitting around
waiting to fucking die.
Don't be scared, Wendy.
Uncle Mickey only slaps little girls.
And you're a big girl, aren't you?
Want to see a magic trick?
I'm gonna take my thumb off
for you, all right?
Yeeow!
God, that hurts.
Seen that one before?
Okay, let me think
of another one.
Making your cigar disappear?
(chuckles)
(laughs)
(rumbling) (Wendy screams)
Bobby:
Oh, shit.
Shit.
(metal groaning)
Marilyn:
It's a rescue.
Down here!
- Cut the lights.
- What the hell for?
Just do it.
You guys,
what's going on up there?
Hey, okay,
we're civilians, all right?
Okay, we're all
on the same side, right?
(Grunts)
- Whoa, what are you doing?
Didn't you hear him?
(Wendy screams) Mommy!
Help me!
No!
(screaming)
- No!
- Help me!
Wendy!
No, no!
No! No!
- No!
(gunshot)
- Get back.
(screaming)
Go, go, go! Run!
(Gunshots) (groans)
God!
(Breathing heavily)
(electronic pulsing)
(electronic pulsing quickens)
We've got another
2-8-Baker.
(Rapid electronic pulsing)
(screaming)
(shouting)
(screams)
(electronically distorted chatter)
(roars)
(panting)
(groaning)
Give me the lock!
- What lock?
- Get me the chain!
- I don't need your help.
- Get out of the way.
Come on, come on.
Put the chain on there.
- Bobby: Mickey!
- Josh: Hey, Mickey!
I need some help.
Adrien got shot.
- Put him down over here.
- What? Okay.
- Whoa, whoa.
(groans)
Hey, somebody fucking
get something. He got shot!
(Whimpering)
- Oh, shit.
- I got to look.
(Adrien screams)
Oh, shit, Bobby.
- What the fuck?
- Somebody get a medical kit.
Thank you.
- I got it. I got it.
- I don't know what to do.
- There's nothing here that's usable.
It's all from, like,
1934 or something.
- You gotta take the bullet out, right?
- It's gonna sting, okay?
All right.
(Screams) Oh, fuck!
- Sorry.
- You're gonna be okay, man.
- He's gonna die.
- Eva: He's fine.
- He's gonna fucking die.
Shut up!
He's not gonna fucking die.
What do you want me to do?
It's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be all right, all right?
- Arch your back. Just lean a bit.
- Come on.
- Almost got it.
- Almost? He's gonna be all right?
- So he's gonna be okay?
- He's gonna be okay.
You're lucky it didn't hit
the artery.
- He's gonna be okay.
- Okay, you got to clean that out.
I got it. Thank you.
Come over here.
Okay?
Put your hand on the back there.
Press hard on the front,
keep your hands on the back.
- That's fine. That's good.
- Yeah.
Just like that.
He'll be all right.
Where's Sam?
- Hold this.
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Hold this as hard as you can.
- I'm here. I'm here. I got it.
Sam. Sam.
You okay?
You hurt?
You're alive.
- You're alive.
- Are you okay?
I'm okay.
(grunting)
(panting)
(shivering)
Looks like some sort
of biohazard suit.
Mickey:
It's a radiation suit.
Bet we got hit by one of those loose
nukes I've been reading about.
It's just a matter of time
before one of them hajis
got their hands on one of them.
So you're saying it's the Arabs?
Of course they're Arabs.
They've been at war
with us for 20 years.
It's just that we've been too busy
stuffing ourselves
at the trough to notice.
We should have wiped them
off the map when we had the chance.
Now it's probably too fucking late.
(Moans)
Oh, shit.
Okay, that's disgusting.
Let me guess, North Koreans.
- You're a fucking idiot.
- Get out of here.
Oh, fuck!
(screaming)
Holy shit.
Grab the tape.
I got her.
All right. Okay.
I got her. Ow!
All right, all right.
Take it easy.
Grab her arms.
Put her in the storage room.
Come on.
Get the door.
No!
(wailing)
(radio squealing)
Top rations.
Mickey's orders.
I'm fine. You take it.
You take it.
Can you make anything out?
Only thing I caught was something
about finishing up the sweep.
And they're American accents.
Mickey:
Turn off the fucking radio, man.
That's what got us in trouble
in the first place.
Hey, Mickey,
what is that in your pocket?
Whether it's making
a damn fine sausage
or exterminating
an entire race of people,
those Germans
don't fuck around.
You're holding out food
on us now?
I got a couple of bits and pieces
in my room.
It's my place.
It's my right.
- Just go back to your room.
- Damn it!
Has anyone fed Marilyn?
(laughs)
What the fuck is your problem, man?
Don't waste that.
What's so funny?
What?
Oh, nothing.
Just what you said
and how you said it.
"Has anyone fed Marilyn yet?"
Like she's your fucking dog.
(Barking) (laughing)
He gets it.
Show some respect.
She just lost her kid.
Go back to sleep, Adrien.
Where are you going?
(Mocking) Where are you going?
She's pissed.
You've got something on your face.
Other side.
That's it.
(Sobbing)
She's all that's good in me.
I'm sorry.
(Sobbing)
(wailing)
- Too risky.
- What do you mean it's too risky?
Eva: Whatever's in the air outside,
it's in here.
Your goddamn duct tape
won't make any difference.
At least we can find out
what's going on out there
even if we don't find her kid.
- You're volunteering?
- I'm volunteering.
He's volunteering.
I say if he wants to go, let him go.
- Let me go. Come on.
- I don't trust you coming back.
What is your problem with me?
- He's got a problem with everybody.
- What about Josh?
- No. Fuck, no.
- Me?
- What about Josh?
- You want me to go?
He ain't got the brains
and that faggot ain't got the balls.
- He'll come back for his brother.
- Thanks, Mickey.
I'll go.
Sam: No, no, no, Eva.
Eva, you can't be serious.
- I'll go.
- Don't be stupid.
- Delvin: You happy, Mick?
You a punk. You know that?
You a punk.
When you ain't got no ax in your hand,
then you got something to say.
I don't think he's gonna like
what he finds out there.
At least we have to try.
Glove.
- How's your tube?
- Tube is good.
Excuse me.
Do you have air?
Is it working?
- You got one more to go.
- Is the compressor gonna work?
- Yeah, it's fine.
- There it is.
(Breathes deeply)
- Good to go?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Promise me you'll bring her back.
I'll do my best.
- Delvin: Let's go, guys.
- Let's do it. Let's go.
Let's do it.
What the hell is that?
Hey, Josh.
Don't worry, man.
I... I got this.
(Breathing heavily)
(machines beeping)
Wendy.
Hold it.
Go.
(alarm sounding)
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What did you see?
- You're okay.
- I think I got two of 'em.
- What did you see?
- Where's your gun?
They got this... this lab set up there.
It's like... it's like...
- Sam: Josh, what else?
- Like what?
- What else?
- What do you mean what else?
That's it.
There's no survivors.
There's no other civilians.
There's no fucking Red Cross.
I don't know if they're army.
I don't even know if they're American.
I'm sorry.
(clanking)
They're coming back.
Mickey: No.
They're welding us in.
(Voices shouting)
- How are you holding up?
- Uh, I'll live.
Delvin gave me his pain meds.
Mind if I take a look?
I just want to clean it.
You know it's gonna sting a little.
(Groans)
- Sorry.
You a nurse or something?
No.
You're just gonna have
a nasty scar.
Yeah, well,
chicks dig scars, right?
(sighs)
You lived below us, right?
Yep.
Was that you who played guitar?
Yeah. Did that annoy you?
No.
No, I actually really liked it.
Helped me sleep sometimes.
It keeps most people awake.
Not me.
Is everything all right?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
(coughing)
Marilyn: Ugh, how can you
eat with that smell?
We've got to get rid
of those bodies.
How, exactly?
Chop 'em up,
toss 'em down the septic.
Should have tried harder
to get that door open.
That door is welded shut.
We should have put the bodies out
when Josh went out.
Shame we let
those bodies go rotten.
Sam:
What do you mean?
You ever heard about that rugby team
that survived the Andes?
Their plane crashed.
They were forced to eat
their friends and family.
They survived up there
for months.
They ate everything...
ears, toes, assholes.
Uh-huh, arms, legs,
brains, the spleen.
The only thing they didn't eat
was the penis.
If worse comes to worst, you all have
full permission to eat my body.
Yeah, you do.
But not my penis.
Nobody... nobody but nobody
- eats Bobby's penis.
(giggles)
(ax clanks)
What's that for, Mickey?
Uh-uh.
Delvin?
Well, yeah.
Fuck, yeah.
Yeah, I'll do it.
Come on.
I can do this, man.
I got this.
But can he live with it?
- Hey, Bobby?
- I got this, man.
Yeah, I'll be... fine.
(Exhales)
It's just like cutting lumber.
I'll start with the arms.
I'll just get my swing down.
(Breathing heavily)
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe.
Chop a body from head to toe.
(screams)
(screaming) (ax hacking)
(ax scraping)
(ax clatters)
It's blunt.
(groaning)
(unzips pants)
(urinating)
(door opens)
Man, what you doing in here?
What?
How did you get in here, man?
I heard you.
- When did you come in here?
- Fuck off.
How did you get in here?
What you got in your pocket?
Punk.
I was dreaming about Mom.
You think she's okay?
I don't care.
She's your mom.
She's not mine.
Just 'cause she cut
my sandwiches...
- Hey, Adrien.
- Yeah?
I only went out there to see
if there's a way out for us.
(Sam coughing)
Hey, was Mickey an aviator
or something?
Look at these.
What the hell's going on in here?
Come on, Mickey, we're just looking
for some escapism, all right?
I told you from day one
that this was my room
and you were to stay out.
Your casa is our casa now.
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but you're gonna regret this.
This is my ball.
You got it out of my apartment?
- I got it out of your ass.
- You got it out of my apartment.
Hey, he's got forks.
- Adrien.
- I've been looking for this ball.
Don't need to use
your dirty fingers any... hey!
- This is a very valuable ball.
- You got it fixed.
Hit down here, come this way,
and jab real hard
and start firing like this.
Now if they're behind you
and they have a gun behind you...
- This is amazing.
- ...what you want to do is feel that tip.
Once you feel it,
come to the outside.
The gun will discharge this way.
Take your arm,
take both their hands,
pull with this hand, and go forward
and you'll take the gun away.
All right, soldier, fight safe
and come back
to the United States.
- Oh, another one?
- Mm-hmm.
- Where the hell did you get that one?
- It's the last one.
(Knocks)
- Marilyn: Come in.
Hi.
Here's the makeup.
Thanks.
Makeup.
(Coughs)
Hey, listen, Marilyn.
You know, if you need
to talk about anything,
anything like that, I'm here.
You know?
'Cause...
I'm sure she's better off
than we are right now.
- What are you talking about?
(coughing)
Wendy.
Eva.
You are a very beautiful girl.
(laughs)
And I know you know
what men are like.
- Oh, yeah.
- What do you think's gonna happen
the longer that we stay
down here, huh?
What do you think
is already happening?
- I don't know.
- I do.
Listen, if you need to talk
about anything, I'm here, all right?
Don't you think
you should just be
a little nicer
to the rest of the boys?
Especially Josh.
Fucking hands off me.
(Clatters)
Delvin: All you knew
we had was this much?
That's all there is!
What do you want me to do?
- That's not all there is.
- That's just fucking wonderful, Mickey.
That's impossible. There is no way
we can survive with that.
No way. No way.
Josh: You got us
into this situation, now fix it.
Mickey: I got us into this situation?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
I was rationing them.
We're gonna fucking starve
to death, Mickey.
We're gonna die of thirst, Mickey.
Where's the food?
What do you want me to do?
I'm not your nanny,
you arrogant prick!
I'll bet you're just waiting
for one of us to die
so you can have all the food
that you can fucking eat, huh?
(Grunts)
- Oh, shit. What are you...
What is your problem, Mickey?
What is your problem?
(Shouts) My problem is you!
- You're fucking dead.
- And you, and you!
- You're fucking dead, Mickey.
- You're my fucking problem!
- Get back. Get out of here.
- You get out of here!
- Take a walk.
- You get out of here.
- It's my fucking-
- Take a fucking walk!
Sam: Guys, please.
Delvin, come on.
You see he's the only one
not dropping any pounds?
Always stuffing his pig face.
I'm telling you, that motherfucker
is up to something.
Stop playing around with that.
Okay? I'm trying to talk to you.
What do you want to do, Josh?
I want to get
that fucking door open,
- even if we rip it off its hinges.
- Fucking-A right, man.
Do you agree with everything
my brother says?
You mean
your half-brother, right?
What, you don't agree?
Have you looked at us?
Huh?
Look at me.
We're dying in here.
Where would you rather be?
Door's welded shut.
We got one working suit.
There's not a lot of options.
There's always options.
(Door opens)
I knew you had some stuff
in here somewhere.
You crazy fuck.
It's a peace offering for...
Thank you. Uh-huh.
Back up.
Back up and open it.
All right.
Move over so I can see it.
Start again.
Don't give me an excuse
to use this. Open it.
(clicks)
Got it.
Now push it open.
- Where's it lead to?
- The fucking White House.
- Where are the lights?
- There ain't no fucking lights.
Don't you fuck with me.
Oh, man.
(Shouts)
(gunshot) (gasps)
Help!
It's Delvin and Mickey.
Holy shit!
What the fuck, Mickey?