BILL: I don't understand it.
I just filled up the gas tank
20 miles ago.
WIFE: Well, it's empty now, Bill.
(THROWS KEYS)
Hey.
Just wondering if you could help me out.
My wife...
...my wife and I, we ran out of gas
down the road.
Could you give me a lift back to
the station?
Whoa.
It's really fortunate I ran into you.
(CLOSES DOOR)
Trevor Moorehouse.
(SAW WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(SAW WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
No! No!
(SCREAMING) No!
(PUNK ROCK SONG PLAYING)
WHITNEY: How could he drive
with a chainsaw for a right hand?
It was his left hand.
And I'm telling you it happened.
It's well documented.
Trevor Moorehouse.
The guy's legendary in these parts.
Yeah, I mean, I heard
something about that.
Bullshit.
It's camp-lore.
There's no such person
as Trevor Moorehouse.
I guess that's what we'll tell ourselves
when we're trying to sleep at night.
(TOBE WHIMPERING)
(CHUCKLING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
How you doing back there, Jewels?
I'm fine.
I'm really glad you decided to come.
Contrary to what your father would
have you believe.
I'm not the big bad wolf, Jewels.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Hey.
Let's see.
Dean, Whitney,
Jason, Julie, and Tobe.
Wow! Do you bend spoons, too?
(ALL LAUGHING)
I recognize you from your applications.
I'm Patrick.
How's it going?
How are you doing?
I'll be your boss for the
next six weeks.
Hey, who else is here?
BRAD: Hey, Patrick, what do you
want us to do with these paint cans?
WHITNEY: Uh-oh.
Hey, Brad.
This is Julie, Whitney, Jason...
Yeah.
Yeah, we've met.
Look, I didn't know he was
going to be up here.
Maybe this isn't such a good idea.
Yeah, maybe it isn't.
Somebody wanna fill me in here?
Jason and I used to run track against
each other at school.
Last time we ran for qualifications,
he broke his knee 10 yards from
the finish line.
Yeah, it's funny.
I don't recall us last time you raced.
So I guess most of you know each other.
Hey.
- How you doing?
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Hey.
Look, I'm sorry there's some bad
history here, guys.
But we got a job to do.
Is this gonna be a problem?
No problem here.
No. No problem.
Good.  'Cause we got a lot
of work ahead of us.
Dean and Jason, you guys help me
move this wood.
And you three can get started
on the food.
All right?
Truck's outback.
TOBE: It frightens me to think that
my diet for the next eight weeks
will consist primarily of cream, spinach
and Mrs. Pete's Tater Tots.
Ugh, not me.
I'm sticking with what I know.
Ritz Crackers and peanut butter.
Basic building blocks of a well-rounded
eating disorder.
Wow. No shortage of knives in here.
Look at this.
More than I can say for the rest
of the kitchen.
It's pretty bare, isn't it?
Where do you think these go?
Probably in the pantry.
I think I saw it over there.
Jesus! You can cut diamonds
with the stuff in here.
Tobe, the door!
Well, don't look at me.
I didn't know it locked from
the outside.
There was sign posted on the door.
(SIGHS)
It's summer, all right.
I'm not exactly looking for
a reason to read.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Hey, Whit!
So, Dean, am I a happy camper?
Have I ever let you down?
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Oh, yeah.  (LAUGHS)
Whose is this?
Oh, it's Tobe's.
He brought it to scare the kids.
(LAUGHING)
Get that out of here.
(BANGING CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
Are you mad?
No, I'm not mad.
Well, you know if it comes down to it,
I'm willing to be with you carnally.
In order to stay warm, of course.
(LAUGHING) Tobe!
Word of advice for the summer...
Try and plan your hookups
in room temperature or above.
You'll never get a girl to take
her shirt off in the refrigerator.
Hey! Watch the footing there, Whit.
Dean, I swear to God,
I'm gonna kill you.
What's the matter?
Whitney doesn't know how to swim.
No way!
Thanks, Dean.
Hey, wait, hold up, I'll help you guys.
Okay, on the count of three.
One, two, three.
Nice work today, guys.
This is the last one.
Just a little more.
- Okay.
Yeah, this is good.
Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
Everybody, meet Drew Zemke.
Drew, this is Whitney, Dean,
Jason, Julie, and Tobe.
Hi, everybody.
ALL: Hey.
- Hey, how's it going?
Julie, you and Drew will be
co-counselors.
Cool.
So, where are you from?
All over.
We moved around a lot.
Boston most recently.
What about you?
Small town.
About two-and-a-half hours
south of here.
Small towns are great.
Yeah, if you don't have to
live in one.
Well, try living
in a city for a while,
after that, you really crave the peace
of a small place.
I don't know.
Oh, come on.
Everybody knows your name.
All those deep, dark, hidden secrets
that everybody tries to ignore...
That's good?
(SCOFFS)
Okay. Where else have you lived?
That's it.
I've lived there all my life.
Julie, I have to go back.
I forgot my camper list.
I'll meet you back up at the cabins.
(GASPS)
You scared me.
There's danger in these woods.
Excuse me?
Nelson's come back for revenge.
JULIE: Hey, Patrick.
Hey, Julie.
I thought you said these woods
were uninhabited.
As far as I know, they are.
I just saw an old man off the trail.
Oh, that must have been Henry.
Yeah, he used to run the camp
up here years ago.
Back when I was a camper.
That was before the Alzheimer's
kicked in.
(SHAKING)
- (LAUGHS)
He didn't scare you, did he?
Uh, no.
Here. Take one of these, will you?
Sure.
- Thanks.
JULIE:
"You were right about this place.
"It really is beautiful up here.
"I miss you, Dad.  Write me.
"Love, Julie."
Is that your mom?
She's really pretty.
Yeah.
She, um...
She died recently.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
I lost one of my parents, too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
(KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
Don't do that.
Hey, everybody's meeting out
by the lake.
You wanna come?
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLING)
Don't you wanna come?
Nah, not tonight.
I'm a little out of it.
I was thinking I might just catch up
on my sleep.
Next time?
- Yeah, next time.
Hey, but do you mind if I
check my email?
Not at all. Go for it.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
So, anybody wanna play Bloody Murder?
How do you play?
JASON: Well, the rules are simple.
As in the best of games,
one person is "it."
That person runs off to hide
as the rest of the group waits by home base
and counts till midnight.
1:00, 2:00, 3:00,
etcetera.
At midnight they break off
in separate directions
and try to find "it."
Whoever manages to find "it" first,
yells, "Bloody murder."
And everybody runs back to home base.
But if "it" manages to attack anyone
before they reach home base,
that person is "it" next game,
and the whole thing starts over again.
Sounds fun. Let's play.
All right. Well, you need a big group
to make it work.
I'm in.
Yeah, all right.
I'll play.
- Tobe?
Why not.
Okay.
Jewels?
What is this, kindergarten?
Come on.
Yeah, okay.
Brad?
Hmm, I don't think so.
Come on, it's just a game.
All right.
- JASON: Awesome.
All right, I'll be "it" this round.
Let's make that tree over there base.
Oh, and you guys,
remember to keep an eye out
for Trevor Moorehouse.
We're playing in his backyard.
Jason, just show yourself
so we can get this over with.
I hate this stupid game.
Mmm.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Relax, it's only me.
You loser! You scared
the shit out of me.
Whit, was that you?
Sorry. False alarm.
What else is new.
(LAUGHING)
Brad, buddy,
why don't you look over there.
I got this area covered.
Yeah, all right.
Douche bag.
Brad...
Could you yell, "Bloody murder"
for me?
(EXHALES)
(GASPS) Jesus Christ!
No. No.
No! No!
(LAUGHS)
Very funny.
That was Shakespeare, man.
Did you see his face?
Hey, man, no hard feelings.
Oh, shit.
What happened?
Oh, we were playing a joke on Brad
and he tripped.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'll be fine.
I better get him
back up to the cabin.
Hey, man, I really am sorry.
It's okay, don't sweat it.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Look, why don't you at least
just hear me out?
Or else what?
You'll punch me in the stomach?
Look, you know things have been
a little crazy for me lately
and Brad Thompson showing up
doesn't exactly help.
Jewels, I thought...
I thought coming up here would
help me get away from everything.
But instead, it's
just made matters worse.
Look, I'll apologize first thing
in the morning.
I promise.  I was a jerk.
I just...
I can't handle your being
mad at me right now.
Come on, I love you, Jewels.
What am I gonna do with you?
Hi.
- Hi.
How was your night?
Nightmare is more like it.
Well, do you want to talk about it?
No, I don't think so.
I'm just really tired.
(LAUGHING)
It's a habit I picked up
while I was living in Guam.
Helps me relax.
Do you smoke?
No.
I mean, I have, I just don't
do it regularly.
(UNZIPPING)
(URINATING)
(EXHALES IN RELIEF)
Oh, give it to her, Jas.
Shit!
(GRUNTS)
(ZIPPING)
Unbelievable.
Do you wanna smoke?
No, thanks, I really shouldn't.
Well, let me know
if you change your mind.
I will.
Good night.
- Good night.
Tobe, did Jason stop by your cabin
this morning to apologize?
He told me...
- No.
And I'm not so sure we should be
talking in public.
Wouldn't want to give anybody the idea
I was trying to put my tongue
down your throat.
Come on, Tobe, don't be like that.
(SIGHS)
Hey, Whit, have you seen
Jason around?
No, sorry, haven't seen him.
Dean, have you seen Jason this morning?
We had a fight last night.
And I haven't been able to
find him ever since.
No, I haven't seen him.
He mentioned something last night
about blowin' off camp.
Hitting the road for a while.
Patrick...
- Hey, Julie.
I'm worried about Jason.
We had a fight last night
and this morning he's
nowhere to be seen.
I checked his bed and it hasn't even
been slept in.
Has he ever taken off like this before?
Well, yeah.
Then he's probably trying
to scare you.
I wouldn't worry too much about it.
Maybe.
Don't you think we should call
the police or something?
Whoa.
Police can't do anything until he's
been missing at least 24 hours.
Look, I'm... I'm sure he'll show up
by dinner time.
If he doesn't, I'll call the Sheriff.
But in the meantime,
don't let it get to you.
The kids are gonna be here in three days
and we still got a ton of stuff to do.
Okay.
- Okay?
Come on, we'll just...
we'll just go out a little ways.
I don't know.
Look, we're friends now, Whit.
Don't you trust your friends?
Okay. But just until
I say we head back.
You got it.
- Okay.
This is far enough.
We did have some good times together too,
though, didn't we?
Yeah.
In the beginning.
I just wonder if we can work on it some
and...and make it better.
I mean, I know I can change.
I just...
I just need to feel like
I'm getting the same effort from you.
Dean, I wanna go back.
Don't you think we could give it
another shot?
Dean, this isn't funny.
Take me back.
I saw you last night, Whit.
What are you talking about?
He was my best friend.
Couldn't you pick someone else?
Stop it, Dean!  I mean it.
(SCREAMING)
Dean, wait, please come back!
Grab the oar, Whitney, I'll pull you in.
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
You all right?
Just take me back.
(PANTING)
Julie...
Any sign of Jason yet?
No. I'm getting really worried.
Yeah, I talked to Dean
and he said
the last time they talked last night,
Jason mentioned something about
taking off for a while?
Did Jason mention anything
about that to you?
No.
But we had a fight.
Patrick, Dean is acting really strange
by the lake today.
DREW: Yeah.
- Strange how?
Like scary strange.
He was out in the canoe
with Whitney.
I know he knows she can't swim.
He tipped the canoe over anyway.
It looked really odd to me.
All right, I'll keep an eye on him.
Thanks.
Thanks, Patrick.
Oh, and Julie,
don't worry about Jason.
I'm sure he'll show up
when we least expect him.
All right.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Somebody let me out of here, please.
Please help me!
Help me, please!
(WOMAN PANTING)
(BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
Have you seen my lighter?
Thanks.
(BEEPS)
TOM:  "Hi, Sweetie.
Nothing to report from this end.
"Glad you're having fun.
"Love, Dad."
(MOVIE CONTINUES)
I'm gonna go get something to eat.
Do you want anything?
I'm good, thanks.
- Okay.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SIGHS) Very funny.
Now, take off your mask and show yourself.
(SCREAMING)
Hey.
Whitney disappeared last night.
(SIGHS)
SHERIFF:
So, let me get this straight.
You're now telling me that there's
two camp counselors missing.
I'm afraid so.
Well, why didn't you report
the other kid missing yesterday?
Well, he had a fight with his girlfriend
early last night and...
Well, you know how these 18-year-old
teenagers are.
Yeah, working around these camps
made sure of that.
Sheriff...
This maybe way off, but...
Could there be anything to these
Trevor Moorehouse stories?
(SCOFFS)
Son, I've been working in and around
Placid Pines for 20 years now,
and I've seen a lot of strange things,
but I've never seen one iota
of evidence
that Trevor Moorehouse exists.
But, then, anything out of
the ordinary happens,
it's, "Trevor Moorehouse
is back for revenge."
And, "Trevor Moorehouse stole my cat."
And, "Trevor Moorehouse smashed my car."
Take it from me, there is
no such person as Trevor Moorehouse.
SHERIFF: So, the last anybody
saw of her,
she was heading into this room?
Yeah, that's right.
What time was that?
Uh...
About 10:30.
Hmm.
Well, there's no sign
of a struggle.
Is there anything missing?
Um, not so far as I know.
Hmm.
Anybody at the campsite give the girl
any trouble?   A boyfriend?
Ex-boyfriend, maybe?
Yeah. Yeah.
SHERIFF: So, you don't have any idea
what might have happened
to Whitney last night?
Wish I could help you.
Well, if you don't
mind me asking, Dean...
Where were you at approximately
10:30 last night?
10:30?
- Mmm-hmm.
I was in the mess hall
watching the movie.
You have anybody that can vouch for you?
Tobe. I helped him set up the movie.
TOBE:  Yeah, Dean was there.
But we set up the VCR and screen just
before we started the movie.
That was at 10:00 sharp.
I know that because I programmed
my watch to beep on the hour.
(WATCH BEEPING)
So, you can account for Dean's whereabouts
from 10:30 until midnight
last night?
Well, not exactly.
I... I can account for his whereabouts
at 10:00 p.m.
And then again after 11:43 p.m.
last night.
You see, the VCR we were using
is kind of a piece of shit...
Oh. Can I say that to a cop?
Anyways, I sat next to it just in case
the film got caught.
And Dean was sitting
a coupla chairs behind me.
The movie was Sleepover Camp Massacre 14.
It's a summer camp slasher movie.
It has a running time of an hour
and 43 minutes.
It's... It's relatively long
for movies in this genre.
I'm gonna go get something to eat.
Do you want anything?
I'm good, thanks.
- Okay.
TOBE:  It's at least possible that Dean
seeing Whitney leave her seat,
could have snuck out of the
other side of the cabin.
And... And followed her into the kitchen.
Given that Whitney had to walk over people
and around the screen,
Dean would have had about 30 seconds
on her to reach the kitchen.
This would have given him just enough time
to get ready for her.
It's about 10:32 now, and Whitney
enters the kitchen.
Not seeing anybody, she continues
into the pantry.
Seconds later, while Whitney was searching
for something to eat,
Dean could have come up from
behind her in the pantry.
Very funny.
Now, take off your mask and show yourself.
At this point, it will be about 10:35.
That's an hour and seven minutes
before the movie ends.
This would have given Dean
more than enough time
to brutally murder Whitney,
dispose of the body,
clean up the pantry,
and return to his seat before
the tail credits rolls.
But, of course,
that's just a theory.
Nice! I'm gonna set you down
over there.
Dean!
I'm gonna have to ask you to come
in to the station with me
for some more questioning.
Listen, Brad, about the other night...
Don't worry about it.
Some people just have your number
and there's nothing you
can do about it.
I guess.
Besides... (CHUCKLES)
It's nothing compared
to the crazy shit
that used to pull up here
when my dad was a counselor.
So, you're a second
generation CPP as well.
Oh, yeah.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Seems like everybody
raised in our town
did time
at Camp Placid Pines.
Father or mother?
My father.
I was hearing
about these woods
before I could even walk.
(LAUGHS)
I'm glad to hear
I'm not the only one
who's fated to
work at this place.
What's going on?
Whitney disappeared
last night
and the Sheriff wants
to ask Dean
some questions.
You don't think
he did anything
to her, do you?
Julie, I don't know
what to think.
There you are.
I was really starting
to get worried.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
I guess
I needed to runaway
for a little while.
Well, what's on
your mind?
I don't know.
(SNIFFLES) Everything.
My mom, Jason.
Now Whitney.
This summer isn't
exactly turning out
as I expected.
Well, is there anything
I could do to help?
You wouldn't
by any chance
have one of those
Guam cigarettes on you,
would you?
(LAUGHS)
Actually,
I brought one with me.
Just in case.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(COUGHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You okay?
My father would kill me
if he knew I was doing this.
I won't tell
if you won't.
(EXHALES)
It just
doesn't seem fair.
Seventeen years.
I was just getting
to know her, you know.
Yeah. I never got
to meet my dad.
He died
before I was born.
Jeez, listen to me.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Misery comes in lots
of different forms.
It's all miserable.
(SNIFFLES)
Do you ever
feel cheated?
Well, sometimes
I get angry.
I seek out
other people to blame
for my father's death.
My therapist calls it
transference.
It's where
I feel too guilty
to blame him,
so I look out
for other people
to be angry with.
(CHUCKLES)
Your toes are beautiful.
Thanks.
It's called  mehndi.
It's a form of
body painting I learned
while living in India.
I can do yours
if you want.
I'd like that.
I'm telling you,
I have no idea of
what happened
to Jason and Whitney.
As I said before,
they hooked up
by the lake, the night
that Jason disappeared.
Took off like he said
he was gonna do,
got bored
and came back
for Whitney.
(SIGHS)
Okay, Dean,
I've got three officers
out there
combing the area
for Jason and Whitney
right now.
I've notified
the state police
of the disappearance.
And if they're out there,
we'll find them.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to
hold you overnight.
(SIGHS) Oh.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
Nice going, Drew.
(TURNS OFF SHOWER)
(GASPS)
Nelson's come back
to even the score.
Sorry, I...
Ask Tommy McConnell
what really happened
to Nelson that night.
How do you know
my dad's name?
JULIE:  "There's an old man
up here named Henry.
"Patrick said
that he used to run
the camp years ago.
"Anyway, he knew
your name
"and asked me to ask you
what really happened
to Nelson.
"Any idea what
he was talking about?
"Miss you.
Love, Jewels."
(BEEPS)
So, what do you guys think
is going on around here
anyway?
Simple. I think that Dean
got dumped by Whitney.
He couldn't handle it,
went psycho on her.
End of story.
I've known Dean
a long time.
I don't think
he's capable of
anything like that.
I still think
we're overlooking
the obvious here.
And what's that?
Trevor Moorehouse
is back for revenge.
Get out of here.
I'm not kidding.
I heard this guy
was real.
Okay, who's
Trevor Moorehouse?
DOUG:
The camp boogeyman.
Look, take it for
whatever it's worth.
But my older sister swears
she knows someone
whose brother's friend
disappeared up here
coupla years ago
during the summer.
What is this?
Six degrees
of mutilation?
There's no such person
as Trevor Moorehouse.
That's what my sister
said she told that guy
a few years ago.
The night
he disappeared.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Where you going?
Set up the archer range
for first activity.
I thought one of us
should take responsibility
for this camping.
Good thinking.
Oh, hey, Brad...
What?
Don't forget to lookout
for Trevor Moorehouse.
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPS)
TOM:  "Hi, Sweetie.
"I don't remember anyone
named Nelson being at
the camp when I was there.
"Henry must have
had me confused
with someone else.
"Hope you're having fun."
"Love, Dad."
Brad!
(PHONE RINGING)
Sheriff Wilson.
I see.
Uh-huh.
I'll be right down.
SHERIFF: Dean!
I'm sorry about
the confusion.
Yeah, whatever.
Don't get too used
to the idea of
having me around.
So, you say that Jason
had a beef with
Brad Thompson.
That's right.
Brad was the last person
Jason competed against
in track before
he blew his knew out.
Jesus!
Some of these kids
are taking their sports
way too serious today.
Don't worry, Patrick,
we're gonna catch Jason.
I've got every officer
in the state working
to make that happen.
Well, that's great.
What shall we do about
the camp in the meantime.
Well, I don't
think you'll have
anymore trouble,
but just in case,
I'll put a man
down there on Von Road
across from the arch way.
Anything suspicious,
you just give a holler,
he'll come running.
Great.
Thanks, Sheriff.
Sure.
What's going on
with the police car
out front?
Well, the Sheriff thought
it might be a good idea
if somebody kept an eye
on the camp.
It's just a precaution.
TOBE: Of course,
this is so obvious.
We're at
a sleepover camp.
Naturally, the killer
had to be Jason.
What's he talking about?
Julie, Brad disappeared
earlier today.
The Sheriff thinks
Jason might have had
something to do with it.
That's crazy.
I don't believe it.
Well, come on, Julie,
we all saw the look
in his eyes
when he discovered
that Brad was up here
for the summer.
He was upset.
Jason couldn't possibly
do anything to hurt anyone.
Oh, great.
I'm a dead man.
The one guy
I pissed off
this summer
had to be a psychotic killer
named Jason, no less.
There's got to be
some other explanation.
I hope there is,
believe me.
But in the meantime,
we can't be too careful.
Patrick, can I talk
to you alone?
Um, sure.
Tobe, why don't you
head back down
to the lake
and make sure
the canoes are secured.
Oh, sure.
You know, this is a great time
for me to be walking
to the camp alone.
Why don't you just
paste a sign on my back
that says,
"Please kill next."
Go.
Henry said something to me
by the showers yesterday.
He said,
"Nelson's come back
to even the score."
Then he told me to
ask my dad what really
happened that night.
Do you know
what he's talking about?
No. Henry's sick, Julie.
He doesn't always make
complete sense
as we know it.
I'll tell you what,
I'll go through
the camp archives
and look for this...
Nelson.
Right.
If that will make you
feel any better.
Thanks.
I wouldn't get
your hopes up though.
Henry's always saying
one thing or another
and nine times out of ten
it's meaningless.
DREW:  "Hi, Julie.
I went down to the lake
for a swim.
"Come join me. Drew."
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(TWIGS SNAPPING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Jesus Christ,
McConnell!
What the hell
do you think
you're doing?
(PANTING) Nothing. I...
I thought I saw
an animal in the woods.
Great.
Now I gotta deal
with a flat.
Are you going somewhere?
Far away from
this fucking place
as possible.
What do you think
is going on up here?
(SIGHS)
I think somebody
is playing a rather
elaborate prank on us.
It's like that
Bloody Murder joke we played
on Brad the other night.
My old man told me
they used to run that gag
every year up here.
Hey, have you
seen Henry around?
Not lately.
But you could probably
catch him up at his house.
Uh, McConnell,
I can give you a ride
back to the camp
if you don't
mind waiting.
No, it's okay.
I'll walk.
Hey! The camp's
back that way.
Everyone's whacked
at this place.
Oh, by the way,
I saw your boyfriend
slam-tackling
my ex-girlfriend
by the lake the other night.
Just thought
you'd want to know.
(CHOKING)
Julie! Julie!
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
Henry?
Henry,
if you're in there,
I... I'd like
to speak to you.
Creepy old cottage.
I guess this is
the right place.
JULIE:  "Thing are
getting a little creepy
out here.
"Jason took off
a few days ago.
"And now,
Whitney and Brad
are missing.
"I found a picture of you
when you were
a counselor here.
"You're standing right
next to a camper named
Nelson Hammond.
"Are you sure
you don't remember him?
"Please call me
as soon as you get
this message.
"Love, Jewels."
DREW: There you are.
(GASPS)
We missed you
down at the lake.
Sorry. I got
a little sidetracked.
That's all right.
Is this your towel?
Yeah.
I found it on the path
down by the lake.
Thanks.
Sure.
SHERIFF:
Does Jason have a shoe
that matches this print?
Well, yeah,
he does, but...
That's it.
Jason Hathaway
is our boy.
I'll notify his parents
and I'll triple our efforts.
It always helps to know
who you're looking for.
Thanks, Sheriff.
Patrick,
I went by Henry's place
and I found something.
See, right there,
that was my dad
25 years ago.
And according to this,
that was a camper
named Nelson Hammond.
Julie, you gotta start
facing the facts here.
You've got a jilted
boyfriend out there
with a history
of violent behavior.
Who's trying to
make your life
very unpleasant.
Look, if you
don't feel...
If you don't
feel comfortable
staying up here
until this is resolved,
I'd understand.
I'll probably go
out of my mind
if you left,
but I'd understand.
Hi, Dad,
it's me again.
Look, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
It's kind of important.
Please give me
a call tonight
when you go home.
I'll be up
for a while. Bye.
(BEEPS)
JULIE:  "Nelson Hammond.
"12-year-old Nelson Hammond
taken to hospital
"after mysterious accident
at Camp Placid Pines.
"August 1, 1974.
"12-year-old Nelson Hammond
was rushed to the hospital
Saturday,
"after nearly drowning
in Lake Placid Pines.
"Counselors report
he was playing a game
of Bloody Murder
"when the accident
occurred."
Have you seen
my scissors?
Uh... Yeah.
Thanks.
"July 2, 1981.
"Nelson Hammond
was committed
"to the Carpenter County
Medical Institution yesterday
"for the murder of
his former camp counselor,
Bill Anderson.
"When asked if
he were remorseful
for the murder,
"Hammond replied only,
'Have you ever played
Bloody Murder?'
"Bill Anderson is survived
by his pregnant wife,
Patricia."
(BEEPING)
Where you going?
To check the phone
in the office.
The one in our room
is not working.
Do you want me
to come with you.
No, thanks,
I'll be fine.
If the phone starts working
and my dad calls,
let him know
I'll be right back, okay?
Sure.
Thanks.
Julie, wait, Julie!
(PANTING)
Hello?
(BANGING ON DOOR)
JASON: Open the door.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Somebody help me.
Hey, open the door.
Jason?
Jewels, let me explain.
Jason!
It's not
what you think.
No!
Dean threatened to tell you
about me and Whitney
by the lake
the other night
if I didn't leave.
I couldn't risk
losing you.
The next think I know
my picture's everywhere
and the cops are after me.
Julie, you've gotta
believe me.
Jason, how could you?
I didn't do anything.
Look, you gotta help me.
Just... Just open the door
and we'll talk.
Open the door, Julie.
Julie, open the door.
You did the right thing,
Julie.
Well, that should be
the end of trouble in Camp
Placid Pines for a while.
JULIE: What time is it?
It's late.
I didn't wanna
wake you.
You seemed
really tired.
Hey, did my Dad
ever call back?
No. I didn't
hear from him.
What happened to you
last night?
Jason came back.
Ew. Creepy.
Yeah.
Are you all right?
It's weird,
but I think I am.
Well, that's good.
I'm glad.
(CHUCKLES)
Listen, Tobe and I
have to go down
and finish setting up
the obstacle course.
Do you wanna come?
Sure. In a minute.
There's something
I need to check first.
All right.
Well, take your time.
(BEEPS)
TOM: " Hi, Sweetheart.
"I had to leave town suddenly
on business yesterday.
"I hope you weren't
trying to reach me.
"I'll be back tomorrow
and we can talk.
"Take good care
of yourself.
I miss you.
"Love, Dad.
"P.S. Now that
you've mentioned it,
"I do remember Nelson Hammond.
What ever happened to him?"
Here you go.
Thanks.
How's it coming?
Good.
We're almost finished.
Do you wanna
give it a run?
I'm game.
All right. I just need,
like, five minutes to finish
marking the course. Okay?
Uh, Julie, I just wanna
let you know I understand
how painful breakups can be
and I'm here if
you need someone
to talk to.
Or perhaps
a rebound relationship.
Thanks, Tobe.
You're a good friend.
"Friend." (SCOFFS)
You think she's ready?
Probably.
Wish me luck.
Just stay within
the orange markers.
Okay.
(LAUGHS)
(CREAKING)
Oh, shit!
Julie!
Are you all right?
I think so. Ouch.
I don't understand it.
Tobe and I tested
that rope together.
That's okay,
I'm fine.
What happened?
The rope broke,
Julie fell.
It's okay, really,
I'm fine.
Doug, have you seen
the tug-of-war rope
around here anywhere?
Yeah, I stashed it
in the back office
when we first got up here.
I looked back there.
I couldn't find it.
Hmm. Well,
I'll tell you what.
I'll look for
the tug-of-war rope,
you take this stuff
to the picnic area.
Deal.
All right? Cool.
Oh, speaking of
lost items...
You haven't seen a pair
of black boots laying
around, have you?
I misplaced it
the first day
I got up here.
Sorry,
I haven't seen 'em.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(GROANING)
Oh, my God!
(GASPING)
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Is it any better?
(SIGHS) Yeah, a little.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I have something for you.
It's just a little
something to commemorate
our summer together.
It's beautiful.
(CHUCKLING) Thanks.
Drew I wanna tell you.
I feel really lucky to
have been partnered
with you.
I don't know what
I would have done
these past coupla days
without you.
Oh, I'm lucky, too.
Here we are,
five days into the summer
and I already have
a new best friend.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Here.
So, what do you guys think
they're gonna do with Jason?
Well, if memory
serves me correctly,
they'll probably have to
incinerate him.
And then bury him
in an ancient Indian
burial ground
to destroy him.
(LAUGHS)
Sheriff Wilson said
they're gonna hold him
for a while,
until Whitney and Brad
show up.
Yeah, but I like
my version
a lot better.
Do you think
he did anything to him?
I don't know.
At first, I wouldn't
have thought so,
but now
I'm not so sure.
Have you guys
seen Doug today?
Yeah, I saw him
about an hour ago.
He was looking
for a pair of shoes
he lost up here
the first day.
Any of you guys seen 'em?
Not my style.
Haven't seen 'em.
Oh, me neither.
Hey, I'm gonna load
the paintball guns.
Anyone care to join me
in a test duel. Huh?
(LAUGHS) Pass.
Thanks.
Chicks.
Hey, Jewels,
how's your knee?
It's much better.
Good.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Dad?
(CHUCKLES)
Hey!
Hey.
Oh.
What are you
doing here?
I got your messages
last night
when I didn't
hear from you, well...
Hi.
You must be Julie's dad.
I've heard a lot
about you.
Dad, this is Drew Zemke.
Drew's my partner
for this summer.
Oh, hi, Drew.
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
So, Julie tells me
you used to be
a counselor up here.
About 100 years ago.
Well, couldn't have
been that long ago.
Patrick!
Come meet my dad.
Hi, I'm Patrick.
I'm Tom.
Nice to meet you.
Um, Julie,
have you seen
my camper's list?
I've... I've looked
everywhere.
Well, I have a copy
in my cabin.
Let me get it for you.
Great, thanks.
Take care.
Nice talking to you.
Duty calls.
Julie, do you want me
to get it for you?
I'd better go.
It's under a bunch
of things.
Hey! Why don't you
show my dad around?
I'll meet you guys
at the lake in 20?
Are you sure?
Yeah, go ahead.
"Kevin Thompson,
"Whitney Chambers,
"Becky Chambers,
"Drew Zemke.
"Mother, Patricia Zemke.
"Father, Bill Anderson?"
DREW:  Sometimes
I get angry.
I seek out
other people to blame
for my father's death.
My therapist calls it
transference.
TOM:  "Hi, Sweetie."
DREW:  "I don't remember anyone
named Nelson being at
the camp when I was there."
(GRUNTS)
No.
(GROANING)
JULIE:  It was Drew.
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
What? Oh, vicious paintball
gun loading accident.
Tobe! Get to the phone
and call the police.
It wasn't Jason.
It was Drew!
It was Drew all along.
What was Drew all along?
What are you talking about?
Drew murdered them.
Nelson Hammond
killed her father
and now she's
seeking revenge.
I don't have time
to explain.
Have you seen my dad?
Yeah, I saw him with Drew,
they were heading
to the lake.
Who's Nelson Hammond?
Walking around these woods
must bring back a lot
of memories for you.
Yeah, sort of.
My dad was a counselor
at the same time
you were up here.
Really?
Uh-huh.
What's your
father's name?
Bill Anderson.
Bill Anderson?
Wow. That's a name
I haven't heard in ages.
How's he doing?
He died.
Before I was born.
(SIREN WAILING)
Any sign of 'em?
No, sir. Drew said
they were heading
down to the lake
and when I told Julie that,
she went after 'em.
All right. Billy,
I want you to go around
east side of the lake.
I'll take the west.
Tobe, I want you and Jason
to gather everybody else
in the camp.
As of this moment,
this camp is officially
closed for summer.
Let's go.
TOM: The lake hasn't
changed one bit.
DREW: I love it here.
Is this where
we're supposed
to meet Julie?
Yeah. She should be
down here any minute.
The girls are
really gonna love her.
She's just the type
to have the magic touch.
Yeah.
I guess she got that
from her mother.
Well, from what
Julie tells me,
she sounded like
an amazing woman.
Yeah. Well...
You really should
check out the view
from the end of the dock.
It's extraordinary.
Oh, after you.
You looking for somebody?
Oh. Hi.
I didn't see you.
Where's my dad?
He's waiting for us
down by the docks.
That's strange.
He was here
when I left.
Drew!
What did you do
with my father?
Nothing.
He was standing
right here when I left.
Drew!
I know!
You know what?
I know your father
was Bill Anderson.
So?
"So?" I know
what you're doing.
I know how
you killed them.
And you were
probably going
to kill me.
What are you
talking about?
Your father was murdered
by Nelson Hammond.
You seek out others
to blame for his death?
Transference! I know.
Julie, turn around.
Where's my dad?
Turn around.
I'm not turning around
until you tell me
where my father is.
Look!
(SCREAMS)
Get away from him.
Jump!
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTS)
No, no.
Please, please.
(SCREAMS)
Patrick!
I'm over here.
He's over there
by the dock!
He's got Drew.
All right, all right.
Let's get you
safe first.
Patrick, I'll be fine.
We've got to help Drew.
I'm afraid nothing
can help Drew now.
What are you
talking about?
I mean,
she's dead, Julie.
There's nothing
I or anybody can do.
How do you know
she's dead?
Because I killed her,
Julie.
Just like I killed
your father.
Yeah.
Just like I killed
your friends.
Just like
I'm gonna kill you.
What?
Oh, yeah.
They treated me awful
20 years ago.
And for that
they have to pay.
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
Patrick,
I don't understand.
"Patrick,
I don't understand."
I'm sorry, you have me
confused with someone
named Patrick.
That wouldn't be
that Patrick, would it?
(SCREAMS)
Tell me something, Julie.
Have you ever played
Bloody Murder?
You're Nelson Hammond.
Oh, very good.
(CHUCKLES)
You kids today,
you think your computers,
and your telephones,
and your email
can keep you safe
in the woods?
Well, let this be
a lesson to you, Julie.
Email could
be intercepted.
And it's not
always considered
Internet worthy news
when they let you out,
as it is when
they lock you up.
Say, "Bye-bye."
(SCREAMING)
Get away!
JULIE: No!
Dad!
(GROANING)
Dad! Dad!
Somebody help me!
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
You're not playing
by the rules, McConnell.
You have to
yell, "Bloody murder."
Aw.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Somebody help me.
He's right behind me.
It's okay, everybody.
The Sheriff arrested Drew
by the lake.
Now, Julie was hit
in the head.
She's got
a mild concussion.
I need to take her
to the hospital.
Jason, do something.
He's the killer!
It's okay, Julie,
it's over.
Just do what
Patrick says.
Get in the car, Julie.
Somebody believe me.
He's Nelson Hammond.
Stop right there!
Whoa. Look who
you're talking to, Tobe.
It's me, Patrick.
I mean it,
not one more step.
(CLICKING)
(GUN FIRES)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
Everything is gonna
be fine, Dad.
I'll meet you
at the hospital.
And then tomorrow
we can go home.
If I'd known,
I would have warned you.
It's okay.
I'm a big girl now.
I can take care
of myself.
How do you feel?
(SIGHS) It's weird,
but I think
I'm all right.
I mean, I came up here
to deal with some
unresolved issues
about my father's death.
And in a weird way,
I... I guess you could
say I did.
I guess I just didn't
expect it to be
so literal.
Is it strange to say
I'm happy for you?
(CHUCKLES)
Probably.
(LAUGHS)
In that case,
I'm happy for you.
Okay.
I'll meet you
at the hospital, okay?
Well, I'm out
of here, Jewels.
Bye.
See you next summer?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You know...
(GROANS)
I could kind of understand
in a backward way
why you killed
Whitney and Brad
and Dean.
But why Doug?
Doug never did
a thing to you.
Come on.
(GROANING)
I didn't kill Doug.
Must have been...
Trevor Moorehouse.
You need some help?
Thanks.
I feel like such a jerk
trying to save the day
with no bullets like that.
I don't think
you're a jerk at all.
Not many guys would
take the risk of doing
what you did for me.
Yeah, well, don't let that
influence your decision
as to whether or not
to sleep with me.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I'll try not to.
It's gonna
be really hard.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
I'm so glad
we can finally put
all this behind us
and get back to
how things were before.
So, we ready to go?
Uh, yeah.
Take care, Tobe.
No hard feelings,
huh, buddy.
Jason, Tobe is
coming with me.
What, we're gonna
give him a ride
to the bus station?
Hey, that's cool.
No, Tobe's coming with me
to the hospital.
I'm gonna
give you a ride
to the bus station.
(LAUGHING) What, Jewels?
You're gonna runaway
with Mr. Bull this year?
Well, don't do me
any favors, all right.
Have a nice
life together.
Uh, are you gonna
be all right?
Definitely.
Let's go.
(SAW WHIRRING)
(JASON SCREAMING)