Dismissed? Me?
You have brought shame upon
Lord Desler's plan!
If you are unable to deal
with the Yamato problem,
then my own position is jeopardized,
as I recommended you for commander.
Don't worry, sir.
I can deal with one or
two Terron ships!
I'm sure you already know this,
but "failure" is not a word in
the Garmillas dictionary.
Nor in my own.
Y-Yes, sir!
I shall await good news, Goer.
Zar Belk!
Commander, about that ship we lost
contact with several days ago...
Irrelevant.
But that ship has an Imperial Guard
Information Officer on board...
It doesn't matter!
Only the Yamato does.
Find the Yamato, and destroy it!
Here is the Yamato's
predicted trajectory.
They should be within
this 7-korm area...
I will assume command.
Launch the fleet!
Take care, Brother.
Ship now entering warp navigation.
All crew, prepare for warp.
I've gotten used to it now.
Repeat: Ship now entering warp navigation.
We warp, and next thing
you know, we're there.
All crew, prepare for warp.
Destination coordinates entered.
Galactic longitude 274.76,
Galactic latitude -12.73.
Distance is 63.7 parsecs.
Confirmed.
Coordinate axis fixed.
Wave Motion Engine
chamber pressure rising.
Engine pressure has
reached critical point.
5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
Warp.
Warp!
What is this?
This isn't how it usually is.
Situation report.
The ship appears to
still be in warp.
I see.
We're currently inhabiting the 1
nanosecond of the ship's warp.
This has never occurred before...
The automatic navigation room?
Mori, go and check the
automatic navigation room.
Yes, sir.
Message from the XO.
We are currently still in warp.
Listen, it's your own uncertainty
that's causing the blurry vision.
But we are encountering some
complications as we assess the cause.
Not a chance...
What's happened to me?
Misaki?
Are you okay?
Y-Yes!
Where are we?
I want damage inspections now.
Nothing on radar or scanner.
It seems like we can use
hyperspace transmission.
Probably only in here, though.
Those only resonate within this space.
We can't reach the outside.
Captain, it appears we've fallen
into a dimensional rift.
Where dimensions intersect...
In other words, a dimensional fault?
This is the engine room.
Energy leak of unknown origin
occurring within the Wave Motion Engine.
Shut down the engine.
This area's space-time
characteristics are inverted.
Normally, the Wave Motion Engine
produces infinite energy out of vacuum.
But in this place, it leaks
energy to the outside.
Warning.
Multiple unidentified objects ahead.
What?
It's like a ship graveyard.
They were unable to escape,
and wandered this alternate
dimension for eternity.
A universal Sargasso Sea, huh?
I didn't see anything unusual.
Understood.
Garmillas ship detected at eleven o'clock!
Identified as L-class cruiser.
It's still on line...
The Garmillas ship is on alert.
There's only one ship.
Should we attack?
We hold the firepower advantage, sir.
If two lions mired in a bog fight
one other, both will sink.
I'm certain they understand that.
Captain, enemy ship is hailing us.
Open a channel.
Alpha 2, stand by in catapult.
Cosmo Zero, on launch standby.
Enemy plane has launched.
Launch the Zero.
Alpha 2, this is the Yamato.
Guide the Garmillas plane to hangar 3.
This whole pretense of sending
an envoy has to be a trap.
But they claimed to know
how to escape this area.
If that's true, why have they not left?
That's something we need to know.
Get hangar 3 pressurized at once.
Pressure rising. Oxygen in hangar
now approaching normal levels.
That's a Garmillan!
What are they like?
They're trying to destroy humanity.
I'm sure they're some
kind of monster.
Look.
No way...
That's impossible!
They're human?
That's a human!
It certainly looks that way, and...
A woman, isn't it?
Her skin is blue.
<We greet you as a
ceasefire ambassador.>
<Your Garmillan is
difficult to understand.>
It's fine.
I can translate your language.
More importantly, I'd like
to confirm something.
Is this a Terron ship?
Terron?
The one called "Yamato"
or something similar?
Lower Storm Leader Ditz has
docked with the Yamato.
If that's the Yamato,
it's a lucky break for a second-class
Garmillas ship like yours, Captain.
Director-General Gimleh will be pleased.
Damned Imperial Guard...
I am Melda Ditz, of the 707th
Galactic Theater Air Corps.
My rank is Lower Storm Leader.
I am the ship's tactical
officer, Susumu Kodai.
Within my empire's territory, there are
others like you, without blue skin.
Are there?
Inferior races from systems we've
absorbed or from colonized planets.
The second-class Garmillans.
Are you sure you're here to negotiate?
And you ask that I trust someone who
brings a gun to meet a negotiator?
Well, the Terrons enjoy war
so much, they attacked
without even a formal declaration.
You were the ones who
started this war!
For generations, my family has
held important military posts.
I swear by my family honor
that I speak the truth.
You lie! You were the ones
who attacked us first!
Kodai?
I'll hear your proposal.
The Wave Motion Gun?
Yes.
I see.
It's theoretically possible.
The Wave Motion Gun
generates a powerful
Dimensional Wave Motion
along its line of fire.
If we aim at the dimensional
fault's phase boundary,
by our calculations, the waves of
interference should clear an exit.
But how did they know about
the Wave Motion Gun?
They must have been paying attention
when we used it at Gliese 581.
But using the Wave Motion Gun would
cost us most of our remaining energy.
It would knock the Yamato off-line!
Don't worry about that.
We promise that our ship will
tow the Yamato to safety.
We need a weapon to create an exit,
and you need someone to get you
out, once the way is open.
If we don't work together,
we cannot escape.
I don't think we can trust them.
It's possible they'll let us fire the Wave
Motion Gun, and then escape alone.
These are the people telling us we're
responsible for this war, after all.
Even as we speak,
we're losing energy.
We must reach a swift conclusion,
or even firing the Wave Motion
Gun will become impossible.
Indeed.
There's no time to hesitate.
Then what do we do?
Is there anything we can do?
There is.
Believe in them.
We've reached our decision.
We'll agree to your plan.
I'm glad.
I thank you.
This is Vars Lang,
Captain of the EX-178.
I am Captain Juzo Okita
of the Yamato.
Captain Lang, we thank
you for your proposal.
Just like you, we have been
stuck here, unable to escape.
We thank you, as well,
for acceding to our plan.
Lower Storm Leader Ditz will remain there,
to serve as a point of contact.
You may take it as a
gesture of our goodwill.
So, a convenient hostage, huh?
But once we return to normal space,
we will be enemies once more.
Understood.
I look forward to exchanging fire with you.
Transmission over.
If we use the Wave Motion Gun, we won't
have energy for our main artillery.
I know.
This is a promise between men.
So Admiral Ditz's daughter
stays with them.
The Terrons must trust us now.
That is a beautiful stone.
While not as splendid as a noble
blue, red is a lovely color.
Red is the color of my home.
And it is my color.
It seems quite important to you.
Just like Kodai's gun.
What do you mean?
Both are mementos our beloved
ones left behind.
Before you killed them all.
Incoming tow beam.
Switch to emergency power.
It's begun.
Prepare to fire the Wave Motion Gun!
Releasing safety lock.
Activating force injector.
Final safety released.
Tachyon particle pressure
rising in chamber.
Garmillas ship is leaving the firing line.
Engage anti-shock and
anti-flare defenses.
Target scope open!
Electronic cross-gauge,
display brightness twenty.
Five seconds to fire.
4... 3... 2... 1...
Fire.
Fire!
Exit has been created.
But now, the Yamato no longer has
the power to move on her own.
Confirmed fissure in dimensional boundary.
It's an exit.
This ship will commence towing
the Yamato from the area.
Garmillas ship has begun to tow us.
Captain, you don't plan to...
You are an outsider here,
Storm Leader.
Hail to our Leader!
Tow beam output
stabilized and normal.
The tow beam has been cut!
The Garmillas ship has sent a hyperspace
transmission to the opening.
It's encrypted, and we can't read it!
Then they do plan to escape
and leave us here!
That's what we get
for believing them.
Impossible!
I knew it.
I knew this was your plan!
What are you doing?
Captain, I...
You're the one who alerted Commander
Goer that we found the Yamato?
I shall report this treason
upon our return.
This is no treason.
You're the traitor here, Captain.
They're our enemy!
You are our enemy.
If you think I'm an enemy,
shoot me. Do not hesitate.
Tow beam has been reconnected.
What's going on?
Stay on alert.
For now, just focus on getting out.
Three minutes until we
reenter normal space.
The exit is becoming unstable.
Maintaining relative
distance to Garmillas ship.
One minute left.
Detecting phase fluctuation.
Accelerating to 12 gat.
You're a pilot, right?
We don't need this thing between us.
Tow beam released.
Ship has returned to regular space.
We did it.
We made it out, right?
Yeah, we're saved!
Good...
All crew to battle stations.
Order Lower Storm Leader Ditz to return.
The Yamato, huh?
A splendid enemy.
Friendlies are Geschtaming in.
Garmillas fleet warping in,
off our port bow.
So it was a trap!
EX-178...
You are in our line of fire.
You're in the way. Move!
Commander Goer, Admiral Ditz's
daughter is aboard that ship!
Commander...
I don't care. Fire.
We're under friendly fire!
Evade! Evade!
EX-178 has been shot down!
Confirmed destruction of EX-178.
The Yamato shot down the missing
ship we were searching for.
That's what happened, right?
Yes.
All right!
All ships, open fire on the Yamato!
Exterior armor hit, port side!
Damage control! Hurry!
Let's counterattack.
Turn the ship around.
We're running?
Yes.
Don't let them escape!
Pursue and destroy them!
The enemy fleet is being annihilated.
A huge dimensional quake!
A dimensional fault is
forming at the epicenter.
R-Retreat!
Jump out of here now!
But the flagship cannot retreat before
issuing the order to the other ships.
Do you all want to die?
Enemy fleet has been eradicated.
The exit from the rift tried to
collapse into its original position.
The reaction temporarily expanded
the rift, sucking them in.
Yes, understood.
They said your prior
destination no longer exists.
Episode 10: Graveyard of the Universe
Everyone lives with secret feelings.
It takes courage to reflect on a horrible
past and one's own mistakes.
But look toward to the future.
Now is the time to go forward.
The Yamato advances, on an
unimaginably long journey.
Next time: A World I Once Saw.
There are 323 days left
before humanity is extinct.