City people think they're smart
but their brains are in the wrong place.
Yeah, they don’t
even get simple things...
How did they find out
that we're doing the healing ritual?
I don’t care if they film the ritual.
But the joke is, the want us to act it out.
That’s just plain stupid.
Well, maybe we should just do it.
Let them have a taste of
what the spirits are really like.
Fools. You cant mess
around with the spirits.
Its not like what you see on TV.
They are looking for trouble.
So, what’s the story
with that land on the beach?
Hey, isn’t that Pekin Ibrahim?
I don’t know. But that’s Faizal Hussein.
Him, I know.
Give me two or three days,
and ill settle it for you. Don’t worry.
Ill take over your debt.
Isn’t that Zahiril Adzim?
Its sorted.
The generators dying. The powers
going to cut. Were watching TV here.
Enough?
Yes.
How long has it been?
He’s been sick for some time.
He’s possessed by the
spirits of the shadow puppets.
Have you prepared everything?
Everything’s in place.
What about the healers and the musicians for it?
They are ready and waiting.
Ill need to ask Boss.
Alright, you ask him. Just a second.
Looking for Boss?
He just left.
Is Deng around?
Over there. Hang on.
That guy over there...
I saw him. Who let him in?
He’s looking for fighters.
What if he’s a cop?
If Pinoy knows, you're dead.
He’s from Kelantan.
Whatever. Go watch the door.
We got screwed today. How about you?
Business as usual.
What’s the story, Deng?
Bunga Lalang. He had a debt
to settle with Pinoy.
He was supposed to fight to the end.
But that didn’t happen.
Some kids pulled him out of the ring.
Who?
They looked like Malays. Like you.
Pinoy wants him back.
Your other jobs? All done?
I don’t baby-sit. You know my style.
And we know Boss style.
There is no choice.
If the kid acts tough?
Do what you have to.
His manager didn’t show up today.
Maybe he planned it.
The Chinese Bird Guy.
I don’t baby-sit either.
If I were you, Id just finish off the kid.
So, what do you want?
Stop moving.
Where are you taking me?
To a safe place.
The Thais will be looking for us.
Tapa, turn left up ahead.
Then go straight.
None of the border checkpoints will be safe.
They will be all over the place by now.
The border? What are you talking about?
The safest place is back home.
I didn’t ask to be brought here.
I don’t have a choice now.
Why don’t you have a choice?
You can stay here and die.
Or you can go home.
Its up to you.
Lets go.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
My name is...
Say it. Oi!
Maybe the bird doesn’t speak English.
What is... your name?
Bunga Lalang.
My name is... Bunga Lalang.
What do you want?
Where is he?
He’s not here.
I don’t know. And I don’t want to know.
He went his own way.
He doesn’t listen to anyone.
You’re the one who’s not listening.
I asked, where is he?
I...
Tell me. Don’t make this
hard for yourself. Say it.
Bunohan.
Bunohan. Bunohan.
Bunohan
Whose kid are you?
Why are you playing here?
Where do you live?
Over there.
Father, you can move back
into the master bedroom.
I’m here now. Ill take care of the house.
I’m thinking of moving back here to teach.
I can take care of you.
What does your mother say about this?
This is her idea.
Once I get a job,
Anna and Farah will join me here.
Anna can work at the local bank.
I going to start a business.
Can you help me?
Find Adil.
I want to see him.
5 years is quite a while, Father.
If he cared, he would have come back...
Four years and ten months.
Please find him.
Its too late, Yeah
Adil
Adil!
Leh, Don’t mind if I help myself.
Sure. Go ahead.
Patience.
I have to make my way in first.
These things take time.
We have to move fast.
Five years ago I didn’t have the cash.
But now, I do.
You have been in the city for too long.
You cant bring Kuala Lumpur back here.
You asked me to take care of it. So let me.
Its like this. Ill give you a way in.
These people owe money.
So you help them settle their debts,
Then they will be indebted.
Its like shares and the stock market,
Their gratitude is the commodity.
Once they owe us, we reap the dividends.
What’s with the kickboxing club?
That’s how we get in.
Awang Sonar owes me money.
Perfect. We can set up fights at his club.
But you’d want good fighters,
and they don’t come cheap.
Across the border,
they are tied to Thai gangs.
You don’t need to worry.
I’ve got some fighters in mind.
I saw Bunga Lalang.
New shoes, Jolok?
Yeah, check them out. Crocodile leather.
Must be the Golok River crocodile.
Watch it! They just might bite you.
I’m here.
Ill go look for Pok Wah.
You gave that to my son years ago.
I remember.
Was it the year of the rabbit?
Or the eagle?... Owl maybe?
Crocodile.
That’s how the women here still remember you.
I’ve heard all kinds of stories about you.
Mahdi said he worked with you on a ship.
In Mesir, I think.
I bumped into him once.
Not in Mesir.
In Marseille. France.
You? And this boat?
People like you work on ships.
You get to see the world.
But in the end, even the world
gets washed up on the beach.
I’m a lost cause. My woman wont
let me fish at sea anymore.
I remember getting one of these.
But I cant remember where.
You didn’t come here just to
catch up with an old friend.
I’m looking for this kid.
Bunga Lalang.
That’s shouldn’t be difficult.
Try your fathers house.
There’s nothing in that house for me.
What are you talking about?
He was born around the time you left.
In the ring,
he is known as Bunga Lalang.
But his real name is Adil. Your brother.
Did his second wife have another kid,
or did the old pervert get another wife?
That’s why my mother divorced him.
Your dad was quite the crocodile.
But he didn’t take a third wife.
That kid is his son.
So he’s my half brother. What do I care?
Ill get you a mattress.
Are you still doing your old job?
Don’t worry. You wont be involved.
Pok Wah.
Its hard to find peace in this world.
I run away from
the world and still they come.
Are you man or the devil himself?
Someone is not well.
Man is indeed sick.
What do I care?
I don’t do that kind of work anymore.
Please, Pok Wah.
You tell him that I cannot do anything.
Man has made a pact with
the devil to destroy this earth.
I cannot help him.
He has to help himself.
Its Adil who is injured.
Why didn’t you say so earlier?
What’s wrong with you?
It was hard to get a word in
while you made your speech.
What? You think Im a politician,
making speeches?
No sign of you for months, Suddenly,
you come to save me like some hero.
Be grateful.
Its a good thing I knew about the fight
Or should I have left you to die there?
For years I worked my way up,
and made a name for myself over there.
Now you’ve brought me back to this dump.
Thanks a lot, Mr. Muski Abdul Rahman.
Even in the darkness, there will be light.
Leave the bad, and take the good.
Father, some people from
Kuala Lumpur are interested in our land.
It could be a good opportunity for us.
Adil doesn’t care about these things.
He doesn’t even care about our family.
You cant say such things.
You do not know him anymore.
You do not even know who I am.
We are just like the shadows on your screen.
What stories are you making up now, Bakar?
You are the storyteller.
All the villagers talk about your story.
People will say all kinds of things.
You were too young to remember.
You are too old to remember.
The villagers talk about you
and your ex-wife, Mek Yah.
You forget.
The land I gave to you,
you sold. The money, gone.
Now you want the 30 acres.
I might as well give it to llham.
What did that animal ever do for you?
I know that you don’t care about him.
At least I have a plan to do
something with the land.
You know nothing about that land.
Just stay out of it.
If you sell that land,
what will become of our stories?
How will we live?
You should stick to teaching.
We cannot live on stories alone.
If I develop that land,
Then people can see how it should be done.
You cannot pay people to learn, Bakar.
You’re stubborn, Yah.
Like I said, this is the work
of your half-brother, Bakar.
He’s been paying some guys
to move the old graves.
You’re wasting your time.
Your mothers grave is no longer there.
Why is he doing this?
He’s planning a project
on your fathers land.
That’s what I heard.
These are the relocated graves,
originally from the cemetery on your beach.
Look at this. Male and female
tombstones on the same grave.
There, two headstones on one grave.
I’ve been meaning to see you
for some time now.
There’s something I want to discuss,
and ask for your permission.
You have that land by the beach, don’t you?
The 30 acres,
next to Awang Sonars boxing club.
Yes. That one.
If you are interested,
some people are very keen to buy it.
They are willing to pay a deposit 30 percent.
In cash. Immediately.
Here you go.
A drink? You shouldn’t
have troubled yourself.
Bakar.
Talib. But people call me Jolok.
So, if you agree, those Kuala Lumpur
people want to meet you...
And see the land. Better still,
if they can see the land title as well.
Its obvious, he’s going to cheat.
Its always the same old story.
Its like this Jolok.
I cannot make the decision.
The owner of the land is not here.
But it is your land, isn’t it?
It is in my name.
But it is not mine.
What’s the story now?
Its not his land. So whose is it?
Its ok. Ill sort it out.
You said that you saw Adil. Where?
I was across the Thai border.
I had some bets on a kickboxing fight.
I lost everything. Some guys
pulled him out of the ring and ran.
Who is he, Bakar?
I hear that he helps a lot of people.
Father, its time for your medicines.
What’s he doing?
It was supposed to be an easy job.
Looks like he’s planning
to kill the whole village.
Maybe he’s digging his own grave.
But, that’s a lot of graves.
Maybe he’s got a lot of dying to do.
You can go back. Ill handle this.
See, there’s nothing here.
Its my mothers grave. I cant just let it go.
Enough llham. This is pointless.
You’ve been gone for over 20 years.
Nobody even remembers anymore.
Only stories are left.
Some folks say that
she turned into a creature.
Stories like that are a waste of time.
If you want the truth,
you have to find it yourself.
Awang, I have settled your debt with Bakar.
Now you just need to settle it with me.
Bakars helped you villagers a lot.
Now, you should try to help him.
But Bakar didn’t tell me
anything about this.
Bakars too shy to say anything.
He’s not the type to
ask for his money back.
Then let me settle with him.
There’s no need to trouble
yourself like that.
Like this, lets fix up your club.
Then we organize a fight.
We make money out of that.
After the fight,
your debt will be cleared.
Ill need to speak to Pok Wah about this.
We started this club together.
Its best that he knows as well.
Listen carefully, Jolok.
He works hard and Im good
to hardworking people.
He farms fish, doesn’t he?
Life is unpredictable.
Crops can fail.
And so can fish.
Ketot, this is the last batch, right?
Hurry up, Ketot.
This place gives me the creeps.
You’re fine digging up graves.
But here you’re scared?
That place was different.
Gasi, what’s going on over there?
He’s healed so fast.
What kind of medicine did you give him?
Its not easy to
find these things anymore.
Because mankind is
bent on destroying nature.
But if we do right,
the earth will give to us.
Where did you learn this stuff?
Adils mother.
Mek Ani?
Everyone has a mother.
Its even better if
she has a touch of magic.
If you can have both,
you will want for nothing.
I’m also going to need
a touch of magic soon.
I have a fight coming up.
You have a fight?
Yeah, Awang Sonar arranged it.
Its time I started helping my mother.
So I hear you are having a fight.
Joloks setting it up.
We can fix up the club,
and make a bit of money.
If something isn’t broken,
why do we need to fix it?
There’s no harm fixing up the place a bit.
Are you in debt?
Well, kind of.
Just spit it out.
I took a loan from Bakar,
to start my fish farms.
Then Jolok bought over the debt.
Now I have to pay him instead.
This morning, all my fish died.
This is not about our club.
Its the land they are after.
How could you be so stupid?
I asked you to take care of this club.
Not give it away to other people.
I haven’t given it away.
Do you trust that Jolok?
Do you know who he is?
Its not like you think.
We could make a bit of money.
One fight will not make any money.
Were putting four fighters in,
including Adil.
You might as well throw me in.
Then they can really have the land.
You’ve been poisoned
more than your fish.
Father, here’s
a new medicine. Try some.
It wont help.
I feel so strangely tired today.
Father, here are some
documents relating to the land.
Please have a look.
Have you found Adil yet?
I have friends tracking him
down in Thailand.
I need to discuss some things with you.
Those people, they have come up
with quite a good plan.
I’m sure they have.
Ill take a look at it later.
Were going ahead. Don’t worry. Be patient.
Ill give you a bonus as well.
No, don’t come here.
Ill go over to your place.
Stubborn people like you
always look for trouble.
They are the ones looking for trouble.
Even being stubborn
has its time and place.
This is not a normal fight.
The puppet master
is none other than Bakar.
I’ve already told Awang. I’m fighting.
Its thanks to him that were in this mess.
Whatever it is, we still have to fight.
You are the one who taught me to be brave.
I also taught you to find other ways.
What other way is there?
Tell that to my father, or my brother.
There’s no point talking to the deaf.
Adik, why are you playing in here? Get out.
Get out, I said.
Bakar didn’t tell me that you were back.
I need to talk to you.
I’ve given Bakar his share.
Its time I gave you
the 30 acres by the beach.
That’s ok. I don’t want anything from you.
It is your land.
Id like to talk to you
about other things too.
23 years have passed.
And now you want to talk?
This is all the time I have.
I know all about time.
Whether I live or die
is decided in 3 minutes.
Maybe you can give me 3 minutes.
Nobody can force
23 years into 3 minutes.
What have you been
doing all these years?
Mek Ani and Bakar
treated me like a bastard.
You never stopped them.
Back then, I didn’t know.
You didn’t know?
You didn’t know that Mek Ani
wouldn’t let me call her Mother?
Let me honor a promise I once made.
Please take that land.
Your three minutes are up.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
There is nothing here for you.
Why are you here?
I came back to take care of Father.
Our land. Some people want to buy it.
If we sell now, it would help the family.
What damned family?
It could help you too.
Better than breaking
your bones across the border.
Broken bones can mend.
The problem is you.
You break peoples spirit.
If you really want to help,
just write off Awang Sonars debt.
You have to speak to Jolok about that.
I managed to talk him
into coming back to see you.
Its his land.
We cant for him any longer.
Its too late, Bakar.
I have to make a decision now.
This is all that’s left for me to do.
I have no strength left.
Since I was young, i've hated sleeping.
And I hate people who sleep a lot.
Its a waste of time.
Well, it looks like you’re
still not sleeping.
When I first started doing this,
it wasn’t easy.
He begged me for a couple more days,
to see his mother.
After that, it was easy.
Like lighting a cigarette. That’s the truth.
What? Sleeping?
Killing.
Our very own champion,
Adil Bunga Lalang from Bunohan.
What kind of a fight was that?
Were you fighting or running amok?
Who taught you to fight like that?
Stubborn people like you
will never get anywhere.
What are you talking about?
Its your land that’s at stake here.
Maybe you should go
meditate under that tree.
What a fight!
Nice! Nice.
This is Jolok.
I could punch that jerk.
Take it easy, its his money
that’s helping the club.
Helping? To destroy it?
What did she become?
You said she turned into a creature.
What kind of thing?
When did you get cut like that?
How much longer is he staying?
Not much longer.
Keep an eye on him.
I need to get some bandages.
Why are you always
messing around on that boat?
Don’t be so nosy, woman.
Jolok, did you hear about
the two bodies found in the river?
People say it looked
like crocodiles got them.
Leh, there are only
two crocodiles around here.
Me. And the one I wear on my feet.
If you say so.
Brother, we made history in Bunohan.
We won big.
After deducting my investment,
you get 7 percent of the profits.
That’s a lot. Normally,
you would only get about 3 or 4 percent.
But, what about my boys?
Yes, your fighters certainly won.
Instead, he beat the
other kid so bad, he’s in hospital.
I’m paying for that too.
But you promised.
We organize a fight,
then my debt is settled.
Awang, we live in
the 21st century now.
This is what saddens me
about our people.
They don’t think long term.
But its ok Awang.
Like this. We do another fight.
This time, only two fighters.
A smaller investment,
with higher returns. Sounds good, no?
Awang!
Forget it.
Awang.
The 21st century sure has its challenges.
Here, let me give it a shot.
Its not that complicated.
Hey, Bakar, can this thing find people?
That dickbrain Gasi disappeared.
Must be shagging in Golok.
Give it back.
Once we control it,
we control the whole area.
Bakar, what’s the story with
the kickboxing clubs land.
If we don’t have that,
we don’t have access to your land, right?
Were just waiting
to sign the papers, sir.
If its not sorted in a couple of days,
were pulling out. Understand?
Jolok.
Were running out of time.
Tomorrow, I want you to
put up a fence and a signboard.
And clear a road to this place. Got it?
Your dad? What’s the deal?
Should we pray?
Yeah, you pray. I will answer.
That’s weird. Gasi and Ketot
moved all the graves the other day.
Well, maybe you need to pray some more.
Call a shaman.
Get him to cleanse the land.
You are doing a shadow
play in the daytime?
No, it isn’t the right time for it.
But in Java, they do it in the daytime
to chase away the evil spirits.
But how will we see anything?
There are no shadows.
What a clever boy you are.
We don’t do that over here.
That’s why there is so much evil everywhere.
Don’t worry, ill help you to fight.
I have some puppets.
Where did you get those?
I found them in the other room.
Whose are they?
I made them back
when I was teaching my sons.
Why didn’t you color them in?
I never finished.
This is my mothers land.
She moved here after
Mek Ani married your father.
Look at all this.
Your brother Bakars handiwork.
Your mother would be
so pleased if she knew.
I don’t have anything
to do with them anymore.
I got out of here as soon
as I could. Just like you.
I kill people.
So i’ve heard.
Your own brothers life,
what’s it worth?
Everything.
You destroyed everything.
You chased my mother out.
She shouldn’t have had to live like this.
All alone. Dead without a trace.
I shouldn’t have...
Do your dirty work somewhere else.
He claims this is his mothers land.
Father!
Is Father in?
What do you want?
Why does he want to give me that land?
Ilham says it is his mothers,
that it belongs to her.
I want to speak to Father.
He doesn’t need to speak to you.
I want to know whose son I am.
Father! I have a right to know.
Who am I? Father! Answer me!
Father!
I have a right to know.
Who am I? Father! Answer me!
Adil is not my real brother.
Whose son is he?
Who is Adil?
It looks like I have to baby-sit now.
Why didn’t you just do your job?
It could have been so simple.
Come here, take him out, leave.
What’s that?
Herbs.
This guy is injured, and
you’re giving him stuff that goats eat?
If you crush them and apply to
his wound, hell heal really fast.
Where did you learn this stuff?
His mother taught me.
She was the best traditional healer.
Here, go buy some real medicine.
I need to find Bunga Lalang after this.
Before my boss sends
someone else down here.
You’re looking for him as well?
What do you want with him?
Don’t worry. You wont be involved.
You guys are all the same.
How did llham end up like that?
Who knows when it comes to lllham.
Just take care of him well.
I want to see llham.
Now, what do you want?
Pok Wah, is there anything
you want to tell me?
You father should be
the one to tell you.
When Mek Yah gave birth to you,
Pok Eng asked my mother to help.
We are Chinese.
We can keep your secrets.
Jing...
If we wait for you,
when will it ever come out?
You were born out of wedlock.
Mek Yah is your real mother.
You were born after they divorced.
Wah, my mother promised Mek Yah..
if Adil ever asked...
I know.
I guess this is the time.
If you care about that kid, make sure
I never see him across the border.
Your friend Kruba just called me.
He might be coming down
in the next couple of days.
He needs to settle
some unfinished business.
That would be my work.
I hear you have some jobs to do.
Must be tough, bearing
the burden of two jobs at once.
What if I help carry Miss Bunga?
He has unfinished business with me.
That should help lighten your burden.
How about it?
Its ok. He’s a friend.
I can take care of my own problems.
Were practically brothers.
We speak the same language.
Only our dialect is slightly different.
Today, you are here on
this side of the border.
Tomorrow, my people will
be over there, on your side.
Friend, we have always helped each other.
You just take care of llham.
For the coffee.
Jolok, if you were in politics, you’d win.
That would be you.
I cant. I’m much too honest.
Here’s the fruit you asked about.
Its not easy to find.
What do you want with it?
Its poisonous, you know.
I’m using it as medicine.
Here’s the money.
Enough?
Yes, thank you.
I would prefer to have
the Main Puteri ritual.
But I I can tell you,
you will need many shamans.
More than the usual.
You promised a bonus.
You finish the job first.
Muski, your brothers
haven’t brought the goats back.
Its getting dark. Can you go find them?
Alright.
You have to help me.
I need the money. My mothers ill.
Do this job well, and I will
give you more than a bonus.
I have a new project coming up and
ill need help. People like you.
But first you have to
prove your loyalty. How about it?
Did you know my mother very well?
I’ve heard people say
all kinds of things about her.
Don’t listen to them.
Your mother was not like other people.
She had her own way.
But she wasn’t a bad person.
That’s the problem with our people.
They fear things
they don’t even understand.
How fear turns into hate,
I have yet to find the source.
Do you have any idea
who Im fighting against?
I’m troubled that they
haven’t made a decision yet.
I’m not that worried.
All I ask for is a clean fight.
That I cannot promise.
Have faith. You have to fight well.
After this fight, I want
to go back and see Father.
Come, its deep enough now.
Let me drive.
If you didn’t do this,
what would you be doing?
Id have gone to see the world.
I should have come back more often.
But its ok, shell be back soon.
Mines bigger.
Mines sharper.
Father.
Father!
Its getting dark. You’d better go home.
I want to watch.
You want to see, come back tomorrow.
Go now, its getting dark.
You haven’t paid anyone to
pull you off the ring this time?
Come place your bets.
Come on, come on.
Gentlemen, tonight were
expecting a spectacular fight.
In the red corner...
Muski the Black Stallion!
And in the blue corner,
its none other than...
Bunga Lalang!
That’s the end of the second round.
Don’t be the frog under the coconut shell.
If you want to go, you should.
There’s an endless ocean out there.
Its not my calling yet, I guess.
Its fate that Im here with you.
I should be in Paris now, sipping wine by -
What’s that river called?
I don’t know how to say it either.
Yeah, yeah, in your dreams.
Round three!
Perhaps you were fated to be here,
or is it my fate that brought you here?
This is the way we are. Our lives caught
in the web of other peoples stories.
But my story ends here.
Your brother?
Leave him. Let him go.
What's happened to Adil?
What’s wrong Pok Wah?
Poison? Poison!
Carry him!
When you married the other woman,
I knew all would be shattered.
Come. Go with me.
Its too late Yah.
Its late, but its not over yet.
Healing needs time.
And time needs healing.
Look at me.
I am ravaged, torn and ripped apart.
But still, I am here.
There are no more like me.
I am the last of my kind.
You are stubborn, Yah. Hard as a rock.
For people like me,
this is the only way to live.
Otherwise, I would have
ended up just like the others.
Throwing away the land,
throwing away our stories.
I have always loved you.
I was never ashamed of our love.
Even if I had to become a creature
that crawled the earth.
You forgot how we spoke,
Loved and sang to
the spirits of the earth.
Speak to me. Sing to me.
I must release the spirits
trapped inside you,
And return them to the land.
I have no strength left.
I will give you strength.
Till we speak again with meaning,
Our words will mark like
footprints on the earth.
Our breath will stir the leaves,
move the waters, and hold up
the birds in their flight.
Our love will set the world ablaze.
Father.
Why are you disturbing me
out here, Bakar? I’m working.
Father, I want that land. I don’t care.
You’re so crude. Is the land
all you can think of?
How did it end like this?
I heard the voices of the shadow
puppets coming from his body.
The voices of the different characters.
Now I cant really hear them.
I’m not as strong as I used to be.
Then we have to help.
If we don’t, all will be lost.
We have to perform the healing ritual.
How are we going to do that?
Mek Yahs not here. No one's left.
Well just have to find away to do it.
Its time. Lets go now.
"Proposed Development for Marina and Resort
Complex of 200 Chalets and Golf Course"