Subs created by: David Coleman.
She's really pissed off.
Panic and confusion.
I turned around and whoomp.
Definitely an impact.
Had a heart attack and that was it.
I see pools of blood.
People were quitting on me left and right.
You don't want to walk through the door.
He came behind me, trying to grab my back.
They came to watch a boy die.
There's something down there.
My name is Amy Allan.
A lot of dead people are here.
I see dead people..
This is not good.
I speak to dead people..
He is very pissed off.
And they speak to me.
The house is angry.
But there's only way to know
if my findings are real.
He's killed people.
I rely on my partner.
I'm Steve Dischiavi.
I'm a retired New York
City homicide Detective.
He got shot at his house?
And I know every person,
every house, has secrets.
Aren't you terrified, being here?
It's my job to reveal 'em.
That sounds like something
out of "The Exorcist".
But Steve and I never speak..
We never communicate
during an investigation..
Until the very end..
It's bad.
When we uncover if it's
safe for you to stay..
I'd like some answers.
Or time to get out.
Amy and I remain completely
separate during our investigations.
I gather the facts through research
and interviews with key witnesses.
After we're done..
We'll meet with our clients to
disclose our findings to them..
And to each other for the first time.
I'm just about an hour North of New York
City in a small town called Carmel.
I'm on my way to meet
with a guy named Anthony
who works Security at a
restaurant called Smalley's Inn.
Anthony's a tough guy.
I can tell just by the way he talks.
But he's so scared about the things
that are happening in the restaurant,
he's thinking about quitting.
This restaurant contains a lot of
photographs and personal items.
So I have to be careful to remove or cover
anything that could
influence Amy's findings.
Once the location is cleared.
Amy can begin her walk.
I saw..
This female.
And I've seen her before at home.
It was her and two men..
Surrounding my bed.
And they were trying to kill me.
Whether I'm at home or
traveling to a location,
the dead know I'm coming long before I do.
So sometimes they'll appear
to me days before my walk.
And if they feel threatened, they'll
try and stop me any way they can.
She was, like, white and transparent.
And she really hates me.
She's here.
She seems to cause..
Death.
- Anthony.
- Hey, Steve. How you doing?
Good to meet you.
When we spoke on the phone, you
sounded a little concerned.
- Yes.
- Um, what.. What's going on here?
A lot of things are happening here.
I've seen apparitions.
I've seen things getting
pushed off a table.
I have been shoved from behind.
- You're kidding.
- Swear to God.
I hate to say that I'm scared, but, yeah.
I grew up in the streets of the Bronx,
and I had a gun pointed at my head..
But it's when you can't see the stuff
- that it will drive you crazy.
- Yeah.
You don't want to walk through
the door to come to work.
I know exactly how Anthony feels.
I've been in a few shootouts myself.
But I think if I ever actually saw a
ghost, it'd scare the hell outta me.
All right, so this is
actually hurting your income.
Yes. I've cut my hours down, yes.
I need to support my wife and three kids.
I can't afford to lose this job.
She cries.
Really nasty.
She is..
What..
People would call a Banshee.
Most people have heard of
Banshees from Irish folklore.
They're actually a kind of omen.
If you hear one, someone you love will die.
If you see one, you are going to die.
You all right?
No.
She's happy causing chaos.
She really hates..
Living people.
It's really strange.
I think she's here.
Where?
Downstairs.
This is why I cut.. I cut my hours.
- Because of the basement?
- Yeah.
All right, can you show me?
All right. Let's go.
Watch your head.
Wow.
All right.
All right. So happened to you down here?
One of the barmaids asked
me to get, uh, some ice.
Okay.
And I came down here.
I reached about where the ice machine is..
And a woman that was, very like, proper..
Uh, whispered something in my ear.
I turned around, and whoomp..
I got tossed.
I mean, God, I'm a big guy.
Yeah. I mean, I got 210.
You gotta be at least 275, 280, right?
Easy, easy.
It threw me Back here. And, um..
She walked right by me.
She doesn't make eye contact
or nothing like that..
Nothing. Like I'm not even there. Like..
Like she does it every day. Like every..
This.. This is where she belongs to go.
Mm. I just felt like that kind
of bash-in-the-head thing.
Ow.
Someone here has caused a
great deal of physical pain.
And now I can feel it
running all across my body.
And I have this, like, pain, like, whoa.
Ow.
(Bleep)
Definitely an impact.
Describe the way the woman looked.
She was dressed, like, in the 1800s look..
The big puffy dress..
- Okay.
- Nice hat.
What color was her hair?
Blondish, and I could see through her.
What'd you do?
I took off like a bat outta hell.
Wow.
She's..
Up in everybody's (Bleep).
She's really pissed off.
And she..
Sees an opening and takes advantage of it.
It's like revenge, seek revenge.
So what else have you seen down here?
I've seen, um, a male apparition.
And the same (Bleep).
I came down here to get some liquor,
and I almost struck..
Like, bumped into him.
Like, I thought it was a customer.
Can you describe the guy to me?
Yes, the hat was half on.
Curly white hair, jacket.
The ruffles in the shirt.
And I'm.. And I'm ready to pop him, I'm
ready, you know, to smash this guy, and..
He went that way.
I went after him. Nothing.
Gone.
And now I know this is theirs.
I don't belong down here.
- If that happened to me..
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know if I could even come
back down in the basement like this.
Well, I don't.
And there goes my pay.
And there goes putting food on the table.
There's a man in uniform down here.
What kind of uniform?
He's wearing, like, a poufy outfit.
With, like, it comes out.
The arms come out.
Then a rifle with a, uh..
Could cut.. Kill you.
Like a knife on the end?
Mm-hmm.
But I don't feel good about it.
Because he made me feel uncomfortable
when I was walking down the stairs.
- Mm-hmm.
He feels like maybe the
basement's his area or something.
He follows people. He likes to intimidate.
It's all, like, sneak
attacks, though, for him.
Sneaky in the dark,
sneaky behind your back.
He gives off panic and confusion.
Makes me feel..
Scared.
Mm. I just got, like,
this really angry male.
He makes me feel..
Scared.
The vibe he gives off is
this panic and confusion.
He's not confused, but he
kind of puts that out there.
You know what I mean? Like..
That feeling.
Very intimidating.
I don't know what his problem is.
And I don't know why he's still here..
Or even how he got here.
Now I understand there's a lot of
strange things going on in this place.
Have you experienced anything?
I've seen, uh, an apparition at the bar..
A man wearing a suit and a tie.
I couldn't see his face.
There used to be some video
games next to the bar.
When you played the video game,
you'd see another face..
Looking out at you.
And you're just thinking, all
right, someone's looking over
my shoulder and seeing what I'm
doing with this video game.
And then you'd take a break,
and that person's not there.
And a lot of times when I tell these
stories, the hair on my arm..
I just get goosebumps.
I can see 'em.
Tony, are you concerned that business
is hurt by any of these stories?
- It did scare off a lot of customers.
- Okay.
People have got tugged on their
sleeves, pulled on their aprons..
Tapped on the shoulder, stuff like that.
Oh, what happened?
I don't know.
He came behind me and was, like..
Trying to grab my back.
It feels like this soldier guy..
Or Captain, whatever he is.
I don't know, he's hiding.
- Hmm.
- Do you know where he went?
No.
This angry soldier doesn't
like me wandering around.
He's already attacked me once, and
I'm concerned he'll do it again.
Hmm. Weird.
He's just..
Hiding.
People were quitting on me left and right.
A girl was getting ice
from the ice machine.
She glanced off into the back
where the liquor cabinet is..
And noticed a soldier standing
there, looking at her.
So did she describe what she saw?
A blue uniform with a yellow stripe
going down the, uh, side of the pants.
So civil war or an.. An..
An older army uniform.
Yes.
- The girl quit that night.
- She did?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Did anything like that happen to
anybody else that worked for you?
Yeah, I had one waitress, and
she got tormented a lot.
In what way? Anything in particular?
Things getting thrown at her.
The ice scoop from the ice machine
was actually thrown at her.
Is she around so I could talk to her?
No, no. She's no longer with us.
She died?
Yeah. She passed, uh, prematurely..
And by accident.
So, Tony, Mr. Smalley, I assume, who the
restaurant's named after, is that..
Yeah. He actually purchased
the place in 1852.
And how long have you owned this place?
Well, it's been in the
family since, uh, 1965.
It's clear Anthony and Tony have had
their share of experiences here.
But I need to talk to someone who wouldn't
be influenced by workplace rumors.
So I found a contractor who did
some work in the basement.
But was too scared to finish the job.
- So you were contracted to do work here?
- Yeah.
Now what happened while
you were on the job?
The first couple of weeks were fine.
We got a lot of stuff done.
After a few more weeks went on,
I noticed that, within two or three hours,
I would get sort of a negative feeling..
A sadness feeling, sort
of like a depression.
I didn't want to see people
and I would get very tired..
Extremely tired, like, as
if, I worked a whole day.
And.. And this, strangely enough, is,
you know, when I would get in the car
and leave here, then, you know, within
45 minutes, I'd begin to feel better.
- Had you ever felt like that before?
- No.
Are.. Are you starting to feel any of
those feelings now while we're down here?
I do feel a little sensation.
I feel tired already.
- You do?
- I do.
I feel like that soldier guy..
I think he feels like maybe the
basement's his.. His thing.
Do you think that he makes himself
known to people in the basement?
I think that they might feel
him before they see him.
I don't think he really likes to be seen.
They got a problem with
the lights down here.
They would just fizzle out and burn up.
- You know that that doesn't happen.
- Yeah, that doesn't really happen.
Now if a regular bulb explodes, when they..
When they normally burn out,
they make, like, a flash,
- like a camera flash.
- Right.
These ones would just, like you..
If you had it on a dimmer.
We're talking, like, two
or three bulbs a night.
- A night?
- A night.
Anything else strange?
I did have a pile of lumber on
the other side of the room.
There was about seventy-five
2x4s on the floor over there.
And the first night I started,
they were on that side.
The next night I came back, all the 2x4s,
just as neatly stacked as I had 'em..
Were on the other side here.
Like I was disturbing something.
Jeff, I gotta ask you, what..
What made you stop working here?
I couldn't get anything done.
I can't continue to do work at a place
where we can't get anything done.
And then, uh, depression.
I just wanted to leave and go home.
Now would you normally walk off a job?
That's absolutely not my personality.
I've never walked off a job before.
His favorite place is the basement.
And he is very protective of it.
He doesn't like anybody down there.
And he moves stuff.
This soldier believes it's his job to
guard the basement against any intruders.
And he'll do anything
to protect that space.
His technique is to..
Is to freak people out in the dark.
It feels very claustrophobic.
Like you can't see your way out to escape.
I don't really like being in
the dark here for some reason.
Being in the dark here is uncomfortable.
And that's odd, because I
don't really care about that.
It feels like this..
Soldier guy his, uh..
Technique is to..
Is to freak people out in the dark.
Tony told me that the original owner of
the Inn was a guy named James Smalley.
So I'm headed over to meet
with a local historian
who knows everything about this guy's past.
As you know, I'm doing the investigation
- on the Smalley's Inn.
- Mm-hmm.
I was talking to the
owner, and, uh, he said
the place was originally
owned by James Smalley.
James Smalley bought the building in 1852.
And he turned it into an Inn,
a Tavern, and a Restaurant.
- Okay.
- And here's a picture of James.
By all accounts, he was magnanimous.
He was, uh, outgoing.
People said he would do
anything for anyone.
He was quite active in the community..
Uh, town supervisor,
Sheriff, treasurer, assemblyman.
He even recruited soldiers
for the civil war.
Do we know when he died?
He died in 1867.
Of what was called a sudden
morning heart attack.
In.. In the building itself.
Do we know how old he was when he died?
He was about 54.
One morning, he woke up.
Had a heart attack, and that was it.
I also get this guy.
Um, I don't know if he worked
here or owned the place..
Uh, but he was very much in
charge and was here all the time.
And he also is more, like..
Residual.
The vibe around him was really happy, good,
you know, care.. Like, just really awesome.
But he died here.
He died here.
And how did he die?
Oh, I think he had a heart attack.
So did James Smalley have a family?
Yes.
His first wife was named Harriet, and
they had nine children together.
Two of them died in infancy.
Now do we know what
Harriet passed away from?
We don't know, but she died in 1850.
And then he married
Harriet's sister, Emily.
And had an additional six children.
So things must have been
very crowded in the Inn.
Yeah. That's, what, 15 kids?
Right. Unfortunately, two of
James and Emily's children..
Died very young of diphtheria.
Linda, what exactly is diphtheria?
It's a disease that's contracted
through contaminated food.
It affects the respiratory system.
Similar to what we would
think of with pneumonia..
Very difficult to breathe,
affects the nose, the throat.
A very painful, slow death
for the two children.
It's weird, because I see,
like, people living down here.
What do you mean?
Like, they all lived down here.
Maybe like ten people..
Are sleeping down here.
Do you know if they have any
relationship to each other?
Yeah.
It feels like, uh, maybe one family.
Okay.
I do see some people who are sick.
What kind of sick?
Like flu.
Just like a passing..
I think a couple of kids died from it.
Again, just getting this, like, loud..
People yelling.
This is a long time ago.
It is weird, though, because I
do see, like, pools of blood.
Where?
On the floor.
The blood on the floor is, like, an
indicator of how many people died here.
Linda mentioned James Smalley was
very active in The Civil War.
That caught my attention because
Tony said several people reported
seeing an apparition of a soldier in
an old-fashioned military uniform.
I need to find out exactly
what his involvement was.
So I'm off to meet with an elected
official who happens to be a war buff.
He promised he could fill me in.
I'm doing an investigation
at the Smalley's Inn,
and I learned that James Smalley was
pretty active during The Civil War.
Oh, he was extremely
active in The Civil War.
He handled the draft rolls, get the
young people from the County to enlist.
Okay, so his role was to actually
get men to go off and fight?
Yes.
Did Smalley actually serve in the war?
He was too old to serve in the war.
So, Richie, did he serve any other way?
Oh, yes, he did.
He, uh, he actually had a
mortuary underneath the Inn.
Now that was in the basement?
Yes.
Soldiers that died of their
wounds in hospitals,
who were shipped home for burial.
Were put up temporarily in
his morgue beneath the Inn.
Okay.
Mm. Someone's talking
about something medical.
What do you mean?
Mm..
I'm seeing tables here..
Like, a long table.
There's a lot of people here, and there's..
Oh, my God.
They're bringing in these men.
People are freaking out, and they're..
Been injured.
And, like, someone's digging
a bullet out of somebody.
It's gross and dirty and disgusting.
After meeting with Richie,
I wanted to see what other
information I could find
out about Smalley's Inn.
So I went to the local library to see
what I could uncover in their records.
Digging through the archives, I
came across several articles
about a convicted murderer
by the name of George Denny.
Who was executed at the Courthouse right
down the street from Smalley's Inn.
It turns out, there's a local author who's
actually writing a book about this case.
I've reached out to him,
and he tells me, there's
a lot of weird twists
and turns to the story.
So, Vin, I came across an
article, uh, from the 1800s,
where this kid, George Denny, got executed.
It looks like it was the only
one in Carmel's history.
So what were the circumstances
of the homicide? What happened?
In October of 1843, an 80-year-old
man named Abraham Wanzer.
Is in his cabin, middle of the
woods, and someone calls him out.
When he walks outside, he's shot
point-blank in the chest with a shotgun.
So they arrest 17-year-old George Denny.
Who was virtually a homeless boy.
Bring him here, put him in the
jail behind the Courthouse.
They have a trial in November.
Hung jury, let him go.
I had read they had a second trial.
Yeah, then they do a second trial..
And in the second trial, the jury said..
Hang him.
On the day of the execution.
4,000 people..
Came here, here, in front
of this Courthouse.
All night long, wagons came in and out.
And it was like a.. A circus.
They came from everywhere
to watch a boy die.
So they have him on the
steps of the Courthouse.
Then they put the rope around his neck.
They take the boy with the
noose around his neck..
Led him down the steps..
In front of Smalley's Inn.
Then they parade him to the
back where the gallows are.
And they execute him.
So, Vin, after his execution,
what happens to the body?
There is no grave for this boy.
There is no monument of any kind.
We're not even sure what
cemetery he might be in.
Amy, who would you like to draw?
Well, I would like to draw a woman.
She looks like a Banshee.
Okay.
She's very, very thin..
Very thin mouth.
Her nose is long and pointy.
And the hair?
She has long, long white hair.
Does she have, um, an
expression on her face?
If anything, kind of sad.
Is this who you saw?
Yes, it is.
Now that our investigation is finished,
it's time for Amy and me to
present what we've discovered
to the clients and each other.
Now these two tough-looking guys
that are sitting in front of you.
Have, uh, called us in.
Anthony here works Security
for the restaurant.
- Mm-hmm.
- He's a tough kid, but..
He's pretty frightened by some of the
things that have happened to him here.
And he's actually considering quitting
because it's that frightening for him.
Okay.
Tony owns the place.
He's been here for a lot of years.
But he's concerned about maybe losing
customers because of what's going on here.
With that, I'm gonna turn it over to
Amy and, uh, hear about her walk.
Well, um, there was something I
encountered before the walk.
I was at home, and these
three dead people showed up.
And one of 'em was a female.
And she was standing beside my bed. And..
They don't want me to continue doing
what I'm doing because I'm, like..
Telling people how to make them go away.
I get here, and I do my
opening, and she's there.
And she's, like, you know, hates
me and wants me dead and..
So you're saying she's here?
Yeah.
- Oh, jeez.
- And I'm like, "oh, okay".
She hates all living people.
She's pissed off and really depressed.
So she does cry a lot and,
like, moans or wails.
And she had long hair..
That looked white.
And I could see through her..
Which was really weird.
Most people think that the dead usually
show themselves as transparent.
But that's actually very rare.
To me, they usually appear
as solid as living people.
She was showing herself to me
in a very interesting way.
You said it was transparent?
Yeah.
Have you ever heard of a Banshee?
I've heard the term.
A Banshee is, like..
A Grim Reaper.
Usually in, like, Ireland or Scotland.
They wander about..
- Yeah.
- And they scream and they cry.
If somebody sees them..
That person's gonna die.
If somebody hears them, someone close
to that person is going to die..
Very soon.
Banshee's don't intervene
and cause a person to die.
They just, like, are notifying them.
This one is also potentially causing..
Them to die.
And she'll go around the area.
It's not just here.
She's affecting other
locations around here.
So that's great. I could take this
woman to my house with my kids, right?
Yes, you can.
Um, well, actually, I sketched her.
Yeah, when Amy does a
sketch, I don't see it.
Oh, my God.
This is freaking me out.
It's not really like a sketch
I've seen you do before.
Well, she was transparent.
The woman I saw downstairs..
Was transparent. I could see through her.
Her eyes were just all white.
You're almost, like, describing a witch.
That's a scary looking picture.
What else did you, uh, see on your walk?
I encountered a..
Big guy who had dark hair,
and he was really happy.
Um, big smile on his face all
the time, really good vibes.
And I got that he was
an owner of this place.
And he had a heart attack.
- You saw that?
- Yeah.
It sounds like..
One of the original owners, who this
place is named after, James Smalley.
That's how people described the guy.
Everybody liked him.
Here's a picture of Smalley.
He died of what they called..
A sudden morning heart attack.
His first wife died.
He had nine kids with her.
He wound up marrying her sister..
A couple of years later and had
another six kids with her.
This is his second wife..
Emily.
I heard and seen this lady.
You saw her?
I saw her downstairs.
This is his second wife..
Emily.
Oh.
I've heard and seen this lady.
You saw her?
I saw her downstairs.
She had a hat on.
You know, very well-dressed.
Beautiful gown like they wore back then.
And one of the.. One of the reasons
we're here, he was in the basement..
And he got shoved.
As I'm.. Filling up the ice..
I hear a whisper in my ear.
I got flung like I was..
Like I was nothing.
Now why'd you say "oh"
when you saw the photo?
Well, I felt, when I saw
this photo, that it was her.
It looks like her, though.
Looking at her, the mouth,
the nose, the eyes..
Even the hair parted down the
middle, for that matter.
I was relieved to see that photo
because that was the woman I saw.
And living people can
never become Banshees.
This makes me believe she was
just projecting herself as one.
In order to scare people away.
Now moving forward on the walk,
uh, anything else after that?
I saw long tables.
Uh, and then I saw three pools of blood.
And these men were brought in.
They were bloody, messed up.
The room was disgusting.
I mean, it was dirty, really, really dirty.
We were talking about Smalley.
The guy was the Sheriff, you know,
he was on the City Council.
He.. He was also the Coroner.
During The Civil War, the
basement acted as the morgue.
For the soldiers that were
getting ready for burial.
Oh.
What else did you see?
In the, uh, basement..
I see this guy, and he's, like, a soldier.
I'm walking back up the stairs..
And he pushes me.
And what I felt was his
hands go inside my back,
and then he's pushing me, pushing
me, pushing me, pushing me out.
He follows people. He likes to intimidate.
It's all, like, sneak
attacks, though, for him.
He gives off panic and confusion.
Makes me feel..
Scared.
He.. He's really good
at that kind of stuff.
There was a.. A.. A waitress.. Who saw..
A soldier standing in the back
room by that liquor cabinet.
She was messed with a lot.
The basement area, it's his territory.
You can definitely..
Feel him.
Before you have an experience with him.
It's funny, because I interviewed a
contractor that was working for Tony.
And, uh, who won't come back here.
He's working in the basement,
and the lights would just dim.
And just go out four or five times a night.
And he's never seen that before.
He had 78 pieces of 2x4 lumber.
That were literally moved overnight.
From one side..
Of the basement to the other side.
He knows how to physically
manipulate his surroundings.
Moving plates or..
Or chairs or glasses.
This person kind of reminds me of him.
And I don't know how I can't explain that.
He was really big, uh, during
The Civil War, he recruited
guys to fight in the war, but
he was too old to serve.
Could he be the guy wearing the uniform?
Possibly.
I believe the happy man I encountered was
residual energy from when he was alive.
But in death, he showed himself to me as
an angry soldier to protect his property.
So, Amy, you didn't happen to
pick up anything on a hanging?
No hanging, no, no. Not at all.
Well, there was this guy, Abraham Wanzer.
And he was killed by a
kid named George Denny.
George Denny was convicted
and tried of the murder.
Right before they hung him, they
paraded him right in front of here.
There was 4,000 people here
to watch this execution.
And they dragged him around with the noose
around his neck, then they hung him.
Why do you think you didn't know..
You didn't get the kid that got hung?
So when I walk in, it's like everybody's
talking, there's a lot of images..
And so I just try to hone in on..
What I feel is important.
You just never know what you're gonna get.
No one sensitive,
is ever a hundred percent accurate.
And if they are, you better wonder why.
Well, Anthony, Tony, the good
news is, you're not crazy.
There's obviously stuff going on here.
The question is, is it
safe for you to be here?
For that, I'm gonna turn
it over to Amy and see
what she thinks about how to resolve this.
She is your first priority to deal with.
Honestly, when I saw the photo,
I kinda got a little excited..
Because then I'm like, well,
maybe she's not a real Banshee.
Yeah, well, that's good, because
I'm actually getting nauseous.
But it doesn't matter if
she's not a real Banshee.
Because she..
Is still doing what she's doing.
So the biggest thing.. To take care of in..
Is this person.
And it's not gonna be easy.
Be very, very careful.
You know, my suggestion
is to find a priest.
And you need a medium at the same time.
The medium is basically going
to make contact with..
Her.
You know, find out what
her issues are, let..
Basically, let her vent.
And they're both gonna ask her to please..
Leave.
You also have to get rid of the soldier.
The priest is gonna do a blessing.
And that's going to help,
with him to leave.
He needs to go.
This is your time.
It's not theirs.
It's time for them to go.
You don't tolerate this.
Well, are you guys gonna
listen to Amy's advice?
Absolutely.
What about you? Are you gonna do
the right thing and participate?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, good.
The transparent woman who attacked
me is still extremely dangerous.
Anthony and Tony need to follow my advice.
Or she could do a lot of damage.
Not only to the restaurant, but also
to its employees and customers.
Subs created by: David Coleman.