TRY AS THEY WILL,
AND TRY AS THEY MIGHT,
WHO STEALS ME GOLD WON'T LIVE
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
A LIMOUSINE!
WHAT IN THE WORLD
HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU,
MR. O'GRADY?
JUST THE START.
JUST THE START,
MY DEAR.
TAKE THE LAST LOOK
AT THIS DUMP.
TOMORROW, WE'LL BE
LOOKING AT MANSIONS.
MANSIONS?
WILL YOU LISTEN TO YOURSELF?
AND A LIMOUSINE!
WE'VE GOT NO MONEY
FOR THIS!
RIGHT INSIDE.
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
DID THE FUNERAL PARLOR
DELIVER THE PACKAGE?
AYE.
'TIS ON THE PORCH
WHERE THEY LEFT IT.
WILL YOU TELL ME WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE, DANIEL O'GRADY?
WILL THAT
BE ALL, SIR?
AH. JONES.
BON VOYAGE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, SIR.
YOU HAVE A NICE EVENING.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE
IS WE'RE RICH.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BURY YOUR MOTHER.
NOT SEND HER ASHES ALL
THE WAY FROM IRELAND.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
IT'S NOT ME MOTHER'S ASHES.
GOLD, LEAH! GOLD!
WHAT IN THE
LORD'S NAME...
A POT OF GOLD!
A WEE PERSON,
A LEPRECHAUN!
I CAUGHT HIM...
AND MADE HIM SHOW ME
WHERE HIS GOLD IS!
IT'S THE RULE, YOU KNOW.
AH, YOU'RE
A DRUNKEN FOOL
AND A STORYTELLER.
- IT'S THE TRUTH I'M TELLIN'!
- THERE'S A STORM BREWING.
I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH!
COME ON TO BED, NOW,
AND I'LL MAKE YOU
A POT OF NICE HOT TEA.
LEPRECHAUNS, INDEED.
POT OF GOLD!
WHATEVER NEXT?
DAN? DAN, IS THAT YOU?
I CAN'T BREATHE.
PLEASE OPEN THE SUITCASE.
I'M GOING TO SUFFOCATE.
LIKE THE GOLD BUCKLES
ON ME SHOES?
I WANT ME GOLD...NOW!
OH, GOD, NO!
NO PROBLEM.
I SMELL
SOME TEA BREWING.
I HID THE GOLD, LEAH.
WE'RE RICH NOW.
WHERE DID YOU
HIDE IT, DAN?
DID YOU HIDE IT SOMEWHERE
NEAR THE HOUSE?
TELL ME WHERE
YOU HID THE GOLD
HOW DID YOU FIND ME?
THE WEE PEOPLE HAVE
THEIR MAGICAL WAYS.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
WITH MY WIFE?
OH, THE POOR LASS.
I SHOULD'VE TOLD HER
TO WATCH HER STEP.
I'LL GET YA!
IT'S MY GOLD!
I'LL FIX HIM!
I'LL GET HIM!
YOUR WIFE MAKES
A FINE POT OF TEA,
- WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
- I'LL FIX YOU, YOU BASTARD!
HERE'S WHAT YOU'LL GET,
YOU MONSTER.
GET IT AWAY!
PUT IT AWAY!
I GOT THE GOLD
FAIR AND SQUARE.
THEM WERE THE RULES.
CATCH ME IF YOU CAN!
YOU CAN'T GET AWAY.
LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
Y-Y-YOU KILLED MY WIFE.
HELLO, DAN. I'M OK.
I JUST GOT A LITTLE KINK
IN ME NECK.
I SHOULD'VE KILLED YOU
WHEN I CAUGHT YOU IN IRELAND.
GIVE HIM THE GOLD, DAN.
HE'S A NICE LITTLE LEPRECHAUN.
I'LL GIVE YOU
MORE THAN GOLD!
YOUR BULLETS WON'T
STOP ME FOREVER.
I'LL KEEP COMING BACK.
THE POWER OF THIS CLOVER
WILL KEEP YOU IN THERE
FOREVER.
GET THAT DAMN CLOVER
OFF THIS CRATE!
WHERE'S ME GOLD,
DANNY ME BOY?
DON'T STRAIN YOURSELF, NOW.
NO.NOT GASOLINE.
YOU CAN'T BURN ME.
I WON'T LET YA.
DON'T STRAIN YOURSELF.
YOU'RE NOT AS YOUNG
AS YOU USED TO BE.
YOU MIGHT HAVE A STROKE.
I CURSE YE
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
I'VE TRADED ME SOUL
FOR ME GOLD.
YOU'LL TRADE YOUR LIFE.
IF YOU GIVE ME ME GOLD BACK,
I'LL GO AWAY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
BURN IN HELL,
YOU LITTLE GREEN BASTARD!
DID THE MATCH
GO OUT, DANNY?
10 años después
DAD, I'M SO DEPRESSED.
HERE I AM IN NEW MEXICO
WITH MY HICK FATHER
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER.
NO OFFENSE.
FIRST OF ALL,
IT'S NOT NEW MEXICO.
IT'S NORTH DAKOTA.
LIKE IT MATTERS.
ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS IT'S NOT L.A.
THIS IS A JOKE, RIGHT?
THIS IS OUR POOR
NEIGHBORS' HOUSE,
AND THEN YOU'RE GOING
TO TAKE US TO OUR HOUSE.
NEVER JUDGE A BOOK
BY ITS COVER, HONEY.
DAD, THIS BOOK DOESN'T
EVEN HAVE A COVER.
I'M GOING TO BE
MISERABLE HERE!
THERE'S NO SWIMMING POOL,
SHOPPING MALLS OR CABLE.
BET YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE A TV.
THIS SURE AIN'T
BEVERLY HILLS.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE THIS HOUSE.
CAREFUL.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT THIS
COULDN'T GET ANY WORSE--
AN OLD BASEMENT.
GREAT PLACE TO STORE ALL
THE ROCKS AND PINE
CONES I'M GOING TO FIND.
OK, IT'S A LITTLE DUSTY.
I ADMIT THAT.
WE'LL JUST CLEAN IT UP A LITTLE BIT,
SPLASH SOME PAINT AROUND.
YOU'D NEED TO SLAP SOME BULLDOZERS
AROUND TO FIX THIS PLACE UP.
OH, GOD! GROSS. COBWEBS.
YOU'RE MAKING TOO BIG A DEAL
OUT OF THIS, HONEY.
THIS IS A GREAT HOUSE.
I GOT A GREAT BUY ON IT.
YEAH, FROM WHO,
DRACULA?
HOW ABOUT I GET A HOTEL
AND YOU CAN COME VISIT...
LIKE ONCE A WEEK?
HEY, I'LL PAY FOR IT.
TORY, HONEY...
YOU REALLY THINK MONEY'S
ALL YOU NEED TO GET BY
IN THIS LIFE?
OK, I'LL GO WITH
THAT THEORY.
DO YOU SEE THAT SPIDER?
IT'S HUGE!
THAT THING
COULD KILL US!
OK, I'M GOING TO TURN AROUND.
AND WALK OUT OF THIS BASEMENT,
GOING BACKTO THE JEEP,
AND MAKEA RESERVATION
AT THE NEAREST HOTEL IN TOWN.
THIS IS WORSE THAN SUMMER CAMP!
I'D RATHER SLEEP IN A TENT!
HOLD ON! HELLO?
WE'RE BREAKING UP.
WAIT
I'D LIKE TO MAKE
A RESERVATION.
YES, I'D LIKE IT TO BE
A REALLY TALL ROOM, AND--
GREAT!
WHO ARE YOU?
I WAS A GUY CARRYING
SOME PAINT THINNER.
HERE. DOES THAT
COVER IT?
YOU KNOCK OVER MY CAN
OF PAINT THINNER, THEN YOU
OFFER ME BUCKS?
OK. HOW ABOUT THAT?
THAT DO IT?
BUT IF YOU SAID
YOU WERE SORRY,
YOU KNOW, IT MIGHT.
KEEP THE CHANGE.
I'M IN A BIG HURRY.
IT'S A BIG UGLY DISGUSTING
HOUSE I'D JUST LIKE TO
DISTANCE MYSELF FROM.
WHAT,
THE O'GRADY PLACE?
YEAH. IT'S REALLY GROSS.
THERE'S BUGS. THERE'S COBWEBS.
GOD ONLY KNOWS WHAT ELSE IS IN THERE.
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
IT'S JUST FUNNY THE WAY
GIRLS ARE ALWAYS AFRAID
OF SPIDERS AND STUFF.
DID I MISPLACE
MY s CALENDAR HERE?
"GIRLS"?
LISTEN, BUD, OK?
THIS IS THE NINETIES.
WOMEN ARE TREATED EQUAL.
WELL, FIRST OFF,
MY NAME ISN'T BUD,
IT'S NATHAN.
I DON'T KNOW MANY GUYS
THAT ARE AFRAID OF HOUSES.
OH, IS THAT SO?
YEAH
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NEITHER AM I.
I'M NOT AFRAID
OF ANYTHING.
TORY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M NOT GOING TO
FIGHT YOU ANYMORE.
YOU HATE THE HOUSE--
IT'S DIRTY,
IT'S DUSTY.
YOU REALLY THINK I'M AFRAID
OF A LITTLE DUST AND BUGS?
COME ON, JUST PUT
THE BAGS BACK, OK?
I'M GOING TO STAY.
DAD, WOULD YOU
PUT THE BAGS BACK?
I'M GOING TO STAY.
IT CAME RIGHT DOWN
OUT OF THE SKY.
THERE IT WAS...
THIS FLYING SAUCER.
IT HAD THESE REALLY
WEIRD LIGHTS, YOU KNOW?
AND IT MADE ALL THESE
WEIRD NOISES,
KIND OF LIKE,
OZZIE, I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO TELL ANY MORE STORIES.
THIS REALLY HAPPENED, ALEX.
IT DID!
IT--LIKE MAGIC,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE, WHEN YOU SEE A STAR
IN THE NIGHT SKY--
THE FIRST STAR--
YOU CAN MAKE A WISH.
IT'LL COME TRUE.
STOP WITH
THE MAGIC STUFF.
AND NO MORE LIES,
OK?
HOW YOU DOING, BOYS?
I'M J.D.
I JUST MET YOUR BROTHER NATHAN.
HI. I'M ALEX. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- THIS IS MY FRIEND OZZIE.
- HI.
SO, YOU BOYS NEED
ANY HELP OUT HERE?
OUR LIABILITY INSURANCE FORBIDS
ANYONE BUT US HANDLING
THE TOOLS AND EQUIPMENT,.
BUT THANKS
FOR THE OFFER.
BOY,I COULD GO FOR
A BEER RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE TOO LITTLE TO DRINK.
DON'T YOU DRINK THAT STUFF!
HEY, OZZIE, WHAT'S THIS?
AH, GOTCHA!
NATHAN?
I'M SORRY. YOU ALL RIGHT?
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
DOWN HERE.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO MAKE
A PEACE OFFERING,
BUT I THINK IT'S ALL
IN THAT CRATE.
HOPE I DIDN'T RUIN
WHAT'S INSIDE.
YOU COULDN'T DAMAGE
WHAT'S IN HERE.
THE O'GRADYS COLLECTED
A LOT OF JUNK.
- THE O'GRADYS?
- YEAH. DAN O'GRADY.
HE USED TO OWN THIS PLACE.
HE WAS REALLY A
WEIRD, STRANGE GUY.
OH. YOU MEAN
WEIRD AND STRANGE.
LIKE GUYS WHO OWN TRUCKS
AND PAINT HOUSES
FOR A LIVING?
HEY, LET'S SEE WHAT
HE'S GOT IN THIS THING.
UNLESS YOU'RE SCARED.
SCARED? ME?
GIVE ME A CROWBAR.
GOT A HAMMER.
FINE. A HAMMER IS GOOD.
THAT SOUNDS
LIKE OZZIE.
BLUE IS NOT
YOUR BEST COLOR.
ALEX, I ASKED YOU TO HOLD
THAT LADDER STEADY.
NOW LOOK WHAT HAPPENED!
I'M NOT EVEN GOING
TO ASK WHAT HAPPENED.
THERE'S A BATHROOM
OFF THE KITCHEN IN THERE.
AT LEAST, IT LOOKED
A LITTLE LIKE A BATHROOM.
HELLO?
WHO'S IN THERE?
WHAT NEAT JUNK.
PLEASE LET ME OUT.
PLEASE?
WHY WON'T YOU LET ME
OUT OF THIS CRATE?
HOW DID YOU
GET IN THERE?
PLEASE...
LET ME OUT.
I DON'T LIKE IT IN HERE.
PLEASE.
HELLO?
I'M BACK!
HEY, TUBBY...
YOU GOT A LIGHT FOR AN
OLD LEPRECHAUN'S PIPE?
I'M STARVED.
HAVEN'T EATEN IN YEARS.
WHAT--WHAT ARE YOU?
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE,
ME LAD?
SEE THE HAT? THE BUCKLES
ON ME SHOES?
WHY,
I'M A LEPRECHAUN!
A SHOEMAKER BY TRADE.
AND SPEAKING OF SHOES...
YOURS COULD USE
A SHINE.
BUT FIRST...
HAVE YOU SEEN A CROCK OF GOLD
LYING AROUND?
TELL ME! OR I'LL BITE
YOUR EAR OFF,
AND I'LL MAKE
A BOOT OUT OF IT.
YOU ONLY GOT AWAY
'CAUSE ME POWERS ARE WEAK.
I NEED ME GOLD!
THERE'S A LEPRECHAUN
IN THE BASEMENT!
HOLD ON!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE COME OUT OF A BOX!
HE HAD THESE LONG,
REAL SCARY FINGERS.
AND HE ATE A BUG!
LEPRECHAUN?
LET'S INJECT A LITTLE
REALITY IN HERE, PLEASE.
I SAW HIM! REALLY!
HE TRIED TO
POLISH MY SHOES!
THEN WHERE'S
YOUR POT OF GOLD?
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTS!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
IF IT'LL MAKE YOU FEEL ANY
BETTER, OZZIE, WE'LL ALL GO
CHECK IT OUT.
DON'T GO IN THERE!
OK?
JUST IN CASE.
I BETTER GO WITH YOU.
NATHAN...
I DON'T THINK
THAT STICK'S BIG ENOUGH.
WAIT FOR ME. I'M COMIN'.
JUST IN CASE.
OZZIE, YOU REALLY
BUSTED UP THIS CRATE.
NO, I DIDN'T DO THAT.
THAT--THAT WAS
THE LEPRECHAUN.
UH-HUH.
LEPRECHAUN.
I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING, OZZIE.
BUT THIS GUY...
WAS REAL.
I MEAN, HE HAD
THE BUCKLES ON HIS SHOES
AND HE HAD THEM
REAL HORRIBLE TEETH,
AND THEY WERE ALL ROTTEN
AND EVERYTHING,
I--I KNOW HE NEVER
DOES BRUSH THEM.
THAT'S HIM
HE'S GOING TO KILL
EVERY ONE OF US,
AND I'M FIRST.
OZZIE, COME HERE!
I AIN'T GOING IN
THAT DARK CORNER!
NEITHER AM I.
WHAT WAS THAT?
HANG ON, HANG ON.
IT'S ONLY A RAT.
IT'S JUST A RAT.
WELL, OZZIE, I THINK
WE FOUND YOUR LEPRECHAUN.
NO. YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
HE WAS BIGGER
THAN THAT.
WE'VE SOLVED THIS MYSTERY.
NOW CAN WE JUST
GET OUT OF HERE?
HEY! HEY, LOOK UP
IN THE SKY!
SO WHAT, OZZIE?
IT'S JUST A RAINBOW.
IT'S A MAGIC RAINBOW.
LEPRECHAUNS AND RAINBOWS...
IT'S A SIGN!
IT'S A SIGN TO GET
BACK TO PAINTING.
NO. WE GOT TO GO SEE
WHAT'S AT THE END.
OZZIE, YOU'RE
EMBARRASSING ME.
COME ON,
GO WITH ME.
WE GOT TO GET TO THE END
OF THE RAINBOW.
THERE'S ALWAYS A POT OF GOLD!
HE'S SO EASILY SIDETRACKED.
LIKE ALWAYS, I'LL
TAKE CARE OF IT.
OZZIE, COME ON!
ALEX!
OH, LET THEM GO
CHASE RAINBOWS.
LET'S GO PAINT.
UM, THIS IS
BIODEGRADABLE?
OZZIE, THIS IS STUPID.
YOU CAN'T FIND
THE END OF THE RAINBOW.
IT'S WHERE THE RAINBOW ENDS.
IT DOES SORT OF LOOK
LIKE WHERE IT ENDS.
HEY, LOOK,
IT'S GOING AWAY.
DON'T CUT YOURSELF ON ANY
OF THIS RUSTY OLD METAL.
IF YOU DO, IT'LL MAKE
YOUR JAW LOCK SHUT.
HEY, OZZIE, I GOT AN IDEA.
LET'S HOT-WIRE THIS.
I DON'T THINK THE BATTERY
WOULD BE ANY GOOD.
LOOK AT THAT.
GIVE ME IT.
LET ME LOOK AT IT
FOR A MINUTE.
I'LL GIVE IT BACK
TO YOU. I PROMISE.
GIVE ME THAT.
WOW, LOOK AT THAT.
HERE'S YOUR COIN.
I FOUND A BAG
FULL OF THEM.
OH! I TOLD YOU.
I TOLD YOU.
UH-OH. THAT'S WHAT
THAT LEPRECHAUN
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
WOULD YOU STOP WITH
THAT STUPID STUFF?
WE FOUND THIS GOLD.
FINDERS KEEPERS.
I JUST HOPE
IT'S REAL.
I KNOW HOW TO TELL
IF IT'S REAL.
YOU BITE ON IT.
OH, MY GOD.
I SWALLOWED
THAT GOLD COIN
NICE GOING, JAWS.
CAN YOU DIE
FROM SWALLOWING GOLD?
YEAH, AFTER I KILL YOU!
YOU JUST LET ME
TAKE CHARGE, OK?
I'M GOING TO KEEP ONE.
I CAN GET IT
CHECKED OUT IN TOWN.
WE'VE GOT TO HIDE
THE REST.
WE CAN'T TELL ANYONE
ABOUT THIS.
RIGHT, RIGHT. WHY?
'CAUSE YOU KNOW HOW ADULTS
ARE, ESPECIALLY WHEN
IT COMES TO MONEY.
THEY'LL TRY
TO TAKE IT AWAY.
LET'S HIDE IT IN
THE OLD WELL
BESIDE THE HOUSE.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
WE'RE RICH, AND I CAN
BUY COMICS EVERY WEEK.
- YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
- WHAT ELSE?
- WE CAN GET YOU AN OPERATION.
- FOR WHAT?
TO MAKE YOU SMART.
WE CAN GO TO THE HOSPITAL
AND HAVE THEM OPERATE
AND FIX YOUR BRAIN.
BUT...BUT
I--I'M SMART.
YEAH. WELL, SORT OF.
WHAT I MEAN IS WE CAN
MAKE YOU REAL SMART.
THAT WAY, PEOPLE
WON'T MAKE FUN OF YOU.
- THEY MAKE FUN OF ME?
- NOT IN FRONT OF YOU.
ONLY BEHIND YOUR BACK.
LET'S GO TO THE WELL.
COME ON.
HERE. START IN THE CORNERS.
NICE, EVEN STROKES.
THAT'S IT.
YOU GOT IT.
NOT BAD, HUH?
YEAH,
A REGULAR PICASSO.
PUT ME OUT OF BUSINESS.
OH, WE NEED ANOTHER CAN
OF PAINT.
JUST WATCH HOW A PRO
GETS A CAN OF PAINT.
LET ME GET A RAG FIRST.
GO AHEAD.
NATHAN.
NATHAN, COME ON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, MY GOD.
OH, JEEZ.
HONEY, ARE YOU OK?
I HEARD YOU SCREAM.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS YOU
RUBBING MY LEG.
AND YOU LET ME?
SOMETHING WAS RUBBING
MY LEG, CARESSING IT.
IT'S PROBABLY
JUST A POSSUM.
I KNOW WHAT CARESSING
MY LEG FEELS LIKE.
YOU DO?
WE GOT TO GET
THESE CUTS CLEANED UP.
- I SHOULD LOOK
FOR THAT ANIMAL.
WHY?
IT MIGHT HAVE RABIES.
Great!
IT WAS A CAT.
I THINK WE FOUND
YOUR SECRET ADMIRER.
IT WASN'T A CAT.
IT SOUNDS HURT.
COME ON, KITTY, KITTY.
WHAT?
THAT CAT BIT ME.
PUT PRESSURE ON IT.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE YOU
TO THE HOSPITAL.
WE'RE TAKING HIM TO
THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
SHOOT,
THE DISTRIBUTOR CAP.
COME ON, COME ON!
WE MAY BE A WHILE.
GET A BITE TO EAT.
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S OUR CHANCE.
WHAT, TO GET
SOMETHING TO EAT?
NO, TO CHECK OUT THE GOLD COIN.
COME ON.
IT'S GETTING DARK.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
A COIN LIKE THIS.
THE SYMBOLS--INCREDIBLY
STRANGE MARKINGS.
WHAT'S IT WORTH?
WELL, IF THIS IS
SOLID GOLD,
COULD BE WORTH $.500
BUT THERE'S
HISTORICAL VALUE.
IT COULD BE PRICELESS.
COULD I KEEP THIS
OVERNIGHT AND STUDY IT?
YOU WON'T LOSE IT?
NO, I'LL PUT IT IN MY SAFE.
I'LL WRITE UP A RECEIPT.
YOU RECKON THAT COIN MIGHT HAVE
COME FROM A LEPRECHAUN?
NEVER MIND.
OK, WE'LL COME BACK TOMORROW,
AND LET'S JUST KEEP THIS BETWEEN US.
WE'D BETTER GET TO THE RESTAURANT.
THEY'RE GONNA BE PISSED
WE WERE GONE SO LONG.
I MUST BE HEARING THINGS.
OK. I'LL GET THIS
PUT AWAY HERE.
I WANT ME GOLD COIN!
ME COIN!
IT'S NOT NICE TO STEAL GOLD
COINS FROM A LEPRECHAUN.
BAD SHOP OWNER.
I'LL BE BACK.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO PLAY.
DO YOU WANT TO PLAY WITH ME?
THIS OLD LEP, HE PLAYED ONE
HE PLAYED POGO ON HIS LUNG
TEACH YOU TO STEAL
ME GOLD.
OH. CAN'T HAVE
DIRTY SHOES NOW, CAN WE?
THERE.
NICE AND SHINY.
OH. HE'LL BOUNCE BACK
IN NO TIME.
ONE GOLD COIN... TO GO.
BY THE LUCK OF THE IRISH.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU TOLD OZZIE AND ALEX
WHERE THIS PLACE IS?
RELAX. THEY'RE KIDS.
PROBABLY STOPPED OFF
TO BUY OZZIE A COMIC
OR SOMETHING.
BOY, WHAT A NIGHT. MY FIRST DAY HERE,
AND MY FATHER ENDS UP IN THE HOSPITAL.
IT'S JUST FOR OBSERVATION.
HE'LL BE FINE
IN THE MORNING.
LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
THE WORST IS OVER.
SAY, AREN'T WE A LITTLE YOUNG
TO BE OUT THIS LATE?
NO. I'M YEARS OLD.
OK, SMART ASS...
TAKE THAT RIDICULOUS MASK OFF
AND STEP OUT OF THE CAR.
IT'S NOT NICE TO MAKE
FUN OF A LEPRECHAUN.
IS THAT SO? SO NOW
YOU'RE A LEPRECHAUN, HUH?
YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT ANYTHING?
NO. I MEAN YES,
I DO WANT SOMETHING.
WHAT I WANTED WAS A WATERCRESS
SALAD AND AN EVIAN WATER.
BUT THEY DON'T
HAVE THAT HERE.
ALL THEY HAVE IS CHEAP
WHISKEY AND WARM BEER.
WELL, HERE'S YOUR WATER.
JEEZ. THANKS.
GET AWAY FROM ME,
YOU LITTLE CREEP!
SO YOU WANT TO PLAY
HIDE-AND-SEEK, HUH?
OVER HERE.
I'M OVER HERE.
STOP.
NO MORE.
WHERE THE FUCK
ARE YOU?
OH, THANK GOD.
NOW, THAT WAS FUN.
YOU KNOW, TORY, YOU LOOK
A LITTLE SKINNY.
NO OFFENSE, BUT, UH...
YOU SHOULD HAVE
SOME MEAT LOAF.
OH, NO. DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT IS?
YEAH, IT'S MEAT LOAF.
NO. THAT'S CUT-UP,
DEAD COW.
AND THAT'S IF YOU'RE
LUCKY IN THIS PLACE.
I DON'T EAT MEAT,
AND I DON'T KILL LIVING THINGS.
I FEEL VERY STRONGLY
ABOUT THAT.
REALLY?
REALLY.
NATHAN, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
CUT-UP, DEAD COW. THAT'S
WHAT YOUR SHOE IS.
GIVE ME MY SHOE.
NATHAN, GIVE ME
MY SHOE BACK.
ALEX AND OZZIE ARE COMING.
WOULD YOU TRY TO SET
A MATURE EXAMPLE?
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE WENT DOWN
TO THAT PLACE.
NOW, WHERE'S ME CROCK
OF GOLD?
I WANT ME GOLD.
GOD.
UH-OH. I THINK SOMETHING
GOT IN HERE.
NO SHIT, SHERLOCK.
YOU'D BETTER WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
GO WASH IT OUT WITH SOAP
RIGHT NOW, BOY.
SURE. SURE. AND RIGHT
AFTER THAT, OZZIE,
I'LL BE SURE TO GROUND
MYSELF FOR WEEKS.
THIS IS CRAZY.
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON HERE?
IT COULD HAVE BEEN A BEAR.
THEY SOMETIMES COME DOWN
FROM THE HILLS FOR FOOD.
MY DAD HAD TO BRING
FOOD INTO THIS PLACE.
THAT LEPRECHAUN, HE TRIED
TO SHINE MY SHOES.
HE SAID HE WAS
A SHOEMAKER.
YOU GUYS CAN SIT
AROUND HERE AND THEORIZE.
BEAR OR NO BEAR,
I AM GETTING OUT OF HERE.
I'M WALKING OUT THAT DOOR,
AND I'M NOT COMING BACK.
A LITTLE TOO DARK
OUT THERE.
LET'S CLEAN
THIS PLACE UP.
HERE. YOU KNOW HOW TO WORK
ONE OF THESE, RIGHT?
WE FINALLY GOT THAT
KITCHEN STRAIGHTENED UP.
YEAH, I'M REALLY BEGINNING
TO GET THE HANG OF THIS THING.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT SOUNDS LIKE A BELL.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND.
GREAT, OZZIE.
I'M GOING TO GO
CHECK OUT THE BEDROOMS
AND FIND OUT WHERE WE'RE
GOING TO STAY TONIGHT.
ALEX, DO YOU THINK YOU
COULD KILL A LEPRECHAUN?
OZZIE, YOU CAN KILL
ANYTHING.
YOU JUST GOT TO KNOW
HOW TO DO IT.
NOW, ME, GIVE ME
A . MAGNUM,
PRESS IT TO THE LITTLE
GREEN CRITTER'S TEMPLE,
AND BLAM!
BRAINS AND GUTS DRIPPING
ALL DOWN ITS HEAD.
THE GUY IS GONE
WITH A CAPITAL DEAD.
OZZIE, WILL YOU CUT IT OUT
WITH THAT STUPID BELL?
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
COMING FROM THE KITCHEN.
WE'RE, LIKE,
REALLY SCARED.
STAY HERE. I'M GOING
TO CHECK IT OUT
NATHAN, BE CAREFUL.
OH, MY LEG!
I GOT YOU
IN A BEAR TRAP
I GOT YOU IN A BEAR TRAP
YOU LOOK LIKE A STUPID SAP
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE HURT.
LET'S PLAY SURGEON.
NATHAN!
TORY, NO!
GET BACK.
OH, MY GOD.
CALL THE POLICE!
GET OFF!
YOU CAN'T HURT ME.
ALEX, GET THE SHOTGUN.
HURRY UP, ALEX!
HELP! HELP!
IT'S HAPPENING!
THE ATTACK IS ON
O'GRADY FARM!
SEND HELP. THE LEPRECHAUN
IS ATTACKING!
ARMY, NAVY, GUNS, MARINES,
AND WE'LL NEED
SOME MEDICINE.
OK, THANKS.
HEY, SHERIFF, I GOT
A CALL FROM OZZIE
HE SAYS THE LEPRECHAUN
IS ATTACKING.
WHAT WAS IT LAST WEEK?
WAS IT UFOs?
HE'S A GOOD BOY.
A LEPRECHAUN.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
TAKE IT.
KILL HIM! KILL HIM!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, OZZIE?
HURRY UP!
GET ALEX ON THE PORCH!
I DON'T WANT TO GO
TO THE PORCH!
HE WENT OFF
INTO THE BUSHES.
GOD. NATHAN, THAT WAS
NO FUCKING BEAR.
MY GOD. GONE.
GOD, NATHAN, YOUR LEG.
LOOK AT IT.
WE GOT TO CALL A PARAMEDIC.
I TOOK CARE OF IT.
I TOLD THEM WE NEEDED THE ARMY,
MEDICINE,
AND A PARAMEDIC.
OZZIE, YOU DIDN'T
TELL THEM THAT IT WAS
A LEPRECHAUN, DID YOU?
OF COURSE I DID.
THAT'S WHAT IT WAS,
WASN'T IT?
WE JUST GOT TO GET HIM
BACK TO THE HOUSE.
SHIT! THE LINE'S DEAD.
ALEX, YOU EVER IN THE BOY SCOUTS?
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
HELP ME WITH THIS.
STOP THE BLEEDING.
GO TO THE BATHROOM.
GET EVERYTHING YOU CAN--
TISSUE, ALCOHOL, COTTON.
TORY, DID THAT THING LOOK
LIKE A LEPRECHAUN TO YOU?
OZZIE, GO!
COME ON.
YOU'LL BE OK, NATHAN.
OK, SO, SOON AS WE STOP THE
BLEEDING, WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
NATHAN TO THE PICKUP.
BUT WHAT IF IT'S
STILL OUT THERE?
NO WAY. I PUT ROUNDS
INTO THAT THING.
IT'S GOT TO BE DEAD.
ALEX, GET ME SOME ICE.
WE'LL STOP THE SWELLING
ON NATHAN'S LEG.
HURRY UP AND
GET HIM OUT HERE.
CAREFUL.
WANT HELP?
DID YOU SEE HIM?
OH, GOD, THAT HURTS.
GET HIM IN THE TRUCK.
WHAT IF HE COMES?
HURRY UP, NATHAN.
OK, WE MADE IT.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THE TRUCK?
DISTRIBUTOR CAP.
ALEX, BE CAREFUL.
HURRY.
AHH, LET ME IN!
CLOSE THE DOOR!
CLOSE THE WINDOW!
MY--MY EAR!
HE GOT MY EAR!
WHAT THE HECK IS
HE DOING IN THERE?
RING AROUND THE ROSIE
A POCKETFUL OF POSIES
FASTER! FASTER!
ASHES, ASHES
WE ALL FALL DOWN
WHERE'D YOU GO,
ME FRIENDS?
I WANT TO KNOW
WHERE ME GOLD IS.
GIVE IT BACK TO A NICE
HARMLESS LEPRECHAUN.
OK, LET'S GO NOW.
WHERE IS HE?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING,
ME FRIENDS?
PHONE. PHONE.
I GOT TO CALL FOR HELP.
THE PHONE'S DEAD.
OK...MY PORTABLE!
HELLO? I NEED THE POLICE.
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
THIS IS TORY REDDING.
I'M CALLING FROM THE O'GRADY FARM.
SOMETHING TERRIBLE HAS HAPPENED.
WE NEED YOU TO SEND
SOMEONE OUT HERE.
OK, PLEASE HURRY. YOU'VE GOT--
HELLO?
GODDAMMIT.
THE BATTERY DIED.
IT'S OK, I GOT THROUGH AND
THEY'RE GONNA SEND SOMEBODY.
WE'RE GONNA BE OK.
DEPUTY TRIBIT COME IN.
THIS IS SHERIFF CRONAN.
TRIBIT, CAN YOU READ ME?
I READ YOU SHERIFF.
GO AHEAD.
THIS IS SHERIFF CRONAN.
WE GOT A CALL FROM OVER THERE AT
THE O'GRADY FARM.
A FEMALE CALLED TORY REDING
CALLED IN AN EMERGENCY.
GET OUT THERE. ON A CODE 1
PRIORITY RIGHT AWAY.
ROGER, SHERIFF.
MY E.T.A. IS LESS THAN 3 MINUTES.
IF I NEED BACKUP,
I'LL CALL IT IN.
YOU GOT THE BACK DOOR, RIGHT?
RIGHT, AND THE BASEMENT WINDOWS
ARE LOCKED UP TIGHT.
NOW, DOUBLE-CHECK THE WINDOWS
IN THE KITCHE
MY EAR SURE HURTS.
I BET THAT LEPRECHAUN
MADE A BOOT OUT OF IT.
HE DIDN'T GET YOU EAR.
HE JUST BIT IT.
- WHERE THE HELL IS THE POLICE?
- THEY SHOULD BE HERE BY NOW.
NOW I'M GONNA MAKE TIGHT.
TOO TIGHT?
NO, IT'S ALRIGHT.
THAT LEPRECHAUN SURE IS MEAN.
IT IS NOT A LEPRECHAUN
DAMM IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT THING WAS,
BUT IT'S NOT A LEPRECHAUN.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
WHAT ABOUT THE GOLD IN THE
OLD, RUSTY CAR.
NEVER MIND WHAT I JUST SAID
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "GOLD"?
ALEX, TELL ALEX THE GOLD.
WE WERE GONNA SAVE IT TO GET
OZZIE AN OPERATION.
ALEX, YOU CAN'T FIX OZZIE'S BRAIN.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT HE DOESN'T.
TELL ME ABOUT THE GOLD.
IN THE WATER BUCKET, RIGHT?
JUST PULL IT UP AND THERE'S
A BAG OF GOLD COINS.
IT'S GOTTA WORK.
ALL HE WANTS IS HE GOLD,
HE'S GOTTA LEAVE US ALONE.
NO, YOU'RE HURT TOO BAD.
SIT DOWN.
LOOK, JUST TAKE THIS GUN
WITH YOU, OK?
JUST COCK AND AIM ITT
AND PULL THE TRIGGER.
YOU EVER WORKED ONE OF
THOSE THINGS BEFORE?
NO.
WATCH OUT FOR THOSE TEETH.
COME ON.
IS THAT ME GOLD?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
I'M A LEPRECHAUN, ME DEAR.
HERE. THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR, RIGHT?
ME POWERS ARE RETURNING!
IT SOUNDS LIKE ME GOLD...
IT LOOKS LIKE ME GOLD...
IT SMELLS LIKE ME GOLD...
IT TAKES LIKE ME GOLD...
OH, GOD.
ME GOLD!
ME DELICIOUS GOLD.
BE CALM, BE CALM.
OK, HE TOOK IT.
HE GOT WHAT HE WANTED.
NOW WE'LL GET HIM TO A HOSPITAL.
AND CALL FOR HELP.
94, 95...
96, 97...
98, 99.
A MISSING COIN?
I'VE BEEN TRICKED.
THEY'VE GOT ME COIN.
NO ONE TAKES A LEPRECHAUN'S GOLD
ALEX, YOU GOTTA GET ICE FOR OZZIE'S EAR.
AND BOIL SOME WATER.
I'LL COVER YA.
COOKING, KIDS?
IT'S IN THE CABINETS.
OK TORY I WANT YOU TO OPEN THEM
AND GET BACK QUICKLY, OK
I WANT ME GOLD
QUICK.
YOU SHOULD'VE TAKEN
DOOR NUMBER TWO
YOU MISSED ME!
WHERE IS HE?
YOU CAN NEVER CATCH
A LEPRECHAUN.
THERE HE GOES.
HE'S GETTING AWAY.
WHERE DID HE GO?
HE WENT IN THERE!
STAY WITH OZZIE.
I AM RIGHT HERE.
AND I AIN'T NO SANTA CLAUS.
YOU GOT THE SUCKER.
BE CAREFUL.
YOU THINK HE'S DEAD?
YEAH, HE'S DEAD
NOT A CHANCE, ME LAD.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
COME ON.
HE'S IN THERE.
WAIT. HE'S IN THE BASEMENT.
HE'S OVER THERE,
I HEAR HIM.
LISTEN
THERE HE IS,
RIGHT HERE
COME ON YOU LITTLE GREEN THING.
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S OUTSIDE
HE'S GONE
IT'S GONNA BE OK.
DO YOU HEAR ANYTHING?
HE WENT DOWN THE BASEMENT.
HELLO? HELPS US PLEASE.
WE'RE TRAPPED INSIDE HERE
WHERE'S THE REST
OF ME GOLD?
HAVING PROBLEMS?
DO YOU NEED A HAND?
WHAT THE FUCK'S GOING ON?
WE GAVE HIM HIS GOLD.
I THINK I KNOW
WHAT HE WANTS.
WHAT?
HE WANTS HIS LAST GOLD COIN.
STOP HIM! HE'S GOT THE LAST
GOLD COIN IN HIS STOMACH.
YOU CAN'T GO OUT THERE.
THERE'S GOTTA BE ANOTHER WAY.
THAT THING IS A LEPRECHAUN
AND WE HAVE TO STOP IT.
THE OLD O'GRADY, HE MIGHT
KNOW HOW TO KILL IT.
WHEN I WAS A KID, HE USED TO TELL ME
STORIES ABOUT FAIRES AND LEPRECHAUNS.
IF ANYBODY WOULD KNOW HOW TO
KILL THIS THING, HE WOULD.
HE OWNS THIS HOUSE
HE PROBABLY PUT THAT THING
IN ITS CRATE.
WHERE IS HE?
OLD MAN O'GRADY,
HE'S IN A REST HOME
HE HAD A STROKE ABOUT
10 YEARS AGO.
WE GOTTA GOT THERE RIGHT NOW
HOW WE GONNA GET THERE?
THE JEEP.
WAIT A SEC,
I GOT AN IDEA.
ALEX, DON'T LOCK.
HELLO, LOVE
FARTHER!
SHINY-SHINY
WE'RE CLEAR.
I'LL BE BACK
MR. O'GRADY, IT'S OUT.
IT'S OUT OF THE CRATE.
NO ONE BELIEVED IT
WAS A LEPRECHAUN.
I BELIEVE IT.
HOW DO WE STOP IT?
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO KILL
A LEPRECHAUN.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU.
I'LL NEVER TELL YA.
OPEN UP, OPEN UP
HE CAME BACK FOR ME.
I KNEW HE WOULD BUT,
NOBODY WOULD BELIEVE ME.
WE GOTTA GET YOU DOWN.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT NOW.
BUT YOU HAVE TO KILL IT
HOW CAN WE KILL IT?
A FOUR-LEAF CLOVER
FROM THE CLOVER PATCH
BESIDES THE WELL.
YOU GOTTA PUT IT ON HIS BODY.
HE HAS TO TOUCH IT,
THEN YOU CAN KILL IT.
LITTLE GIRLS SHOULDN'T BE
LOOKING FOR CLOVERS.
COME TO ME, ME DEAR
OH MY GOD, A COP.
YOU GOTTA HELP US,
PLEASE HELP US.
I WANT ME GOLD.
GET OUT! PLEASE
GET OUT
AN EYE FOR AN EYE,
ME DEAR
PLEASE, GET OUT.
TORI? WE HEARD YOUR SCREAMS
WHERE'S ALEX?
HE'S UP IN THE HOUSE.
O'GRADY SAID WE NEED TO HAVE
A FOUR-LEAF CLOVER.
WE BETTER GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THAT THING WAKES UP
THERE'S GOTTA BE A FOUR-LEAF CLOVER,
HE SAID THERE WAS.
OK, COME ON, LET'S GO
WE'RE NEVER GONNA FIND A
FOUR-LEAF CLOVER IN HERE.
YES WE CAN.
I FOUND MANY WHEN I WAS A KID.
HEY!
NEVER MIND.
I'M NOT AFRAID.
I CAN GET THAT LEPRECHAUN
PLEASE DON'T BE HERE YET.
I KNOW I CAN GET HIM.
I'M NOT AFRAID.
I'LL KILL HIM.
I CAN GET HIM.
I'M NOT AFRAID.
WE'RE NOT GONNA FIND IT.
YOU CAN FIND IT...
YOU JUST GOTTA BELIEVE.
OZZIE I'M SO SICK OF YOUR MAGIC
AND YOUR STUPID FANTASIES.
IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME...
...TO SIT HERE AND
LOOK FOR CLOVES
THAT THING'S GONNA WAKE UP.
YOU'VE LOST YOUR FAITH.
YOU GOTTA BELIEVE.
YOU GOT TO.
ALRIGHT, LOOK.
I BELIEVE, I BELIEVE.
YOU FOUND ONE.
I TOLD YOU. I TOLD YOU.
WE GOTTA GET THIS ON
THE LEPRECHAUN.
GOOD MORNING, ME LAD.
NOW I'LL FINISH WHAT I STARTED.
HELP! PLEASE, NATHAN.
SOMEBODY HELP ME.
IT'S ME, IT'S ME YOU WANT YOU
GREEN SON OF A BITCH.
I GOT THE LAST GOLD COIN.
IT'S IN MY STOMACH.
THEN IT'S YOUR BELLY I WANT.
USE THE CLOVER.
I WANT ME LAST COIN.
HANG ON, OZZIE.
I'LL SAVE YOU. HANG ON.
FUCK YOU, LUCKY CHARMS
WE DID IT.
I DID A SMART THING, DIDN'T I?
YOU'RE REALLY SMART OZZIE.
JUST HANG IN THERE, OK?
WHAT'S THAT?
GOTCHA.
FIRST TIME I EVER GOT YOU.
SURE DID, OZZIE.
I WANT ME GOLD.
I'LL NOT REST UNTIL I
HAVE ME GOLD
CURSE THIS WELL
THAT WE SOLE SHALL DWELL
TILL I FIND ME MAGIC
THAT BREAKS THIS SPELL