- [Grunting] No!
[Indistinct whimpering]
No!
[Indistinct whimpering] No! No!
[Indistinct whimpering] No!
No! No!
No!
No! No! No!
[Whimpering]
I didn't tell. - I read now from the charter,
a supremely holy book of voodoo
- i read now from the charter,
a supremely holy book of voodoo and black magic.
A supremely holy book of voodoo and black magic.
- [Screams]
And black magic.
- [Screams] [Whimpers]
- [Screams] [Whimpers] Why?
[Whimpers] Why?
[Whimpering]
Why? [Whimpering]
- "Black God of death, hear me.
[Whimpering] - "Black God of death,
hear me. We surrender our mind and body
- "black God of death, hear me.
We surrender our mind and body to your will.
Fill us with your power so that
to your will. Fill us with your power
so that we may serve you always."
Fill us with your power so that we
may serve you always." - [Grunting]
We may serve you always."
- [Grunting] -"We are yours forever,
- [grunting]
- "We are yours forever, oh, loving, oh, giving..."
- Please let me go.
Oh, loving, oh, giving..." - Please let me go.
- "...Oh, sweet chosen lord."
- Please let me go.
- "...Oh, sweet chosen lord." - What?!
[Panting] Please.
Please.
No! Stop!
No, please. Stop.
Stop! No, please.
Stop. Please.
No, please. Stop.
Please. [Sobbing]
[Panting] Why?
- [Demonic voice] Nothing can
why?
- [Demonic voice] Nothing can be gained if nothing is
- [demonic voice] Nothing can
be gained if nothing is sacrificed.
Be gained if nothing is sacrificed.
- [Spits]
Sacrificed.
- [Spits] No!
[Sobbing]
No! [Sobbing]
- Come, sisters, and drink from
[sobbing]
- Come, sisters, and drink from the covenant.
- [Sobbing]
- [Speaking arcane language]
Amen.
- Wow.
- Careful.
This place is falling apart from the inside out.
Morgan?
The inside out. Morgan?
- Yes.
Morgan? - Yes.
- Oh, it's so nice to finally
- yes.
- Oh, it's so nice to finally meet you.
I'm Ms. grace, Dean of the Greek
meet you. I'm Ms.
grace, Dean of the Greek association.
I'm Ms. grace, Dean of the Greek association.
- [Sighs]
Association.
- [Sighs] Thank you so much for letting me
- [sighs] Thank you so much for letting
me pledge so late in the semester.
Thank you so much for letting me pledge
so late in the semester. - Oh, it's okay.
Pledge so late in the semester.
- Oh, it's okay. Your aunt told me about your
- oh, it's okay.
Your aunt told me about your little... Incident.
How are you feeling?
Little... Incident. How are you feeling?
I heard it was touch and go for
how are you feeling?
I heard it was touch and go for a while.
- Um, much better now, thanks
a while.
- Um, much better now, thanks mostly to aunt Brenda.
- Mm.
Mostly to aunt Brenda.
- Mm. She and i were Alpha girls back
- mm. She and i were Alpha girls
back when it meant something.
She and i were Alpha girls back when it
meant something. Everybody loved Brenda.
When it meant something.
Everybody loved Brenda. She was -- she was just
everybody loved Brenda.
She was -- she was just fabulous.
She was sweet.
Fabulous. She was sweet.
She was gorgeous -- truly larger
she was sweet.
She was gorgeous -- truly larger than life.
She made this a place for
than life.
She made this a place for sisters.
- Huh.
Sisters.
- Huh. I guess that makes me a legacy.
- Every girl gets in on her own
i guess that makes me a legacy.
- Every girl gets in on her own merit.
You're here because you're
merit.
You're here because you're special, Morgan.
- Well, that remains to be
special, Morgan.
- Well, that remains to be seen.
- Veronica, lovely.
Seen.
- Veronica, lovely. Morgan, your chapter president.
- Charmed.
Morgan, your chapter president.
- Charmed. - [Clears throat]
- Charmed.
- [Clears throat] Likewise.
- Well, i leave you in the
likewise.
- Well, i leave you in the pledge master's capable hands.
[Door opens, closes]
- You will learn poise, etiquette, humility.
You will learn Greek, Latin, and
etiquette, humility.
You will learn Greek, Latin, and geometry.
You will learn every sorority
geometry. You will learn every sorority
member's name and you will learn
you will learn every sorority member's name and
you will learn to address every sorority member
member's name and you will learn to
address every sorority member as "sister."
To address every sorority member as "sister."
You will learn because i will
as "sister."
You will learn because i will teach you.
You're mine to shape.
Teach you. You're mine to shape.
And my every fucking word...
You're mine to shape.
And my every fucking word... Is gold.
- [Chuckles nervously]
Is gold.
- [Chuckles nervously] I'm just looking to fit in.
You can expect zero trouble from
I'm just looking to fit in.
You can expect zero trouble from me.
- I can always tell which girls
me.
- I can always tell which girls won't make it.
And you just don't have what it
won't make it.
And you just don't have what it takes.
- Oh.
- All right, kids, new meat.
- God. - And try not to wear
- God.
- And try not to wear yourselves out too much tonight.
We're gonna be running drills in
yourselves out too much tonight.
We're gonna be running drills in the morning.
- Hi. I'm Morgan.
The morning.
- Hi. I'm Morgan. - Great.
- Hi. I'm Morgan.
- Great. Another prom queen taking up
- great.
Another prom queen taking up space.
- Cassidy.
Space. - Cassidy.
- It isn't exactly roomy in
- Cassidy.
- It isn't exactly roomy in here, Juliette.
- Sorry.
Here, Juliette.
- Sorry. We've been trapped in here a
- sorry.
We've been trapped in here a while.
It's been absolute torture.
While. It's been absolute torture.
- Has it been that bad?
It's been absolute torture.
- Has it been that bad? - Sleep deprivation, verbal
- has it been that bad?
- Sleep deprivation, verbal abuse, slave labor.
- Sleep deprivation, verbal abuse,
slave labor. Sorority pledges are the lowest
abuse, slave labor.
Sorority pledges are the lowest form of life on campus.
- Then why did you sign up?
Form of life on campus. - Then why did you sign up?
- I'm rebelling against my
- then why did you sign up?
- I'm rebelling against my trailer-park roots.
- And i have to join a sorority
trailer-park roots. - And i have to join a
sorority in order to keep my scholarship.
- And i have to join a sorority in order to keep
my scholarship. Otherwise, i wouldn't be able to
in order to keep my scholarship.
Otherwise, i wouldn't be able to afford school at all.
- And my grades are shit.
Afford school at all.
- And my grades are shit. But sorority girls make
- and my grades are shit.
But sorority girls make connections.
So... It's worth it.
Connections. So... It's worth it.
- You can justify anything if
so... It's worth it. - You can justify
anything if you think about it long enough.
- You can justify anything if you think about
it long enough. - Hey, give me those back.
You think about it long enough.
- Hey, give me those back. - Contraband?
- Hey, give me those back.
- Contraband? Might have to tell on you.
- Keep them. I just quit.
Might have to tell on you.
- Keep them. I just quit. - Got a light?
- Keep them. I just quit.
- Got a light? - Oh, afraid not.
- What good is smoke without
- oh, afraid not.
- What good is smoke without fire?
- Oh, we have got our work cut
fire?
- Oh, we have got our work cut out for us today, girls.
I can't miracle the dumb and
out for us today, girls.
I can't miracle the dumb and ugly off of you.
You've got to fight for it!
Ugly off of you.
You've got to fight for it! Let's go!
You've got to fight for it!
Let's go! Move it!
Are you gonna cry, Cassidy?
Move it! Are you gonna cry, Cassidy?
Cry. It would make my day.
Are you gonna cry, Cassidy? Cry.
It would make my day. Fuck your shoes! Move!
Cry. It would make my day.
Fuck your shoes! Move! Let's go!
Fuck your shoes! Move!
Let's go! No one loves you.
- Filthy slut.
No one loves you.
- Filthy slut. [Laughter]
- You are flawed.
[Laughter]
- You are flawed. - Bitch.
- You are flawed.
- Bitch. [Laughter]
- You must be willing to
[laughter]
- You must be willing to confront your... Limitations...
- Pussy pimple.
Confront your... Limitations...
- Pussy pimple. - ...And move beyond them.
- Pussy pimple.
- ...And move beyond them. - Whore!
- ...and move beyond them.
- Whore! - Do not drop the bricks.
- Whore!
- Do not drop the bricks. These bricks must never ever
- do not drop the bricks.
These bricks must never ever touch the ground.
Juliette!
Touch the ground. Juliette!
Juliette, keep those bricks up.
Juliette! Juliette, keep those bricks up.
So help me, God.
Juliette, keep those bricks up.
So help me, God. I will break your arms.
So help me, God.
I will break your arms. Now keep it up.
None of you saggy-tit bitches is
now keep it up. None of you saggy-tit
bitches is gonna make it into my beloved
none of you saggy-tit bitches is gonna make it
into my beloved sorority until you can learn to
gonna make it into my beloved
sorority until you can learn to run a 5k.
You are entering into a secret and mysterious society.
Alpha beta is the most elite
and mysterious society.
Alpha beta is the most elite sorority in the world.
That power's expensive.
Sorority in the world. That power's expensive.
I read now from the charter, a
that power's expensive. I read now from the charter,
a supremely holy book of voodoo
i read now from the charter,
a supremely holy book of voodoo and black magic.
Supremely holy book of voodoo and black magic.
[Chuckles]
And black magic.
[Chuckles] nothing comes without sacrifice.
[Chuckles] Nothing comes without sacrifice.
Do you think you're unique?
Nothing comes without sacrifice. Do you think
you're unique? Do you think your dreams will
do you think you're unique?
Do you think your dreams will just come true?
Do you think you can get what
just come true? Do you think you can
get what you want without giving up a
do you think you can get what you want
without giving up a little piece of yourself?
You want without giving up a little piece of yourself?
Repeat after me.
Little piece of yourself?
Repeat after me. "Black God of death..."
Now, dirty pig fuckers. "Black God of death..."
"...I surrender my body, my
"black God of death..."
"...I surrender my body, my mind to your will."
"...i surrender my body, my mind to your will."
"...I surrender my mind and
mind to your will."
"...I surrender my mind and body to your will."
"...i surrender my mind and body to your will."
"I am yours forever, oh,
body to your will."
"I am yours forever, oh, loving, oh, giving, oh, sweet
"i am yours forever, oh, loving, oh, giving, oh,
sweet chosen lord."
Loving, oh, giving, oh, sweet chosen lord."
"I am yours forever, oh,
chosen lord."
"I am yours forever, oh, loving, oh, giving, oh, sweet
"i am yours forever, oh, loving, oh, giving, oh,
sweet chosen lord."
Who among you is brave enough to go first?
There must be a volunteer.
To go first?
There must be a volunteer. Morgan.
There must be a volunteer.
Morgan. Morgan wants to go first.
What? No.
Morgan wants to go first. What?
No. She can't for it -- right on
what? No.
She can't for it -- right on the butt.
Shut up, Cassidy.
The butt. Shut up, Cassidy.
I can't do this.
Shut up, Cassidy. I can't do this.
Think of something else.
I can't do this.
Think of something else. Enough!
Think of something else.
Enough! It has begun.
Enough!
It has begun. Wait!
[All screaming]
[All coughing] Welcome to hell week, bitches.
Welcome to hell week, bitches. [Laughter]
[Southwork's "higher" plays]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪ Hot damn and i saw your face
♪ ♪ i got ready to forget my
and i saw your face ♪ ♪ i got ready to forget my chase ♪
♪ i got ready to forget my chase
♪ ♪ ...Could make my move
chase ♪ ♪ ...Could make my move ♪ come on, baby,
now it's under
♪ ...could make my move ♪ come on, baby,
now it's under the groove ♪
♪ come on, baby,
now it's under the groove ♪ ♪ let's go
the groove ♪ ♪ let's go ♪ i know you want to dance
♪ let's go ♪ i know you want
to dance ♪ uh-uh uh-oh, baby
♪ i know you want to dance ♪ uh-uh uh-oh,
baby ♪ come take a ch-ch-ch-chance
♪ uh-uh uh-oh, baby ♪ come take a
ch-ch-ch-chance ♪ oh, let my love t-t-t-take you
♪ come take a ch-ch-ch-chance ♪ oh,
let my love t-t-t-take you higher ♪
♪ oh, let my love t-t-t-take you higher ♪ ♪ well,
let my love take you
higher ♪ ♪ well,
let my love take you higher, baby ♪
♪ well, let my love take you higher,
baby ♪ ♪ oh, let my love take you
higher, baby ♪ ♪ oh,
let my love take you higher ♪
♪ oh, let my love take you higher ♪ ♪ oh,
let my love take you
higher ♪ ♪ oh,
let my love take you higher, baby ♪
♪ oh, let my love take you higher,
baby ♪ ♪ ooh
i feel like i know you.
[Sighs] I'm j.D. I'm around a lot.
Oh, i just got here.
I'm j.D. I'm around a lot.
Oh, i just got here. Freshman.
Oh, i just got here.
Freshman. No. Transfer.
Flunked out, huh?
No. Transfer. Flunked out, huh?
I decided i was finished.
Flunked out, huh?
I decided i was finished. Good for you.
I decided i was finished.
Good for you. So, let me guess.
You're a, uh, photography major.
So, let me guess. You're a, uh,
photography major. I don't even go here.
You're a, uh, photography major.
I don't even go here. I'm just crashing your party.
I don't even go here.
I'm just crashing your party. Morgan!
I'm just crashing your party.
Morgan! Ooh.
Um... Hold on a moment.
Ooh. Um... Hold on a moment.
Don't move.
Um... Hold on a moment.
Don't move. ♪ ooh, yeah
don't move. ♪ ooh,
yeah a little help?
♪ Ooh, yeah a little help?
[Grunts]
A little help? [Grunts] April,
you look drunk.
[Grunts] April, you look drunk.
This is the best night of my
April, you look drunk.
This is the best night of my life!
In recent memory.
Life! In recent memory.
Guys, I've been standing by
in recent memory.
Guys, I've been standing by myself for over an hour.
I don't know anyone here.
Myself for over an hour. I don't know anyone here.
Guys, the whole point of a
i don't know anyone here.
Guys, the whole point of a rush party is to meet and talk
guys, the whole point of a rush
party is to meet and talk to people.
Rush party is to meet and talk to people.
Excuse me.
To people. Excuse me.
[Chuckles]
Excuse me. [Chuckles] Morgan,
I'm allergic to small
[chuckles] Morgan,
I'm allergic to small talk.
Morgan, I'm allergic to small talk.
I'm with her.
Talk. I'm with her.
You two make me weep for our
I'm with her.
You two make me weep for our generation.
What does that mean?
Cassidy, can you be somewhere else right now?
Hey, Morgan.
Else right now? Hey, Morgan.
Do you know diddy, too?
Hey, Morgan. Do you know diddy, too?
Oh, not as well as you, i
do you know diddy, too?
Oh, not as well as you, i gather.
Uh, Cassidy was just reading
gather.
Uh, Cassidy was just reading my fortune.
Oh, I'm sure she knows all
my fortune.
Oh, I'm sure she knows all sorts of tricks.
Hmm.
Sorts of tricks. Hmm.
I'm half gypsy on my mom's side.
Hmm. I'm half gypsy on my mom's side.
Our people are tied into some
I'm half gypsy on my mom's side.
Our people are tied into some really spiritual stuff.
Really? What's in my future?
Really spiritual stuff. Really? What's in my future?
You sure you want me in your
really? What's in my future?
You sure you want me in your head, little girl?
I see... Pain...
And heartbreak. Die alone.
Washed away in a storm.
Die alone.
Washed away in a storm. Aah!
You stupid white-trash bitch!
Aah!
You stupid white-trash bitch! Aah!
You stupid white-trash bitch!
Aah! What the fuck is going on
aah!
What the fuck is going on here?
Sorry, sister Veronica.
Here? Sorry, sister Veronica.
Uh-huh.
Sorry, sister Veronica. Uh-huh.
We're just having a little
uh-huh. We're just having a little fun,
sister Veronica.
We're just having a little fun,
sister Veronica. You're not welcome here,
fun, sister Veronica.
You're not welcome here, townee.
That's cool.
Townee. That's cool.
I was just leaving.
That's cool.
I was just leaving. Thank you.
[Camera shutter clicks]
Thank you.
[Camera shutter clicks] and thank you for having me to
[camera shutter clicks] And thank
you for having me to your party.
I'm out. Unacceptable.
Oh, girls, there is no beef
unacceptable. Oh, girls,
there is no beef between sisters.
Oh, girls, there is no beef between sisters.
All quarrels are settled
between sisters.
All quarrels are settled amicably -- according to the
all quarrels are settled amicably --
according to the ancient rule of combat.
Amicably -- according to the ancient rule of combat.
Release the kraken.
Ancient rule of combat.
Release the kraken. [Cheers and applause]
Go, Morgan! Go, Morgan!
You can beat that bitch! Go, Morgan!
You can beat that bitch!
Go, Morgan! Yeah! Yeah!
[Cheers and applause]
Yeah! Yeah! [Cheers and applause] chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug!
[Cheers and applause] Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Drink up, bitches.
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Drink up, bitches. Drink it up, bitch!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Drink it up, bitch! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Drink! Drink!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Drink! Drink! Whoo!
Whoo! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! [Both vomiting]
[Both panting]
[Coughs] [Groans] Get in.
[Groans] Get in.
Aah! You bitch!
Get in. Aah! You bitch!
You're the bitch.
Aah! You bitch! You're the bitch.
I'm usually the nice one.
You're the bitch.
I'm usually the nice one. And a liar, too.
I don't know if we could still
and a liar, too.
I don't know if we could still be friends.
I'm sorry.
Be friends. I'm sorry.
Are we friends?
I'm sorry. Are we friends?
- Yes. Maybe.
Are we friends?
- Yes. Maybe. I think this is as close as
- yes. Maybe.
I think this is as close as we'll ever get.
I'm a pretty dysfunctional
we'll ever get.
I'm a pretty dysfunctional person.
- Yeah, i guess i am, too.
- I know.
- Broken girls. I got thrown away.
- [Sighs]
I got thrown away.
- [Sighs] Don't worry.
We'll fix each other.
Don't worry. We'll fix each other.
Stick with me.
We'll fix each other. Stick with me.
This is gonna be the best year
stick with me.
This is gonna be the best year ever.
- ♪ LA LA LA LA
ever.
- ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA
- ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA
♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA ♪ on a cold,
cold evening with
♪ LA LA ♪ on a cold,
cold evening with my dear, dear friends ♪
♪ on a cold, cold evening with my dear,
dear friends ♪ ♪ i found a lovely woman
my dear, dear friends ♪ ♪ i found a lovely
woman ♪ i could love her till the end
♪ i found a lovely woman ♪ i could love
her till the end of time as we know it ♪
♪ i could love her till the end of time as
we know it ♪ ♪ my face surely shows it
of time as we know it ♪ ♪ my face surely
shows it ♪ and no one can deter my love
♪ my face surely shows it ♪ and no
one can deter my love ♪ LA LA LA
♪ and no one can deter my
love ♪ LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA
♪ LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA
♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA
♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA ♪ on a warm,
warm evening with
♪ LA LA ♪ on a warm,
warm evening with my newfound love ♪
♪ on a warm, warm evening with my newfound
love ♪ ♪ i took a breath, left death to
my newfound love ♪ ♪ i took a breath,
left death to rest my soul up above ♪
♪ i took a breath, left death to rest my
soul up above ♪ ♪ and although my body
rest my soul up above ♪ ♪ and
although my body lays there ♪
♪ and although my body lays there
♪ ♪ my love always stays, dear
lays there ♪ ♪ my love always stays,
dear ♪ right amongst your heart
♪ my love always stays,
dear ♪ right amongst your heart and soul ♪
♪ right amongst your heart and soul ♪ ♪ LA LA LA
and soul ♪ ♪ LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA
♪ LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA
♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA
♪ LA LA LA LA ♪ LA LA ♪ on a bright,
bright morning
♪ LA LA ♪ on a bright,
bright morning many years from now ♪
♪ on a bright, bright morning many years
from now ♪ ♪ somebody just might find me,
many years from now ♪ ♪ somebody just might find me,
dig me up from the ground ♪
♪ somebody just might find me,
dig me up from the ground ♪ ♪ and although i rest
dig me up from the ground ♪ ♪
and although i rest in pieces ♪
♪ and although i rest in pieces
♪ ♪ my passion never ceases
in pieces ♪ ♪ my passion never
ceases ♪ 'cause no one can
♪ my passion never ceases ♪
'cause no one can deter my love ♪
♪ 'cause no one can deter my love ♪ ♪ no,
no one can
deter my love ♪ ♪ no,
no one can deter my love ♪
- I don't know how we're gonna pay for all of this.
I have like a dollar to my name.
Pay for all of this. I have like a dollar to my name.
- It's covered.
I have like a dollar to my name.
- It's covered. - Yeah, the five-finger
- it's covered.
- Yeah, the five-finger discount works for like 10 items
- yeah, the five-finger discount
works for like 10 items or less.
Discount works for like 10 items or less.
- I never told anyone what I'm
or less.
- I never told anyone what I'm about to tell you.
So if you laugh, i will punch
about to tell you.
So if you laugh, i will punch you.
- Okay.
- My Nana practically raised me.
She's very weird -- always
me.
She's very weird -- always muttering little prayers under
she's very weird -- always muttering
little prayers under her breath.
Muttering little prayers under her breath.
Nana told ghost stories about a
her breath. Nana told ghost stories
about a covenant of witches who chased
Nana told ghost stories about a covenant of
witches who chased their people from the old
covenant of witches who chased
their people from the old country.
Their people from the old country.
It was like ancient-time and
country.
It was like ancient-time and blood-and-Gore shit.
They wrote it down in their
blood-and-Gore shit.
They wrote it down in their demon Bible.
- Right.
Demon Bible.
- Right. This explains nothing.
- [Scoffs]
This explains nothing.
- [Scoffs] Look, i just got to show you.
- Is that everything?
- We would like one lottery ticket -- scratch-and-win,
- we would like one lottery ticket
-- scratch-and-win, please.
Ticket -- scratch-and-win, please.
- What about all this other
please.
- What about all this other stuff?
- Cool your jets.
Stuff? - Cool your jets.
- That'll be $1.
- Cool your jets. - That'll be $1.
- Go one. Pay the man.
- That'll be $1.
- Go one. Pay the man. - [Scoffs]
- [Speaking arcane language]
[Scratching ticket]
- Come on. You can't do that at the
- come on.
You can't do that at the counter.
- That should about cover it.
Counter. - That should about cover it.
- Holy shit!
- That should about cover it.
- Holy shit! You just won 250 bucks.
- What?
You just won 250 bucks.
- What? [Laughs]
- What?
[Laughs] All right.
- Where did you get... That?
- I took it. Veronica doesn't know exactly
- i took it.
Veronica doesn't know exactly what she's dealing with.
- But... You do?
What she's dealing with. - But... You do?
- I've seen a thing or two.
- But... You do? - I've seen a thing or two.
- If Veronica finds out, she's
- I've seen a thing or two.
- If Veronica finds out, she's gonna be pissed.
- Yeah, she might make our
gonna be pissed. - Yeah, she might
make our lives miserable or something
- yeah, she might make our lives
miserable or something like that.
Lives miserable or something like that.
- It's okay.
Like that.
- It's okay. We're gonna put it back anyways.
- [Chuckles]
We're gonna put it back anyways.
- [Chuckles] Okay, near as i can tell, this
- [chuckles] Okay, near as i can tell,
this charter's like a yearbook passed
okay, near as i can tell, this charter's like
a yearbook passed between Alpha girls for
charter's like a yearbook passed
between Alpha girls for generations.
Between Alpha girls for generations.
It's full of rituals and
generations.
It's full of rituals and hexes -- powerful words that can
it's full of rituals and hexes --
powerful words that can alter reality.
Hexes -- powerful words that can alter reality.
This is their dirty little
alter reality.
This is their dirty little secret behind their fame and
this is their dirty little secret
behind their fame and fortune.
Secret behind their fame and fortune.
- Stop teasing, Cassidy.
Fortune.
- Stop teasing, Cassidy. It's not funny.
- It makes perfect sense.
It's not funny.
- It makes perfect sense. How else can a bunch of rich
- it makes perfect sense. How else can a
bunch of rich white people get so rich and
how else can a bunch of rich white
people get so rich and white?
White people get so rich and white?
- It says in here that every
white?
- It says in here that every sacrifice to the black God of
- it says in here that every sacrifice to
the black God of death can bring untold
sacrifice to the black God of
death can bring untold happiness.
Death can bring untold happiness.
- Sacrifice?
Happiness. - Sacrifice?
- Dark one consumes life.
[Inhales deeply]
[Speaking arcane language]
Give me true knowledge of things as they are,
the understanding of the world, the beginning and
as they are, the understanding of the world,
the beginning and the end of eras and what lies in
of the world, the beginning and the end of eras
and what lies in between, the cycles and years of
the end of eras and what lies in between,
the cycles and years of constellation, the thoughts of
between, the cycles and years of constellation,
the thoughts of men, the power of spirits, the
constellation, the thoughts of men,
the power of spirits, the virtue of roots.
Men, the power of spirits,
the virtue of roots. I desire it all.
Virtue of roots. I desire it all.
Secret or manifest!
- What do i do?
- Close your eyes. Make a wish.
[Whimpers]
I want straight a's.
[Coughing]
- [Inhales deeply] I want to be rich.
- [Sighs]
- I just want everyone to like me.
[Sighs]
Me.
[Sighs] [Coughs]
- I want power.
- Ew!
- Gross. Stop it.
Stop it.
- Ew! - Ugh!
- [Laughing] Ew!
- [Screams]
- Oh. Oh, God! Oh, God, wake up. Wake up.
- What's wrong?
Oh, God, wake up. Wake up.
- What's wrong? - Oh, God, there's bugs.
- What's wrong?
- Oh, God, there's bugs. - Ew!
- There's bugs everywhere.
- Ew!
- There's bugs everywhere. Cassidy, wake up. Wake up.
- Go away.
Cassidy, wake up. Wake up.
- Go away. I don't have class till noon.
- Cassidy, wake up.
I don't have class till noon.
- Cassidy, wake up. There's bugs.
- Cassidy, wake up.
There's bugs. [Groans]
- [Screams]
[Groans]
- [Screams] [All screaming]
- [Moans] It's a sign.
He heard us.
- When you're done in here,
the rest of the house will be waiting.
Rest of the house will be waiting.
- This isn't fair,
waiting.
- This isn't fair, sister Veronica.
This wasn't our fault.
Sister Veronica. This wasn't our fault.
- But you're my goddamn slaves.
This wasn't our fault.
- But you're my goddamn slaves. So you'll do as i.
- But shouldn't the whole
so you'll do as i.
- But shouldn't the whole sorority --
- but shouldn't the whole sorority --
- the whole sorority?
Sorority --
- the whole sorority? The rest of the sisters are
- the whole sorority?
The rest of the sisters are staying in a hotel tonight.
But i so graciously volunteered
staying in a hotel tonight. But i so graciously
volunteered to stay back and make sure you
but i so graciously volunteered to stay
back and make sure you get the job done.
To stay back and make sure you get the job done.
And i expect it to be spotless
get the job done.
And i expect it to be spotless by bed check.
- [Sighs]
By bed check.
- [Sighs] I don't like her.
- She's just freaked out.
I don't like her.
- She's just freaked out. You know, I'm a little scared,
- she's just freaked out.
You know, I'm a little scared, too.
- Do you think we did this?
Too. - Do you think we did this?
- It is a pretty strange
- do you think we did this?
- It is a pretty strange coincidence.
- We made this happen with our
coincidence.
- We made this happen with our mind.
Our prayers will be answered.
Mind. Our prayers will be answered.
Dark prince wants us to
our prayers will be answered.
Dark prince wants us to continue.
- It's just something weird
continue.
- It's just something weird that happened.
- [Groans]
That happened.
- [Groans] Irregardless, we're being blamed
- [groans] Irregardless,
we're being blamed for it.
Irregardless, we're being blamed for it.
[Chuckles]
For it.
[Chuckles] I think this calls for an epic
[chuckles] I think this calls for an epic prank.
[Duct tape rips]
- Wake up, my little sunshine.
You think it's funny to boss us
around and pretend you're real bad?
Around and pretend you're real bad?
You don't know what bad is.
Bad? You don't know what bad is.
I hate you.
You don't know what bad is.
I hate you. I hate people like you.
I hate the way you look down on
i hate people like you. I hate the way you look
down on everyone and try to make us just
i hate the way you look down on
everyone and try to make us just like you.
Everyone and try to make us just like you.
- [Speaking arcane language]
- You're not better than me. - [Muffled screaming]
- [Muffled screaming] - [Speaking arcane language]
- I wear my ugly on the
- [speaking arcane language]
- I wear my ugly on the outside, and you cover it up
- i wear my ugly on the outside,
and you cover it up with your trendy haircut and
outside, and you cover it up with your
trendy haircut and your padded bra.
With your trendy haircut and your padded bra.
- [Screaming continues]
- Everything about you is tacky.
- You're a rotten human being!
Tacky. - You're a rotten human being!
- With the glory and power that
- you're a rotten human being! - With the glory
and power that is yours, oh, mighty father, so
- with the glory and power that is yours, oh,
mighty father, so that we may serve you forever
is yours, oh, mighty father,
so that we may serve you forever and ever.
That we may serve you forever and ever.
- [Screaming]
And ever. - [Screaming]
- Cassidy!
- [Screaming]
- Cassidy! Cassidy, no!
Sister Veronica. Sister Veronica, please.
Please wake up.
Sh-she's dead. You killed her.
- Wkilled her.
You killed her.
- Wkilled her. - Oh, my God.
- Wkilled her.
- Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
- You were only supposed to
what are we gonna do?
- You were only supposed to scare her.
- She looks scared to me.
Scare her. - She looks scared to me.
- We're all going to jail!
- She looks scared to me.
- We're all going to jail! - Our lives are over!
- This is the beginning of a
- our lives are over!
- This is the beginning of a new life.
Come, drink from the covenant.
New life. Come, drink from the covenant.
- I am not going down with that
come, drink from the covenant.
- I am not going down with that bitch.
I can't go to jail!
Bitch. I can't go to jail!
I mean, I'm not a criminal!
I can't go to jail! I mean, I'm not a criminal!
- 'Course not.
I mean, I'm not a criminal!
- 'Course not. You're an honor student.
- She had everything handed to
you're an honor student.
- She had everything handed to her, her whole life.
- She had everything handed to her,
her whole life. Fuck her.
Her, her whole life. Fuck her.
- Why does the world need
fuck her. - Why does the world need
Veronica when it has you to take
- why does the world need Veronica
when it has you to take her place?
Veronica when it has you to take her place?
- Shut up! Just --
her place?
- Shut up! Just -- everybody, just shut up!
We can handle this.
Everybody, just shut up! We can handle this.
We're not calling the cops.
We can handle this. We're not calling the cops.
- This concerns a higher power.
We're not calling the cops. - This concerns a
higher power. [Southwork's "amazing grace/
- this concerns a higher power. [Southwork's
"amazing grace/ house of the rising sun" plays]
- ♪ Ooh ♪ ooh ooh ♪ ooh
♪ ooh ooh ♪ ooh
- ♪ and, yes, when this flesh
♪ ooh
- ♪ and, yes, when this flesh and heart shall fail ♪
- ♪ and, yes, when this flesh and heart
shall fail ♪ ♪ and mortal life shall cease
and heart shall fail ♪ ♪ and mortal life
shall cease ♪ but i shall possess...
♪ And mortal life shall cease ♪ but i shall possess...
- In a couple of days, it will
♪ but i shall possess...
- In a couple of days, it will be like this never happened.
- ♪ ...A life of joy
be like this never happened.
- ♪ ...A life of joy and peace ♪
- ♪ ...a life of joy and peace ♪
- ♪ ooh
and peace ♪
- ♪ ooh ♪ ooh ooh
- ♪ ooh ♪ ooh ooh ♪ ooh
♪ ooh ooh ♪ ooh ♪ ooh ooh
♪ ooh ♪ ooh ooh ♪ ooh
♪ ooh ooh ♪ ooh
- ♪ amazing grace,
♪ ooh
- ♪ amazing grace, how sweet the sound ♪
- ♪ amazing grace,
how sweet the sound ♪ ♪ that saved a wretch like me
how sweet the sound ♪ ♪ that saved a
wretch like me ♪ i once was lost, but now
♪ that saved a wretch like me ♪ i once was lost,
but now I'm found ♪
♪ i once was lost,
but now I'm found ♪ ♪ i was blind, but now i see
I'm found ♪ ♪ i was blind, but now i see
- [Sighs] [Sniffles]
♪ I was blind, but now i see
- [Sighs] [Sniffles] Her parents have filed a
- [sighs] [Sniffles] Her parents
have filed a missing-persons report.
Her parents have filed a missing-persons report.
But it's been days.
Missing-persons report. But it's been days.
If you girls could remember
but it's been days.
If you girls could remember anything at all...
If you girls could remember anything at all... Well...
Anything at all... Well...
- [Sobbing]
Well... - [Sobbing]
- Let us keep Veronica in our
- [sobbing]
- Let us keep Veronica in our prayers.
Thank you, girls.
- [Sighs]
- April, may i speak with you for a moment?
April?
- I'm -- I'm sorry, Ms. grace. It's just a lot to take in.
- I just wanted to tell you how
it's just a lot to take in.
- I just wanted to tell you how proud i am of you.
When you began rushing, your
proud i am of you. When you began rushing,
your gpas were abysmal, but now you
when you began rushing, your gpas were abysmal,
but now you are going to make the Dean's
gpas were abysmal,
but now you are going to make the Dean's list.
Are going to make the Dean's list.
I am very impressed.
List. I am very impressed.
In fact, i think you can do more
i am very impressed. In fact,
i think you can do more to apply yourself this semester.
In fact, i think you can do more to
apply yourself this semester. - M-more?
To apply yourself this semester.
- M-more? - I want you to represent the
- m-more?
- I want you to represent the university in a national
- i want you to represent the university
in a national academic competition.
University in a national academic competition.
- Like... A...Spelling bee?
Academic competition.
- Like... A...Spelling bee? - An essay challenge.
- Like... A...Spelling bee?
- An essay challenge. "Moral fortitude in the age of
- an essay challenge.
"Moral fortitude in the age of instant gratification."
- Uh, i don't know.
Instant gratification."
- Uh, i don't know. I-i mean --
- uh, i don't know. I-i mean --
- honestly, dear, you don't
i-i mean --
- honestly, dear, you don't have much else going for you.
- Honestly, dear, you don't have much else
going for you. You need to focus on your
have much else going for you.
You need to focus on your academics.
Winning an honor such as this
academics.
Winning an honor such as this would set you apart from
winning an honor such as this would
set you apart from everybody.
Would set you apart from everybody.
- Uh, okay.
- Hi.
- But she wouldn't run away.
[Sobbing] She loved Alpha house too much.
Something terrible's happened.
She loved Alpha house too much.
Something terrible's happened. I just know it.
- Excuse you.
I just know it.
- Excuse you. - Uh, sorry.
- Excuse you.
- Uh, sorry. Mail call.
- [Sobbing]
- What? [Chuckles]
[Chuckles]
[Giggles]
- Veronica pennington -- missing.
Do you know the whereabouts of
missing. Do you know the whereabouts
of this debutante turned gambling
do you know the whereabouts of this
debutante turned gambling addict?
This debutante turned gambling addict?
Last seen three weeks ago hopped
addict? Last seen three weeks ago
hopped up on goofballs hitchhiking to
last seen three weeks ago hopped up
on goofballs hitchhiking to Mexico.
Up on goofballs hitchhiking to Mexico.
If spotted, do not approach.
Mexico. If spotted,
do not approach. She's a biter.
If spotted, do not approach. She's a biter.
- You're making a scene.
She's a biter. - You're making a scene.
- I'm spreading this
- you're making a scene.
- I'm spreading this information.
- Will you stop that?
Information.
- Will you stop that? You're wasting the fliers.
- What's it matter?
You're wasting the fliers.
- What's it matter? They're pretty much pointless.
How long are we gonna have to do this for?
I mean, can't everyone just get
this for? I mean,
can't everyone just get over it?
I mean, can't everyone just get over it?
- They're gonna find her...
Over it?
- They're gonna find her... Sooner or later.
- Just stay cool, honor the
sooner or later.
- Just stay cool, honor the code of silence, and he won't
- just stay cool, honor the code of silence,
and he won't let that happen.
Code of silence, and he won't let that happen.
- [Scoffs]
Let that happen.
- [Scoffs] You mean the devil won't let
- [scoffs] You mean the devil won't let that happen.
You mean the devil won't let that happen.
- [Chuckles sarcastically]
That happen.
- [Chuckles sarcastically] If it were only that easy to
- [chuckles sarcastically] If it
were only that easy to explain.
If it were only that easy to explain.
- Are you listening to
explain.
- Are you listening to yourself?
- Everything we wanted is
yourself?
- Everything we wanted is happening.
- I mean, i can't explain it,
happening.
- I mean, i can't explain it, but it's true.
I have more money than i could
but it's true.
I have more money than i could ever spend.
- Ever since i stopped going to
ever spend. - Ever since i stopped going to class,
my grades have never been
- ever since i stopped going to class,
my grades have never been better.
Class, my grades have never been better.
- Oh, yeah? Hey, Cassidy.
Better.
- Oh, yeah? Hey, Cassidy. Where are your powers at?
How about you do a fucking magic
where are your powers at?
How about you do a fucking magic trick?
- [Chuckles sarcastically]
Trick?
- [Chuckles sarcastically] I forgive you for doubting me.
- [Sighs]
- Are you sure you don't go to this school?
- I was just thinking about
this school?
- I was just thinking about you.
I heard about that girl that got
you.
I heard about that girl that got kidnapped.
- Yeah, um, nobody knows what
kidnapped.
- Yeah, um, nobody knows what happened to her.
They [Clears throat]
Happened to her.
They [Clears throat] some of the sisters think she
they [Clears throat] some of
the sisters think she ran away.
Some of the sisters think she ran away.
- Well, I'm not gonna miss her.
Ran away. - Well, I'm not gonna miss her.
- I'm really sorry about the
- well, I'm not gonna miss her.
- I'm really sorry about the other night.
We kind of have to do whatever
other night.
We kind of have to do whatever she says.
- But she's not around anymore.
She says. - But she's not around anymore.
You could hang out with me
- but she's not around anymore.
You could hang out with me later.
If you want.
Later. If you want.
- Maybe.
If you want.
- Maybe. What did you have in mind?
- I only do fun things.
What did you have in mind?
- I only do fun things. [Camera shutter clicks]
- I only do fun things.
[Camera shutter clicks] [Arcade music playing]
- This place is really awesome!
[Arcade music playing]
- This place is really awesome! - I know the owner.
- This place is really awesome!
- I know the owner. He finds all these old games and
- i know the owner.
He finds all these old games and fixes them up himself.
- Oh, cool.
Fixes them up himself.
- Oh, cool. - Love coming here!
- Oh, cool.
- Love coming here! It's kind of the best.
- [Chuckles]
[Camera shutter clicking]
[Gasps] Are you taking pictures?!
- You're just so beautiful.
Are you taking pictures?! - You're just so beautiful.
- Not cool, dude. Erase them.
- You're just so beautiful.
- Not cool, dude. Erase them. - No worries.
- Not cool, dude. Erase them.
- No worries. I'm not gonna show them to
- no worries.
I'm not gonna show them to anyone.
- Erase them right now!
Anyone. - Erase them right now!
- I don't trash pictures.
- Erase them right now!
- I don't trash pictures. It's a matter of principle.
- I don't trash pictures.
It's a matter of principle. [Groans]
- Fuck off, creeper.
- Uh, Morgan! - Is everything all right?
- You mean... You don't know?
- Is everything all right?
- You mean... You don't know? - Wow, kid.
- You mean... You don't know?
- Wow, kid. I mean, i really didn't think
- wow, kid. I mean,
i really didn't think you had it in you.
I mean, i really didn't think you had it in you.
- All right, cut the shit.
You had it in you.
- All right, cut the shit. What's going on.
No! No, no, no! No! No!
What's going on. No! No, no, no!
No! No! Where is this?!
No! No, no, no! No! No! Where is this?!
- [Chuckles]
Where is this?!
- [Chuckles] Your boyfriend put it all over
- [chuckles] Your boyfriend put it all over the Internet.
Your boyfriend put it all over the Internet.
I think... This one's my
the Internet. I think...
This one's my favorite.
I think... This one's my favorite.
Your eyes look really pretty.
Favorite. Your eyes look really pretty.
- You think this is funny?
Your eyes look really pretty.
- You think this is funny? - Guys, don't.
- You think this is funny?
- Guys, don't. - You did this.
- Guys, don't.
- You did this. You made this happen!
- No, he did.
You made this happen!
- No, he did. It's okay.
We'll make him pay.
- Just relax. Everything will be all right.
- Hey!
Everything will be all right.
- Hey! - [Chuckles]
- Morgan?
- Shh. You're so much sexier when
- shh.
You're so much sexier when you're not talking.
Every word that comes out of
you're not talking. Every word that comes
out of your mouth... Is a lie anyway.
Every word that comes out of your mouth...
Is a lie anyway. - [Speaking arcane language]
Your mouth... Is a lie anyway. - [Speaking
arcane language] - Black God of death, hear me!
- [Speaking arcane language] - Black God of death,
hear me! - [Speaking arcane language]
- Black God of death, hear me!
- [Speaking arcane language] - [Gasps] Cassidy?
- [Speaking arcane language]
- [Gasps] Cassidy? Oh, my God! Did you see that?!
- Accept this sacrifice in your
oh, my God! Did you see that?!
- Accept this sacrifice in your name!
- Cassidy!
Name!
- Cassidy! Th-there's something here!
- Stop.
Th-there's something here!
- Stop. You scared him very much, but
- stop. You scared him very much,
but can we please leave?
You scared him very much, but can we please leave?
- For the glory and the power
can we please leave? - For the glory and
the power is yours, almighty father, so
- for the glory and the power is yours,
almighty father, so that we may serve you forever
is yours, almighty father,
so that we may serve you forever and ever!
That we may serve you forever and ever!
- I changed my mind.
And ever!
- I changed my mind. I don't want to do this anymore.
- I changed my mind.
I don't want to do this anymore. Please stop.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Please stop. Cassidy!
I'm sorry.
- [Chuckles] You have no idea.
- That wasn't like before!
You have no idea.
- That wasn't like before! That was fucked up!
- Oh, yeah?
That was fucked up!
- Oh, yeah? You all enjoy the new lives you
- oh, yeah?
You all enjoy the new lives you guys got?
Well, that shit ain't free!
Guys got? Well, that shit ain't free!
- I... I don't want to do this
well, that shit ain't free!
- I... I don't want to do this anymore.
- You can't back out now.
Anymore.
- You can't back out now. It doesn't work that way!
- Things got out of control!
It doesn't work that way!
- Things got out of control! - [Chuckles]
- Things got out of control!
- [Chuckles] I can't believe what I'm
- [chuckles] I can't believe what I'm hearing.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
You're all against me.
Hearing. You're all against me.
- No, it's just... I think it
you're all against me.
- No, it's just... I think it might be best if we just... Take
- no, it's just... I think it might be best if we just...
Take a break from each other.
Might be best if we just... Take a break from each other.
- [Chuckles]
A break from each other.
- [Chuckles] You're all pathetic.
- Kill yourself, Cassidy.
- [Chuckles] Tried.
Didn't work.
[Loud knocking on door]
- Um... Can i help you? - Is Juliette Wilson here?
- We'd like to ask her a few
- is Juliette Wilson here?
- We'd like to ask her a few questions.
[Door buzzes]
- So, Juliette...
Have you made any large purchases lately?
- Um... I paid my tuition this
purchases lately?
- Um... I paid my tuition this week...
Bought some books.
Week... Bought some books.
- These are receipts for
bought some books.
- These are receipts for clothing, electronics, and an
- these are receipts for clothing, electronics,
and an airline ticket to London, all
clothing, electronics, and an airline ticket to London,
all bought and paid for in the past
airline ticket to London,
all bought and paid for in the past two weeks, all in
bought and paid for in the past two weeks,
all in Juliette Wilson's name.
Two weeks, all in Juliette Wilson's name.
- I've never been outside the
Juliette Wilson's name.
- I've never been outside the country.
I was gonna treat myself.
Country. I was gonna treat myself.
- Where does a kid like you get
i was gonna treat myself.
- Where does a kid like you get this cash?
- Part-time job, been saving
this cash?
- Part-time job, been saving up.
- Something like that.
Up. - Something like that.
- I think you stole the money.
- Something like that.
- I think you stole the money. I think it belongs to
- i think you stole the money.
I think it belongs to Juliette Wilson from
i think it belongs to Juliette Wilson from Jacksonville,
age 72.
Juliette Wilson from Jacksonville, age 72.
- We got you on identity theft.
Jacksonville, age 72. - We got you on identity theft.
- Ripping off an old lady --
- we got you on identity theft.
- Ripping off an old lady -- that's real cute.
- No, you don't understand!
That's real cute.
- No, you don't understand! I didn't -- i didn't do this!
- You stole her life savings.
I didn't -- i didn't do this!
- You stole her life savings. - No, i didn't do it!
- You stole her life savings.
- No, i didn't do it! I'm a good person!
- That's not gonna hold up in
I'm a good person!
- That's not gonna hold up in court.
- Look!
Court.
- Look! We did something, and it made
- look! We did something,
and it made all of this happen.
We did something, and it made all of this happen.
- What do you mean?
All of this happen.
- What do you mean? What happen?
- Something awful.
What happen?
- Something awful. We hurt someone.
- Something awful.
We hurt someone. If i tell you, i need
we hurt someone.
If i tell you, i need protection.
I need to be protected from her.
Protection. I need to be protected from her.
- We'll be right back.
I need to be protected from her.
- We'll be right back. [Door buzzes]
[Electricity crackling]
- Cassidy?
- You were gonna dime us out. - No.
- You were gonna dime us out.
- No. - I heard everything, Juliette.
- What we did was -- was wrong.
- I heard everything, Juliette. - What we did was
-- was wrong. It wasn't magic it was... Murder.
- What we did was -- was wrong. It wasn't
magic it was... Murder. - I find your lack of faith
it wasn't magic it was... Murder.
- I find your lack of faith disturbing.
- [Exhales deeply]
Disturbing.
- [Exhales deeply] How are you here?
- I'm not. I'm in your mind.
How are you here?
- I'm not. I'm in your mind. You're in a police station...
- I'm not. I'm in your mind.
You're in a police station... Choking to death.
- [Gasping, choking]
- [Singsong] Where do you think you're going?
- Ms. grace just left.
Think you're going?
- Ms. grace just left. I've been expelled.
- She can't do that.
I've been expelled. - She can't do that.
- My essay was plagiarized.
- She can't do that.
- My essay was plagiarized. - Really?
- My essay was plagiarized.
- Really? - [Sighs]
- Really?
- [Sighs] I just don't get it.
I never handed it in.
I just don't get it. I never handed it in.
I didn't even write it.
I never handed it in.
I didn't even write it. [Scoffs]
I didn't even write it.
[Scoffs] Ms. grace says she
[scoffs] Ms.
grace says she double-checked my exams and
Ms. grace says she double-checked my
exams and found "abnormalities consistent
double-checked my exams and found
"abnormalities consistent with cheating."
Found "abnormalities consistent with cheating."
Whatever that means.
With cheating." Whatever that means.
- Well, when you resist the
whatever that means.
- Well, when you resist the spirit's will, there are grave
- well, when you resist the spirit's will,
there are grave consequences.
Spirit's will, there are grave consequences.
- Whatever.
Consequences.
- Whatever. Well, guess it's back to the
- whatever. Well, guess it's back to the boonies for me,
not that any of
well, guess it's back to the boonies for me,
not that any of it really matters.
Boonies for me, not that any of it really matters.
I bet Juliette is spilling her
it really matters.
I bet Juliette is spilling her guts to the cops right now.
- I'm not worried. It'll all work out for me.
- I'm going to get as far from
it'll all work out for me.
- I'm going to get as far from here as possible.
I suggest you do the same.
Here as possible. I suggest you do the same.
- Still got some unfinished
i suggest you do the same.
- Still got some unfinished business with Morgan.
Do you know where she is?
Business with Morgan. Do you know where she is?
- I don't know, and i don't
do you know where she is?
- I don't know, and i don't care.
I think you two should run away
care.
I think you two should run away together.
I'm sure that'll make you very
together.
I'm sure that'll make you very happy.
[Chuckles]
Happy.
[Chuckles] I guess this is goodbye, then.
Accident on the expressway
causing major delays.
[Gasps]
You can't run from the covenant.
I can be anywhere.
Covenant. I can be anywhere.
Fuck you, Cassidy!
I can be anywhere.
Fuck you, Cassidy! I never liked you!
Well, i always hated you.
Please. P-p-p-ple-please!
Please! I won't tell anyone.
P-p-p-ple-please! Please!
I won't tell anyone. I'll run away from here.
I just want to go home.
I'll run away from here. I just want to go home.
It doesn't matter who you
i just want to go home.
It doesn't matter who you tell.
I'm unstoppable.
Tell. I'm unstoppable.
He's inside of me.
I'm unstoppable. He's inside of me.
[Gasps, gurgling]
He's inside of me.
[Gasps, gurgling] Every death brings us closer.
We're becoming.
In the old days, witches would serve poison mixed
in with their coffee to mask the bitter taste.
Serve poison mixed in with their coffee to mask
the bitter taste. Do you want to know what's
coffee to mask the bitter taste.
Do you want to know what's really cool?
What are you doing here,
really cool?
What are you doing here, Cassidy?
The cool part is they use the
Cassidy?
The cool part is they use the same trick to hide the love
the cool part is they use the
same trick to hide the love potion.
Same trick to hide the love potion.
I'll cut right to it, Morgan.
Potion. I'll cut right to it, Morgan.
Why don't you want to be my
I'll cut right to it, Morgan.
Why don't you want to be my friend anymore?
I don't want anything to do
friend anymore?
I don't want anything to do with magic.
Hmm.
With magic. Hmm.
It's a little bit too late for
hmm. It's a little bit too late for that,
don't you think?
It's a little bit too late for that,
don't you think? [Scoffs]
That, don't you think?
[Scoffs] This -- this isn't real.
Don't lie to me like you're
this -- this isn't real.
Don't lie to me like you're one of them.
Juliette and April weren't
one of them.
Juliette and April weren't special like us.
We know what's out there.
Special like us. We know what's out there.
Weren'special?
We know what's out there.
Weren'special? What did you do, Cassidy?
- [Scoffs]
What did you do, Cassidy?
- [Scoffs] Those two were loose ends.
I took care of it.
Those two were loose ends.
I took care of it. You've seen cop shows on
i took care of it.
You've seen cop shows on television.
We couldn't trust them.
Television. We couldn't trust them.
- Oh, God. No.
We couldn't trust them.
- Oh, God. No. Cassidy, tell me you didn't.
Not the girls, too.
Cassidy, tell me you didn't. Not the girls, too.
- [Chuckles]
Not the girls, too.
- [Chuckles] Don't expect me to feel bad.
- Am i next?
Don't expect me to feel bad.
- Am i next? - Mm.
- Am i next?
- Mm. This isn't easy for me.
- I'm not gonna make it easy.
This isn't easy for me. - I'm not gonna make it easy.
- [Chuckles] Seriously?
- I'm not gonna make it easy.
- [Chuckles] Seriously? You're gonna have to do better
- [chuckles] Seriously?
You're gonna have to do better than that.
I'm not even here.
Than that. I'm not even here.
You're in my trance.
I'm not even here. You're in my trance.
I'm a figment of your fucking
you're in my trance.
I'm a figment of your fucking imagination!
How are you going to hurt me?
Imagination! How are you going to hurt me?
- It's not for you.
How are you going to hurt me?
- It's not for you. [Screams]
[Insect buzzing]
- Try to be your friend, and
this is what i get.
- Bless me, father, for i have sinned.
- How long has it been since
sinned.
- How long has it been since your last confession?
- This will be my first and my
your last confession?
- This will be my first and my last.
- So much weight in a young
last.
- So much weight in a young girl's voice.
- Last year, i...
Girl's voice.
- Last year, i... [Sighs]
- Last year, i... [Sighs] Last year,
i tried to kill
[sighs] Last year,
i tried to kill myself.
Last year, i tried to kill myself.
There was a rumor that went
myself.
There was a rumor that went around.
It wasn't true.
Around. It wasn't true.
Everybody believed it, even my
it wasn't true. Everybody believed it,
even my friends.
Everybody believed it, even my friends.
People i trusted most in this
friends. People i trusted most in
this world -- people I've known my
people i trusted most in this world -- people
I've known my whole life -- thought i was
world -- people I've known my whole life --
thought i was capable of such nasty things.
Whole life -- thought i was capable of such nasty things.
I tried to explain myself, and
capable of such nasty things. I tried to explain myself,
and they nodded their heads in pity,
i tried to explain myself, and they nodded
their heads in pity, pretending to believe me.
They nodded their heads in pity, pretending to
believe me. But they never looked at me the
pretending to believe me.
But they never looked at me the same again.
And i thought... "Your friends
same again. And i thought...
"Your friends think you're scum.
And i thought...
"Your friends think you're scum. You must be."
Think you're scum. You must be."
If my roommate hadn't come
you must be." If my roommate hadn't come home...
I'd have bled out.
If my roommate hadn't come home...
I'd have bled out. The doctor said i was really
home... I'd have bled out.
The doctor said i was really gone for a moment.
You know, really dead.
Gone for a moment. You know,
really dead. I don't remember anything.
You know, really dead.
I don't remember anything. There was nothing.
I don't remember anything.
There was nothing. When i left the hospital,
there was nothing. When i left the hospital,
i... I'd see these shadows out of
when i left the hospital,
i... I'd see these shadows out of the corner of my eye.
I... I'd see these shadows out of the corner of my eye.
They were so familiar.
The corner of my eye.
They were so familiar. I knew...
I knew there was something
i knew...
I knew there was something reaching for me, and,
i knew there was something reaching for
me, and, eventually, it was gonna pull me
reaching for me, and, eventually,
it was gonna pull me right back down.
Eventually, it was gonna pull me right back down.
I was marked.
Right back down. I was marked.
Father, i should have been
i was marked.
Father, i should have been scared...
But i felt invincible.
- I can receive your confession.
If you truly are sorry, then God
confession. If you truly are sorry,
then God will know, but taking a life --
if you truly are sorry, then God will know,
but taking a life -- even your own -- is an
will know, but taking a life -- even
your own -- is an unforgivable sin.
Even your own -- is an unforgivable sin.
- I just need to make things
unforgivable sin.
- I just need to make things right.
- There are millions of demons,
right. - There are millions of demons, devils,
and lords of darkness
- there are millions of demons, devils,
and lords of darkness entering our world through idols
devils, and lords of darkness entering our world
through idols as objects to be worshipped, and
entering our world through idols as objects to be
worshipped, and these monsters know only death.
As objects to be worshipped, and these monsters
know only death. "May the holy father, protector
these monsters know only death. "May the holy father,
protector of heaven and earth, who has
"may the holy father, protector of heaven and earth,
who has enlightened every heart, help
of heaven and earth, who has enlightened every heart,
help you to travel the righteous
enlightened every heart,
help you to travel the righteous path.
You to travel the righteous path.
Though you walk through the
path. Though you walk through
the valley of the shadow of death,
though you walk through the valley of the
shadow of death, fear no evil with him at your
valley of the shadow of death,
fear no evil with him at your side."
Fear no evil with him at your side."
[Speaking native language]
Go, now, and trample underfoot all that
stands in the way of the one, true God.
- Cassidy? Cassidy, i came to talk.
- Give up your soul, my child.
Cassidy, i came to talk.
- Give up your soul, my child. He awaits for you.
- Give up your soul, my child.
He awaits for you. [Indistinct whispering]
- You're not in control of
[indistinct whispering]
- You're not in control of yourself.
That thing inside of you... Is
yourself. That thing inside of you...
Is really dangerous.
That thing inside of you... Is really dangerous.
And when it doesn't need you
really dangerous. And when it doesn't
need you anymore, it's just gonna throw
and when it doesn't need you anymore,
it's just gonna throw you away.
Anymore, it's just gonna throw you away.
- You're frightened of me!
You away.
- You're frightened of me! Whore!
- You're frightened of me!
Whore! No one loves you.
- You don't know what that is.
No one loves you.
- You don't know what that is. Filthy slut.
- Stop it!
Filthy slut. - Stop it!
- Everything about you is
- stop it!
- Everything about you is tacky!
- Stop it!
Tacky!
- Stop it! Cassidy, I'm not scared of you!
[Whispering continues]
- Nothing comes without sacrifice.
The dark lord consumes life.
Sacrifice. The dark lord consumes life.
[Whispering continues]
The dark lord consumes life.
[Whispering continues] This is gonna be the best year
[whispering continues] This is
gonna be the best year ever.
This is gonna be the best year ever.
- This is crap.
Ever.
- This is crap. This is just another drama for
- this is crap.
This is just another drama for you to play out -- another
this is just another drama for you to play out
-- another excuse to push everyone away!
You to play out -- another excuse to push
everyone away! Boo-hoo! Nobody loves baby cass!
Excuse to push everyone away! Boo-hoo!
Nobody loves baby cass! You know, not everyone is your
boo-hoo! Nobody loves baby cass!
You know, not everyone is your enemy.
We could've been friends.
Enemy. We could've been friends.
You said that we would be.
We could've been friends. You said that we would be.
We were gonna fix each other.
You said that we would be.
We were gonna fix each other. - Broken girls.
We were gonna fix each other.
- Broken girls. I am thrown away.
- Damn it!
I am thrown away.
- Damn it! Why won't you answer me?!
- 'Cause i want to say this to
why won't you answer me?!
- 'Cause i want to say this to your face.
- Oh, fuck.
Your face. - Oh, fuck.
- Since when is this my fault?
- Oh, fuck. - Since when is this my fault?
You're the real backstabber.
- Since when is this my fault? You're the real
backstabber. We had something, and you went,
you're the real backstabber. We had something,
and you went, and you threw it all away over
we had something, and you went,
and you threw it all away over what?
And you threw it all away over what?
A boy?
What? A boy?
Some hurt feelings?
A boy? Some hurt feelings?
A bad reputation?
Some hurt feelings? A bad reputation?
We're dealing with something
a bad reputation?
We're dealing with something bigger than that.
The learning curve is gonna be
bigger than that.
The learning curve is gonna be very sharp.
- You can justify anything if
very sharp. - You can justify anything
if you think about it long enough.
- You can justify anything if you think about
it long enough. - I didn't need that long.
You think about it long enough.
- I didn't need that long. - You're not gonna kill me.
- I didn't need that long.
- You're not gonna kill me. - Yeah?
- You're not gonna kill me.
- Yeah? Maybe.
I don't know.
Maybe. I don't know.
I think i might be in love with
i don't know.
I think i might be in love with you.
Not that I'm gay.
You. Not that I'm gay.
Hard to explain, but whatever.
Not that I'm gay. Hard to explain,
but whatever. This is college.
Hard to explain, but whatever.
This is college. Things should have been
this is college.
Things should have been different.
- It is what it is.
- Morgan! Morgan!
[Crying] Morgan.
Morgan! [Crying] Morgan.
Morgan, wake up!
[Crying] Morgan. Morgan, wake up!
- Black God of death, hear me!
Morgan, wake up! - Black God of death,
hear me! I surrender my mind and body to
- black God of death, hear me!
I surrender my mind and body to your will!
Fill me with your power so that
your will!
Fill me with your power so that i may always serve you!
[Speaking arcane language]
- J.D.!
- She's crazy. She's gonna kill me.
Morgan, I'm so sorry for
she's gonna kill me.
Morgan, I'm so sorry for everything that I've done.
I'm never gonna do anything like
everything that I've done.
I'm never gonna do anything like this ever again.
I know I'm a jerk.
This ever again. I know I'm a jerk.
I know I'm the scum of the
i know I'm a jerk.
I know I'm the scum of the earth.
I know I'm an asshole.
Earth. I know I'm an asshole.
I don't deserve to die.
Fuck! - How do you like me now?
- Cassidy, don't!
- How do you like me now?
- Cassidy, don't! Please! No more!
- Aww, Morgan.
Please! No more!
- Aww, Morgan. I just don't get you.
This guy's worthless, and you're
i just don't get you. This guy's worthless,
and you're still gonna defend him?
This guy's worthless, and you're still gonna defend him?
We could have whatever we
still gonna defend him? We could have
whatever we want -- the secrets to wealth
we could have whatever we want -- the
secrets to wealth and fame could be ours.
Want -- the secrets to wealth and fame could be ours.
Everyone will love us.
And fame could be ours. Everyone will love us.
- That would mean hurting a lot
everyone will love us.
- That would mean hurting a lot of people.
- I'm okay with that.
- [Whimpers] [Screams]
- [Speaking arcane language]
[Screams]
- [Speaking arcane language] - No!
- [Speaking arcane language]
- No! [Gasps]
We can save him!
We can -- we can take him to the hospital!
They can fix him!
Hospital! They can fix him!
- [Gasping, gurgling]
- [Demonic voice] Shut up! You had your chance.
- I was wrong.
You had your chance.
- I was wrong. I thought there might be a
- i was wrong.
I thought there might be a little piece of you left inside,
i thought there might be a little piece of you left inside,
but you're too far gone.
Little piece of you left inside,
but you're too far gone. You're a monster.
But you're too far gone. You're a monster.
- [Normal voice] I'm a very
you're a monster.
- [Normal voice] I'm a very compassionate person.
That's why i saved you for last.
Do you feel that?
It's like -- it's like there's another.
- Girls?
Another.
- Girls? Hello?
Is anybody here?
[Gasps] Girls?
I phoned, but... No one returned my call.
I didn't want to notify campus
my call.
I didn't want to notify campus security unless it was
i didn't want to notify campus security
unless it was absolutely necessary.
Security unless it was absolutely necessary.
I did tell my neighbor where i
absolutely necessary. I did tell my neighbor
where i was going in such a hurry, what
i did tell my neighbor where i was going in such a hurry,
what with all that's been going on.
Was going in such a hurry, what with all that's
been going on. You can't be... Too... Careful.
With all that's been going on.
You can't be... Too... Careful. [Gasps]
- [Screams]
[Panting]
Aah!
[Indistinct whispering]
- Dear, God! - God is not here today.
- Cassidy! What happened?
- God is not here today.
- Cassidy! What happened? - Cut the shit!
- Cassidy! What happened?
- Cut the shit! - I... I-i-i don't understand.
- [Scoffs] Come on!
- I... I-i-i don't understand.
- [Scoffs] Come on! You know what this is about.
You know exactly what's going
you know what this is about.
You know exactly what's going on.
I could feel the hair on the
on.
I could feel the hair on the back of my neck stand up the
i could feel the hair on the back of my neck
stand up the minute you walked in the house.
I can't believe i didn't put it together sooner.
You are an Alpha girl!
Together sooner. You are an Alpha girl!
- Class president, glee
you are an Alpha girl!
- Class president, glee captain, homecoming queen!
- Class president, glee captain,
homecoming queen! I was the Alpha girl!
Captain, homecoming queen!
I was the Alpha girl! And i will not abide with this
i was the Alpha girl!
And i will not abide with this kind of behavior!
So very unbecoming.
Kind of behavior! So very unbecoming.
- [Gasping, choking]
So very unbecoming. - [Gasping, choking]
- You're out of control!
- [Gasping, choking]
- You're out of control! You're drunk with rage!
Your power is ill-gotten!
You're drunk with rage!
Your power is ill-gotten! You didn't earn it!
- [Strained] I'm gonna eat
you didn't earn it!
- [Strained] I'm gonna eat your eyes out, you old hag!
- It's a real shame.
Your eyes out, you old hag!
- It's a real shame. There was some raw talent there.
If you'd have continued your
there was some raw talent there. If you'd have
continued your studies, you might have become
if you'd have continued your studies,
you might have become something.
Studies, you might have become something.
- I'm gonna kill you!
Something.
- I'm gonna kill you! [Choking]
- You'll do no such thing!
[Choking] - You'll do no such thing!
[Demonic voice] I am a master,
- you'll do no such thing! [Demonic voice] I
am a master, and yare merely an undergrad!
[Speaking arcane language]
I am yours forever, oh, loving, oh, giving, oh, sweet,
chosen lord!
Oh, giving, oh, sweet,
chosen lord! Fill me -- what?! Aah!
Lord! Fill me -- what?! Aah!
Girls, back! Aah! Darlings!
Fill me -- what?! Aah! Girls, back!
Aah! Darlings! It's me, grace!
Girls, back! Aah! Darlings!
It's me, grace! [Screaming]
It's me, grace!
[Screaming] [Shouting indistinctly]
- [Demonic voice] He's with me now.
You should move on.
I feel it, too, girls.
Morgan... Don't do anything stupid.
- Cassidy, it's the book.
Stupid.
- Cassidy, it's the book. It's a gateway for that thing.
As long as the charter exists,
it's a gateway for that thing. As long as the
charter exists, then -- then the demon can
as long as the charter exists,
then -- then the demon can affect us.
Then -- then the demon can affect us.
I have to destroy it.
Affect us. I have to destroy it.
- I wasn't gonna hurt you.
I have to destroy it.
- I wasn't gonna hurt you. Not for real.
I get a little crazy sometimes.
Not for real. I get a little crazy sometimes.
You know me.
I get a little crazy sometimes. You know me.
I mean -- i mean, Morgan, don't
you know me. I mean -- i mean, Morgan,
don't be like this.
I mean -- i mean, Morgan, don't be like this.
- But people died.
Be like this. - But people died.
- They would've done worse to
- but people died.
- They would've done worse to us!
To them, you're just some
us! To them,
you're just some girl -- that girl!
To them, you're just some girl -- that girl!
Never good enough, never smart
girl -- that girl! Never good enough,
never smart enough, never pretty enough!
Never good enough, never smart enough,
never pretty enough! I can't go back!
Enough, never pretty enough!
I can't go back! I won't!
Morgan! Morgan, please!
- I'm sorry.
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Unearthly screaming]
[Shouting in arcane language]
- Morgan, I'm your court-appointed attorney.
- I didn't ask for a lawyer.
Court-appointed attorney. - I didn't ask for a lawyer.
- Well, you're gonna need one.
- I didn't ask for a lawyer. - Well, you're gonna
need one. They say you killed 15 people.
- Well, you're gonna need one.
They say you killed 15 people. - 16.
They say you killed 15 people.
- 16. I'm responsible for the deaths
- 16.
I'm responsible for the deaths of at least 16 people.
- Are you sure you want to
of at least 16 people.
- Are you sure you want to offer up a confession just like
- are you sure you want to offer
up a confession just like that?
Offer up a confession just like that?
- What's the point?
That?
- What's the point? Nothing i can say can change
- what's the point?
Nothing i can say can change what happened.
- There are options.
What happened. - There are options.
- I deserve to rot.
- Listen, Morgan -- i want you to know I'm
gonna do everything i can to get you out of here.
To know I'm gonna do everything i can to get
you out of here. It's kind of personal for me.
I can to get you out of here.
It's kind of personal for me. You see, my wife's an
it's kind of personal for me. You see,
my wife's an Alpha girl, too.
You see, my wife's an Alpha girl, too.
We met in school.
Alpha girl, too. We met in school.
I'm a member of the men's
we met in school.
I'm a member of the men's chapter, omega pi.
You're part of the family.
I'd never let anything bad happen to you.
- [Crying]
- ♪ Amazing grace,
how sweet the sound ♪ ♪ that saved a wretch like me
how sweet the sound ♪ ♪ that saved
a wretch like me ♪ i once was lost --
♪ that saved a wretch like me ♪ i once was lost --
- the Alpha beta sorority was
♪ i once was lost -- - the Alpha beta
sorority was founded in 1910 by 9 seniors
- the Alpha beta sorority was founded in
1910 by 9 seniors at west penn university.
Founded in 1910 by 9 seniors at west penn university.
They established a secret
at west penn university.
They established a secret society with rules and rituals
they established a secret society with rules
and rituals that remain unchanged to this
society with rules and rituals that
remain unchanged to this day.
That remain unchanged to this day.
Many of the richest and most
day. Many of the richest and most
influential women in the world
many of the richest and most influential
women in the world got their humble starts as
influential women in the world got
their humble starts as Alpha girls.
Got their humble starts as Alpha girls.
Alpha house is the sorority's
Alpha girls. Alpha house is the sorority's
three-story brownstone on the
Alpha house is the sorority's three-story
brownstone on the corner of 13th street, buried
three-story brownstone on the corner of 13th street,
buried in the city's campus.
Corner of 13th street, buried in the city's campus.
- The house is a very spooky
in the city's campus.
- The house is a very spooky place.
It gives off a very
place. It gives off a very uncomfortable aura,
and when
it gives off a very uncomfortable aura,
and when one walks through the front
uncomfortable aura, and when one walks
through the front door of the house, one is
one walks through the front door of the house,
one is instantly overcome with, uh,
door of the house, one is instantly overcome
with, uh, uh, the knowledge that very
instantly overcome with, uh, uh,
the knowledge that very nightmarish things have
uh, the knowledge that very nightmarish
things have happened there.
Nightmarish things have happened there.
- Inherited by a founding
happened there.
- Inherited by a founding member and donated to the
- inherited by a founding member and
donated to the organization upon her own
member and donated to the organization
upon her own death, the Alpha house,
organization upon her own death,
the Alpha house, technically, has no owner.
Death, the Alpha house, technically, has no owner.
- There are countless legends
technically, has no owner. - There are countless
legends about the initiations that take
- there are countless legends about the
initiations that take place there, and the
about the initiations that take place there,
and the psychodrama that they put their
place there, and the psychodrama
that they put their pledges through.
Psychodrama that they put their pledges through.
I have heard stories of devil
pledges through.
I have heard stories of devil worship, stories of human
i have heard stories of devil worship,
stories of human sacrifice, even cannibalism.
Worship, stories of human sacrifice, even cannibalism.
- The insides have been
sacrifice, even cannibalism.
- The insides have been described with all the
- the insides have been described with
all the trappings of a late-victorian
described with all the trappings
of a late-victorian gothic fantasy.
Trappings of a late-victorian gothic fantasy.
- This is not a mere social
gothic fantasy.
- This is not a mere social society.
This is not a ladies' sewing
society.
This is not a ladies' sewing circle.
This is a-a-a-an organization
circle. This is a-a-a-an organization
built upon the worship of dark
this is a-a-a-an organization built
upon the worship of dark forces.
Built upon the worship of dark forces.
- [Scream]
Forces. - [Scream]
- The rumors started almost as
- [scream] - The rumors started almost
as soon as the house was founded.
- The rumors started almost as soon as the house
was founded. A 19th-century report mentions
soon as the house was founded. A 19th-century
report mentions a book, uh -- "demons' Bible"
a 19th-century report mentions a book,
uh -- "demons' Bible" - this encyclopedia of evil
a book, uh -- "demons' Bible" - this encyclopedia
of evil contains ancient words that can
- this encyclopedia of evil contains
ancient words that can bend reality.
Contains ancient words that can bend reality.
With a few careful whispers,
bend reality. With a few careful whispers,
anything that these girls can
with a few careful whispers, anything that
these girls can dream of will become theirs.
Anything that these girls can dream of will
become theirs. That is the true secret to the
dream of will become theirs.
That is the true secret to the Alpha girls' success.
- The Alpha girls seem
Alpha girls' success.
- The Alpha girls seem particularly instrumental in
- the Alpha girls seem particularly instrumental
in bringing the young women of the
particularly instrumental in bringing the
young women of the American plutocracy and
bringing the young women of the American
plutocracy and initiating them into their web.
American plutocracy and initiating them into their web.
- Now, in the past, they were
initiating them into their web. - Now, in the past,
they were the women behind the power --
- now, in the past, they were the women
behind the power -- puppet masters to their fat,
the women behind the power -- puppet masters
to their fat, pompous husbands, but today's
puppet masters to their fat, pompous husbands,
but today's Alpha girl alumni are the
pompous husbands, but today's Alpha girl
alumni are the Western establishment.
Alpha girl alumni are the Western establishment.
- In her 1999 autobiography,
Western establishment. - In her 1999 autobiography,
condoleezza rice devotes just
- in her 1999 autobiography, condoleezza rice
devotes just one sentence to her membership
condoleezza rice devotes just one
sentence to her membership in Alpha beta.
- Mainstream scholars would like you to
believe that the Alpha beta is just a regular
like you to believe that the Alpha beta is
just a regular sorority, a boarding house for
Alpha beta is just a regular sorority,
a boarding house for snooty rich girls and a way
sorority, a boarding house for snooty rich
girls and a way for the establishment to
snooty rich girls and a way for the
establishment to nurture, promote, and build up
for the establishment to nurture, promote,
and build up people that think like them,
nurture, promote, and build up people that
think like them, but this goes beyond a regular
people that think like them, but this goes
beyond a regular "you pat my back, and I'll pat
but this goes beyond a regular "you pat my back,
and I'll pat yours."
"You pat my back, and I'll pat yours."
This is a vicious group of
yours."
This is a vicious group of incestual bloodlines that
this is a vicious group of incestual bloodlines
that worship dark forces and seek to
incestual bloodlines that worship dark forces
and seek to impose their will upon the
worship dark forces and seek to impose
their will upon the global population.