Tibburon!
I know it's you.
Show yourself!
Tibburon!
Where are you, huh?
It's tiburon.
Get me out of these chains.
And you called me to
a peace conference
and then tried to kill me.
That's your own fault,
tiburon.
You buried what the cartel
built for years.
They found you,
and they'll find you again.
They're never
gonna stop hunting you.
If I was you,
I'd get my house in order.
You know the game?
I'm not playing your game.
I'll face my death like a man.
Well, you've got 15 seconds.
No. No, no, no, no. No.
No. No.
F...
15 seconds.
12 seconds.
Seven seconds.
Five seconds.
3...
2...
1.
Too late.
Not very manly.
Yes, the other case
is pushed to 10:30,
I believe, so we're
gonna be good on time.
Thanks again.
Brian?
I didn't do a thing.
We don't give a shit.
I--
Thank you.
Wh--hey!
No, seriously.
Yeah. Look,
fax over the documents,
and I'll get it to you back
later today.
No, no, it's good.
Good. That's gonna work.
I'm telling you.
I know this guy.
I know her.
It's gonna be all right.
It's really not a problem.
Mr. holt.
What--Jack,
I'll call you back.
Hey...
Are you okay?
Who are you?
I'm Cal.
Are you all right?
Where are we?
I don't know.
None of you are here by chance.
You're here...
Because of your actions.
Do you always drug
and shackle your guests?
Shh, shh, shh.
Be quiet.
It's about to begin.
We're about...
To play a game...
Of life and death.
Whoever you think I am...
Whatever you think I did,
there's no way
that I deserve to die.
Wait. No.
No! No!
Oh, my God!
No.
Pups.
Some bull, some blue, some...
Threshers.
And the thing about the
sharks is they're--
they're only--
they're only babies.
They're only less
than two months old,
but far more sophisticated
and independent
than humans 20 times their age.
That's the thing about sharks.
Heh.
They enter the world
prepared for the world
because of 20 million
years of evolution.
They're just
garbage cans of the sea.
No. No.
They're--they're
predatory perfection.
They don't sleep.
They don't retreat.
They don't get fatigued or ill.
They swim, and they feed,
and they mate.
Sharks are life.
They're the oldest and purest
forms of being on this world.
They're gods.
They should be revered.
So that's how it's gonna be?
You're gonna feed us
to baby sharks?
The thing is...
This pool is a gateway,
and the pups are sentinels.
If you can enter,
you can get to a pathway...
And your challenge is to
move along that pathway
from this side of the
island to the other.
Yeah, well, what's the catch?
Oh, there's no catch, no catch,
no catch whatsoever.
There are a few
challenges along the way,
but each day, you're
going to encounter
another different kind
of species of shark.
If you kill that shark...
I, being the kind man that I am,
will, uh, give you a reward
to survive the next shark,
but only, only a bit.
You're sick.
Do not say that again, or...
I'll cut out your tongue.
If you wanted to kill us,
why'd you bring us here?
Why didn't you just do it
when you had the chance?
Revenge...
Is like a fine wine.
If you have it,
why not linger over it?
If you play,
you might live.
If you refuse...
You are guaranteed a death.
How's that for motivation?
Oh, you'll be tempted
to swim straight
for the escape hatch,
and that is not
in your best interest.
See, one of the pups is wearing a
collar with the key around it,
so find the puppy.
Find the puppy.
- No!
No!
- Don't! Don't!
No, you son of a bitch! No!
Look for the key!
They're everywhere!
- Where is it?!
- I don't know!
They're eating me alive!
They're not dangerous.
Just bat 'em away.
I got it!
I think he's got the key.
Swim towards the gate.
Come on!
Hurry! Open it!
Francine! Swim!
Go next, ragan.
Hmm. They all
made it through.
Okay, okay.
Where are we?
We made it to the beach.
No, I think it's
just a sand barge.
Make room.
What do we do now?
We've gotta swim to shore.
I'm not getting
back in that water
until daylight.
Well, that shouldn't
be much longer.
Let's just try to rest here
until daybreak.
Oh, God.
What--baby, what are
you talking about?
You--
I want to stay.
Leave me.
No.
Come on, sweet tibu.
Let me just watch.
You know how I love to watch.
This is not a game!
If you don't leave me,
I might feed you
to the sharks as well!
Asshole.
Good morning, everyone.
I hope you slept well.
We have an exciting day
ahead of us.
Jesus Christ!
Better get used to it.
How can you be so flippant?
We're pawns
in this psycho's game.
Well, how the hell do you expect
me to act, lady? Hysterical?
How's that gonna help things?
Enough!
Is everyone okay?
They got me all over.
They got all of us.
Is anyone badly hurt?
No.
I'll live.
Yeah, but for how long?
All right, down to business.
Let me see that.
Oh, my God.
The key unlocks our handcuffs.
Thanks.
Hey.
Who is that lunatic?
You're here now.
Playing stupid
ain't gonna help you.
He's Ethan McKay, aka tiburon.
You mean that drug trafficker?
But what that's
gotta do with me?
I'm an EMT.
What are we gonna do?
I don't want to die.
Don't know about the rest of you guys.
I'm gonna be just fine.
You don't know that.
I do know that.
I planned. I'm prepared.
Prepared for what?
It's my business.
What kind of business is that?
None of yours.
I don't pay
for the best k-and-r
for nothing.
What's k-and-r?
It's kidnap
and ransom insurance.
Look, I have an rfid chip
in my shoulder,
and right now, securecorps'
armed response team
is knocking
on tiburon's front door.
- Hey, buddy.
- It's holt.
You're bleeding
from your shoulder.
Hold still.
I don't see any sort
of object in there.
I'm betting your rfid
chip is on a plane
halfway to Seattle by now.
What do you know?
They'll find me.
That's what I pay them for.
Why do you have
kidnapping insurance?
Why do you ask
so many damn questions?
It's my job.
That's where I know you from.
You're on that TV show,
hit 'em hard, right?
Pete, would you mind
taking a look at my leg?
Yeah, of course.
Let's go sit over there.
I'm Francine, by the way.
Sorry, Francine.
Holt, you've got a bite
on your leg, too.
So where do we go now?
We can't go backwards,
so we start going forwards.
All right. Well, everyone
hold on to their shackles.
We could use every
resource that we have.
Look, we need to start
thinking ahead
if we're gonna survive
this sick game.
You are way too calm
and know way too much.
Who are you?
Ancient Hawaiians
used to drown sharks.
How do you drown a fish?
Well, sharks breathe
by moving forward
to push water through their
mouths and over their gills,
so if you can stop it from
moving, you can drown it.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Or we could pull it backwards.
That'll work, too.
All right, everyone,
grab your shackles.
You, too.
Where are we going?
Inland. Let's find
somewhere to rest.
Let's find a place to hide.
He can't kill us
if he can't find us.
Tiburon's got
cameras everywhere
and booby traps to make sure
we don't stay in one place.
Frankie's right.
The only way out
is to follow the path.
If we don't,
tiburon will find a way
to kill us for sure.
What is it?
Yeah.
Locked.
Should have known.
Hey, Cal, where's that key?
Ah, shoot.
Combination locks.
Should have known.
Let me see that.
Maybe we can pry it open.
No, don't. You'll break the key.
Yeah, Cal's right, sweetie.
We don't know if we're
gonna need this again.
Yeah, like right now.
What is it?
Try this.
5-4-1-2-6-0.
Good eye, Francine.
Yeah.
Ohh.
First-aid kit,
ladies?
Friend.
Swarming around
the food like pups.
Well, you're about
to meet the mama.
I can't go back in the water.
I'm just gonna
sit here and die.
Layla, you-- you've
gotta calm down.
Look, securecorps
knows I'm missing.
I don't care
where that chip is.
If it's not at my desk
at the federal building...
It will trigger a search.
The federal building, huh?
I work at the federal building.
I'm a judge.
I'm a federal prosecutor.
I'd say we acquire
some pretty dangerous enemies.
You guys busted him,
didn't you?
No. Busted his son,
junior.
That's right.
He was killed in bedel canyon.
I was there.
This is starting to make sense.
What did you do?
I was one of
the undercover cops.
Did you shoot him?
Lot of people shot him.
No.
Pete, what's wrong?
It's--it's his son.
I treated him.
Well, at least I tried to,
but he was already
dead when I got there.
There wasn't anything
that I could do for him.
I signed the warrant.
I put the case together.
We outsmarted his son.
We can outsmart him.
If we don't play along,
he'll kill us for sure.
If we do, we might find a way
to beat him at his own game.
Okay. Let's keep
moving, then.
The quicker we move, the
sooner this game will be over.
I thought I saw a trail
head back this way.
Come on, Layla.
Who put you in charge, huh?
Picking fights isn't
going to solve anything.
You save that psychobabble
for somebody else.
I don't care about
your feelings.
I just need you to shut up
and let me figure this out.
It's not just the sharks that
are gonna get us killed.
Shark's blood.
To hunger
and vengeance.
Come on, baby.
You're having all the fun.
Can't I just watch?
It's time to chum the water.
Ah, man.
If we stay out of the water,
we'll be fine, right?
I mean, no water,
no sharks, right?
It can't be that easy.
All right?
Tiburon's crazy,
but he's not stupid.
If he wants us in the water,
we're going in the water.
What the hell?!
Everybody get back to back!
Keep your eyes open.
The door you see is your exit.
The locked door, that is.
Question is,
"where is the key?"
There's--
there's no keyhole...
No lock.
There's--
there's nothing.
Can any of you tell me why...
The majority of shark attacks
take place
in three feet of water?
Shh.
Don't answer him.
We may have to play along,
but we do not have
to entertain him.
Okay. We're all
intelligent people.
But I'll tell you.
The majority of shark attacks
take place
in three feet of water
because that is
where the food is.
The exact amount of water
you are standing in.
Everyone give me your shackles.
We're gonna connect 'em.
We're gonna make a noose.
Oh.
You're gonna drown a shark?
We are.
Francine, ragan,
scan the water.
Holt, you and I
are gonna loop this
around the shark's tail.
Pete and I'll grab the
end and pull it back.
What should I do?
Be quiet.
Don't die.
Keep your eyes on the water,
any ripple, any movement.
Hammerheads...
Are bottom swimmers,
and because of the
placement of their eyes,
they are always looking up.
That's why you never
know where they are
till it's too late.
Any second now.
- Pete!
- Oh, my God!
- The hell with this!
Pete, hang on!
Get the tail!
Oh, my God!
- Pete!
It got him!
Get him!
- Pete!
- Hell with this!
Pete!
Pete, hang on, man!
I'm gonna tie the noose
around the shark's tail.
Yeah! Come on!
- Be careful, Cal!
- Oh, my God!
Help me move
the shark backwards.
- Pull! Pull!
- Pull!
- I got it.
- Is he dead?
Pull it!
- Aah!
- Pull! Pull!
- Get it off me!
- No! He's dying!
- Pull!
The shark is slowing down.
I think it's drowning.
- Pull it!
Oh, my God.
Is it dead?
Hmph.
He was innocent!
He didn't kill your son!
He tried to save him!
Are you defending yourself
or him, detective?
Doesn't matter.
You'll get your turn.
You all will.
- All right.
Can we get out of here now?
Let's get out of here.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh, God.
We need more food and water.
There's got to be another
container somewhere.
Amazing.
It's not just the
sharks that can learn.
Hope they don't learn too fast.
That was even more
exciting than I expected.
Heh.
I'm gonna see if I can find
something to crack 'em open with.
Do we trust him to go
on a search alone?
Yeah, what if he's
helping tiburon?
You know, it seems
like he knows more
about why we're here
than we do.
- What's the difference?
- You can go with him
if you'd like,
but I'm fine right here.
Yeah. Me, too.
Yeah, me, too.
I'm fine here, too.
Look, now we know
what to expect.
We just have to outsmart the
shark before it gets one of us.
Hah! Easier
said than done.
We have to strike
before the shark does.
That's just stupid.
Where the hell
did you find a knife?
You working with them?
What? No.
I don't work
for tiburon anymore.
I'm just as screwed
as the rest of you all.
I found this knife sticking
out of a tree back there.
You know him?
Get us out of here.
Look, if I can't
get out, nobody can.
Give me the knife.
What did you have to do
with his son's death?
Look, lady, I don't
have to tell you anything.
And you're not
getting the knife.
Okay, listen. I know
we're all scared here,
but we're gonna have
to work as a team.
We have a weapon now.
We can fight back.
Hey, there's seven of
us and just one of him.
Wouldn't it be easier to fight
tiburon than the sharks?
What? Do you really think
you could fight him?
Do you really think it's just
tiburon and Elena on this island?
Tiburon has an entire
army at his disposal.
Then why don't you tell us
what you're doing here?
What are you hiding?
What'd you do to his son?
Nothing! I loved the kid
like a brother.
I would never hurt him!
All right.
Whatever you say, man.
Frankie, you need to chill out.
Would you at least be
willing to use your knife
to cut down some
of those sticks over there?
We could sharpen 'em.
At least we'd all
have a weapon.
Yeah. I can do that.
Good luck piercing
the thick skin of a shark
with pointy sticks.
We have one knife and a bunch
of sticks against a shark.
We're dead, all of us.
You can't talk like that.
We killed one shark.
We can kill another one,
especially now that
we're more prepared.
The hammerhead isn't even
the toughest of the sharks.
What if we would have come
up against something worse?
We can't kill all of them.
We're already dead.
Take it then.
What?
Use it to cut your wrists.
Why would I do that?
'Cause, man, you keep
talking about it,
you're gonna be
nothing but a burden
on the rest of us.
I get what you're doing,
but, no, thanks.
Take your knife.
So what's our plan?
I guess we start
with what we know about sharks.
They can hear your heartbeat.
And they have
heightened perceptions.
Blood, movement,
they're attracted
to those things.
You know, I just
thought of something.
I must have seen it on TV, a
nature channel or something,
but there was this guy.
He was swimming with sharks,
and he would touch them in
this spot on the receptors.
He would just pet them
a couple of times,
a-and then they would
go into this trance.
They would roll belly-up and
be out cold for a few minutes.
You want to hypnotize a shark?
That's your big plan, Francine?
No, what I'm saying is if
touching them in that spot
puts them into a sleep,
maybe stabbing them would be a
pretty damn good way to kill them.
But it's gotta be a punch.
It's gotta be hard,
because the shark's skin
is so thick,
and we have just sticks.
Maybe the eye.
Yeah, the eyes are good,
but it's only fatal
if you get to the brain.
There's a better route to that.
Just right over the top.
That doesn't make any sense.
If you're close
enough to stab it,
you're close enough
to get bitten.
You know what?
I'm not doing it.
Look, if you're not going to help
us plan, then keep your mouth shut.
This is a conversation
we need to have,
but we don't need to have
it right this second.
It's been a hell of a day.
But, uh, in the end,
it comes down to that moment,
and for that,
you need a clear head
and all the strength
you can muster.
If we want to get through this,
if we want to live,
we have to be focused.
Cal's right.
We keep walking in
circles, we'll be useless.
I have a plan.
Maybe we can
distract the shark.
How do you distract a shark?
With a heartbeat and blood.
What are you saying?
I'm a bad person.
I'm not like all of you.
I deserve to be here.
I deserve to die. Feed me to the
shark while you guys escape.
That's not true.
No one deserves this.
But it'll work.
We won't let you do that.
We're gonna stick together,
and we're gonna get out
of this alive.
Mind if I borrow that
knife for a second?
Thanks.
Hey, where you going
with the knife?
I'm going to get
some shark's teeth.
You need a hand?
Nope. I got it.
Sorry.
What does he think he's gonna be
able to do with shark's teeth?
They're sharp.
That's a weapon.
Are you serious?
As a heart attack.
You want one?
No, but I'll take
my knife back.
Yeah, give me one.
What the hell, right?
Fine. Who else
wants one?
Take it.
Maybe we can tie
the shark tooth
to the stick and make a spear.
I can't sleep.
Just try, sweetie.
Close your eyes.
Can't sleep either?
No. Can't get my mind
to be quiet.
Too many questions
without any answers.
Yeah. Know what you mean.
What about the others?
Well, I think it's pretty hard
to sleep out here
with the sun blazing,
but everyone's giving it a try.
They seem peaceful, huh?
All things considered.
I'm just trying not to
lose my mind, honestly.
Whatever's left of it.
There you are.
Been looking all over for you.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Good morning.
Time to get up.
We have so many
fun activities planned.
Follow the marked path
down the hill into the caves.
Thirsty.
We should have
brought coconuts.
We'll find some more.
We have been drugged
and kidnapped by a maniac
making us fight
a different shark every day.
You'd be lucky
if you die of thirst.
So what do you think
it'll be this time?
The trap, or the shark?
Oh, God.
I meant the trap,
but now I mean both.
There's no way of knowing,
and nothing we could do
even if we did.
Just keep your eyes open.
Tiburon could spring it
on us at any moment.
As long as Frankie's got
that knife, we got a chance.
Let's keep moving.
There it is.
Jesus. Look at
the size of that thing.
Looks like round two.
This is not good.
Stay calm.
- How the hell am I supposed to do that?
- Try!
Listen, guys, we've got our
Spears to fight this thing.
What else have we got?
I got a knife.
I got the wire.
Okay.
Frankie, knife.
What are you doing?
Something stupid.
What the hell?
I'm with stupid.
Oh, hell.
- What are you guys doing?
- No! Stop!
Don't do it!
Hang on, cowboy.
- Did it work? Come on, holt.
- Nothing.
It's not working.
Come on, Layla.
Throw something.
Francine!
Oh, my God!
What the hell?
Am I too late?
Oh, you're never
too late, darling.
Where is it?
Where are they?
Cal!
Francine?
Come on.
She's gone.
What's happening?
A new day.
Let's see if we
can find some food,
whatever else
tiburon has left for us.
Hey, guys, it's a boat!
It's a boat.
Told you they were
coming for me.
Do you really think tiburon
is gonna leave us a boat?
Only if he left us
a shark in it.
Let's check it. Maybe
there's a cellphone
or a flare gun or something.
And we'll push it in the water.
We can get off
this island, guys.
See anything?
It's full of holes.
Never gonna get off this island.
We need to keep moving.
Even if we could get
this thing in the water,
this thing's not gonna float.
We can't go that way.
Then we'd just be
going in circles.
Stop!
Uh-oh.
It's a mine.
There is no way
we're going through
that minefield.
It's okay.
We're gonna make it.
It's not okay.
None of this is okay.
If I go, I'm dead, and
if I stay, I'm dead.
You don't want to go, fine.
Then go back,
and have one of tiburon's
men finish you off.
Well, then you go first, then.
- Fine. Maybe I will go first.
- Calm down.
This doesn't help
our situation.
It'd make me feel better
if you went first.
Shut up!
It's all right.
Just follow me.
Step lightly.
Here.
Uh-oh. Cal.
Yeah?
Can't move.
What?
I can't move my leg.
The rest of you
keep moving slowly.
How you doing?
Terrified. How do you
think I'm doing?
What are we gonna do?
Give me a few seconds
to think about it.
How many you need?
- 3...
- Okay.
- 2...
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
Run!
Hmm.
I don't get it.
This is all about his son.
You were at bedel canyon.
I don't know about you two.
Yeah, when I was
researching the story,
I didn't see
either of your names.
I was supposed to be at
bedel canyon, not junior.
Like I said earlier,
he was like family to me.
I was out getting
shitfaced drunk that night,
and junior covered me.
Well, that explains it.
Junior was not supposed
to be there that night.
Thought we caught
a lucky break.
When he showed up
to make the buy,
we couldn't believe it.
And it all went to
hell, and he got shot.
Wasn't supposed
to go like that.
What about you?
What can I say?
I'm a junkie.
I went to go buy some
stuff one night.
They asked me if I knew junior,
and I told them what
they wanted to hear.
I just told them so I
can get out of there.
Congratulations.
You've connected the dots.
Now off to the next shark
that awaits you.
That's the biggest fish
I've ever seen.
It's not even
the tiger shark's size
that is its most
intimidating attribute.
Tiger sharks,
more so than any others,
truly have a taste for humans.
They crave us.
They will actually swim
in fresh water
just to get us.
If there was ever
an man-eater...
It's the tiger shark.
We can't go in
with that monster.
We gotta find a way
around the side.
Around the side?
Where are we gonna
go around the side?
Is it even worth
trying anymore?
Look at this.
I have an idea.
I can't wait to see what it is.
Cal, what you got planned?
I need you guys
to link arms with me
and hold me up over the water.
Layla, hold this.
Holt, come on.
Cal, what are you doing?
I'm gonna feed the fish.
Almost.
Got you.
You're not gonna make it, Cal.
We need another person.
Layla?
I'm the smallest and lightest.
Are you sure?
No.
They'll kill themselves
before the sharks
get the chance.
Maybe.
Little more.
Oh, my God!
Layla!
- Layla!
We gotta
help her. Layla!
Layla! No!
Layla, hold on!
- Hold on!
- Help me!
Help me!
- Come on!
- Come on, swim!
Come on!
You can do it!
You can do it.
Swim to the exit.
- Where'd it go?
- Come on!
Help me!
Come on, Layla.
You could do this.
- Go!
- Hang on!
Yeah, come on.
Swim over
to the exit.
Come on.
You can make it!
Come on!
You can do it!
- You can make it.
- Swim!
Come on.
Come on, Layla!
- Come on.
- Come on, Layla.
Come on!
Shit.
Come on.
Don't give in.
Swim over to the exit.
Come on. Come on.
Don't give up.
- Layla, hold on.
- Come on!
Come on, Layla!
Swim!
Don't give up.
Come on.
It's coming for you.
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Go!
Swim!
Get out of there!
No. Just go.
You can make it.
Come on.
Go!
Layla!
Layla.
You did good.
We gotta keep moving.
You're making it too easy.
I thought the whole point
was to let the sharks
just rip them apart.
Everyone needs hope, Elena,
my bloodthirsty Elena.
Even if it is false.
Hey, wait. I see
something, guys.
Look, guys.
I got it.
It's a harpoon.
So this is our next trap.
Think of it as our
next chance to escape.
I'm too old to play pretend.
You're almost
at the finish line.
If you pass this challenge,
you will be rewarded
with a boat.
We really believe him?
Do you want to wait
and find out?
Listen, we've gotta assume
what he says is true.
You know what we have to go do.
Anyone want Sushi?
Frankie, wait!
Frankie!
Come on, holt.
Come on! Where are you,
you son of a bitch?!
Oh, there it is, Cal!
Come on, Cal!
Stab him!
Cal!
No!
Aah! It got my leg!
Frankie!
Frankie, hold on!
No!
Frankie.
Ragan!
Holt!
Come on!
You okay?
Yeah.
Well, you know what they say.
You mess with the bull...
You get the horns.
You all right?
Yeah.
It's like a vacation.
I'm serious.
How you holding up?
I don't want to die.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
How can you say that?
Promise.
And now...
We come to the final act.
You know, if it
wasn't so terrifying,
it'd be beautiful.
Well, the real beauty
is waiting in the water.
As always, the best
must be saved for last.
It's gonna be all right.
How?
The great white shark.
The fiercest, strongest...
And the apex predator
on the planet.
You really can't give up,
can you, Cal?
I guess that's
what you're built for, hmm?
It's admirable,
but it will do you no good here.
Face it.
No.
Not me.
No tricks this time.
No traps this time.
The great white is
the ultimate obstacle.
Get out of the water,
that's it. You win.
Hey, we can make it.
But not together.
W-what are you doing?
We go in together,
we die together.
But if one of us can distract
the shark long enough,
the other can get to shore.
Distract the shark?
But th-that's suicide.
Probably, but if I can
distract it long enough,
then you can get to shore.
What? N-no.
No, you can't do that. No.
We have to face it.
But I need you to get to shore.
I promised you're gonna live.
I'll get to the shore,
and then I'll
distract the shark
so you can come over.
That's the plan.
There!
Cal!
No!
Ragan.
Ragan...
I got it.
You did?
Is it really dead?
Yeah. I really
killed it.
Let's get out of here.
Oh, God.
- Ohh!
- Ahh!
Ragan!
Cal!
Ahh! Come on!
Bitch!
See, I--
I can't let you
leave the island.
I won't let you.
If I'm not leaving,
neither are you.
God!
Yaah! Bitch!
See? Heh.
Tiburon likes drama.
But I told him it would
be a lot more easier
if I put a bullet
in your vapid little head.
Oh, sh...
The game's over, tiburon.
Ah. So the last man
standing is a woman.
Well done, ragan.
You're not getting off
of this island alive.
Who's going to stop me?
I will.
I already killed your whore.
Ah...
Elena.
But whores are replaceable.
You're not
gonna get the chance.
You people...
Killed my son,
my only pride and joy.
I said I would have revenge,
and I did!
It's over!
Tell me where we are!
You're 100 Miles South
of key west.
International waters.
You know what
that means, don't you?
I've got a yacht
in my harbor, several.
You can take one.
You've earned your freedom.
That's not what I want anymore.