Eight, nine, ten.
Ready or not,
here I come.
Larry!
Rachel!
Who are you?
What are you
doing here?
We're playing
a game.
I'm playing with
Larry and Rachel.
Who are you?
I'm Michelle.
You brought me here.
You drove me.
(SIGHS)
(PHONE LINE TRILLING)
LARRY:  Yeah, Darkroom?
I got your card
from Rachel Lefferson.
She's a therapist at...
Oh, yeah, Rachel.
Rehab center.
Right.
Parents gone.
Any other
living relatives?
No. (SIGHS)
What about school?
They took away
my aid
after the accident
and the court order.
(TURNING PAGE)
I'm gonna come
to the point, Michelle.
You're eligible to leave
with my signed approval.
But you'll stay indefinitely
until I give you
a good review.
If you want
to get out of here,
you have to prove it.
(SHIP HORN TOOTING)
(CAR APPROACHING)
Someone call
for a ride?
Yeah.
(MICHELLE SIGHS)
Thank you.
No problem.
So, where to?
The address
is 1040 Millview Lane.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just...nothing.
Do you mind if I ask
what happened?
To your leg?
It doesn't matter.
I'm sorry, my mouth
goes too fast sometimes.
RACHEL:
And then what happened?
I woke up in the hospital,
and I had never felt
that pathetic.
(SIGHS) Oh, God, my brother.
How could I have...
He's gone.
(SNIFFS)
RACHEL: Thank you, Jean.
Takes a lot of courage.
(JEAN SOBBING)
RACHEL: The process has begun.
You've started
on the course of penitence.
And you'll find peace.
I know you will.
Michelle, have you decided
to share
your experience
with the group?
How about it?
No?
Well, we're here, I guess.
Michelle!
You can pull around back.
Nancy will take
care of you.
Yeah, she'll be doing
your hair and wardrobe.
I thought I was just
doing some PA/gopher stuff.
Not today,
I had a model drop out.
That's okay, right?
It's the same pay.
Oh, you want me
to model?
Hmm.
What exactly
is this for?
It's for print
fashion shots
for a real
estate periodical.
Real exciting stuff, huh?
Well, I've never
done this before.
Ah. Don't worry.
I'll take good
care of you.
I'll see you in a bit?
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
Hey, there.
I'm Daniel.
I've seen you around.
Michelle.
I work here,
odds and ends.
Yeah, I've seen you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You ready for
the bad news?
We're not allowed
to smoke here.
I've heard.
Shit.
Thought I was
enlightening you.
Hmm.
Well, I'll see you around.
Yeah.
(HUMMING)
Thanks for the ride.
DANIEL: Sure thing.
Give a call
if you need
a ride back.
Okay. Thanks.
Hi, you must be Michelle!
Uh, yeah. It's me.
You find it okay?
Okay, come on, come on,
let's get started.
This place
is amazing!
Does someone
actually live here?
It's for sale.
Come along.
No time for today.
MICHELLE: Place is huge.
Larry wants to start
in the study, then move
to the backyard.
I think the weather
is gonna hold up
just fine.
You need to use
the little girl's room?
Uh, no, I'm fine.
(CHUCKLES)
All right,
let's get started.
Larry likes to keep
his schedule.
Could you take off
your jewelry?
My, you are
very lovely.
(SIGHS) Thank you.
(NANCY HUMMING)
Am I hurting you?
No.
(HUMMING)
Ooh, so sorry.
Did I hurt you?
Pretty, pretty.
Okay, outfit, outfit.
MICHELLE:
Larry said that this was
some sort of
real estate shoot?
It's like a PR shoot.
You just have to smile
and be yourself.
Here we go.
Yeah, this looks
like your size.
You'll look great.
Oh, and, uh...
Put these on
and I'll give you
some privacy.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
The reason I'm not
in school anymore
is because, um...
I was in
an accident.
You can do it, Michelle.
You can be purged
and free of your past.
Come on.
(MICHELLE SIGHS)
I was driving.
And Trey was...
(STUTTERS)
He was my boyfriend.
We were arguing.
(INAUDIBLE)
He was distracting me.
It wasn't my fault.
Is that it?
Yep.
Knock, knock.
Excellent, Larry
is gonna be so pleased.
So, the study
is down the hall.
This way, you make a right.
It's the last room.
My parents died
when I was 14.
And I just moved around
from foster home
to foster home...
Until I realized
I was better off on my own.
My dad died
when I was young, too.
Makes it hard
to trust people.
You know,
I felt better
when I talked.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't mean
to upset you.
I just... I can't talk
about this anymore.
(SIGHS)
You're so lucky
to be leaving this dump.
Remember, you gotta
talk about what got you
into here, Michelle.
It's the only way out.
You got
no other choice.
See ya.
Hello?
Nancy?
(SIGHS)
Can I, uh...
Can I talk to you?
Jean got here
after I did.
(SIGHS)
Why am I still here?
Jean was
an active participant
in this community.
When you participate,
then you can go, too.
But I just want
to move on
with my life.
Well, I find that
very offensive.
I'd say you have
plenty of issues
to work out here.
(WOMAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER P.A.)
Hello! Nancy!
Larry?
(KIDS LAUGHING INDISTINCTLY)
Hello?
Is anyone there?
(KIDS LAUGHING INDISTINCTLY)
(ANXIOUSLY) Larry?
Nancy?
Hello.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Shit! (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Oh, my God!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KIDS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Please answer me.
BOY: Come get me, Rachel.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BOY:  Oh, careful!
WOMAN:  Boys, play nice.
Play nice.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
WOMAN:  Boys, be sweet,
be sweet. Come on, Daniel.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
Is your name...
No.
BOY:  I can't pick it up...
(MOTHER GASPS)
(ALL LAUGHING ON TV)
GIRL:  It's not working.
Here, you try.
(INDISTINCT SPEECH)
MOTHER:  Amy!
(KIDS GRUNT)
(GASPS)
Oh, my God.
(MUTTERS)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(SHOUTS) Hey!
What the fuck is this?
Let me out! Come on!
(GRUNTS)
What do you want
from me? Come on!
(RATTLING KNOB)
No!
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
RACHEL: This is your key
and the address where
you're gonna be living.
Work is really
a big part of
the rehabilitation process.
Do you have
any thoughts?
I'll see what comes.
I do want you
to stay off the street.
I wouldn't want you
to end up some kind
of dirty girl.
What's this?
Larry's a friend.
He sometimes has
opportunities for our girls.
I'll let you
finish up here.
Hello?
Hello, you fucks!
Hey!
Oh, fuck! Fuck you!
Hello?
You fuckers!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Cheers.
And another.
Well, if you act
like a dick, I'm gonna
keep going at it.
Look, stop lecturing me.
Oh, you're such
an asshole.
Get over here!
Hey! Hey!
What?
Watch your hands.
You're twisting
her arm.
And how is that
any of your business?
I'm making it
my business,
all right?
Stay out of it!
Oh, my God!
Yo, why don't you
take control
of your girlfriend.
Uh, you know what?
Fuck you.
No, fuck you!
No! It's not
my fault. Help!
Get out of here!
Hello?
Is anyone there?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Hi.
So, you're leaving us.
Finally.
You must feel good.
Uh...
Yeah, I mean,
as good as it can feel.
I still got some shit
to work out, though.
You'll do fine. Hey.
I brought you something.
What?
Thought you could
think of me when
you smoke them.
You know, uh,
maybe we could...
I have some
additional forms for you.
Daniel, I thought that
you needed to pack up
the art supplies?
Yeah, I'm on it.
Good luck out there.
(SHRILL FEEDBACK)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
No!
(SOBBING)
(WOMAN WAILING ON TV)
Oh, my God!
Please help me!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHRILL FEEDBACK)
(SHOUTING)
Let me out of here!
LARRY:  Quiet!
What is this about, okay?
Let me out!
Shut your mouth!
Have a seat.
Have a seat in a chair!
Let's begin.
LARRY: (ON TV)  Confess.
Confess, my child.
WOMAN: (ON TV)  I confess.
LARRY:  What do you confess?
I was wrong.
Oh.
Praise God.
The purging has begun.
Been a naughty girl,
haven't you?
Haven't you?
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
Say it.
I've been
a naughty girl.
LARRY:  You're a slut!
A Goddamn whore.
(SOBBING)
(LARRY SLAPS)
WOMAN:  What are you doing?
(SCREAMING)
What are you doing?
Please! No!
Confess.
LARRY:  You have to confess.
Huh?
MICHELLE: (ON TV)
No! Let me out!
Let me out! Hey!
(SCREAMS)
LARRY: (ON INTERCOM)
Shut your mouth.
(SCREAMING) Oh, my God!
(SOBBING)
How is this my fault?
I was trying
to protect you.
Look, I don't need
your protection.
ERIC: Guys,
it's done, relax!
LAUREN: No, no, no,
the night's over,
I just... Done.
ERIC: Okay.
TREY: What would you
have done to that guy?
Oh, shit!
ERIC: Michelle,
should you be driving?
I am fine, okay?
It's my ride,
my rules.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GASPING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUD)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
Let go of me.
(SCREAMING) No!
Stay the fuck
away from me!
What do you want
with me?
Stay the fuck
away from me!
No!
(SCREAMS)
(DOOR OPENS)
I told you
she was a dirty girl.
MICHELLE: You bitch!
The Lord hates
a crude tongue.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
LARRY: Patience, sister.
(GRUNTS)
(MICHELLE SCREAMS)
MICHELLE: No!
(SCREAMS)
Welcome to my
little fun house.
Isn't that right, Daniel?
(MICHELLE GROANS)
We had so much fun
here as kids.
(SCREAMS)
Why are you
doing this to me?
I didn't do
anything to you.
We got plenty of time
to answer that question.
(BONE CRACKING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
Fuck you!
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
What is wrong
with you?
You put me
in a very bad position.
I can't keep
protecting you.
Stop it.
Daniel knows
his role.
He better know
This is your responsibility
to teach him.
We can't take care
of him forever.
I have work to do.
Go be eyes and ears.
(PUNCHING WALL)
Don't ever talk that way
in front of him again.
Know your place.
WOMAN: (FAINTLY) Hello?
WOMAN: Hello?
Hello?
Is someone there?
WOMAN: Yes.
Who is this?
(SNIFFS)
My name is Jean Balfour.
Jean?
Oh, my God,
it's Michelle.
Michelle.
Oh, my God.
JEAN: (MUFFLED)
We gotta get out of here.
These people are nuts.
(SIGHS)
Um...
Is there anything
in your room?
Anything at all?
JEAN: Just a chair.
I'm wearing some
stupid green dress.
My God, I think
they're gonna kill us.
MICHELLE:
They're not gonna kill us.
We're gonna
get out of this room.
How?
I don't know.
I just...
I need to think.
(SIGHS)
(GASPING) Oh, God!
(DISTANT THUDDING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, God.
Michelle!
(SHOUTING) Michelle, help!
Wait, what are you... Wait!
What are you doing?
(JEAN GASPING)
Oh, no, no,
no, no! Please!
Please!
(GROANS)
(SHOUTING) Leave her alone!
(DRILLING)
(SCREAMING)
No! Stop it!
MICHELLE: Let her go!
Jean!
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(JEAN GASPING)
(SHOUTS) Hey!
Jean!
Hello? (SOBBING)
(SCREAMS)
(CRYING)
God!
(MOANS)
RACHEL: Sweetheart.
I have something for you.
(PANTING)
Not so fast.
You have to sing
for your supper.
Give me the food, bitch.
Tsk, tsk.
The Lord hates
a crude tongue.
RACHEL: Now let's remain
lady-like, shall we?
Shall we leave you
in the dark?
No, no, no just...
I'm sorry.
I'm just really hungry.
RACHEL: Shut up!
Now do as I say.
Go to chair and sit.
Who's a dirty girl?
RACHEL: Who's
a dirty girl?
Please just tell me
what you want me to do.
Who's a dirty girl,
you little slut?
Me.
Me!
(GASPS)
Mmm...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(VOICE ECHOES)
(LAUREN CHOKES)
(COUGHS)
(GROANING)
We gotta get out
of here, okay?
Easy, easy.
Okay.
(SCREAMS)
Help me.
Please don't leave.
You have to help me, okay?
I wish... (GROANS)
You can make it. Go.
I can't go.
I can't go!
Go.
Michelle...
I can't go!
Go.
I'm sorry.
(SOBS)
LAUREN: You can make it.
You can make it.
(SOBBING)
You left me there, Michelle.
Lauren.
It wasn't my fault, Lauren.
(INAUDIBLE)
(CAR HONKING)
Help, please!
I was worried they put
too much medicine
in your food.
My brother and sister
are angry, that's all.
I need to...
I need to get up.
Here, I can help.
What is it?
You sniff this.
DANIEL: It'll make
the nightmares go away.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Feel better?
Mmm... (SNIFFLES)
Do you want to see my scar?
I saw yours and that's how
I knew we would be friends.
I haven't shown this
to anyone,
but we have
a real connection
I got this a long time ago.
That's right, Daniel.
We have a connection.
You want to be
friends, right?
We need to help each other
get out of here, together.
I don't think
that can happen.
DANIEL: That's between
Larry and Rachel.
We can stay here, though.
You people
are fucking crazy!
Don't call me that.
That is not nice.
This is our funhouse,
like my brother said.
LARRY: Daniel?
Larry, please.
I was just...
You see what
you've done to him?
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
LARRY: (ON INTERCOM)
Michelle...
Wakey-wakey.
(GROANS)
Since you bullied
my brother...
Now I'm gonna bully you.
I didn't bully him.
LARRY:  Choose.
I don't want to.
Choose or you get both.
LARRY:  Hmm?
Okay.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(FOOTSTEPS FADING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GASPING)
Michelle?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(DRILL GUN WHIRRING)
(DRILLING)
No! (SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING) Larry,
she's getting away!
(GASPING)
(WHIRRING CONTINUES)
(MICHELLE GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
Larry! Help me!
Don't go!
Please, come back.
MICHELLE: No!
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Just wait till your sister
gets home, you moron!
All right, little girl.
There's no way out!
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS)
Help!
Help me, please!
Help me.
Okay.
(CRIES) Help.
What did he do?
He helped one of them
with food.
She's in the ceiling...
Like a little bitch.
A little rat bitch!
But he's sorry now.
Right, Daniel?
You can turn around.
I'll get the whore.
Don't bother.
She can't escape.
I made sure.
She'll be down
soon enough.
There's someone
down the hallway
who needs your attention.
Oh, yeah, right.
(PANTING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
MICHELLE: Oh, my God.
Is that Jean?
Jean.
(WATER RUNNING)
I don't get it, Daniel.
What's gotten into you?
Is it the new whore?
Is it her dirty body?
Parts?
I could cut them off?
Give them to you as
an early birthday present?
No, Larry.
(STUTTERS) That's not...
Honestly, Daniel,
I sometimes despair
for your soul.
Are you worried
about this?
You don't need
to worry about this.
It's for the dirty sinners.
Are you a dirty
sinner, Daniel?
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
No, you're no sinner.
You're the most
innocent of us.
(INHALES) Too innocent, hmm?
(SCREAMS)
A little pain
to remind you of
what's important.
We're family, Daniel.
It's all about
the family, hmm?
(KISSES)
I love you.
(WHIMPERING)
MICHELLE: Jean?
Okay.
Come on.
(TELEVISION SWITCHES ON)
(TV PLAYING)
RACHEL:  Larry!
LARRY:  Tickle Rachel.
Tickle Daniel!
Daniel!
(ALL LAUGHING)
Be nice, boys!
Play nice. Play nice.
Now children,
who has sinned?
ALL:  We have, Mother.
WOMAN:  And who needs
to be purged?
We all need purging.
Remember that.
What were you doing
in your room, Daniel?
Nothing, Mother.
Idle hands
are the Devil's
playground.
You were looking
at these comics again,
weren't you?
Is this a funhouse?
Do you know what God
told King David in the Bible?
He said, "Fear not.
And show courage."
"For your Father
is with you always."
Your superheroes
act bravely, Daniel.
It's what
makes them special.
You're a little coward,
aren't you?
Open your shirt.
Mother, please!
(SHOUTING)
Open your shirt!
Now! Now!
Open.
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God.
WOMAN:  What are you
telling me?
I started to bleed.
From your private area?
I hoped you wouldn't
be touched by this.
But you're a dirty
little girl.
Say it!
What are you?
A dirty girl.
(WHISPERING)
I can't hear you.
A dirty girl!
A dirty girl.
MOM:  Thankless child...
You were supposed to put
together Mother's table.
You didn't do it right.
Mother got hurt.
I'm sorry, Mother.
That's all right.
MOM:  But I think
you know God's law.
What is it?
An eye for an eye.
MOM:  I'm sorry, my child.
This is painful
for me as well,
but you made your bed.
Now you have to lie in it.
(DRILL GUN WHIRRING)
Mother, no!
Oh, my God.
Ugh!
(WOMAN CRIES)
LARRY: You have to confess.
Are you a sinner?
No. I am not a sinner.
Hmm? But you
are a sinner.
And you must
confess your sins
in order to be free.
I am a sinner.
I want you
to say it louder,
so you can get purged.
I am a sinner.
Louder.
I am a sinner...
(GRUNTS)
(CROWBAR CLINKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(LOUDSPEAKER FEEDBACK)
(FEEDBACK SWELLING)
Jean.
Jean!
You're gonna be okay!
Oh, my God.
Come on, baby.
Come on!
(CRIES)
We're gonna go.
You're making it.
(COUGHS)
JEAN: I can't do...
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Back pocket!
(MICHELLE GROANS)
(STRAINING)
(SCREAMING) Michelle!
Ssh...
You've been
a very bad girl.
But everything's
gonna be okay now.
I'm gonna get
the dirty girl
back to normal.
Pretty girl. Ssh.
Mommy loves you.
You are one
resourceful girl.
Shoes are important.
Usually we take
much longer.
Seeing it takes time
to purge.
But since you
messed up our schedule
with your stunt.
Choose.
(INHALING)
Choose, or you get both.
Time to purge.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(CRIES)
(GASPS)
Praise the Lord.
I knew from
the first moment I saw you,
how rotten you were.
RACHEL: Confess.
When your mother tells you
to do something, you do it!
I confess.
For what?
For killing my friends.
Not your dirty whore friends.
I'm talking about me.
What do you confess to me?
The dirty girl
just doesn't get it,
does she?
Apparently not.
(CRIES)
(ALARM BEEPS)
(BEEPING STOPS)
(SIGHS) We'll be back.
Don't go anywhere.
I have a new friend
to attend to.
Handle this.
Come here.
You know what to do.
I'll be there
in a few minutes.
(DOOR OPENING)
You really messed up.
I wanted to be friends.
Why couldn't you do it?
When we met,
I was nice to you...
Because I thought
you were special.
I thought you would
understand me.
And then I saw
your scar...
And I knew we had
a real connection.
Larry?
Hi. Kristen, right?
Yeah, you said,
uh, 2:00.
I did, you know,
it's the darnedest thing.
We had a scheduling problem
with yesterday's model.
I know, I know,
it's such a bummer.
Do you think we could
reschedule tomorrow?
No, but Mother
always said,
you can't trust
a pretty girl.
I know that now.
No, please!
Oh, don't be such
a coward! A baby!
No, let me tell you,
Mother!
No, let me
tell you, Daniel.
Let Mother speak.
You know what
I always say.
That courage is the most
important thing.
And that what makes
a superhero special,
is their bravery.
And you've been very brave.
You've proven
that you could
stand up to Mother
and be your own man.
I'm so sorry, Daniel!
Now come,
give Mother a hug.
(LAUGHING)
I may have
to work tomorrow.
I was really psyched
about getting
the photos today.
I promise
I'll pay you double
and we'll give you
extra shots.
Huh? Just for being
such a sweetheart?
I'm so sorry.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Okay.
Thanks, Kristen.
Tomorrow, I promise you,
a shoot you'll never forget.
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
No!
(SCREAMING)
Daniel...
(GASPING)
Rachel!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SOBBING)
The Lord is my shepherd.
And I shall not want.
He leadeth me
to the soul...
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(CROWBAR CLANGING)
I'm with you.
Are you okay? Huh?
(BOTH PANTING)
Okay.
Let's go this way.
(INAUDIBLE)