Hello
There are people here
Hey, what are you doing here
Sorry l'm just looking for someone
It's a private place
Can you help me, please l've been
looking for months
His name is Frank
Oh
We call the police.
Where?/Hospital
He was there
Why is there
He died
Hello, it's me, what did l wake you
What time? / l find him
l found
l'll see him tomorrow morning. / Good
He'll be fine
l'll be right back
Franc
You've arrived at the destination
Yes l'm here to see the doctor
Barrows
lt is a secure unit
for people with severe mental
disorders and alzaimer, l think that
in the suffering father
He sent three months ago, there were
reports that's why he brought it to
us
How bad is he. / He may remember you,
but the memories come and go
Most of the time he was in his world
But his illness made him very
paranoid
l understand how hard it is
Franc
We do not know frank. / Course
He was not the first to come here
without identification
But still there is not detected, it
is not unusual unfortunately
l'm surprised you could find us. /
Yes, it is not easy
l've been looking for months
We're close, l know him
He's like what
What are you talking like he's dead.
/ Sorry, must have been very
difficult
Frank that he is not the person we
care who you know
You must understand it is not frank,
it penyakkitnya
and it is easier to think of him as
a different person
Strangers even, maybe you can see
for yourself
Good yes, that's what makes the
difference
What? / This pie
Come on frank you were special
visitors
You can identify who he is Frank
Your son is coming to visit you,
it's James
Jimmyku
l'll leave you two
l'm out if needed. / Thanks
You're okay
Hospital
Thanks. / Not
Where's my stuff. / l do not know
Dad. see it
Yes, you can remember. / Be careful
Be careful.
Come on
You watch yourself
Here it is
That was a good walk. / l'm sorry
This treatment, he often exchange
l do not know who the actual
original frank again
l try the best, you want me to do
l do not know what to say
He was sick, very sick
But l want to say
Pago. / What?
l'm sorry
Do not like it, because l could not
l see what l can do, okay
This, wear
He's better since lunch
Hello dear, l'm Susie
Yes. / There are people here to see
you, son Jamie
Hmm
Now
Are you going to say sorry no frank
You really hurt him. / lt
No. ..
All right. / l will never hurt you
Jamie
Come on
What he
l do not know
Do not know. / l notice you
Time to treatment he
Frank wait .. wait
Wait a minute, make sure he drinks
Come on
Okay, this is
No, what you're doing, you can not
do it
Come on ..
Good
Come on
l told
l'm telling you, use one of these
Well .. that's enough
There are not any there
What face, pretty face
l like what
This
That night, what makes you relaxed
Yes
OK
lt was good stuff
You want to
lt's just a game
There is no father, this
Here
l miss you
Hit me
Excuse me. / Yes. / Stop him
lt's a big mistake. / Hit me
l'm not supposed to be here
l'm not supposed to be here. / Hit me
l do not want to. / Hit me
Hit me. / Stop father
Hey, stop
Stop
l need your help, l want you to get
up
Come on, slowly
Correct
So this way
Come on
Take me, l'll come with you. / You
go back into the
Stay with me
You see
Come on
Take your bike lock
What are you doing
Spin
Father release
We managed to do
We came out
This is good yes
What about music sedikt
Okay
Little memory yes
Follow me
You can remove the current
l'm paranoid right
Okay
Dad let's get back to the car
Do not let him
Come relax
Come on .. back kemobil
Sign kemobil, let
can not believe
You know what l would do
Come True
You're going to drive, okay
Are you comfortable
Do not do it
You do not ... father opened the
door, you can not drive this car
Daddy please do not, please ... open
the door, the father ...
Shit, dad ...
fuck you
You're crazy huh
Will you let me drive now. / Yes
All cops are bastards.
lt's true father.
Those who create it.
Frank.
Are you okay?
Are you crying?
No.
What is it?
l'm not feeling well.
l do not want to come.
You should come, it's your birthday.
l'm scared.
What are you afraid of, Frank.
l can not remember.
Listen.
Do not be afraid.
There are haunted me.
l do not know, Frank.
We will do this?
- Together with you and me.
- Yes.
Yes.
l'm sure to fancy.
- That's right.
- Do not start the party without me.
- No.
Promise me.
Come on you have to be prepared, you'll be late.
You scared me, you silly!
Do you like it?
See l never cried before.
l cried.
Come on!
Come on dad, let's wake up!
Wake up!
Are you okay?
Hey!
Frank!
Frank come tea.
l want to be alone.
l do not want to go home.
Yes, we will meet with her, l've
said.
l do not want to go there.
Let's not start that again.
Frank what are you alright?
l want you out now.
l'll send you entered.
Hallo.
Yes, yes we were on our way.
- You've got to go.
- No, he's fine. he's fine.
l'm always serious, come on!
Yeah, okay.
l can not.
Uh .. at the moment l can not say.
lt's up to you.
Be careful.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute, l'll be back soon.
Give me the phone!
- Okay, no problem.
- Give me the phone.
Did you talk to the Gift.
lt is the mother.
Yeah.
Come to me.
Yes you have to meet with the mother.
Family reunion.
l'm not Katty.
l remember James.
l really miss you.
You do not realize it.
You can kiss me.
Dad, l remember this.
Yes, father, all right, all right!
Look it's not what you think. right?
Okay, yes?
Or maybe she was great in bed, huh?
- l want in bed.
- You want to, let's finish this.
Are you drunk?
Oh no, what are you doing!
You peed on me!
Are you crazy, come on wake up!
You piss everywhere! Wake up!
Do not touch me ...
Father, release the hand!
You're crazy, why do it?
- He touched me!
- What?
- Keep your voice down.
- Damn!
- Stop it!
- Get out!
- Put it!
- Get out! Away with you!
- Well, l'm gone!
Damn it!
He has touched me.
Come on dad, let me in!
- l could not stay outside, right?
- He came to me.
Room service!
Hello daddy!
Not ...
Not bad, right?
l saw he was out.
-Are you okay?
- Yes.
Maybe we should pull up your pants first.
- My son ...
- Dad!
Damn it!
Please you stroll out,
Good slowly, okay?
Wait a minute l close the door.
Listen, l'll take you to the place
beautiful, how it sounds?
That's great.
- Nice to get out.
- That's right.
-Are you okay now?
- Oh, he's right.
Well, you managed to get out of bed, right?
You eat everything?
Do not worry about it
they will clean it up.
l can do it.
- Dad what are you doing now?
- Get out!
- Stop it l'm James.
- Sorry, there's nothing wrong?
Sometimes he is angry nothing l can do.
l'm really sorry.
- What's his name?
- Frank.
- This father Lou, are you okay?
He would take us out and help.
- No ...
- We take your music.
Frank Let's find fresh air.
Be careful there are tables in there.
Thank you very much l appreciate.
- Fuck ...
- Well, come on, do not be difficult for him.
- l do not make it difficult ...
- Yes, you have destroyed this place.
Take it easy Frank.
- Fuck ...
- What's wrong with him?
Oh sorry bother you, he's just upset.
-All right, let's go dad.
- No one's doing that.
- Someone did that to you.
- Yes, he'll be fine.
- Consider your ways, yes.
- You're ajerk!
She'll be fine.
- Fuck.
-All right, polite.
- Very good dad.
- See Frank.
- You're gonna be okay?
- We'll be alright.
- Thank you very much for
meaning most people do not.
- No problem.
- l honestly forget about the money, take care.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
Goodbye Frank!
Daddy stop, let's go already finished ...
- Oh shit!
- Damn you!
-Are you okay?
- Yes, we're going the wrong way.
- We will come again next time.
- Get out!
Goodbye Frank!
We must continue. Yes, we're screwed.
Come over here.
All right, let's go.
Damn, keep your head!
Get down and shut up.
Jeez.
Almost alone we caught.
Damn it!
Hello, l can not talk on the phone.
l'm sorry ...
Well ...
What?
Okay, daddy!
He will not be back as ...
Old ...
Daddy!
Dad.
What?
Daddy!
What the fuck have you done?
What are you doing police
come, let's open the door!
Open the door!
What are you doing?
Do you want to find dead ... Hey!
Way!
He should not be driving?
You should not be driving!
- He could have killed someone.
- Back off!
You did it!
Did you see that!
l can not believe you did this!
lt's really incredible dad!
He was so surprised.
Damn ...
Well done Dad, l do not believe it.
On arriving at the next corner
we exchange places, huh?
- No.
- Seriously l don't think idea you're driving.
Maybe you should eat some of your medicine.
Which one should you eat?
l'm not sick.
Yes but this is for your own good.
Stop, it's not real.
lt's real.
No, l can not see.
Maybe you need medication.
Yes, that's what you gonna do, right?
You really are crazy.
You really are stupid, right?
What are you doing?
Well you can not do
we will slip.
l'm fine.
l can.
- l just want to have fun.
- l put the music to make you concentrate.
- You like?
- This is not good.
- This comes from here.
- Old songs.
l've often heard.
Good father.
Yes, we are on the way.
Yes, l will not be faster
if you call me, right?
Oh, finally, we will get there.
Oh, okay, just calm down.
lt was all good.
Jesus.
Yes, we can copy messages.
Can l drive, then?
No.
Okay, fine. Just keep driving
this afternoon.
You can not mess up.
Close your eyes, Ben.
Remained closed.
Not him, you're still here.
You'll be safe, do not make a mess.
- Can l help you?
- l'm looking for a husband. Where is he?
Sorry, not here.
- Hey! Luke, up now.
- Mom!
l'll call the police.
Let go!
He owes me.
You've been drinking.
You're not yourself today.
Who is it?
Pretty rough, it's me.
That was today.
- So what?
- So...
What?
Who am l?
What is the name me?
Look, stop playing like that.
- You do not know, right?
- Of course l know, stop teasing me.
- l think we have to meet someone.
- l'm fine, just leave me alone.
- lt was not.
- That you make me a damn.
So who am l?
Why are we stopping?
- He was there, right?
- Come on, Ted, let's keep moving!
Listen, we should be there now.
Who is it?
- Who is he?
- Let me drive.
l'm going, okay. The 1, 2, 3, and we
exchange. Okay?
1, 2, 3.
Dad.
Jesus Christ.
Come on, dad. l'm your son.
That would be good, let's go, let me go.
- Stop it!
- Come on, let me in! Open the door.
Come on, damn it, we should!
Oh, no! No, no! Huahio!
Huahio Damn! You fuck! You're damn Huahio!
- Damn idiot! What is wrong with you?
- One of you!
- What is wrong with you?
- Fucking shut up!
l'll shut up if l like it! Well, l'm a
you deliver, and then the damn car!
Daddy!
Damn it, Ted! l just messed up!
Well, l'm screwed! Can you work out how?
Good? Okay.
Look, Ted, right?
Just think what we would do, right?
- Yes.
- We can not stay here. We can get there.
Or we stop the car and into the hotel,
and the food is good,
Yes, we'll know where we fucking are.
And we will be back.
Do you want to go? We go. What's the problem?
l was driving the car, where is the problem?
- Gasoline. We have no petrol.
- What?
Fuck!
- Damn it!
- Do not shout like that!
- Damn it! Come on dad!
- Come on!
You go back to the car.
- Where are you, where are you know?
- Wait.
- l'm not kidding.
- Go back.
- What happened to you, it's me!
- You go into here, the highway!
You're damn!
Frank, who am l?
lt's me!
Dad?
Frank?
What's wrong with you?
Dad, you can not walk around
everywhere?
Where did you go?
What happened to you, Frank?
lt's me.
Who am l? What are you doing?
Frank, where are you?
Kate?
Return.
Back to me!
- l can not.
- lt's me, you need to go, cover him.
l just can not do it.
l just can not, he is my friend.
- He drinks, right?
- That he will be finished.
- He said he quit!
- lt does not drink. lt was someone else.
- Do not make me a reason.
- l know, l do not. You do not understand.
- He needs me.
- Yeah, but he's dangerous.
- You're not safe, you need to go.
- To whom are you speaking?
Frank, you're frightening me.
- Wake up.
- l'll call you later.
- l ask you, Kate. Mose?
- lt was Mose.
What is it?
Who is this?
Hello?
Look at me, Kate.
Look at me, honey.
Tell me the truth.
Did you see anyone else?
Do not do it, Frank?
- Who is he?
- Jane.
- Who?
- Our children. JB.
Kate, we do not have kids.
Oh, what's wrong with you?
Do not say that.
l can take it, please. Do not say that!
Tell me the truth.
Are you leaving me?
No.
Frank, what are you doing?
you've told me.
Oh no Frank.
Thank you.
- You'll understand.
- lt hurts.
You really sucks.
No.
You would not know.
Stupid.
lt's all you gave me?
You'll know Frank.
- You can not ..
- l can ...
Frank told me.
- l know ..
- Yes.
You do not know which is more painful.
- Frank ..
- No!
- You have to run here.
- Come on.
l do not want you to say so.
Come on, hurry!
No.
Frank, come on, where are you going?
Hey come on.
Please, c'mon.
Come on, back everything up!
Jack!
Hey.
Crazy, you're totally crazy!
Why do you want to kill yourself? jerk!
l want to go, let me finish.
Can you come here?
Perhaps, too, you'll understand.
Mother.
Come.
l thought you were asleep.
View.
Jeez.
Halo.
Look what l found?
Hey what's up?
Are you okay?
l do not have there.
Maybe l should check the machine there.
Oh no, there's nothing wrong?
Maybe you've found it right?
l will fix this.
Come on.
Will be.
No, no, you would not know.
Come on you all.
What is it?
Maybe you'll come back?
That's great.
l guess l should get there.
Hey asshole, we had an arrangement.
Where is Frank?
Give me Frank, or l will
comes to family, you understand?
Do you hear me?
- Yes.
You know we could choose?
Come here, okay.
Listen, hey, where did you go?
- Back home.
- Where to?
What's wrong with you?
Are you going to believe?
lt may be very strange.
Come on, it's very foreign, you know what?
Perhaps no one came?
Let me see them.
Oh shit once.
Hey.
Come you.
Dad.
l'm not happy, okay?
You're going to believe this.
Hey, what do you know.
Come on, you do not know Jamie.
You do not know for sure.
No.
- No, no ...
- Dad
You have to understand, come on ..
1, 2 and the other car.
- Go into the car please, go.
- No, no!
- Jerk.
- No!
No.
-Are you okay?
- Yes, he is my father.
Nothing strange calm.
- lt was the police.
- Shut up dad.
- l do not know anything.
- What?
- Fuck ...
- Shut up, you shut up? Shut up!
- l do not know you.
- Stop the father.
You do not need to know, see what
you do.
- Calm down.
- He's a little crazy you know?
Yes, here is not safe, you know,
l had to move.
- lt's your car?
- Yes, this is my car.
He was my wife, she was my wife.
What is it dad?
My wife is ...
- You ...
- You have to understand ..
- l know.
yes, he was fine, just take it.
- You're there.
- Yes, thank you.
- Come here.
- Yes, where did you go?
Go into the car.
Do you understand?
Do you understand? Go into the car.
Now, let's go.
Sign fast, head down.
Step your feet, come on ..
Yes, the smart go.
You have to be quiet, l do not want any
cheating.
Well, you'll understand.
Oh thank you.
You stay there, you understand.
Come on.
- Oh really.
- Yes.
Fucking! How do you do this?
Or is it brake to it!
Brake what the fucking brake, what the...?
Kill me.
You'll be doing me a flavour.
Please remember that.
Your own welcome, aren't you, Frank.
That's my phone.
Give me that.
Shit.
Hello luv. Hello sweetheart, it's me.
l couldn't.
l lost my phone.
Listen, calm down. Alright, calm down.
Tell me what happened?
Well, l couldn't.
l lost my phone.
Stay where you are, alright?
Stay where you are, l'm gonna find you.
Okay, l'm coming now.
l coming now, okay? Alright.
Fuck!
Fucking! Fuck.
Bring me the young day.
Yeah, yeah, give me that.
Give me that.
He'll be alright.
No, no, no.
You stay where you are.
- l want to go.
- You stay right there. You just wait.
You're not going anywhere.
You stay where you are, alright?
Don't you love me?
You love me.
Because l love you.
When you love someone.
You'll gonna have a chat, alright?
You can help me out.
Come on, open your mouth.
Open mouth and put these in it.
You're going to help me out.
That's it.
Fuck!
What's the fuck is that?
Okay, right.
l don't need it all!
Alright, open your mouth.
Open your mouth.
Go.
Swallow it.
Alright, swallow it, come on. Swallow it.
Swallow it! swallow it!
That's it. That's it.
Open your mouth. Let me see.
-All right.
- l want to go home.
- Going home again, you said you wanted to come.
See you in a minute.
l'll be back soon.
What the fuck is going on?
l don't want you to speak of it, okay?
- l'm looking after, where the hell have you been?
- Don't start, alright?
- l just want to ... Move! Move!
- What have you done?
That's okay, Sof.
l'd take care of it.
lt's fine. lt's fine.
Hello, mate. Come here you.
How you're doing?
- How are you? Have you miss me?
- Yeah.
Yeah, l miss you.
You be a good boy, okay?
- lt's over.
- You'll be good.
So what the fuck is going on?
You don't know.
Did you have any idea?
-Any idea what we've been through?
- l'm sorry.
Sorry?
Jeremy.
Jeremy?
Hello, boy.
Your daddy's home.
You know what he did?
- You could have been killed.
- Oh, come on. Don't say that.
You're going to do, will find someone
and you're off. That's what you said.
- That's what it was.
- lt's over.
l'm sorry, just a little at out of hand.
Alright, but l'm fixing it after today.
- Don't lie to me.
- l swear to God.
Did you miss me?
Jeremy.
Where's Mommy?
Over there.
Come on, l'm sorry, okay?
But it's gonna be okay.
lt's gonna be okay.
lt's gonna be okay,
l promise you that.
Yeah? l promise you that.
Maybe tonight you must stay
at your sister. Just for safety.
Because l want you to be safe.
Alright, l'm fixing this.
Okay? l'm fixing this.
l'm had of this.
- So many times.
- What?
- The gambling, the debt. When is it gonna stop?
- lt will stop.
lt's done.
This is the point we are discussing this.
l did this for you to be happy.
l just want you to be happy.
- lt is enough to be happy.
- Yeah.
- Love me.
Coming to an end.
Hey.
Hey, you.
No, hey. Don't touch him.
Give him to me! Give him to me!
- Don't come near him.
- Give him to me!
- Don't fucking touch me!
- Don't you touch him!
Don't you touch him!
Why? Why would he do that?
- He's my boy!
- Should you let him!
- Call the police! Call the police!
- Steward, who is this?
- Yeah, l told you.
- Steward.
- What happened?
- Stu, it's me.
lt's me, James. He's not your son.
Son, James.
Look at me. Look at me.
- Hi, it's me.
- Jeremy.
lt's me.
-All right.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it is. You want it?
- lt.
- Yeah, you want it.
l want to go home.
lt's okay, l'll take you home.
Steward.
We're fuck, alright? l know.
He wasn't supposse to be in the hospital.
So l had to get him out.
Of course.
lt's up in shoe why did they take the risk?
- l have no choice.
- There is always a choice!
Yeah, not with them there isn't.
You got no idea. l got to
do something so l told his son.
- You fucking idiot.
- l don't know what else to do.
lt was his word against mine.
He don't remember a fucking anything.
Maybe we should call the police.
What?
l can't just give it up him away.
What will l do with him?
Do with him?
Jesus Christ, look what they did to us.
lf they want him so badly.
They can have him.
Look, they probably gonna killed him.
- lf so, can you live with that?
- Rather him than us.
What you want me to say?
We are what we are.
l just wanted to do
the right thing, that's all.
lt's too late for that now.
- Do it.
- What?
Never mind, l'll keep doing it.
- Stop it, Dad!
- No.
No more lies.
- Tell the truth.
- l'm not your son.
l'm not your son.
- Who are you ajerk?
- l'm a nobody.
- l was just told to bring you back.
- Go back where?
Go back to your house.
- No.
- l do not know.
- l do not know his name.
- Do not mess around.
l do not know enough.
Believe me.
He said you ran,
l must take you back to the hospital.
- No.
- Then what?
l just wanted to go.
Stop ...
No, just ...
You know where we are?
You will not.
Okay, this is it.
That's it. Please exit.
Come on, check this out, okay?
l give money, okay?
Accept it, it's all l've got.
This is for you.
- Where?
- What? l do not know where Frank, okay?
Meet someone to ask for help,
or search the police.
Or come to me and ask for help.
You watch yourself.
That's it, come on.
Go away.
Hello, Frank.
Are you okay?
Come in the car.
Come along with me,
get in the car.
Well, you just wait there.
- Okay?
- Mm-hm.
l had guests, one guest.
- Fever.
- Yes.
l hope you can understand.
How much do you remember?
l just wanted an excuse, l need a good reason
why do l have to understand you.
l'm afraid, Frank.
l had a big problem,
l owe money.
lt made me afraid.
At my son.
My son.
Please, l need a good reason.
l want you to understand.
Do you understand?
Do not worry, she will keep you.
Who are you?
Who is he? Who is that guy?
Who is that guy? Tell me.
- lt's Kevin. My wife.
- Kevin. Yes, your wife.
lt's about him.
- lt's about ...
Hello?
No, l can not do this.
Yeah, l thought l could, but it was not.
No, tell me what exactly your plans.
l'll beat you!
Do not play with me! Call you when l'm ready.
Oh, shit.
That sounds good.
She is gorgeous.
- You want to try to approach him? Yes?
- Yes.
- With my friends.
- You're smart, too.
Okay.
lt's for you Kevin.
Me too.
Beautiful.
- You're crazy.
- No.
- You lied to him.
- We're just friends.
- You are approaching him.
Say ''with my friends''
- Believe me, l am not worthy.
- You've come this far.
No.
Why? She is very pretty.
You know.
- What?
- Leave me.
Alright. Here, give me a kiss.
Why? Stop staring at me.
Excuse me, can you get me a vodka tonic.
- l'm sure you're thirsty.
- Yes.
What do you want?
Vodka Tonic
Yeah, can l ask which one like this?
- l'm Lisa.
- l'm George.
- Oh, bless.
- He's good, right?
Yes, it's your dad?
No, he's just a friend.
So do you mind
l was invited to another place?
No, wait-wait sorry
l'm, l'm married.
- With who?
- With my wife.
Actually, you know, he's incredible.
You're late.
Yes Frank, what's up?
- l do...
- What's the problem?
- l just call...
- lt's just...
You're crazy, oh God.
- Leave him alone!
- Take it easy.
- l'm fine.
- Yeah, you're fine.
- Yes.
Hey, it's your birthday,
why not take a picture?
Yes, can you picture us, man?
Smile for the camera.
Goddamn it, what's the problem?
Do not play games with me.
- You've got to go.
- No, you have to calm down.
- l do not know!
- Frank, time to go home.
- Let him go.
- Go you jerk!
Stop it!
- Do not touch it!
- Fred, it's not going to help!
What are you doing?
- Excuse me, are you okay?
- l'm just trying to help!
What's the matter with you, actually!
- What do you think?
- l'm just trying to help.
- Come time to go.
- No, no, do not go!
- Let's go.
- Do not go, stay with me!
Damn it!
Come on Frank. That's enough, right?
Watch your step..
Well Frank, you're doing well.
How was it, right?
This he had already reached the
house, come on, do you want to go?
l have a surprise for you.
Someone very
special to see you.
Be a good girl.
- l want you to sit on the bed.
- Yes.
Let's not wait,
You have to sit here, come on.
That's it, you're set, right?
You have to look good.
Well, are you ready?
Very good.
Are you ready, Frank?
- Sure.
- Yeah, sure, sure you're ready.
Turn on the music.
l want you to take your pills.
- You'll do just fine.
- No.
These pills you, man.
Do you want to recover, right?
You have a visitor, right?
Alright.
Yes, here..
Someone wants Frank to do.
Can you do?
After this, l will pay you again.
Alright.
- Do not be scared.
- Trust me, it will not.
Can tell your name is Kevy.
- Okay.
- Yeah, all right.
ls there something wrong with him.
lt's okay, he's fine
alone, he's just a little shy.
That was my best friend.
Yes, you'll be her personal babysitter.
Who is he?
Frank, look who's here.
lt Kevy.
Hallo.
Kev?
Okay, good.
Let you approach him.
Do you really Kevy?
l really miss you.
You'll be fine.
What, what to talk about?
lt's okay.
You do not have anything.
l'll Stand you.
Yes.
Come on, hurry.
Like this.
- l'm very happy.
- Good.
l think of losing you.
- l really miss you.
- You do not have anything.
Sit down.
You look nervous.
You must immediately leave me and my family
and never met with Frank again.
Do not you worry about them.
You only need to worry about yourself.
Oh come on, please, hold your words.
We had a deal, oh
no, l have to say.
l said, this should be done.
l do not do anything else, right?
lt was no use.
You owe me.
- What would you do, sir?
- That's not a problem.
Where is he?
l will not say easy.
Good?
l know money has been widely used, but l'm telling
you, it's not worth it, it does not deserve.
- l do not care.
- Do not be stupid like that.
l was brought in to the hospital, and
they said he was crazy.
You have to trust me, he's not healthy.
You can tell them.
l never told you to do that.
All l have to say is it's not worth it.
You have to think of all that must be done.
Look at you trying to
work out there.
You do not even find clue.
You are a gift to me.
- You're hurting me.
- l did not hear you.
Where is Frank?
Do you feel too sad to him?
Have you made him cry?
You do not know Frank.
Stop.
My God, Frank what are you doing?
Get off me!
- Who are you?
- Get off me!
What's wrong with you!
Stop it, you see me.
l do not care about that, either? He was not
The same people he does not even remember.
He will be remembered.
Something he would never forget.
What's wrong with you?
l will come to Perth Paul.
For Christ sake, Frank what have you done?
- Burning Hell.
- You're crazy.
- l do not care.
- You have to help.
- What did you do with Jeff.
- No!
- You lied.
- Stop it.
- Do not do Frank.
- l love you.
What would you do,
you're going to kill you?
l help you,
believe this is what you want.
You think you know Frank.
You do not know what he's doing.
- l do not know.
- Look at me! Are you happy?
- Stop it.
-Are you crazy?.
Oh No.
Please take me to her Steward.
l will not do it.
- What do you want?
- l do not want to do it.
- Do not run!
- Move it!.
Who are you?
Kevin's me, remember?
Frank.
You're hurting me.
l'm sorry.
l'm going to go right?
That was me.
- What?
- l'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Do not go,
please do not go.
Do not go.
Please do not go.
l'm sorry.
Why are you doing this?
He is nothing to you.
- Do not.
- Frank.
Frank are you okay?
Frank.
Frank, Come on up.
What are you doing on the floor?
Wake up. Come on we gotta go.
Frank, Come on get up we have to go.
We're leaving now.
What? Come on.
No, what are you doing?
Wake up, do not you know,
Frank woke up.
Shit, I'll call an ambulance.
You'll be fine.
- Damn.
- Please do not call.
Let me sleep, l just want to sleep.
Believe me.
Frank what do you want?
Come on.
l'm going to bed.
- l'm going to bed.
- Sleep, all right.
You can sleep.
Please Frank you can sleep.
Okay, Frank,
You can sleep.
- You want to join me?
- Okay.
You want to drink?
Frank. Come on.
- Okay.
That's all right.
Do not worry, kid.
All right, Frank.
What, are you happy my dear?
Yes. Please.
Come here baby, l miss you.
every day.
Meet me.
That's him.
He's my dad.
FOR RlCHARD, CHRISTINA AND TOM
Sub by mbendholz knetz
Mei, 2013
Timing & Sync : KNETZ 22 Team
Member of
IDfL.us