SOME ONE WHO DRIVES ME CRAZY
WHO FILLS ME WITH FEAR
WHO'S THRIFTY
WHO PREFERS CASH TO FLOWERS
WHO ONLY LIKES MY BROTHER
WHO LOVES ME MORE THAN I LOVE MYSELF
WHO EMBARRASSES ME
WHOM I DON'T WANT TO RESEMBLE
THE FIRST WORD OF A LIFETIME
MAMA
Warming up!
One! Two! Three! Four!
Once more! One! Two! Three! Four!
Clapping! One! Two! Three! Four!
Up high! One! Two! Three!
Four! Stretch!
Thank you for
this wonderful day!
Let's eat!
What are you
doing today, hon?
Study English in the morning
- Read history cartoon books at 1.
- And?
Research the Louvre
at 3 o' clock.
And exercise at 4 o' clock.
Wow!
Busy! Busy! Busy!
Really busy!
- Apple!
- Chapel!
- Cap full!
- Cap full?
- Two, Three...
- Babble!
Babble?
Babble...babble...
Bubble!
Bubble! No?
Do you even know
what babble means?
Doesn't it mean to jabber?
Wow! That's my boy!
You're the smartest!
I hope this is good.
It's hot!
I'm off to keep
our country healthy!
I love you so much!
I love you too, mommy!
Lunch's in the microwave.
Make sure you exercise, okay?
- Bye, mom!
- Bye!
# To the end of this world
# I will devote
entirely to you
# And hold you
# in my arms.
Min-hyuck.
Min-hyuck?
Hey Min-hyuck!
Was it my turn?
What are you doing?
I've always wanted to do
pantomime on the stage.
- Sorry?
- This is an orange.
Look.
I'm peeling it.
It's really easy.
Don't believe
there's an orange here.
Just forget
that there isn't one.
So sour!
You're good.
Very good.
What a loser.
- This is bullshit.
- Come on.
It would be easier
for me to pretend
to love an orange than her.
She's my mother's age!
How can I pretend I love
someone like that?
That's a bit too harsh,
isn't it?
This is professor HANG.
She's the hottest
singer in Korea!
Didn't you tell me
to try acting
when you were auditioning me?
Would you be able to act
in a situation like this?
Could you pretend to love
that wrinkled old granny?
- It's just acting.
- No it's not!
This is a scam!
Hey! Min-hyuck!
What's up with you man?
Have some orange, sir!
What's with
the orange today?
I was worried
about doing a musical
but the music's
quite elegant!
I feel good about this,
better than when I did
Madame Butterfly in 97.
You always feel good.
But your personality sucks.
I can't believe
Min-hyuck's an idol star..
He's got perfect body
but he's not
very bright, is he?
Idol my ass.
He's an idiot.
At least his voice isn't
too bad for a young man.
Hey! You think
they're your clothes?
Careful with those hot pants!
- Where to next?
- Home.
Hello, sir!
Yes, I'm in this one too.
They just insist they
can't do it without me.
I know, I know.
I'm incredibly busy.
Time to go.
KOO Seung-cheul!
You son of a bitch!
I'm a bit busy
so I gotta get going.
My boys will
get through to you.
You have something to say?
You say it!
How dare you kick me out and
Leave me with your boys?
We have to get rough if you
keep on lying like this.
Plus!
My boys punch better than me.
Got it?
I have no time to goof
around with you.
Fuck! God damn it!
KOO! How dare you!
I'm sorry,!
Grandma!
I told you it looks barbaric
to run like that.
And don't call me grandma.
I'm Professor HANG.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Bye, now.
Mrs. HANG!
You're home early!
We picked up some good pork.
Join us for dinner?
Yeah! Eat with us,
Professor Grandma!
We can't stink up
Professor HANG's house.
She'll freak out.
Plus, she's having just
a slice of tofu tonight, alone.
We can't cramp her style.
You speak as ugly
as your face.
Let's go in.
Sweetie, we're having tofu
for dinner today.
- No!
- it’ll be good!
- Just do it.
- I said no!
Hey!
Fuck!
Let go!
- What did you steal?
- Shit!
- Hey!
- I said let go!
It's just cheap yogurt!
Then you pay for it!
That's okay.
What'll become
of that rascal!
Sorry to scare you, sir.
- No, no.
- Thank you.
No problem.
Here.
Let's just say I bought
those kids that yogurt.
Here. Take it.
Then let me get you
a few things.
Just wait here for a bit.
Please.
- Mom!
- Well!
Is this my dear son?
There was crazy traffic jam!
Am I late?
- No, you're just on time!
- Good!
Smells so good!
- Dinner will be ready soon.
- Okay.
Samba samba samba samba!
- For you!
- Thanks.
Samba samba samba!
This is amazing, mom.
You've got magic hands!
It's not that good but
thank you anyway.
- Honey?
- Yeah?
- Say Cheese Please
- What's that?
If you keep on saying
CHEESE PLEASE like this
you'll get smiley wrinkles.
I'm just worried about
your face these days.
It's threatening
like a gangster face.
How can you say that to
a teacher? That's cruel, mom!
You have to go to
the hospital tomorrow.
- Okay.
- These are too thin.
I'm scared.
Scare of what, mom?
Don't you worry!
If anything happens I'll
set fire to that damn place.
Geez! What a potty mouth!
You're a teacher!
But I can't help
feeling anxious.
Come on mom!
I said don't worry
about a thing!
Just drop by at the hospital
then come home to pack.
I'll send you to Japan
for hot springs next week.
What?
I just got back from Canada!
Stop wasting your money on me.
But I like hot springs!
Why can't you
pronounce Canada?
Say Ka-Na-Da!
No! It's Canada!
Like the Gana Fish Sauce!
Here.
This is good for you.
Sweetie?
- Look at this.
- Yeah?
Hey lady! Listen
to my son's English.
What's bean
curd in English?
That's easy!
De... defireve.e.
In English, it's defireve..
I'm so proud of you, son!
Excuse me.
I just wanna help out.
I heard you speaking.
I'm an English teacher.
It's not defireve.
It's Tofu.
This is tofu. Okay?
He's a bit lost.
It's not defireve.
It's defireve...
Fierve! Okay?
Yeah, I hear you.
But it's no defireve..
It's tofu.
What the hell
is he on about?
You America?
- I'm an Australian.
- So you are!
He's speaking our language!
You speak Korean!
Why give me a hard time?
So how do you say that
in Australian?
- Tofu.
- Tofu?
Yeah.
Just say defireve just once.
Or get out of here.
- Okay?
- Tofu.
Right.
Get going.
You speak Korean so well!
How amazing!
Mom, don't even
talk to him.
No one who speaks English
calls that tofu!
We all call it defireve.
- I'm an English teacher.
- Right.
- Dumb bastard!
- Yeah, dumb bastard!
Go learn proper English,
you fool!
COULD YOU COME CLEAN
THE FRIDGE TODAY?
Of course I can!
What time?
6 in the morning?
You must be so pissed off.
But men are just like that.
What was that?
Oh my God!
Oh, shoot!
Are you okay, ma'am?
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Oh no.
- It's okay.
Shouldn't you go to a hospital?
No, there's no need.
- Go to a hospital.
- I'm okay.
I'm okay. Really!
I'm fine.
You can go.
It's okay. You can go.
Then let me buy
some yogurt from you.
Really?
You really don't have to.
Why don't you try this.
This is an instant solution.
When you drink it,
you poop out this much!
Okay then. I'll take ten.
Ten?
I mean, give me twenty.
Twenty? This much!
You're amazing.
What do you work
so hard for?
To travel around
the world with my son.
Is your son sick?
There's always new medicine.
My son will get better soon.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Don't you worry!
- I'm sorry again.
- Bye!
Thank you!
What the hell
did you just say?
Where are you going?
Who told you to go?
You asshole!
- Calm down, sir.
- No.
You piece of shit!
How dare you scream!
Don't think we can do
it without you?
Please calm down!
You asshole!
Damn it!
They're out of organic stuff.
Just use this.
I don't know why
I even hired you.
The director seems pretty
ticked off. What's with him?
That idol quit.
He doesn't like me.
Hi, Professor KIM.
Yeah, I called.
Are you busy these days?
Wanna do a musical?
I'm in it.
The staff are best
in the country.
Just tell them
I recommended you.
They know who I am.
Right?
Get ready to go
to the lecture.
The organizers will
contact you soon.
I gave them your number.
Hey!
Mom, I'm here!
Hey, guys!
Look how much you've grown!
Walking already?
Hi Choco!
You're so cute!
Hey! Stop eating!
Where's mom, guys?
Hi, mom!
I'm home, mom!
Were you changing
the briquette?
I'll do it, mom!
So thanks to that,
she bought twenty more!
At this rate,
we'll be travelling
the world in no time! Right?
Here's hot water.
Bon appetite, mom.
I made you some sauteed beef,
your favorite.
Make sure you eat
all of it.
Don't let it go bad.
There, there!
Come on.
You cry so much,
just like my mom!
I'm the one who
should thank you.
When I come visit you
I feel like I'm seeing my mom.
I told you.
My mom couldn't
speak either.
You can hold my hands
for as long as you want.
Only doctors hold your hands
when you get old.
What are you saying?
Are you saying that l
have to cut off one breast?
Yeah.
But you can always get
a breast implant later.
But what's the need
at your age?
Have you sobered up?
What am I going to do?
Mom?
Let's step out for a second.
- This can't be happening.
- She's your mom?
How hilarious!
Phone. Off.
What?
What are you doing?
If anything ever
happens to my mom
I'll carve out your nipples.
Both of them.
Got it?
Yes.
Why does your grandma drink
coffee in a cup like this?
Mom, what are
these fish called?
Golden Tetra.
They glow more than before.
They glow more
as they get older.
Do people glow more
as they get older?
Ask your grandma that.
She's a blinding star.
I'm just a dull
ordinary person.
- You're home early.
- Hi grandma.
- What is it?
- This is bullshit.
Fire me?
Professor HANG Hee-Kyoung?
This can't happen!
I won't let it! I won't!
Mom, is grandma crazy?
She's just very angry
right now.
I won't have that surgery.
I'm scared to get
sliced up.
I don't want to be
a breastless woman.
Over my dead body.
You know mom...
Modern technology is
so developed these days.
They can even turn a black
person into a white person.
It'll be over
in the blink of an eye.
Another blink,
and you'll have a new breast.
So there's nothing you
have to worry about!
What are you saying?
That I'll be uneven?
Why would you be uneven?
They'll make you a new one!
No! I'll be uneven!
I can't even go
to the sauna anymore!
That's what you're
worried about?
I'm uneven!
No more sauna!
What's this?
From that fall?
Ow...
- Thank you, Dong-sook.
- No problem.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I put the food back
in the fridge.
Thank you.
See you soon.
Oh my god!
Dong-sook!
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Dong-sook!
Wake up!
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
- I'm okay.
- What's wrong?
- Are you okay to stand?
Two months?
Even with the surgery?
The surgery won't heal you.
It'll just give you
more time.
It's also possible you won't
make it through the surgery.
Doctor, I am very healthy.
Even now,
I don't feel any pain.
Ovarian cancer is
usually symptomless.
Regular check-up is
the only way to prevent it.
You're a bit too late.
This can't be.
I can't be sick.
My son has Duchen's
muscular dystrophy.
He can live
for five more years.
I have to be with him.
We're supposed to go
on a world trip.
If you want,
you can get
a second opinion elsewhere.
Would my results
be any different?
I don't think so.
Sir.
You can't say this to me.
What about my son, then?
- Please calm down.
- I can't die.
Just five more
years, doctor.
What about my son?
Please help me.
Please doctor.
Don't do this, doctor.
Let's just calm down.
Wait. Please.
I was so beautiful.
When did time
pass by so fast?
Oh my!
Deok-soo!
Mom!
Where are you, mom?
I got something for you!
Look at this, mom.
I bought you all this
from the department store!
Luxury bath lotion,
your favorite!
I also have
this sparkly thing!
I'm serious!
Get up and take a look!
Why even bother?
They're all useless anyway!
Come on, mom!
Geez!
Mom.
Let's just do it.
Get your surgery.
Then I'll do
whatever you wish.
You think you're Buddha?
Well no, but I would do
anything for my mom.
I would even split the earth
in two if you asked me to.
So tell me
everything you want.
It's not that
I want something.
Okay?
But there is someone
I want to see.
Who, mom?
Go on, say it!
Someone from my youth.
My first love.
First love?
I was nineteen years old.
Your grandma asked me
to bring a sack
of rice flour.
I was on my way
home struggling
with the heavy thing.
I'd skipped lunch and
my shoulder was killing me.
Just then a man came and
took my rice flour sack.
He was the second son of
the distillery shop family.
He was tall and handsome
And strong!
All girls in the village
were crazy about him.
And of all girls,
he chose me!
I felt so lucky!
He taught me how to sing.
He rode me on his bike
And made me flower rings.
Before he went
to Seoul to study
Everyday felt like a dream.
I' m sorry I'm late.
Looking back...
It was the most
exciting day of my life.
Did you call me, boss?
Yeah.
You're good with films?
- Pardon me?
- Films.
- You mean movies?
- Look.
You playing smart?
Movies or films or whatever.
Do you feel that good when you
pretend to be that smart?
You have this thing
about being uneducated.
- I'm sorry, boss.
- It's an inferiority complex.
I'm sorry, sir.
We're gonna
make a mellow film.
Find me an actor.
JANG HEE-KYOUNG
QUEEN OF OPERA
Mom!
Mom.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
You know how
I got this far?
You're gonna get wrinkles
if you keep on crying like that.
And your hair.
It's like a metal sponge.
It'll be okay, mom.
Don't cry.
- Dong-hee?
- Hi, sis. What's up?
Hey! Sang-hoon!
- Dong-hee?
- Yeah?
I have something
to tell you.
What is it?
- Sang-hoon!
- Dong-hee...
Sang-hoon!
I said come here!
Sorry, sis.
Sang-hoon's made a mess.
- I'll call you later.
- Okay.
- Sorry, okay?
Shit, man.
Cheers!
The men here are good.
What the?
It's your first time
at this cabaret, isn't it?
Yes.
I couldn't help noticing you
when I was singing.
Is your name
'Ok' by any chance?
No, sorry.
- Get over here!
- Have a beer.
Where is he, bitch?
- Honey! Please!
- Is it that asshole?
Come here, you old fart!
Please stop it!
What are you waiting for?
Bring him here before
he gets beat up.
Yes boss!
Honey!
I can't believe my mother
fell for such a loser.
Damn it!
So.
You're Ok-joo's son?
Yeah.
Are you sure you're
HANG Deok-soo?
I know it's been a long time
but how can you
turn out like that?
She sure raised a good son.
Let me repeat.
I got it.
So you want me to
put on a show?
With my looks, I can pass
for a doctor or a lawyer.
Or even a CEO.
So just tell me
what you need.
I'm a pro at things
like this.
By the way.
How much will you pay me?
You'll give me
enough, right?
You ever tried human meat?
We have a lot of meat.
A lot of human meat.
We'll give it to you
if you want it.
Money or meat or whatever!
You'd better be
damn convincing!
I'll skin you alive
if you screw up!
Wrinkles and all!
Got it!
Okay!
Let's do it!
Yeah?
Mom?
What else would I be doing?
I'm teaching.
Hello, every baby!
Miss me already?
You want cabbage fritters?
Why here, of all places?
It's freezing.
It's your first time
to come outside like this.
Here.
- Drink this, grandma.
- No.
Just a bit!
- Yuck!
Let's try to have fun
since we're here.
I'll put on some music.
How's my singing?
People will hate you
if you sing like that.
Close your eyes and
feel the music.
Be confident.
What's that?
Like this.
Wow!
Our special guest
today is Kim Yoon-ji
the remarkable soprano singer
from the musical Loveholic.
Hello?
- Hello.
- Leave it.
Your role was originally sung
by JANG Hee-Kyoung, right?
Right.
I think the musical was too
challenging for Professor JANG
with her age and all.
I'm hoping that I can sing
better than her.
Excuse me,
but how old are you?
Twenty-three.
Hi, it's me.
You said you knew the chairman
of Haklim Foundation?
- Where are you going, mom?
- Can I see him right now?
What about the car?
I'll be right there.
Mom!
Hello!
This place might look slummy
But it's the only place in Seoul
that has cabbage fritters.
Right.
Deok-soo was an eloquent man.
It was tough finding
this place.
Do they taste like
in the old days?
May be he's become a judge.
I'm not sure
about these fritters.
What would you
like loser, I mean...
that man to have become?
It's not really what I want.
This is just
my own imagination.
Knowing how bold
and smart he was
maybe he's become
a successful businessman.
What do you want to do
when you meet him?
What would we do
at this age?
Just eat something delicious.
Something delicious.
Talk about the old days.
Go sing a song at a karaoke.
Watch a movie in a theater.
- Hey KOO! Long time no see!
- Eat an egg at a sauna.
Go up Namsan Tower
and sightsee Seoul.
by the old palace.
We can head to the river
when the sun is about to set
And go on a ferry.
Honey, this is
like a dream come true!
So tell me again.
This says that
Deoksoo is coming
to see me
from America, right?
I told you.
It says right here.
- So Mom!
- Yes?
You have to get the surgery.
I'm worried.
What if he doesn't
even recognize me anymore
because I'm too old?
No way.
Why did time have to pass
by so fast, damn it?
Aren't you going
to the gym?
Smart kids these days
sing and
dance so well.
Wait til she
sprains her back.
- Hi there!
- Yeah.
- Hi!
- Going somewhere?
Zip me up?
- Where are you going?
- To practice.
Practice?
I'm back on. Get ready.
5 minutes.
HANG Hee-Kyoung.
You're a coward.
- I'm not done peeling.
- What?
Do you really
have to do that?
What's it to you?
You already
have everything.
You should learn
to let things go.
How can you have such
endless greed?
What do you mean
I have everything?
Leave it!
Who told you to touch that?
Then what about you?
Don't you have
any ambitions?
I hired you
so you won't starve.
But you have no talent
nor ambitions.
Where you going?
Stay and listen!
You're just a servant for
your husband and kid.
What's your dream?
Did you even have one?
Why don't you answer that?
What's her goal?
- What does she want to do?
- I wanted to sing!
I wanted to be a singer!
So is your mom coming?
Way to go, Eun-sung!
Do your best.
# Before I knew it
# Wrinkles filled my forehead
# Oh my! Please!
# Let me be young again.
# Before I knew it
Mom!
How vulgar!
I couldn't sing
after that.
So I gave up.
I hated my mother who was
embarrassed of me.
So I did everything
to despise you.
Vulgarly I got married
to an older guy
right after high school.
Vulgarly I had
a baby right away.
Vulgarly I became
your maid.
You're asking such a vulgar
person about her dreams?
You have a husband,
child and mother.
You have everything.
Don't you feel sorry
for your mother
who has nothing
but a voice?
Don't blame me.
You wanna sing?
You think singing is a joke
because you see me
sing every day?
Well,
let's listen to you.
Sing.
I felt sorry
for you these days.
I liked being next to you
and consoling you.
But I was wrong.
You're hopeless.
Now I understand why dad
cheated on you.
So that's why you married
a loser like your dad
and completely infuriate
your mother?
Sing?
Let's hear you sing.
Music?
Don't you dare insult it!
Dad, I have to poo.
Let's poo.
What a nice surprise!
You're taking me out!
Look, mom!
That store's still there!
- Look, sweetie!
- Look at the bubbles!
Take this.
What's this?
- Vitamin.
- Vitamin?
It's so nice being out,
isn't it?
Sweetie?
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
For what?
Everything.
Don't do it again then.
I'm so sleepy mom.
I slept a lot
before coming out.
Let me give you
a piggy back.
- Wanna play rhyming game?
- Okay.
Elope.
Cope.
Mope.
Grope.
Slope.
Pope.
Rope.
Hope.
I like the word hope.
So I put it on my wall.
Hope will never abandon you.
It's you who abandons hope.
Mom.
Let's go home.
I'm so sleepy.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Let's live.
We'll be okay, baby.
Let's go home.
Mom!
Are you sleeping?
- Are you home, baby?
- Yeah.
- Are you sick?
- No
Then what's wrong?
You're meeting
Deok-soo in a few days.
You'll have a wonderful date.
I'm not gonna meet him.
Yeah right.
Why not?
I hate everything.
What's wrong?
Did you eat dinner?
What the?
Look at me.
Look, mom!
Let's see you, mom!
What?
What's wrong
with your face?
Out of my way!
Move, idiot!
Where's the doctor?
- I need a doctor!
- What's the matter?
Come this way.
Why is she here?
I don't know what she did
but look at her face.
- Look at her!
- Let's see your face, ma'am!
Let's see your face!
It's okay, mom!
Did you burn yourself?
Is your face burnt?
- No.
- Huh?
I uh...
What?
What did you do?
Botox!
What's Botox?
Botox...
- Put ointment on her.
- Okay.
Are you mad?
No, I'm not mad.
Yes you are mad!
I'm not.
Let's go.
You are.
I said I'm not.
Come on!
No.
Are you mad, mom?
Here. I'll give you
a piggy back.
No.
- You are mad again?
- No.
- Piggy back, mom!
- That's okay.
Just get on my back.
It's okay.
- Happy?
- Yes. Happy.
Geez, mom!
You almost scared me
to death!
- Really?
- Yeah.
They said you'll be okay
after the treatment tomorrow.
- So don't you worry.
- Okay.
- I'm not mad by the way.
- Yes, you are.
- I'm not.
- You are!
I'm not!
- Mom.
- Yeah?
I'm so happy I have you.
I'm so happy
I have you, son.
- Really?
- Really.
I'm so glad!
- How do you feel, mom?
- Good!
- Good?
- Yeah!
- Then sing me a song!
- What?
On the streets?
That's so classless!
But you'll do it
anyway, right?
How did you know?
One Two Three Four!
Samba samba samba samba!
My dear love!
Samba, samba,
samba, samba!
Be happy and smile
as much as possible.
Watch what you eat.
Fight lethargy
with light exercise.
Of course, doctor.
I'm getting better.
The key is to stay positive.
I'd like to book a flight
for two to Paris.
When would you
like to leave?
April 29th.
It's my son's birthday.
I'm all better.
Here comes the cake!
Happy birthday,
Sang-hoon!
I want to blow out
the candles after him!
You're not a baby!
- It's kimbap!
- You're six already!
Can you get me
kimchi, please?
Kimchi?
We have to get some out.
We ate it all.
- You do it.
- Come on...
My back aches.
- Okay.
- Thanks!
It's the one in front
of the door, right?
Yeah.
Your kimchi is the best!
Where is it, sis?
Second container
on the right platform!
I'll be back.
I'm coming!
Eat, guys!
- Wait!
- Here, let me see too!
You can see Paris
and New York!
What is it?
- Wait!
- Show me!
You're blocking it!
Dong-sook!
I um...
You know...
You said You know 1 3 times.
You know, I'm...
Sick?
A lot?
More than me?
But you can fight it,
right?
Of course.
I can fight it.
It's nothing.
YOU'RE A STAR OF TOMORROW!
Where are you?
Do what you want.
Follow your dreams.
Or you'll regret it.
I'm on your side.
By the way
Did your dad have
square jaw line too?
Hi sweetie!
We found mom!
Hi. Um...
I'd like to audition.
CLASS CANCELLED
Let's record your mom.
Way to go, Mom!
Oh Penny!
Please take me the way I am!
Am I that revolting?
Revolting?
These are my savings.
Sis.
Everything will be alright.
I know.
PRESCRIPTION
I'm just here to get
Yeon-doo's book.
Come give me a massage.
I'm in pain.
You do have strong hands.
# I'm crazy.
Crazy just for you!
What a freak show.
Come back to work.
I need you.
It's not my style
to take the taxi.
- Do you have a cold?
- Yeah, a bit.
Are you crazy?
Do you know how
important this concert is?
It'll be the end of me
if I get a cold.
How can you be
so thoughtless?
Go home!
What's your child to you?
I mean
What am I to you?
You don't know how
the world runs.
This isn't just about me.
It's about the whole concert.
You're right,
I don't know.
Then shut up and go home.
Hurry!
You're a nasty woman.
What?
I'm going on that audition
you just saw on TV.
I'm gonna go on it
and humiliate you.
Yeah right you will.
Stay right there!
Don't you feel sorry
for your mom?
I feel sorry for myself!
I feel sorry that I have
a mother like you!
Take your book,
you moron!
Come out, sweetie!
Breakfast is ready!
Hurry.
I'm gonna count to five.
Here I go.
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five!
Sweetie?
Honey?
Are you in here?
Won-jae!
Honey!
Have you seen Won-jae?
No, sorry.
Where are you,
Won-jae?
Won-jae!
Won-jae! Won-jae!
Hello?
Who is this?
Excuse me.
I'm supposed to meet Dr. HIN
in Gynecology here.
- Have you seen him?
- No, sorry.
Dr. HIN!
Doctor!
Where is Won-jae?
Is he hurt?
He's fine.
He came to see me this
morning on my way to work.
Begging me
to save your life.
Doctor,
please save my mom.
Please sir!
Save my mom!
I don't want
my mom to die!
Please don't let her die.
Mom.
What are going
to eat in Paris?
Hmm?
Tuna!
How about in Italy?
Beef.
My little boy!
What do I call you?
My little puppy!
You're so cute
when you smile.
Sweetie!
Close your eyes.
Mommy's face.
Mommy's forehead.
Mommy's eyebrow.
Eyes.
Smile.
I'll be coming home
smiling like this.
It's cold out.
Don't come here again.
Okay?
- You trust me, right?
- Of course.
Of course.
My little puppy.
Baby, we have a problem.
Grandma's concert and mom's
audition are both tomorrow.
What should we do?
Simple. I go to Mom,
you go to Grandma.
How about the other
way around?
No.
No fair.
They'll both do well,
right?
But what
if I don't go tomorrow?
Dead.
I'm dead, right?
Do you like me
or that game?
- You.
- Thanks.
You're so lucky
you're young.
Sorry?
Your mother
must be beautiful.
Your skin is so soft!
It's good to be young!
You know concert's
tomorrow, right?
Don't be late.
Got it?
I'm so lucky I don't
have a daughter.
Really really lucky.
Look who's calling!
Hello, my dear son!
Shopping again?
You just bought me last week!
Don't buy anything.
What a bitch!
Sir?
- Hmm?
- Just one more day.
- Do I look good?
- Of course you do!
You probably couldn't
sleep well last night.
Sleep a bit in the car.
No way!
What if my face gets
all puffy?
It's Mr. LEE. Hold on.
- Hi, Mr. LEE!
- We have a problem, boss.
Yeong-man's boys got the old man.
What?
- Did they take him?
- Yes, boss.
He wants you to come
to Juliana Club.
I'm sorry, boss.
I'll be there.
Get the boys there too.
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Are we there already?
No. Um...
It looks like
the plane will be delayed.
What?
What do we do, then?
It won't be
delayed too much.
Actually...
Your hair style
is strange today.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Why did you do that?
- It looks bad?
- Yeah.
Really?
Oh. Shoot.
It is a bit strange.
Okay! I'll redo it!
Great idea, mom!
Let me just go
to school quickly.
Okay.
KIM Young-man!
Welcome.
What the hell
are you doing?
Me?
I'm just having fun with
your mother's first love.
Why are you shaking?
Cold or scared?
What do you want?
Is it me?
Take your shot.
KOO Seung-chul.
Hey, KOO!
One!
Three!
Four! Five!
- Boss!
- Come here, you son of a bitch!
Get that old man!
I said get that old man!
SURGERY CONSENT FORM
Get ready for your surgery
at 4 o' clock this afternoon.
I'm all ready.
I'm sure you have
everything under control.
- Right, sis?
- Right!
Sis.
It's Won-jae.
My little puppy! You're up?
Did you have breakfast?
I'm going
in for surgery now.
I'll be out in no time.
- Are you listening?
- Yes.
Why the sad voice?
Mom...
You'll be okay, right?
Of course!
Who am l?
- My mom.
- Correct!
Your mom is the strongest
person in the world.
We'll be taking you
into surgery.
- Sweetie?
- Yeah?
I love you.
See you soon.
I love you too, mom.
HOPE
PLEASE DO NOT BE LATE
FOR YOUR AUDITION
Are you scared, mom?
No.
I know but what can I do?
All the parents
are begging ne
so I can't refuse.
You're in good hands
with Mr. LEE.
Just relax and enjoy
your date, mom.
Okay. It's too bad
but what can we do.
It's not your fault you're
the most popular English teacher.
Thanks mom.
You're the best.
Have a great time, mom.
Ouch.
Aren't you coming?
Wanna see my mom pass out?
I'm so sorry.
We've planned everything
perfectly so don't screw up.
I'll be watching you.
I am the king of acting.
Don't you worry.
Yeah right.
Mom...
I miss you...
Two hours
to dress rehearsal.
Yes, sir.
I'll be right there.
Who is it?
I'm cheering for you,
Mrs. HANG!
I knew you'd come.
Get Eun-sung to get me
a bottle of mineral water.
She's gone for the audition.
What? She really went?
Yes, as far as I know.
Where's my cell?
She probably can't pick up.
Why not?
She should be in
the middle of her audition.
I'm going on that audition
you just saw on TV.
I'm gonna go on it
and humiliate you.
- Go start the car
- Pardon?
- Hurry!
- Your flower
- Now!
- Yes, ma'am
I'm so nervous.
Hi, dad.
Okay.
# Please forgive me.
# Come back I beg you.
Thank you.
Pretty good.
You don't have
a solid base.
You seem fake.
Souless.
Sol. Do Re Mi Fa Sol.
PARK Eun-sung,
you're next.
Okay.
Let the film roll.
Que!
- Ok-joo.
- Deok-soo.
You're not him.
It can't be.
It's me, Deok-soo.
- Who are you?
- HANG Deok-soo.
- Massage here.
- Yes, sir.
Are you okay?
Hey. Which restaurant
did you reserve?
The best one in Seoul.
We ordered a full
course meal.
- How about the theater?
- Theater, Karaoke, Sauna.
We've rented them all.
Well done.
Now it's all up
to that old fart.
It was a busy morning.
I'm feeling hungry now..
It's not very
nice out, is it?
Are you cold?
Should we get you
something to put on?
But my son always
takes me shopping.
Actually...
there's somewhere
I really want to go.
Where might that be?
Hey!
Come quickly!
Get in!
Don't get in that, mom!
Damn it!
We're headed down
a rough path.
- Quick! Get in!
- Yes, boss.
Move out of the way
A bike is coming!
This place might
look slummy
but they have the best
cabbage fritters in Seoul.
It's been a while since
you've had this, right?
I had reserved the best
restaurant in Seoul!
My son is so good to me.
He found these
places for me.
Thanks for noticing, mom.
Oh yeah!
Did I tell you my son is
a popular English teacher?
I knew that!
He's doing very well!
What?
Have you met my son?
No, not exactly.
I meant, that's what
I've heard from others.
I see.
I'll tell you what.
Let's go see my son
teach English.
He speaks English
so well!
His work's not far from here.
Why, mom?
Actually...
Why would I want
to meet your son?
You're right.
Let's not spoil this.
Let's go for
coffee somewhere.
Where you going now?
Don't you worry.
You'll be alright.
See you soon, okay?
Auntie!
Where's mom?
How about me?
It's hot!
Be careful!
Don't burn yourself!
- It's roasted well!
- Hot!
Damn it!
Where the heck are they?
They got here 1 5 minutes ago
and gulped down their coffee.
They circled this area twice.
Answer my question.
Where are they?
This way.
Spread out!
Yes, boss
Stick close to them and
tell me what they're saying.
Yes, boss
Wait a moment, sir.
Here I go.
Ok-joo, how are you
feeling today?
I can't describe it.
I was an old
fart living a dull life.
But thanks to you
I feel like
I'm in heaven now.
Did my mom just say that
she was living
a dull life?
Are you delivering
this correctly?
Yes, sir.
Look, dumbass.
Just tell me what they're
saying minus the emotions.
You're giving me
goose bumps.
I thought you might
find this useful.
- Ok-joo.
- It's nothing expensive.
Would you...
Like to come with me?
Sorry?
What the hell's he up to?
Shit.
My life-long wish was
...to see you before I die.
Oh my god.
You still had this
after all these years.
But after seeing you
like this
I don't think I can
live without you.
Oh, Deok-soo
Boss!
Hey! Hey!
You know...
I've led a bad life.
My life's been a real mess.
But I think that
if I can just be with you
I...
I can live a decent life
like everyone else.
Really...
Can l...
Can I really go with you?
Would you?
Won-jae.
Your mom won't be
out for awhile.
Let's go and have lunch.
We have to stay
strong for your mom.
It's okay.
I'll eat with my mom later.
Then I'll go out and get
something to eat. Stay here.
Hurry up!
- KANG Eun-sung?
- Yes?
- You're a housewife?
- Yes.
Are you.
- No.
- Sorry?
I'm not.
Weren't you
a back dancer before?
Right. I danced
on the back stage.
Let's be quick.
I have a cold coming.
This is so sweet!
Is there a particular
reason why you're here?
I've wanted to sing
since I was young.
Why are you auditioning
so late?
Because of my mother.
As a married woman it
must've been hard to get here.
Why do you want
to start singing?
- Because of my mother.
- Bitch!
Mommy!
You're right.
You should sing well just
like your famous mother.
Your mother is HANG Hee-kyoung
the soprano singer, right?
- HANG Hee-Kyoung?
- From the musical Loveholic?
You're going to be singing
a pop music, not classical!
I'm really looking
forward to this.
Let's see how you
compare to your mother,
the best soprano singer
in the country!
In the breeze...
Thank you.
Ma'am? Come.
I guess you're nervous.
You're so unlike
your proud mother!
Your mother never had problems
being cruel to others!
That asshole!
Let's hear it again!
What's the need?
I said I have a cold.
I told you no to do it.
Thank you.
The exit's on your left.
I wanted to sing!
I wanted to be a singer!
Hey! KANG Eun-sung!
Grab that microphone.
# In the breeze
# I can here love calling
# The love that left me
When darkness fades and
tomorrow comes.
This is your story.
Focus on the lyrics.
Close your eyes
and be confident!
- Let's go, mom!
- You can do it, hon!
# When darkness fades
# and tomorrow comes
# My past days of longing
You're great!
# Just might come back
# Come back to me slowly
# I won't cry anymore
# It hurts to say goodbye.
# Even if I leave again
# I'll give you all my love.
Everyone together!
# I can't remember
# But I can't forget
# The longing
when sadness passes
# Even when time passes
# Stay by my side
# Just like now and forever.
# Like now and forever.
She's glowing!
How vulgar!
Thank you.
You're coming with me?
Yes.
In next life.
Your son will get
married and leave you.
Someday you'll have to
live your own life.
I'll do anything for you.
You know I married
a lowlife loser
And got beat up all my life.
I died over and over again.
You know who saved me?
My son.
To me,
My son is my guardian.
I..
I can never leave
my guardian.
Son, you make me so happy.
Mom, you make me
so happy, too.
Forehead.
Eyes.
Then... Smile.
Surprise!
I thought you might be
alone right now.
I'm taking
my surgery very well.
So please keep your smile!
And pray for me.
I love you.
Hope shows magic
to its beholder.
HOPE
HOPE WILL COME TRUE.
BELIEVE IT, WON-JAE!
HOPE
EVERYTHING COMES FROM HOPE.
CHEER UP, SWEETIE.
Hi there. I'm
the yogurt delivery lady.
Long time no see.
I've been a bit sick
so I'm getting a surgery.
The doctor says
that I could die.
But he's wrong.
I know I'm going
to fight through it.
Why?
Because I have to
keep my promise
with my son who is fighting
muscular dystrophy.
My son is just 11 years old.
He 's not even able
to come to the hospital.
He 's alone,
probably praying
desperately for his mom.
Please help him fight
through this.
All he needs is
your message of hope.
Hope is his favorite word.
Those messages and your
energy will protect my son
and I believe
they'll save me.
I'm going to make
through this.
I have to.
I have no other choice.
HOPE COMES TO THOSE WHO DREAM.
STAY STRONG FOR YOUR MOM, WON-JAE!
YOUR MOTHER WILL GET BETTER.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
Because I'm a mother.
Mom?
I don't like Edelweiss.
It's so outdated!
Edelweiss is
the fundamental of music!
You need a strong base.
And here!
Every morning you greet me
It's not just
greet me here.
It's greet me
with a strong t' sound.
Got it?
From the beginning.
Nice.
Let's go.
# Edelweiss,
# edelweiss
# Every morning you
greet me. Hear it?
She's someone
I just can't hate.
- # Samba, samba, samba, samba!
- # Samba!
- # My dancing queen
- # Queen
# Samba, samba, samba
She's someone I thank
for just being alive.
Breakfast, sweetie!
Come on, get up!
I'm gonna eat all
of your favorite fish!
- I'm sleepy!
- One, two, three!
She's the strongest
person in the universe!