Episode 1
DumbLand
THE NEIGHBOR
Yes?
I was just looking at that
wooden shed over there.
Oh... Yes...?
I like that shed.
That's my shed.
I know it's your fucking shed!
I like that wooden shed.
I have a false arm...
What's that you say?
Fuck you, you motherfuckin' helicopters,
you motherfuckers!
Fuck you, you fuck!
You fucking motherfucking helicopters!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, you fucking motherfuckers!
I heard once someone said
you fuck ducks.
I am a one-armed duck-fucker.
THE END
Episode 2
DumbLand
THE TREADMILL
Stop your fucking exercising!
Hey dad, let me try!
Hey dad, let me try! Hey dad...
Fuckin' twit.
'Scuse me!
Hi.
What the fuck...
You look like you might be
interested in a household product
that makes things
smell really good.
Smell gud
What if I was out in yard takin' a shit?
You think of that?
I can repeat the Gettysburg Address
if you'd care to hear it...
Four score and seven years ago
our forefathers brought forth
upon this continent a new nation...
Hey dad, hey dad!
Hey dad! Hey dad! Hey dad!
Ha! And they said you were stupid.
THE END
Episode 3
DumbLand
THE DOCTOR
Hey!
You got any mail for me?
Sorry, no mail for you!
Oh yeah?
Well I got two letters for you...
F U, stamp licker!
Who broke the fuckin' lamp?!
I, I, I, I...
I, I, I, I, I...
I did!
I'll fix it my-fuckin'-self!
I am the doctor.
Does that hurt you?
No.
No...
Wait just a fucking second!
Does that hurt you?!
Just what I thought.
You're completely normal.
THE END
Episode 4
DumbLand
A FRIEND VISITS
What the fuck?!
- That's my new clothes line!
My God! - Not for long.
That's my clothes line!
That's my new...
What if I had to come out
in the yard at night to take a shit?!
I could slice my fuckin' head off!
That's my new clothes line!
That's my new clothes...
Say what?
A friend visits...
Are you goin' up to the mountains?
Yup. I'm goin' fishin'.
Cut their heads off
right there by the stream...
Gut 'em... fry 'em up...
I like to kill deer.
Who don't?
Same thing. I cut their heads off
right there in the woods...
Then I rip 'em open...
...gut 'em, and fry me up
some genuine old deer meat.
You like to kill sheep?
Sure do.
Same thing. Sheep are fun
to have around and I like to kill 'em.
You cut their heads off?
Sure do.
Same thing. Clean their heads up some
and hang 'em up on the wall.
I got two of 'em
hangin' up in the latrine.
I say, "You sheep keep starin'
at me and I'm liable to shit."
I cut the heads
of all the animals I kill.
Horse head, dog head,
cat head, pig head...
All of 'em.
That's right.
I tell you what, the wall's full of 'em.
Better believe it.
There's nothin' like
sharin' a kill with a friend.
I like to kill things.
THE END
Episode 5
DumbLand
GET THE STICK
Hey dad, there's a man
with a stick caught in his mouth!
There's the man with the stick
caught in his mouth!
Get the stick!
Get the stick! Get the stick!
Fuckin' stick.
I'll get the fuckin' stick.
Get the stick!
Get the stick! Get the stick!
You broke his neck!
The fucker won't sit still.
Make him sit still!
Get the stick! Get the stick!
You poked his eye out!
Get the stick!
Get the stick! Get the stick!
You poked his other eye out!
You got the stick!
Watch the traffic!
Watch the traffic! Watch the traffic!
Fucker never even said thank you.
THE END
Episode 6
DumbLand
MY TEETH ARE BLEEDING
My teeth are bleeding!
My teeth are bleeding! ...
Fuckin' flies!
THE END
Episode 7
DumbLand
UNCLE BOB
This is how it's gonna be...
You're gonna stay here
and watch your uncle Bob.
Stop your whining, bitch!
I'm not afraid of this
dickhead husband of yours.
Uncle Bob's not feelin' well,
you lay one hand on him
and I'll cut your nuts out.
You're goin' shoppin'
with your momma.
Remember what I told you
about your nuts.
We'll be back when we get
good and ready.
Later...
Uncle Bob!
What's wrong with uncle Bob?!
How the fuck should I know?!
I saw that!
Later...
They're gone!
You're safe!
She took uncle Bob to the hospital!
Uncle Bob bit his foot off!
THE END
Episode 8
DumbLand
ANTS
Fuckin' ants!
Here it comes, fuckers.
When we look at you...
we see an asshole.
Ass-hole!
When we look at you...
we see an asshole.
Ass-hole!
When we look at you...
we see a shithead.
Shit-head!
When we look at you...
we see a shithead.
Shit-head!
When we look at you...
we see a dumb turd.
Dumb turd!
When we look at you...
we see a dumb turd.
Dumb turd!
When we look at you...
we see an asshole.
Ass-hole! Shit-head! Dumb turd!
Ass-hole! Shit-head! Dumb turd! ...
What?!
Fuckers!
I'll get you, you motherf...
THE END