www.zoom.lk
The apartment building is on fire.
2 victims on the ground floor.
Four terrorists blew up a building in the center.
36 people are feared dead.
More than 70 have been injured.
A suicide bomber drove a car laden with explosives
-
The central bank's premises.
Anti-terrorist group does not know the author.
Crime scene investigators rushed to the scene
.
Bomb attack on the fortress
Police Station
Lost.
- Over there.
Do not you remember other characters?
- I do not.
Signature here, sir.
Call me next week.
Next!
Seat. What's this?
- I lost my wallet.
How did it happen?
- What?
How do you lost it?
- I do not know. It was a back pocket.
Where did it happen?
I do not know.
- What was in your wallet?
The image of my wife. Driver's license.
Receipt of the payment.
Credit Card. Picture of my wife.
- Mentioned it.
What?
- Wife picture.
Did you find money in your wallet?
- 400 - 500 rupees.
Please enter the form name and address.
Vincent Dias, Windsor Flats 16,
is it true?
Vince.
- Phone number?
077-7534109.
- And the landline?
It has not worked in months.
- Sign here.
What?
- So, thank you.
Please call a few days later.
We will tell if something has happened.
Where is the bathroom?
- Right through that door.
Come on, lady.
How many?
Good Lord!
Receipt.
How many were there?
About a decade.
- What time did it happen?
Six countries.
Have you been there before?
A pound of tomatoes.
Terrorism has been ravaged before a peaceful city.
Ten years
attacks have become regrettably common.
Dilky Thenuwara,
TV1 Colombo.
Discuss how the attacks affected the Sri Lankan politics.
Vietyäni you go to the police station.
Call if you need anything.
- Okay.
I hate traveling alone.
You'll be fine.
I will visit on Saturday.
Hello. Did you buy the almonds and raisins?
- Yes.
Buy tomatoes.
- I already bought.
When you come home?
- Seven.
Try to get there early for dinner.
Pavithra the last bus leaves.
- Okay.
POLICE UNIT READY
deputy chief of MORRIS DaSilva
Yeah?
- Morris De Silva?
Listen to me carefully.
You know the effective C-4 plastic explosive?
Who's there?
Listen carefully, Mr. Deputy
.
AP Lord.
I put the bomb in five different locations in the city.
They are explosive,
, but it can be avoided...
Who's there?
How did you get my number?
AP, do not you ever interrupt me.
Like I said, this can be avoided.
I'll call you in an hour .
Discuss your requirements.
Decide who has the power to agree to the
.
Hello?
Victor? Trace a previous call on my cell
. The issue is important.
Call the police chief.
He is the ASEAN meeting in Jakarta
. He'll be back tomorrow.
Request a constable Mohideen here.
I do not know!
Give me a second. Hello.
Miss Dilky Thenuwara?
- Yes. Who's there?
Miss Dilky, for me, is a clue
of the biggest news.
We have a hot-line
for the information.
What is this?
This is not reality TV in the
air-conditioned studio.
This is the most important day of your life.
- The most important day of my life?
Where is it happening?
Polgodan police station.
Go there now.
Mohideen, we may have a problem.
Someone called and said that he
detonate five bombs in Colombo.
We need to take the threat seriously.
Gather the necessary troops,
intelligence unit, and bomb squad.
Soon.
- Yes, sir!
Cancel my appointments.
I got the story tip.
Polgodan I'm on the way to the police station.
I'll contact you later.
POLGODAN Police Station
right. No.
Cell phone is registered
Rudra Wilson. It is closed.
Let's go.
Good morning. Sit down.
We have a problem. Someone threatens to blow up the
five bombs in the city.
It may be a joke, mad ravings
or terrorist attack.
We can not know.
He ​​called me on my cell.
All what is happening here,
remaining confidential.
Co-operation is vital.
- Yes, sir.
Ganesha,
ask what the intelligence unit to know.
Warner? Find out all the
transport of explosives in Colombo.
Especially heksogeenin ratio.
Use the informant.
Victor?
Turn my cell phone speakers.
Be ready to trace the call
when he plays.
Who is with me?
Where is the Prime Minister?
Do you think that the Prime Minister be talking to you?
Why not? During the election they were talking about
to us. Are they now too busy?
Right. Politicians have to explain
bomb attacks in people afterwards.
Whom am I speaking?
He uses a number of mobile phones
and replace the SIM card.
Do this.
Tell the deciding issues,
that prisons are four warriors.
Sarath Master. D. Gopinath.
Prakash Kumar. Akthul Majood.
Do not you remember?
Two arrested in Colombo, Jaffna
one, and one in Hong Kong.
What about them?
- Release them.
Release?
- I want you release them.
It should not be difficult.
They are doomed to terrorists.
They have been imprisoned long enough to
. Three is Welikadan prison.
The fourth is an unknown place.
Gather them together.
You can not be serious.
- Serious?
Do you think you joking?
- I do not know.
What is your connection with them?
- They are warriors.
They are not supposed to be behind bars.
Are you trying to dictate terms?
Why should I believe you?
Polgodan the police station is a two-kilo heksogeenipommi.
It will explode in 40 minutes.
Perhaps you will take me seriously then.
Mohideen! If he is telling the truth,
need to find a bomb in 40 minutes.
Victor! The call lasted a long time.
He is in town, but we need the
time figuring out the location.
Go to  Polgodan station bomb group
sergeant with the anuran.
Hello.
- Hello.
Polgodan the police station to explode a bomb.
Polgodan police station is in shambles.
Bomb squad and police dogs
examining the position.
We received an anonymous tip about the bomb.
Victor, please call the inquiry.
I would like to know about them prisoners.
Prepare to evacuate the building.
Clear the area.
- Isolate area.
Wait for further instructions.
Go away.
A bomb has been found.
C-4 and dynamite
, combined with a lighter.
Counseling can not override
this time.
We need more time.
Bomb will explode in three minutes.
So.
- It is useless to panic.
I tell you how the bomb landed?
Yes. Tell.
- Now do you believe me?
I believe! Tell.
Lighter goes three wires.
Three wires lighter!
Cut the green wire.
- Switch off the green wire!
Bomb demolition in progress.
A bomb landed successfully.
Well, release the prisoners?
Need more time.
- It is not.
Mohideen? Call the Secretary of State.
Secretary of State to call.
Deputy Chief Morris Da Silva.
- How are you?
Well, sir.
Can I speak to the minister?
He is a political meeting
Kandy.
I understand.
Sir, we have a problem.
Do you expect the minister to return?
We do not.
I can not speak on the phone.
You have to come here.
- Okay. Half an hour.
Thank you, sir.
Hello.
- Did you talk to?
Bentota We went just wide, though.
- Okay.
You sound a little strange.
- It's nothing. I'll call you later.
We found an important clue.
Broker.
He sold six pounds heksogeeniä.
He ​​refuses to speak.
How so?
Look for Officer Ranjan.
He put the man to talk to.
The man has his sources of information.
Where a prisoner is?
Talk station officer.
Somebody had to see something.
There is a young news reporter.
He ​​is there before anything happens.
Command Victor interrogate him.
We Polgodan the police station.
Upon impact is not taken responsibility.
Secretary of State came.
- What is it?
Tiilanne has worsened.
Please indicate the province as soon as the Prime Minister.
Police Station environment is isolated.
We will tell more later.
I Dilky Thenuwara, TV1.
DUNSTAN PERERA Kosovo Prime Minister
What is this?
- I am a police headquarters.
Deputy Chief is here, sir.
The Prime Minister wants to talk to you.
Good morning, sir.
- What's the matter?
The caller said
put five bombs in the city.
Polgodan One of the demolished police station. The man is a serious threat.
He ​​agrees to talk only with policy makers.
This means you, sir.
We can combine his calls to you.
No. It is clearly
general public order.
Bomb threat?
He can not be a terrorist.
This is more of your border.
I do not have the authority.
Speeches, marketing is very different from
incident management.
I'll give you full power.
- On one condition.
You do not intervene, nor to criticize
me afterwards.
The matter is settled.
Keep me informed of the situation.
EXAM TITLE
Stick.
Calid, who bought the explosives?
I do not know what you're talking about.
Do not lie to me.
You know how she is.
Tell me the name or I beat it on you.
I do not know!
Tell the name!
Forwarded the 6 pounds heksogeeniä
dealer. You know him.
Pithala Nihal. Cross Street 5
Sale of used computers.
PITHALANIHAL arms dealer
heksogeenin Who did you sell?
Tell her name!
Tell his name!
Hello.
- This guy does not know anything.
None.
Back here.
I will tell the Deputy Head.
D. Gopinath,
criminal accountant, was caught -
Illegal weapons and explosives
cease-fire with the territory.
He was convicted of two
bombing. He is a clever man.
He is suffering from a life sentence Welikadassa.
Sarath Master, which is known as
bombing the embassy.
He ​​is responsible for the death of a number of torture.
He is suffering from a life sentence Welikadassa.
Akthul Majood organized training camps.
He ​​provided a number of weapons to terrorist organizations.
He trained more than a thousand fighters.
All of them were 16-20 years of age.
He has suffered a six-year sentence
5 years and 8 months Welikadassa.
Why Akthul Majood?
He ​​would soon be free.
Prakash Kumar, known as PK.
Pilots
which provided weapons and ammunition to the enemy.
A close vihollisjohtajalle.
He ​​is considered to be in an unknown place.
The two of you! Come here!
Come on!
News reporter, sir.
Miss Dilky Thenuwara.
When did you first call?
He ​​used to take advantage of you.
He ​​follows the events using newscast.
You are his eyes!
Do not you understand?
What kind of person are you?
- I beg your pardon.
I am a Sri Lankan woman.
Supplier.
Good.
I would ask the Sri Lankan woman's help.
I do not have time to reporters.
It's insane to use
to you.
We need to import
the four prisoners together.
Three is Welikadassa, but the fourth...
He is a closely guarded
military base.
Search and search for him immediately.
WELIKADAN PRISON
dangerous terrorists are transferred from prison to an unknown location.
We do not know the reason for the transfer of prisoners.
Follow my instructions. Good.
Three prisoners are Welikadassa.
Kumar's whereabouts are unknown.
I need time to his discovery.
- He must be found.
He is an important part of the plan.
You can not waste any more time.
- What do I do prisoners?
Katukurundan Take them to the airport runway.
Obey  so casualties should not be.
- They were delivered to the site.
How many police officers are not accompanied by a warrior?
Five.
- Too many.
Two police officers.
Two mobiles on both sides.
They have to be able to block calls.
Anything else?
- One of the thing.
The airport explosives.
Do not bring in a bomb dogs or impact forces.
I can blow up the four bombs
call.
Bombs Explode at 18:00.
Wait a minute!
How do I know that you extract the bombs?
Do you want to warranty?
I do not want deaths.
The inmates are responsible for the
mass murders in our country.
Do as I say.
I'll call you at three.
Did it work?
- Weird. I do not focus on the...
Is he definitely a city?
- Yes, sir.
Then
call seems to come from a different country.
Chennai. Mumbai.
Karachi, Pakistan.
Singapore. Maldives.
- How is that possible?
He ​​is clearly a communication expert.
Get Your Own specialists.
- We need a hacker.
Get a new one. Quickly.
- Yes, sir.
Study Katukurundan airport without attracting attention.
I hope he is not going to capture the
machine.
On duty does not remember anything strange.
Sergeant Bernard to remember the man who went to the toilet.
We have his number.
- Call it.
Well?
- He said he was Vincent Dias.
Phone number and address.
He ​​had a green bag.
Good. Anything else?
- I remember him clearly.
He said that
had lost his wallet. He was left-handed.
Number is not in use.
Tutkinko address?
- She does not live there.
Make a sketch about the suspect.
Hello.
- Miss Dilky.
Do you know Katukurundan airport?
- I can not do this.
I'm sorry what?
What do you mean?
You are using me!
- Of course.
If you were not interested,
you had said it immediately.
You're making me share the blame.
- Come on, Miss Dilky.
You are not so important. If Sri Lanka lost to India in cricket
-
it does not implicate the TV channels.
You look to the people what has to be.
This is not cricket, damn it!
Son of a bitch. You're right, Dilky.
And there is no shortage of suppliers.
They're rushing about around the stupid stories behind.
This is the right news.
Am I right, Dilky?
Where should I go?
- Katukurundan the airport at five.
Search equipment armory.
Contact Officer Ranjan that.
Opponent is smart, Mohideen.
I trust you both.
Sir.
Or, he was removed from the task...
Outrageous.
He is  Dilfer, sir.
Yeah?
- Welcome.
Dilfer is ethical and unethical hacking
expert.
Is he qualified?
- Must be overqualified.
He has helped to resolve the
serious crimes.
Difficult for you, not for me.
Do not worry.
I can help you, buddy. Sir.
That's why you're here, boy.
You will help us to find the madman.
Right. Let's do it.
Why paapomme terrorists?
I teloittaisin them all.
Calm down. We are police officers.
You are not a Terminator.
- Why can not I be?
WELIKADAN SOUTH GATE PRISON
SECRET SECURITY HOUSE, COLOMBO
Status Report.
- Everything is going according to plan.
We picked up  Kumar.
We are on the way to the airport.
Call me when you get there.
What's going on?
Where are you taking us?
- Shut up.
- Shut up, damn it!
We'll find out soon.
KATUKURUNDAN AIRPORT
Aisa?
- Hello.
Where are you?
- Still on the train.
The train is more and more behind.
I do not know the reason.
How's the baby?
- Roshi sleeps like a log.
I think he likes the train movement.
Call me when you arrive.
Aisa? I love you.
I love you too.
What is this?
Is your husband at the airport?
I would like to talk to them.
What are the names of the police officers?
- Ranjan Jayaweera and Mohideen Anver.
Mohideen? He wants to talk to them.
Put him on speaker.
Officer Mohideen,
I want to talk to my brothers.
Greetings.
- Greetings.
How do you do?
- Suojelkoon god for you.
Make sure that you have the right of conscience.
Tell me your name.
Akthul Majood.
- Sarath Master.
D. Gopinath. God bless you.
- Prakash Kumar.
Follow my instructions.
You will soon leave.
Mohideen, take the speaker off.
Enter your phone Mr. Akthulille.
Hello.
Were you a medication by mouth or with a needle?
No.
Forced you to eat something?
- No, but we're in handcuffs.
Do not worry, you are about to be free.
As God wants.
Mohideenille your phone and put him on speaker.
Mohideen.
- Yes?
Open the handcuffs.
Do you see the little engine end of the runway?
- Yes.
Warriors will get on a plane.
When the plane is in the air,
I will explain how the bombs landed.
Do as I say.
Time is running out.
Prakash Kumar. You are flying in the machine.
You have an award-winning pilot.
Run the airplane on the runway and wait for my instructions.
The machine has a cell phone.
Trivendramiin the telegraph.
Fuel is enough. This must be done in ten minutes
.
Deputy listening?
Yes . Mohideen, do as he commanded.
- Yes, sir!
Is there any survived?
- The call comes near Mount Lavinia.
Near the sea, and height.
- Are you sure?
If he calls again,
I tell her its exact location.
The guy is smart, but not the best.
I need the Air Force for help.
Connect the Air Force Commander.
We believe that he is
southern parts of the city.
Right.
- Probably the high altitude.
Suspected presence has no description.
Keep your eyes open.
Investigate the area.
We see an empty building, Mount Lavinia.
Coastal plain to the east.
Check on.
His position may be
to the south of you.
Right.
We do not see anything in the building.
He may be to the south of you.
Right. We fly to the south.
Warriors board the aircraft. Right now.
Go into the plane!
Ranjan, what do you do?
Let him go.
What if we are not told
bombs locations?
Bombs, and these men the range of
must have a connection!
Ranjan, we have our orders.
We accordingly.
I release him when I know where the bombs are.
What Akthul?
- Come on! Leave it to him!
Let's go!
- No.
Calm down.
We have to wait for instructions.
I have to go! They leave!
Mohideen. What is it?
Are the four prisoners on the plane?
Where is it?
Phone is here!
- Give it to me.
What did you do?
Warriors are on the way.
Sir!
Mohideen.
What happened?
- I do not know. They died.
What?
- There were probably a bomb.
It exploded.
Three prisoners were killed.
What do you mean three?
Master, Gopinath and Kumar have died
.
Akthul Majood live.
We bring her there.
What the hell did you do?
No. No.
You made a big mistake.
You will replace it.
Enter Akthulin to hear this.
Intention was to release all the four prisoners of this world.
The work was never completed. Officers,
you will take care of it in the end.
What do you mean?
If the kitchen is cockroach -
hellitkö it or liiskaatko it?
Just what this is all about.
'll Clean the cockroaches in the corners.
- Enough! Where's the rest of the bombs?
Who are you?
Do you have a name?
Why is it interesting?
You know me very well.
I am afraid to get on a train or a bus.
My wife thinks that I go to
for the war, when I go to work.
He plays every couple of hours, it
afraid that I will not return.
call to hear if I'm alive. If I want to open a shop -
I do not dare to name it, because it can be burned
brawler.
Fought  anyone,
I'm always the first victim.
Choose someone in the crowd.
I am he.
Sri Lankan citizen.
Fallen in love with the country.
Why do you have a nice special occasion?
We all love our country.
What kind of man are you?
Who do you think you are? Superman?
I'm not Superman.
Rather, the Invisible Man.
I have even removed
voting register.
I do not exist.
So, Mr. AP... In order to purchase
-
heksogeenipommiin materials need not be Teräsmies.
It manages the invisible man.
Take a look at the internet.
Hundreds of pages will guide in making bombs.
Do not ask me how, ask us why!
Why? Focus on the present moment,
Mr. AP.
One of the cockroach still have to whack.
Then tell you where the bombs are.
If we do not kill Majoodia,
you are going to blow up the bombs.
You're killing innocent people.
Right. If he is released, he will kill thousands of
.
I ask only one person.
He ​​would have to death.
Compare the alternatives.
This is a good bargain.
Why are these four
so many terrorists?
These four held a lottery happiness.
Do not you dare to tell your name?
- Do not worry about it.
You should have to destroy these creatures
after the attacks.
Sessions were several
but did not do anything.
Causes of terrorism does not matter.
The same place where they are from.
Causes need to be addressed, but not
at the expense of innocent lives.
They hit the train station.
We cried a couple of days.
Then they hit the holy city.
Then to the airport.
How many were killed? Have you already forgotten?
Forgetting is a national sicknesses.
Terrorism must be destroyed.
A quick right.
- Why not? Terrorism is urgent.
If we wait, it just evolves.
New names, new shapes.
The core remains the same. Terrorism.
You want to destroy terrorism but to terrorize us!
What religion you belong to?
Religion? There is...
This is not about religion.
Gopinath was a Hindu. Murderer.
I killed him. So am I a Muslim?
Sarath Master, a Buddhist.
Thousands killer. I killed him.
Does that make me a Christian?
You may argue religions attributed
unsuspecting people.
It is up to you.
You can push out the lies on TV
and brainwash the gullible.
Do not join together by me to any group.
I am an ordinary citizen,
which went into action.
Maybe I'm just a Christian or a Buddhist.
Communist or an atheist.
Do not we have the right to get angry?
Right to say that enough is enough.
This is not about race, religion or politics,
.
You'll need to know
that the people will be angry.
Do not tempt the patience.
I do not know what you're trying to prove,
but you will not succeed.
I'll find you.
I have already succeeded, Mr. AP.
I got your attention.
Tell me something.
Someone close to you he dead in bomb attacks?
Why should I wait
that anyone close die?
I'll tell you one thing.
There was someone on the train.
Approximately twenty-something man.
I do not know his name.
He always greeted me with a,
when the boarded the train.
I salute him.
We did not know each other's names.
We said only "hello" to each other.
He showed me the engagement rings
previous day.
He was happy.
The next day
missed the train, and I cheated death.
He did not.
After the train was no longer the familiar words.
Wagons full of the unknown.
What does it matter who I am?
When you leave home,
may not be able to return.
When the children go to school,
not be able to see them ever again.
Akthul, Gopinath and Sarath
may be a crossroads -
bomb.
He ​​will blow your dreams.
They kill anyone.
Terrorism must be crushed as soon as it starts.
You behave like a crazy terrorist.
Let me explain.
If they killed 300 - 400 people -
you expect the court.
I'll kill four terrorists,
and you are panicking.
I do not blame you.
You decided that we need to
wait for court action.
Too little, too late.
Am I crazy?
Perhaps, perhaps, perhaps.
Three bombs explode at exactly six.
The clock is ticking. You run out of time.
Officer Mohideen,
you decide whether this is the last call.
Supplier Thenuwara
arrives there in ten minutes.
He may look like on TV,
that Akthul Majood is dead.
You know what is at stake.
Then I'll tell where the bombs are.
Deputy Chief.
The situation is not under control.
Should I call the Prime Minister?
This will be the consequences.
It's too late to worry about it.
Sir.
What if something goes wrong?
Right.
These are going to a funeral.
I have been here since the beginning.
The feeling is mutual.
Forgot your cell phone.
Take it for him, Victor.
Wipe it.
Prime Minister's hands must remain clean.
Hello.
- Where are you?
At the airport. What blew up?
- It'll be fine.
Go next to the runway.
- Okay. Let's go!
Mohideen, remember that you are a police officer.
Sir!
- Mohideen? Can you hear me?
- Mohideen?
Hello! Sir!
Ranjan ! Ranjan, do not do it!
Ranjan, no!
We have to take him back.
No!
Ranjan! Do not do it!
Ranjan, stop it!
I will not let you do that.
Terrorist trying to escape
Jayaweera and Mohideen work.
The prisoners were transferred for security reasons.
During the transfer, they were able to free
and hijacked the aircraft.
Officer Jayaweera and I
to stop them.
The prisoner tried to escape.
We had to shoot him.
Oh, my God!
- Thank you, Mr. AP.
It was a pleasure to work with.
- Where the hell are the bombs?
This is a live broadcast of the Katukurundasta.
The terrorists tried to escape.
All four were killed.
Why they were brought here?
Where they were going to go?
Miss Dilky,
I have news for you.
Dilky, Dilky? Can you hear me?
- Yes.
I live on.
- I know Dilky.
I know that you are describing.
Tell the viewers,
where the other three are the bomb.
Listen carefully, I will say this only once
. Three bombs.
Bus. Pettah Matthegodaan.
Number 32
Train. At seven o'clock train Galle.
Mall. O'Dells, 1 layer.
None of them explode.
Take care of yourself, Dilky.
Thank you.
Officer Mohideen!
Stay tuned. Dilky Thenuwara
Katukurundan Airport.
What is this?
The train is stopped.
Call me back then.
Do not worry about it.
Are you ready?
I need an image quickly!
This does not work, sir.
How so?
- I'm sorry, sir.
What is that building?
Is he in there?
What happened?
You said that you are able to do this.
Can not you find him
whether or not you want to find?
Am I the only one who wants to capture the
of the man?
I understand.
What time is it?
My watch has stopped.
Have you been shopping?
Did you get everything you asked for?
Why are not you answering?
Are you on your way home?
- Yes.
I can not hear you.
Yes, honey. I'm on my way home.
My name is Morris Da Silva.
The CTU Deputy Head of Unit
.
"Mr. AP."
This will be a beautiful evening.
Nice and calm.
Transalate By Dj | Nimantha
www.zoom.lk