- PREVIOUSLY ON THE EXES...
- LOOK,
WE'RE FRIENDS,
AND--AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
WE'RE AVOIDING EACH OTHER
BECAUSE OF, WHAT,
ONE SILLY KISS?
- I KNOW.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
- FRIENDS?
- FRIENDS.
DUDE.
- DUDE.
- LET'S GO,
LET'S GO.
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR THE WEDDING.
WOW.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
- I KNOW.
I LIKE TO THINK THIS IS
WHAT JAMES BOND WOULD LOOK LIKE
IF HE WASN'T ALWAYS
A PASTY WHITE, ENGLISH DUDE.
- UH, WHAT IS KEEPING HASKELL?
IF HE MAKES US LATE
FOR THIS WEDDING,
I AM GONNA BE
ONE HOT MESS.
- DON'T WORRY,
WE'LL GET YOU THERE
IN TIME
TO CATCH THE BOUQUET.
ANYWAY, RELAX.
THIS IS PAUL'S WEDDING,
NOT YOURS.
- HELLO, GENTLEMEN.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING,
BUT I THINK
WE CAN ALL AGREE
IT WAS WORTH IT.
- HASKELL,
THAT IS ONE BEAUTIFUL TUX.
WHAT IS THAT, HUGO BOSS?
ARMANI?
- NOPE.
SHING-SHING WOO.
THIS LITTLE BABY COMES
FROM THE CHINESE PROVINCE
OF GUANGDONG CHENG.
IT COST ME $49.95,
AND MOST OF THAT
WAS SHIPPING.
- WELL, LET'S GO.
I DON'T WANT
TO KEEP MY DATE WAITING.
SHE'S MEETING ME
AT THE WEDDING.
- WHOA.
YOU'RE BRINGING A DATE?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
WEDDINGS ARE MEANT
TO BE SHARED WITH SOMEONE.
WHEN I WAS MARRIED,
I ALWAYS HAD LORNA,
BUT NOW, I DON'T WANT
TO BE THAT SAD BASTARD
ALONE IN THE CORNER.
- A DATE?
AT A WEDDING?
WHAT A WASTE.
WEDDINGS ARE STACKED
WITH BITTER, LONELY WOMEN
WONDERING,
"WILL IT EVER HAPPEN FOR ME?"
THEY'RE DESPERATE.
THEIR DEFENSES ARE DOWN.
THEIR BAR IS LOW...
WHICH IS WHERE I COME IN.
THE LAST TRAIN
OUT OF SAD TOWN.
- THERE ARE MY BOYS.
OH, YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
- HOLLY, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY WITH US
GOING TO PAUL'S WEDDING?
- OH, OF COURSE.
LOOK, IT WAS SWEET OF THEM
TO INVITE ME,
BUT LET'S FACE IT--
HAVING THE HOT, SUCCESSFUL,
CHARMING EX-GIRLFRIEND THERE
WOULD BE A DISTRACTION.
YEAH, IT WOULD BE SELFISH
OF ME TO GO.
AND, AFTER ALL,
THE WEDDING'S NOT ABOUT ME.
- WELL, GOOD FOR YOU.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU WEREN'T GOING
'CAUSE YOU WERE
FEELING JEALOUS
THAT PAUL
WAS GETTING MARRIED.
- HOW LITTLE YOU KNOW ME.
- I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU WERE THINKING
YOU MADE A MISTAKE
BREAKING UP WITH PAUL.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
- WELL, I THOUGHT--
- STOP THINKING!
GUYS, REST ASSURED,
I HAVE NO REGRETS
ABOUT BREAKING UP
WITH PAUL, ALL RIGHT?
I HAVE A RICH,
REWARDING LIFE--
[gasps]
THERE'S THAT COOKIE.
I'M SAVING YOU FOR LATER.
OH, WHO AM I KIDDING?
[upbeat music]
?
- WOW.
LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
ORCHIDS, DOM PERIGNON,
CAVIAR--
IT'S THE KIND OF WEDDING
EVERY YOUNG GIRL DREAMS ABOUT.
AND THE OCCASIONAL
40-YEAR-OLD MAN.
- DAMN, CHECK HER OUT.
WHEN IT'S TIME
TO KISS THE BRIDE,
I'M GETTING IN LINE.
- WELL, IF LUCK IS ON MY SIDE,
SHE'LL HAVE
A SAD, DESPERATE TWIN
WITH A DRINKING PROBLEM.
- HEY, THERE HE IS.
THE MAN OF THE HOUR.
- CONGRATULATIONS, BUDDY.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
- YOU SENT AN INVITATION.
- WHAT INVITATION?
- YOU DIDN'T MEAN
TO INVITE US?
- WHY WOULD I WANT
MY EX-GIRLFRIEND'S BEST FRIENDS
AT MY WEDDING?
- OH, WOW.
SORRY, MAN.
- YEAH, WE DIDN'T MEAN
TO INTRUDE
ON YOUR SPECIAL DAY.
- I'M JUST MESSING
WITH YOU GUYS.
- YOU GOT US AGAIN, BUDDY.
- YOU RASCAL.
- TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU DO THAT.
- WELL, I GOTTA RUN.
I PROMISED MY NANA
I'D TAKE A PICTURE WITH HER.
- AH, YOU MEAN THAT OLD LADY
LYING FACE DOWN ON THE FLOOR?
- WHAT?
- I'M JUST MESSING
WITH YOU.
- WHAT AN AWFUL THING
TO SAY,
AND ON MY WEDDING DAY.
- I CANNOT TELL YOU
HOW SORRY I AM.
- I'M JUST MESSING
WITH YOU.
I THOUGHT
IT WAS HILARIOUS.
[shouts]
- GIRL, YOU ARE LOOKING
SMOKIN'.
- THANKS.
YOU LOOK PRETTY HOT YOURSELF.
- WELL, UH, SINCE WE GOT
ALL THIS HEAT,
MAYBE LATER,
WE CAN SNEAK OFF
AND PUT EACH OTHER'S FIRES OUT.
- SOUNDS FUN, BUT--
- HERE YOU GO, EDEN.
- AH. THANKS.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- UM, BRETT, THIS IS PHIL.
PHIL, BRETT.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING, MAN?
- HEY.
- OKAY.
UM, SO YOU BROUGHT A DATE.
THAT'S COOL.
IT'S COOL.
- DIDN'T YOU BRING A DATE?
- HELL, YEAH.
BECAUSE THAT IS
HOW I ROLL.
NOW I JUST GOTTA
FIND ONE.
- WOW.
EDEN LOOKS GORGEOUS.
- YEAH.
- WHO'S THAT GUY SHE'S WITH?
- SOME DATE.
- GOOD-LOOKING GUY.
- OH, YOU THINK
THAT'S GOOD-LOOKING?
STUART, THIS HERE?
THIS IS GOOD-LOOKING.
YOU'RE JUST USED TO IT
'CAUSE YOU SEE IT EVERY DAY.
YOU'RE SPOILED.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'VE SCANNED THE ROOM.
THIS PLACE IS PACKED WITH
BITTER, DESPERATE, LONELY WOMEN.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS, WHO'S
GONNA WIN THE LUTZ LOTTERY?
[laughs, winces]
- WHAT'S WITH THE SCRATCHING?
- MY, UH--MY SHING-SHING WOO
IS A--IS A TAD ITCHY.
- HASKELL, THIS THING IS MADE
OF 10% WOOL AND 90% YAK.
[cell phone ringing]
HI, HELEN.
UH, WHA--WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU CAN'T MAKE IT?
HOW SICK?
YES, 104 IS ALARMING,
BUT YOU MADE A COMMITMENT.
NO, IT'S FINE.
I--YES.
I UNDERSTAND.
FEEL BETTER.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- BITCH CAN'T MAKE IT.
- OH, GOD.
- OH, NO, NO.
I'M ALONE AT A WEDDING
WITHOUT A DATE.
THANK GOD
YOU AND I CAN HANG OUT.
- I LIKE YOUR DESPERATION,
BUT I'M HAVING A HARD TIME
PICTURING A BIG PAYOFF
AT THE END OF THE EVENING.
- HOLLY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT
YOU WEREN'T COMING.
- OH, WELL,
I WAS SITTING AT HOME,
THINKING ABOUT HOW UNSELFISH
I WAS BEING BY NOT COMING,
WHEN I REALIZED,
HOW SELFISH OF ME NOT TO COME.
I MEAN, THEY'RE ALL
GONNA BE THINKING,
"WHERE'S HOLLY?
WHY ISN'T SHE HERE?"
AND THE LAST THING
I WANT TO DO
IS MAKE THIS WEDDING
ABOUT ME.
- MM.
OF COURSE.
- MM-HMM.
OH, THERE THEY ARE,
THE HAPPY COUPLE.
- YEAH, THEY DO LOOK HAPPY,
DON'T THEY?
- MM.
THAT COULD'VE BEEN ME.
BUT IT'S NOT,
AND, FORTUNATELY,
I'VE MOVED ON.
- HOLLY--
- I SAID I'VE MOVED ON.
- HOLLY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M JUST TAKING A PICTURE
WITH THE GROOM.
- HOLLY, MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE COME.
YOU'RE CLEARLY
HAVING SOME REGRETS
ABOUT BREAKING UP
WITH PAUL.
- WHAT? THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'M FINE.
- OKAY, GOOD.
- I GOTTA GO
MEET THE BRIDE.
- WAIT.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
BAD IDEA.
YOU CAN'T.
- NO, I HAVE TO.
SEE, I'VE JUST REALIZED,
I R.S.V.P.'D NO,
AND IF SHE WALKS DOWN THE AISLE
AND SEES ME,
SHE'LL GET SO DISTRACTED,
SHE WON'T EVEN
HEAR HER VOWS.
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA
LET THAT HAPPEN,
'CAUSE THIS WEDDING'S
NOT ABOUT ME.
- [sighs]
KEEP 'EM COMING.
- LOVELY WEDDING.
- WHAT'S SO DAMN LOVELY
ABOUT IT?
I'M SO SICK
OF BEING A BRIDESMAID.
I MEAN, WHEN'S IT GONNA
BE MY TURN?
WHEN IS IT--I'LL TELL YOU WHEN.
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN.
NEVER.
I'M SORRY, SORRY.
I DIDN'T--
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO SOUND SO DESPERATE.
- ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
HASKELL LUTZ.
- HELLO.
- HI.
- [chuckles]
HOW'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
IN THE ROOM?
- [sneezes]
NOT SO GOOD.
I HAVE
THE WORLD'S WORST COLD.
OH.
SAMANTHA.
- PHIL.
- NICE TO MEET YOU, PHIL,
BUT I THINK I NEED
TO GO HOME AND REST.
- OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S THE WORST THING
YOU CAN DO.
I MEAN,
YOU KNOW THE OLD SAYING.
"WALK OFF A COLD,
PARTY ON WITH A FEVER."
- YOU THINK SO?
- LET THE HEALING BEGIN.
- OKAY.
- I KNOW
I'M ALREADY FEELING BETTER.
- HEY, EDEN,
CAN I GET YOU ANOTHER DRINK?
- HUH?
- A DRINK?
- OH, YEAH.
SURE.
- YEAH.
- WOW, WHO'S THAT GIRL
THAT PHIL'S WITH?
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
- GORGEOUS?
YOU THINK SHE'S GORGEOUS?
THAT'S NOT GORGEOUS.
I KNOW GORGEOUS.
- OKAY.
UH, SORRY.
I JUST THOUGHT
SHE WAS KIND OF PRETTY.
- OF COURSE YOU DID.
ANYONE LOOKS PRETTY
IF YOU'RE ALONE AT A WEDDING,
STUART.
- OH--
[knocking at door]
- HELLO?
LAUREN?
ANYONE HERE?
[chuckles delightedly]
AAH, AAH.
OH.
HEY.
OH, ALL THE WAY
FROM HAWAII.
I DO.
[clears throat]
OH, I DO.
[gasps]
OH, CRAP.
HI, PAUL.
- I MUST ADMIT,
I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHAT YOU'D LOOK LIKE
AS A BRIDE.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- REALLY?
- REALLY.
[knock at door]
- PAUL?
UH, WE'RE READY FOR YOUR PICTURE
WITH THE FAMILY.
- OKAY.
- WELL, MY FATHER
WAS ALWAYS WORKING,
AND MY MOTHER
SPENT ALL HER TIME
WITH MY SISTER
AT HER BEAUTY PAGEANTS.
LITTLE MISS TIPPY-TOES.
- YES.
BUT YOU HAD THE REAL TALENT,
THE REAL BRAINS.
YOUR MOTHER JUST
COULDN'T SEE IT.
- NO.
NO, SHE DIDN'T SEE IT AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, BOYFRIENDS WOULD
COME OVER TO MY HOUSE,
AND GUESS WHO
THEY WERE INTERESTED IN.
- YOUR SISTER?
- NO, MY MOTHER.
- OH.
IT WAS YOU THEY SHOULD HAVE
BEEN LOOKING AT,
A BEAUTY THAT TOOK
A MORE DISCERNING EYE TO SEE.
- AWW.
HASKELL, YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY.
- WELL, I'M JUST SPEAKING
FROM MY HEART.
UH, COULD YOU EXCUSE ME
FOR A MOMENT?
- SURE.
- THANK YOU.
[grunting]
THANK YOU.
LOVELY WEDDING.
TRY THE PRAWNS.
- STUART, STUART, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BELIEVE WHAT HAPPENED.
- OH, WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED WITH THE BRIDE?
- OH, SHE WASN'T THERE.
- AND YET THAT CRAZY LOOK IN
YOUR EYE TELLS ME THERE'S MORE.
- SO I'M IN THE BRIDAL SUITE,
WEARING THE VEIL,
HOLDING THE BOUQUET,
AND THEN
SOMETHING WEIRD HAPPENED.
- WHAT COULD BE WEIRDER
THAN THAT?
- PAUL CAME IN
AND KISSED ME.
- OKAY, YOU WIN.
WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU DOING
KISSING THE GROOM
BEFORE HIS WEDDING?
- HE KISSED ME.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT THE BEST PART IS?
- THERE'S A BEST PART?
- I FELT NOTHING.
SO NOW I'M SURE
I DON'T WANT TO MARRY PAUL.
IT WAS JUST WEDDING FEVER.
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
BUT WHAT ABOUT PAUL?
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE'S OBVIOUSLY
STILL IN LOVE WITH ME.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I'VE DESTROYED THIS WEDDING.
[gasps]
I'M LIKE A GORGEOUS,
SEXY WRECKING BALL.
- [sighs]
YOU BETTER GO
SET PAUL STRAIGHT.
- YEAH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
SUDDENLY, THE WEDDING'S
ALL ABOUT ME.
HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
- [laughs loudly]
- HEY, UH, WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME CHAMPAGNE?
- WHY NOT?
- OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
OH, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TAKE THIS ONE.
NO, NO, MAYBE--
[stammering]
EDEN.
I DIDN'T SEE YOU OVER HERE.
- WHO IS YOUR FRIEND?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
EDEN, SAY HI TO SAMANTHA.
SAMANTHA, THIS IS EDEN,
AND HER DATE, BRAD.
- NO, BRETT.
- BRETT, THAT'S RIGHT.
BRETT. BRETT.
- SO, UH,
NICE WEDDING, HUH?
- YEAH, IT IS WHEN YOU'RE, UH,
WITH THE RIGHT PERSON.
- YEAH.
I COMPLETELY AGREE.
OOH.
- WELL, THIS WOMAN HERE
HAS GOT IT ALL, OKAY?
- [coughs]
- WELL, NOT AS MUCH
AS THIS GUY.
[growls playfully]
- OH, REALLY?
- MM.
- OH.
- [sneezes]
- OH!
I'MA KEEP IT REAL
WITH YOU, GIRL,
THAT'S JUST NASTY.
- I KNOW.
I BETTER GO.
IT WAS NICE
MEETING YOU, PHIL.
- "MEETING YOU"?
SHE WASN'T EVEN YOUR DATE.
- HEY, EDEN,
I BETTER GO, TOO.
I GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE VALET STATION.
SORRY.
- VALET STATION?
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE BRINGING A DATE,
AND SO I PANICKED
LAST MINUTE,
AND I PULLED BRETT
OUT OF A MOVING PRIUS.
- WHAT ARE WE DOING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE ACTING LIKE PEOPLE
WHO ARE MORE THAN FRIENDS.
- AND WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO DO ABOUT IT?
- WELL, I-I--
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO ABOUT IT?
- WELL, I'M WILLING
TO GIVE IT A TRY IF YOU ARE.
- REALLY?
- YEAH, REALLY.
- WELL, I'M UP FOR THAT.
- I WOULD LOVE
TO KISS YOU RIGHT NOW.
TO BE KISSED RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH.
- BUT WE CANNOT.
- RIGHT.
RIGHT.
- NOT IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
- YEAH.
YEP.
WAIT FOR THE RIGHT MOMENT
TO TELL HOLLY AND THE GUYS.
- YES.
- RIGHT.
- NEAT WEDDING, HUH?
- GREAT WEDDING.
LET'S GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- I ALMOST DIDN'T
COME TODAY.
- BUT YOU THOUGHT
THAT FATE MIGHT STEP IN
AND YOU WOULD
MEET A MAN--
MR. GOOD ENOUGH.
- OH, YOU KNOW ME SO WELL.
I'VE GOT
A CRAZY IDEA, HASKELL.
- I LIKE IT ALREADY.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE BLOW OFF THIS WEDDING,
GO UPSTAIRS TO MY ROOM,
AND, I DON'T KNOW,
YOU MAKE MY LIFE PERFECT
FOR ONE NIGHT?
- YES.
YES, YES.
BUT FIRST, JUST ONE THING.
[shouts]
- WHY DO I EVEN
SHOW UP TO THESE THINGS?
- LAUREN, HAVE YOU
GOT A MINUTE?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I REALLY NEED TO TELL YOU.
- PAUL, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO SEE THE BRIDE
BEFORE THE WEDDING.
- I'M SORRY.
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN
TO UPSET YOU.
- WELL, YOU DID.
AND NOW IT'S TOO LATE.
- OH, MY GOD.
I'M TOO LATE.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- I'M PAUL'S EX-LOVER, HOLLY.
- I THOUGHT
YOU WEREN'T COMING.
- OH, WELL, YES,
BUT THAT WOULD BE SELFISH,
AND IT'S YOUR DAY,
YOUR SPECIAL DAY.
SO LET ME PUT YOU AT EASE.
WHEN PAUL KISSED ME,
IT MEANT NOTHING.
- YOU KISSED HER?
- YOU DIDN'T TELL HER?
- NOPE.
- OH.
LOOK, IT WASN'T
PAUL'S FAULT.
I MEAN, HE CAME IN,
SAW ME WEARING YOUR VEIL--
- WHY WERE YOU
WEARING MY VEIL?
- OH, LET'S NOT
GET BOGGED DOWN IN DETAILS.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS,
THIS WEDDING MUST GO ON,
BECAUSE, PAUL,
YOU AND I WILL NEVER BE.
- PAUL?
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
- LAUREN, IT'S TRUE.
I DID KISS HOLLY.
- HE COULDN'T HELP HIMSELF.
- [shrieks]
- AND I FELT NOTHING.
- NOTHING?
- NOTHING.
- BUT YOU STILL
KISSED ANOTHER WOMAN
ON OUR WEDDING DAY.
- LAUREN, I'LL ADMIT THAT THERE
WAS A TEENY, TINY PART OF ME
THAT WAS WONDERING IF I STILL
HAD ANY FEELINGS FOR HOLLY.
KISSING HER WAS LIKE
KISSING MY 90-YEAR-OLD AUNT.
- OH, COME ON.
- AND NOW I'M MORE CERTAIN
THAN EVER
THAT YOU'RE THE ONE I WANT TO
SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH.
- OH, PAUL.
- HOLLY...
- OH.
- THANK YOU.
THIS IS THE GREATEST GIFT
YOU COULD HAVE GIVEN US--
THE KNOWLEDGE THAT YOU MEAN
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO ME.
- IT WAS BETWEEN THAT
AND A BREAD MAKER.
- COME ON, SWEETHEART.
LET'S GO GET MARRIED.
- THERE YOU GO.
[sighs heavily]
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- WELL, LET'S JUST SAY,
STUART,
THANKS TO ME,
A MARRIAGE WAS SAVED.
THANK GOD I HELD BACK
ON THAT KISS.
- HOLLY, DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT IF I EVER
GET MARRIED AGAIN,
I'D REALLY LIKE IT
IF YOU STAYED HOME.
- HEY, STUART,
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
DO YOU EVER THINK
I'M GONNA MEET A GUY
I LOVE ENOUGH TO MARRY?
- YES, I DO.
THE TRICK WILL BE FINDING
A GUY WHO DESERVES YOU.
- THANKS, STUART.
- OUT OF MY WAY!
OUT OF MY WAY!
MY SKIN IS ON FIRE!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, MY GOD.
- E-EDEN?
PHIL?
- HI, HI.
- LOOK WHO I BUMPED INTO.