[ UKULELE PLAYS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> ♪ OOH, OO-OO-OOH
♪ OO-OO-OOH, OO-OO-OOH
♪ WHEN YOU'RE IN LOVE, SO IN
LOVE ♪
♪ YOU JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S
ABOUT ♪
♪ OOH, OO-OO-OOH
♪ WHEN YOU'RE IN LOVE, SO IN
LOVE ♪
[ REGGAE MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> ♪ WHY MUST I BE SO IN LOVE?
>> ♪ SHOO-DOOP, SHOOBY-DOO
>> ♪ MY HEART SKIPS A BEAT EVERY
TIME SHE COME AROUND ♪
♪ YEAH
>> ♪ SHOO-DOOP, SHOOBY-DOO
>> ♪ SHE GIVES ME HEEBIE-JEEBIES
EVERY TIME SHE WALKS ON BY ♪
♪ I JUST CAN'T CONTROL MY
FEELINGS ♪
♪ EVERY TIME OUR EYES MEET
♪ YEAH
>> ♪ SHOO-DOOP, SHOOBY
♪ SHOO-DOOP, SHOOBY-DOO
>> HO, RALSTO.
>> ♪ SHOO-DOOP, SHOOBY
♪ SHOO-DOOP, SHOOBY-DOO
♪ OO-OOH, OO-OO-OOH
♪ OO-OO-OOH, OO-OO-OOH
>> HELLO.
>> HO. WHAT'S UP?
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> ♪ OO-OOH, OO-OO-OOH
>> THANK YOU, SWEETIE.
IS THAT ENOUGH TOAST FOR YOU?
>> MM.
>> [ RETCHING ]
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
[ WATER RUNNING ]
[ WATER SHUTS OFF ]
[ SLURPS ]
[ SETS DOWN MUG ]
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> AUSTIN?
>> MM?
>> I THINK WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
I'M PREGNANT.
>> WHAT?
>> SERIOUSLY.
I JUST THREW UP.
[ SNIFFLES ]
AND IT'S BEEN LIKE THIS FOR
ALMOST A WEEK.
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
>> MAYBE YOU'RE JUST SICK.
IT'S NOTHING TO FREAK OUT ABOUT.
>> I'M NOT FREAKING OUT.
>> YEAH, BUT...
[ SIGHS ]
I MEAN, HOW CAN YOU KNOW FOR
SURE WITHOUT --
>> BECAUSE.
IT'S MY BODY, AND I KNOW WHAT IT
FEELS LIKE.
REMEMBER?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
>> I'M OFF TO WORK, THEN.
DON'T FORGET TO TAKE THE RUBBISH
OUT, OKAY?
YOU OKAY, SWEETIE?
>> [ SIGHS ] YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS FIGHTING AGAIN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW HOW SHE GETS.
>> SO, YOU'RE GOING TO WORK
TODAY?
>> YEP.
>> 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, TODAY IS
THE LAST DAY TO FILL OUT
APPLICATIONS AT THE OFFICE.
>> MOM.
I ALREADY HAVE A JOB.
>> I KNOW, SWEETIE, BUT YOU
CAN'T HANG OUT AT THE SKATE SHOP
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
>> IT'S BETTER THAN NOTHING.
>> "NOTHING."
OH, NOTHING IS WHAT YOUR DAD
DID, AND LOOK WHERE THAT LEFT
US.
>> OH, MOM.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS LATER?
PLEASE?
>> FINE.
HONEY, DON'T FORGET TO FINISH
YOUR TEA, OKAY?
WE   ARGONNA TALK ABOUT IT.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> [ SLURPS ]
[ SETS DOWN MUG ]
>> HEY.
I'M SORRY.
>> WHAT DID YOU JUST TELL YOUR
MOM, AUSTIN?
>> WHAT?
OH...NO.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT WORK.
SERIOUSLY.
>> [ SIGHS ]
I DON'T WANT TO GO THROUGH THIS
AGAIN.
PROMISE ME YOU WON'T LEAVE ME
LIKE HIMO DID.
>> I WON'T.
I PROMISE.
[ SMOOCHES ]
>> ♪ WHOA, NOW, NOW, NOW
♪ COME HERE CLOSER, THEN
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO
DO?
I MEAN, HOW ARE WE GONNA TAKE
CARE OF THIS?
>> LAST TIME, I HAD TO GO TO THE
CLINIC AND...
I SHOULD HAVE SEEN THE SIGNS.
>> I CAN GET IT TOGETHER.
NO WORRIES, OKAY?
[ BRAKES SQUEALING ]
>> SHIT.
>> ♪ SLOWLY RUB, OH
♪ GIVE ME THE RIDE
>> I'LL CALL YOU LATER, OKAY?
>> ♪ ANYTHING YOU WANT ME DO,
I'LL ABIDE ♪
♪ ALL YOUR SECRETS I WILL
CONFIDE ♪
♪ ONLY YOU AND ME WILL KNOW THE
TIME ♪
>> HO.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> HEY, ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO
KAILUA?
>> NO.
>> NAH.
WHY? YOU NEED A RIDE?
>> SHOOTS.
>> HEY, THESE CANS AIN'T GONNA
LOAD THEMSELVES, BRAH.
COME ON. HURRY UP.
>> OH.
NO, NO, NO.
PUT IT IN THE WAGON.
THE RANGER'S BUST.
>> HURRY UP. HURRY UP.
>> HURRY UP. I'M HUNGRY.
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO. GRAB THE REST OF THEM.
HURRY UP.
AFTER THAT, WE GO.
>> ♪ COME, ME SEE YOUR PASSION
BURNING UP LIKE THE FLAMES ♪
♪ AND ME FEEL LIKE AN ANIMAL,
YOU WANT ME TAME ♪
♪ OH, GIVE ME THE RIDE, GIVE ME
THE MORNING RIDE ♪
♪ ANYTHING YOU WANT ME DO, I'LL
ABIDE ♪
♪ ALL YOUR SECRETS I WILL
CONFIDE ♪
♪ ONLY YOU AND ME WILL KNOW THE
TIME ♪
[ BANGING, RATTLING ]
>> COME ON.
HO.
>> HEY, WE GO GRIND.
>> SHOOTS.
>> THANKS. MANY THANKS.
>> THANK YOU. OOH.
>> OH.
OVER EASY -- JUST HOW I LIKE
THEM.
>> OH.
THAT'S ALL YOU GET?
>> WANT A SAMPLE?
>> NO, I'M GOOD.
>> OH.
HEY, WE'LL DUMP ROAD AFTER THIS.
THE GUY SAYS HE'S SEEN A VAN.
BY DA KINE OVER THERE.
>> OH, SHOOTS.
MAYBE FIND PARTS FOR THE RANGER,
TOO, HUH?
>> HEY.
WHAT -- ARE YOU SICK OR WHAT?
>> THAT WASN'T YOU THROWING UP
THIS MORNING, HUH?
>> WHAT?
ALEA?
>> BRAH, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT CHICKS THROWING UP IN THE
MORNING, HUH?
[ SCOFFS ] NAH.
[ SIGHS ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
I TOLD YOU -- GOT TO WRAP IT UP.
>> SOMETIMES, BUT, YOU KNOW...
>> SOMETIMES, I KNOW YOU GET DA
KINE, TOO, BUT I MAKE SURE I USE
THE RHYTHM METHOD.
>> WHAT IS THAT -- THE RHYTHM
METHOD?
>> BRAH, YOU KNOW.
TURN ON THE RADIO, ROCK 'EM TO
THE RHYTHM.
>> SHUT UP. I'M SERIOUS.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> CHILL.
SERIOUSLY, WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
GET -- GET DA KINE, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT ALEA SAID.
>> SO, YOU'RE GONNA GET DA KINE?
YOU GOT MONEY?
>> SOME.
IT'S COOL.
I JUST GOT TO ASK ROB FOR MORE
HOURS.
>> SURE.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD.
[ MAN SPEAKING ON RADIO ]
>> WHAT SHOULD I GET?
>> TEAR UP DA KINE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HEY, MAKE IT FAST, HUH?
[ PATI'S "ISLAND GIRLS" PLAYS ]
>> WHY YOU GUYS ALWAYS GET BEERS
AT THE FISHING STORE?
>> OH, WELL, THEY GOT THE DEALS.
>> [ LAUGHING ]
OOH! OOH! OOH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> HO. THIS CHICK. COME ON.
>> ♪ AND THEN YOU LOOK AT ME
>> JUST TAKE THAT. JUST TAKE IT.
JUST TAKE IT.
>> ♪ ALL THE WHILE, NOWHERE
ELSE IN THE WORLD ♪
>> JUST MOVE!
JUST GIVE ME SOME SPACE! PLEASE!
>> ♪ WHEN THE SKY IS CLEAR AND
THE GRASS IS GREEN ♪
♪ ISLAND GIRLS, YOU ARE A MAN'S
BEST DREAM ♪
>> ♪ ISLAND GIRLS
>> HEY, I TOLD YOU, "HURRY UP."
DON'T MAKE THE BOY LATE.
>> RELAX.
>> IN THE EARLY 19th CENTURY,
THE AMERICAN WHALING FLEETS
BEGAN WINTERING IN HAWAII, AND
THE ISLANDS WERE VISITED WITH
MOUNTING FREQUENCY BY EXPLORERS,
TRADERS, AND ADVENTURERS.
THIS INCLUDED
CAPTAIN GEORGE VANCOUVER, WHO
INTRODUCED LIVESTOCK TO THE
ISLANDS IN THE YEAR 1792.
AND BY 1820, THE FIRST OF THE
NEW ENGLAND MISSIONARIES HAD
ARRIVED.
BY THE MIDDLE OF THE CENTURY,
THERE WERE FRAME HOUSES,
HORSE-DRAWN VEHICLES, SCHOOLS,
CHURCHES, TAVERNS, AND
MERCANTILE ESTABLISHMENTS, A
WRITTEN LANGUAGE HAD BEEN
INTRODUCED, AS WELL AS
EUROPEAN AND AMERICAN SKILLS.
ALONG WITH THAT, THEY BROUGHT
THEIR RELIGIOUS BELIEFS.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
[ POP ]
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> DUDE, YOU'RE LATE.
>> ONLY 10 MINUTES!
>> TRY AN HOUR AND 40.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO OPEN.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
>> HO! HOWZIT?
>> [ SCOFFS ]
>> WHAT?
>> [ SIGHS ]
LOOK, I GOT TO MAKE SOME PHONE
CALLS.
YOU THINK YOU GOT THIS?
>> YEAH. NO WORRIES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND THERE'S SOME GIRLS IN THE
CHANGING ROOM, OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS FINDING EVERYTHING
OKAY?
>> YES.
CAN I GET DISCOUNT IF WE BUY 20?
>> UM, I THINK IF YOU BUY 30,
THERE'S A FREE GRIP, SO IT'S
LIKE 10% OFF.
>> [ SPEAKING IN JAPANESE ]
>> MM.
>> OKAY. WE BUY 30.
>> SHOOTS.
UM, YOU CAN PUT THEM OVER HERE
WHILE YOU LOOK.
[ BEEP ]
>> WHAT'S UP, RALSTO?
>> OH.
DUDE, YOU LOOK LIKE CRAP.
>> YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
I GOT FUCKING LEFT --
>> HI, SEAN.
>> HO, WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
I DIDN'T SEE YOU HERE.
>> YEAH, SHE'S PICKING UP
SOMETHING FOR THAT PARTY TONIGHT
IN KAHALU'U.
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT IT?
>> THE BLACK SQUARE PARTY,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> UH, THAT'LL BE $125.08.
>> HEY, COME ON, MAN.
HOOK HER UP.
>> UM...
>> DON'T WORRY.
JUST GIVE HER MY TEAM-RIDER
DISCOUNT.
SO, YOU NEED ME TO BUY YOU BEER?
>> YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
>> THAT'LL BE $78.53.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> OH, NO. IT'S COOL.
>> PRETTY COOL.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
>> THANKS.
>> BYE, SEAN.
>> BYE, GIRLS.
[ SIGHS ]
I NEED TO HOOK THAT UP.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> OKAY. THERE YOU GO.
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
[ BEEPING ]
>> SO WHAT, ROB? BONUS DAY?
SHE BOUGHT IT BEFORE NOON!
>> HEY, DID YOU JUST GIVE THEM A
DISCOUNT?
>> WHO?
OH, YEAH, FOR THE BOARDS.
UM, 30 DECKS AND A FREE GRIP.
RIGHT?
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> WHAT?
>> SEAN, GO GET ME A RED BULL.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
WERE YOU GONNA TELL ME ABOUT
THIS?
>> SEAN SAID I COULD GIVE HER
HIS DISCOUNT.
>> WELL, IS SEAN YOUR BOSS?
[ SIGHS ]
LOOK, AUSTIN, THIS ISN'T WORKING
OUT.
>> JUST BECAUSE I GAVE A
DISCOUNT?
>> COME ON.
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE WE TALKED
ABOUT THE DISCOUNTS?
AND THE LATENESS?
I DON'T THINK YOU'VE BEEN ON
TIME ONCE THIS WEEK.
>> I KNOW, BUT IT'S -- IT'S JUST
I HAVE SOME OTHER THINGS GOING
ON RIGHT NOW, AND I --
>> WELL, NOW YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
PLENTY OF TIME TO FIGURE THOSE
THINGS OUT.
AND I CAN FINALLY GET YOUR SHIT
OUT OF HERE.
>> SO YOU'RE FIRING ME?
>> YEAH.
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT TAKING IT
SERIOUSLY, AND SOONER OR LATER,
AUSTIN, YOU'RE GONNA NEED TO
LEARN THAT WORK IS WORK.
>> DOES THIS MEAN I CAN'T HANG
OUT HERE ANYMORE?
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> HEY, GIRL.
YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, IT'S JUST...MY STOMACH
FEELS ALL FUNKY.
>> FROM THE...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S EITHER THAT OR THE TEA
AUSTIN'S MOM GAVE ME.
IT WAS SO GROSS.
>> SHE DOESN'T KNOW, DOES SHE?
BUT...YOU TALKED TO AUSTIN,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> AND?
>> [ SIGHS ]
AND HE DOESN'T -- HE DOESN'T
WANT TO KEEP IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN GO THROUGH
THAT AGAIN.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU CAN ALWAYS KEEP IT.
>> MAYBE.
I JUST WISH I COULD TALK TO
AUSTIN INSTEAD OF BEING STUCK
HERE.
>> YOU WANT TO USE MY PHONE
AFTER LUNCH?
>> THANKS.
>> COME ON.
YOU KNOW, HAVING A BABY ISN'T
THE END OF THE WORLD.
[ WHEELS ROLLING ]
>> WHAT'S UP, SUZIE?
>> HEY, SEAN.
>> YOU NEED ME TO SEND THAT FOR
YOU?
>> UM --
>> NOT UNLESS YOU'RE GONNA SEND
IT HOME.
>> WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BARRY AND SAM MADE ME LATE.
>> LATE AGAIN?
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT MY
FAULT.
>> OH, NOT YOUR FAULT?
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW.
YOU KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE YOU'RE GONNA FILL OUT AN
APPLICATION.
>> OH, MOM, I TOLD YOU...
>> TOO BAD.
YOU HAVE NOW JOINED THE RANKS
OF THE UNEMPLOYED, SO IT APPEARS
TO ME YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
SIT.
>> HI, AUSTIN.
>> HERE YOU GO.
OH, YOU NEED A PEN.
>> UM, CAN I FILL THIS OUT
LATER?
>> NO, YOU NEED TO TAKE THIS
SERIOUSLY.
>> I KNOW, BUT SEAN IS WAITING,
AND --
>> OH, IS SEAN GONNA GET YOU A
JOB?
>> [ SIGHS ] NO, BUT...
>> YOU HAVE TO FILL THIS OUT,
AUSTIN.
>> I WILL. I PROMISE.
[ SMOOCHES ]
OKAY?
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> SHOVE OFF, DUDE.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
>> GIVE ME THE BABY.
GIVE ME THE BABY.
>> YOU GO GRAB THE BABY.
>> GIVE ME THE BABY.
>> LOOK AT HER.
YOU WANT THE BABY? FINE. HERE.
[ BABY CRYING ]
WANT TO PAY ME NOW, HUH?
YEAH. GRAB THE BABY.
MAKE HER STOP CRYING!
NOW YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL!
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
OKAY, ASSHOLE.
DON'T YOU FUCKING SLAM THE DOOR
AT ME!
GUESS WHAT HAPPENED.
THAT FUCKING ASSHOLE -- GOING
OUT TILL 5:00 A.M. IN THE
MORNING, LEFT ME ALL NIGHT LONG
WITH THE KID CRYING!
I DON'T GET ANY SLEEP AT ALL.
I'M SO TIRED AND SO EXHAUSTED.
YOU JUST PARTIED LAST NIGHT,
MAN.
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
THE WHOLE FRICKIN' ENTIRE
WEEK.
I WAS WITH THE KID ALL FRICKIN'
HE DIDN'T DO SHIT.
WEEK.
ALWAYS I HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING
HE DIDN'T DO SHIT.
LIKE I'M A SINGLE MOTHER.
ALWAYS I HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING
BUT HE DIDN'T DO SHIT.
LIKE I'M A SINGLE MOTHER.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
BUT HE DIDN'T DO SHIT.
I CAN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
I GOT TO DO FREAKING LAUNDRY.
I CAN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
I GOT TO COOK, I GOT TO CLEAN.
I GOT TO DO FREAKING LAUNDRY.
I GOT TO DO EVERYTHING EVERY
I GOT TO COOK, I GOT TO CLEAN.
SINGLE, FUCKING DAY.
I GOT TO DO EVERYTHING EVERY
I HAVE TO EVERYTHING ON MY OWN
SINGLE, FUCKING DAY.
LIKE YOU JUST FUCKING WON'T DO
I HAVE TO EVERYTHING ON MY OWN
SHIT!
LIKE YOU JUST FUCKING WON'T DO
>> DUDE, LAST NIGHT SUCKED.
SHIT!
>> WHY? WHAT HAPPENED?
>> DUDE, LAST NIGHT SUCKED.
>> I WENT OUT WITH NALU, JUST
>> WHY? WHAT HAPPENED?
DRINKING AND WATCHING HIS BACK.
>> I WENT OUT WITH NALU, JUST
>> WELL, HE HIT ANYTHING UP?
DRINKING AND WATCHING HIS BACK.
>> NOTHING GOOD.
>> WELL, HE HIT ANYTHING UP?
JUST A COUPLE LITTLE ONE-LINERS.
>> NOTHING GOOD.
AND THEN WE FOUND THIS OLD VAN
JUST A COUPLE LITTLE ONE-LINERS.
ON DUMP ROAD.
AND THEN WE FOUND THIS OLD VAN
>> OH, YOU DO THE WHOLE THING?
ON DUMP ROAD.
>> YEAH. IT TOOK FOREVER, MAN.
>> OH, YOU DO THE WHOLE THING?
I ENDED UP PASSING OUT ON THE
>> YEAH. IT TOOK FOREVER, MAN.
SIDE.
I ENDED UP PASSING OUT ON THE
>> FOR REAL?
SIDE.
>> THE FUCKER JUST LEFT ME
>> FOR REAL?
THERE, BRAH.
>> THE FUCKER JUST LEFT ME
>> [ LAUGHS ]
THERE, BRAH.
>> DUDE, THAT SUCKED.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> OH, AT LEAST YOU HAD A ROOF
>> DUDE, THAT SUCKED.
OVER YOUR HEAD.
>> OH, AT LEAST YOU HAD A ROOF
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
OVER YOUR HEAD.
>> YEAH, MAYBE I CAN MOVE IN
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
THERE.
>> YEAH, MAYBE I CAN MOVE IN
IT WOULD BE BETTER THAN PAYING
THERE.
THE RENT.
IT WOULD BE BETTER THAN PAYING
HELLO?
THE RENT.
OH, WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
HELLO?
YEAH, YEAH, WE'RE JUST CHILLING
OH, WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
AT THE BEACH.
YEAH, YEAH, WE'RE JUST CHILLING
HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
AT THE BEACH.
IT'S ALEA.
HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING AT THE
IT'S ALEA.
BEACH?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING AT THE
I JUST TALKED TO ROB, AND --
BEACH?
YEAH, WHATEVER.
I JUST TALKED TO ROB, AND --
I GUESS YOU DON'T SEEM TOO
YEAH, WHATEVER.
WORRIED ABOUT IT.
I GUESS YOU DON'T SEEM TOO
I DON'T KNOW.
WORRIED ABOUT IT.
I JUST -- I THINK MAYBE IT'S A
I DON'T KNOW.
SIGN.
I JUST -- I THINK MAYBE IT'S A
A SIGN THAT WE SHOULD KEEP IT.
SIGN.
NO. I'M SERIOUS.
A SIGN THAT WE SHOULD KEEP IT.
[ Chuckling ] WHAT?
NO. I'M SERIOUS.
I CAN'T --
[ Chuckling ] WHAT?
NO, IT'S MY BODY.
I CAN'T --
I THINK I HAVE THE RIGHT.
NO, IT'S MY BODY.
NO.
I THINK I HAVE THE RIGHT.
NO, I GET OUT OF HERE AT 2:30,
NO.
BUT I HAVE PRACTICE RIGHT AFTER.
NO, I GET OUT OF HERE AT 2:30,
[ SIGHS ]
BUT I HAVE PRACTICE RIGHT AFTER.
YEAH, FINE.
[ SIGHS ]
FINE. YEAH. WHATEVER.
YEAH, FINE.
>> SO, WHAT, HE'S AT THE BEACH?
FINE. YEAH. WHATEVER.
>> HE'S AT THE BEACH.
>> SO, WHAT, HE'S AT THE BEACH?
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> HE'S AT THE BEACH.
>> WHAT, SHE'S PISSED YOU GOT
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
FIRED?
>> WHAT, SHE'S PISSED YOU GOT
>> DUDE, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
FIRED?
>> IT'S NOT LIKE YOU GUYS ARE
>> DUDE, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
MARRIED.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE YOU GUYS ARE
>> HEY, I GOT TO CALL NALU.
MARRIED.
I CAN?
>> HEY, I GOT TO CALL NALU.
>> JUST PICKING UP BUSINESS, YOU
I CAN?
KNOW?
>> JUST PICKING UP BUSINESS, YOU
TRYING TO GET SOME MORE OF THAT
KNOW?
SHIT, BUT, UH...
TRYING TO GET SOME MORE OF THAT
>> YEAH?
SHIT, BUT, UH...
>> JUST THROW ME SOME MORE TIME,
>> YEAH?
CUZ.
>> JUST THROW ME SOME MORE TIME,
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
CUZ.
>> YEAH, ONE MORE TIME, HUH?
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID THE LAST
>> YEAH, ONE MORE TIME, HUH?
TIME.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID THE LAST
>> COME ON, MIKE.
TIME.
>> MIKE? THAT'S "VEGAS MIKE."
>> COME ON, MIKE.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> MIKE? THAT'S "VEGAS MIKE."
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> WHAT, YOU FUCKER?
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
OH, WHAT'S UP, RALSTO, WHAT?
>> WHAT, YOU FUCKER?
HOW'S SEAN FEELING?
OH, WHAT'S UP, RALSTO, WHAT?
WHAT?
HOW'S SEAN FEELING?
YEAH, BRAH, I KNOW, BUT...
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, DUDE, CAN WE TALK
YEAH, BRAH, I KNOW, BUT...
ABOUT THIS LATER?
YOU KNOW, DUDE, CAN WE TALK
I STAY IN TOWN.
ABOUT THIS LATER?
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GET RICHARD
I STAY IN TOWN.
LATER AT DA KINE, BUT, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GET RICHARD
YEAH, SHOOTS, OKAY.
LATER AT DA KINE, BUT, YEAH.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
YEAH, SHOOTS, OKAY.
>> FRICK!
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
HERE.
>> FRICK!
[ SIGHS ]
HERE.
I GOT TO GET TO THE HIGH SCHOOL.
[ SIGHS ]
>> NO, FUCK THAT, DUDE. COME ON.
I GOT TO GET TO THE HIGH SCHOOL.
LET'S GO TO THE SKATE PARK.
>> NO, FUCK THAT, DUDE. COME ON.
YOU CAN GET A RIDE FROM THERE.
LET'S GO TO THE SKATE PARK.
LET'S GO. GRAB YOUR SHIT.
HURRY UP!
>> HEY. HI!
>> HEY.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD. YOU?
>> GOOD.
HEY, YOU GUYS REMEMBER ALEA,
RIGHT?
>> HOW'S KANA DOING?
>> OH, HE'S GETTING SO BIG.
AND HE CRAWLS AROUND ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
>> OH, WE NEED HIM TO COME TO
THE BEACH AGAIN.
>> I KNOW.
WE GOT TO GET YOU IN THE WATER,
TOO.
IT FEELS SO GOOD WHEN YOU'RE ALL
HAPAI.
NO MORE PAIN IN THE BACK.
>> MAYBE THEN HE'D STOP KICKING
SO MUCH, ALL THE TIME, WRESTLING
IN THERE.
[ GIGGLES ] SEE?
HE KNOWS WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
HIM.
>> OH, MY GOD.
ALEA, YOU GOT TO FEEL THIS.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
>> WHAT'S UP, RALSTO?
>> HO, CHRISTIAN.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
>> HEY, UH, DO YOU WANT TO BUY A
BOARD?
>> YEAH.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
>> OH.
THAT'S PRETTY SICK.
SO, WHAT, $10?
>> UM, I WAS THINKING, LIKE,
$20.
>> [ Sighing ] OH, MAN.
I'M ON A BUDGET, YOU KNOW?
>> $15?
>> UH, $10's REALLY ALL I GOT.
>> HOW ABOUT $10 AND A RIDE TO
THE HIGH SCHOOL?
>> NAH, I GOT PICK UP LITTLE
EMMA IN LIKE 20 MINUTES.
>> FINE. $10.
>> SICK.
>> AND I CAN USE YOUR PHONE?
>> YEAH, BUT, UH, NO
900-NUMBERS, ALL RIGHT?
>> SO, YOU BOYS DOWN FOR A GAME
OF SKATE?
>> YEAH. DO I GET TO GO FIRST?
>> SHOOTS.
>> NAH. I GOT TO FIND A RIDE.
>> CATCH UP.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> YOU ALMOST DONE WITH THAT?
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
BRO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PUT THEM OVER THERE.
>> DUMMY.
[ RINGING STOPS ]
>> YOU DIDN'T EVEN GET A LETTER?
>> NOPE.
HEY, ANY LUCK?
>> DUDE, WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST
SKATE THERE?
>> WHAT ABOUT THIS?
>> FUCK IT, DUDE.
I'LL SELL THEM FOR YOU.
>> YEAH?
>> I GET HALF, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, WHATEVER, MAN.
JUST...TRY TO GET AS MUCH AS YOU
CAN, OKAY?
>> SHOOTS.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT HERE.
HEY.
COUPLE DECKS, NEW SHOES.
>> HEY, ALEA!
ALEA, GIRL.
CAN YOU COME TO THE OFFICE WITH
ME?
>> I'M NOT IN TROUBLE, AM I?
>> NO, NO.
SOMEONE'S HERE TO SEE YOU.
LET'S GO.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> HI.
HI, HONEY. HI.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
I, UM...
[ CHUCKLES ]
HONEY.
I AM SO SORRY ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMETIMES --
>> SOMETIMES?
MOM, DO YOU SEE THE WAY HE LOOKS
AT ME?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
I -- SHUT UP.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> AND NOW YOU DEFEND HIM.
>> I KICKED HIM OUT AFTER YOU
LEFT LAST NIGHT, AND I'M NOT
GONNA SEE HIM ANYMORE.
>> SURE, MOM.
>> HONEY. HONEY.
THIS TIME I AM SERIOUS.
>> THIS TIME? PLEASE.
>> WAIT. WAIT.
I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S SO PRETTY.
YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
I THINK THE RECEIPT'S IN THE
BAG, AND YOU COULD RETURN IT IF
YOU WANT.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT, MOM?
>> I WANT YOU TO COME HOME.
I-I MISS YOU.
SORRY.
>> I GOT TO GO TO CLASS.
>> OKAY. OKAY.
WELL, WILL YOU CALL ME AT LEAST?
YOUR DRESS!
HONEY, DON'T FORGET YOUR DRESS.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> STILL NEED A RIDE?
>> DUDE, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW
HELLISH THAT WAS.
>> OH, BRAH, YOU SHOULD HAVE
WAITED.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> I WENT AND STOPPED BY THE
PARK.
>> DID NOT.
>> NAH, FOR REALS.
♪ 'CAUSE I GOT THE REAL THING
♪ THE REAL THING
♪ NATURALLY, PHYSICALLY
♪ I WANT A NIGHTTIME LOVER
♪ NOT A LIFETIME LOVER
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
BRAH!
>> HEY, SO YOU GET MONEY, OR
WHAT?
>> NAH, SOON, CUZ. NO WORRIES.
>> DUDE, I'M SERIOUS.
>> NO, BRAH. ME TOO.
I JUST GOT TO TAKE CARE OF A FEW
THINGS FIRST, OKAY?
>> NO, IT'S NOT OKAY.
IF I DON'T GET THE MONEY SOON,
ALEA'S GONNA THINK IT'S ANOTHER
SIGN.
>> A SIGN FOR WHAT?
>> FOR KEEPING THE BABY.
>> BRAH!
ARE YOU STUPID?
>> COME ON, NALU, DUDE.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
>> HOW MUCH YOU NEED?
>> LIKE $400.
>> OH, WHAT, ROB NEVER PAY YOU?
>> YEAH.
AND I SOLD A DECK AND SOME
SHOES, BUT I ONLY GET LIKE $200.
>> OH, THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> ENOUGH FOR WHAT?
>> BRAH, IF YOU GIVE ME $200, I
CAN GET YOU AT LEAST $600 BY THE
END OF THE DAY.
>> DUDE, THERE'S NO WAY I'M
GIVING YOU MORE MONEY.
>> OH, FINE, THEN, RIGHT.
YOU CAN COME AND WAIT, BRAH.
BUT I KNOW YOU NEVER LIKE TO
BET.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> ABOUT A COCKFIGHT, CUZ.
BRAH, MY BROTHER GAVE ME A SURE
THING.
FOR REALS.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
>> HEY, UH, DON'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT DA KINE, OKAY?
>> OH, WHO AM I GONNA TELL?
BRAH.
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING AFTER
PRACTICE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
AUSTIN SAID HE MIGHT COME.
>> OH.
>> THERE HE IS.
>> HO, I THOUGHT HE WAS GOOD.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
>> HO, WHAT'S UP, GIRLS?
GOT SOME HOT PLANS FOR TONIGHT?
>> YOU HEARD BLACK SQUARE'S
PLAYING, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> WHO HASN'T?
>> HO, I DIDN'T EVEN SEE YOU
GUYS HERE.
>> WE WERE JUST WATCHING YOU.
>> OH, HOW CUTE.
HEY, IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND
ABOUT DA KINE, BRAH...
NICE DAY, CUZ.
>> WHY DO YOU HANG OUT WITH HIM?
OKAY.
I'M GONNA GO CHANGE FOR
PRACTICE.
I'LL LEAVE YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS
ALONE.
>> HEY, I'LL MEET YOU IN THE
LOCKER ROOM, OKAY?
>> OKAY, THEN.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
BETTER NOW THAT YOU'RE HERE.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT WOULDN'T BE
THE END OF THE WORLD IF WE HAD A
BABY.
>> YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
>> I AM.
>> YOU'RE NOT READY FOR THIS.
TRUST ME.
>> ME?
>> I MEAN "US."
WE'RE NOT READY FOR THIS.
>> OH, OKAY, SO -- SO NOW IT'S
US?
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> IT WOULDN'T -- IT WOULDN'T BE
THAT BAD.
YOU COULD GET A SECOND JOB WHILE
I STAY IN SCHOOL, AND I'M SURE
IF YOU TALK TO YOUR MOM, SHE'D
BE --
>> NOW YOU WANT ME TO TELL MY
MOM?
>> WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
TELL HER EVENTUALLY.
>> [ CLEARS THROAT ]
LOOK, NOT IF WE GET DA KINE,
OKAY?
ROB GAVE ME MY LAST CHECK.
HEY.
ROB GAVE ME MY LAST CHECK, AND
NALU SAID HE CAN PAY ME BACK.
WE CAN HANDLE THIS.
>> YOU TOLD NALU?
>> NO.
SERIOUS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE ME ONE CHANCE.
PLEASE.
>> FINE, BUT IF NALU DOESN'T PAY
YOU BACK, WE'RE GONNA BE
THINKING ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE,
OKAY?
I GOT TO GO TO PRACTICE.
WE'RE HANGING OUT LATER, RIGHT?
>> OF COURSE.
HO, WHERE YOU STAY?
SHOOTS. SHOOTS.
HEY, YOU THINK I CAN GET ONE
RIDE?
AT THE HIGH SCHOOL.
COME ON, MAN. YOU OWE ME.
FOR MAKING ME LATE.
I GOT FIRED.
YEAH, FOR REAL.
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN YOU GET HERE.
WHAT?
FINE.
I'LL MEET YOU BY THE BRIDGE.
OKAY.
[ SIGHS ]
>> HO, RALSTO!
>> HO.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> WHAT'S UP?
LET'S GO.
>> [ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> HO, CUZ.
YOU KNOW HOW FAR THAT IS?
>> COME ON, MAN.
IF YOU DIDN'T MAKE ME LATE
TODAY...
>> HEY!
>> ...I WOULDN'T HAVE...
>> YOU NEVER WOULD HAVE BEEN
FIRED?
>> YEAH.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
>> WHERE YOU GONNA MEET UP?
>> YOU KNOW WHERE ALL THE
CHICKENS STAY?
>> BRAH, LOSE MONEY, CUZ.
>> YOU REALLY THINK YOU'RE GONNA
WIN?
>> NALU SAYS WE'RE A SURE THING.
>> NEVER GO WITH A SURE THING,
CUZ.
>> YOU COULD COME WORK WITH US,
HUH, BARRY?
>> YEAH. COME WORK WITH US.
>> YOU'RE IN THE RUBBISH ALL
DAY.
SHE'D PROBABLY HAVE THE BABY
BEFORE I EVER GOT ENOUGH MONEY.
>> WHAT, YOU THINK YOU'RE BETTER
THAN US?
>> NO. [ SIGHS ]
NO, NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
I-I JUST...
>> YOU JUST WHAT?
YOU THINK WE'RE STUPID?
LIKE WE'RE ONLY GOOD ENOUGH TO
DRIVE YOU AROUND?
[ HORN HONKS ]
FUCK YOU, THEN.
>> I WONDER WHERE HE WENT.
>> WAS HE GONNA WAIT FOR YOU?
WELL, HEY, YOU WANT TO GO TO THE
MALL?
>> I GUESS.
>> I GOT TO MEET DUSTIN.
[ Singsong voice ] IT'S PAYDAY.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> HEY, HEY, STOP!
>> NOW WHAT?
>> YOU GUYS STILL LOOKING FOR A
RANGER?
>> OOH, YEAH.
>> IT'S DA KINE, RIGHT?
>> IT'S DA KINE, BUT I DON'T
KNOW IF IT'S DEAD DA KINE OR
WHAT.
>> TRY FEEL THE HOOD.
>> IT'S COLD, BRAH.
>> POP 'EM.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
GOT EVERYTHING WE NEED.
>> GEEZ.
[ RATCHETING ]
>> PASS THAT 5/8th.
COME ON, BABY. YEAH.
>> WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING
TO MY TRUCK?!
>> HO.
OH, WE THOUGHT DA KINE HAD GOT
LEFT HERE.
>> WHAT?
>> HEY.
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU SAYING,
MAN?
>> HEY, IT'S COOL, MAN.
WE -- WE THOUGHT THE TRUCK WAS
ABANDONED.
>> YOU'RE STRIPPING MY TRUCK.
>> IT'S COOL.
>> IT'S PRETTY FUCKING FAR FROM
BEING COOL, MAN!
[ SIREN CHIRPS ]
>> FUCK.
>> HEY, LET ME HANDLE THIS.
HO.
>> WHAT, THIS YOUR CAR?
>> YEP.
>> WHERE'D YOU GET DA KINE
BOTTLES IN THE BACK?
YOUSE DRINKING?
>> WE WERE TAKING TO DA KINE FOR
GOOD MONEY.
>> AND THE TRUCK?
WHAT, YOU STRIP THEM?
>> TOO MANY BREAKDOWNS.
I WAS HELPING THE GUY FIX THEM.
>> THIS YOUR TRUCK?
>> YEAH. IT'S MINE.
>> HE FIX THEM FOR YOU?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, DARN THING KEEPS BREAKING
DOWN ON ME.
>> YOU GOT A SAFETY CHECK?
>> OH, IT'S RIGHT...THERE ON THE
BUMPER.
>> HOW LONG THIS GONNA TAKE?
>> ALMOST DONE.
>> OKAY, THEN.
FINISH HIM UP AND MOVE OUT OF
HERE.
>> SHOOTS.
>> JUST LIKE WE FOUND THEM.
>> SO, WE COOL, BRAH?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
MAN, I THOUGHT WE WERE FUCKED,
MAN.
HEY, YOU WANT SOME?
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> SHROOMS.
>> [ SNIFFS ]
NAH.
WE'LL STICK TO THE BEERS.
>> COOL. THAT'S COOL.
HEY, YOU GUYS REALLY TURN THOSE
CANS, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> HUH.
SO, YOU GUYS GO AROUND, LIKE,
LOOK FOR THINGS TO RECYCLE?
>> THAT'S THE PLAN.
>> WOW.
HEY.
YOU GUYS SHOULD GO TO THIS PARTY
THAT MY SON'S GONNA PLAY AT
TONIGHT NEAR THE PLANTATION.
PLENTY OF BOTTLES AND CANS, MAN.
>> HEY, YOU'RE JOSH'S DAD, HUH?
>> [ Laughing ] YEAH.
YOU KNOW HIM!
>> YEAH, EVERYONE KNOWS
BLACK SQUARE.
>> LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
>> SO THEN, YOU COMING, THEN?
>> YEAH, MAN.
THANKS, HUH?
>> RIGHT ON.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> HEY. WHERE YOU STAY?
OH, OKAY, I SEE YOU.
YEAH, FINE.
SORRY, YEAH?
>> THAT'S COOL.
>> HI.
>> HEY. DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
>> UH, YEAH. JUST A SEC.
JUST WAIT HERE.
THIS WON'T TAKE LONG, OKAY?
>> HEY.
>> HI. HOW ARE YOU?
>> DOING GOOD.
HOW'S KANA?
>> HE'S GOOD.
>> YEAH?
>> HE'S GETTING BIGGER.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
>> SO, I WAS JUST WONDERING.
DO -- DO YOU THINK YOU CAN BRING
HIM ON TIME NEXT TIME?
I MEAN, YOU TOLD ME IT'D BE
12:00, AND THEN YOU BROUGHT HIM
AT, LIKE, WHAT WAS IT?
LIKE 2:00 OR SOMETHING?
>> I TOLD YOU I WAS BRINGING HIM
AFTER PRACTICE.
THAT'S WHAT I TOLD YOU I WAS
DOING.
>> RIGHT, BUT YOU TOLD ME 12:00,
AND THEN YOU DIDN'T GET --
>> NO, I DIDN'T!
IS IT MY FAULT THAT PRACTICE
WENT OVER?
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO FIGHT WITH
YOU.
CAN YOU BE A LITTLE MORE
RESPONSIBLE AND TELL ME?
>> RESPONSIBLE?
YOU'RE GONNA TALK TO ME ABOUT
RESPONSIBLE?
>> NO. I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT.
ALL I'M ASKING -- ALL I'M ASKING
IS DO YOU THINK I COULD AT LEAST
SEE HIM NEXT WEEKEND?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS LATER?
>> [ SIGHS ] YEAH.
>> ALEA'S WAITING FOR ME, AND...
I GOT TO GO, SO...
>> YEAH. RIGHT.
OKAY. GO.
>> THANKS.
>> YEAH.
>> I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
>> SAME OLD SHIT.
>> BRAH, COME ON.
I'M TELLING YOU, COME DOWN HERE,
GET YOUR MONEY AND SOME EXTRAS.
YOU KNOW, WE'LL ALL PAD OUR
POCKETS.
WE'RE ALL HAPPY.
NAH, IT'S A SURE THING, BOO.
I'LL LEAVE YOUR ASS AT HOME,
THEN, IF YOU DON'T WANT TO COME.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
NO, FUCK IT, DANNY. NO.
I'LL HIT YOU UP LATER. OKAY.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
BRAH, I KNEW YOU WAS GONNA MAKE
IT, BRAH.
NOW BE LETTING NALU BOY WORK
HIS MAGIC.
>> I HOPE I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
>> WHY? ARE YOU DOUBTING ME?
COME ON, MAN.
JUST THROW YOUR STUFF IN THE
TRUCK.
LET'S GO.
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
>> HEY, HOW DO YOU KNOW THIS IS
GONNA WORK?
>> AW, TRUST ME, BRAH.
I DID THEM LAST WEEK.
I SHOULD GET THE MEANEST
FIGHTERS ON THE ISLAND.
JUST KEEP IT IN MIND.
IT'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
WHAT? YOU DON'T TRUST ME?
>> DUDE, THAT'S WHAT GOT ME
HERE.
NO WAY, MAN. I'LL HOLD THEM.
>> AW, FINE, THEN, BUT --
[ SCOFFS ]
YOU NEED ME TO PLACE THE BET.
>> HEY! WHATCHA DOING?!
>> FUCKER. DON'T DO THAT, MAN!
[ BLOWS NOSE ]
SO, WHAT? POPEYE IS UP FIRST?
>> THIS IS TYSON -- THE BLACK
ONE.
>> WELL, AS LONG AS THEY WIN,
YOU CAN CALL THEM ANYTHING YOU
LIKE.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
HI.
>> WHAT'S UP, BRAH?
>> OH, YOU KNOW. YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST LIKE VEGAS.
YOU GOT TO BE WHERE THE ACTION'S
AT, RIGHT?
>> TRUE. TRUE.
>> YOU MAKING SOME?
>> MAN, NOTHING YET, BUT --
[ SCOFFS ] WELL, MY BROTHER'S
BIRDS NEVER LOSE.
>> OH, YEAH?
HE'S A REAL WINNER, HUH?
THAT'S A NICE COCK.
WHEN ARE YOU UP?
>> NEXT FIGHT.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT!
I GUESS WE'D BETTER GET RINGSIDE
THEN, HUH?
SEE YOU THERE.
>> SHOOTS.
FUCK.
>> DUDE, WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
>> OH, NOTHING, BRAH. NOTHING.
>> SO WHAT?
>> AFTER THE FIGHT, JUST GET
DA KINE AND MEET ME AT THE CAR,
OKAY?
>> BRAH. I WAS GONNA --
>> WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST DO IT.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> DUDE!
>> HEY, WE NEED TO JUST PLACE
THIS BET AND THEN WE CAN GET THE
FUCK OUT OF HERE.
>> YOU WANT TO TELL ME WHAT'S
GOING ON?
>> YEAH, VEGAS MIKE.
>> WHO?
>> JUST THE WRONG DUDE TO RUN
INTO RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
>> WELL, FRICK, LET'S JUST GET
OUT OF HERE, THEN.
>> YOU KNOW, DUDE, I TOLD YOU
I WAS GONNA GET YOUR MONEY BACK.
FUCK. AND I'M GONNA.
[ CHEERING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WHO IS NEXT?
[ CHEERING INTENSIFIES ]
>> ALL RIGHT. WE'VE GOT THIS.
THIS SIDE EVEN, MAN.
EVEN. THIS SIDE.
YOUNG BOY. EVEN THIS SIDE.
THIS SIDE EVEN, MAN.
YOU? EVEN. THIS SIDE.
YOUNG BOY.
[ CHEERING CONTINUES ]
WANT YOU? EVEN. THIS SIDE.
>> THIS SIDE'S EVEN. COME ON.
>> LET US DO THIS!
>> YOU. EVEN NUMBER THIS SIDE?
>> TWO.
>> TWO? LET'S DO IT.
>> WELL, YOU GOT TWO?
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW I -- FUCK.
HEY, GIVE ME $200. COME ON.
>> DUDE, I GOT IT.
>> COME ON!
>> LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> WELL, THANK YOU, SON.
>> IT'S A GO.
[ CHEERING INTENSIFIES ]
>> COME ON. COME ON.
>> COME ON!
>> WHOO-HOO!
>> YEE-HEE!
YEAH!
>> COME ON.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
GET OUT OF HERE!
GO! GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
RICHARD, GET THE FUCK OUT OF
HERE RIGHT NOW!
COME ON, DUDE.
YAY!
>> WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE
QUICK, CUZ.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
GRAB THEM.
NO, NO, NO. THE CAGE.
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
COME ON. COME ON. COME ON.
>> WHOA. WHERE YOU GUYS GOING?
>> [ GROANS ]
>> WELL, WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE YOU GIRLS TRYING TO SKIP OUT
ON ME?
>> BRAH, YOU GOT ALL MY MONEY.
I TOLD YOU I WAS GONNA GET THE
REST SOON.
>> YO, MAN, WHY WOULD I WAIT FOR
THAT WHEN I CAN GET IT ALL RIGHT
NOW.
>> [ GRUNTING ] DAMN IT.
>> DON'T STOP. THERE'S MORE.
OH. I'M NOT STUPID.
I  SAWYOU PASS IT TO HIM.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> WELL, THAT'S NOT QUITE
ENOUGH, IS IT?
SO, UH, HERE'S WHAT WE'RE GONNA
DO.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE THOSE.
>> YOU FUCK.
>> AND THEN WE'RE ALMOST EVEN.
GOOD, NALU BOY?
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
YOU NEED ANYTHING FROM THE
STORE, COOKIE?
>> COME ON, BRAH.
>> NO, NO, NO. LET IT GO, BRAH.
LET IT GO, HUH? YOU LET IT GO.
>> COME ON. STOP IT.
>> WHOO! PUT 'ER THERE, BUDDY.
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ GASPS ] WOW. LOOK AT YOU.
>> OOH!
>> [ GASPS ]
>> [ GIGGLES ]
>> YOU THINK JOSH WILL LIKE IT?
>> JOSH?
>> FROM BLACK SQUARE.
MM! HE'S SO HOT.
>> ♪ ISLAND BOY, I LONG TO...
>> HEY, UM, DO YOU HAVE NALU'S
NUMBER IN YOUR PHONE?
>> NALU?
WHY DO YOU WANT HIS NUMBER?
>> WELL, I THINK AUSTIN IS WITH
HIM.
>> SO?
>> SO I WANT TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
STILL GOING TO THE PARTY
TONIGHT.
>> ♪ WITH THOSE SOFT BROWN
EYES ♪
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
>> OH, YEAH.
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
OOH.
NOW ONE MORE.
AWW, THANK YOU, AUNTIE.
YEAH.
YEE-HEE-HEE!
OUR AUNTIE HOOKED IT UP.
AW, BRAH, YOU NOT HUNGRY?
[ SCOFFS ]
[ RINGTONE PLAYS ]
SHIT.
[ SNIFFS ]
WHAT?
OH. WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
YEAH, YEAH. UM, JUST ONE SEC,
OKAY?
OH, BRAH, IT'S ALEA. FORGET IT.
JUST DON'T SAY NOTHING ABOUT THE
PRANK.
YOU KNOW, I GOT A PLAN.
>> [ SIGHS ] HELLO.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA MEET UP
LATER.
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
JUST SOME CHICKENS BY THE SIDE
OF THE ROAD.
UH, I THINK WE'RE GONNA GET
SOMETHING TO EAT, AND --
[ CHUCKLES ] YEAH, OF COURSE
WE'RE STILL GOING.
UH, I'LL PROBABLY...GET A RIDE
WITH NALU.
[ SNIFFLES ]
UH, YEAH.
HE SAID HE CAN PAY ME BACK,
SO...
[ SIGHS ]
YEAH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
[ Chuckling ] YEAH, I KNOW, BUT
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
TRUST ME, OKAY?
[ SIGHS ]
YEAH, I MISS YOU, TOO.
OKAY.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
>> OH, BRAH.
>> WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
>> NOTHING.
>> WHY IS HE GETTING MONEY FROM
NALU?
>> HI. I NEED TO EXCHANGE THIS.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WANTED TO KEEP
IT.
>> I DO.
NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST -- [ SIGHS ] I TOLD
HIM I'D GIVE HIM A CHANCE.
>> [ SCOFFS ] WELL, IF NALU IS
HIS CHANCE, HE BETTER START
THINKING ABOUT KEEPING IT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NALU IS SUCH A LOSER.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WENT OUT
WITH HIM.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> WELL, FUCK VEGAS MIKE.
>> WE'RE NOT REALLY GOING IN
THERE, ARE WE?
>> WELL, WE DIDN'T DRIVE ALL THE
WAY OUT HERE FOR NOTHING, BRAH.
>> OH, LOOK. THERE HE GOES.
>> WHAT IF HE COMES BACK?
>> AW, TRUST ME, BRAH.
I KNOW THIS GUY.
HE GO DA KINE EVERY FRIDAY NIGHT
FOR HAPPY HOUR, TRIES TO HIT ON
CHICKS BEHIND THE BAR, AND NONE
OF THEM FUCKING EVEN GIVE HIM A
CHANCE.
BUT EVERY WEEK HE WOULD TRY.
>> HEY, WHERE DO YOU THINK HE
PUT TYSON AND POPEYE?
>> I TOLD YOU FORGET ABOUT THOSE
FUCKING CHICKENS, RICHARD.
>> THEY'RE NOT CHICKENS.
THEY DON'T LAY EGGS. STUPID.
>> DON'T BE STUPID.
WHAT? YOU, TOO?
WELL, WE'RE DOING THIS.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
OKAY. THE COAST IS CLEAR.
LET'S GO.
[ DOG BARKING ]
HEY, GOOD BOY. GOOD BOY.
GOOD BOY. GOOD BOY.
HEY, COME ON AND GRAB THESE.
COME ON. HEY, GOOD BOY.
GOOD BOY. GOOD BOY.
THERE WE GO. THERE WE GO.
>> TYSON AND POPEYE.
>> LET'S GO.
HEY! COME ON!
>> HE NEVER EVEN GAVE THEM
WATER.
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
>> GO AHEAD.
HEY, YOU STAY OUT HERE AND KEEP
WATCH, OKAY?
BRAH, DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
>> Psst! Hey! Psst! Hey!
>> OH, MEAN, HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HURRY UP.
>> WHAT THE FUCK?
COME AND BAG THEN.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> OH, RIGHT HERE.
COME ON.
>> HO!
>> LOOK AT THIS.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF WEED.
>> I'M JUST GONNA PILFER THEM
BIG BAGS AND THEN BUST THEM UP
AT HOME.
>> HEY, WHY DON'T WE JUST GRAB A
BUNCH OF 20s AND EIGHTHS?
>> BRAH, BRAH.
YOU DON'T SEE THIS FUCKING BAG,
BRAH?
THE "V" AND A "M"?
HUH?
IT'S VEGAS MIKE, YOU FUCKER.
COME ON. BRING THEM OVER HERE.
[ DOG BARKING ]
WHAT IS THAT?
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
NEVER MIND. COME ON. JUST --
>> CALM YOURSELF.
>> JUST DO IT.
>> WHAT THE FUCK IS RICHARD
DOING?
>> NEVER MIND. COME ON.
>> FUCK, YEAH, DUDE.
GO CHECK IT. GO CHECK IT.
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
>> [ SNIFFS ] YOU FUCK.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT?
[ DOG SNARLING ]
>> WHOA!
>> WHAT THE FUCK?!
[ ROOSTERS CLUCKING ]
>> GET AWAY FROM ME! GET OFF ME!
>> DUDE, IT'S VEGAS MIKE!
>> OH, SHIT.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
COME ON. COME ON. COME ON, DUDE.
>> IS IT IN?
>> I DON'T SEE HIM.
>> JUST GO.
JUST GO, GO, GO!
>> WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT,
RICHARD?!
>> I THOUGHT WE WAS TRYING TO
GET THEM.
>> I TOLD YOU FORGET ABOUT THOSE
STUPID FUCKING CHICKENS --
ROOSTERS -- COCKS!
WHATEVER!
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO SAVE THEM.
>> DUDE, WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
VEGAS MIKE IS GONNA KNOW WE WERE
THERE, AND WE DIDN'T EVEN GET
THE WEED.
[ BAG CRINKLES ]
>> BRAH, FUCK VEGAS MIKE.
[ J BOOG'S "AYE OK" PLAYS ]
>> ♪ HEY, NO, I'M OKAY
♪ HEY, NO, I'M ALL RIGHT
>> ♪ LIKE OUTWEIGHING IT'S THAT
YOUR LOVER'S OUTGROWN ♪
♪ AGAIN, GANJA FEATURES AND
ADDICTED AND TONED ♪
♪ NEVER KNOW WHAT YOU GET UNTIL
YOU'RE IN ♪
♪ YOU THINK IT'S LOVE, SO YOU
THOUGHT SHE GIVES YOU A GRIN ♪
♪ WHY YOU PUT YOURSELF IN A BAD
SITUATION? ♪
♪ YOU'RE SO WEAK, SHE'S SO
STRONG ♪
♪ COME ON, WHAT DO YOU STAND
FOR? ♪
♪ NO MORE I RISE WITH MY
FAMILY ♪
♪ LET ME BREAK IT DOWN FOR YOU
♪ YOU KNOW THAT'S ACTUALLY REAL
LOVE, TRUE SOUL ♪
♪ THEY NEVER EVER WANT TO --
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
>> OKAY, JUST LIKE I TOLD YOU
GUYS.
NOW, YOU KEEP HIM BUSY, AND I
CAN GO TOMORROW AND WE'LL BREAK
THEM UP.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> BRAH, WHAT?
>> [ SNIFFS ] DUDE, THAT STUFF
REEKS.
[ BAG CRINKLING ]
>> OH, SHIT.
RICHARD, PASS ME MY HOODIE.
[ SIGHS ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> OKAY, WE GOT A LITTLE
PROBLEM.
BUT IT'S COOL. IT'S COOL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> I'M HOME.
OH. HEY, DAD.
>> HI, HONEY.
>> HI.
>> HI, ALEA.
>> HEY, GIRLS.
>> HEY.
>> [ GASPS ] OOH.
DID YOU DO A LITTLE SHOPPING
TODAY?
>> YES.
[ GASPS ]
[ Singsong voice ] HI.
OH, SLEEPY BOY.
HI, HONEY.
OH. HEY, COME HERE.
OH! ISN'T HE CUTE?
[TELEVISION PLAYING ]
>> SO, WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
>> YEAH. HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU HOLD HIM?
YOU GOT HIM?
>> HEY, GUY.
[ BAG CRINKLES ]
>> LOOK.
>> OOH! I LOVE IT.
>> YOU WANT TO TRY IT ON FOR ME?
>> [ GASPS ] SURE.
MWAH!
>> HEY, DAD.
>> OH. GOOD.
YOU BOYS ARE JUST IN TIME.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> TO UNLOAD THE TRUCK.
HEY, AUSTIN, HELP WITH THIS,
I'LL LET YOU STAY FOR DINNER.
>> HEY, AUSTIN.
>> OH, HEY.
>> YOU GONNA EAT WITH US?
>> UM...[Chuckling] IF IT'S
OKAY.
>> YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALWAYS
WELCOME AT OUR TABLE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> AHH, NO WORRIES. COME ON. GO.
>> ARE YOU JOKING?
>> LET'S GO.
UH, SO WHAT, DAD?
I LIKE BODIES.
>> DOESN'T SHE LOOK AMAZING?
I BETTER SEE HOW TUTU IS COMING
WITH DINNER.
>> THANKS, MOM.
[ BABY COOS ]
>> I GOT HIM.
MM.
>> HEY, CLOSE THE DOOR.
>> DO YOU REALLY THINK THAT'S A
GOOD IDEA?
>> WHAT? 'CAUSE OF THE...
IT'S FINE.
I SMOKED, DRANK, AND PARTIED FOR
THE FIRST THREE MONTHS.
AND KAHANA CAME OUT JUST FINE.
[ VEHICLE DEPARTS ]
SO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
WE'RE GONNA PARTY TONIGHT.
ALL WE NEED IS A RIDE.
OH, TRY PASSING MY PHONE.
>> [ GRUNTS ]
[ METAL CLANKS ]
>> SO WHAT, POPS? THAT'S IT?
>> YEP. THANKS, BOYS.
LET'S GO SEE WHAT MAMA'S GOT FOR
DINNER.
>> HEY.
YOU KEEP AN EYE ON MOM AND DAD
SO ME AND RALSTO CAN BREAK UP
DA KINE.
>> SURE THING, BOSS.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
OKAY, WE JUST GOT TO GET DA KINE
AND GET THEM UP TO MY ROOM,
OKAY?
>> BRAH, DON'T.
>> GET IN THERE.
OH, MOM, STOP.
>> WHAT?
>> MY HOODIE IS --
>> DON'T WORRY.
YOU CAN THROW IT IN THE DRYER
AFTER DINNER.
NOW COME ON. GO WASH UP.
COME ON.
GO WASH UP FOR DINNER.
YOU TOO. COME ON, AUSTIN.
[ KAHANA CRYING ]
>> IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
SHIT!
>> HEY.
MNH-MNH.
>> [ SIGHS ] SORRY.
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
OH, HERE, YOU TAKE HIM.
>> SO, YOU GIRLS GOT ANY BIG
PLANS TONIGHT?
>> I THINK WE'RE GOING TO THE
MOVIE, IF THAT'S OKAY.
>> SO, WHAT MOVIE ARE YOU GUYS
GOING TO?
[ DRYER RUNNING IN BACKGROUND ]
>> THE ONE WITH THE -- THE GUY
FROM DA KINE.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> RICHARD, ARE YOU GOING, TOO?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WE USED TO GO THE MOVIES
EVERY WEEKEND, HUH, HONEY?
>> [ CHUCKLES ] MM-HMM. YEP.
[ DRYER ALARM BUZZES ]
>> UH, AT LEAST WAIT FOR AUSTIN.
>> OH, SORRY, MOM.
>> [ SLURPS ]
MMM.
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD, MRS. B.
>> OKAY, BOYS. YOU CAN GO.
>> HEY.
FINISH YOUR VEGETABLES, BOY.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Aw, man.
What the fuck?
Oh, I got to get this out of
here.
[ SIGHS ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
>> YOU MUST BE HERE FOR LEILANI.
COME IN.
>> HI. I'M JOSH.
>> HI.
SO, WHAT MOVIE ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA SEE?
>> HUH?
>> WERE YOU GUYS GOING TO --
>> HEY, MOM. [ CHUCKLES ]
>> NICE MEETING YOU.
>> OKAY, YOU TOO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BYE.
YOU GUYS HAVE FUN.
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK ANYONE'S
>> BYE.
GONNA BUY THAT.
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK ANYONE'S
>> GREAT.
GONNA BUY THAT.
[ RAP MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> GREAT.
>> BRAH, HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO
[ RAP MUSIC PLAYING ]
KNOW?
>> BRAH, HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO
>> NOW WHAT, NALU?
KNOW?
>> I KNOW.
>> NOW WHAT, NALU?
LET'S GO DOWN TO THE POINT, HAVE
>> I KNOW.
SOME BEERS, TALK TO THE BOYS.
LET'S GO DOWN TO THE POINT, HAVE
>> IS THAT ALL YOU CAN THINK
SOME BEERS, TALK TO THE BOYS.
ABOUT?
>> IS THAT ALL YOU CAN THINK
>> WELL, BRAH, YOU GOT A BETTER
ABOUT?
IDEA?
>> WELL, BRAH, YOU GOT A BETTER
>> [ SIGHS ]
IDEA?
>> HEY. PICK.
>> [ SIGHS ]
I DON'T KNOW. LATERS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
GEE-HEE-HEE!
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>>   HELLO, GOOD PEOPLE OF THE
WORLD.
>> WHATCHA DOING?
>> THAT'S MY JAM, CUZ.
>>   YEAH.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
>> ♪ HE GOT LOVELY, WHOA-AYE
♪ HE GOT LOVELY, WHOA-AYE
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
♪ KEEP ON FLOATING, SPREAD YOUR
LOVE LIKE A... ♪
♪ OH, A-A-AYE, YA
>> WHAT? YOU'RE NOT COMING?
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
>> YOU DITCHED ME, MAN.
>> MY BAD, HOMEY.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH RALSTO?
>> RALSTO? JUST BEING RALSTO.
>> ♪ HE GOT LOVELY, WHOA-AYE
>> YO, RALSTO. YOU WANT A BEER?
>> THANKS.
>> ♪ HE GOT LOVELY, WHOA-AYE
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> OH, HERE. I ALMOST FORGOT.
>> WHAT'S THIS?
>> I SOLD BOTH THE DECKS AND THE
SHOES.
DON'T WORRY, MAN.
I DIDN'T TAKE A CUT.
IT SEEMED LIKE YOU NEED IT MORE
THAN I DID.
>> THANKS, MAN.
IT'S JUST TOO REAL FOR ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S A LONG STORY.
>> SHOOTS.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
SO, HOW'S NALU?
[ CHEERING ]
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO, GIRL.
>> WHOO-HOO-HOO!
IN YOUR FACE!
>> WHATEVER.
>> OH, MY GOD. [ CHUCKLES ]
SO, DOES YOUR BROTHER HAVE
ANYTHING TO SMOKE?
>> NO, BUT I DO. WHY?
YOU LIKE SMOKE?
>> YEAH.
IS IT COOL IF MY FRIEND COMES,
TOO?
>> IF SHE'S AS CUTE AS YOU.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> BUT, UH, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HEY, BRAH.
THESE TWO CHICKS LIKE SMOKE.
CAN I USE YOUR CAR?
>> WHY? YOU GET BUDS?
[ BAG CRINKLES ]
WHERE'D YOU GET THIS?
>> I DIDN'T GET POPEYE BACK, BUT
AT LEAST I GOT SOMETHING.
>> HOW MUCH YOU GET?
>> JUST THIS ONE.
>> WELL, SHOOTS.
LADIES.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
I HEARD YOU GUYS WANT TO GET
HIGH.
>> JUST A LITTLE BIT.
>> SHALL WE?
>> ALL RIGHT. SURE. LET'S GO.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> I'M GOING OVER THERE.
>> SO YOU'LL DEDICATE A SONG TO
ME?
>> OF COURSE.
EVERY SONG'S FOR YOU.
>> [ Chuckling ] OH.
OH, GOD, YOU GUYS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> [ Chuckling ] WHAT?
SEE YOU LATER.
>> BYE.
>> ♪ NA, NA, LA, NA, NA
♪ I LOVE YOU, GIRL
♪ AND I GIVE YOU ALL
>> [ SIGHS ] OOMPH.
HE IS SO HOT.
CIGARETTE?
>> SURE.
>> ♪ GIRL, WHY DON'T YOU SIT
RIGHT BESIDE ME? ♪
>> MM.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
♪ IT'S A LITTLE HOT NOW
♪ COME ON, STAY CURLY AND
KNOTTY, YEAH ♪
>> OH, YOU DON'T LIKE SMOKE?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> YOU PROBABLY SHOULD SMOKE.
YOU WOULDN'T BE SO FUCKING
TIGHT.
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> ♪ NOW WE CAN MAKE BELIEVE
♪ SEEMS LIKE ARE READY TO TURN
IN OUR SEATS, YEAH ♪
>> [ GIGGLES ]
>> ♪ HEY
[ SINGING INDISTINCTLY ]
♪ LOVE'S LIKE A FURNACE FIRE
>> OH. YOU GIRLS NEED A DRINK?
>> TWO VODKA RED BULLS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ] ALL RIGHT.
TWO VODKA RED BULLS. [ SNIFFS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> YOU KNOW HOW MANY HOTTIES ARE
GONNA BE HERE TONIGHT?
SNAP OUT OF IT.
>> I'M MIKE.
VEGAS MIKE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HAIR?
>> THAT'S THE FUTURE OF
ROCK 'N' ROLL, BABY.
THAT...IS THE FUTURE OF
ROCK 'N' ROLL.
>> THANKS.
>> OH, HEY.
THEY'RE STARTING TO PLAY.
LET'S GO.
>> OH. [ CHUCKLES ] WHAT'S UP?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> THE FUCK'S WRONG WITH HIM?
>> STILL GOING.
>> HO!
HO. YOU'RE READY.
>> OH, THANKS.
[ CAN OPENS ]
>> SO WHAT? HOW ARE YOU?
>> SHITTY.
>> WHAT? LOSE MONEY?
>> NO, I WON, BUT FREAKING NALU
F'd IT ALL UP.
>> SEE? TOLD YOU.
NEVER BET ON A SURE THING.
NEVER.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHY YOU EVEN HANG OUT WITH THAT
GUY?
>> THAT GUY JUST LOSE MONEY.
>> HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN ALEA?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> [ SIGHS ] ALL RIGHT.
SHOOTS, THEN.
>> WHERE YOU GOING, BRAH?
>> YOU WANT TO CHASE A BEER?
HO, BABY. WHAT'S UP?
>> HO, BABY.
>> WELL, YOU LOOK ONE SIDE
GRAVY.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ UP-TEMPO ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> ALL RIGHT. TEE UP. GO!
[ SAXOPHONE SOLO ]
>> DO YOU GUYS DO THIS EVERY
WEEKEND?
>> PRETTY MUCH.
>> YEAH?
WHAT'S THIS?
IS THIS YOUR, UH, YOUR FUTURE OF
ROCK 'N' ROLL?
>> [ GIGGLES ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
LOOK AT THIS JOKER.
>> WHO? NALU?
>> YEAH.
YEAH. YOU KNOW HIM, HUH?
>> YEAH. WHY?
>> YOU EVER, UH, BEEN TO A
COCKFIGHT?
>> [ Chuckling ] BOTTOMS UP.
[ RAP MUSIC PLAYS ]
MMM.
>> ♪ POT OF GOLD, THERE NEVER
COMES THE RAIN, NO, MNH-MNH ♪
>> YEAH, RALSTO. YOU'RE UP.
>> OH, NO. I'M GOOD.
>> WHAT?
>> I GOT TO FIND ALEA.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
>> [ CHUCKLES ] NO, MAN, I
HAVEN'T SEEN HER, BUT YOU'RE
GONNA FUCKING DO ONE OF THESE.
>> OH, NO. I'M SERIOUS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ] YEAH. ME TOO.
GET ME A LEMON.
>> ♪ I AIN'T GRUMBLIN'
♪ 'CAUSE IT'S COVERIN'...
>> DUDE, YOU'RE BLOWING IT.
♪ WATCH OUT, FOR THE
HELICOPTER'S OVERHEAD ♪
♪ CHOOGA, CHOOGA, CHOOGA
♪ WHAT YOU HEAR?
>> YOU WANT ANOTHER SHOT?
>> ♪ MAYBE I'M JUST PARANOID
[ MID-TEMPO ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA NEED
SOMETHING A LITTLE STRONGER,
HUH?
>> WHAT?
>> DO YOU GUYS WANT TO GET THIS
PARTY STARTED?
>> LET'S GO.
>> [ Chuckling ] ALL RIGHT.
>> ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO
THIS?
>> YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, BUT I THOUGHT YOU
WANTED TO TALK TO AUSTIN.
>> [ SIGHS ] FUCK AUSTIN.
>> ♪ FIVE KARATS ON MY PINKY
RING ♪
♪ HAZARD LIGHTS ON MY BEEMER GO
BLINKY-BLINK ♪
♪ GUAVA JUICE MIXED WITH AVARU,
DRINKY-DRINK ♪
>> HEY, YOU STILL LOOKING FOR
ALEA?
>> WHY? YOU SEEN HER?
>> YEAH, BRAH.
...SOME OTHER GUY.
>> WHERE?
>> ♪ GONNA LOOT A TRAIN WRECK
♪ WE WANT THE BEST CRIB
♪ SPEND A WHOLE PAYCHECK AND
RE-UP FOR THE NEXT FLICK ♪
>>   THAT'THE GUY?
>> YEAH, BRAH.
LOOK AT THAT.
FUCKING OVER THERE WITH
RALSTO'S CHICK.
HEY! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> HO!
>> WHAT THE FUCK?
HEY.
>> DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
>> HEY.
LEAVE HIM THE FUCK ALONE.
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
>> ♪ BUST SOME SHOTS
♪ WE ALWAYS SEARCHING FOR THE
END OF THE RAINBOW ♪
♪ THE POT OF GOLD, IT NEVER
COMES OUR WAY, NO ♪
>> WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING?!
>> ME?!
>> YOU CAN'T GO PUSHING ME
AROUND LIKE THAT.
DON'T YOU KNOW IT'S BAD FOR THE
BABY?
>> OH, AND PARTYING IS OKAY?
>> I JUST HAD A COUPLE OF
DRINKS.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT WERE YOU AND LEILANI DOING
IN THE BATHROOM?
>> SHUT UP.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> WHAT DID YOU HAND TO VEGAS
MIKE?
>> SHUT UP!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT, OKAY?
LEILANI SAID --
>> WHY DO YOU LISTEN TO THAT
SHIT?
>> DON'T INTERRUPT ME!
LEILANI KNOWS WHAT SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
>> SHE CAN HANDLE THE
RESPONSIBILITY OF HAVING A BABY,
UNLIKE SOME PEOPLE.
>> OH, YEAH.
I'VE BEEN BUSTING ASS ALL DAY.
AND NOW I --
>> AND WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SHOW
FOR IT, HUH?
NOTHING!
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'RE A FUCKING LIAR.
NALU NEVER PAID YOU BACK.
VEGAS MIKE TOLD ME EVERYTHING.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT?
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY PAPERS?
>> PAPERS? ANY...
>> WHAT?
THIS?
>> PAPERS? ANY...
>> WHAT THE FUCK?
THIS?
>> IF YOU WANT TO SMOKE WITH US,
>> WHAT THE FUCK?
YOU CAN.
>> IF YOU WANT TO SMOKE WITH US,
WE JUST NEED SOMETHING TO PUT IT
YOU CAN.
IN.
WE JUST NEED SOMETHING TO PUT IT
>> WHERE THE FUCK DID YOU GET
IN.
THIS?
>> WHERE THE FUCK DID YOU GET
>> FROM A GUY.
THIS?
>> WAIT.
>> FROM A GUY.
I WILL -- I WILL GIVE YOU ALL OF
>> WAIT.
THESE IF YOU TELL ME WHERE THAT
I WILL -- I WILL GIVE YOU ALL OF
GUY IS, OKAY?
THESE IF YOU TELL ME WHERE THAT
>> MM.
GUY IS, OKAY?
>> SO IT'S ALL MY FAULT?
>> MM.
>> WELL, I MEAN, YOU'RE ALL DAY
>> SO IT'S ALL MY FAULT?
WITH YOUR SIGNS, AND --
>> WELL, I MEAN, YOU'RE ALL DAY
>> SO IT'S ALL MY FAULT?
WITH YOUR SIGNS, AND --
YOU HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
>> SO IT'S ALL MY FAULT?
ANYTHING, RIGHT?
YOU HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
>> JUST LISTEN.
ANYTHING, RIGHT?
>> WHY?
>> JUST LISTEN.
SO YOU CAN LIE TO ME SOME MORE?
>> WHY?
>> LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD TALK
SO YOU CAN LIE TO ME SOME MORE?
ABOUT THIS TOMORROW.
>> LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD TALK
>> WHY?!
ABOUT THIS TOMORROW.
SO YOU CAN COME UP WITH MORE
>> WHY?!
EXCUSES?
SO YOU CAN COME UP WITH MORE
>> NO!
EXCUSES?
YOU'RE JUST -- YOU'RE NOT
>> NO!
THINKING STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE JUST -- YOU'RE NOT
>> OH, I'M NOT THINKING
THINKING STRAIGHT.
STRAIGHT?
>> OH, I'M NOT THINKING
HE'S TRYING TO TELL ME THIS IS
STRAIGHT?
ALL MY FAULT.
HE'S TRYING TO TELL ME THIS IS
CAN YOU FUCKING BELIEVE THIS?
ALL MY FAULT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
CAN YOU FUCKING BELIEVE THIS?
YOU'RE JUST LIKE YOU'RE BOY
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
NALU -- ONE BIG FUCKING LOSER!
YOU'RE JUST LIKE YOU'RE BOY
[ CHUCKLES ]
NALU -- ONE BIG FUCKING LOSER!
>> WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LISTEN TO
[ CHUCKLES ]
ME?
>> WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LISTEN TO
>> LIES.
ME?
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE FUCKING
>> LIES.
TELLING ME.
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE FUCKING
YOU KNOW WHAT?
TELLING ME.
I'M OVER THIS!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU CAN'T TAKE CARE OF ME,
I'M OVER THIS!
I'M GONNA FIND SOMEONE WHO CAN.
IF YOU CAN'T TAKE CARE OF ME,
>> YOU FUCKING LOSER.
>> FUCK.
>> WHAT'S DOING?
WHERE YOU GOING?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> RALSTO.
>> I'M OUT OF HERE, MAN.
GIVE ME YOUR KEYS.
>> COME ON, BRAH.
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
>> GIVE ME THE KEYS.
>> FINE, THEN.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
>> HEY, WE STILL SKATING
TOMORROW?
>> HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BRAH.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> BRAH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> DUDE. DON'T TOUCH ME.
>> WHAT?
>> ARE YOU FUCKING CRAZY, MAN?
>> YOU BUST UP MY HOUSE AND YOU
>> WHAT?
THINK YOU'RE GONNA GET AWAY WITH
>> YOU BUST UP MY HOUSE AND YOU
IT?
THINK YOU'RE GONNA GET AWAY WITH
TONIGHT, I'M GONNA BURY YOU LIKE
IT?
A PIG AT A LUAU.
TONIGHT, I'M GONNA BURY YOU LIKE
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FUCK
A PIG AT A LUAU.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> OH, YOU GOT YOUR BOYS?
GREAT. MINE ARE ON THEIR WAY.
YOU READY TO DO THIS, COOKIE?
DON'T WORRY.
I'M GONNA TAKE GOOD CARE OF HER.
[ SPEED DIALING ]
>> GIVE ME YOUR KEYS, MAN.
>> NO, WE GOT IT.
WE CAN TAKE THEM.
>> I SAID, "GIVE ME YOUR KEYS."
>> DON'T CROSS WITH ME.
>> GEEZ, BRO.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
>> GIVE ME THE FUCKING KEYS!
GIVE ME THE FUCKING KEYS!
>> HOLD ON, BRAH. WAIT UP.
YOU'RE MAKING ME RUN.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> OUT OF HERE.
>> WELL, GO THEN.
>> HERE, MAN.
YOU WANT IT?
IT'S YOURS.
>> HEY. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> LET HIM GO. COME ON.
>> COME ON.
>> NO.
>> [ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> DROP THE KNIFE!
DROP THE KNIFE!
>> WHOA, WHOA, FUCK.
>> STAIRS.
>> YEAH.
>> WHOA. WHOA.
>> I'M DRUNK.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> HEY, JOSH.
>> WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
>> OKAY. I'M OKAY.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
LET'S GO.
>> [ GRUNTS ]
[ YELLS ]
>> ♪ YOU KEEP RUNNING AWAY
♪ FROM THE PROBLEMS THAT
SURROUND YOU ♪
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> ♪ STEP UP AND REALIZE
♪ THE POTENTIAL THAT HAS FOUND
YOU ♪
♪ WHOA-OH
♪ YOU KEEP RUNNING, RUNNING,
SHUNNING ♪
♪ WHOA-OH
♪ STEPPING, STOPPING, GOING
♪ BILLING, DRAGGING, BLOWING
♪ WHOA-OH
♪ WHOA-OH, OH-OH-OH
♪ SOME WILL TELL YOU THERE'S NO
PATH TO CHOOSE ♪
♪ BUT A WISE MAN TOLD ME, "NO
PREDETERMINED RULES" ♪
♪ WHEN IT'S OVER IT'S UP TO
EVERY MAN ♪
♪ FOR HIM TO CHOOSE A PATH, FIND
HIS PROMISED LAND ♪
>> ♪ THEY KEEP RUNNING AWAY
♪ FROM THE PROBLEMS THAT
SURROUND YOU ♪
♪ STEP UP AND REALIZE
♪ THE POTENTIAL THAT HAS FOUND
YOU ♪
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
>> GEEZ.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
>> HO.
YOU LIKE A BEER?
>> YEAH.
>> SHOOTS.
>> THAT WHERE YOU WAS?
TOOK US FOREVER TO FIND YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> BRAH, PARTY GETTING NUTS
AFTER YOU LEFT.
>> AND THE COPS JUST SHOWED UP.
>> YEAH?
>> RIGHT WHEN NALU AND THE VEGAS
GUY WERE SCRAPPING.
>> OH, AND THEN THEY GRABBED THE
VEGAS GUY, TOOK HIM AWAY.
>> [ Chuckling ] FOR REAL?
>> RIGHT AFTER THEY TOOK HIM
AWAY, STARTED KICKING EVERYBODY
OUT.
>> THEN, YOU REMEMBER MUSHROOM
GUY?
HE LET US STAY, AND WE GRABBED A
WHOLE CAR FULL OF BOTTLES.
>> CHECK THEM OUT.
WE'RE LOADED.
>> LOCO MOCOS ALL MORNING.
>> BRAH.
>> HEY, WHAT HAPPENED TO ALEA?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
BRAH, SHE WENT HOME ON A BUS.
>> OH, YOU FUCKING SHUT UP.
GET ME ANOTHER BEER, BITCH.
>> BRAH...
>> SHUT UP.
LET'S GO OVER, HUH?
MUSHROOM GUY'S SON WILL DRIVE
HER HOME.
>> YEAH?
>> NAH, NO WORRIES, BRAH.
THEY'RE GOOD PEOPLE.
>> HEY, YOU LIKE ONE MORE?
>> NAH, I'M GOOD.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
WHATEVER. MORE FOR US.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> BRAH, THAT WAS DA KINE PARTY,
HUH?
SO, WHAT?
WE GO, THEN?
>> YEAH, SHOOTS.
>> [ SIGHS ] OH, GOD.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> ♪ YEAH, YEAH
♪ AND I CAN'T HELP IF YOU CAN'T
SEE THE THINGS I DO FOR YOU ♪
♪ TRYING NOT TO MAKE YOU SEE ME,
TOO ♪
♪ I REMEMBER YOU WERE ALWAYS BY
MY SIDE ♪
♪ DO YOU WANT TO MAKE THINGS
RIGHT? ♪
♪ I WANT YOU HERE WITH ME
♪ YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I NEED
♪ EVEN IF THIS AIN'T A REAL
THING TO OFFER ME ♪
♪ ALL I WANT FROM YOU IS JUST A
LITTLE LOVE ♪
♪ JUST A LITTLE LOVE
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
>> THERE YOU ARE.
>> YEAH, SORRY, MOM.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
LAST NIGHT GOT KIND OF CRAZY.
>> TOO CRAZY TO EVEN GIVE ME A
CALL?
I'VE BEEN SITTING HERE ALL NIGHT
WORRYING ABOUT YOU.
DO YOU KNOW HOW THAT FEELS?
[ SIGHS ]
OH, SWEETIE.
I GUESS IT WASN'T CRAZY IN A
GOOD WAY, HUH?
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
LISTEN, I-I'LL COOK SOME DINNER
TONIGHT AFTER WORK, AND WE'LL
TALK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
>> [ GROANS ]
I DON'T WANT TO. STOP.
>> PLEASE?
>> [ GROANS ]
DON'T.
>> HEY.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> GET UP.
>> IT HURTS.
>> DON'T WANT TO.
>> GET UP.
[ INDISTINCT GRUMBLING ]
>> DON'T WANT TO.
>> HONEY.
[ INDISTINCT GRUMBLING ]
COME ON, HONEY.
>> HONEY.
>> [ GROANS ]
COME ON, HONEY.
GO AWAY. STOP.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> PLEASE?
GO AWAY. STOP.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> PLEASE?
>> PLEASE, HONEY.
>> [ GROANS ]
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
>> PLEASE, HONEY.
>> FUCK. GET OFF ME.
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
GET OFF ME.
>> FUCK. GET OFF ME.
>> WHAT?
GET OFF ME.
>> YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
>> WHAT?
>> WHY?
>> YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
>> JUST GET THE FUCK OUT!
>> WHY?
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING
>> JUST GET THE FUCK OUT!
ABOUT?
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING
>> GET OUT!
ABOUT?
>> WHY?
>> GET OUT!
>> GET THE FUCK OUT!
>> WHY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> GET THE FUCK OUT!
>> GET OUT!
>> ALL RIGHT.
SHIT.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> OH.
HEY, WHAT'S UP, ALEA, GIRL?
>> LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> NO, NO, NO. HEY. HEY.
>> GET OUT!
MOM! MOM!
>> [ SCREAMS ]
WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN THERE?
YOU KNEW SHE WAS IN THE
BATHROOM.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN THERE?
>> HEY, CALM DOWN.
>> NO.
[ INDISTINCT ARGUING ]
>> [ GROANING ]
[ URINATING ]
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ ARGUING CONTINUES ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
NO.
[ CRYING ]
OH.
OH, MY GOD.
NO.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ CRYING ]
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
[ SOBBING ]
I'M SORRY.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> HEY, MOM.
I KNOW IT MIGHT BE TOO LATE, BUT
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE THIS
TO THE POST OFFICE FOR ME?
[ SMOOCHES ]
>> OH, UM...
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT.
>> ♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
>> ♪ A LONG TYPE OF LOVING,
GIRL ♪
>> ♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
>> ♪ DO YOU WANT TO SHOW THEM
OFF? ♪
>> ♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
>> ♪ LISTEN UP
♪ I WANT TO KISS YOU AND HOLD
YOU TIGHT ♪
♪ YOU'RE FAR AWAY
♪ A KIND OF FEELING WHEN I LOOK
IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ FAR AWAY
♪ I COULD HAVE BEEN THE MAN IN
YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ YOU'RE FAR AWAY
♪ YOU KNOW IT'S WRONG, BUT IT
FEELS SO RIGHT ♪
♪ YOU'RE FAR AWAY
♪ SO MANY NIGHTS I'M AWAY FROM
YOU ♪
♪ ARE YOU SITTING AT HOME WHILE
I'M FEELING SO LONELY? ♪
♪ YEAH, UNDERSTAND WHY I'M HERE
FOR YOU ♪
♪ COULD IT BE IT'S YOUR LOVE?
'CAUSE IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY? ♪
♪ SO CRAZY
>> ♪ YEAH, YOU DRIVE ME CRAZY
>> ♪ CRAZY
>> ♪ OH, YEAH
>> ♪ WHEN SHE WALK UP ON THE
FLOOR, I GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ AND WHEN SHE LOOKS AT ME, I
GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ AND WHEN SHE MOVE HER BODY, I
♪ WE COME TO TELL YOU ONCE
GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
AGAIN ♪
♪ WE COME TO TELL YOU ONCE
♪ WHEN SHE WALK UP ON THE FLOOR,
AGAIN ♪
I GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ WHEN SHE WALK UP ON THE FLOOR,
♪ AND WHEN SHE LOOKS AT ME, I
I GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ AND WHEN SHE LOOKS AT ME, I
♪ AND WHEN SHE MOVE HER BODY, I
GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ AI-TA-AI-AI-AI
>> ♪ SO MANY NIGHTS I'M AWAY
FROM YOU ♪
♪ ARE YOU SITTING AT HOME WHILE
I'M FEELING SO LONELY? ♪
♪ YEAH, UNDERSTAND WHY I'M HERE
FOR YOU ♪
♪ COULD IT BE IT'S YOUR LOVE?
'CAUSE IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY ♪
♪ ME CRAZY
>> YEAH, YOU DRIVE ME...
>> ♪ CRAZY
♪ OH, YEAH
>> ♪ WHEN SHE WALK UP ON THE
FLOOR, I GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ AND WHEN SHE LOOKS AT ME, I
GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ AND WHEN SHE MOVE HER BODY, I
[ SINGING INDISTINCTLY ]
GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ WHEN SHE WALK UP ON THE FLOOR,
[ SINGING INDISTINCTLY ]
I GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ WHEN SHE WALK UP ON THE FLOOR,
♪ SHE LOOKING IN MY EYES, I GET
I GET LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ SHE LOOKING IN MY EYES, I GET
♪ SHE'S SEXY BODY, KILLED 'EM,
LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
I'M LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
♪ SHE'S SEXY BODY, KILLED 'EM,
♪ AI-TA-AI-AI-AI
I'M LOST IN THE DANCE ♪
>> ♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
♪ AI-TA-AI-AI-AI
♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
>> ♪ OH, WHOA, YEAH, YEAH
♪ YEAH