[ Wind Blowing ]
[ Thunder ]
[ Speaking Italian ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Grunts ]
What the hell
are you doing to me?
[ Speaking Italian ]
What are you doing?
[ Muffled ]
Goddamn it! Where am I?
A boat.
A fishing boat.
You were in the water.
We pull you out.
What water?
You were shot.
See? There are the bullets.
Ohh. Look. There is
a number for a bank.
Why was it in your hip?
My hip?
Yeah. In your hip
under the skin.
Uh. Oh, God!
You need to rest.
Wait. Please. Slow down.
I'm a friend.
I'm your friend. Huh?
My name is Giancarlo.
Who are you?
What's your name?
Uh, I don't know.
- Oh, God.
- [ Thud ]
[ Chattering ]
It's been confirmed, sir.
Mission failed.
[ Chattering ]
[ Bourne's Voice,
Speaking French ]
Speaking German ]
[ Speaking Italian ]
If you want to eat,
you better get in there.
Based on these charts, I think
I may have been closer to the coast.
What's this?
You tied these knots?
So it start
to come back, huh?
No, it doesn't start
to come back. The knot's
like everything else.
I just found the rope
and I did it.
The same way I can--
I can read, I can write.
I can add, subtract.
I can make coffee.
I can shuffle cards.
I can set up a chessboard.
Yes, yes. It will come back.
No, it's not coming back,
goddamn it! That's the point!
I'm down here
looking through all this shit.
For two weeks I'm down here.
It's not working. I don't
even know what to look for.
You need to rest.
It will come back.
What if it doesn't come back?
We get in there tomorrow,
I-I don't even have a name.
It's not much,
but it should get you
to Switzerland.
Thank you.
[ Woman On P.A., Indistinct ]
[ Speaking German ]
Hey.
All right.
No. I-I don't--
I don't have any papers.
I lost-- [ Speaking German ]
[ Gun Cocking ]
These people have threatened
my family, my babies.
So I'm telling you,
when the evidence is clear...
I will have a nice story
for you to read about.
And all my friends out there,
you will read about yourselves.
'Cause if you want
to play this game...
after I've been reasonable,
I will show you.
That's Nykwana Wombosi speaking
in Paris the day before yesterday.
He was an irritation
before he took power...
he was a problem when
he was in power and he's been
a disaster for us in exile.
He's writing a book about
the agency's history in Africa.
He's going to name names.
It's basically a shakedown.
He's demanding the agency's help.
He wants us to put him back
in power in six months or else.
This interview, and I'll
make the tape available
to anyone who wants it...
he goes on to claim
that he's just survived
an assassination attempt.
He says it's us.
He says he's got proof.
The director wants to know
if there's any possible shred of truth
in this accusation.
I've already assured him
there's nobody that reckless
on my senior staff.
[ Elevator Dings ]
I was recalling a conversation
we had some time ago,
talking about Treadstone.
I seem to remember
Nykwana Wombosi's name
might have come up.
I'm not sure
what we're talking about.
Someone tried to take him out.
Tried and failed.
Was this Treadstone?
You're asking me
a direct question?
Yes.
I thought you were
never gonna do that.
What happened?
Well, we, uh, lost
communication with our man.
This was almost
two weeks ago.
We've been working
around the clock, the whole unit.
We've been sleeping down there.
Believe me, we're doing
everything we can.
And you don't
let me know this?
You never wanted to before.
You never made
a mistake before.
[ Typing ]
Uh, yes. I'm here about
a numbered account.
If you just enter your account
number here, I'll direct you
to an appropriate officer.
[ Elevator Beeps ]
[ Speaking German ]
[ Beeps ]
My name is Jason Bourne.
I live in Paris.
[ Man Speaking German ]
[ Dialing ]
[ Bourne's Voice ]
Yes. In Paris. Do you have
the number for a Jason Bourne?
[ Woman's Voice ]
Yes, sir. Would you
like me to connect you?
Yes. Please.
[ Ringing ]
[ Beep ]
[ Bourne's Voice ]
This is 4-6-9-9-0-3-8-4.
Leave a message
at the beep.
[ Bourne's Voice,
Speaking French ]
[ Siren Blaring ]
[ Horn Blowing ]
[ Speaking German,
Faintly ]
[ Siren Blaring ]
I'm an American.
Okay.
Hold it. Wait.
You have no jurisdiction here.
[ Speaking German ]
No. Excuse me. No.
This is not my current
address, okay?
This was my current address
until two days ago...
when I started standing
in line outside.
Now, I lose my apartment,
okay? That means no address,
no phone, no money, no time.
- I still have no visa.
- Miss Kreutz, I'm gonna have to
ask you to keep your voice down.
[ Kreutz ]
Excuse me. But where's the guy
that I talked to last week?
Every week it's a new person.
How am I supposed to--
I don't know
who you saw last week.
Well, let me help you.
- I'm sure I have it. Hold on.
- Could I have your attention
for a moment, please?
[ Kreutz ]
It's right here. Look at it.
[ Man Speaking, Indistinct ]
This is a student visa now.
It's not about a green card anymore.
- It's completely different.
- It's not a menu, Miss Kreutz.
You don'tjust
pick what you want.
You! Red bag! The red bag!
Stop right there!
Put your hands up.!
[ Gasps ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Alarm Blaring ]
I'm on the east-- Ohh!
[ Man's Voice ]
Move it.! Now.! Now.!
Check. Clear!
[ Man's Voice ]
Bravo Unit moving up staircase.
Proceeding to second floor.
[ Alarm Continues Blaring ]
[ Man's Voice In Earphone,
Indistinct ]
- [ Woman Screams ]
- On the floor! Down!
Clear.!
[ Man ] Go.! Go.! Come on.!
He's in Zurich now?
Right now?
Yes. It just came in.
But they're sure?
Sure it's him?
Yes. He went to the bank.
Our source at the bank,
that's who called.
- Come on.
- He's got to assume we're
watching the bank, right?
I don't know. Come on.
I mean, he cleaned out
the box. He left the gun.
What does that mean?
I said I don't know.
I liked it better
when I thought he was dead.
[ Mumbling, Indistinct ]
Oh, Scheibe.
What are you looking at?
I heard you inside.
What?
The consulate. I heard
you talking. I thought maybe
we could help each other.
How's that?
You need money.
I need a ride out ofhere.
I'm not running a car service
just now. Thank you.
I'll give you $1 0,000
for driving me to Paris.
What is this, a joke?
Some kind of scam?
No, it's no scam.
And I'll give you another ten
when we get there.
[ Siren Blares ]
Jesus.
- Is that for you?
- Look. You drive, I pay.
It's that simple.
Scheibe.
I got enough trouble, okay?
Okay. Can I have
my money back?
[ Man ] All right, go.
Keep going. Go.
There. Wait.
[ Man #2 ] No. It's
got to be near the end.
Oh, come on, folks.
We caught a break here. Let's go.
Okay, I'm up.
We're getting grids.
Airline, train, hotels--
Did you get the address?
The street?
Gemeinschaft.
- Here we go.
- I got it. I think I got it.
Is it him?
Unreal.
This is 38 minutes ago.
Hey, Zurich police are looking
for an American man carrying
a red bank bag.
Hejust tore up the embassy,
and he put two cops
in the hospital last night.
Get everybody up. Do it now.
I want them all activated.
All of them?
At the same time?
You heard me. I want Bourne
in a body bag by sundown.
Let's get a map up here.
Come on, folks. Work it.
Take a look.
The grids are good info.
[ Beeping ]
[ Kreutz's Voice,
Indistinct ]
[ Kreutz ] Which was fiine for me,
because I was ready.
You know, because, I mean,
after six months in Amsterdam...
you're not sure if you've been
there 20 minutes or 20 years,
if you know what I mean.
So I went and I took
all the money I had...
and I went in with friends
and we took over this really
cool surf shop outside Biarritz...
um, which was
right by the water;
it was amazing.
It was just amazing
for about three months...
until it turned out
that this, uh,jerk who
had found us the lease...
was actually shining
everyone on and-- [ Sighs ]
And what?
What do you mean what?
Listen to me.
I've been speed-talking
for about 60 kilometers now.
I talk when I'm nervous.
I mean, I talk like this
when I'm nervous.
I'm gonna shut up now.
No. Don't do that.
I haven't talked
to anybody in a while.
Yeah, but we're not talking.
I'm talking.
You've said, like, ten words
since we left Zurich.
Well, listening to you,
um, it's relaxing.
I haven't slept
in a while and--
and I've had this headache.
It's like a constant thing
inside my head.
And it's just starting
to move to the background, so...
keep going.
Really. If you want,
please keep talking.
Okay.
[ Chuckles ]
What kind of music
do you like?
Huh? What do you like?
Come on.
Um--
[ Turns On Radio ]
You know what, never mind.
No. It's fine. Tell me.
[ Switching Channels ]
What do you want
to listen to?
I don't know.
Come on.
It's not that hard.
What do you like?
Tell me.
I don't know.
[ Turns Off Radio ]
Who pays $20,000
for a ride to Paris?
Fuck it. I can't remember
anything that happened
before two weeks ago.
Lucky you.
No. I'm serious.
I don't know who I am.
I don't know where I'm going.
None of it.
What, like, amnesia?
Yes.
Amnesia?
Great.
- That's the best angle
of the courtyard?
- That's the only angle.
Well, what do they have
of the streets or the area?
They must
have something.
Hang on.
[ Typing ]
Oh, what is he doing?
Is it a game?
Is he warning us?
Is it a threat?
Sir, look at this.
What's that?
It's an angle of the street.
It's some sort of alley.
Just enhance it.
[ Typing ]
Who the hell is that?
Marie Helena Kreutz.
She's 26.
Born outside of Hannover.
Father was a welder.
He died in '87.
Still don't have the mother.
The grandmother,
she's still there in Hannover...
and looks like
she's the anchor for this
little domestic disaster.
And there's a stepbrother.
It's tough. The girl's a gypsy.
She pops up on the grid
here and there,
but it's chaotic at best.
She paid some electric bills
in Spain, '95...
had a phone in her name for
three months in Belgium, '96.
No taxes, no credit.
I don't like her.
I want to go deep.
Get a phone log for granny
and the half brother...
anybody we can cross-file.
I want to know every place
she's slept in the past six years.
Have Paris get these
out in the field.
[ Typing ]
[ Bourne ]
I'm not making this up.
These are real.
Okay.
Who has a safety
deposit box full of...
money and six passports
and a gun?
Who has a bank account number
in their hip?
I come in here...
and the first thing I'm doing
is I'm catching the sight lines
and looking for an exit.
I see the exit sign too.
I'm not worried.
I mean, you were shot.
People do all kinds
of weird and amazing stuff
when they're scared.
I can tell you
the license plate numbers
of all six cars outside.
I can tell that
our waitress is left-handed...
and the guy sitting up at
the counter weighs 21 5 pounds
and knows how to handle himself.
I know the best place
to look for a gun is the cab
of the gray truck outside.
And at this altitude, I can
run flat-out for a half mile
before my hands start shaking.
Now why would I know that?
How can I know that
and not know who I am?
Hey.
Ah, I slept.
I can't believe it.
Yeah. Well, you were tired.
I haven't slept.
Oh. Here. For 20,000,
I like to throw in breakfast.
Did you stop for gas?
[ Sighs ]
You were
pretty out of it.
Yeah.
Ohh.
So, do you think there's,
like, a family waiting for you?
I don't know.
I haven't
thought about it.
[ Kreutz ] Is that it?
One-o-four.
Yeah, that's it. That's the address.
No, no. Keep going.
Keep going.
Okay.
Where?
Just, uh,just take a left.
Go on over here.
So this is it, right?
Yeah. I guess.
Yeah, but I don't
recognize any of this.
Okay. You should go.
Jason.
Oh, God. Money. Right.
Yeah.
Here.
Danke, okay?
Thanks for the ride.
Anytime.
Well, you could come up
and you can--
Or you could wait here.
I can go check it out,
but you could wait--
Uh, no, no. No, no.
Um, with you, you would
probably just forget
about me if I stayed here.
How could I forget about you?
You're the only person I know.
Yeah. That's true.
[ Buzzes ]
I guess you're not home.
[ Speaking French ]
Hello?
You sure this
is all yours?
I guess.
[ Beeping ]
[ Clanks ]
This is my kitchen.
- Any clues?
- I think I'm in
the shipping business.
So it's all
coming back, huh?
Do you mind
if I use the bathroom?
- Uh, sure.
- Okay.
[ Beeps, Dialing ]
[ Woman Speaking French ]
Uh, yeah. Hello? Hello?
Yes, sir.
Hotel Regina, Paris.
How may I direct your call?
Yeah. You're in Paris?
Yes, sir.
I'm looking for
a, uh, guest there.
Uh,Jason Bourne.
One moment, please.
Thank you.
I'm afraid I have no one
by that name registered, sir.
Uh, okay. Uh, thank you.
Uh, wait. No, no, no.
Uh, are you there? Hello?
Sir?
Uh, can you check another,
uh, name for me, please?
Uh, bear with me one second.
Um...
uh,John Michael Kane.
Kane with a ''K.''
One moment, sir.
Thank you.
[ Man ]
You call about Monsieur Kane?
John Michael Kane?
Uh, yeah. That's right.
You are a friend of his?
Uh, uh-huh. Yep.
I have some very
bad news for you, sir.
I'm terribly sorry
to tell you this...
but Monsieur Kane
has passed away
almost two weeks ago.
There was an accident
on the motorway.
Apparently,
he was killed instantly.
Really. I'm terribly sorry
to be the one to tell you this.
When they came for his things,
people made note for us, you see?
- Who-Who came?
- His brother.
Did his, uh, brother leave
a number or a way to get
in touch with him?
I think not.
So I'm sorry--
[ Water Running ]
[ Kreutz ]
Uh,Jason?
There's no hot water.
It's freezing.
Uh, I'll go, uh, try
the water in the kitchen.
Why don't you just stay
in the bathroom? I'll-I'll
see if I can... get it hot.
Yeah, it's really
cold in here too.
The water is still cold.
Yeah, it's cold
in the, uh, kitchen too.
I got it running though.
So--
What?
Nothing.
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
What is it?
Something wrong?
[ Machine Gun Fire ]
Jason!
Open that.! Open that.!
Tell me what's inside.
Who are you?
[ Speaking French ]
[ Bourne Speaking French ]
Oh, my God.
- [ Bourne Speaking German ]
- Ohh.
[ Bourne ]
Answer me.! Who are you?
- He's got my picture.
- All right.Just... stop.
[ Babbling, Indistinct ]
No, no, no!
I don't-- How--
Where did you get this?
Stay there.! Stay there.!
How did you get my picture?
Marie, stay there. Come on.
Where did you get this from?
How did you get--
Don't do this. I'll do this.
You stay there. Stay there.
[ Grunts ]
But he--
[ Thud ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ People Screaming ]
[ Horns Honking ]
Where are your shoes?
Get your shoes.
Sure. Yeah. Sure.
Uh, he went out the window.
Why would someone do that?
We can't stay here.
It's not safe.
Look, I can get us out ofhere,
but we got to go.
We got to go right now.
Okay. Look, uh,
you could wait.
You could wait
for the cops. It's okay.
You just wait for them
to get here, but I can't.
I got to go.
[ Siren Approaching ]
Marie?
[ Kreutz ]
Ohh.! Ohh.!
Quiet. Quiet.
[ Vomits ]
- Don't look.
- [ Siren Approaching ]
[ Dialing ]
[ Man's Voice ] Code in.
Alpha three-seven-
five-zero-nine.
[ Rings ]
Yeah?
Hang on.
Bourne, he went to Paris.
He went to the apartment.
We got him? Tell me.
[ Woman ]
He killed our man.
What? In the apartment?
Yeah.
Well, you got to clean that up.
No, I can't clean it up.
There's a body
in the streets.
So?
There's police.
This is Paris.
Put up the scanners.
Get as much radio
information as you can.
Okay. You stay here. I'll go
find a place for this money.
I'll be back in ten minutes.
[ Woman On P.A.
Speaking French ]
Hey. I told you
to stay in the car.
Jesus Christ.
I told you to stay in the car.
I needed a drink.
I didn't think you would
come back anyway.
You got to go to the cops.
Right now.
You got to go before
this gets any worse.
By myself?
It's gonna be okay.
Take my passport, okay?
You show this to them.
You have that picture.
You have the 20,000.
You tell them everything
that happened. Everything.
They're gonna believe you.
They have to believe you.
Marie, you can't just sit here.
It's not safe here.
Safe? This is from
inside the embassy.
Who can do this?
This is from yesterday.
I-I don't know.
How can they even know
that we're together?
Look, I'm trying to do
the right thing for you,
okay? Just--
Try-- How are you gonna
make this right...
by sending me there alone?
Do you think I want you
to go to the cops?
You think that's
good for me?
You want to go, fine.
You go to the cops,
I gotta run.
You tell them what happened.
I don't know what happened!
I don't know who this guy was!
I don't know about that picture!
I don't know who I am!
Look, I'm-- You're acting like
I'm trying to burn you here.
- I'm just trying
to do the right thing.
- Nobody does the right thing.
Look, I can't
run with you. I can't--
We run-- I gotta live
like this. I gotta--
I don't even know
who I'm hiding from.
These people know who I am.
Now I gotta--
I gotta stay here.
I gotta figure this out.
So figure it out.
You take care
of this car?
What do you mean?
Tires felt a little splashy
on the way over here.
It pulls a little to the right.
[ Siren Approaching ]
Last chance, Marie.
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Siren ]
So...
What?
uh, we got a bump
coming up.
[ Screaming ]
[ Horn Honking ]
Turn your head away.
[ Horns Honking ]
- Ohh!
- [ Yelling ]
[ Turns Engine Off]