[cheers and applause]
- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
PLEASE WELCOME AZIZ ANSARI!
[cheers and applause]
- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
WHOA, WHOA.
OH, WOW.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THAT'S SO NICE OF YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU.
I RECENTLY MOVED
TO LOS ANGELES AND, YOU KNOW,
A BIG ISSUE HERE AND EVERYWHERE
IN THE COUNTRY RIGHT NOW
IS GAY RIGHTS.
AND I WAS WALKING DOWN
THE STREET ONCE,
AND THIS GUY CAME UP
TO ME WITH A CLIPBOARD.
AND HE GOES, "HEY, MAN.
DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT
FOR GAY RIGHTS?"
AND I WENT, "SORRY, MAN.
I'M IN A LITTLE BIT OF A RUSH."
AND THEN THAT DUDE WATCHED ME
WALK INTO A JAMBA JUICE.
AND HE WAS A LITTLE UPSET.
HE WAS LIKE, "REALLY, MAN?
"YOU'RE IN A RUSH TO GET
TO JAMBA JUICE?
I'M OUT HERE TRYING
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"WELL, ACTUALLY, MAN,
"THERE'S A GUY THAT WORKS
IN THAT JAMBA JUICE
"THAT SAID SOME REALLY
HATEFUL STUFF
"ABOUT A CLOSE
GAY FRIEND OF MINE
AND I'M GOING
IN THERE TO STAB HIM."
[laughter]
AND THEN I PULLED OUT
TWO KNIVES
AND I TOSSED HIM ONE.
I WAS LIKE, "DO YOU HAVE
A MOMENT FOR GAY RIGHTS?
"OH, DIDN'T THINK SO.
"SO SIT THERE WITH YOUR LITTLE
CLIPBOARD AND JUDGE ME.
"I KILL FOR GAY PEOPLE.
I MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
YOU DON'T DO SHIT."
[laughter]
I ACTUALLY HAD A GAY FRIEND
OF MINE GET REAL MAD AT ME
'CAUSE OF A TEXT MESSAGE
I SENT HIM.
AND I LOOKED AT MY PHONE
AND I REALIZED
IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
IT WAS MY PHONE'S FAULT.
I GOT THAT FEATURE ON THERE
CALLED SMART TYPE,
WHERE YOU TYPE THINGS AND IT
GUESSES WHAT YOU'RE TYPING.
BUT SOMETIMES
IT GUESSES WRONG.
LIKE, YOU'LL TYPE IN "GAVE."
IT'LL GUESS "HAVE."
TEXTS GET MISINTERPRETED.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED TO ME.
WHAT I WAS TRYING TO SEND
MY GAY FRIEND GREG
WAS A TEXT THAT SAID,
"HEY, GREG.
"DON'T THINK I CAN COME
TO THE BAR.
TIRED.
GONNA HIT THE HAY."
THAT'S WHAT I WAS TRYING
TO SEND.
BUT WHAT SMART TYPE DECIDED
TO SEND WAS, "HEY, GREG.
"DON'T THINK I CAN COME
TO THE BAR. TIRED.
GONNA HIT THE HAY, YOU FAGGOT.
FUCK YOU."
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
SMART TYPE, THAT AIN'T
WHAT I WAS TRYING TO SAY!
WHY YOU GETTING
ALL HOMOPHOBIC ON ME?
GREG'S GONNA PISSED OFF
ABOUT THAT TEXT!
[laughter]
NOW MY WHOLE TAKE ON, YOU KNOW,
THE GAY RIGHTS ISSUES,
PARTICULARLY GAY MARRIAGE IS--
LET'S BE HONEST.
IF YOU'RE AGAINST GAY MARRIAGE,
YOU JUST DON'T LIKE GAY PEOPLE,
AND YOU WANT
TO STICK IT TO 'EM.
AND I'M NOT SAYING I WOULDN'T
DO THE SAME THING
IF I WAS PRESENTED
WITH SIMILAR OPPORTUNITIES.
LIKE IF THERE WAS A LAW UP
FOR DEBATE WHERE IT WAS LIKE,
"HEY, MAN, YOU THINK GUYS THAT
WEAR TIGHT T-SHIRTS
"AND GET BOTTLE SERVICE
AT NIGHTCLUBS SHOULD
BE ALLOWED TO OWN PROPERTY?"
I'D BE LIKE, "NO!
FUCK THOSE GUYS!"
HA-HA-HA-HA!
YEAH, UM...
IT VIOLATES THE SANCTITY
OF OWNING PROPERTY
AND IT SAYS IN THE BIBLE
THEY'RE DOUCHEBAGS.
WHATEVER I NEED TO SAY
SO YOU DON'T THINK
THIS IS COMING FROM PURELY
A PLACE OF HATE.
[laughter]
I WAS GETTING SOME SHEETS DOWN
AT BED BATH & BEYOND.
MAN, THEY GOT SO MANY SHEETS!
I WAS LOOKING AROUND
AND I SAW THIS GUY
AND HE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO BUY,
AND HE LOOKED ALL CONFUSED.
AND HE LOOKS OVER
AT ME AND GOES,
"MAN, THIS IS WHY
I NEED A GIRLFRIEND."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"REALLY?
THIS IS WHY YOU NEED
A GIRLFRIEND?"
SO IF YOU HAD A GIRLFRIEND,
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN BE HERE.
YOU'D BE BACK AT YOUR HOUSE
SITTING ON A LA-Z-BOY,
DRINKING A BEER, GOING,
"BITCH, GO GET ME SOME SHEETS!
"YEAH, I'M IN
A RELATIONSHIP NOW!
"I DON'T HAVE TO BUY
MY OWN DOMESTIC GOODS!
"PICK UP ONE OF THOSE BOTTLES
WE CAN PUT STICKS IN
"AND MAKE THE ROOM
SMELL LIKE VANILLA BEAN.
"I BEEN FARTING ALL DAY.
IT SMELLS LIKE SHIT
IN HERE!"
[laughter]
NOW ALL I KNOW
ABOUT SHEETS IS...
THE HIGHER THE THREAD COUNT,
THE BETTER THE SHEET, RIGHT?
THIS LADY'S LIKE,
"RIGHT. YEAH.
"I GOT 700 BACK AT MY HOUSE.
IT'S LIKE SLEEPING
IN LOTION."
SO I'M LOOKING AROUND,
TRYING TO FIND SOME NICE SHEETS.
I SEE THIS BRAND CALLED
HOTEL LUXURY LINENS.
600-THREAD COUNT.
THAT SOUNDS FANCY TOO, RIGHT?
GOT A GIRL BACK AT YOUR PLACE,
SHE'S LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
DID WE JUST TELEPORT
TO A FIVE-STAR HOTEL?"
NAH, BABY.
THESE ARE JUST HOTEL
LUXURY LINENS.
BY THE WAY, THE TECHNOLOGY
FOR TELEPORTATION
DOESN'T EXIST YET.
YOU MUST BE KIND OF STUPID.
SO I GRABBED THE SHEETS
AND I GET 'EM HOME.
AND I'M PSYCHED
TO PUT 'EM ON MY BED, RIGHT?
AND I FEEL 'EM AND THEY FEEL
A LITTLE ROUGH TO THE TOUCH.
I GET A LITTLE SUSPICIOUS.
I DO A LITTLE GOOGLING.
I FIND AN
INVESTIGATIVE REPORT
IN SOUTHERN LIVING MAGAZINE,
WHERE THEY INVESTIGATED
THREAD COUNT CLAIMS,
AN ISSUE THAT DEFINITELY
NEEDED DELVING INTO.
AND THEY HAD A LITTLE CHART,
AND IT SAID "BRAND,
ADVERTISED THREAD COUNT,
ACTUAL THREAD COUNT."
SO IT'S LIKE,
"BRAND, WAMSUTTA.
"ADVERTISED, 500.
ACTUAL, 497.
"BRAND, SOFT SHEETS.
ADVERTISED, 600.
"ACTUAL, 600.
"BRAND, HOTEL LUXURY LINENS.
"ADVERTISED, 600.
ACTUAL...
296!"
ARE YOU SHITTIN' ME,
MAN?
I ALMOST SLEPT
ON THAT SHIT!
296 IS SANDPAPER
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
IF THAT WAS A DRUG DEAL,
I WOULD HAVE SHOT
HOTEL LUXURY LINENS
IN THE FACE.
WHERE THE REST
OF MY THREADS?
[imitates gunshot]
YOU DIDN'T THINK
I WAS GONNA
COUNT THAT SHIT,
MOTHERFUCKER?
[laughter and applause]
I WAS DOWN AT CVS,
AND I HAD
A RATHER ODD ASSORTMENT
OF ITEMS I NEEDED TO GET.
I HAD TO GET A LITER
OF JACK DANIELS,
A TWO-LITER BOTTLE
OF COCA-COLA,
A BOX OF CONDOMS,
AND A TEN-PACK
OF BLANK CDR DISCS.
AND I THOUGHT IT'D BE AWESOME
IF EVERY MORNING
I WENT AND BOUGHT
THOSE SAME FOUR THINGS
FOR, LIKE,
SIX MONTHS,
JUST TO DEVELOP THIS REALLY
WEIRD REPUTATION
WITH THE STAFF THERE,
WHERE THEY'D BE LIKE,
"HOLD ON A SECOND, MAN.
"THIS GUY DRINKS A LITER
OF JACK AND COKE EVERY DAY.
"HAS SEX 12 TIMES A DAY.
"AND THEN BURNS
TEN BLANK CDs?
"TEN BLANK CDs?
"10 DISCS,
THAT'S LIKE 7.5 GIGS A DAY.
"WHAT KIND OF DATA'S
HE BACKING UP?
"WOULD IT MAKE MORE SENSE
JUST TO GET
"AN EXTERNAL HARD DRIVE
AT THIS POINT?
"IS HE BURNING MUSIC?
"WOULDN'T IT MAKE MORE SENSE
JUST TO GET AN IPOD?
"MAYBE HE'S MAKING MIXED CDs
FOR ALL THESE GIRLS
"THAT HE'S FUCKIN'.
"TWO OF THOSE GIRLS AIN'T
GETTING CDs THOUGH.
"WHICH TWO ARE THOSE?
WHICH TWO DON'T
GET THE CDs?"
[laughter]
I GOT TO TRAVEL A LOT
WHEN I'M DOING STAND-UP,
AND I WAS ON A FLIGHT
ONE TIME
AND I HAD A LITTLE BIT
OF A RUNNY NOSE.
AND SO I WENT LIKE THIS...
[sniffs]
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
THE GUY NEXT TO ME GOES,
"HEY, MAN!
"YOU GONNA BLOW YOUR NOSE,
OR AM I GONNA
"HAVE TO LISTEN
TO YOU HAVE THE SNIFFLES
FOR SIX FUCKING HOURS?"
AND I WAS STUNNED
FOR TWO REASONS.
ONE, I COULDN'T BELIEVE HE'D
BE SO RUDE TO A TOTAL STRANGER.
AND TWO, I NEVER HEARD
THE WORD "SNIFFLES"
AND "FUCKING" IN THE SAME
SENTENCE TOGETHER BEFORE.
[laughter and applause]
[chuckles]
CLAP IF YOU USE CRAIGSLIST.
[cheers and applause]
HOLD ON A SECOND THOUGH.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT LIKE,
"OH, HEY,
I'M LOOKING FOR AN APARTMENT,"
CRAIGSLIST.
I'M TALKING ABOUT,
"GIVE ME A HANDJOB,
I'LL GIVE YOU
MY COFFEE TABLE."
LIKE THAT KIND OF CRAIGSLIST.
THAT'S CRAIGSLIST.
I SAW A POST LIKE
THAT ONCE
WHERE THIS GUY WAS TRYING
TO SELL CONCERT TICKETS
AND THIS IS WHAT
HE POSTED UP THERE.
HE GOES, "WILLING
TO GIVE UP TWO TICKETS
"FOR THE SOLD-OUT
SHOW TONIGHT.
"MUST BE FEMALE,
AGE 20 TO 25,
"AND BE WILLING
TO PERFORM ORAL SEX
"FOR A HALF HOUR
IN MY CAR.
"MUST REMOVE SHIRT
AND BRA.
YOUR FRIEND CAN
BE THERE FOR SECURITY."
[laughter]
NOW THAT GUY'S INSANE
AND YOU CAN TELL,
'CAUSE HE PUT THAT PHRASE
IN THERE.
"MUST REMOVE SHIRT AND BRA."
'CAUSE THAT IMPLIES
HE'S DONE THIS IN THE PAST
AND THE GIRL WAS LIKE,
"HOLD ON!
YOU DIDN'T SAY NOTHING ABOUT MY
SHIRT AND BRA COMING OFF."
HE'S LIKE, "DAMN, I GOTTA
REMEMBER TO PUT THAT
"IN THE AD NEXT TIME.
I WANT TO SEE SOME TITTIES."
[laughter and applause]
AND THEN HE ACTS LIKE HE'S
THROWING YOU A BONE
BY PUTTING THAT PHRASE
IN THERE.
"YOUR FRIEND CAN
BE THERE FOR SECURITY."
REALLY?
WELL, THAT'S GONNA BE
A TOUGH FAVOR TO ASK FOR.
"HEY, DENISE.
"YEAH, IT'S ME, CAROL.
"LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
"YOU EVER DONE
ANY SECURITY WORK BEFORE?
"WELL,
IT'S NOTHING TOO CRAZY,
"BUT I'M GONNA
BE BLOWING THIS GUY
"FOR A HALF HOUR
IN HIS CAR,
"AND I JUST NEED YOU
TO SIT IN THE BACK SEAT
"AND MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T
DO ANYTHING SKETCHY.
"BY THE WAY, YOU MIND HOLDING
MY SHIRT AND BRA?
THOSE WILL BE OFF!"
[laughter]
NOW, I WENT TO THAT CONCERT.
I GOT TICKETS IN ADVANCE
AND I GOT THERE
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I SAW?
THEY WERE SELLING EXTRA TICKETS
AT THE DOOR.
SELLING EXTRA TICKETS
AT THE DOOR!
COULD YOU IMAGINE BLOWING
A GUY FOR A HALF HOUR
FOR SOLD-OUT CONCERT TICKETS AND
THEN FINDING OUT
THEY'RE SELLING THEM
AT THE DOOR?
THAT'D BE LIKE BLOWING A GUY
FOR A HALF HOUR
FOR SOLD-OUT CONCERT TICKETS
AND THEN FINDING OUT
THEY'RE SELLING 'EM
AT THE DOOR.
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY
TO COMPLETE THAT ANALOGY
'CAUSE THAT'S THE SHITTIEST
THING THAT COULD EVER
HAPPEN TO YOU.
[laughter and applause]
ONE THING THAT SCARES ME ABOUT,
LIKE, CRAIGSLIST AND STUFF
IS THAT PEOPLE GO ON THERE AND
THEY FIND RANDOM ROOMMATES.
THAT'S A TERRIFYING
PROPOSITION TO ME.
LIKE, THE ONE TIME I HAD
A RANDOM ROOMMATE,
IT DID NOT GO WELL.
LIKE, I WOULD COME
IN THE ROOM
AND IT'D ALWAYS SMELL
LIKE TUNA.
AND I'D BE LIKE,
"WHOA!
"NOT IN MY TOP FIVE SMELLS
FOR THE ROOM TO HAVE.
WHY'S IT ALWAYS SMELL
LIKE TUNA?"
AND IT'S 'CAUSE THIS GUY
WILL EAT CANS
OF STARKIST TUNA
ALL THE TIME.
AND YOU KNOW ALL THE JUICES
THERE AT THE BOTTOM
WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED?
HE'D SHOOT THE JUICE BACK
LIKE A TEQUILA SHOT.
YES, I AGREE
IT'S DISGUSTING.
IF YOU'D APPROACHED ME
ON THE STREET LIKE,
"HEY, AZIZ.
"WHAT'S THE MOST
DISGUSTING THING
YOU CAN CATCH YOUR
NEW ROOMMATE DOING?"
I'D BE LIKE,
"DRINKING THE TUNA JUICE
AT THE BOTTOM
OF A STARKIST TUNA CAN."
THEY'D BE LIKE, "MAN, THAT'S
A REALLY SPECIFIC ANSWER."
THERE'S OTHER THINGS LIKE
HE PLAYED THE FLUTE
ALL THE TIME.
NOTHING WRONG
WITH PLAYING THE FLUTE,
BUT HE'D ONLY PLAY
ONE SONG ON THE FLUTE.
CELINE DION'S
MY HEART WILL GO ON,
THE THEME SONG TO TITANIC.
IF YOU'D APPROACH ME
ON THE STREET LIKE, "HEY, AZIZ,
"WHAT'S THE MOST
ANNOYING SONG A DUDE
COULD PLAY ON THE FLUTE
ALL THE TIME?"
I'D BE LIKE, "CELINE DION'S
MY HEART WILL GO ON,
THE THEME SONG TO TITANIC."
AND YOU'D BE LIKE,
"GOD DAMN,
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD
AT THIS GAME."
BUT THE CRAZIEST THING
WAS TOWARDS
THE END OF OUR TIME
TOGETHER.
HE WAS ACTING REALLY WEIRD
AND I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING ON,
SO I ASKED A FRIEND OF HIS.
I WAS LIKE, "HEY, MAN,
WHAT'S UP WITH THIS GUY?"
AND HE GOES,
"OH...
"HE THINKS
HE'S POSSESSED
BY SCAR, THE EVIL LION FROM
THE LION KING MOVIES."
OH, YES!
THAT HAPPENS! SURE!
IF YOU'D APPROACHED ME
ON THE STREET LIKE, "HEY, AZIZ.
"WHAT'S THE MOST RANDOM
DISNEY VILLAIN
A KID COULD THINK
HE'S POSSESSED BY?"
I'D BE LIKE, "SCAR, THE EVIL
LION FROM THE LION KING MOVIES."
AND YOU'D BE LIKE...
[imitates buzzer]
"SORRY, IT'S ACTUALLY
THE HOCKEY TEAM FROM ICELAND
IN THE MIGHTY DUCKS 2."
[laughter and applause]
NOW...
I HAVE A SMALL UPDATE
ON THAT JOKE.
I WAS LOOKING AROUND
ON THE INTERNET ONE DAY,
AND I SAW THIS BLOG
HAD WRITTEN ABOUT ME.
I LOOKED IN THE COMMENTS THREAD
AND SOME GUY HAD WRITTEN,
"I LIVED WITH THIS GUY.
HE'S A DOUCHEBAG."
IT WAS THAT FUCKING GUY!
OH, REALLY?
I'M A DOUCHEBAG, HUH?
WELL, YOU DON'T TELL ALL
THESE PEOPLE ABOUT
HOW YOU DID TUNA JUICE SHOTS
ALL DAY.
[imitates flute playing]
OH, YOU DON'T TALK
ABOUT THAT.
YOU JUST SAY
I'M A DOUCHEBAG.
WELL, IF I'M A DOUCHEBAG,
THIS IS WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
I'M GONNA FIND OUT WHERE
THAT GUY LIVES, RIGHT?
I'M GONNA GO OUTSIDE HIS HOUSE,
LIKE, OUTSIDE HIS WINDOW
REAL LATE AT NIGHT,
RIGHT?
AND WAIT TILL IT'S,
LIKE, REALLY LATE
AND I'M JUST GONNA GO,
[singing in tongues]
AND HE'D BE LIKE,
"NO! THE DEMONS!
"THEY'RE BACK!
SCAR, GET AWAY FROM ME!
LEAVE ME ALONE!"
WHAT I SHOULD HAVE DONE IS JUST
WENT ON THE COMMENTS THREAD
UNDER THE USERNAME "HYENAS"
AND WROTE,
"WATCH OUT,
MOTHERFUCKER!"
[laughter and applause]
I USED TO LIVE IN NEW YORK
AND I LOVE LIVING THERE
'CAUSE YOU CAN WALK
AROUND EVERYWHERE.
AND, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WALK AROUND,
SOMETIMES PEOPLE
RECOGNIZE ME FROM THINGS
THEY'VE SEEN ME ON TV
OR WHATEVER AND THEY'D SAY,
YOU KNOW, STUFF,
AND A LOT OF TIMES
I WOULDN'T HEAR WHAT THEY SAID
'CAUSE I'D HAVE HEADPHONES ON.
SO I'D KIND OF JUST GO,
"COOL, MAN.
GLAD YOU LIKE THE SHOW,"
AND I'D JUST KEEP WALKING.
AND THIS ONE GUY SAID
SOMETHING TO ME ONE TIME
AND I WENT, "COOL, MAN.
GLAD YOU LIKE THE SHOW."
AND THEN RIGHT WHEN I WALKED
PAST HIM, I REALIZED,
"OH, MAN, THAT GUY DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT THE SHOW."
HE WENT, "HEY, MAN,
YOUR FLY'S DOWN."
AND I WENT, "COOL, MAN.
GLAD YOU LIKE THE SHOW.
"GLAD YOU LIKE SEEING MY DICK
POP OUT OF MY PANTS.
COME BACK NEXT WEEK,
YOU CAN SEE ONE OF MY BALLS."
[laughter]
I WENT TO A COOL SHOW
IN NEW YORK ONCE
CALLED WALKING WITH DINOSAURS.
AND IT WAS THIS THING
WHERE THEY HAD THESE, LIKE,
ANIMATRONIC DINOSAURS THAT
WOULD, LIKE, WALK AROUND.
IT WAS REALLY COOL.
BUT I WAS THE ONLY PERSON THERE
REALLY IN MY AGE GROUP.
IT WAS MOSTLY, LIKE,
LITTLE KIDS AND THEIR PARENTS.
AND I WAS BORED WAITING
FOR THE SHOW TO START,
SO I STARTED TALKING
TO THIS LITTLE KID NEXT TO ME,
AND HE WAS PRETTY COOL.
HE WAS, LIKE,
MAYBE EIGHT, TEN YEARS OLD.
WE HAD A LOT IN COMMON THOUGH,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE, WE BOTH PLAYED
CALL OF DUTY 4 ON THE XBOX.
WE BOTH REALLY
HAD SIMILAR THEORIES
ABOUT WHAT WAS REALLY
GOING ON ON LOST.
AND HE WAS JUST A COOL KID.
AND EVENTUALLY HIS DAD WAS LIKE,
"HEY, BRIAN,
"I'M GONNA GO MAKE
A COUPLE PHONE CALLS.
"YOU THINK YOU'LL
BE ALL RIGHT HERE
TALKING TO YOUR NEW FRIEND?"
HE'S LIKE, "OKAY, DAD."
AND THE DAD LEAVES FOR, LIKE,
A REALLY LONG TIME.
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
A CHILD MOLESTER AT ALL.
BUT IF I WAS,
I'D HAVE BEEN LIKE,
"SOMEBODY'S DOING
SOME MOLESTIN' TONIGHT!
"LET'S DO THIS SHIT,
BRIAN!
"YOUR DAD DOESN'T
GIVE A FUCK ABOUT YOU!
"HE LEFT YOU ALONE
WITH A GROWN MAN
"WITH A FULL BEARD
AT WALKING WITH DINOSAURS!
"CLEARLY
I'M OUT HERE SCOUTING
AND YOU ARE MY MAN!"
[laughter and applause]
I'M JUST SAYING
I COULD HAVE FUCKED THAT KID.
[laughter]
I'M ORIGINALLY
FROM SOUTH CAROLINA, AND--
[scattered cheers]
THANK YOU.
AND MY BROTHER
SENT ME SOMETHING
THAT REALLY REMINDED ME OF HOW
CRAZY IT IS DOWN THERE.
IT WAS A PROMO VIDEO
FOR THIS THING CALLED
"THE SIMPLE MAN CRUISE."
AND THIS IS THIS CRUISE SHIP
WHERE THEY GET
ALL THESE SOUTHERN ROCK BANDS
LIKE .38 SPECIAL,
THE MARSHALL TUCKER BAND,
LYNYRD SKYNYRD
AND THEY THROW 'EM ON A BOAT.
ALL THESE REDNECKS
GET ON BOARD,
THEY SET OUT TO SEA,
AND IT'S SCARY AS SHIT!
'CAUSE I'VE NEVER SEEN REDNECKS
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I LIVED IN SOUTH CAROLINA
FOR 18 YEARS.
NEVER SAW PEOPLE LIKE THIS.
THIS ONE DUDE GETS ON
THE SCREEN, HE'S LIKE,
"AW, HELL, MAN.
"YOU CAN SWING
A DEAD CAT AROUND HERE,
YOU BOUND TO HIT
A GOOD GUITAR PLAYER."
WHAT THE HELL
DOES THAT MEAN?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I LIKE
THE WAY THIS GUY TALKS.
I WANT HIM TO REVIEW EVERYTHING
FOR ME IN MY LIFE.
LIKE WHEN I NEED AN OPINION,
I'LL GO TO HIM.
I'LL BE LIKE,
"HEY, MAN, I WAS THINKING
"ABOUT BUYING SOME CDs
AT THAT MUSIC STORE
"DOWN ON, LIKE, SUNSET.
IS THAT A GOOD PLACE
TO BUY MUSIC?"
"AW, HELL, MAN.
"YOU CAN GO IN THERE
AND SLING A POT
"OF CREAMED CORN,
SOME OF IT'S BOUND
"TO LAND ON SOME GREAT NEW
AND USED CDs.
"YOU MIGHT GET A LITTLE CORN
ON YOUR CDs,
"BUT THAT'S EASY
TO CLEAN OFF,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU HAVE
A BISCUIT."
[laughter]
OKAY, MAN.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
BUYING A PRIUS.
IS THAT A GOOD CAR TO GET?
"AW, MAN,
HERE'S WHAT YOU NEED TO DO.
"RUN DOWN TO THE WOODS,
FIND TWO DEAD POSSUMS,
"PICK 'EM UP,
TURN 'EM INTO PUPPETS,
"BE LIKE, 'HEY, MAN,
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
"'BUYING A PRIUS.
THAT A GOOD CAR TO GET?'
"'I DON'T KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT CARS.
"I'M JUST A POSSUM.'
TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
YEAH."
[laughter]
UH, HEY, MAN.
I WAS SEEING
ABOUT BUYING AN LCD TV.
IS IT A GOOD TIME
TO BUY AN LCD TV?
"HERE'S WHAT
YOU NEED TO DO, MAN.
"GO DOWN TO THAT ELECTRONICS
STORE IN LA BREA,
"JERK OFF ON 12 BISCUITS,
SLING 'EM AROUND,
"ONE OF THEM'S BOUND
TO HIT A GREAT LCD TV.
"YOU MIGHT CATCH A LITTLE HELL
FOR WHAT YOU DID
TO THOSE BISCUITS, BUT YOU'RE
GONNA GET A GREAT DEAL."
[laughter]
HOW MANY OF YOU GUYS--
CLAP IF YOU STILL HAVEN'T SEEN
THE DARK KNIGHT YET.
IF YOU STILL HAVEN'T SEEN
THE DARK KNIGHT, CLAP.
[sparse clapping]
WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG
WITH YOU PEOPLE?
THAT MOVIE'S INCREDIBLE!
MY FAVORITE REVIEW
OF THAT MOVIE
IS FROM MY LITTLE
COUSIN HARRIS
THAT'S 14 YEARS OLD
AND LIVES IN GEORGIA.
AND I LOVE HARRIS 'CAUSE
HE HAS REALLY ODD CHOICES
IN ENTERTAINMENT.
LIKE, HIS FAVORITE TV SHOWS
ARE HOUR-LONG DRAMAS
ON USA AND TNT.
LIKE, YOU KNOW HOW
YOU SEE BILLBOARDS
FOR SHOWS LIKE BURN NOTICE.
YOU'RE LIKE, "WHO THE HECK
WATCHES BURN NOTICE?"
HARRIS WATCHES BURN NOTICE!
HE LOVES IT!
HARRIS TOLD ME HIS SENIOR
QUOTE'S GONNA BE,
"TNT KNOWS DRAMA."
YOU CALL UP HARRIS,
YOU HEAR THINGS LIKE,
"HEY, HARRIS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?"
"I'M PISSED OFF, MAN!
"MY DAD JUST ERASED
ALL MY SHOWS FROM THE DVR.
GUESS I WON'T FIND OUT WHAT
HAPPENS ON LAS VEGAS THIS WEEK."
WHO DVRs LAS VEGAS?
JOSH DUHAMEL DOESN'T DVR
LAS VEGAS.
AND YOU DON'T GET THAT JOKE,
'CAUSE JOSH DUHAMEL'S
THE STAR OF LAS VEGAS,
AND NOBODY WATCHES LAS VEGAS!
[laughter and applause]
SO I ASKED HARRIS--
I'M LIKE, "HEY, HARRIS.
YOU LIKE THE DARK KNIGHT?"
"YEAH."
"IS IT BETTER
THAN BURN NOTICE?"
"YEAH."
"IS IT BETTER THAN LAS VEGAS?"
"IS IT BETTER THAN
EATING AT CINNABON?"
"NO."
HEY, I KNEW THAT WOULD
GET HIM,
'CAUSE HE'S A LITTLE
CHUBBY GUY AND HE LOVES
SHOVING CINNABONS
INTO HIS LITTLE CHUBBY FACE.
[muttering]
AND I LOVE THAT ABOUT HIM!
I LOVE THAT HE'S CHUBBY.
'CAUSE THERE'S NOT A LOT
OF CHUBBY LITTLE INDIAN KIDS.
MOST OF THEM ARE SMALL
AND SKINNY LIKE ME,
BUT EVERY NOW AND THEN
YOU SEE A CHUBBY ONE
AND IT'S AWESOME!
IT'S KIND OF LIKE SEEING
A SHOOTING STAR
ONLY IT'S FAT, BROWN,
AND ON THE GROUND.
[laughter]
I'VE FOUND HARRIS TO
BE MOST ENTERTAINED AT ME
WHEN HE'S REALLY
ANGRY AT ME.
AND I FOUND THE QUICKEST WAY
TO GET HIM ANGRY
IS TO FUCK
WITH HIM ON FACEBOOK.
HE DOES NOT LIKE IT.
HE'S GOT HIS LITTLE UPDATES
METICULOUSLY PLANNED LIKE,
"HARRIS JUST BECAME
A BIG FAN OF WILL SMITH."
AND I'LL WRITE UP THERE,
"FUCK WILL SMITH."
AND HE'LL BE LIKE,
"WHY DID YOU DO THAT?"
AND SO ONE TIME I NOTICED
HE WAS POSTING A LOT
ON A STUDY GROUP
FOR HIS WORLD HISTORY CLASS.
AND I WAS LIKE,
"I KNOW WHAT I'LL DO.
"I'LL JOIN THE STUDY GROUP.
"I'LL WRITE ALL THIS DUMB
SHIT ON THERE,
"HARRIS WILL GET
REALLY PISSED,
AND IT'LL BE AWESOME."
AND THAT'S EXACTLY HOW
THAT SHIT WENT DOWN!
AS SOON AS I STARTED POSTING,
I STARTED GETTING
ALL THESE, LIKE,
ANGRY I.M.s FROM HARRIS.
HE'S LIKE, "HEY, MAN, YOU NEED
TO GET OFF THE BOARDS."
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHY?"
HE'S LIKE, "THE ADMINS
ARE GETTING ON MY CASE."
AND HE POSTS THIS CONVERSATION
HE HAD WITH THE ADMIN,
WHERE THE ADMIN'S LIKE,
"HEY, HARRIS, WHO'S AZIZ?"
HE'S LIKE, "MY COUSIN.
WHY DO YOU ASK?"
HE GOES, "HE'S POSTING
ON A.P. WORLD WALL.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT PERIOD
HE HAS A.P. WORLD?"
AND HARRIS WRITES IN ALL CAPS,
"NO!
YOU GOT TO BOOT HIM NOW!"
WITH, LIKE, 30 "O"s,
30 "W"s,
AND 50 EXCLAMATION POINTS.
AND OTHER PEOPLE ARE STARTING
TO GET SUSPICIOUS
OF MY PRESENCE
ON THE BOARD AS WELL.
MAYBE BECAUSE I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE IN THE NINTH GRADE
AND I HAVE A FULL BEARD.
BUT I'M TRYING TO ACT
LIKE I BELONG, RIGHT?
THAT I'M IN THE CLASS
AND I KNOW WHAT'S UP.
SO THERE WAS, LIKE,
A CONTROVERSY
ABOUT THIS ONE QUIZ QUESTION,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"I KNOW WHAT I'LL DO.
"I'LL GO INDEPENDENTLY
DO SOME RESEARCH
"AND I'LL POST MY FINDINGS
ON THE BOARD.
THEY'LL THINK I'M SMART
AND THAT I BELONG IN THE CLASS."
SO THE NEXT POST
I WROTE WAS,
"GUYS, I'VE BEEN
DOING SOME RESEARCH.
"I THINK THE VIEWS ON SALVATION
IN BUDDHISM AND CHRISTIANITY
"ARE FAR FROM SIMILAR.
"IN BUDDHISM, SALVATION IS
SOMETHING ONE CAN ONLY
"ACHIEVE THROUGH THE NOBLE
EIGHTFOLD PATH,
"WHEREAS IN CHRISTIANITY,
SALVATION IS GIVEN
"TO ALL THOSE WHOM ACCEPT
JESUS CHRIST AS THEIR SAVIOR.
"QUOTE, 'FOR WHOMSOEVER SHALL
CALL UPON THE NAME OF THE LORD'
"'SHALL BE SAVED,'
ROMANS 10:13.
"I HATE TO SAY IT, GUYS,
BUT OUR TEACHER
MR. EDELSTEIN IS RIGHT."
BAM!
AND THEN I WAITED, LIKE,
TWO MINUTES
AND THEN I WROTE THIS.
"GUYS, I JUST GOT AN EMAIL
FROM MR. EDELSTEIN!
"HE READ WHAT I WROTE HERE
AND GAVE ME
"AN EXTRA POINT
ON THE QUIZ.
"HE SAID I SHOWED INITIATIVE
AND CRITICAL THINKING SKILLS.
WHAT A COOL GUY!"
AND THEN THIS KID REPLIED,
"WHAT?"
AND THEN AT THIS POINT,
HARRIS GOT FUCKING FURIOUS.
HE'S LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU SHOULD HAVE WROTE
THAT WALL POST, AZIZ,"
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHY?"
HE GOES, "WHAT IF PEOPLE
GO IN TOMORROW AND SAY,
"'HEY EDELSTEIN,
I HEARD YOU GAVE AZIZ
"'AN EXTRA POINT ON THE QUIZ.
"'CAN I GET AN EXTRA
POINT BACK TOO,
"BECAUSE I PUT THE
SAME THING HE DID?'
"AND HE'LL BE LIKE,
'I DON'T TEACH AZIZ.
THAT PERSON DOESN'T EXIST.'"
AND I WAS LIKE,
"FUCK YOU, HARRIS.
I DO EXIST."
AND THEN HE STARTS ATTACKING ME
PUBLICLY ON THE BOARDS.
HE WRITES IN ALL CAPS,
"AZIZ, GET OUT OF THIS GROUP!"
WITH, LIKE, A BUNCH
OF EXCLAMATION POINTS
AND THEN EMOTICONS
THAT ARE LIKE--
[angry chattering]
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHAT'S
THAT SUPPOSED TO BE, HARRIS,
YOU EATING CINNABON ALL DAY?"
AND THEN I STARTED
MOUNTING MY OFFENSIVE.
I STARTED POKING HIM
LIKE CRAZY.
I STARTED SENDING
HIM VAMPIRE REQUESTS,
WHATEVER THE FUCK THAT IS.
HE'S LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON."
AND THEN HE WRITES UP THERE--
HE GOES, "HEY, EVERYONE.
"IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULDN'T GO TO EDELSTEIN
"AND ASK FOR POINTS BACK
ON THAT QUESTION.
I'M POSITIVE YOU WON'T
GET THE POINTS BACK."
AND THEN I WRITE,
"NO, GUYS.
"I JUST TALKED
TO EDELSTEIN AGAIN.
"YOU'LL DEFINITELY
GET THE POINTS BACK.
"JUST MENTION MY NAME
AND THE FACT THAT I EXIST.
FUCK YOU, HARRIS!"
THEN--
AND THEN THIS KID WRITES,
"YOU'RE NOT EVEN IN THIS CLASS.
YOU'RE THE GUY
FROM THAT TV SHOW."
AND SOME OTHER KID WRITES,
"WHAT TV SHOW ARE YOU ON?"
AND I WRITE,
"GOSSIP GIRL."
AND THEN I GOT KICKED
THE FUCK OUT.
[laughter and applause]
I DO THIS--
DO THIS TV SHOW RIGHT NOW,
AND, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU PROMOTE A TV SHOW
YOU'RE ON, YOU GOT TO DO
A LOT OF INTERVIEWS AND STUFF.
AND I WAS DOING AN INTERVIEW
ONCE AND THIS GUY GOES,
"SO YOU MUST
BE PRETTY PSYCHED
BY ALL THIS
SLUMDOG MILLIONAIRE STUFF."
AND I LIKE,
"UM, YEAH, I AM!
"I HAVE NO IDEA WHY THOUGH.
"I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH THAT MOVIE.
"IT'S JUST SOME PEOPLE
THAT KIND OF LOOK LIKE ME
"ARE IN THIS MOVIE
THAT EVERYONE LOVES
AND WINNING OSCARS
AND STUFF."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
ARE WHITE PEOPLE JUST
PSYCHED ALL THE TIME?"
IT'S LIKE, "BACK TO THE FUTURE,
THAT'S US!
"GODFATHER, THAT'S US!
GODFATHER PART TWO, THAT'S US!
"DEPARTED, THAT'S US!
SUNSET BOULEVARD, THAT'S US!
"CITIZEN KANE, THAT'S US!
JAWS, THAT'S US!
"EVERY FUCKING MOVIE
BUT SLUMDOG MILLIONAIRE
"AND BOYZ N THE HOOD IS US!
WE ARE WHITE PEOPLE!
SUCK OUR DICKS!"
[laughter and applause]
[chuckles]
I DID THIS SHOW
ON MTV ONCE
AND, UM, MTV's GREAT.
THEY LET US DO THIS SHOW,
AND LET US MAKE IT AWESOME
HOWEVER WE WANTED,
AND CREATIVELY,
THEY WERE SO AWESOME
AND IT WAS SO COOL.
HOWEVER, I GOT TO SAY,
SOME OF THE SHOWS
ON THE NETWORK,
NOT REALLY MY CUP OF TEA.
UH, MAINLY BECAUSE
I DON'T LIKE
HUGE PIECES OF SHIT
IN MY TEA.
[laughter and applause]
I--I WAS WATCHING THIS DATING
SHOW ON THERE CALLED NEXT.
MAN, IF ANYONE HERE HAS EVER
BEEN A CONTESTANT ON NEXT,
DO ME A FAVOR
AND GO AWAY AND DIE.
'CAUSE YOU'RE A HORRIBLE PERSON
AND I DON'T WANT COMEDY
BRINGING ANY KIND
OF SATISFACTION
INTO YOUR MISERABLE EXISTENCE.
[laughter]
FIRST GUY THAT COMES OUT,
RIGHT?
HE'S THE GUY GOING OUT
ON THE DATES.
AND HE COMES UP THERE
AND HE SAYS THIS--HE GOES,
"YO, THIS GIRL
BETTER BE PRETTY,
"'CAUSE IF SHE'S
A PAIN IN THE ASS,
I'M GONNA NEED SOMETHING
CUTE TO LOOK AT."
AND I WAS STUNNED
THAT HE COULD SAY THAT.
THAT'S SO OFFENSIVE.
AND AT THE SAME TIME,
ON MY SHOW,
THEY DIDN'T WANT US
TO SAY THAT A CHARACTER
WAS RAPED BY A DINOSAUR.
RAPED BY A DINOSAUR!
'CAUSE THAT'S TOO OFFENSIVE.
OH, I GUESS THEY DIDN'T
WANT ALL THESE ANGRY LETTERS
FROM PALEONTOLOGISTS
WHO ARE LIKE, "HEY, MAN!
"THERE'S NOTHING
IN THE FOSSIL RECORDS TO SUGGEST
"THAT KIND OF BEHAVIOR.
SO WHY DON'T YOU CHILL
WITH YOUR ACCUSATIONS?"
[laughter and applause]
AND THEN AFTER
YOU MEET THIS DUDE,
THEN YOU MEET THE GIRLS HE'S
GOING OUT ON THE DATES WITH.
AND THEY COME UP THERE
AND THEY SAY THINGS LIKE,
"IF HE HAS A NECK TATTOO,
I'M GONNA LICK IT."
[laughter]
IT'S LIKE WHOA!
HOW SLUTTY CAN YOU BE
IN FIVE SECONDS?
AND AFTER THEY SAY THAT,
THEY FREEZE,
AND, LIKE, THREE FACTS ABOUT 'EM
POP UP ON THE LEFT SIDE.
AND THE FIRST TWO FACTS
ARE ALWAYS REALLY NORMAL,
BUT THE THIRD FACT ALWAYS COMES
WAY OUT OF LEFT FIELD.
IT'S ALWAYS LIKE,
"MONICA'S 22.
"SHE'S A HAIRDRESSER
IN HOLLYWOOD
AND SHE HATES PURPLE
GIFT WRAP."
LIKE, HOW DOES THAT
DEFINE HER AS A PERSON?"
AND THE WHOLE SHOW
JUST BUMMED ME OUT, MAN.
'CAUSE THE THINGS
THEY TRY TO KEEP OFF TV
ARE JUST, LIKE,
REALLY EXPLICIT SEX OR VIOLENCE,
AND NO ONE CARES ABOUT THEIR
KIDS SEEING ATTITUDES
LIKE THAT ON TV,
AND THAT'S WAY WORSE TO ME.
LIKE, I'D MUCH RATHER
HAVE A DAUGHTER
THAT GREW UP AND SHOT ME IN THE
LEG AND BURNED MY HOUSE DOWN,
THEN SOME REALLY SLUTTY
GIRL THAT,
"HATES THE SOUND OF PEOPLE
EATING BANANAS."
[laughter]
MY FAVORITE THIRD FACT I EVER
SAW ON NEXT THOUGH
WAS THIS ONE GUY
NAMED CLARENCE.
HIS THIRD FACT WAS THAT HE HATES
THE PHRASE "RIVER VIEW."
YOU DIDN'T MISHEAR ME.
WHEN THE WORDS
"RIVER" AND "VIEW"
START COMING TOGETHER,
CLARENCE IS LIKE,
"HOLD UP!
DON'T DO THAT!"
I WAS LIKE,
"WHAT WOULD MAKE A MAN
HATE THE PHRASE
'RIVER VIEW'?"
AND I COULD ONLY
THINK OF ONE SCENARIO
AND IT'S TERRIBLE,
BUT I HAVE TO SHARE IT WITH YOU.
SO ONE DAY, THIS GUY CLARENCE
IS COMING HOME, RIGHT?
AND HE'S WALKING DOWN
A DARK ALLEY,
AND GETS JUMPED BY THIS
MOTORCYCLE GANG
AND THEY JUST START
RAPING HIM, RIGHT?
AND ALL HE CAN SEE IS THIS SIGN
THAT SAYS "RIVER VIEW."
AND THESE GUYS ARE JUST LIKE,
"SAY IT, CLARENCE! SAY IT!"
HE'S LIKE, "RIVER VIEW!
RIVER VIEW! RIVER VIEW!
R-R-R-R-R-ROO!"
SO, YEAH, IF YOU WERE RAPED
BY THE RIVER VIEW RAPE GANG,
SURE, HATE THE PHRASE
"RIVER VIEW."
OTHERWISE JUST STOP LOOKING
AT PROPERTY IN THAT AREA!
[laughter and applause]
I THINK YOU NOTICED SOMETHING
REALLY WEIRD ABOUT ME
WHEN I DO THAT BIT,
AND THAT IS THAT
I'M A VERY LAZY RAPIST.
I JUST BEND MY KNEES
A LITTLE BIT, VERY LOW IMPACT.
ANYBODY THAT'S WORRIED
ABOUT GETTING RAPED BY ME
AFTER THE SHOW IS LIKE, "MAN,
IT'S NOT GONNA BE THAT BAD.
"I GOT RAPED BY AZIZ AFTER
THE SHOW LAST NIGHT.
THAT WAS PRETTY REFRESHING."
I MET THIS GUY WHEN
I WAS BACK HOME LAST TIME
WHO WAS A DOCTOR AND HE MOVED
FROM SOME COUNTRY IN ASIA
TO ALABAMA.
AND I WAS LIKE, "MAN, OUT OF ALL
THE STATES IN THE COUNTRY,
WHY WOULD YOU CHOOSE ALABAMA?"
AND HE GOES, "OH, WELL, I DON'T
HAVE MY GREEN CARD YET,
"SO IF I WORK IN A PLACE
THAT'S UNDERSERVED,
LIKE ALABAMA,
THEY'LL GIVE ME A WAIVER."
I WAS LIKE, "WHOA,
THAT'S KIND OF A WEIRD DEAL."
GOVERNMENT'S LIKE,
"OH, YEAH, YOU CAN COME
"TO THE UNITED STATES.
COME ON. COME ON.
"YEAH, YOU, COME ON.
BUT YOU GOT
TO GO TO ALABAMA."
[laughter]
IT'S KIND OF LIKE
A GIRL GOING,
"YEAH, YOU CAN
SEE ME NAKED,
"BUT YOU CAN ONLY
LOOK AT MY LEFT ELBOW
AND MY LEFT ELBOW'S
RACIST."
[laughter and applause]
I LIKE LIVING IN L.A.
ONE THING I DON'T LIKE ABOUT
LIVING HERE IS DRIVING.
I ALWAYS GET BORED
WHEN I'M DRIVING.
AND WHEN I GET BORED,
I GO ON THE INTERNET
ON MY BLACKBERRY,
SO I'M GONNA DIE!
AND WHENEVER THEY
GO THROUGH THE WRECKAGE,
THEY'LL FIND MY PHONE
AND BE LIKE,
"WHOA! THAT'S WHAT HE LOOKED UP
RIGHT BEFORE HE DIED?"
GONNA BE SO SAD.
IT'LL BE LIKE,
"COMEDIAN AZIZ ANSARI WAS KILLED
IN A CAR ACCIDENT TODAY.
"HE WAS STRUCK
BY ANOTHER VEHICLE
"WHILE USING IMDB
TO SEE IF VAL KILMER
"WAS INDEED
IN THE FILM WILLOW.
"REPRESENTATIVES FROM MR. KILMER
CONFIRMED HE WAS
"INDEED IN THE THE FILM,
AND HOPES THIS WILL PREVENT
"FUTURE TRAGEDIES
OF THIS NATURE.
"THIS IS THE THIRD
WILLOW-RELATED DEATH THIS YEAR.
"COMEDIAN AZIZ ANSARI WAS KILLED
IN A CAR ACCIDENT TODAY.
"HE WAS STRUCK BY ANOTHER
VEHICLE WHILE CHECKING
"SHOWTIMES FOR UP
ON FANDANGO.
"HE JUST PURCHASED A SINGLE
TICKET FOR A 4:00 SHOW
"AT A $2 THEATER
IN ORDER TO LIVE OUT
"THE SADDEST AFTERNOON
OF ALL-TIME.
"COMEDY BAD BOY AZIZ ANSARI,
A-K-A COMEDY HEARTTHROB
"AZIZ ANSARI, WAS KILLED IN AN
AWFUL AUTOMOBILE ACCIDENT TODAY.
"HE WAS STRUCK
BY ANOTHER VEHICLE
WHILE GOOGLING
HIS OWN NAME."
[laughter]
I DO DO THAT, MAN.
IT'S HARD NOT TO.
EVERYONE I KNOW,
THEY GOOGLE THEIR NAME,
SEE WHAT PEOPLE WRITE,
AND IT'S SO FUNNY TO READ IT,
'CAUSE PEOPLE ALWAYS
THINK LIKE,
"OH, MAN, THERE'S NO WAY HE'D
HAVE TIME TO EVER READ THIS."
HA-HA! YEAH, I DO.
I DON'T DO ANYTHING!
I TAKE NAPS ALL DAY!
AND...
I READ THIS ONE TIME THIS GIRL,
LIKE, HAD WRITTEN ABOUT,
LIKE, HOW SHE HAD
A CELEBRITY CRUSH...
ON ME.
AND IT'S FUNNY,
'CAUSE SHE NEVER THOUGHT
IN A MILLION YEARS
THAT I'D READ THAT.
YOU KNOW, NEVER IN A MILLION
YEARS WOULD I READ THAT.
BUT I DID.
[laughter]
SO ONE DAY I'M JUST GONNA EMAIL
HER AND BE LIKE,
"HEY! IT'S ME, AZIZ!
"I HEARD YOU HAVE A CELEBRITY
CRUSH ON ME.
"I'M A LOT LONELIER
THAN YOU THINK I AM.
WHERE IS YOUR HOUSE?
I WILL COME THERE NOW!"
[laughter]
I LOVE PERFORMING
AT MUSIC FESTIVALS.
THAT'S ALWAYS FUN.
I DID THIS FESTIVAL
CALLED BONNAROO
AND IT'S REALLY COOL,
'CAUSE THEY HAVE, LIKE,
INDIE-ROCK STUFF AND, LIKE,
HIPPIE STUFF COMING TOGETHER.
LIKE, THEY HAD THIS WEIRD
HIPPIE THING THERE
CALLED "THE SONIC FOREST."
AND THAT WAS BASICALLY--
THEY'D HAVE THESE POLES SET UP
AND YOU'D SLAP
THE SIDES OF THE POLES
AND ALL THESE BELLS AND WHISTLES
AND LIGHTS WOULD GO OFF
AND THEY HAD, LIKE,
30 OF 'EM IN ONE LITTLE AREA,
AND IT WAS LIKE,
"THAT'S THE SONIC FOREST."
I WAS LIKE, "MAN,
HOW DUMB ARE THOSE HIPPIES
TO BE ENTERTAINED
BY SOMETHING SO STUPID?"
[chuckles]
AND THEN THE LAST DAY I WAS
THERE, I ATE MUSHROOMS.
AND THEN I WAS LIKE,
* SONIC FOREST
* I TOTALLY GET YOU NOW
AND I SLAPPED THE SHIT
OUT OF THOSE POLES
FOR, LIKE, FOUR HOURS,
'CAUSE THE SONIC FOREST
IS THE GREATEST IDEA EVER!
[laughter]
I DID A FESTIVAL IN TELLURIDE,
COLORADO, ONCE.
IT'S A SKI TOWN.
NOT A LOT OF MINORITIES THERE.
AND I WAS TALKING TO THIS DUDE
AND HE WAS LIKE,
"YO, MAN, BEFORE YOU GO,
I GOT TO ASK YOU ONE THING.
WHERE ARE YOU FROM?"
AND I WENT, "WELL,
I'M FROM SOUTH CAROLINA,
BUT MY PARENTS
ARE FROM INDIA."
AND HE WENT,
"WHAT?
BUT YOU TALK EXACTLY
LIKE I DO!"
AND I WAS LIKE, "WELL, I MEAN,
HERE'S THE THING, MAN.
"THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
COME HERE FROM OTHER COUNTRIES
"AND, YOU KNOW,
THEY HAVE CHILDREN HERE,
"THEY GROW UP
IN THIS SOCIETY,
"AND SOMETIMES
THEY DON'T HAVE ACCENTS.
THEY'RE CALLED IMMIGRANTS."
AND THEN I SHOWED HIM A VIDEO
OF AN ASIAN KID RAPPING,
AND HIS HEAD EXPLODED.
[laughter]
I WENT TO A PLACE RECENTLY
I THINK IS ONE
OF THE MOST FUCKED UP
PLACES I'VE EVER BEEN TO.
I'M CONVINCED THIS PLACE IS
THE EPITOME OF AMERICAN EXCESS,
OF AMERICAN GREED.
I'M TALKING ABOUT A PLACE
CALLED COLD STONE CREAMERY.
WHOA.
IF YOU HAVE NOT BEEN THERE,
THE BASIC GIST OF COLD STONE
IS THAT THEY TAKE
ICE CREAM
AND THEN THEY JUST
GO APE SHIT WITH IT.
THEY'RE JUST, LIKE,
SLAMMING BROWNIES
AND GUMMY BEARS AND JUST
HAMMERING IT IN THERE.
WHATEVER FAT PEOPLE
WANT IN THERE.
SNICKERS BAR, CHEESEBURGER!
LET ME FUCK A BUTTERFINGER INTO
IT FOR YOU.
IT'S LIKE, "WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
"JESUS!
"THIS IS WAY TOO INTENSE
FOR ME.
"IS THAT GUY'S DICK
A BUTTERFINGER?
"WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
"WHOA! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
"I THINK I'LL JUST HAVE A SMALL
CUP OF VANILLA IF THAT'S OKAY.
THIS IS JUST
TOO INTENSE FOR ME."
LADY BEHIND THE COUNTER'S LIKE,
"NO, NO, NO!
"YOU SHOULD TRY ONE
OF OUR CREATIONS
"LIKE BIRTHDAY CAKE REMIX,
WHERE WE TAKE CAKE BATTER
ICE CREAM, YELLOW CAKE,
FUDGE CHUNKS, SPRINKLES!"
IT'S LIKE, "YOU KNOW, THAT JUST
SOUNDS TOO INTENSE FOR ME.
I'LL JUST HAVE
A SMALL CUP OF VANILLA."
SHE GOES,
"QUIT BEING A BITCH!"
WHOA!
AND THEN I COULDN'T
EVEN GET A SMALL
'CAUSE THEIR SIZES
ARE ACTUALLY,
"LIKE IT," "LOVE IT,"
AND "GOTTA HAVE IT"!
WHAT KIND OF CRACKHEAD
TERMINOLOGY IS THAT?
"HEY, WHAT SIZE YOU WANT,
MAN?"
"I DON'T KNOW, MAN!
I JUST GOTTA HAVE IT!
"PUT SOME ICE CREAM
IN A CUP!
I'M TWEAKING! I'M TWEAKING!
I'M TWEAKING!"
[laughter]
AND, YOU KNOW,
I FELT BAD FOR PEOPLE
THAT HAD TO WORK THERE,
MAN.
SO I WAS LIKE,
"AWW, I'M GONNA DROP
A COUPLE OF DOLLARS
IN THE TIP JAR ON MY WAY OUT."
WHOA, THAT'S WHEN ALL HELL
BROKE LOOSE!
'CAUSE APPARENTLY WHENEVER
THEY GET EVEN $1
IN THE TIP JAR,
ALL FIVE EMPLOYEES
ARE REQUIRED TO BUMP OUT
INTO A SONG AND DANCE NUMBER
WHERE THEY TAKE CURRENT
POPULAR MUSIC
AND SHOVE COLD STONE LINGO
INTO IT,
AS IF THEY'RE SOME RETARDED
SECOND COUSIN OF WEIRD AL
THAT'S OBSESSED
WITH ICE CREAM.
AND IT'S RIDICULOUS.
FIVE PEOPLE ARE SINGING
AND DANCING FOR $1.
THAT'S 20 CENTS A PERSON!
IF YOU SAW A HOMELESS DUDE
OUTSIDE A COLD STONE,
YOU'RE LIKE, "HEY, MAN,
I'LL GIVE YOU 20 CENTS
TO SING SOME SONGS
ABOUT COLD STONE."
HE'D GO, "HEY, MAN.
GO FUCK YOURSELF!
THAT'S DEGRADING!"
[laughter and applause]
ONE THING THAT'S COOL ABOUT
DOING THOSE MUSIC FESTIVALS
IS, YOU KNOW, YOU GET TO MEET
MUSICIANS AND STUFF
THAT, LIKE,
YOU'RE A FAN OF,
AND, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S ALWAYS COOL FOR ME.
LIKE, I MET M.I.A. ONCE,
AND, UM, I WAS LIKE,
"MAN, I GOT TO SAY SOMETHING
COOL TO M.I.A.
SHE'S SO COOL!"
I WAS LIKE,
"THIS IS WHAT I'LL DO.
"I'M SAY SOMETHING IN TAMIL,
"THIS OBSCURE,
SOUTHEAST ASIAN LANGUAGE
THAT WE BOTH HAPPEN
TO SPEAK."
HERE'S THE THING.
I DON'T SPEAK TAMIL
THAT WELL.
LIKE, I WOULD NEVER SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
BUT IF I WANTED TO SAY,
"YOU HAVE BEAUTIFUL BREASTS,"
I COULDN'T SAY THAT.
WHAT I'D HAVE TO SAY IS--
[speaking Tamil]
WHICH TRANSLATES TO,
"FOR YOU, RIGHT HERE,
IT'S AWESOME."
WHICH IS A TERRIBLE LINE!
[laughter and applause]
ONE TIME, IN L.A., KANYE WEST
CAME TO ONE OF MY SHOWS,
AND I WAS SO PSYCHED.
I'M SUCH A HUGE
KANYE WEST FAN.
AND EVERYTHING HE DID
TO ME WAS SO FUNNY.
LIKE, HE WAS IN THE BATHROOM
FOR, LIKE, A REALLY LONG TIME.
AND THEN HE CAME OUT,
HE GOES,
"YO, JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I WAS ON
"AN IMPORTANT PHONE CALL.
I WASN'T TAKING A SHIT."
[laughter]
BUT, UM, WHEN HE WAS LEAVING,
HE WAS LIKE,
"YO, MAN, WE SHOULD
HANG OUT SOMETIME.
THAT'D BE COOL, RIGHT?"
AND I WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, THAT'D BE CRAZY.
I'M SUCH A HUGE FAN.
THAT'D BE AWESOME."
SO THIS IS THE STORY
OF THE FIRST TIME
I HUNG OUT WITH KANYE WEST.
SO HE TEXTS ME,
HE'S LIKE,
"YO, WE'RE AT THIS CLUB.
COME DOWN."
SO I GRAB MY FRIEND JASON,
WHO'S ANOTHER GUY
THAT DOES NOT LOOK
LIKE HE BELONG
IN A HIP-HOP NIGHTCLUB.
AND WE HEAD OVER THERE,
RIGHT?
AND WE GET THERE,
WE GET IN THE CLUB,
AND THEY'RE LIKE,
"YO, WE'RE AT CAPACITY."
I WAS LIKE, "WELL, KANYE WEST
TOLD ME TO COME DOWN."
AND HE WAS LIKE,
"SOMEBODY'S GONNA HAVE
TO COME AND GET YOU."
[chuckles]
AND SO I TEXTED KANYE.
I WAS LIKE, "HEY, MAN, LIKE,
THEY'RE AT CAPACITY."
I SAID, "SOMEONE NEEDS
TO GET ME."
AND THEN BEFORE
I COULD EVEN HIT "SEND,"
I GET A TEXT FROM HIM,
"ON MY WAY!"
AND HE COMES OUT.
HE'S LIKE--
AND WE GO IN.
IT WAS REALLY COOL
OF HIM TO COME GET US.
AND WE GO INSIDE, AND, LIKE,
HE'S SITTING THERE
AT A TABLE WITH,
LIKE, JAY-Z AND ALL THESE MODELS
AND STUFF AND, LIKE,
WE JUST DID NOT BELONG THERE.
LIKE, IF YOU HAD
A PHOTO OF THAT TABLE,
YOU'D BE LIKE, "WHO PHOTOSHOPPED
THOSE TWO DUDES IN THERE?
THAT WAS A REALLY GOOD JOB."
[laughter and applause]
AND--
YOU KNOW, JAY-Z'S THERE DRINKING
VODKA HE MAKES.
LIKE, HOW BALLER IS THAT?
JAY-Z SIGNED THE TAB,
MONEY WENT BACK
INTO HIS OWN POCKET.
HE WAS LIKE, "YOU'RE CRAZY
FOR THIS ONE, JAY.
HOV! PSHH!"
[laughter and applause]
AND SO KANYE EVENTUALLY GOES,
"YO, MAN.
"WE'RE HEADING BACK
TO THE CRIB.
YOU WANT TO COME DOWN?"
I WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, THAT'D BE AWESOME.
THAT'D BE CRAZY
TO SEE YOUR HOUSE."
AND SO WE GO DOWN THERE,
ME AND JASON,
AND WE GET THERE
PRETTY EARLY.
AND THERE'S NO ONE
REALLY THERE,
AND I WALK IN AND I HEAR
808s AND HEARTBREAK PLAYING,
WHICH IS HIS ALBUM.
AND I WALK UP AND I SEE HIM
SITTING ON THE COUCH.
HE'S LIKE...
[laughter]
"SHH!"
I WAS LIKE, "YO, MAN.
"ARE YOU LISTENING TO YOUR OWN
ALBUM IN YOUR OWN HOUSE,
BOPPING YOUR OWN HEAD?"
AND HE GOES, "YEAH.
THESE BEATS ARE DOPE."
AND I GO, "THAT'D BE LIKE IF
I HAD A STAND-UP ALBUM,
"YOU CAME OVER TO MY HOUSE AND
I WAS LISTENING TO IT GOING,
'HA-HA-HA-HA-HA!
THESE JOKES ARE DOPE.'"
[laughter]
AND WE'RE SITTING THERE HANGING
OUT AT HIS HOUSE,
AND, LIKE,
EVERYTHING THAT KANYE SAID TO ME
MADE ME LAUGH SO HARD.
LIKE, AT ONE POINT WE WERE,
LIKE, SITTING THERE
TALKING ABOUT MUSIC.
LIKE, TALKING ABOUT
TV ON THE RADIO
OR SOMETHING, AND,
LIKE, HE JUST, LIKE, CUT ME OFF.
HE WAS LIKE, "YO, MAN.
HOLD ON A SECOND."
AND HE SAID THE GREATEST THING
I WILL EVER HEAR IN MY LIFE.
HE GOES, "HOLD ON A SECOND.
"I'MA GO OVER THERE
AND LOOK IN THE TELESCOPE
WITH THIS GIRL
WITH THE BIG TITTIES."
[laughter]
[chuckles]
AND THEN LATER ON, YOU KNOW,
HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT COMING TO MY SHOW,
AND HE WAS LIKE, "MAN, I HAD
A GOOD TIME AT YOUR SHOW."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"OH, THANK YOU FOR COMING."
YOU KNOW, AND HE'S LIKE,
"YO, MAN.
"YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU NEED TO DO TONIGHT?
YOU NEED TO DO SOME
OF YOUR JOKES."
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, MAN.
"YOU KNOW WHAT
I NEED TO DO TONIGHT?
NOT DO THAT."
BUT HE KEPT BRINGING IT UP.
HE WAS LIKE,
"COME ON, MAN. PLEASE?
"IT'D BE REALLY COOL IF YOU DID
SOME JOKES, MAN.
IT'D BE REALLY COOL."
AND EVENTUALLY I HAD
A COUPLE MORE DRINKS.
I WAS LIKE, "FUCK IT!
I'LL DO SOME JOKES!"
AND NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
LIKE,
MY FRIEND JASON'S
IN THE LIVING ROOM LIKE,
"THIS NEXT COMEDIAN COMING
TO THE STAGE..."
AND, LIKE, I COME UP
TO THE LIVING ROOM,
AND, LIKE, HE'S GOT, LIKE,
30 PEOPLE ARRANGED
IN HIS LIVING ROOM AND I'M,
LIKE, TELLING MY JOKES
AND THIS IS A NIGHTMARE
SITUATION FOR A COMEDIAN.
BUT EVERYONE
WAS VERY QUIET AND NICE.
THEY LISTENED, THEY LAUGHED,
AND IT WAS GREAT.
BUT MY FAVORITE PART WAS,
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
SOMEONE WOULD BE
IN THE KITCHEN, LIKE,
MAKING A DRINK
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
AND THEY'D MAKE
A LITTLE NOISE,
AND THEN KANYE WOULD
JUMP UP AND BE LIKE,
"YO, SHUT THE FUCK UP!
HOMIE'S OVER HERE TRYING
TO TELL SOME JOKES!"
WHICH IS THE BEST THING ANYONE'S
EVER YELLED AT A COMEDY SHOW.
[laughter]
MY COUSIN DARWISH,
WHO IS HARRIS' OLDER BROTHER,
ACTUALLY GOT INTO A LITTLE BIT
OF A TIFF WITH KANYE.
AND, YOU KNOW, DARWISH IS,
LIKE, 18 YEARS OLD,
SO HE JUST STARTED LISTENING
TO MUSIC.
AND, UM, HE WOULD
ALWAYS I.M. ME
ABOUT NEW BANDS
HE'D HEARD OF OR WHATEVER.
AND ONE TIME HE'S LIKE,
"AZIZ, HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
"OF KANYE WEST?
THAT SONG AMAZING,
IT'S AMAZING!"
AND HE WAS LIKE, "ARE THERE
ANY OTHER GOOD RAPPERS
I SHOULD LISTEN TO?"
I WAS LIKE, "OH, YOU EVER LISTEN
TO ANY WU-TANG CLAN?"
HE'S LIKE,
"NO, BUT I'VE HEARD OF HIM.
HE RAPS A LOT ABOUT
KARATE, RIGHT?"
AND I WAS LIKE,
"NOT EXACTLY."
AND...
SO I COPIED THAT CONVERSATION
AND EMAILED IT TO KANYE.
AND HE RESPONDED
BACK RIGHT AWAY.
HE GOES, "WOW!
NEW FANS!
YAY! MORE PEOPLE
THAT DON'T HATE ME!"
THAT'S HOW HIS EMAILS
SOUND TO ME.
AND--
[laughter]
AND THEN A LITTLE BIT LATER,
I GET ANOTHER I-M FROM DARWISH.
HE'S LIKE,
"AZIZ!
"THAT KANYE SONG
FLASHING LIGHTS,
"THAT'S A RIP-OFF
OF A NE-YO TRACK.
KANYE STOLE THAT BEAT!"
AND I WAS LIKE,
"REALLY?"
HE'S LIKE, "YEAH.
WHAT'S KANYE'S EMAIL?"
AND I WAS LIKE,
"YOU'RE REALLY GONNA EMAIL HIM?"
AND HE GOES, "I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S PRETTY MESSED UP."
AND SO I WAS LIKE,
"I'LL EMAIL HIM FOR YOU."
AND SO I SEND
THAT CONVERSATION TO HIM.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, SHIT.
DARWISH IS ACCUSING YOU
OF JACKING BEATS, HOMIE!"
AND THEN RESPONDS BACK
RIGHT AWAY.
HE GOES, "NO!
THAT SONG
CAME OUT AFTERWARDS!"
[laughter]
AND I SHOWED THAT
TO DARWISH,
AND, YOU KNOW,
DARWISH APOLOGIZED
AND, YOU KNOW, I JUST PASTED
ALL THOSE CONVERSATIONS
ON MY WEB SITE.
AND THEN THE NEXT DAY,
I WENT ON KANYE'S BLOG
AND I SAW THIS.
THAT'S MY COUSIN DARWISH!
KANYE WEST VERSUS DARWISH!
SO I CALLED UP DARWISH,
AND I'M LIKE,
"HEY, DARWISH.
HAVE YOU BEEN ON KANYE'S
WEB SITE BEFORE?"
HE'S LIKE, "NO.
HE'S GOT A WEB SITE?"
KEEP IN MIND,
DARWISH IS NOW, LIKE,
THE HUGEST KANYE WEST FAN
RIGHT NOW.
AND I WAS LIKE, "HAVE YOU
BEEN ON HIS WEB SITE?"
HE WAS LIKE, "NO."
I WAS LIKE, "GO ON THERE
RIGHT NOW."
HE GOES ON THERE.
HE GOES, "WHAT?
I GOTTA GO CHANGE
MY FACEBOOK STATUS!"
CLICK.
[laughter and applause]
YOU KNOW, MY FAVORITE MUSICIAN
THAT I'VE EVER MET
WAS, UH, R. KELLY,
I THINK.
AND, UM, IN CASE YOU'RE
NOT FAMILIAR,
R. KELLY IS A BRILLIANT
R&B SINGER/CRAZY PERSON.
[laughter]
LIKE, THEY DID AN INTERVIEW
WITH HIM ON B.E.T., RIGHT?
AND THE GUY DOING THE INTERVIEW
WAS PROBABLY A GUY LIKE ME.
YOU KNOW, HUGE FAN OF R. KELLY
AND HIS MUSIC,
AND HOPES HE REALLY IS INNOCENT
OF THOSE TERRIBLE THINGS
HE'S ACCUSED OF.
SO FIRST QUESTION,
THE GUY GOES,
"NOW, ROBERT, ARE YOU ATTRACTED
TO TEENAGE GIRLS?"
AND R. KELLY--
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE R. KELLY,
THAT'S EASY, RIGHT?
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS BE LIKE,
"NO, NOT AT ALL. NO!"
THAT'S ALL YOU GOTTA DO, RIGHT?
THAT'S ALL YOU GOTTA DO.
THAT IS NOT
WHAT R. KELLY DOES.
R. KELLY GOES,
"DEFINE 'TEENAGE.' "
LITERALLY THE WORST ANSWER!
THE ONLY WORSE ANSWER WOULD HAVE
BEEN HE WENT,
"HA, YEAH."
[laughter]
SO THAT'S THE PERSON WE'RE
DEALING WITH.
SO I GO TO HIS CONCERT
WITH MY FRIEND JASON.
WE GET THERE.
SHOW'S SOLD OUT.
PEOPLE ARE PSYCHED
FOR R. KELLY.
JASON LOOKS OVER AT ME
AND GOES,
"HEY, AZIZ.
"ME AND YOU ARE THE ONLY
TWO WHITE PEOPLE
AT THIS CONCERT."
AND I WAS LIKE, "FIRST OF ALL,
JASON, I'M NOT WHITE.
"SECOND OF ALL, YOU'RE THE ONLY
WHITE GUY AT THIS CONCERT.
WE MIGHT KILL YOU, JASON!"
[laughter]
SO THE CONCERT STARTS,
AND IT'S INCREDIBLE.
R. KELLY IS THE BEST SHOWMAN.
LIKE, HE HAS THIS PART
IN THE SHOW
WHERE HE HAS SEX
WITH AN INVISIBLE WOMAN.
YOU CAN SEE
THE SOUND EFFECTS.
SO HE'S, LIKE,
TAKING OFF HER BLOUSE.
[imitating zippers]
[imitating slapping]
[imitating explosion]
AND THEN WHEN HE DOES THE...
A SPOTLIGHT SHOOTS
OUT OF HIS COCK,
AND THEN GOES OVER
THE WHOLE AUDIENCE
LIKE HE'S COMING
ON THE WHOLE CROWD.
AND THEN A SPOTLIGHT
HITS A SCREEN,
AND THE SCREEN EXPLODES!
AND I WAS LIKE,
"WHOA!
"YOU ARE NOT GONNA
SEE SHIT LIKE THAT
AT A MODEST MOUSE CONCERT!"
WOW!
AND THEN, LIKE, THERE'S
ALL THIS OTHER WEIRD STUFF.
LIKE, AT ONE POINT,
HE LEAVES THE STAGE, RIGHT?
AND THEY CUT TO A VIDEO
OF HIM PLAYING BASKETBALL
WITH HIS FRIENDS.
LASTS ABOUT FOUR MINUTES.
COMES BACK ON STAGE.
GOES INTO THE NEXT SONG.
DOESN'T ADDRESS WHY
HE SHOWED THAT VIDEO!
YOU CAN'T DO SHIT
LIKE THAT!
I CAN'T LEAVE THE STAGE,
SHOW YOU SOME VIDEO OF ME
PLAYING FOOSBALL
WITH MY BUDDIES,
AND THEN COME BACK
AND BE LIKE,
"MAN, iPHONES ARE CRAZY."
YOU'D BE LIKE,
"YO, MAN, WHAT WAS UP
"WITH THAT VIDEO
YOU SHOWED?
"YOU GOT TO EXPLAIN
THAT SHIT!
THAT WAS WEIRD!"
[laughter and applause]
THEN, YOU KNOW,
WE GO BACKSTAGE
AND MEET HIM
AT THE END OF THE SHOW.
HE'S VERY NICE.
HE'S LIKE,
"HEY, YOU GUYS SHOULD COME
TO THIS AFTERPARTY
WE'RE DOING."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, SURE."
AND SO WE GO
TO THIS NIGHTCLUB
AND ONCE AGAIN,
JASON AND I ARE
THE ONLY TWO WHITE
PEOPLE THERE.
AND WHEN PEOPLE KNOW R. KELLY'S
IN A NIGHTCLUB,
THEY LOSE THEIR SHIT.
AND THEN HE TOOK THE STAGE AND
PEOPLE WENT NUTS.
AND HE STARTED DOING
THAT SONG THAT'S LIKE,
"I'M IN LOVE
WITH A STRIPPER."
AND HE'S DOING THE SONG
AND AT ONE POINT,
THIS WOMAN JUST
JUMPS ONSTAGE
AND STARTS
GIVING HIM A LAP DANCE.
SHE FINISHES THE LAP DANCE
AND R. KELLY GOES,
"* WHO CAN TOP THAT SHIT
* WHO CAN TOP THAT SHIT "
SECOND WOMAN COMES ONSTAGE,
GIVES HIM
AN EVEN CRAZIER LAP DANCE.
AND R. KELLY GOES,
"* WHO CAN TOP THAT SHIT
* WHO CAN TOP THAT SHIT "
THIRD WOMAN COMES ONSTAGE
WITH HUMONGOUS BREASTS,
WHIPS 'EM OUT,
SLAPS THE FIRST THREE ROWS,
GRABS R. KELLY'S HEAD
AND JUST GOES,
"ARRGH!"
AND THEN R. KELLY POPS OUT HIS
HEAD AND GOES,
"* WHOA
"* AIN'T NOBODY GONNA
TOP THAT SHIT *
* I'M OUT "
AND HE LEAVES.
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHOA!
WHAT A PERFORMANCE!"
BUT...
MY FAVORITE--
MY ABSOLUTE FAVORITE PART
OF THE R. KELLY SHOW WAS,
LIKE,
20 MINUTES IN,
HE STOPS EVERYTHING,
AND HE STARTS TALKING
TO THE CROWD.
AND WHAT'S GREAT ABOUT
THAT IS THAT R. KELLY
DOES NOT TALK
LIKE YOU AND I TALK.
HE TALKS LIKE R. KELLY TALKS.
SO HE GOES LIKE THIS.
"* LADIES AND GENTLEMEN
"* I DON'T KNOW THE NAME
OF THIS BUILDING *
"* BUT THE PEOPLE
THAT RUN THIS BUILDING *
"* THEY SAID 'ROBERT'
"* 'YOU'VE BEEN ONLY DOING YOUR
SHOW FOR 20 MINUTES *
"* 'AND IT'S ALREADY GETTING TOO
FRE-E-E-E-E-E-E-EAKY TONIGHT' *
[laughter]
"* THEY SAID 'ROBERT'
"* THEY SAID
'MOTHERFUCKING ROBERT' *
"* 'THERE WILL BE NO TOUCHING
OF YOURSELF *
"* 'IN THIS AREA TONIGHT'
"* DO YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT I TOLD 'EM *
"* I SAID L.A. DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW WHAT I TOLD 'EM *
[cheers and applause]
"* I SAID L.A. DO YOU WANNA
KNOW WHAT I SAID *
"* TO THESE PEOPLE WHEN THEY
SAID THAT TO ME *
"* DO YOU WANT KNOW WHAT I
"* TO-O-O-O-O-O-OLD 'EM
[cheers and applause]
"* I SAID I'M A GROWN
"* ASS
"* MAN
"* AND I CAN DO WHATEVER
THE FUCK I WANT TONIGHT *
* L.A. CAN I DO MY SHOW "
AND EVERYONE'S LIKE,
"FUCK, YEAH!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS IS!"
AND THAT WAS THE GREATEST
CONCERT I'VE EVER SEEN.
THANK YOU, GUYS, SO MUCH!
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU, GUYS.
[cheers and applause continue]
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
UM...
[exhales]
THIS NEXT BIT I WANTED
TO DO, UH,
IT'S SOMETHING
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
UM, I PLAYED A CHARACTER
IN THIS MOVIE FUNNY PEOPLE,
UH, NAMED RANDY,
WHO IS A STAND-UP COMEDIAN.
AND WHEN I DID THE MOVIE,
I WROTE, LIKE, SOME JOKES
FOR RANDY AND I ENJOY
DOING THEM AND SO I THOUGHT
IT'D BE FUN TO DO A LITTLE BIT
OF RANDY IN THIS SPECIAL.
SO, UH, WE'RE GONNA
DO A LITTLE BIT
WHERE IT'S BASICALLY
LIKE,
"WHAT WOULD RANDY DO
IF HE HAD A SPECIAL?"
SO GIVE ME A SECOND.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[cheers and applause]
[air raid sirens wail]
- Y'ALL ARE ABOUT
TO BE AMAZED IN WAYS
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
AMAZED BEFORE!
IF YOU GOT A SECOND
SET OF SKIN,
Y'ALL BETTER BREAK IT OUT,
'CAUSE WE FIXING
TO BURN IT OFF,
Y'ALL!
Y'ALL AIN'T SEEN SHIT LIKE THIS
SINCE YOU TURNED AROUND,
SAW YOUR MAMA'S VAGINA,
AND WATCHED YOURSELF
GETTING BORN!
LET'S GET IT STARTED!
[rap music plays]
YEAH!
PREPARE TO BE AMAZED!
IT'S COMING DOWN!
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER!
MAKE NOISE!
SMACK A BITCH IN THE FACE
IF YOU CAN,
'CAUSE HERE COMES
MY MAN RANDY!
[cheers and applause]
YEAH!
YOU ARE ABOUT
TO WITNESS THE BEST!
HE'S PUTTING MONEY
ON Y'ALL FOOLS!
I HOPE YOU GOT
BANK ACCOUNTS,
'CAUSE HE'S SPREADING OUT
LARGE AMOUNTS.
THEY CALL HIM RANDY!
STRAIGHT RANDY, Y'ALL!
*
- WHAT'S UP?
[cheers and applause]
MY NAME IS
RA-A-A-A-A-A-A-ANDY
WITH EIGHT "As"!
IF Y'ALL ARE READY
TO LAUGH YOUR DICKS OFF,
LET ME HEAR YOU SAY,
"YEAH."
all: YEAH.
- I SAID, "IF Y'ALL ARE READY
TO LAUGH YOUR DICKS OFF,
LET ME HEAR YOU SAY,
'YEAH.'"
all: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN IT'S RANDY TIME.
LET'S DO THIS SHIT.
FIRST JOKE.
[laughter]
OH, SHIT. OH, SHIT.
- WHAT'S UP, RANDY?
- IT'S TIME FOR ANOTHER
ONE OF RANDY'S
CRAZY FUCK STORIES,
A.K.A. A FUCK TALE.
IF Y'ALL WANT TO HEAR
A FUCK TALE,
LET ME HEAR YOU GO,
"FUCK TALES.
* OH-OOH-OOH "
[crowd replies]
SINCE YOU ASKED SO NICELY,
I'LL TELL YOU ONE.
[laughter]
I WAS HOOKING UP
WITH THIS GIRL RECENTLY...
* IN A FUCKIN' HOT TUB
AND WE'RE SITTING THERE
DOING OUR THING
AND IT'S GOING GREAT.
AND EVENTUALLY,
SHE'S LIKE, "RANDY?
"RANDY?
RANDY?
WILL YOU GO DOWN ON ME?"
AND I WAS LIKE, "YES,
I CAN DEFINITELY DO THAT."
BUT HERE'S THE THING,
Y'ALL.
WE'RE IN A HOT TUB.
SO I HAD TO DO THAT SHIT
UNDERWATER!
[laughter and applause]
SO I HOLD MY BREATH
AND I GO DOWN THERE.
I'M JUST SWIMMING AROUND
LOOKING FOR THE PUSSY,
LOOKING FOR THE PUSSY.
BAM! I FIND IT!
I START DOING MY THING.
IT'S GOING GREAT,
BUT EVENTUALLY I'M LIKE,
"DAMN!
"I CAN'T HOLD MY BREATH
THAT MUCH LONGER.
I GOT TO COME UP FOR AIR."
BUT THIS GIRL HOLDS MY HEAD
DOWN UNDER THE WATER.
THAT AIN'T COOL, LADIES.
THIS GUY KNOWS
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THIS GUY DEFINITELY KNOWS
BUT...I CAME UP FOR AIR.
AND THINGS ARE FINE.
BUT I KIND OF WISH
I WOULD HAVE DROWNED,
'CAUSE THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN THE
MOST BALLER DEATH OF ALL TIME.
THEY'D BE LIKE,
"HEY, RANDY'S PARENTS,
"THERE'S BEEN A TERRIBLE
CUNNILINIGUS ACCIDENT.
"YEAH, RANDY WAS EATING PUSSY
UNDERWATER.
I KNOW IT'S AWESOME,
BUT HE'S DEAD."
I'D HAVE THIS AWESOME
HEADSTONE.
IT'D BE LIKE,
"HERE LIES RANDY.
HE DIED WHILE EATING PUSSY."
AND THEN IT'LL HAVE
MY HANDPRINT RIGHT THERE
AND YOU WALK BY, THE HANDPRINT
WILL GIVE YOU A HIGH-FIVE.
BA-PAM! BA-PAM!
[laughter and applause]
FELLAS, YOU EVER BEEN
IN THIS SITUATION?
YOU GOT A GIRL BACK AT YOUR
PLACE AND SHE'S DOWN.
YOU'RE ALL EXCITED.
YOU'RE LIKE,
"* I'M GONNA GET MY FUCK ON
"* I'M GONNA GET
MY FUCK ON TONIGHT *
"* YES I'M GONNA
GET MY FUCK ON *
"* I'M GONNA GET MY FUCK ON
"* I'M GONNA GET
MY FUCK ON TONIGHT *
"* YES I'M GONNA
GET MY FUCK ON *
"* I'M GONNA GET MY FUCK ON
* I'M GONNA GET MY FUCK
ON TONIGHT *"
AND SHE'S LIKE,
"RANDY, STOP DANCING."
[laughter]
AND YOU DO.
YOU STOP DANCING,
THEN YOU HEAD TO THE BEDROOM,
AND YOU ABOUT TO SET IT OFF.
AND WHAT HAPPENS EVERY TIME
YOU GET TO THIS MOMENT, FELLAS?
WHAT HAPPENS EVERY TIME
YOU GET TO THIS MOMENT?
YOU GOT TO TAKE
A HUGE SHIT!
SO YOU RUN IN THE BATHROOM AND
START PLAYING THE GAME
THAT RANDY LIKES TO CALL,
"MAKE A LOT OF NOISE
SO IT DON'T SOUND LIKE YOU
TAKING A SHIT!"
YOU CUTTING ON THE SINK
AND SHOWER.
SHE'S LIKE, "RANDY,
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THERE?"
"NOTHING.
I'M JUST BRUSHING MY TEETH
AND TAKING A SHOWER
AT THE SAME TIME."
BUT THAT'S ENOUGH NOISE EITHER,
SO YOU GOT TO RUN
IN THE KITCHEN.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE BLENDING
CARROTS AND CELERIES
AND TOMATOES.
SHE'S LIKE, "RANDY WHAT
ARE YOU DOING IN THERE?"
"BITCH, I'M MAKING
YOU A SMOOTHIE!"
AND YOU GO BACK TO THE BEDROOM,
AND WHAT DOES SHE SAY?
WHAT DOES SHE ALWAYS SAY?
"RANDY?
I GOT TO GO PEE."
"NO!
YOU GON' SMELL MY SHIT!"
[laughter and applause]
- * RANDY
- I WAS THINKING
ABOUT THIS THE OTHER DAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT MUST BE CRAZY?
GETTING YOUR DICK SUCKED
IN AN IGLOO.
HOW YOU SUPPOSED TO STAY HARD
WHEN IT'S SO COLD?
IT'D BE LIKE,
"ESKIMO RANDY?
"ESKIMO VERSION OF RANDY?
CAN I GIVE YOU A BLOWJOB?"
I'D BE LIKE, "NO!
GIVE ME A BLANKET!
MY DICK'S COLD!"
- * RANDY
[laughter]
- KNOCK THAT
SHIT OFF.
IT'S TOO COLD.
[laughter]
- FELLAS, DO YOU KNOW HOW
TO GET YOUR GIRL
TO DO THE CRAZY SHIT?
I MEAN, THE CRAZY SHIT?
IT'S SIMPLE.
YOU CAN'T ASK HER
IN YOUR NORMAL VOICE.
IF I GOT A GIRL BACK
AT MY PLACE, I'M LIKE,
"HEY, LET'S HAVE SEX
IN MY KITCHEN."
SHE'D BE LIKE,
"NO, RANDY! NO!"
[laughter]
BUT IF I ASK HER IN MY SMOOTH,
SEXY, R&B VOICE--
IF I'M LIKE,
"* GIRL
"* I'M SAYING GIRL
"* I WANT TO FUCK YOU
IN MY KITCHEN TONIGHT *
* BY MY FRIDGE BY MY OVEN
BY MY FOREMAN GRILL *"
SHE'LL BE LIKE, "DAMN, RANDY.
LET'S DO THAT SHIT NOW!"
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
FUCKING AND MAKING CHICKEN.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
RANDY FUCKING AND MAKING CHICKEN
SINCE '86, BITCHES.
[cheers and applause]
- YOU GUYS LIKE IMPRESSIONS?
[cheering]
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS MY IMPRESSION
OF ME, RANDY,
GETTING A BLOWJOB AT AN IKEA.
"EXCUSE ME.
"CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE THE
LIGHTING AND HOME FURNISHING--
WHOA!"
- THEY CALL THAT SHIT
A "OOFSK."
[laughter and applause]
- THIS IS MY IMPRESSION
OF ME, RANDY,
GETTING A BLOWJOB
AT A WHOLE FOODS.
"EXCUSE ME.
"ARE THOSE YOUR ORGANIC
STRAWBERRIES OR ARE--
WHOA!"
- SHE GAVE YOU
A FAIR-TRADE BLOWJOB.
- YEAH.
[laughter and applause]
YOU GUYS, NOW--
ANYBODY SHOUT OUT
A SUGGESTION.
I'LL DO MY IMPRESSION
OF ME, RANDY,
GETTING MY DICK
SUCKED THERE.
[overlapping yelling]
SIX FLAGS.
HERE WE GO.
"UM, EXCUSE ME.
"CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE I CAN
FIND THE THING WHERE YOU--
"YOU KNOW, WHERE YOU ROLL
THE--WHAT IS IT CALLED?
SKEE BALL!"
- YOU MUST BE THIS TALL
TO RIDE RANDY'S DICK.
[laughter and applause]
RANDY.
- KEEP 'EM COMING.
KEEP 'EM COMING.
WHERE ELSE?
WHAT ELSE?
[indistinct yelling]
FUNERAL?
OH, YOU TRYING
TO STUMP RANDY, HUH?
YOU DON'T THINK RANDY GETS HIS
DICK SUCKED AT FUNERALS?
YOU ABOUT TO GET DEALT WITH.
[laughter and applause]
THIS IS MY IMPRESSION
OF ME, RANDY,
GETTING MY DICK SUCKED
AT A FUCKING FUNERAL.
[laughter]
"HEY, I JUST WANTED
TO SAY THAT, UM--
"THIS IS REALLY HARD FOR ME
TO SAY THIS,
"BUT I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR YOUR LOSS!"
THANK YOU, GUYS, SO MUCH!
MY NAME'S RANDY, Y'ALL!
GOOD NIGHT!
[rap music]
- MAKE SOME FUCKING NOISE
FOR RANDY!
STRAIGHT UP DOING IT
TO YOU EVERY TIME!
- GET THAT MONEY!
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com