Please!
Help me! Help me!
Thanks.
Yeah.
So what's left?
Well, we've got
all the camping gear.
You've got your
camera stuff, right?
Yeah, it's in the truck.
Well, then looks like all
we got left are the girls.
Are they ready?
Yeah, I just called.
Told them we're on our way.
Sounds good.
Hey, Will.
Yeah?
I really appreciate you coming
out on this trip with us.
Oh, it's no problem, man.
So we gonna have fun, or what?
I guess.
Come on, man,
are we gonna have fun?
You know it.
Well, let's hit it!
Um... Is Brooke here?
I'm sorry.
You must be Kyle.
We couldn't have chosen a more rainy day.
This weather, huh?
Brooke!
If I had nickel for every time...
Right.
Looks like you two hit it off.
Yeah.
He almost caught me sneaking her
out of the house in high school.
Apparently he hasn't
forgotten about it.
Hey, whoa!
Hey, Jenna.
Hey, James.
Will, you know Jenna, right?
Yeah. Of course.
Hi.
All packed up?
Yeah, yeah, just one second.
That was a pretty
enthusiastic greeting.
What're you talking about?
Whoa!
You two still have
something going on?
Maybe. Why?
Don't bullshit me.
I'm not. I'm not bullshitting you.
You're doing that face
you do when you lie.
Okay. All right.
It's a small thing.
Let's not make it into
a big thing, okay?
What the hell is he doing?
I'm so sorry.
You can't be serious.
He fucking hates me.
You... You didn't tell
about us, did you?
You serious?
He'd freak out.
We've got it under control.
Daddy didn't know
that Will was going.
He's not too fond of you, Will.
Great.
Chill. Just chill.
It's okay.
Hey.
Heard you're coming along?
Yeah.
All right.
It's good to have you, man.
Will, what brings you along?
Well, James asked me to come
along and take some photos
while you guys
conduct your interview.
Interview?
What interview?
That's what
we're doing actually.
We're going to Madison County
to interview an author.
Why?
Well, I've been writing letters
back and forth with this guy
for a few weeks now.
He invited us out to interview
him for my thesis paper.
I thought we'd make
a trip out of it.
There's a lot of controversy
around the book actually.
It's about a guy
named Damien Ewell.
According to the author,
David Randall,
he killed around 33 people over the
course of a couple of decades.
No one in the town told anyone.
Is this true?
David Randall claims it is.
But no one believes him, right?
I'm not sure. I mean,
that's part of the interview.
I want to get the people's point
of view on the whole situation.
So about how far away is this?
It's a good half day drive.
The only way to get to it
is through the hills,
so lots of twists, and turns.
Hope nobody
gets motion sickness.
I guess this is a good chance
to get out and stretch
if anyone needs to.
Anybody need anything to drink?
I'll take a water.
Water. Anybody else?
All good.
How about you, Kyle? You
want a hotdog or something?
Thank you.
Who's that?
You need a jump?
No, sir. We're just waiting on our
friend over here to get his sea legs.
Oh, I see.
Where are you headed?
We're actually headed
to Madison County.
What're you doing going there?
Well, we're gonna write
this, like, paper...
We're actually headed that
way to get to the Mulberry.
Gonna do some canoeing.
Oh.
Where are your canoes?
Uh, we're gonna rent 'em
down at the entrance.
Smart man.
Yes, sir.
All right, y'all take care.
You know, there's a road
that you could take
just before the 16.
Save you almost 30 minutes.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, and it's not
as hilly either.
Be good for your
friend over there.
It's called Pettigrew.
All right, I appreciate that.
No problem.
Y'all take care.
So, how'd you get
a hold of this guy?
Well, I contacted him from the
address on the back of the book.
But it took him a while
to get back to me.
Does he write you often?
Yeah, yeah, kind of.
I mean, it usually
takes him a few days
to get back to me
each time though.
Why don't you just
e-mail, call?
I would, but he doesn't
have a phone or a computer.
God, that's gotta be awful.
Can you imagine the privacy?
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Do you want me to come with you?
No, I'm a big girl.
I can go by myself.
So, James, are you finally
going to make your move?
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God, don't play dumb.
She's into you.
Really? What'd she say?
Hey, I can't break
the code of girl talk.
But I definitely think
she likes you.
Don't act like it's some
kind of surprise, okay?
Yeah.
So, what's the plan
for tomorrow?
Kyle.
No, no, it's fine.
Well, when we get into town,
we're gonna talk
to some of the people
before going out
to David's place.
There. Happy?
So. About Jenna.
I really think that
you should just...
What're you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Do it.
Thanks. Thanks for the help.
You're...
Ow! What the...
Hell, my...
Hey, James.
Yes, ma'am?
I was wondering, you
didn't happen to notice
anyone else here camping
last night, did you?
No. Not that
I know of. Why?
No reason.
It's just I saw a car leaving
earlier this morning.
It looked like the one
from last night.
Well, we are still kind
of close to the highway.
I know.
You don't think that guy had
any bad intentions yesterday,
do you?
Nah, he seemed friendly enough.
I figure if he was going
to do us any harm,
he would've done it last night.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Hey! What the
fuck are you doing?
Oh, what you thought I was
actually going to take that road?
Why not?
What are the chances of that
guy telling us it's faster,
we take it and then
get completely lost?
You've got a point.
So, Kyle, do you
have a girlfriend?
No.
No, no, don't let him fool you.
He's got lots of lady friends.
Who knows, Kyle,
maybe we can find you
a little hillbilly girl to
hang out with out here, huh?
What about you, Brooke?
No. No boyfriend for me
at the moment.
I'm probably going
to grad school.
You know, trying to
keep my options open.
Really?
Yeah, why?
Just never really
talked about that.
Well, it's something that I've
been thinking about by myself.
Hey can you pull over soon?
I have to pee.
Hey, I'm gonna go
in those trees.
I'm gonna come keep a look out.
No. No, no.
I'll be fine.
I'll be within earshot.
Got to take a piss anyway.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, come on, man!
Oh, no, don't "come
on" me, that's cute.
Go on.
There we go. Oh!
Okay, rub his belly.
Okay, now go lower.
Just kidding.
Wonderful work,
ladies and gentlemen.
Those ought to be good.
Maybe.
Just because
he's a good photographer.
So, what's the story with Will?
He seems like a nice guy.
Oh, he's a great guy.
We met in high school.
Always had a camera
in his hand.
Yeah, you two seem to
be really good friends.
Yeah, we are.
Well, it was actually his idea to
come out here and take pictures
to go with my thesis.
Pretty interesting, huh?
Not really.
Hey, Brooke, you ready?
Holy shit!
What was that?
I'm sorry, baby.
I just thought we'd have
a little bit of fun
while we're out here
in the middle of nowhere.
That's not exactly the
kind of fun I had in mind.
What kind of fun
did you have in mind?
Do you wanna fuck
right here in the woods?
Uh-huh. You know,
I do have the camera.
Uh-huh.
Mmm.
Psych.
What do you mean, psych?
What? Is it the rain?
You fell for it. Yes.
It's too wet to do that here.
It can get a lot wetter out here.
Ah!
What? What the fuck?
- Come on.
- What was that?
What was what?
I heard a noise.
Hang on.
Will, I heard a noise.
I didn't hear anything.
What the fuck were you
doing with my sister?
Kyle, stop!
Were you spying on her?
No, this isn't what
it looks like.
No, Kyle!
Come on. Stop!
No, I wasn't.
Let me see your camera.
Why?
Because I want to see the camera.
I want to see the fucking camera.
Let me see
the goddamn pictures.
I'll show you the pictures.
Stop it.
Give me the fucking camera.
Stop it!
Ahhh!
Whoa! Whoa! What happened?
This fucking pervert
was spying,
probably taking
pictures of Brooke.
No, I wasn't.
You know what?
This guy is fucking nuts.
You're fucking kidding me.
Hey! Hey!
Kyle, chill.
Will wouldn't do that.
I don't know, what the
fuck he would do.
Will's my boyfriend, Kyle!
All right?
We've been seeing
each other for months.
What... What?
It's true. You need
to chill out, Kyle.
Let's just drop it, okay?
There's no sense in getting
pissed at each other.
Let's get back to the car.
We've gotta keep moving.
- Fuck!
- You okay?
Phew! You really know how to pick
a place, you know that, James?
So, we're here now.
Where do we go?
Hungry?
Starving.
Let's stop and get some food.
If we can find a place.
Why is everyone staring at us?
I don't know.
Hi, ma'am.
Hi there, young man.
What can I do for you?
We were wondering if we
could get some food?
Certainly. What would you like?
Just whatever.
Burgers, fries, and sodas for all 5 of us.
Of course.
Uh, ma'am, do you
have veggie burgers?
She's a vegetarian.
No, I'm sorry.
We don't get many
of those around here.
I'll just have some fries.
That'll be $15.
What? That's it?
Thank you.
Let me ask you something.
Why does everyone here
have a staring problem?
Well, it's because
we don't get many
strangers around here.
Oh, yeah?
Why is that?
Well, there are a lot of folks
who don't like people
they don't know
around them and their families,
and farms and such.
Jeez, paranoid much?
Well, we mean you no harm.
No. I'm sure.
Why don't you kids have a seat.
Your food will be ready
in a few minutes.
So, ma'am...
Erma.
Erma. Uh, you wouldn't
happen to know
David Randall would you?
David Randall... Hmm.
Nope. Sorry,
doesn't ring a bell.
Well, he's the writer of this
book, Devil in the Woods.
Oh, that David Randall.
Yes, ma'am. What can
you tell me about him?
He's long gone,
as far as I know.
What about Damien Ewell?
Oh, Damien Ewell's
just a made-up person.
Doesn't exist,
just like that book.
But the letters.
I've been getting letters.
Oh!
Someone was
playing a prank on you.
All right. Thanks.
So, what'd she say?
She says, David isn't here
and Damien isn't real.
You're joking, right?
Please tell me we didn't
come all the way down here
for someone who isn't real.
He is real.
And David is here. I have
the letters to prove it.
Well, I guess we're
gonna need more than that.
What are you doing?
I'm going outside.
I'm coming too.
So, where are we going?
I don't know, I just wanted
to see what was down here.
Oh, I wonder
who these belong to.
Damien.
They're his trophies.
Oh, look, there's a nice spot
for a car right over there.
Uh, do you think she was
telling the truth about David?
I don't know.
She seemed a little off.
I can't believe
he lives out here.
He's like a hermit.
Yeah.
Maybe he's a lone
rider kinda guy.
You know, like your brother.
Um... I'm sorry
about him, earlier.
No, no. Don't be.
He overreacts sometimes.
No. The guy
doesn't like me.
That's not overreacting.
Dad's told him some stuff
that he's heard about you.
Bad reputations never
leave you in small towns,
do they?
Well, what's my reputation?
You are the cute,
innocent girl next door
that got swept away
by the dashing rebel.
Then why am I with you?
Because I'm irresistible.
Mmm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
And I'm going to use that
to win over your dad
and he's going to love me too.
And you think that'll work?
Yeah.
I'm gonna make it work.
Because I don't want Kyle
tagging along on our honeymoon.
Not funny.
Funny?
You should have heard
what I was going to say.
Will, come on.
We're leaving!
Duty calls.
You're ready to go?
Mmm-hmm.
- Where you've been?
- So what's the plan?
We're gonna go
to David's house.
I got the woman to tell
me where the address is.
And we're going to trust
some old lady
who lives in the middle
of the woods?
Got no other choice.
Let me get a quick
shot of the diner.
Oh! Sorry.
What exactly are you
takin' pictures of?
My friends and I are doing a
write-up on Madison County.
- Is that so?
- Mmm-hmm.
Well, you see this is
my truck right here,
and I don't appreciate
you takin' pictures of it.
Well, you see, I don't want anything
to do with you or your truck.
So why don't you
move it out of my shot?
Want to say that again?
It'd be in your best interest
to put that knife away.
You kids best be getting out
of here while you still can.
He'll be gettin' wind of you
soon and when he does...
Shit. Thank you. I can't
believe you did that.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Did you see that?
Yeah.
I think we should leave.
We're not leaving.
That guy pulled
a knife on us, James!
You've never seen
a knife before?
People get robbed daily
in big cities,
and they don't move away.
No, that doesn't make it
any better, James.
We're staying.
We leave now, then all that
shit we just went through
was for nothing.
Will got a knife pulled on him.
So what?
You get your interview,
you get your pictures,
and we get the hell
out of here.
If we leave now,
we're making a bigger
deal than it should be.
We'll just try to stay
out of harm's way...
Look out!
What the fuck?
What the fuck was that?
Fuck who it was,
we almost hit him!
Did you not see his face?
Yeah, it's called inbreeding.
♪ And we'd mellow out
in the light of the sun
♪ We will ride tonight
♪ With evil spirits we'll fight
♪ To protect our land
♪ To protect our kin
♪ They have their full might
on this full moon night
♪ But we'll make 'em understand
♪ On this land we stand
♪ On the full... ♪
Do you think it's safe?
I don't wanna get shot at
or anything like that.
No, we'll be fine.
Come on.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Hey! Open up!
Let's go.
No one's home.
Let's leave.
So we drove all this way
to grab some food
and knock on someone's door?
Sounds like something
I would say.
Because it's stupid.
We're not leaving.
Then what are we
supposed to do?
We need to go back
to the diner,
get more information
from those people.
I'll go.
What?
I'll go back to the diner.
Shouldn't we stay together?
Obviously, he can
take care of himself.
Look, I'll be fine.
Ask to use their phone
when you get there.
Yeah, no problem.
Hey, Kyle!
Here, take the car.
It'll be faster.
Just be careful.
Hi there, young man.
Hi.
Um... You said 1201 Country Lane
is a few miles down the road.
One with the gated drive, right?
Yes, sir.
There's no one there.
Of course not.
He left about the time
his book came out.
Did Damien Ewell kill him?
Oh! I told your friend,
Damien Ewell is
a made-up character.
Where would he get the ideas
for the book if it's not true?
People's imaginations
run wild sometimes.
People around here,
they didn't like it much
that he was telling stories
about them, right?
He made small town
people look bad.
Does David have any family in
the area that we can visit?
No, his family is all
passed, many years ago.
Would you mind telling me where
the nearest cemetery is?
Not at all.
Hey, what about
that barn down there?
Should we go look around?
It might have something
with his name on it.
You know, it could be
where Damien took
the dead body of David Randall.
Doubtful.
Wait. Why, you don't think
this guy's dead?
Not if he's been
sending me letters, no.
Where is he?
And why does everyone around here
act like they don't know this guy?
I don't know.
I'll tell you why? It's because
they're covering something up.
Well, what does the book say?
May I?
Here we go,
story of Damien Ewell.
"Damien was the most dangerous,
undiscovered serial killer in America.
"He killed an estimated
33 people. Maybe more.
"And no one ever
said a word about it."
What the fuck, man?
"He was born in the 1970s.
"His mother was
a great and loving woman,
"until one day, she met a man
that was from out of town.
"He eventually moved in
"and became the closest thing
"Damien ever had to a father.
"But they still
didn't get along."
Hey, are you okay?
I saw you was up here snoopin'.
You ain't with them police,
is you?
Police? No.
What police?
They was looking for
the missing girl.
Have anything to do
with Damien Ewell?
I reckon so.
"Around the age of 11
Damien ran away from home
"and was found days later on the
side of the road, left for dead.
"One of the people
in the town found him.
"He was badly disfigured.
"He'd been tortured to
within an inch of his life.
"They took him home
and from there,
"the townspeople
became very paranoid.
"Someone had hurt
one of their own."
Did they ever find out
who did it?
It was his mother's boyfriend.
That sounds made-up.
It's not.
What happened to him?
He died.
Well, did someone kill
this guy, the boyfriend?
It doesn't say.
Well, that's great.
And here we are,
asking people questions,
I'm sure they don't want
to give the answers to.
You said something
about a girl.
What girl?
Her daddy was sure
Damien did it.
Do you know Erma?
Don't you get it?
They was the ones
that was in on it.
What do you mean?
Hey, I'm not snooping.
Hey, where are you going?
You guys go down
to the end of the driveway.
We'll check the barns
and the house.
Huh! Great.
Come on, let's go poke around.
So, what are we looking for?
Honestly?
I'm not even sure.
Who would've ever thought it
would be this much trouble
to interview a person?
Yeah. No joke.
You know it would
be really easy
to just pack up and go home.
So you're siding with
Brooke and Will now?
No. It just seems like
a lot to go through
just to write a paper,
don't you think?
And wouldn't it be
a huge waste of time
to pack up, drive
all the way out here,
and turn around and go home
after just a couple of hours?
Touche.
So, Jenna,
what brings you all the way
out to Madison County?
Well, once upon a time
there was a really
nice guy named James
who sat behind me in my English class.
Really now?
Yeah, he dragged me
all the way out here
to write a paper on some
book I've never read.
Why didn't you read the book?
Because I've got better
things to do with my time.
Okay.
And what did you think
of this James guy?
He was a bit
of a pig, actually.
Oh, yeah? How so?
Well, occasionally, I would catch
him staring at my ass in class.
And you saw him doing this?
I sure did.
And how come you never brought
this to his attention?
Because I told you earlier,
I didn't mind.
Hey!
It's open.
Should we go in?
Yeah, yeah, I am. You can
stay here if you want.
Hello?
Holy shit!
Look at this.
Is that the guy
from the highway?
Looks like him, doesn't it?
It says David.
Do you think that
means David Randall?
I can't imagine
who else it would be.
What's this?
Daddy, Erma, David
and Damien.
Hey, Brooke!
Jenna, is that you?
This place definitely
has a lot of...
- Sorry.
- Stop.
Let's check this out over here.
Shit.
Jesus!
Looks like a mangled
dungeon master lives here.
Looks like someone
still lives here.
Yeah.
Don't do that.
It's okay.
This is turning
into so much work.
I thought this was going
to be a nice trip for us.
It will, it will.
As soon as we're done with James'
stuff, we'll get out of here, okay?
We'll spend a few relaxing
days in the woods.
Just you and me.
Can my brother come?
That's not funny.
Oh, that's weird.
Hey guys, where'd you go?
Hey!
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought
you were someone else.
I wonder why Kyle's
not back yet.
Do you think he got lost?
Maybe.
I think I'd better go find him.
Well, you're not
leaving me here.
It'll be fine.
I'll just run down there,
it'll be quicker
if I'm by myself.
What, are you trying to
call me fat or something?
There's not an ounce
of fat on your body.
Go catch up to Will and Brooke.
I'll meet you guys
back up here.
Jenna?
Yeah?
Be careful.
Oh, I'm Kyle.
What's your names?
All right.
Fuck me, man.
Mind if I join you
guys down there?
What, me?
Smells really weird in here.
Musty.
That's quite an antler
collection he's got.
Look at this.
What are you going
to do with that?
I don't know.
Bend over, I'll show you.
Will!
Come on?
Yeah, I think I'm going
to hold on to this.
In case we run into any bears
or maybe I get a base hit.
Get out of here.
No mailbox.
I guess the whole not rain, nor sleet,
nor snow thing doesn't apply out here.
Wait, what about
that "posted" sign?
It's got to account
for something.
Maybe we'll run into
a neighbor who will tell us
that we're as crazy
as the old lady did.
Maybe we should just go back.
What if someone's home?
Well, they obviously
don't want to be bothered,
or they wouldn't live out here.
Ah, come on.
Oh, God!
It's a real
fixer-upper.
Got it?
Looks like nobody's home.
Well, let's go meet
with James and Jenna then.
Hey, Brooke?
Yeah?
The stuff you said before,
about grad school,
are you serious about that?
Why?
I don't know. I was just
wondering, that's all.
Will, don't be gay.
Yeah.
Gay! Jesus!
Come on, let's go.
Actually, can you just
give me a quick second?
I'm gonna take a quick
piss somewhere over there.
Okay. Do you want me
to come with you?
Why, you wanna hold it
or something, huh?
No!
No?
Well, then, hang tight,
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Hey!
Brooke?
Decided you wanted to hold it?
Will?
Who the fuck are you, huh?
Huh?
Ahhh!
No! Wait!
Please!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Ahhh!
Will! No!
Brooke!
Brooke, over here!
Jenna, he got Will!
Who?
Who got Will?
I don't know. I don't know.
It's some man!
He killed him, Jenna,
he killed him!
He killed him?
You saw this?
Jenna, we gotta go.
We gotta get help.
Please!
Oh, my!
Where's Kyle?
Are you okay?
My friend.
From earlier.
Yes, dear. He was here.
And?
And he left.
Where did he go?
He went to find some answers,
that's what he told me.
Now, tell me everything
that happened.
He came out of nowhere.
Who?
I don't know.
Keep walking.
Was it the man
from the highway?
Was it the man with the knife?
I don't know.
Jenna!
There wasn't anybody at that
old house you sent us to.
Oh! Of course not.
I told you David hadn't
lived here in many years.
Bullshit!
There was nothing
I could do, Jenna.
Oh, sweetie, don't even think
about something like that, okay?
We're going to get help and
everything is going to be fine, okay?
Are you calling me a liar?
I'm saying that I don't think
you're telling me the truth.
Jenna, he got Will.
Come on.
I thought David didn't
have any family?
Where did you get that?
Where's his daughter?
I think you better leave now.
Why didn't you tell me
you were Damien's mother?
Oh, his face!
It was awful, Jenna.
No, get up.
We have to keep going.
Boy, you have gone and
gotten yourself in a mess
of something you'll
never get out of.
You're in too deep.
Best start runnin'.
You'll never get out alive.
There's no escape.
He's gonna be
on your scent soon.
And when he is,
you're gonna be dead.
Run! Run!
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, nice young man.
Please, Jenna!
James!
Get in the truck.
I told y'all
to go down Pettigrew.
What? What are you talking about?
Are you David Randall?
Yeah, I'm David Randall.
Why didn't you tell me
that when we first met?
It's complicated.
There's so many things that
don't make sense around here.
They'll all make sense
soon enough.
Jenna!
Hey!
Over here!
Come on out.
Where's my daughter?
Is that the last of 'em?
Sorry, James.
Come on, you son of a bitch!
Ahhh!
Help!
Help me!
Please!
Help me, please!
Help!
Help me!
Help me, please!
Jenna.
You kids don't worry none.
He'll be in here soon.
We're never gonna
get out alive.
Don't say that, I'm gonna
get us out of here.
Where am I?
Who is that?
Shh!
Just stay quiet.
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
I had no choice.
What's going on?
Who are you?
Is this your daughter?
Yes.
And this is your plan
to save her?
I had to do something!
You used me as bait!
What are you talking about?
David,
where are my friends?
If they're not here,
they're dead.
We're never
going to get out of here.
Damien, we've done
nothing to hurt you.
Damien.
Let us go. You'll
never see us again.
No!
Ahhh!
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Look out! Ahhh!
No!
He's lost a lot of blood.
Let's get him out of here.
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry!
Dad! No!
No!
Come on.
Howdy there!
Oh, my!
My Lord, child.
What happened to you?
The man...
The man with the face.
He killed my friends.
Who killed your friends, missy?
The pig.
Pig head.
Where are my other friends?
Oh, I haven't seen
your friends, dearie.
We've been slow
since I saw you last.
Oh, my, I'll get you
a glass of water.
Here.
Who did you say
killed your friends?
Big pig head.
We don't have a moment to lose.
You go stand by my car.
I'll get my keys and I'll take
you to the doctor's house,