CROOKED ARROW:
Long ago...
...the Medicine Game was given to the people
of the Haudenosaunee...
...to entertain the Creator.
[MAN 1 SPEAKS IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[MEN WHOOPING]
[GRUNTING]
[MAN 2 SPEAKS IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[MAN 3 SPEAKS IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[MEN WHOOPING]
[MAN 4 SPEAKS IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
BOTH:
Ooh.
BRYAN:
Holy stick work!
Somebody better mail that guy's helmet
back from Syracuse.
[PLAYERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Outlet pass and Coventry Academy is pulling
off another dominating coast-to-coast play.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
BRYAN:
Another goal for Coventry Academy!
All-Star middie Clay Watson
just obliterated a Sunaquot defender.
- Chewy, take him out!
CHEWY: How did you miss that?
OWEN: Are you all right?
JIMMY: I can't move it.
[HORN BLARES]
Let's bring it in.
BRYAN: And at halftime, the defending champs
lead the over matched Sunaquot, eight to three.
It's game one of the season
and it's time for this team to tap out.
If anyone's still listening, please enjoy
this commercial-free intermission...
...as we still have no sponsors, here on
the Bryan Sports Broadcasting Network...
...the number one and only radio show
covering upstate prep school lacrosse...
...and streaming live on BSBN.com.
BEN:
All right, guys, bunch up.
Listen, they are a very good team.
But we can be too.
We have got to bring our minds
together as one.
- Chewy, you gotta move your feet.
- I do move my feet. They move theirs faster.
Reed, you can stop some shots
if you take a step toward the shooter.
- Cut down the angle.
- I was protecting my backside.
This ain't dodge ball, moron.
Your job is to try and get hit.
And your job is to pass the ball, Jimmy.
Owen was wide open
when you got your ass handed to you.
SAMMY:
Oh, whipped.
[ALL LAUGH]
BEN:
Owen. Sammy. Enough.
Starters, get ready for the second half.
We'd be better off scrimmaging
our middle-school team.
But I'm not gonna let today go to waste.
In the second half,
I want you all using your weak hands.
But don't you let up. Not for one second.
Remember who we are.
Scared to go back?
- I'm hurt.
- Your feelings or your shoulder?
- A kiss would fix both.
- Ha.
Ah!
- Toby, you're in.
- Me?
NADIE: At attack.
- Against Coventry?
Okay...
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[PLAYERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
BRYAN:
Number 17 is a real firecracker.
REED:
Keep it up! Give him that shaft! Get him, Nadie!
BRYAN: This guy is frustrating the Coventry
offense with relentless position defense.
Uh-Oh.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
BRYAN:
Number 17 is blindsided by an illegal hit.
CHEWY:
You gotta be kidding me, man!
BRYAN: Here we go! It's a fight, folks!
A rumble on the rez.
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
EMMITT:
Watson, Dawes, enough!
CHEWY:
Come on, boy. Want a taste, Wonder Bread?
EMMITT: Back! Get back.
BEN: Jimmy!
Jimmy, sideline!
EMMITT:
Keep your helmet on!
SAWYER:
Geronimo!
JULIE:
Get off of him! Chewy, on the bench!
EMMITT: Get off of him!
JULIE: Enough!
EMMITT:
Keep your helmets on.
JULIE:
Sam my, stop it.
Nadie.
- Come on.
- No! Ow!
EMMITT: Stay there!
They're not worth it anyways!
Hey, seems as though you got me shaking
Hey, you make me cry
You start me up
And then you leave
You're changing right in front of me
[BUGLE PLAYING "CHARGE"
ON SLOT MACHINE]
- Whoo!
- Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
JOE:
Winning some wampum, ladies?
WOMAN:
Oh, my God! Ah!
Three Tom Hot Toddies.
I want to get that jackpot back.
MAN:
Don't shoot, Chief.
JOE:
Oh! Five dollar free play!
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
Ah. Impressive stacks, ladies.
Hey. Got a fortune for me, Chief y?
Of course. Chief y always has fortunes
for beautiful Indian maidens.
- There you go.
- I hope he has one for me too.
Mr. Geyer.
Ladies, if you don't mind,
I'd like to borrow Chief y for a minute.
[BUGLE PLAYING "CHARGE"
ON SLOT MACHINE]
[WOMEN CHEERING]
GEYER:
That's impressive design work, Joe.
But how far have you gotten
with the casino expansion rights?
Almost there. I'm meeting
with my primary opposition this evening.
GEYER:
Hmm.
Joe, I came to you with this deal because you
were a closer when you worked for me.
And I can guarantee a full partnership
if you pull this off.
But there are a lot of other poor Indian tribes
out there with wasted land.
Yes, but we Sunaquot are poorer
and more wasted than most.
I want to help your people,
but I can't wait forever.
Ah. Look, tell your people
whatever it is they want to hear...
...and get my deal done.
BEN:
Nadie, you need to get that leg elevated.
[EAGLE CHIRPS]
This is your fault.
Why did you enter the game?
Because nobody else would go in, Daddy.
And I was kicking ass out there,
you saw me play.
BEN:
And I heard the doctor.
And if you don't heal properly,
you may never play again.
[BEN SIGHS]
I've got a meeting at the Pow Wow.
You stay with her, this pain medication
can have some side effects.
Oh, no funny business, you two.
Right, because I can't wait to hook up with
the guy that got my ankle broken in two places.
I told you, it's not my fault.
Nobody made you go in the game.
Okay, nobody had to, Jimmy.
We needed a player and you were hurt,
so I stepped up.
Ow! Okay, I said leave me alone!
Now we know the side effects.
[ALL CHANTING]
Good day for a Pow Wow.
How you doing, man?
Hey, Rollingstone. What's up, my man?
It's Rollingwind.
I've told you like 10 times before.
JOE:
Yeah, I meant that.
Julie? Julie Gifford?
What are you doing here?
- I teach high school.
- Since when?
Like two weeks ago.
What are you doing here?
I run the casino.
So how you been?
I'm good. I'm really good.
The casino, huh?
Figures. Joe Money
pimping out his people.
Wow, really?
You do know that my casino profits
paid for your brand-new school buildings.
So if I'm a pimp,
what does that make you?
WOMAN: Ah!
- Grandma!
GRANDMA:
Ah...
Julie!
Of all the teachers in New York,
you just had to hire my ex-girlfriend?
Dr. Gifford is more than a teacher.
Doctor?
Julie wrote the only book there is
about the Sunaquot culture.
You should take one.
It's very enlightening.
And she was the only applicant
we could afford to pay.
Which is a perfect reason
you should deed more land to the casino.
You know my position, son.
We have no more land.
Dad, land is all we have.
And land is all we need.
Come on, let's just enjoy the celebration.
Celebration? What celebration?
Nobody came to the Pow Wow.
Drive downtown
and see the men begging for work.
And then tell me
that the land is all our people need.
Our people.
We haven't been your people
for quite some time, son.
Well, I'm here now, and I have a plan.
But I'm running out of time.
It'd be nice to have your support
at the tribal council.
Not just as an elected official,
but as my father.
[JIMMY SNORING]
JIMMY:
Oh!
How'd she get her pajamas on?
I didn't look, Mr. Logan. I swear.
[DOOR CLOSES]
JOE: Our partner, Geyer Enterprises, projects
that our annual share of gaming revenue...
...will exceed 10 million dollars.
And in five years, we'd be able to build
a hospital, along with the school.
But can we trust his vision?
Have you seen his casino?
We have seen the new school buildings...
...and have decided that Abooksigun may build
on the land between the casino and the river.
What? This is not acceptable.
Your blood cloud your vision, Hagawa?
We are not finished.
Abooksigun, you may expand the casino...
...under the condition
that you first re-examine your spirit...
...and prove yourself worthy
in the manner of your father's choosing.
BEN: You play redskin to the whites,
then white to your people.
JOE:
It's just for show.
BEN:
To show what exactly?
NADIE:
Hey, Grandma.
You have forced me
into a very difficult position, Mother.
For the good of our people.
Yes.
GRANDMA:
Hey, Lady Bug, how is the leg?
NADIE: It still hurts a little.
GRANDMA: Keep it elevated.
- So the swelling goes down.
NADIE: I am.
I have decided the manner
of your spirit quest.
You will return to the Creator's game.
Return? You mean, like, play?
No, you don't play.
Our coach quit
and I'm not a suitable replacement.
Well, neither am I.
I have a business to run.
Which will not expand as you wish,
unless you do as I require.
Dad, you know why I don't play anymore.
I do, and they call it
the "medicine game" for a reason.
Let it heal you.
Our next game is tomorrow,
the season ends on Memorial Day.
I'm only half Sunaquot,
shouldn't that mean only half a season?
Restore pride to our people,
and their game.
That is your first obligation.
- There's more?
- To re-examine your spirit.
Yeah, can you give me some
defined deliverables on that?
No, but I know who can.
Is it within my power to assign
him a spiritual advisor?
It is most certainly.
BEN:
Good, then I assign you.
So, what? You're my babysitter now?
- That's howl roll, baby.
NADIE: Heh, heh.
Great.
[AUSTIN GIBBS' "I LIKE THE ONES"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
I like the ones who, I like the ones who
I like the ones
I like the ones who like to show me things
[MUSIC STOPS]
REED:
Oh, man.
Gentlemen.
SAM MY:
Look at this.
You're late.
Doesn't your fancy car have a clock?
- Yeah, it has GPS navigation too.
GRANDMA: Ugh.
I had to make a pit stop.
Man, you have a nice car here.
You two brothers or cousins?
- Yeah.
Okay, then.
All right, you two play attack,
you three middie...
...you three defense,
and I guess that makes you goalie.
I'm your new coach.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
NADIE:
Watch the cutters.
Go!
BRYAN:
That was quick.
The new suit on the sideline
hasn't made a big difference for the Sunaquot.
NADIE:
Come on, guys.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
NADIE:
Who's got point?
Reed, be aggressive!
Play your position.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Yeah, no, I know.
Yeah, it's a convertible.
You've got to hit him, Chewy!
REED:
Chewy, can you hit him?
CHEWY: Like you're any better, pretty boy
Why don't you step up?
Uh-huh. I'll be there after this game.
Yeah, I'll sign the check.
Just stall them, all right?
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Hey. Unless you're Googling halftime speeches
that don't totally suck...
...I suggest you put that down and coach.
- Stay in the game, man!
- Fine.
All right, guys, they're in a zone.
Run Z82 and work it around the wings.
Joe, they have no idea what that means.
Yeah, but it sounds good.
Jimmy! Whoo! Over here! Yo! Yo! I'm open.
Ball hog! Owen was wide open.
- Get out.
- Z82? It's not even a real play.
Sounds like a radio station.
JOE: You, you're in,
as long as you don't hog the ball too.
JIMMY:
Good luck with that.
Hey, who's the dorky white kid?
NADIE:
It's Toby, Dr. Gifford's son.
- Julie has a son?
NADIE: Oh!
Yeah, and he just got crushed.
Welcome to the club, kid.
[HORN HONKING]
GEYER: So how did your meeting
go with our opposition?
How much land
are you able to deliver, Joe?
JOE: The council approved construction
on the land here...
...where the current casino is,
up to the river here.
Great. We will break ground next week.
Actually, that's where we had to make
one concession.
We can't go until the end of May.
But that's two months.
I know. Uh, it's an ancient tribal law.
What law? I thought you were my insider.
I am. Uh... It's, uh, called:
[SPEAKS GIBBERISH]
It means "No disturb land in spring."
Your people didn't farm in the spring?
No, not really.
They were more hunter-gatherer,
scavenger types.
Like bears,
with a little bit of vulture mixed in.
My clan name means Vulture Bear.
I need a start date, Joe.
N ow.
The day after Memorial Day.
You're sure? There are no other
ancient tribal traditions I need worry about?
No.
This is from last night's reading.
"Loving that Land O' Lakes Maiden,"
by an Onondaga poet, Eric Gansworth.
She is the first lesson in love for many
Indian boys, all tanned hide and feathers
Features straight out of Hollywood
But she lights the spark for those red boys
And probably for some
Black and white and brown ones as well
For anyone who learns her tricks, really
And they're not that hard to master
So, what's this poem about?
That smoking-hot Indian lady
on the butter package.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Yes, Reed, that's clearly stated
in the title, but what else?
That smoking-hot Indian lady is a stereotype
we Native American women have to overcome.
We don't spread easy like butter,
we can be tough and strong.
Jimmy, your thoughts?
I think nobody cares about poetry.
I do. Actually I happen to love poetry.
Well, in that case...
BOYS:
Ooh.
Nadie, my wounded lady
Will you marry me?
I'm strong, tough
And man enough to churn your butter nightly
[ALL LAUGH]
JULIE: Chewy
CHEWY: Mm.
- Oh!
- Ow.
[CHATTERING AND LAUGHING]
JIMMY: Nice shot.
Now Maug has got another one.
Grandma, I'm not late today. Sis.
Wow.
All right, bring it in.
So that was pretty pathetic yesterday.
No focus, no fitness,
and zero team work.
We're gonna start over
with the fundamentals.
Passing and catching, line drills. Go.
Can't. No balls.
Maug's got them.
Okay. Who's Maug?
Protector of the forest.
Six-foot-10,
300 pounds of pure muscle.
Catch a deer
with his bare hands, eat it raw.
What you're saying is we're calling practice
on account of Sasquatch?
PLAYER 1: Yeah, pretty much.
PLAYER 2: Yeah.
Works for me.
- How about you go buy us some more balls?
PLAYER 3: Yeah.
JOE: How about you man up, Jimmy,
and go into the woods and get them yourself?
PLAYERS:
Ooh.
How about you call me Silverfoot.
How about you make me?
[PLAYERS CHUCKLING]
Today's lesson:
If you're afraid to go into the forest,
you've got no balls.
PLAYERS:
Oh!
Come on, Jimmy.
We ain't got no balls.
You're the one walking away.
Look at him, with his face buried
in that Crackberry all day.
[PLAYERS LAUGHING]
So tell me then,
how's your fitness, coach?
You want to go? We can go.
Everybody. On the line.
SAMMY:
Oh, come on.
Ready?
[GASPING]
Maybe you could coach baseball.
Strike three. You're out.
Dude, Italian leather boots.
[PANTING]
I'll show up if I have to,
but I can't coach these guys.
There's no weak warriors, Abooksigun,
only weak leaders.
And in this case, weak and slow.
[GROWLING AND LEAVES RUSTLING]
CROOKED ARROW: There was a time
when you beat the sun, Abooksigun.
JOE:
Crooked Arrow.
I hear you have returned
to the Creator's game.
Yeah, I'm sure you've heard why.
I also heard you're are O and 2.
Yeah, I don't know what to do.
These kids have had sticks
in their cradles.
But they're a joke right now.
Do you remember the story
of the eagle and the arrow?
No.
The eagle once ruled our skies.
And then, one day,
he was struck down by the arrow.
As he lay dying,
the eagle could not understand why.
The shaft of the arrow had been feathered
by one of his own plumes.
We often give our enemies
the means to our own defeat.
Look inside.
Ask your heart.
The truth may sleep, but it never dies.
It was only an oral language
until Hiawatha transcribed...
...the Haudenosaunee constitution
onto a wampum belt. Later, Ben Franklin...
[THUMPING ON WALL]
...copied your version
of three equal branches of government.
[MOUTHING]
Go.
JULIE: His famous quote, "if a bunch
of ignorant savages can govern fairly...
...then we should be able to do the same"...
- ...is the foundation of American democracy.
- What you want me to do?
Nadie?
- Hm?
JULIE: What's going on?
Uh, nothing.
Time for practice.
JULIE: This is my classroom,
and we will stay until I say otherwise.
JOE: So you like your new school so much,
you want to keep the kids late?
Even if it means denying them the opportunity
to participate in a traditional cultural heritage?
Oh, well, maybe I can make it up
to them with afield trip...
...to go visit Chief Wampum
and his bar-dancing waitresses.
Speaking of which, we're hiring,
if you can dance.
- And she can, she was a cheerleader.
STUDENTS: Ooh.
And valedictorian,
which your coach can't even spell.
Well, I guess I'll just sit out here
where it's warm and sunny...
...with a trunk load of surprises
for the lacrosse team.
BOY 1: Yo, are you serious?
BOY 2: What? That's us. We gotta get our buddy.
- All right, fine.
BOY 3: Whoo!
But we have a history test on Friday.
So I was thinking about what
happened when we raced.
JIMMY: When I smoked your ass?
PLAYERS: Ha-ha-ha.
I wasn't properly equipped.
JIMMY:
Yeah, right.
We've been giving our enemies
the means to defeat us.
But not anymore.
- Reebok, best on the market.
PLAYERS: Oh!
[CHATTERING]
PLAYER 1: That's awesome.
PLAYER 2: No way.
Little bang stick, 10K.
REED:
Look at this.
CHEWY:
Look at the bag in it, man.
And that's not all.
Thank you, Marilyn.
Marilyn stayed up all night
making these.
PLAYER 3: Oh, Jackpots.
PLAYER 4: Whoo-hoo!
Gotta look good to be good, right?
BRYAN [ON RADIO]:
That did not look good for the Jackpots.
Despite a makeover, the Sunaquot goalie
stood planted like a tree in the crease...
...insuring the loss to Sulgrave.
Today's broadcast was brought to you
by our very first sponsor...
...the Lucky Indian Casino,
where the Big Game-
[RADIO TURNS OFF]
JOE: Ten dollar free play at Lucky Indian Casino.
- Joe Logan?
- Yeah, that's my name, just use it at the door.
- You played for Coventry in '98, right?
Yeah, that was a long time ago.
No, I played here, at Sulgrave.
Senior year you destroyed us.
Yeah, if you say so.
MAN: He's being humble.
This guy right here, the best I've ever seen.
You went to Syracuse, right?
They called you Logan the Legend.
But whatever happened
in that championship game?
Sorry, man, we gotta go.
Here's another coupon.
Congrats on the win.
Okay, sure.
Good luck!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[CROWD CHEERING]
CROWD [CHANTING]:
Logan! Logan! Logan!
NADIE:
Heh. What you doing?
Hey! She walks.
I was just looking for this.
I've been doing a lot of driving lately and,
you know, trying to keep it fresh.
- Chumbawamba
- Ha-ha-ha.
Come on, these guys were awesome
for the one song.
Ooh. Can I look?
Uh, ahem. No, not tonight.
Okay, total strangers
know my brother better than I do.
Logan the Legend?
I actually prefer Joey Hustle.
- Whatever, they're equally lame.
- Heh.
NADIE:
What was she like?
Strong, like you.
Then how could she die so young.
There was no hospital at the reservation.
But I can fix that now, if Dad will let me.
Oh, my God, is that Dr. Gifford with you?
Yeah, we dated at Coventry.
No way.
Yeah way.
I wouldn't bring it up to her though.
NADIE: Okay.
JOE: Let's have some tunes.
Tunes.
JOE:
Yeah, that's what we used to say in the '90s.
[OVER SPEAKERS]
I get knocked down, but I get up again
NADIE: Are we really gonna listen to that?
- Oh, yeah.
JOE: All right, guys, take your pads off.
Don't need them today.
CHEWY:
What? No practice?
JOE:
Nope. No practice.
JIMMY: Whoo.
CHEWY: Yeah.
- We're running.
PLAYERS: Ugh.
JOE: Up there, to Defiance Rock.
How about you drag your old butt up there
and then you can tell us all about it.
[PLAYERS LAUGH]
I'll make you a deal.
You give me four balls,
I'll rip all four corners with Reed in goal.
[PLAYERS LAUGH]
If I miss, I go alone.
If I hit them all, we all run.
PLAYER 1: Take it.
PLAYER 2: Take that.
I gotta see this.
CHEWY:
Reed, you better save this, man.
He can't shoot.
SAMMY: Come on, Reed.
JIMMY: Come on, Reed.
PLAYERS: Ooh.
ALEX: What's that?
Lucky.
[PLAYERS CHATTERING]
ALEX:
Can't you stop an old man?
[PLAYERS G ROAN]
Reed, you should have stopped that one.
REED:
Right here, gramps, come on.
JIMMY: Come on, Reed.
CHEWY: Come on, Reed.
ALL:
Oh!
JIMMY:
What the--?
[PLAYERS CHATTERING]
JOE: We're running.
ALEX: That was cheating.
JIMMY: Why didn't you tell him to hit the bar?
REED: Why did you take that bet?
SAMMY:
Come on, come on, coach!
ALEX:
Come on, Reed, get bent.
CHEWY:
Guys, wait up.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLAYERS WHOOPING]
And this one's for the fall
And this one's for the earth we never had
JOE:
What's with the stick?
CHEWY:
Maug, he's here. He's everywhere, watching.
JOE: You do know that predators go
for the slowest in the herd, right?
JOE:
Take a right at the dead tree.
How old does my butt look now, Jimbo?
Go!
JOE: Whoo!
CROOKED ARROW: You almost beat the sun.
[JOE CHUCKLES]
CHEWY: Man, there's a reason
the white man invented cable cars.
CROOKED ARROW:
Guard your tongue in youth.
And in age you may mature a thought
that will be of service to your people.
How long does it take you to make one?
I don't make them, the Creator does.
This hickory tree is older than you.
I carve away all but the heart,
leaving only power and strength.
[CROOKED ARROW LAUGHS]
Your opponent does not want
to be clubbed by one.
This was my great grandfather's.
Over 200 years old.
And strong as the day it was made.
But metal sticks have offset heads.
With that you'd have to cradle all the time.
Don't worry, the offset head will fit on this.
The ball lives in the offset head,
but the spirit lives in the stick.
I may be old, but I'm not out of touch
I watch ESPNU on my iPad.
[ALL LAUGHING]
What's this?
That's the Crooked Arrow,
my Sunaquot name.
I have made sticks and arrows
for generations.
Each one is different,
and none are perfect.
No arrow flies straight.
There's nothing wrong
with a crooked arrow.
As long as it follows its own path,
it will find its way.
Sticks up.
Creator gave the game to the people
of the Haudenosaunee Nation.
They played and it pleased the Creator.
Now go play the game for our ancestors
who are no longer here to entertain the Creator.
[ALL WHOOPING]
You put a lot of work into these.
How much do I owe you?
You want to repay me?
Return lacrosse to our people.
BRYAN:
Welcome back to the rez, lacrosse fans.
Not that this game will qualify as lacrosse
against the beleaguered Jacked--
[STICK THUMPS]
Pots.
- Hey, Chad.
- Hello, Nadie.
Yeah, we're not the Jacked Pots any more.
PLAYERS:
Whoo! Crooked Arrows! Yahoo!
And Chad?
How about you show us some respect
on our land, okay?
Two. We're up by two. B line get in there.
BRYAN:
We're late in the third...
...and the newly minted Crooked Arrows
have put in a surprising effort.
Come on. Come on, Jimmy.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Head up, head up, head up. Come on.
Nice pick.
Yes!
Nice! All right, all right.
[JIMMY WHOOPING]
- That's not all right. That's not-- Jimmy!
JIMMY: Whoo!
JOE:
Hey! Hey, Silverfoot, knock it off.
Keep showboating.
Keep dancing, twinkle toes. Keep smiling.
Yeah, you're smiling now.
You won't be smiling later.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
NADIE:
Let's see some sweat, jock straps.
JOE: I'm not running a ballet here, Silvertoes,
this isn't "Dance of the Sugar Plums."
You want to be a ballerina,
plié off to Broadway.
You want to play lacrosse,
respect your team.
What did you guys say?
Hey, hey! Guys, guys, break it up, okay?
Come on.
No secrets now, we're a team.
We all speak the same language.
- Keep them running till I get back.
- Okay. Ready?
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[NADIE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Keeping office hours, Dr. Gifford?
I need Jimmy when you're through with him.
We've got a problem with him graduating.
He's failing English.
You know, I always thought
you'd be a teacher.
Location is a bit of a surprise.
Your people made quite an impression
on me, coach.
Did you know that Jimmy
doesn't understand a word of Sunaquot?
A lot of kids don't learn it these days.
Well, I think they should.
And why would that matter to you?
We're reconnecting with our heritage.
Really?
Okay, what do you have in mind?
"Motion, reverse, zone, V-cut, crease"
and "hit me I'm open"?
The Unishees use Sunaquot on the field.
I think it could give the team a big advantage.
Well, yes, Julie, I will have
dinner with you this evening.
[IN ENGLISH] Joe, when you can ask me
in your native tongue...
...I'd be glad to help
for the sake of my students.
Including the ones who just puked.
[PLAYERS GRUNTING]
[OVER SPEAKERS]
All this time I thought I was wasting
But you've gone and saved me
And now I can breathe again
You're bringing me back to life
[MUSIC STOPS]
You're supposed to meet with Dr. Gifford
today about your test.
Why do you care?
Because if you flunk out, you can't play.
[SIGHS]
You know, Jimmy,
I'm trying to do something special here.
Provide our people with a little hope.
But to do that, I need to win games.
And to do that, I need you.
Why bother?
To honor our people,
make lacrosse matter again.
Look, together we can turn things
around here in a big way.
But for that to happen,
I need you to be a leader, a team player.
I need a captain, Jimmy.
I'm already captain.
Prove it.
You can start by passing the ball.
Hey. He was a ball hog at your age.
Still a show boater.
All right, guys.
I've translated the plays into Sunaquot.
And like the Navajo code talkers
in World War Il...
...we'll confuse the hell out of our enemies.
You two help with pronunciation, please.
[SAMMY LAUGHS
AND SPEAKS IN SUNAQUOT]
SAM MY:
Really?
What you have here for V-cut, vagi...
Uh, actually kind of means like a woman's--
You know?
- What?
REED: Let me see.
Oh, my God, Joe, he's right.
I got this from a very good source.
Well, something got lost in translation,
like maybe tact.
[PLAYERS LAUGHING]
Just fix it, Sammy, okay?
[SAMMY SPEAKS IN SUNAQUOT]
[PLAYERS LAUGHING]
[EAGLE CHIRPING]
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
Hello?
You must be Sasquatch.
Maug.-
I'm Joe, the new coach.
Hardly.
[CHUCKLES]
I guess you've been watching.
Crooked Arrow says you can play.
You can see that we could use
some help on defense.
No, I'm busy.
Well, you could help us win.
Be a part of the team.
Feel the pride.
Meet some girls.
Hit rich boys as hard as you want?
JIMMY: Did I get it right?
SHEENA: No. It's not a trapezoid.
JIMMY:
Yes, it is.
JOE: Hi. Sorry to interrupt, but I'd like
to introduce you to your new classmate.
This is Maug.
I made him get dressed for class.
- Why?
STUDENTS: Ha-ha-ha.
JULIE:
Well, welcome, Maug.
[MAUG SPEAKS IN SUNAQUOT]
He's amazing.
Is it true you can catch a deer,
kill it with your bare hands and eat it raw?
Chill, bro, I'm vegan.
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
BRYAN: Crooked Arrows
showing some aggression, finally!
Another turnover caused by Maug!
This new guy is a hammer.
Come on, guys, set it up! Let's run it.
Come on, Jimmy.
BRYAN: And the Crooked Arrows
are on offense again!
Drop in, drop in.
[CROOKED ARROWS
SPEAKING IN SUNAQUOT]
Find the pass.
BRYAN: Jimmy Silverfoot sets it up.
Passes it to Sammy or is that Owen?
Fakes low, fires high, and goal!
It's tie score late in the fourth.
OWEN:
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh. Watch the feet.
JIMMY: Hey, hey, hey, act like we've been
here before, boys. Come on, let's go.
Amazing improvement
since Joe Logan took over.
Time out, sir, time out.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
BRYAN: Dooley is in a battle, and the
Crooked Arrows are on target for their first win.
Toby, you're in.
Me?
JULIE:
Ah! Yes!
JOE:
Come on, just be aggressive, buddy.
Whoo!
JOE:
All right, guys, come on in. A minute left.
Okay, Lyle, take a breather.
Toby, you're in at middie.
PLAYER 1: What?
PLAYER 2: What?
Sticks up.
Come on, guys, it's tied.
We can win this.
JIMMY: Come on, boys! Let's do this.
Crooked Arrows on three. One, two, three!
ALL:
Crooked Arrows! Whoo! Whoo!
[PLAYERS WHOOPING]
JOE:
You're on wing, Toby.
Toby, on the wing. On the wing.
BRYAN: Now coming off the bench for the
Crooked Arrows, number 12, Toby Gifford.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Watch the double team.
TOBY:
Hey, here! Over here! Here!
Look Toby! Look Toby! Look Toby!
Come on, Toby.
[GASPS]
BRYAN:
And he drops it.
NADIE:
Come on!
BRYAN:
Hudson to Thomas.
Reed, clear crease!
Clear crease, Reed!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
BRYAN:
And it's in!
Dooley pulls out a stunning victory
after a crushing Crooked Arrows turnover.
What a game!
The Arrows are still winless
for the season.
How come their white boys can play?
- Lay off, Jimmy.
- Why was he even out there?
He's out there
because he's a member of this team.
We win and lose together
and nobody played perfectly.
But, hey, you guys played a great game, okay?
We'll get the next one.
So tonight,
steak dinner on me, all right?
[ALL CHEERING]
CHEWY:
I'm getting two steaks.
- How about a lap dance?
WAITRESS: You don't have a lap, honey.
PLAYERS:
Ooh.
[GLASS CLINKING]
- Thanks, Marilyn.
- You're welcome.
The hawk feather has long been
a sign of service for our people.
Warriors could earn feathers
on the field of battle.
Soto Jimmy, for winning
three face-offs and notching two assists.
To the Unishees, great speed, great effort.
And one goal apiece.
To Chewy, for tough position defense.
And to Maug, for creating four turnovers.
And to Nadie, for our motion offense.
I plan to make this a tradition
after every game.
So give ourselves a hand.
[PLAYERS CHATTERING]
Hey.
Listen, I know you're in a tough spot here.
I've been there.
The only poor Sunaquot kid
at a fancy prep school.
You didn't suck.
You know how you get over it?
Take the next shot you have.
And I'll make sure
you get another chance, okay?
Thanks, coach.
Hey, Mom.
Was that a little bit of Sunaquot
on the field today, coach?
I told you, we're working cultural identity
into the game plan.
Uh-huh. A little bit of a loose translation,
don't you think?
Yeah, well, kids kind of made it their own.
Which is why I will be working some proper
Sunaquot into my lesson plan this week.
See you later.
Night.
BROKEN ARROW:
You have been given knowledge and tools.
But now, you must commit yourselves
to the Creator's game.
To the ancient game that began long ago...
...when the birds
first played against the animals.
[PLAYERS SPEAKING IN SUNAQUOT]
However, you must first accept who you are.
[GRUNTS]
Within each one of us
resides an animal spirit.
You must go on a vision quest
to discover your animal spirit.
Actually, sweating kind of makes me
break out, so can I--? Ow!
When the animals of the sky played
the first game against the animals of the land...
...the Creator gave a gift
to every creature.
Tell me your vision.
The deer.
CROOKED ARROW:
A spirit of speed and agility.
Tell me your vision.
[ROARING]
The bear.
CROOKED ARROW:
Great strength.
[HOWLING]
The wolf.
CROOKED ARROW:
Became ferocious and wild.
CHEWY:
The turtle
CROOKED ARROW:
Was able to withstand any blow.
SAM MY:
The hawk.
CROOKED ARROW: The birds were gifted
with flight and swift movement.
OWEN:
The raven.
CROOKED ARROW:
And even the smallest animal...
The squirrel.
CROOKED ARROW:
...would prove his worth to the Creator.
This is good. In one team you represent
both the animals and the birds.
It is said that our loved ones
return as birds to watch over us.
So for you, Abooksigun, the eagle.
May your mother's wings lift you up.
All right, everybody, we're gonna
do a friendship dance now.
So, ladies, grab a man.
[ALL CHEERING]
[DRUMS BEATING AND MEN CHANTING]
So things are looking up around here.
What do you think?
Will we be ready to build
at the end of the season?
Ah, that's yet to be seen.
[SIGHS]
You don't answer to only me
in this quest, Joe.
But to your ancestors.
Grandma Skye tells me you come a long ways,
but there's more to your journey.
Step up, step up, Reed!
Poor goalie play has plagued them again
thanks to Reed "The Colander" Armstrong.
I've never been very good
with nicknames.
Anyway, along pass across the field.
Hit him!
[WHISTLES BLOWS]
Time out, sir.
BRYAN:
Marston Hall climbs within one, 14-13.
Reed, come on, I've seen kittens
more aggressive than you.
No, no, no, Joe, wait. Look.
Reed, you better man up
and clear the freaking crease.
Okay, you hold onto this lead, or I swear...
...I will shove those feathers
so far up your asses, you'll fly.
Okay, me first.
JOE: Sticks up.
JIMMY: Come on, boys.
I mean, I like your hair and your body is tight,
but you play goalie like a wussy.
And that is so un-hot. We straight?
Yeah, we're straight.
JOE:
Reed, buddy!
I got this, coach, okay?
All right.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
BRYAN: Ten seconds left,
Marston on a break, looking to tie.
Baird breaks free, right wing.
REED:
Watch the cutter!
Too far! Too far, Reed!
Ah!
BRYAN:
It's over! The Crooked Arrows win.
Yes!
[ALL CHEERING]