Under a tyranny,
most friends are a liability.
One quarter of them turn reasonable
and become your enemies.
One quarter are afraid
to stop and speak.
And one quarter are killed,
and you die with them.
The blessed final quarter
keep you alive.
Sinclair Lewis said that...
...a long time before
the new millennium.
A long time before
everything changed.
Escaped positive.
Our Father, who art in heaven....
Raise your right hand
and repeat after me.
-I do solemnly swear.
That I will faithfully execute the office
of president of the United States.
-And will, to the best of my ability.
Preserve, protect, and defend
the Constitution of the United States.
So help me, God.
Congratulations.
Mr. Chief Justice, my fellow citizens.
Four years ago when I stood before you
on these hallowed steps...
...we faced together
the awesome task...
...of healing the sick and weary soul
of our great nation.
Don't think a day has passed
since then, that I haven't prayed...
...in thanks for the unity
we have found in that battle.
Together, we have won back our country
from the talkers and the promise-makers.
-We have put the darkness behind us.
-Is there a problem?
The curfews, the econo--
Didn't I tell you
to keep off the streets?
Did you?
Together, we have seen the dawning of
not just a new millennium, but a new--
There's kids around here, man.
You gotta think about that.
Clean this up.
Most courageously of all...
...we have risen at last to the challenge
of this terrible disease.
Never again will the whiners
and the crybabies...
...tell us we can't protect ourselves
and our children.
Yet, but now,
we must ask the Lord to tell us...
...what sin and what sinners...
...we have yet to cast out
of our midst.
We must ask for his help
in returning...
...to the great moral principles
this country was built on.
To the wellspring of our freedoms
and our tradition in this....
I think I got it, Blue.
-We must ask him to put in our heart...
-Got what?
...a greater understanding...
...of why he has stricken us
with this mortal plague.
Most important....
You are such a drama queen,
it's unbelievable.
You don't know anything.
-Laurie, how?
-You know that dance we went to?
The guy with the red hair?
-More than anything, I'm proud...
-Hi.
...of the spirit of decency that is
growing every day among our youth.
And to all you find young men out there
in the home guard, I just want to say:
Thanks.
Will someone please give me a break?
Hey, Bucky, you wanna shut
your sister up for a minute?
-Blue.
-Bucky.
It's your night for dinner.
In honor of the inauguration,
all Workfare Occupation centers...
...will be closing one half-hour early.
I'm going to get tested. I'm gonna go to that
Operation Helping Hand place right now.
What's the hurry? It's two weeks
to quarterlies. Less. Hello?
You think I could sleep one minute
till I found out?
Excuse me, could we get some help?
What? What? Find out what? That you
got a terminal case of hypochondria?
Kilo and a half.
These sores I keep getting
are not hypochondria.
Neither is the way
I'm always tired all the time.
One point eight, 3.5.
Hey, there's my bus.
-I'll send you a postcard from quarantine.
-Laurie.
Can't believe you would take
such a chance.
I had to, Blue.
There was a connection between us.
Did you call him?
Find out if he was sick?
Oh, man, Laurie.
All right, all right,
so I didn't get his name.
He was just this guy, you know?
Anyway, who knows if it was even him?
I could've got breathed on, on the street.
Anyway, you're not always so careful,
are you?
Kind of hasn't been much
of an issue lately, has it?
You think that's better?
God.
No big deal, right?
We're gonna get through this.
Hi.
Just get rid of it.
Name, address, certificate number.
After you have been called
into the examination room...
...you will be requested to remain there
until the results have been determined.
Blue.
Come on.
I would die if you weren't here
with me, Blue.
-I would really just die.
-You'll be all right.
Nothing like a little good news,
is there?
You'll be receiving a registered copy
of your certificate in the next day or so.
-Bye-bye.
-Doctor?
I'm sorry to bother you again,
but I've been waiting for my grandson....
-Can I have a magazine?
-Mrs. Chaney, I'm sorry...
...but you will know
something as soon as we do.
Please, doctor.
Can't you tell me when I--?
Keep that thing out of sight.
Mrs. Chaney.
Where's Tommy?
-If you could step up to my office--
-I'm not stepping nowhere...
...until I see my boy.
I'm afraid that's not possible
right now, Mrs. Chaney.
He's sick.
He's sick. He's dying.
Mrs. Chaney, please. Please, calm down.
Please, please.
Your grandson will be receiving
the best care he possibly can.
-This is a question of public safety.
-Tommy!
This is a medical facility. I cannot
allow you to create a disturbance.
We're gonna get out of here right now
before they come back.
We can't just go. They have my name.
Shit.
I figured as long as I was here,
I might as well get it done too.
-Name, address, certificate-- Okay.
-Yeah, I know.
What are you doing with that? Security.
Security.
Hey, watch it.
Burner, what's your 20?
Move it. They're heading west.
Hey! Come on!
-This way. Come on.
-Come on.
Come on. Get in.
What the hell is this?
There's cops after them, Torch.
They were running out of the center.
You're a good man, Willie.
A lot better than you should be.
Clear them out of here.
Come on, Torch.
They're gonna get nailed.
-We gotta hide them.
-Get it open.
I can't. It's jammed.
Come on. Get back.
-What are they gonna do to us?
-Shut up.
There's a staircase up here.
Officers, officers, wait, please.
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
There were two girls with guns.
They went that way, right that way.
Hey, did they rob a bank
or something?
-Come on. Come on.
-I can't believe that worked.
Wait, wait, wait.
You never saw this place.
You never met me.
You hear me? This never happened.
Okay.
I saw that.
You telling me you weren't scared
you'd get it?
I'm telling you
she was behind the fence.
Yeah. And her guts were spilling out
and her blood was flying around.
Somebody's gotta clean up the trash.
Too bad you missed it, Bucky.
You gotta do more night patrols with
us, man. Anyway, enough about that.
I want you to follow up on that Chink
over at that Laundromat.
That guy shows up late for his
quarterlies, I'm gonna put him on report.
Now, Payne, you still keeping an eye
on that Burack character?
Kind of.
You know, my guess is, he's clean.
He hasn't been around
that weird bookstore much.
Yeah. I don't buy it.
Stay on him for a while.
Yeah, you got it.
Bucky, you're up.
Now, did Rocklyn or did Rocklyn not
start that strike bullshit...
...down at the impound place?
It's hard to tell anything about him.
Mostly he keeps to himself.
Except for this guy from the grocery
he goes to the movies with.
-Just the two of them?
-Yeah. At least, since I've been on this.
Doesn't surprise me a bit.
Guy's got faggot written all over him.
You think that's something
the police should get into?
Department of Health.
They're much faster.
Blue.
Why don't you hang out?
Why don't you stick around a little?
You know what you are, Hunter?
A walking advertisement for not fucking.
Government ought to put you
on a poster.
Thank you....
We have a good time.
All right, first of all.
Say hello over here....
Mom?
Why do you have to be like that?
It makes me sick
just listening to you guys.
Mom.
-Mom.
-You got a problem, talk to the chef.
Mom, you're home from work now.
Do you wanna wash up or keep sleeping?
Sleep.
It's not just you guys, it's everything.
What does that mean?
Well, just-- Everything.
The way everything is.
What, you liked it better
when we were kids?
Everybody taking drugs,
people killing each other...
...nobody having any respect
for anything?
I hate it when you talk like that. Like
you're trying to get an A from teacher.
If I do anymore dancing...
...the vice president's
gonna have to clear his schedule.
If anything's going to save us
from earning less than Mom...
...and sharing the same room
till we die...
...it's this.
Unless you think they're gonna be
giving out jobs for Christmas.
In case you're wondering,
that 3-carat cabochon ruby...
...on the first lady's necklace
is on loan--
Monkey Shines will be back
after this message...
...from Operation Helping Hand,
making your hard choices a little easier.
And they all come
with a five-year guarantee.
I can get you a great deal
on some very nice land in Florida.
What are you so worried about?
I got protection.
Don't be fooled. The only way
to play it safe is not to play at all.
In response to the unprecedented
massing of troops on the 1 6th parallel...
...the president took time out
from tonight's revelry...
...to warn that the United States
will not hesitate to use any means...
...to ensure the security and the freedom
of its allies in the region.
Pentagon sources report
that all forces in the crisis zone....
What am I doing?
Hey.
Hey, could you help me?
-What's the problem, ma'am?
-You're the problem.
-What are you doing?
-Just lending a helping hand.
I told you about coming back here.
Who else knows?
-Knows what?
-What's happening here.
-I wish I knew.
-Simon, move it.
The auto shop's set up.
Lennie, drive.
What are you doing?
Keeping you right where I can see you.
I'm not saying you're out of trouble yet.
At least you're with the good guys.
Welcome to the quarantine express.
All right, anybody here tattooed yet?
Because if you are, we cannot help you.
No.
Okay, pull out, Lennie.
Willie, we're moving.
Forty-five minutes,
they would have had you in quarantine.
You're safe now.
Forget about going home because
that's the first place they're gonna look.
-We just gotta get you out of here.
-And then what?
-Not my department.
-We have safe houses.
They're not the Hilton Hotel, but they're
better than where you were headed.
Be careful not to breathe too deep
around these guys.
-Can't you get it that way?
-Don't you read the government reports?
Perplexing mystery.
Nobody knows for sure.
Isn't that what they said?
The only way to get this disease
is straight into your bloodstream...
...one way or another.
I'm cold. I'm so cold.
Can I call my grandma?
I want her to know I'm all right.
No phone calls. We'll get a message
to her when it's safe.
There's cops behind you, a block away.
Lennie, move it.
You took the wrong fucking ramp,
Lennie.
-The wagons are on the other side.
-Well, what was he supposed to do?
We'll never get across that.
Please tell me this isn't happening.
Don't even think
about going back down.
That cop's still sniffing around.
Pack up the van.
One hand right in front of the other.
That's right.
You're doing great.
Didn't know you had a date tonight.
Wait over there. Over there.
There you go. Okay.
-All right, one hand in front of the other.
-These cops keep hanging around.
I don't get it, man.
-You lost that other guy, I know you did.
-Right across.
Lennie, pull out!
Don't move.
Come on, man. Come on, move it.
-Get back.
-Don't be crazy.
Come on.
We got trouble, man.
There's a cop coming down Pavonia.
He's headed straight for us, Torch.
They must have some kind
of tracking thing in the van.
Don't listen to him.
Walk when I walk, okay?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God.
-Just get up very slowly.
No, I can't move.
Guess you'd rather stick around
and wait for the bomb to go off.
What bomb?
What did you think I was doing
back there, setting my alarm clock?
Don't look down. Look at me.
It's gonna break.
The ladder's gonna break.
-What's your name?
-What?
I asked you what your name was.
-Blue.
-Don't look down. Look at me.
Look in my eyes, Blue.
Don't look down. Look in my eyes.
Just get up very slowly.
You can trust me or you can die.
That's it. That's it. Okay.
You're gonna be okay, Blue.
Ain't got nothing to worry about.
Me, I'm telling you...
...when I go, it ain't gonna be
from falling off no fucking ladder.
Come on, you guys.
Give me your hand. Come on!
Come on.
Give me your hand. Come on.
Hands up! Now!
Call for backup.
Why bother?
-We have the authority for this?
-Are you gonna give me trouble?
I don't know about this, man.
All you need to know
is that we got orders.
Yes!
Okay. Okay, easy with this guy.
Okay, I got him.
Do you do this every night?
What are you doing?
You'd better wear a blindfold
till we get where we're going.
I'm not putting this disgusting thing
on my face.
There are doctors where we're going.
Food. Beds. You don't put that on,
they don't get there.
Willie, sit them down over there.
Make it comfortable.
Help me get this guy
a wheelchair, okay?
-Where are we?
-Someplace they don't know about yet.
-What happened to him?
-I don't know.
Okay, bring him over here.
Bring him down real careful.
Okay. Now,
you just hang in there, Stu.
We'll make you
as comfortable as you can be.
-You'll let my son know I'm all right?
-Just hold real steady.
You okay?
You'd think it would get a little easier
after a while.
You are really sick.
There's some medicine.
Stuff we smuggle in from New York.
-Lennie.
-Yeah.
Take her home now.
Where am I taking you?
1 4 West 90th Street.
Yeah, Hunter...
...she clocked in at 6:03.
I don't wanna hear about it.
Me either.
I wanna hear about this.
I don't get it.
Did Laurie get tested or didn't she?
-Why are you going through my things?
-Where did you get this from?
Stop the presses. I'm only gonna be
a half-hour late for work today.
Did you have a good run?
Mom's really impressed that
you've taken up early morning jogging.
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's great.
You know, it really gets the blood going.
I don't have blood anymore.
I just have coffee.
You should eat something, Mom.
Thanks.
What's going on, Blue?
Bucky...
...you know the stuff they keep
telling us about the quarantine?
How great it's supposed to be,
all clean and happy and wonderful?
-Yeah.
-It's all lies.
They lock these people up,
they don't give them medicine--
They won't let their families
visit them?
The quarantine has to be total.
It's too much of a risk.
Why can't they talk to anybody
on the telephone? Tell me that.
You tell me where you were last night.
Listen to this. You have to hear this.
Authorities attribute the hijacking
of the ambulance...
...to an unnamed group
intent on causing panic in the city.
No suspects have been arrested,
intelligence sources confirm...
...that the terrorists plan to use
the contaminated blood as a weapon....
You know, I never thought
I'd hear myself saying this...
...but I'm beginning to think...
...the only choice
they have is to kill these people.
Like they did when it was drugs.
I don't know what else they can do.
--was applauded
by lawmakers in the state capital.
The Department of Health
asks citizens with information...
...regarding the activities of this group
to contact the home guard...
...or call Operation Helping Hand.
On the international scene....
I know you like her...
...otherwise, you wouldn't bother
to be so mean to her.
I remember you used to try
that with my mom...
...when you were going out with her.
At least in those days,
you used to have a little privacy.
Fine. I'll turn myself into the state.
You meet any hot social workers,
you get their number.
Go downstairs.
-Torch?
-Yeah?
Was my mom a good cook?
Yeah, Willie, she was a good cook.
And she could grow stuff too,
couldn't she?
Radishes and stuff.
I remember I used to help her water.
Think we could start
growing stuff again, Torch?
Torch?
She's not gonna get
any more dead, man.
-You watch your mouth!
-Look.
She was my mom.
I can talk about her if I want to.
She's not gonna get any more dead
if you sleep where it's clean.
Or eat regular food like a person,
or be nice to some girl you like.
She's as dead as she's gonna get.
I hope you flunk your English test.
Too late, it was yesterday.
And I aced it.
Laurie, it was unbelievable.
The way these people
have been treated.
When they get to quarantine,
they put tattoos on them.
These big P's for positive,
so they can track them down with radar.
Do you swear to me,
that when this is over...
...you'll forget
this entire thing ever existed?
I mean it, Blue.
This is it.
Right up that ramp.
Come on.
We fix cars here, ma'am.
You want a doctor, find a hospital.
They know me. I was here last night.
I know what's behind that curtain.
If you'll excuse me,
I have a lot of work to do.
My friend needs somebody
to give her the test.
We don't wanna go back
to Helping Hand.
-Boss!
-I think maybe we should just go.
-No.
-Hey!
You wouldn't believe this, Laurie.
Beds, medicine, hospital stuff.
What is this?
We crossed the continental divide
of weirdness.
You wanna take the test?
Be under the 4th Street bridge
in an hour.
Just the two of you.
Anybody else shows up,
this doesn't happen.
No.
-No.
-Come on.
So who's this person
who's such a big emergency?
Nobody.
Just somebody I met in the park.
All right, now, you just hold real steady.
Are you sure this is sanitary out here?
You mean without any magazines
and a waiting room?
In the Helping Hand clinic
where I work...
...we got all the white tile
you could ever want.
And I wouldn't go there
to get my nose blown.
You work for them?
Not every double agent
wears a trench coat.
Somebody's coming.
Not to worry,
just our friendly mobile testing unit.
Instant results around the clock.
I don't know if I'm ready for instant.
Hi.
The keys are in the cab, Anna.
The equipment's running a little hot,
should be okay, though.
What's his problem?
Who cares?
Torch. Hey, Torch,
what is your problem?
Hey, I ain't got no problem
except for you yelling at me.
I don't get this.
What we went through last night,
and then--
Did I get you pregnant and leave you
by the roadside somewhere?
-I don't remember this.
-I am not talking about marriage.
I'm talking about saying hello.
Hello.
I'm okay.
Blue, I'm okay. She said
it's just allergies or something.
Oh, God.
Let's get out of here.
My mom's on nightshift.
-We got some major celebrating to do.
-Thank you, guys, so much. Thank you.
-Does it feel good to say I told you so.
-Blue.
Blue.
-What?
-Look....
Just because he's messed up
doesn't mean we don't need the help.
Is there any way somebody
could get ahold of you, ever?
What do you mean, in case Mr. Hero
needs someone to impress?
Blue.
You take care of yourself, okay?
Blue? Aren't you gonna show up
to your own party?
You want a beer or something?
Fuck.
Hey, what are you doing in here?
People are starting to wonder.
What's that thing on your head?
I guess you think everything in the world
is just wonderful now.
Fine.
Maybe it's all true. Maybe all this
terrible stuff is actually happening.
But, Blue, you're crazy if you think
that there is one thing...
...that you or I or anybody else
can do about it.
I guess I don't see it that way.
Just don't do anything stupid, okay?
Please? I mean, really.
Hey, you guys, you gotta hear this.
The mobilization of the forces
that have been on alert...
...since yesterday's
unprovoked attack.
We have acted decisively
and we have acted justly.
We have acted because we cannot...
...must not allow tyranny
to cast its evil shadow.
We have acted because
as long as one man is not free...
...no man is free.
-Yeah. All right, yeah.
-Yeah.
Hey, Blue.
We could use an extra hand tonight.
What, the regular girl call in sick?
Look, I'm sorry.
What do you want?
You want me to eat dirt, I'll eat dirt.
That would be nice.
Chicken.
Laurie.
-Where's Blue?
-I don't know.
Hey.
Oh, hi, man.
Use them, okay?
The bleach, the needles, everything.
-Got anybody I could use this with?
-Not my department.
Where the hell you been, man?
-Hey, Willie.
-Hey, Blue.
-There you are.
-Hi.
Hey.
Listen, Laurie, I need some help,
and I don't know who else to turn to.
Help with what?
Is Blue having some sort of problem?
Why would you think
that she was having a problem?
Well, she seems so down these days,
you know?
That's too bad,
because there's so much to be up about.
Things are really starting
to come together.
She's fine. She's perfectly happy.
Hey, Laurie, how about this--?
But Blue
is having some sort of problem.
When the cops get wind of it...
...you're gonna wish real hard
that you wouldn't let someone...
...who's Blue's friend get her out of it
before it was too late.
Blue's fine.
Okay.
Can you believe that somebody
would name their kid Drusilla?
-Criminal.
-It was after some aunt of my dad's.
But my mom turned it
to Dru pretty fast.
Bucky couldn't even say that.
All he could say was Blue.
I guess it kind of stuck.
Hey, it's your turn.
-What's this for?
-For your face.
Oh, yeah.
I got mine from Willie's mom.
She hated her own name. Ellen.
She said it sounded like someone
who won prizes for their handwriting.
I kind of liked it, but I said, ''Okay, we
should make up names for each other...
...only you had to take the name
you got given, period.
No going back.''
We-- We wrote our names on the inside
of matchbook covers, right?
We switched,
counted to three and looked.
I don't know where she came up with it,
but she put down Torch.
I put down Ellen.
We nearly killed each other
on the spot.
What was your name before?
I can't say.
That was another part of the deal.
Who was Willie's father?
She got pregnant on the job.
You know, she said meeting me
got her out of the trade...
...but Willie pretty much talked her
out of it before I ever came along.
What happened to her?
Sure. You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
Well....
It was in the beginning...
...when they first started
taking people away.
The whole world was sticking
its fucking head in the sand.
Oh, but not her, no.
She had this crazy idea that sick people
were supposed to get taken care of.
She started making trouble,
driving people up the wall.
They wanted her bad.
When they raided this place
we were staying...
...she was the only one they took.
The troublemaker.
One morning, Willie wakes up,
and she's just not there anymore.
The way I heard it...
...when she came up positive,
they broke out the champagne.
It meant this time,
they had her for good.
No paperwork.
They were very interested
in what she could tell them...
...about her secret terrorist network.
And the doctors who were present...
...knew how to be effective
in their interrogation.
Because....
Because what the--
What the blood test also showed...
...was that the subject...
...was somewhere between
three- and five-months pregnant.
Patients in the quarantine tried
to take care of her...
...but after a beating like that....
Was it your baby?
Where did you toss Willie's bag?
Can you feel anything with that on?
Enough.
Did you know she was sick
before she got caught?
They call it denial.
Sorry.
Have you ever taken the test?
Everybody's got these calendars
in their head.
So you find out you got five years.
So, what do you do?
Start X-ing off the days
in your datebook?
Take the necessary precautions
and you go from there.
All that stuff they say
about nothing being safe--
Hey, Torch.
You got anything for breakfast?
-Where's my shirt?
-Hey, you ever heard of knocking, man?
I'm starving, man.
We'll pick up a donut
on the way to the bus.
He's a growing boy.
You can't give him donuts for breakfast.
I get him the jelly kind,
it's got fruit inside.
Tell me you didn't actually say that.
Well, don't wake me till Christmas.
No, no, no. You gotta get home
before your brother gets up.
-He can go to hell.
-Very bad attitude.
-You got a cover to keep now.
-I do?
Please, no bright-eyed idealism
before I get my coffee, all right?
Morning, guys.
Do you need a toothbrush, Blue?
-Don't worry, it's brand-new.
-Thanks.
Torch?
Come on, man.
Peace for all, little brother.
See, it's not so bad.
Nice and slow.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
It's okay. Okay--
Ma.
-Ma.
-You take it easy, I'll be right back.
Where are you, Ma?
Ma.
-Ma.
-I'm right here.
I guess you couldn't get Dad
to come, huh?
No, no, he's here,
he's right over there.
He's coming.
Hey.
-It's Russell.
-Russell.
Hey, Dad.
You don't still hate me, huh?
No, I don't hate you, Russ.
I love you, Russell.
I love you too, Dad. I love you, Dad.
So why haven't I heard
any hot details yet?
Because there haven't been any.
Every night with this guy for a month
and I'm supposed to believe that?
-That's right.
-Well, I don't.
Laurie, when have I ever lied to you?
Fifth grade. Scott Berkowitz.
You promised me that you would
never ever mention that again.
How could you do it, Blue?
He smelled like pastrami farts.
Actually, it was more like corned beef
when you got up close.
Stop.
-What are you looking at my watch for?
-Just wanted to see what time it was.
Well, what's your hurry?
We haven't had a normal conversation
in a million years.
I mean, come on.
Why can't you put up posters
a half an hour later?
We're not exactly
putting up posters today.
-Then what are you doing?
-You don't want to know.
Don't tell me what I don't want.
If I got caught,
you'd be better off not knowing.
Just tell me.
I miss talking to you, Blue.
I miss telling each other everything.
We found out that there's
this Helping Hand clinic in New Jersey...
...that's closing tonight.
And they're shipping everybody
that they're holding to quarantine.
And you're gonna rescue them
on the way?
Yeah, we're gonna get them
into safe houses.
These people you're rescuing them from,
they don't have guns?
Blue.
We have guns too, Laurie.
Blue, don't go, okay?
Really, don't go. Just, don't do it.
It's 70 people.
They're gonna lock them up
and starve them.
I just don't think, you know,
if this guy really loved you...
...he wouldn't want you
to be in all this danger all the time.
It's not about him.
It's just....
I don't know, you get put on this planet
and what do you do with that?
So, what are you saying?
You telling me I'm fucked up
because I wanna have a normal life?
-I'm not saying that, you know it.
-No, I don't.
I don't know anything.
-I have no intentions of getting killed.
-Nobody ever does.
Well, I gotta go.
So go.
Call you tomorrow morning?
You're gonna be late.
Go on.
Truck's coming in a little early, Torch.
You'd better hurry up.
-No escort?
-Not that I can see.
And I can see all the way to Canada.
You got enough people down there
for this?
We got everybody we know
out here, Willie.
Now you stay low.
Hold it.
-Nobody move.
-You rat.
Now,
if you kindly drop your weapons...
...and put your hands in the air. Now.
Put it in the truck. Do it.
-Get it open!
-It's not holding.
-Come on.
-Kick it open.
Let's go. Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
We did it. We fucking did it, come on.
-Hands on the truck, come on.
-Where are you, man? I can't see you.
Wherever you are, get out
to Pearl Street, you'll be in the clear.
-What is it?
-My walkie.
Check under the bridge.
Cancel that about Pearl Street.
It's starting to look like
a cop convention down there.
-If you're holed up somewhere, sit tight.
-Shut up.
It's a kid.
It's not a kid, man, it's a sniper.
Torch, where are you?
Come on, Torch, answer me.
I can't see you.
What's going on down there?
There he is, captain.
I got a clear shot at his ass.
-No!
-Torch!
Willie!
-No!
-Give me your fucking hands.
No! Willie!
Willie! No!
No! Get it on the radio.
Get off-- Get off me!
Willie!
Bucky, come here.
Now you know why
we had to come out here today.
But it's cool, man.
People make mistakes.
Instead you'll have to keep an eye on her
now, make sure she learned her lesson.
I can count on you for that, can't I?
In the car.
Oh, Willie. Oh, my God.
Willie.
How could they have found out?
Somebody told them.
Yeah, somebody who knew exactly
what was coming down today.
-What are you saying?
-I'm saying somebody fucked us!
Are you accusing me?
Who else?
She's been with Helping Hand for--
Shut up, shut up!
Would you just shut up?!
Come on, we gotta get out of here
before they come back.
Safest way's under the highway.
Let's go.
Come on!
I'll make you a deal.
You give me the whereabouts
of just one kidnapped positive...
...and we can all get some sleep.
Does that hurt?
One name. One address.
Santa Claus.
The North Pole.
Safe houses.
Addresses, phone numbers.
-Hey!
-What?
He won't be much use to you
if he's dead.
Okay.
I'd kind of hold off on that
for a minute if I were you.
We just got the blood work
in on this one, and in a word, positive.
Dead man.
Fucking bastard!
Looks like some clear skies
ahead of us.
Enemy casualties are reported high
in heavy fighting.
You're not Egan.
What happened to Egan?
What do you think happened to Egan?
Welcome to Tri-State Regional
Quarantine.
Channel Six spoke with the young hero
of the mass arrest.
It's not just us
who make these things happen, you see.
It's also the fine regular people
out there...
...who know what's wrong
when they see it.
And they're not afraid
to speak up about it.
Because, I mean, I don't care
what kind of line-up you got.
You ain't gonna win no football games
if you ain't got the crowd out there.
Blue?
Are you sure he has it?
You think Anna would've said so
if she wasn't sure?
Oh, God, Blue.
You didn't sleep with him ever,
did you?
-Willie's dead.
-What?
Hunter shot him.
He's dead?
Yeah, we just buried him today.
He swore he wouldn't do--
What? Who swore?
What are you talking about?
Laurie?
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
What did you do?
You told him?
-You told Hunter?
-I was so scared, Blue.
I didn't want you to die
or wreck your life.
Listen, they promised me
they weren't gonna hurt anybody.
-They swore. Come back here!
-No.
Blue, Blue,
I need to talk to you, right now.
Talk to me, talk to me.
Oh, shit.
Stop doing this.
Right now
is when we should be very careful...
...with how we use our energies.
Energies?
Hey, Blue.
Blue, wait a minute.
We have to decide about stuff.
-What stuff?
-Everything.
Planning stuff.
Getting everybody back on track.
I can't believe
you're just gonna let it all go to pieces.
It's okay, it's okay. It's me.
-How did you find me?
-I followed you, the other night.
Leave.
I swear to you, I did not have anything
to do with the raid.
Fine. You were just following orders
and God forgives you.
Now would you go away?
I found you a way to see him.
The guy you were with.
What?
I don't know what else I can do.
I can't get him out.
-I can't stop what's happening.
-Nobody can get into quarantine.
Yeah? It's all just money
and connections like everything else.
But you gotta meet the driver
in a half an hour or forget it.
Money, what money?
Guess who just got elected treasurer
of your local home guard?
Jesus, Bucky.
What if Hunter kills you,
what do I do for a brother?
If you hate me for the rest of my life...
...what do I do for a sister?
Don't let anybody get a close look
at that thing.
When I get inside, how will I find him?
Usually, they take the new arrivals
to the Helms wing.
Okay.
I make my delivery,
take care of my business.
Back where I dropped you off
at 6, 6:05.
Now you hear that clock-bell ringing,
you get down there.
You don't show up....
-She doesn't show up, what?
-They find out that the tattoo's fake.
-They shoot her on the spot.
-Jesus.
Do you have a watch?
Yeah.
You'd better synchronize.
What time do you have?
Two forty-seven.
Now the drop off's gonna be
around the corner on White Street.
About 6:30.
-Come on, set your watch.
-I will when I get in.
You don't have a watch.
Don't be crazy.
Bye, Bucky. Tell Mom I love her.
Blue, don't do this!
All right, you're clear.
-How you doing tonight, man?
-How do you think I'm doing?
-Did you get that radiator fixed?
-Yeah, I got it fixed.
-Take you a long time?
-Yeah, took me a while.
Passed curfew, babe. Get inside.
Okay.
This one's still warm enough.
Gonna be the end of our marriage
if you go on.
I've had enough.
Don't you realize that?
You've had enough?
Other people drink.
-Not the way you do.
-Why?
-What's wrong with me?
-I don't know.
You've got everything in the world
that you want.
-Friend of yours?
-Tim, help me.
Help me.
-Hi.
-Did they hurt you?
They didn't get me. I snuck in.
You snuck in? You crazy fuck.
-You got a way to get out?
-Yeah.
My ride's at 6:00 at Receiving.
In there. Go in there.
You shouldn't have come here.
They'll shoot you.
-No, no, don't talk. Don't say anything.
-Watch the blood.
What did they do to you?
Did they get Willie?
-Torch.
-His body, did they get his body?
No.
Come on. Sit on the bed.
Come.
-All right, put your hands up.
-What?
I wanna get this shirt off you.
It's filthy, come on.
Lie back. Lie back.
Oh, it feels good, Blue.
Feels too good.
There's no such thing.
What are you doing?
-We gotta get--
-No, no.
They don't scare me.
No, no, what are you doing?
Look, I can stay as long as I want.
It's a counterfeit black mark.
It's special.
You know how fast
that thing's gonna peel off?
Boy, would they love this.
A negative dropping in on a boyfriend.
Would they make an example or what?
Not if she wasn't negative anymore.
You came here to off yourself.
-I came here to be with you.
-No.
Come on.
-You've got your whole life to live.
-Don't tell me what I got.
Blue.
We never got to go to the movies.
We never got to go out for breakfast.
Medic squad, checkup time.
-Get to the door or I'm coming in.
-Hit the light.
Get out of sight.
Get to the door.
-Back off. Back-- Back off.
-Okay, okay.
You know what to do.
Come on, lift the arms.
All the way, all the way.
All right, pants.
Shorts too.
Come on, turn around.
-What's that?
-It's a mole, we've been through this.
Crack a smile.
All right, you're clean.
-What's that?
-It's a hooker, I got a hooker up here.
What, you got Chinese food
up here too?
-Yeah, you know how it is.
-Yeah?
Get her out here. Come on!
Hey, come out here.
-Hey, bitch!
-I'm coming, I just hurt my leg.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
What do you care?
I've never seen you before.
Yeah, she just got Q'd
a couple of hours ago.
Working fast, huh?
Show me your label.
Come on, move out of the way, huh?
-Can't see it good.
-Can you see it now?
It's very nice. I see it, all right.
-Show me her tits.
-What?
Hey, I'm here.
I might as well kill two birds, huh?
-Now show me her tits.
-I'll show you.
No, no. I want him to do it.
Show me her tits.
Come on.
Rub them.
-Mister--
-Don't ''mister'' me.
She's here after curfew.
She ain't even on my list.
You two ain't got any symptoms yet.
I hardly ever get that.
Rub her tits.
No, not there. Not there. Tits.
Come on. Rub them, rub them.
Show me her--
Show me her bush.
I wanna see it.
Hey, you making friends down there?
No, sir, I'll be right out.
See you two tomorrow. You got it?
That's it. You're out of here.
I want you to go down this ladder.
And I want you to cut through
by emergency down there.
That'll take you right to Receiving.
Come on.
I'm not going.
You want to go through
that shit again?
I want to stay here with you
and finish what I started.
Yeah? Yeah?
You want me to fuck you?
Is that what you want? Come on.
-Is that what you want?
-Stop.
You want me to fuck you? Shut up!
I'll fuck you.
And in every drop of me there'll be
a trillion little poison cockroaches...
...floating around inside of you
for a year, five years, or more.
You'll be checking yourself up
20 times a day.
You're hurting me, Torch.
You put your dress back on
and go back.
What--? What--? What do I do?
Live. Whatever that means, you live.
You can't just live, not without--
-What? Without love?
-Come on, Torch.
We can live as good as we can
for as long as we can.
We can grow old together
even if it doesn't take so long.
We could fix up the place.
We could see
if we could get some paint somewhere.
We're gonna have to be careful
on how we make it look.
Because in a hundred years...
...they're gonna be bringing people
through here on guided tours.
Behind the velvet rope over there,
some--
Some lady with blue hair...
...is gonna be giving a lecture
on how Torch...
...the father of the resistance,
lived in this humble room.
Died in this humble room.
Not alone.
It's almost time. You gotta go.
All right.
I'm going
as long as you tell me one thing.
Tell me that you don't want me here.
No, no. For real.
And you tell me
that you want to be alone...
...when you're going blind
and your head is swelling up with sores?
Tell me that you want me to be alone
when I know what's happening to you.
I'm outside,
picking Pepsi cans out of the trash.
I can't kiss your forehead.
Bring you a glass of water.
Or help you go to the bathroom
when you can't get out of bed.
Tell me that's what you want
and I'm out the window.
-Say it!
-All right, you tell me this.
You tell me how I'm supposed to sit here
and watch you lose 80 pounds...
...and spit up mucus until you die
from what I did to you.
No.
Oh, no.
As messed up as this place may be,
it's still a hospital.
-And that means pharmaceuticals.
-So?
So if it gets too bad,
we could just go to sleep.
A light dinner.
Four grams of Seconal.
Two each.
-We just go to sleep?
-Yeah.
It's morning.
So?
So right now, I'd be....
I'd be....
Now I'd be yelling at Willie
to get up for school.
On a Saturday morning?
-It's Saturday?
-Yeah.
Somebody's supposed to meet the guy
from the printer's...
...to pick up the deaf-mute cards.
Doesn't matter, there's no one
to do anything with them anyway.
There's you.
No.
-You've got two minutes, Blue.
-I'm not going.
-Security!
-No!
I got a negative in here.
I love you, Blue.
You'd better hurry, you just missed her.
She went down the hall.
You know,
she would've been back by now.
No, there might be traffic.
The bridge might be closed.
Yes, and pigs might fly.
You're asking me,
this whole thing's a trap.
What are we trusting this guy for,
anyway?
Because he's her brother.
Come on, Simon.
-Blue.
-Is Torch okay?
He's okay.
-Where are they keeping him?
-Did they tattoo him yet?
Look, can we do
the press conference later?
Right now, we got a lot to figure out.
Like who's gonna go meet that guy
from the printer's up at the bridge?
-If you need me to do--
-What we need you to do...
...is go be an upstanding member
of the home guard.
Starting with getting to roll call
on time.
-They can go to hell.
-Bad attitude.
You've got a cover to keep.
We both do.
Well, I can handle the cards.
Okay.
I think we owe him 20 more dollars.
Do me a favor,
don't talk the guy's ear off.
Just get the cards and come back.
What most we need to figure out...
...is how we're gonna start
covering the clinics again.