[ SILENCE ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
>> JESUS PROBABLY HAD A BIG
PENIS.
>> YEAH.
SO, I THINK IT WOULD ONLY BE
CHRISTIAN OF US -- GOOD GIRLS OF
US -- TO HAVE SEX WITH GUYS WITH
PENISES LIKE JESUS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I THINK SO.
>> WE -- WE SHOULD PROBABLY GO
FOR GUYS THAT LOOK LIKE JESUS.
>> OH, YEAH. OH, GOD.
>> THOSE GUYS DO NOT LOOK LIKE
JESUS.
>> SO, I SAW "STAR WARS."
>> YEAH? HOW IS IT?
>> TERRIBLE.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, IT LOOKS LAME.
>> IT'S GONNA BOMB.
>> THE BIBLE TELLS ME TO BE
RESPECTFUL TO WOMEN.
>> I'VE GOTTEN A LOT OF SLICE
THIS WHOLE CAMP, ALL RIGHT?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
HI, FATHER BOBBINGS.
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT
ELLEN BARRETT?
WOW.
A WOMAN ORDAINED.
>> HE WAS THE KING OF
ROCK 'N' ROLL.
I JUST BOUGHT TICKETS TO SEE HIM
NEXT WEEK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S GONE.
>> I'M NOT SURE IF IT'S THE WANG
OR THE...UNDERGARDEN.
>> OH, YEAH. I DON'T KNOW. YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE THERE'S A BULGE.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING GOING ON
THERE.
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS
ARE TALKING ABOUT, BUT I PLAN ON
PORKING THE...OUT OF BAMBI OUT
THERE.
>> AND I PLAN ON BEING BALLS
DEEP IN BETTY BEFORE 10:00.
>> ...GUYS, LANGUAGE!
>> ...NERDS ARE CRAZY.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> LOOK AT THESE GUYS.
>> YEAH...NUT?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU HAVE
THERE, SON?
>> THIS IS GRADE-A GENUINE
SPANISH FLY, GENTLEMEN.
>> ...LET ME SEE THAT.
>> IT'S REAL.
>> COME ON.
>> WELL, WHERE'D YOU GET IT?
>> MY BROTHER GOT IT FOR ME WHEN
HE WAS DOWN IN MEXICO.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH, MAN.
THESE ARE FROM THE GREAT STATE
OF "MEHICO."
>> YOU YOUNG MEN ARE FULL OF...
>> BROTHER BEAU, LANGUAGE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> I NEVER EVEN LISTENED TO
ELVIS.
PLUS, WASN'T HE A BIG FAT DRUG
ADDICT, ANYWAY?
NO WONDER HE'S DEAD.
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
>> YOU LITTLE...
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> YOU ARE GOING TO BURN IN...
>> WHAT?
>> THE POOR MAN HAD AN EATING
DISORDER, THAT'S ALL.
>> [ SNIFFLES ]
>> GOD...
>> [ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ Crying ] FATHER?
I'M SORRY!
>> LOOKS LIKE SCHOOL'S IN
SESSION, BOYS.
>> GO GET THEM, I GUESS.
>> LOSERS.
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> [ Laughing ] LOOK AT THIS
GUY.
BRUSH YOUR TEETH, FELLA.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> YOU GOT TO REALLY WORK FOR
THOSE YOUNG MEN'S SOULS.
>> SMELL THAT JIZZ.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> WHAT'S THE PROBLEM,
FATHER BOBBINGS?
>> THESE KIDS -- THEY DON'T
RESPECT ANYTHING.
>> [ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
YEAH, I KNOW.
CAN I GET A SIP OF THAT?
>> HMM?
OH, KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
>> GIVE ME A TASTE.
>> SPLASH A LITTLE LOVE IN
THERE.
WE DON'T WANT THESE BROADS
THINKING THEY GOT NAKED ON THEIR
OWN IN THE MORNING, HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> OOH.
OOOOH.
>> ...DID YOU BRING ENOUGH?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
JUST EXCITED.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
THIS IS GONNA MAKE THESE...
HORNY.
>> SYLVESTER STALLONE IS THE
CUTEST ACTOR OUT THERE RIGHT
NOW.
I MEAN, I KNOW HE'S SHORT.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I BET HE HAS A REALLY
LONG CANNOLI.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> TOTALLY.
>> I'LL TAKE THAT.
>> AH!
>> HI, CHAZZ.
>> SCRAM, WILL YOU?
I'M TRYING TO DO SOMETHING HERE.
>> BUT I --
>> I SAID SCRAM, GOD...IT!
>> [ LAUGHTER ]
>> YEAH, I JUST SAW
"SMOKEY AND THE BANDIT," AND I
THINK BURT REYNOLDS IS THE
HOTTEST.
>> I SAW THAT, TOO.
YEAH.
>> AND I REALLY LOVE HIS
MUSTACHE.
I WOULD...HIS BRAINS --
>> LADIES.
>> OOH!
>> SOME VERY SPECIAL DRINKS FOR
A COUPLE OF VERY SPECIAL LADIES.
>> MMM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SURE.
>> HEY, UH, DON'T WORRY, DWAYNE.
>> THANK YOU.
WE LEFT ONE IN THERE FOR YOU.
>> HEY, UH, DON'T WORRY, DWAYNE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
SOMEONE OUGHT TO KILL THOSE
GUYS.
>> CUT OFF THEIR --
>> PAYBACKS ARE...CHAZZ.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ TWIGS SNAPPING ]
>> I'M FINE.
>> IT'S FINE.
[ GIRLS GIGGLING ]
OW.
>> MNH.
>> IT'S FINE.
DO YOU -- DO YOU HAVE ANY GUM?
>> YEAH. YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> IS IT IN YOUR MOUTH?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT IS FAR OUT, MAN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, YES.
>> MMM.
>> SAVE SOME FOR US, HUH?
BREAK IT UP THERE -- OHH.
SORRY, BUT I GOT TO TAKE BAMBI.
>> [ GIGGLES ]
>> YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU DO WITH
HER.
I'M TAKING BAMBI.
>> CHAZZ!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SO...
>> THERE THEY GO.
>> YEAH.
>> BETTY, I WANT TO DO YOU.
LET'S GO.
>> OKAY.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
WHOA!
>> SMOKE THIS AND GET HIGH HERE.
[ KNIFE PLUNGES ]
>> GOD...THESE USELESS PUNK
KIDS.
OHH!
AAH!
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE
DON'T.
[ GASPS ] DON'T.
PLEASE DON'T.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ KNIFE PLUNGES ]
AAH!
[ GASPING ]
>> [ GIGGLES ]
>> HERE WE GO.
>> OW! CHAZZ!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> OH, MY GOD.
NO, STOP.
IT'S FREEZING OUT HERE.
OH, CHAZZ, CHAZZ --
>> I'LL MAKE YOU WARM.
>> IT'S FREEZING OUT HERE.
THERE'S SO MANY BUGS.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE BUGS.
>> I'M GETTING ALL BIT UP.
CHAZZ -- CHAZZ, IF YOU WANT
TO...ME, TAKE ME BACK TO THE
CABIN.
>> I'M TAKING YOU BACK TO THE
>> [ GIGGLES ]
CABIN.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
>> [ GASPING ]
>> Both: WHOA.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ] IT'S OKAY.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> ...THE ROOM.
WHY AREN'T YOU JUST HAMMERING ME
RIGHT HERE?
MMM.
YEAH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
YOU ARE A GOOD MAN.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, TAKING A
PICTURE?
COME ON.
>> OH, CAN I?
OH, YOU WERE BEING SARCASTIC.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO, FORGET IT. FORGET IT.
UH...
>> BACK DOOR'S ALWAYS OPEN
FOR JESUS, BABY.
OW!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AAH. AAH.
>> WHAT NOW?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> OH...
>> WHAT NOW?
UH, NOTHING.
>> OH...
WAIT RIGHT HERE, JUST LIKE THAT.
UH, NOTHING.
STAY JUST LIKE THAT.
WAIT RIGHT HERE, JUST LIKE THAT.
>> [ SIGHS ]
YOU KI-- GOD, I...HATE MEN.
>> ♪ WELL, IF THE DEVIL DON'T
LIKE IT ♪
♪ HE BETTER NOT COME BACK
♪ IF HE DON'T LIKE THAT, NO
♪ HE BETTER LICK MY NUTSACK
♪ IF THE DEVIL DON'T LIKE IT
♪ HE BETTER NOT COME BACK
♪ IF HE DON'T LIKE THAT, NO
♪ HE BETTER LICK MY NUT
>> [ MOANS ]
>> ♪ NUTSACK
[ PEOPLE MOANING ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OKAY.
OH...OKAY.
OKAY, FOCUS.
FOCUS.
HERE WE GO.
UNH.
UH, OKAY, UH...
UH, FARRAH FAWCETT.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
UH, CARRIE FISHER.
CARRIE FISHER.
NO.
SHELLEY DUVALL.
OH, YES.
OH, YES, SHELLEY DUVALL.
OOH.
OH, NASTY.
OH, SHELLEY.
[ MOANS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY, WE'RE GOOD.
OKAY, I'M BACK.
I'M BACK.
LOOK OUT, BABY.
[ BOTH MOANING ]
I'M BACK.
>> OH, YEAH, CHAZZ.
[ BOTH MOANING ]
OH...UNH!
>> OH, YEAH, CHAZZ.
OH, YEAH!
OH...UNH!
OOH! OH, YEAH!
OH, YEAH!
MNH! OH!
OOH! OH, YEAH!
OH...
MNH! OH!
[ BOTH MOANING ]
OH...
YEAH!
[ BOTH MOANING ]
OH! OH!
YEAH!
OH, YEAH!
OH! OH!
OH, GIVE IT TO ME, CHAZZ!
OH, YEAH!
GIVE IT TO ME!
OH, GIVE IT TO ME, CHAZZ!
OH, YEAH! OOH! OOH!
GIVE IT TO ME!
[ LAUGHS ] OH!
OH, YEAH! OOH! OOH!
WHOO!
[ LAUGHS ] OH!
[ BOTH MOANING ]
WHOO!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
[ BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY ]
THAT WAS GREAT, CHAZZ.
>> I KNOW.
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
I GOT TO TAKE A DUMP
>> [ GROANING LIGHTLY ]
>> FATHER BOBBINGS?
AGAIN?
AAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
>> [ GRUNTS ]
[ FARTING ]
[ GRUNTING, FARTING ]
[ WATER SPLASHING ]
[ FARTING CONTINUES ]
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
OH...
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
GOD...IT.
OH...
BAMBI, LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
GOD...IT.
HAVE TO LICK MY RUSTY STARFISH.
BAMBI, LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
BAMBI?
HAVE TO LICK MY RUSTY STARFISH.
WHAT'S WITH THE MASK?
BAMBI?
WAIT.
WHAT'S WITH THE MASK?
AAH! OHH!
WAIT.
OH, GOD!
AAH! OHH!
[ SCREAMING ]
OH, GOD!
[ KNIFE PLUNGING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ] OKAY.
[ KNIFE PLUNGING ]
OKAY, I'M BACK.
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ] OKAY.
I'M BACK, BABY.
OKAY, I'M BACK.
OH, GROOVY, YOU, UH, LITERALLY
I'M BACK, BABY.
DID NOT MOVE.
OH, GROOVY, YOU, UH, LITERALLY
I LIKE IT.
DID NOT MOVE.
UH, ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST GET
I LIKE IT.
THESE DOWN.
UH, ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST GET
[ CHUCKLES ]
THESE DOWN.
NICE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ALL RIGHT.
NICE.
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
HERE WE GO.
OOH, MAMA.
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
OOH, YEAH.
OOH, MAMA.
OOH.
OOH, YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
OOH.
WHAT THE...HAVE I DONE?
OH, MY GOD.
[ Voice breaking ] OH, MY GOD.
WHAT THE...HAVE I DONE?
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ Voice breaking ] OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
[ WHIMPERING ]
WHAT THE...?
OH, MY GOD.
OH, GOD --
[ KNIFE SLICES ]
[ GASPING ]
[ SPITTING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
>> CHAZZ?
CHAZZ?
AAH!
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING ]
UGH!
>> ♪ OH, I'M
>> ♪ ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ WITH JESUS BY MY SIDE
♪ I'M ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ I'M JESUS-SATISFIED
♪ THE FIRST TIME I MET JESUS
♪ I WAS A SLAVE TO SIN
♪ BUT NOW I'M FREE FOREVER
'CAUSE I LET MY SAVIOR IN ♪
>> ♪ YES
♪ ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ WITH JESUS BY MY SIDE
♪ I'M ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ I'M JESUS-SATISFIED
♪ JESUS, JESUS, JESUS
♪ I KNOW WE'LL NEVER PART
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE TOGETHER
'CAUSE YOU'RE RIGHT THERE IN MY
HEART ♪
>> ♪ OH
>> ♪ ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ WITH JESUS BY MY SIDE
♪ I'M ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ I'M JESUS-SATISFIED
♪ YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU, JESUS
♪ YOU SET ASIDE OUR PRIDE
♪ AND NOW I KNOW WE'LL ALWAYS
♪ BE YOUR BLUSHING BRIDE
>> ♪ OH
>> ♪ ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ WITH JESUS BY MY SIDE
♪ I'M ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ I'M JESUS-SATISFIED
>> ONE MORE TIME!
>> ♪ ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ WITH JESUS BY MY SIDE
♪ I'M ROLLING DOWN THE ROAD WITH
JESUS ♪
♪ I'M JESUS-SATISFIED
>> HOLY ROLLING! YEAH!
>> WE LOVE YOU, JESUS!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> JESUS' FATHER'S COMING!
>> YAY, JESUS!
[ GUITAR CHORD PLAYS ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
OH, YEAH.
[ SIGHS ]
[ BREATHING DEEPLY ]
AHH. YOU SMELL THAT, TIMMY?
THAT'S GOOD, FRESH COUNTRY AIR.
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> REALLY?
ALL I SMELL IS COW POOP.
>> [ SNIFFS ]
FAIR ENOUGH.
COME ON, KID.
>> NEED A HAND, BRITTANY?
>> I GOT IT COVERED, BROTHER
ZEKE.
>> OH!
DID YOU HEAR THAT, BROTHER ZEKE?
SHE GOT IT COVERED.
>> YEAH, YOU GOT IT COVERED, YOU
AND YOUR LITTLE HONKY...
>> AH.
SPEND YOUR MONEY WISELY, TIMMY.
I SURE WILL, FATHER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OOH, COOL STUFF.
>> AH.
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
COME ON IN, KIDS.
YEAH.
THERE WE GO. YEAH.
THAT'S IT.
MILLIE.
>> [ GASPS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT, FATHER?
I'M GONNA GO WAIT IN THE VAN.
I'M NOT FEELING VERY GOOD RIGHT
NOW.
>> WHAT'S WRONG, MILLIE?
>> UH, JUST CRAMPS.
I'LL BE OKAY. UNH.
>> OH, DO YOU NEED A TAMPON?
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> OH...YEAH.
...YEAH.
WHAT DO WE GOT?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
>> [ GROANING ]
>> HOW'D YOU GET UP HERE?
TAKE A WRONG TURN?
>> [ SCOFFS ]
YOU KNOW, STEALING IS A SIN.
>> THOSE BLUE EYES ARE A SIN.
SO, UH, WHAT'S THIS BIBLE CAMP
THING, SOME SORT OF PENANCE?
>> WELL, I DO HAVE A LOT TO
REPENT FOR.
>> REALLY?
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD GET DOWN
ON YOUR KNEES AND STARTING
ASKING FOR FORGIVENESS.
>> TO WHO -- GOD OR TO YOU?
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD HOLD ON TO
THIS.
NAME OF THE FATHER AND OF THE
SON AND OF THE HOLY SPIRIT.
>> AMEN.
>> JENNIFER!
THAT'S LIKE BLASPHEMY OR
SOMETHING.
COME ON.
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> [ LAUGHING ]
>> HI.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I'M FATHER CUMMINGS, PASTOR OF
THE ST. JUDAS CATHOLIC CHURCH.
WE'RE, UH -- WE'RE JUST HERE
BUYING SOME SUPPLIES FOR OUR BIG
CAMPOUT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> SO, LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING,
FATHER.
[ LAUGHS ]
ME AND J.J., WE BEEN ARGUING
ABOUT SOMETHING.
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP US MAKE UP
OUR MINDS.
NOW, IS IT GAY IF YOU JUST PUT
YOUR MOUTH ON IT?
>> ON WHAT?
>> THE TALLYWACKERS, DUMMY!
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
THAT'S SKUNK FOR YOU.
WHERE YOU HEADED TO, PADRE?
>> JUST A FEW MILES UP THE ROAD,
TO THE HAPPY DAY BIBLE CAMP.
>> DON'T YOU MEAN THE
BLOODY BLOODY BIBLE CAMP?
[ ALL GASP ]
>> IT'S OKAY, EVERYBODY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
HE'S JUST TRYING TO, UH, YANK
OUR CHAIN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
AREN'T YOU?
L-LISTEN -- I DON'T APPRECIATE
YOU SCARING THE CAMPERS LIKE
THAT.
YOU DON'T SEE ME RUNNING AROUND,
PREACHING FALSE STORIES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
[ CHUCKLES ]
TAKE A LOOK AT MY BROTHER,
DWAYNE.
MY BROTHER WENT TO
BLOODY BLOODY BIBLE CAMP SEVEN
YEARS AGO.
AND SOME CRAZY FREAK NUN THEY
CALL SISTER MARY CHOPPER...NEAR
KILLED HIM, LEFT HIM FOR DEAD.
>> [ SINGING INDISTINCTLY ]
UGH.
>> AAH!
[ KNIFE SLICES ]
AAH!
>> DWAYNE WAS THE ONLY SURVIVOR.
WELL, SOME OTHER BROAD, BUT WE
AIN'T SEEN HER SINCE.
HE AIN'T SPOKE A WORD SINCE THAT
NIGHT.
HE JUST SITS THERE ALL DAY LONG,
STARING AT...
>> UH, RIGHT, UH...
ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S ENOUGH
HORROR STORIES FOR ONE DAY.
IS EVERYBODY READY TO GO?
>> YOU'RE MAKING A BIG MISTAKE,
PADRE, 'CAUSE THEY AIN'T NEVER
CAUGHT THAT SISTER MARY CHOPPER.
I BET SHE'S STILL OUT THERE, AND
I BET SHE'S STILL THIRSTY FOR
BLOOD!
>> [ CHUCKLES ] OKEY DOKEY.
OKAY, CAMPERS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
LET'S HIT THE ROAD.
[ SIGHS ]
>> SO MANY OUNCES, SO LITTLE
TIME.
DO IT.
>> GOD...CHRISTIANS.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ VAN DOOR CLOSES ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> OH, GOD, WHEN WAS THE LAST
TIME ANYONE WAS HERE?
>> [ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
>> WHERE ARE, UH -- WHERE ARE
ALL THE CABINS, FATHER?
>> UH, THEY'RE JUST UP THE ROAD.
UH, IT'S NOT FAR.
BUCK UP, TAD.
BESIDES, WE'RE CAMPING.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> OH.
>> ALL RIGHT, GRAB YOUR GEAR,
TROOPS.
>> YEAH, TAD, WE'RE CAMPING.
>> [ Mockingly ] OH, WE'RE
CAMPING.
OOH!
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
>> THANK YOU TO JESUS FOR
PROVIDING THIS BEAUTIFUL
CAMPGROUND.
IF THE CHURCH BUYS THIS PLACE,
WE CAN COME HERE EVERY SUMMER,
TOGETHER.
>> YEAH!
>> [ GIGGLES ] BE SO COOL.
OH, MY GOSH.
YOU BROUGHT A TAPE.
I FORGOT ALL MY AMY GRANT ONES
AT HOME.
THIS IS NOT CHRISTIAN ROCK.
>> AND?
>> SOMEONE IS GOING TO H-E-L.
THAT'S HELL.
>> A-PLUS, BRITTANY.
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> ...OFF, PRINCESS.
>> NICE LANGUAGE, JENNIFER.
>> MMM, MAN, THAT BRITTANY IS
HOT AS HELL.
>> W-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IS SHE SICK?
DOES SHE HAVE A FEVER?
I HOPE IT DOESN'T RUIN HER TRIP.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> NO, YOU WEASY LITTLE DWEEB.
IT MEANS SHE'S BUTT...
BEAUTIFUL.
I GET A BONER EVERY TIME I LOOK
AT THOSE SWEET LITTLE...OF HERS.
OOH!
>> YOU SHOULDN'T THINK UNPURE
THOUGHTS, TAD, OR SAY THE "B"
WORD OR THE "F" WORD.
>> YOU KNOW YOU GET BONERS, YOU
LITTLE COW PIE, DON'T YOU?
>> OW!
NO, I DON'T!
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
YOU PROBABLY GET THEM WHEN YOU
LOOK AT BOYS, HUH?
[ Screeching ] NO, I DON'T!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> LOOK, YOU'RE GETTING ONE
RIGHT NOW.
>> [ GASPS ]
I'M SORRY, JESUS!
JESUS, PLEASE TAKE MY SINFUL
BONER AWAY!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ LAUGH HONKING ]
>> THIS GUY.
[ LAUGHING STOPS ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
TAD.
>> YOU KNOW, THE REALTY COMPANY
IS VERY EAGER TO CLOSE THIS
DEAL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL PLACE, TOUCHED
BY THE HAND OF GOD.
THEY'RE PRACTICALLY GIVING IT
AWAY.
>> YEAH, TOO BAD IT TAKES US A
DAY TO GET HERE.
>> WELL, BROTHER ZEKE, IF YOU
AND FATHER CUMMINGS DIDN'T EACH
DRIVE A JAGUAR, WE PROBABLY
COULD AFFORD A PLACE CLOSER TO
THE CHURCH.
>> JAG?
I DRIVE A CADDY, BABY.
>> YOU GOT TO PAY ATTENTION,
MILLIE.
COME ON.
>> [ Crying ] I'M SORRY, JESUS!
I'M SORRY, JESUS!
JESUS, PLEASE TAKE THIS SINFUL
BONER AWAY!
PLEASE!
THEN FATHER CUMMINGS WON'T LIKE
ME ANYMORE!
PLEASE! PLEASE!
I'M SORRY!
AHH!
WHAT'S ALL THIS WHITE STUFF?
[ GASPING ]
THIS MUST BE THAT HOLY WATER
THAT FATHER CUMMINGS WAS TALKING
ABOUT.
I G-- I GOT TO GO TELL HIM!
>> DON'T IT SEEM A LITTLE WEIRD,
THOUGH, THEY'D BE SELLING THIS
PLACE SO CHEAP?
>> WELL, MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH IT.
>> NOPE. NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, I THINK YOU'RE
WAY OFF BASE ON THIS ONE,
MILLIE.
NO, I -- I THINK THE LORD
BROUGHT US HERE FOR A REASON.
AND THIS WEEKEND WILL GIVE US
THE OPPORTUNITY TO KNOW THE LORD
A LITTLE BIT BETTER AND KNOW A
WHOLE LOT MORE ABOUT OURSELVES.
NOW, I THINK IT'S NO COINCIDENCE
THAT FATE HAS BROUGHT US ALL
TOGETHER HERE FOR A WEEKEND
THAT'S GONNA BE UNFORGETTABLE, A
WEEKEND THAT WE'LL BE TALKING
ABOUT THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
I CAN GUARANTEE YOU THAT.
>> YO, AMEN TO THAT, FATHER.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> RIGHT ON, BROTHER ZEKE.
>> MNH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> YEAH.
MNH. WELL...
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
OH, THIS IS NICE.
>> OH, THANKS.
A GIRLFRIEND OF MINE MADE IT FOR
ME.
>> ALL I'M SAYING IS YOU SHOULD
THINK ABOUT IT, ALL RIGHT?
[ LAUGHS ]
>> SHE MADE IT FOR ME.
>> YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
>> THANKS.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
>> HEY, TIMMY, HOW'S THAT BONER
TREATING YOU?
>> OH, SHUT UP, TAD.
FATHER CUMMINGS SAYS IT'S A HOLY
BONER.
>> OH, I BET HE DID.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S SAFE...
>> I'M REALLY INTERESTED IN YOUR
SKIN AND THE WAY THAT IT'S LIKE
CONNECTED TO YOUR BONES AND THE
MOISTURE AND THE WAY THAT IT
BREATHES.
I'M JUST --
>> [ SQUEALS ]
>> DUDE, COME ON.
YOU'RE LIKE A PRIEST.
>> NO. I'M A BROTHER.
TUSKEGEE AIRMAN...
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> [ GIGGLES ] TAD!
YOU'RE SUCH A FLIRT.
>> COME ON, BABY.
>> SERIOUSLY, THOUGH, LIKE --
>> SO, IS EVERYBODY HAVING A
GREAT TIME THIS WEEKEND.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HALLELUJAH. HALLELUJAH.
>> AH.
I'LL TELL YOU, KIDS -- IF THIS
WEEKEND GOES WELL, THE CHURCH
MAY JUST BUY THIS LITTLE SLICE
OF HEAVEN.
>> OH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, I'LL TELL YOU, THIS WEEKEND
WE'RE GONNA HAVE FELLOWSHIP,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE FUN, AND WE'RE
GONNA HAVE --
>> HOT WIENERS!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE RIGHT, TIMMY.
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE KIND OF
WIENER YOU WANT TO WRAP YOUR
LIPS AROUND, AND THAT'S --
AND THAT'S -- [ GASPS ]
>> UH...
>> THAT'S A HOT, JUICY JUMBO
WIENER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OOH.
>> HERE YOU GO, VANCE.
PASS THOSE AROUND.
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> WAS, UH, ANYONE ELSE CREEPED
OUT BY THAT STORY ABOUT
SISTER MARY CHOPPER?
>> UH, IT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT
MORE THAN A COUPLE TOOTHLESS
INBREDS TO SCARE ME, HUH?
>> WELL, I GOT TO TELL YOU,
GANG -- TOOTHLESS INBREDS --
THEY DON'T TAKE KINDLY TO
OUT-OF-TOWNERS, ALL RIGHT?
THEY MAKE UP STORIES JUST TO
KIND OF GET THEIR GOAT.
>> YEAH, BUT WHAT ABOUT HIS
BROTHER WHO WAS ALL DISFIGURED?
>> YEAH, THAT BOY LOOKED...
>> UH...
>> MESSED UP.
LORD, PRAY FOR HIM.
>> [ SIGHS ]
WELL, UH, I'LL TELL YOU,
JENNIFER -- HE WAS PROBABLY BORN
THAT WAY.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES THE LORD
PUNISHES US FOR REASONS THAT WE
DON'T KNOW, EVEN AT BIRTH.
BUT YOU HAVE TO KNOW THAT IT'S
ALL PART OF HIS UNIVERSAL PLAN.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
WELL, I, UH -- I GUESS THAT PUTS
THAT TO REST.
AT ANY RATE I WANTED TO LET YOU
GUYS KNOW [SIGHS] THAT I HAVE A
BIG SURPRISE FOR YOU.
I WROTE A SPECIAL SONG FOR THIS
WEEKEND.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OH...
>> [ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
I MUST SAY THAT I AM INSPIRED
THIS WEEK.
I'M INSPIRED BY A VISION, A
VISION OF THE WORLD'S GREATEST
GOD-FEARING BIBLE CAMP
[CHUCKLES] FILLED WITH BOYS WHO,
LIKE THEIR FOREFATHERS, CAN
LEARN HOW TO SHOOT A
BLACK-POWDER RIFLE AND WEAR A
COONSKIN CAP
>> GREAT.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
AND GIRLS -- THE GIRLS WILL
LEARN TO BE GREAT HOMEMAKERS AND
GREAT HOUSEWIVES.
[ LAUGHS ]
HERE WE GO.
♪ AS I LOOKED DOWN UP THE LAND
♪ GUESS WHAT I DID SEE
♪ LOADS OF BOYS BECOMING MEN
♪ JESUS HAS THE HOLY KEY
♪ AND ALL THE GIRLS WILL LEARN
TO COOK AND KEEP HOUSE FOR THE
CLAN ♪
♪ TO BE A LOYAL RANGER RAT TO A
LOYAL RANGER MAN ♪
♪ OH, CAN'T YOU SEE THE DREAM
IS SWEET? ♪
♪ REALLY QUITE AT HAND
♪ BE A BOY IN A COONSKIN CAP
♪ BECOME A CHRISTIAN MAN
♪ WE'LL ALL SPLASH ROUND IN THE
LAKE ALL DAY ♪
♪ YES, WE'LL BE REAL GOOD
SWIMMERS ♪
♪ AND THE GIRLS WILL BLESS THE
DINING HALL WITH BREAKFAST,
LUNCH, AND DINNERS ♪
♪ OH, CAN'T YOU SEE THE DREAM
IS SWEET? ♪
♪ AND IT COULDN'T BE MUCH
KEENER ♪
♪ WE'LL ROAST OUR DOGS IN THE
CAMPFIRE LIGHT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY, GRAB YOUR WIENER
[ SONG ENDS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
WELL, KIDS, IT'S BEEN A LONG
DAY, AND I THINK I'M GONNA GO
HIT THE SACK.
>> [ MOANING ]
OUR FATHER WHO ART IN HEAVEN,
HALLOWED BE THY NAME.
THY KINGDOM COME, THY WILL BE
DONE ON EARTH AS IT IS IN
HEAVEN.
>> [ HUMMING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
>> OOH, YEAH.
>> DO YOU LIKE MY BREASTS?
>> YES.
>> ME TOO.
[ HUMMING ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
♪ YES, I LOVE YOU, JESUS
♪ OH, YEAH
>> [ WOLF-WHISTLES ]
♪ YES, I LOVE YOU, JESUS
OH, YEAH.
>> [ WOLF-WHISTLES ]
THAT'S RIGHT, BRITTANY.
OH, YEAH.
KEEP IT UP.
THAT'S RIGHT, BRITTANY.
[ HUMMING ]
KEEP IT UP.
>> [ Laughing ] OH, YEAH.
[ HUMMING ]
DADDY LIKE. DADDY LIKE.
>> [ Laughing ] OH, YEAH.
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
DADDY LIKE. DADDY LIKE.
GOD, I LOVE WHITE WOMEN.
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
OH!
GOD, I LOVE WHITE WOMEN.
FATHER CUMMINGS.
OH!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
FATHER CUMMINGS.
YOU SCARED ME THERE FOR A
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
SECOND.
YOU SCARED ME THERE FOR A
I WAS JUST, UH, MAKING SURE ALL
SECOND.
THE CAMPERS WERE GETTING TO BED
I WAS JUST, UH, MAKING SURE ALL
OKAY.
THE CAMPERS WERE GETTING TO BED
>> I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU WERE
OKAY.
DOING, BROTHER ZEKE.
>> I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU WERE
>> UH...I'M SORRY, FATHER.
DOING, BROTHER ZEKE.
I PROMISE I WILL NEVER GET
>> UH...I'M SORRY, FATHER.
CAUGHT DOING THAT AGAIN.
I PROMISE I WILL NEVER GET
>> OH, YOU DON'T NEED TO
CAUGHT DOING THAT AGAIN.
APOLOGIZE TO ME.
>> OH, YOU DON'T NEED TO
YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE TO THE
APOLOGIZE TO ME.
LORD.
YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE TO THE
HE'S THE ONLY WHO FORGIVES
LORD.
AROUND HERE.
HE'S THE ONLY WHO FORGIVES
>> YES, FATHER.
AROUND HERE.
>> BUT LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
>> YES, FATHER.
AT LEAST I DIDN'T CATCH YOU
>> BUT LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
SPYING ON THE BOYS UNDRESSING.
AT LEAST I DIDN'T CATCH YOU
[ LAUGHS ]
SPYING ON THE BOYS UNDRESSING.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
>> OKAY.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
>> OKAY.
MM.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
YEAH. NOW HAND IT OVER.
MM.
[ SNIFFS ]
YEAH. NOW HAND IT OVER.
OH, BROTHER ZEKE.
[ SNIFFS ]
THE WAGES OF SIN -- DEATH.
OH, BROTHER ZEKE.
>> Both: ROMANS 6:23.
THE WAGES OF SIN -- DEATH.
>> MM.
>> Both: ROMANS 6:23.
NOW GO TO BED.
>> MM.
WE HAVE A BIG DAY TOMORROW.
NOW GO TO BED.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
WE HAVE A BIG DAY TOMORROW.
>> WHITE DEVIL.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
>> WHITE DEVIL.
>> [ MOANING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
>> YOU'RE GONNA DIE...
>> [ MOANING ]
>> [ GASPING ]
>> YOU'RE GONNA DIE...
[ WHIMPERING ]
>> [ GASPING ]
>> [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
>> THE TALLYWACKERS, DUMMY!
>> [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
>> THE TALLYWACKERS, DUMMY!
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
RISE AND SHINE, BIBLE CAMPERS.
IT'S EXACTLY 6:00 A.M. AT THE
HAPPY DAY BIBLE CAMP, AND TIME'S
A-WASTING.
WE HAVE A FULL DAY OF SWIMMING,
NATURE WALKS, AND, YES, OUR
FAMOUS TRIVIA GAME, THE BIBLE
BOWL!
[ BUZZER ]
>> OH! OH, GOSH!
THE BIBLE BOWL!
I BETTER HURRY UP AND GET TO
BREAKFAST.
IF THERE'S ONE THING I LIKE
BETTER THAN HOT, JUICY WIENERS,
IT'S A BIG, BROWN SAUSAGE.
>> HEY, BE CAREFUL, TIMMY,
BEFORE YOU GET ANOTHER BIBLE
BONER.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> HA HA, TAD.
>> HEY, VANCE, DID YOU HEAR WHAT
I SAID?
>> YEAH, I HEARD YOU.
>> [ SIGHS ]
RISE AND SHINE, BOSS.
>> [ GROANS ] ...THIS...
[ EXHALES HEAVILY ]
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
I PRAY TO ALMIGHTY GOD...
AND TO YOU, MY BROTHERS AND
SISTERS THAT I HAVE SINNER IN MY
WORDS, IN MY THOUGHTS, IN MY
THOUGHTS, AND -- AND -- AND IN
MY ACTIONS, AND IN WHAT I FAILED
TO ACT.
AND -- AND I ASK YOU, BLESSED
MARY, OH, BLESSED MARY, AND THE
HOLY WOMB AND THE BLOOD THAT
FLOWS FROM THE HOLY WOMB -- I'LL
ASK YOU TO PRAY FOR ME.
[ Laughing ] PRAY FOR ME NOW AND
AT THE HOUR OF MY DEATH!
>> ALL RIGHT, CAMPERS!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YAY! FATHER!
OW!
>> THIS IS DEFINITELY GONNA BE
ONE OF THE HIGHLIGHTS OF OUR
WEEKEND.
BROTHER ZEKE AND I HAVE PUT
TOGETHER SOME BIBLICAL TRIVIA
QUESTIONS FOR OUR FRIENDLY
LITTLE CONTEST.
AND THIS SHOULD PROVE BEYOND A
SHADOW OF A DOUBT WHICH ONE OF
YOU CAMPERS IS THE BEST
CHRISTIAN HERE TODAY.
HUH?
ALL RIGHT!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> FATHER!
>> AND THE WINNER OF THE CONTEST
WILL RECEIVE THIS BEAUTIFUL,
BRAND-NEW, GOOD NEWS BIBLE FROM
THE ST. JUDAS CHURCH [CHUCKLES]
WITH A PERSONAL INSCRIPTION BY
YOURS TRULY.
HUH? OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, CAMPERS, ARE YOU
READY?
>> YEAH!
[ APPLAUSE ]
YEAH! FATHER!
>> OW!
>> ARE YOU READY?
HERE'S THE FIRST QUESTION --
WHAT IS THE EIGHTH COMMANDMENT?
>> OH.
>> YEAH, VANCE?
>> "THOU SHALT NOT KILL."
>> NO.
UH, TIMMY?
>> ACCORDING TO THE KING JAMES
VERSION OF THE BIBLE, IT'S "THOU
SHALT NOT STEAL."
>> RIGHT, AS USUAL, TIMMY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY.
OH, CHALK UP TIMMY FOR ONE
THERE.
>> BUT WASN'T JESUS THE PRINCE
OF THIEVES?
>> NO. UH, NO.
UH, THE NEXT QUESTION -- NOW,
EVERYBODY, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
CATCH UP WITH TIMMY 'CAUSE
OBVIOUSLY HE'S LAUNCHED AHEAD,
OKAY?
SO, SEE IF YOU CAN GET THIS ONE.
WHO WAS THE FIRST SON OF ADAM
AND EVE?
>> PAUL!
>> NO.
>> UH, JASON?
>> UH, NO.
>> JOSEPH.
>> NO!
>> JESUS!
>> WRONG AGAIN.
>> TIMMY?
>> CAIN.
>> [ Chuckling ] THAT'S RIGHT.
OH, CHALK HIM UP FOR ANOTHER.
>> OW.
>> [ CLEARS THROAT ]
OKAY, QUESTION NUMBER THREE.
NOW, EVERYBODY, TRY REALLY HARD
ON THIS ONE.
YOU GOT TO CATCH UP, OKAY?
WHAT HAPPENS TO THOSE WHO DON'T
ASK FORGIVENESS BEFORE THEY DIE?
>> Together: THEY GO TO HELL!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> YOU GOT ME ON THAT ONE.
THAT WAS A GIVE-AWAY, WASN'T IT,
BROTHER ZEKE?
GIVE EVERYBODY ONE.
EXCELLENT.
>> WELL, WHAT IF HITLER ASKED
FOR FORGIVENESS BEFORE HE DIED?
>> WELL, THEN I SUPPOSE HE'S IN
HEAVEN, ISN'T HE?
NEXT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
OKAY, UH, NEXT QUESTION --
ACCORDING TO THE GOOD BOOK, WHO
IS RESPONSIBLE FOR KILLING
JESUS?
LET'S GIVE THIS TO SOMEBODY WHO
DOESN'T HAVE A CHANCE.
>> YEAH, YEAH, TO THE BIMBO.
>> UH, BRITTANY!
>> UH...THE, UM...
>> YEAH, THE --
THE -- THE --
>> YOU KNOW...
>> RIGHT, THE...
YEAH, UH-HUH, THE, UH...
YEAH.
>> UM...
GET -- YEAH. YEAH.
>> THE JEWS!
>> OH!
EXCELLENT JOB, BRITTANY, VERY,
VERY GOOD.
TIMMY, I THINK YOU MAY HAVE SOME
COMPETITION OVER HERE.
UM -- [ CHUCKLES ] ALL RIGHT.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT -- WHAT ABOUT
ALL THE -- ALL THE MURDERS THAT
HAPPENED IN THE NAME OF CHRIST?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
UH, DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY?
OKAY, THE NEXT QUESTION IS --
WHAT DOES GOD DO TO WOMEN
WHO HAVE ABORTIONS?
>> THEY BURN IN HELL.
SORRY, JENNIFER.
>> VERY GOOD, VANCE, VERY GOOD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> WELL, WHAT IF GOD WAS A
WOMAN?
WHAT IF GOD'S GRANDFATHER RAPED
HER WHEN HE WAS 12?
>> RAPE?
DON'T BE SILLY, JENNIFER.
EVERYONE KNOWS GOD'S A MAN.
>> AND -- AND HE WAS PROBABLY
WEARING SOMETHING LIKE REAL
SKIMPY AND FLIRTING AND LIKE
ASKING FOR IT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, JIMMY, AND GOD
DOESN'T HAVE A GRANDFATHER,
ANYWAY.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
NOW, LET'S NOT BE RIDICULOUS,
JENNIFER.
BESIDES, YOU'RE SCARING TIMMY,
OKAY?
NOW, THIS SHOULD BE AN EASY ONE.
WHAT HAPPENS TO HOMOSEXUALS?
>> THEY BECOME PRIESTS.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
MM.
[ THE SMOKING VAGINAS' "GET UP"
PLAYS ]
>> ♪ GET UP
>> WHOO!
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> YEAH!
♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> ♪ I CAME HERE TO PRAY
♪ GET UP, GET UP
♪ NOW I'M READY TO PLAY
>> ♪ I CAME HERE TO PRAY
>> YEAH! YEAH!
♪ NOW I'M READY TO PLAY
WHOO!
>> YEAH! YEAH!
>> ♪ ALWAYS PLAYED BY THE
WHOO!
RULES ♪
>> ♪ ALWAYS PLAYED BY THE
>> ♪ I THINK YOU'RE KIND OF
RULES ♪
CUTE ♪
>> ♪ I THINK YOU'RE KIND OF
♪ WHAT YOU THINK WE SHOULD DO?
CUTE ♪
>> ♪ THESE CLOTHES ARE REALLY
♪ WHAT YOU THINK WE SHOULD DO?
HOT AND, GIRL, SO ARE YOU ♪
>> ♪ THESE CLOTHES ARE REALLY
>> WHOOP!
HOT AND, GIRL, SO ARE YOU ♪
>> ♪ NO ONE'S HERE TO TELL US
>> WHOOP!
WHAT'S WRONG OR RIGHT ♪
>> ♪ NO ONE'S HERE TO TELL US
>> ♪ I'VE BEEN HELD UP ALL MY
WHAT'S WRONG OR RIGHT ♪
LIFE, AND NOW I'M READY, READY ♪
>> ♪ I'VE BEEN HELD UP ALL MY
>> [ CHUCKLES ] WHOO!
LIFE, AND NOW I'M READY, READY ♪
>> THERE'S NO SKINNY-DIPPING!
>> [ CHUCKLES ] WHOO!
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> THERE'S NO SKINNY-DIPPING!
♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> ♪ MOMMY AND DADDY AREN'T HERE
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
TO PLEASE ♪
>> ♪ MOMMY AND DADDY AREN'T HERE
>> I DON'T LIKE THIS!
TO PLEASE ♪
THIS IS NOT APPROPRIATE!
>> I DON'T LIKE THIS!
>> IT'S NOT APPROPRIATE?
THIS IS NOT APPROPRIATE!
THIS IS VERY APPROPRIATE.
>> IT'S NOT APPROPRIATE?
>> [ Crying ] NO, IT ISN'T.
THIS IS VERY APPROPRIATE.
>> ♪ BABY, COME OVER HERE  ♪
>> [ Crying ] NO, IT ISN'T.
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING THE
>> ♪ BABY, COME OVER HERE  ♪
DORK ♪
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING THE
>> ♪ I'LL TAKE ALL THAT YOU GOT
DORK ♪
AND THEN I'LL GIVE YOU SOME
>> ♪ I'LL TAKE ALL THAT YOU GOT
MORE ♪
AND THEN I'LL GIVE YOU SOME
>> ♪ NO ONE'S HERE TO TELL US
MORE ♪
WHAT'S WRONG OR RIGHT ♪
>> ♪ NO ONE'S HERE TO TELL US
>> ♪ I'VE BEEN HELD UP ALL MY
WHAT'S WRONG OR RIGHT ♪
LIFE, AND NOW I'M READY, READY ♪
>> ♪ I'VE BEEN HELD UP ALL MY
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
LIFE, AND NOW I'M READY, READY ♪
♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> YEAH!
♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> ♪ GET UP, GET UP
>> YEAH!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> YOU KNOW, UH, YOU REALLY
OUGHT TO CONSIDER BECOMING A
FATHER SOMEDAY, BROTHER ZEKE.
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> UH-HUH.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
WOULDN'T THAT BE SOMETHING?
[ SIGHS ]
>> COOL.
>> [ SIGHS ]
LOOK AT THIS SCENERY.
Whew.
ONLY GOD COULD HAVE CREATED
SOMETHING AS BEAUTIFUL AS THIS.
>> AMEN.
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> SO, WHAT'S NEXT?
TRUST EXERCISES?
>> [ Chuckling ] NO.
I GUESS FATHER CUMMINGS HAS A,
UH, NATURE WALK PLANNED.
>> [ Sarcastically ] RAD.
>> DON'T WORRY.
YOU COULD, UH, ALWAYS PAIR UP
WITH ME.
>> COOL.
I'D LIKE THAT.
>> SO, I GUESS...
YOU'RE NOT REALLY HAVING A GOOD
TIME UP HERE.
>> IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST...
FOR A PLACE THAT'S SUPPOSED TO
BE FOR EVERYONE, KIND OF FEEL
LIKE A LONER, YOU KNOW?
>> YOU SHOULDN'T.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
>> NO. IT'S KIND OF COMPLICATED.
THANKS, THOUGH.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> 2...
>> AND...
>> ...AND 3...
>> ...THEY...
>> ...AND JESUS --
OOH! AND 4...
AND 5...
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
>> ...AND 9...
AND 10.
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> WHAT THE HECK?
STOP IT!
>> UGH.
>> PERVERT.
>> OH. UH...
>> OOH!
>> AND JESUS...
AND 2...
>> UH, UH, UH, UH...
UH, BAMBI.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> IN THE NAME OF THE FATHER,
AND OF THE SON, AND OF THE
HOLY SPIRIT.
OH, JESUS, I KNOW I'VE BEEN SUCH
A BAD GIRL.
[ CRYING ]
BUT I PROMISE, AFTER TODAY, I'M
GONNA -- I'M GONNA GET -- I
PROMISE, I'M GONNA DO BETTER.
I'M GONNA GET ALL THOSE
SINNERS -- ALL OF THEM -- I
PROMISE.
THEY DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH YOU
LOVE THEM.
AND REALLY, I SWEAR, THEY'RE
GONNA KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LOVE
THEM, BECAUSE YOU LOVE THEM AS
MUCH AS YOU LOVE ME!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, JESUS.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
I LOVE YOU.
[ WAILS ]
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
[ WAILS ]
>> [ LAUGHING ]
>> ♪ FROZEN TIME, FROZEN...
>> I WONDER HOW THOSE DUMB...
CAMPING PREACHERS ARE DOING.
>> AW...THEY'RE DOING NOTHING
DYING, IF SISTER MARY CHOPPER
DECIDES TO MAKE AN ENCORE.
>> [ LAUGHING ]
[ CHALK SCREECHING ON BOARD ]
>> OH!
>> AAH!
>> ...DWAYNE!
>> I HATE WHEN HE TALKS!
OH! AAH!
COME ON, COME ON.
OH. OH. OH.
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> OH!
G-GLO-- GLO--
OH...NO.
YOU AIN'T GOING TO THAT CAMP.
YOU HEAR ME?
WE WARNED THEM.
WE DID OUR BEST.
THAT'S ALL WE CAN DO.
AND QUIT WASTING PEANUTS.
>> [ LAUGHING ]
>> ♪ JESUS LOVES ME
♪ THAT I KNOW
♪ FOR THE BIBLE TELLS ME SO
♪ IF WE'RE GOOD AND SAY OUR
PRAYERS ♪
[ Laughing ] ♪ THEN WE KNOW
THAT JESUS CARES ♪
♪ JESUS LOVES ME
♪ THAT I KNOW
♪ FOR THE BIBLE TELLS ME SO
♪ IF WE'RE GOOD AND SAY OUR
PRAYERS ♪
THEN WE KNOW THAT JESUS CARES.
JESUS LOVES YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
[ LAUGHING ]
♪ I LOVE YOU
♪ JESUS LOVES ME
[ Laughing ] ♪ WE ARE A HAPPY
FAMILY ♪
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
[ DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE ]
>> OH, MILLIE, UM, I-I HAD A
QUESTION.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU COULD
JUST...
[ PATS SEAT ]
UM, JUST FOR A MINUTE.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> LOOK, UM, I WAS CONCERNED
ABOUT JENNIFER AND HER BELIEFS.
>> [ SIGHS ]
WE ALL ARE.
>> IS IT TRUE THAT, UH, SHE'S A,
UM -- HERE ON COURT ORDER?
>> [ SCOFFS ]
NOT NOW, VANCE.
>> UM, BUT TAD SAID THAT SHE
WAS, AND...I...
>> I....AM A...
STRAIGHT MAN...
WITH NO HOMOSEXUAL TENDENCIES.
>> WHAT YOU DOING?
>> OH. HEY.
>> HEY.
>> [ PANTING ]
CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE TO BUNK
WITH THAT LITTLE FAT KID.
>> I HATE FAT PEOPLE.
>> TOTALLY.
>> THEY SMELL.
>> I DON'T KNOW,
FATHER CUMMINGS.
I JUST DON'T LIKE TO DRINK MILK
WITHOUT MY COOKIES.
DO I REALLY HAVE TO?
>> WELL, IF YOU WANT TO BE ABLE
TO THROW THE FOOTBALL LIKE TAD,
YOU DO, TIMMY.
>> [ SIGHS ]
I WISH I WAS BIG LIKE TAD.
>> SO DO I, TIMMY.
SO DO I.
>> UH...
SO, YOU'RE KIND OF CUTE.
YOU KNOW THAT?
>> THAT'S JUST WHAT MY DAD SAID.
>> I'M SORRY FOR THE WAY I'VE
BEEN ACTING, MILLIE.
I GUESS I'VE JUST BEEN CONFUSED
ABOUT SOME THINGS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
IT'S NOT HARD TO SEE THAT YOU
HAVE QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR FAITH,
JENNIFER.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL.
>> I JUST FIND IT HARD TO
BELIEVE THAT CHRISTIANITY IS THE
ONLY ANSWER.
>> WELL...
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'D BE KIND OF
PRETTY IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE SUCH A
HORSE FACE.
>> BUT I HAVE PERKY BOOBS.
>> YOU DO SEE MY POINT, THOUGH,
DON'T YOU, MILLIE?
>> I DO.
I SEE YOUR POINT, JENNIFER,
BUT --
>> LET ME GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
>> DO YOU WANT TO PLAY WITH MY
PINK, FUZZY ONE?
>> OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M GONNA GO BACK TO THE CABIN
AND GROW ONE OUT, BUT, UH,
MAYBE LATER, HUH?
>> COOL.
>> OKAY.
>> BYE.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> HE IS SO INTO ME.
>> AND THEN HE DIES.
DOES HE GO TO HELL?
>> I DON'T KNOW, JENNIFER.
I MEAN, WHY DID ABRAHAM HAVE TO
SACRIFICE ISAAC?
WHY DID JESUS HAVE TO BE
CRUCIFIED BY HIS PEOPLE?
>> [ High-pitched voice ] OH,
BRITTANY, YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
[ Normal voice ] I KNOW.
[ CHUCKLES
>> BEAUTIFUL DAY.
>> [ GASPS ] OH.
I WASN'T PLAYING WITH MYSELF, I
SWEAR.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> WELL, MAYBE YOU'D LIKE
SOMEBODY TO PLAY WITH.
>> OH, I'M SORRY.
MY DADDY DOESN'T LET ME PLAY
WITH BLACK BOYS.
SEE YA.
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
YOU GIRLS LOOKING FOR A THIRD?
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE...IT.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
SO, VANCE, SEE YOU READING THE
BIBLE ALL THE TIME.
YOU MUST BE A PRETTY STOUT
CHRISTIAN.
>> YEAH, WELL, I'M JUST TRYING
TO FIND SOME LOOPHOLES IN IT.
>> LOOPHOLES?
WHAT'S THAT?
>> UH, YOU KNOW, DIFFERENT
THINGS.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE, RIGHT NOW?
>> YEAH?
>> UM...
RIGHT NOW, I'M, UH...
JUST TRYING TO FIND OUT WHAT THE
WHOLE BIG DEAL WAS WITH SODOMY.
>> SALAMI?
>> SODOMY.
>> WHAT'S SODOMY?
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ Voice cracking ] SO...
[ Normal voice ] BRITTANY...
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
>> [ Chuckling ] OH, GOD'S THE
ONLY MAN IN MY LIFE.
WHY? DID TAD SAY SOMETHING?
>> NO.
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ SCOFFS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> ♪ JESUS LOVES ME
♪ THAT I KNOW
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
>> [ Sighing ] AH.
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> THERE IS DEFINITELY SOME
JESUS GOING ON THIS WEEKEND.
>> OOH, DON'T I KNOW IT!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> SO, DO YOU REALLY THINK
BRITTANY'S EASY?
>> GOD, I HOPE.
I MEAN, LOOK, LOOK, TAD, SHE'S A
VERY DEVOUT CHRISTIAN.
>> I KNOW, BUT I WAS THINKING,
MAYBE I COULD MAKE HER THINK IT
WAS OKAY BECAUSE I'M A
CHRISTIAN, TOO.
THE LORD'S COOL WITH THAT,
RIGHT?
>> I'M NOT SURE WE SHOULD BE
TALKING ABOUT THIS KIND OF
STUFF.
I MEAN, IF FATHER CUMMINGS
CATCHES US, HE'LL HAVE OUR...
LITERALLY.
>> YOU'RE NOT A FATHER,
BROTHER ZEKE.
COME ON, YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME
THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO GET WITH
MILLIE, HUH?
OR MAYBE THAT LITTLE FREAK
JENNIFER JUST ONCE THIS WEEKEND?
COME ON, JUST ONE TIME!
IT'S THE PERFECT WEEKEND.
NO ONE'S EVEN GONNA FIND OUT
ABOUT IT.
>> IT WOULD BE NICE.
>> ...RIGHT, IT WOULD.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO?
>> YOU MEAN, YOU GOT NOTHING?
>> NO, THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING
YOU.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
LOOK, MAN [SCOFFS] HERE WE GO.
I'LL GO BACK TO THE VAN.
I'LL RUN BACK TO THE
CRACKER SHACK, AND I'LL PICK UP
SOME BEER AND SOME RUBBERS.
>> RUBBERS?
WHAT? WHAT AM I, A HOMOSEXUAL?
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
I'M GONNA HAVE BUTT SEX WITH
BRITTANY?
I'M GONNA GET A.I.D.S.?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE THINKING?
>> DUDE, YOU ARE A...FOOL, MAN.
THE LAST THING WE NEED IS A
COUPLE OF KNOCKED-UP CHRISTIAN
SKANKS!
>> [ Chuckling ] OH.
OKAY, TOTALLY.
TOTALLY.
BUT WHAT'S THE BEER FOR?
>> THE BEER, MY GOOD MAN...
>> MM-HMM?
>> ...IS TO LOOSEN UP THE LADIES
A TAD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
I SMELL YOU.
TO LOOSEN UP THE LADIES.
RIGHT. I LIKE THAT, I LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, MAYBE YOU
BETTER TAKE OFF BEFORE ANYONE
REALIZES YOU'RE GONE.
>> OH, OH, OKAY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, SURE.
UH, ANYTHING ELSE I CAN GET FOR
YOU, MASSA?
>> NO, JUST -- JUST GET THE --
JUST GET THE BEER.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
YEAH, I DEFINITELY AM GROWING
SOMETHING DOWN HERE.
AND THAT'S WHY THEY CALL ME
RAD TAD.
OW!
YEAH!
TAD.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
I AM HE LORD'S SHEPHERD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I SHALL NOT WANT!
[ GASPS ]
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
[ THUD ]
>> [ MOANING ]
>> [ Echoing ] "I AM THE ONE.
I DIED.
AND BEHOLD, I AM ALIVE FOREVER!"
I AM THE KEEPER OF THE KEY TO
HADES AND DEATH!"
>> I WANT TO BE A PRIEST WHEN I
GROW UP.
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
YOU'LL NEVER BE A PRIEST.
YOU'LL BE A GIRL, JUST LIKE
THAT...OF A MOTHER WANTED YOU TO
BE!
>> OH!
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
YOU'RE A GIRL!
>> NO! [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> YOU'RE A GIRL.
>> NO!
NO!
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
>> UGH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ MOANING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> SO, THERE WE ARE, 3 MINUTES
TO GO, 13 DOWN.
NEEDLESS TO SAY, TWO TOUCHDOWNS
LATER, I'M HOLD THE STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP TROPHY.
>> NO WAY.
>> WAY.
>> SO, WHAT POSITION DO YOU
PLAY, AGAIN?
>> QUARTERBACK.
>> THAT'S, LIKE, THE BEST ONE.
>> WHATEVER.
[ SCOFFS ]
LISTEN, I GOT BROTHER ZEKE TO GO
DOWN TO THE STORE AND PICK US UP
SOME BREWSKIES.
>> HOW'D YOU MANAGE THAT?
>> LEAVE THE DETAILS TO ME.
>> WELL, IS HE GONNA GET ANY
WINE COOLERS?
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, JESUS IS COOL
WITH WINE COOLERS.
>> WELL, YOU'LL BE DRINKING
SOMETHING.
>> YEAH?
>> JUST MEET ME AT THE FIRE PIT
AT MIDNIGHT.
>> I'LL BE THERE.
BUT I GOT TO WARN YOU...
I GET A LITTLE SILLY WHEN I
DRINK.
>> SO DO I.
I'LL SEE YOU AT MIDNIGHT...
SILLY.
>> IT'S BRITTANY.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> TAD?
HEY! FATHER CUMMINGS.
WHAT'S UP?
>> UH, WELL, TAD, WE SEEM TO BE
MISSING ZEKE.
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
>> STILL?
>> "STILL"?
>> TAD?
>> I -- I FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
BROTHER ZEKE HAD TO, UH...
HE HAD TO GO BACK TO THE GENERAL
STORE AND PICK UP SOME, UH,
MATCHES.
>> MATCHES?
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH, THAT'S FUNNY.
WE -- WE HAVE LOTS OF MATCHES,
DON'T WE?
>> HMM.
I DON'T, UH, I DON'T KNOW.
I -- THAT'S JUST WHAT HE SAID.
>> HMM.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, TAD.
DO US A FAVOR AND KEEP AN EYE
OUT FOR HIM, ALL RIGHT?
>> WILL DO.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
BROTHER ZEKE.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
ZEKE!
BROTHER ZEKE.
GETTING ON THAT HOLY HIGH!
ZEKE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
GETTING ON THAT HOLY HIGH!
ZEKE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
ZEKE!
ZEKE?
AAH!
ZEKE!
AAH!!
AAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AAH!!
HOLY...
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AAH!
HOLY...
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
OH, YEAH!
AAH!
OH!
OH, YEAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OH!
OH...
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ LAUGHING NERVOUSLY ]
OH...
[ GASPING ]
[ LAUGHING NERVOUSLY ]
NO!
[ GASPING ]
OH, GOD, NO!
NO!
AAAH!
OH, GOD, NO!
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ RUSTLING ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
IN DISTANCE ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> YOU KNOW, THIS WEEKEND HAS
GONE BETTER THAN WE COULD HAVE
EVER IMAGINED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
GOD HAS TRULY BLESSED THIS
WEEKEND, MILLIE.
HE'S BLESSED OUR BANK ACCOUNT,
AS WELL.
WE MAY ACTUALLY BE BUYING THIS
CAMP, AFTER ALL.
UH, SORRY, MILLIE, I DON'T
DETECT ANY ENTHUSIASM ON YOUR
PART.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
I'M SORRY, FATHER.
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
I'M JUST TIRED.
>> WELL, IT IS GETTING LATE.
HMM. MAYBE YOU SHOULD TURN IN.
>> I THINK I WILL.
I'M GONNA GO CHECK ON THE GIRLS
FIRST.
GOOD NIGHT, FATHER.
>> UH, DON'T -- DON'T FORGET TO
SAY YOUR PRAYERS, OKAY?
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
>> [ SNORING ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
>> [ MOUTHING WORDS ]
>> [ STOPS SNORING ]
[ SNORING ]
[ STOPS SNORING ]
WHAT, VANCE?
>> I'M TRYING TO SHUT YOU UP.
YOU WERE SNORING AGAIN.
>> [ Whining ] NO, I WASN'T!
>> YES, YOU WERE.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
I'M GONNA GO FIND A SODA
MACHINE.
I'M THIRSTY.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
[ ANIMAL SCREECHES ]
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
[ INHALING SHARPLY ]
[ CHUCKLING ]
OH, BROTHER ZEKE...
[ SIGHS ]
SOME GOOD...BRO.
[ COUGHS ]
YEAH.
HMM.
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
UH... [ COUGHING ]
WHO'S THERE?
[ Sighing ] GOD.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AW.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OH.
YEAH, JUST A MINUTE!
WHO ARE YOU?
>> "I AM THE WAY."
>> OH, MY GOD!
[ SLASH ]
>> AAH.
>> "I AM THE TRUTH."
[ SLASH ]
>> UGH.
UGH.
>> "AND I AM THE LIFE!"
>> [ MOANING ]
>> "NOBODY COMES UNTO THE LORD
EXCEPT THROUGH ME"!
>> [ GASPING ]
>> [ GRUNTS ]
EPHESIANS 2:8.
[ SLASH ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
[ SIGHS ]
[ SLAPS LEG ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
FATHER CUMMINGS, I FORGOT TO
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
[ SIGHS ]
HMM.
WONDER IF THERE'S A CUP.
[ DRAWER OPENS ]
[ DRAWER CLOSES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ DRAWER OPENS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
HE KNEW.
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> I HATE BOYS.
I SHOULD JUST BECOME A...LIKE
MILLIE.
EW. [ CHUCKLES ]
[ SMOOCHES ]
AT LEAST I HAVE YOU.
[ SIGHS ]
TAD...IS THAT YOU?
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
I KNEW YOU LOVED ME.
SO...
I LEARNED ABOUT THIS THING
TODAY.
IT'S CALLED A LOOPHOLE.
HAVE YOU HEARD OF THAT?
I HADN'T EITHER.
ANYWAY, VANCE SAID IT WAS A WAY,
YOU KNOW, TO GET AROUND SOME OF
THE RULES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO I WAS THINKING, MAYBE WE
COULD DO IT IN THE BUTT.
YOU THINK THAT MIGHT WORK?
I REALLY DON'T THINK HE'D MIND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH. OH!
JUST GO A LITTLE SLOW, OKAY?
'CAUSE -- OH!
[ Chuckling ] TAD.
[ GASPS ] OH.
TAD?
>> CHOKE FOR JESUS, SALOME.
>> AAH! AAH!
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
>> AAH!
>> [ CONTINUES LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ STOPS LAUGHING ]
[ SIGHS ]
♪ JESUS LOVES ME
♪ THAT I KNOW
♪ FOR THE BIBLE TELLS ME SO
♪ IF YOU'RE GOOD AND SAY YOUR
PRAYERS ♪
♪ THAT'S HOW YOU KNOW JESUS
CARES ♪
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
>> BRITTANY?
BRITTANY?
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
OH!
OH, MY GOD!
[ GASPING ]
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
[ CLICK ]
OH, MY GOD!
>> WHAT?
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WE GOT TO CALL THE POLICE!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
THERE'S NO PHONE!
>> [ MUTTERING ]
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
YOUR REAL NAME ISN'T EVEN
MILLIE?!
>> WAIT. WAIT. LET ME EXPLAIN.
MY REAL NAME IS GLORIA ESPERANZA
GUADALUPE EL CAMPO.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS PLACE THE
WHOLE...TIME!
WHO KILLED BRITTANY?!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
TALK...
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
I WAS HERE SEVEN YEARS AGO AS A
COUNSELOR, AND THIS MANIAC
SHOWED UP AND STARTED
SLAUGHTERING EVERYONE.
[ SOBS ]
DWAYNE AND I WERE THE ONLY ONES
TO SURVIVE.
[ MOANING ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> THOU SHALT NOT...
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> [ GASPS ]
[ THUD ]
AAAAH!
[ SLASH ]
>> [ GASPING ]
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
>> [ Crying ] I WAS SO SCARED, I
JUST TOOK OFF RUNNING.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO HIM.
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
UNTIL YOU SAW HIM AT THE STORE?
>> YES.
>> AND THEN YOU COULDN'T GO IN?
GOD.
>> I MEAN, I COULDN'T FACE HIM
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
HOW COULD I, AFTER LEAVING HIM
ALL ALONE?
>> [ SNIFFLES ]
>> I DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING LIKE
THIS TO EVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
BELIEVE ME, JENNIFER...
I NEVER WOULD HAVE PUT YOU GUYS
IN ANY DANGER.
>> [ Sarcastically ] YEAH, WELL,
YOU'RE DOING A REAL GOOD JOB
OF IT...
[ SIGHS ]
WE GOT TO FIND FATHER CUMMINGS.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> [ SNORING ]
YOU'RE WELCOME.
[ SNORES ]
HMM.
[ SMACKING LIPS ]
WHOA!
>> WHERE IS DWAYNE?
>> [ GASPS ] I DON'T KNOW!
>> IF HE WENT TO THAT CHRISTIAN
CAMP, IT'S YOUR...
>> [ WHIMPERS ]
>> WHERE'S DWAYNE?!
>> I DON'T KNOW!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> COME ON, WHERE'S DWAYNE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, I SWEAR.
>> WHERE'S DWAYNE?
>> I DON'T KNOW!
>> WHERE'S DWAYNE?!
>> [ GRUNTING ]
>> GOD...IT.
>> [ CRYING ]
>> I'M GONNA GO CALL THE
SHERIFF.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK I'M
GONNA DO?
>> [ SOBBING ]
>> I'M GONNA SAVE THE DAY.
>> NO.
>> ...NUT.
COME ON.
[ MUSIC FADES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
HAS ANYONE SEEN A SODA MACHINE
AROUND HERE?
>> OH...
>> YOU CAN'T SAY...
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> [ SOBBING LOUDLY ]
AAH! AAH! AAH!
AAH!
>> [ GASPS ]
AAAAH!
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ CHUCKLING ]
UGH!
[ THUD ]
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GASPS ]
>> AAAAAH!
AAAAAH!
>> "FOR GOD SO LOVED THE WORLD,
HE GAVE HIS ONLY BEGOTTEN SON,
THAT WHOEVER BELIEVETH IN HIM
SHALL NOT DIE, BUT HAVE
EVERLASTING LIFE."
OR NOT.
[ SLASH ]
>> [ MOANING ]
>> [ GASPING ]
AAAAH!
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
HAIL MARY, FULL OF GRACE.
OUR LORD IS WITH THEE.
AAAAH.
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> AAAAAH!
AAH!
[ THUD ]
[ GASPING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> [ GASPS ] OH! OH!
OH, GOD!
>> HELP ME. HELP ME.
>> AAH!
OH! OH! OH! OH!
>> UGH.
>> OH! OH! OH! OH!
OH! OH, MY GOD!
>> HELP ME.
>> AAH!
>> HELP.
>> AAH! AAH!
>> [ MOANING ]
AAH!
UGH!
>> AAH!
[ WHIMPERING ]
NO! NO! NO!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
...LET ME IN.
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SOBBING ]
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OH, PLEASE.
[ SOBS ]
OUR FATHER, WHO ART IN HEAVEN
[SOBS] HALLOWED BE THY NAME;
[SOBS] THY KINGDOM COME,
[SOBS] THY WILL BE DONE,
[SOBS] ON EARTH AS IT IS IN
HEAVEN.
[ SOBS ]
GIVE US THIS DAY OUR DAILY
BREAD, AND FORGIVE US OUR
TRESPASSES, AS WE FORGIVE THOSE
WHO TRESPASS AGAINST US.
[ SOBS ]
LEAD US NOT INTO TEMPTATION
[SOBS] BUT DELIVER US FROM EVIL.
[ SOBS ]
THINE IS THE KINGDOM AND THE
POWER AND THE GLORY FOREVER.
[ SOBS ]
>> AMEN.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ SOBS ]
AAAAAH!
AAAAH!
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
>> MY CHILD...
>> OH...MY JESUS.
[ SNIFFLES ]
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
>> YOU CAN BE A BUTT SLAMMER,
TURD BURGLAR...SMOKER,
BALONEY PONY RIDER AND STILL
HAVE THE KINGDOM OF GOD.
YOU COULD BE A PRACTICING
HOMOSEXUAL AND BELIEVE IN THE
LORD ABOVE.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
>> BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
[ SNIFFLES ]
I KNEW ABOUT THIS PLACE, AND I
KNEW WHAT HAPPENED.
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
STILL, I BROUGHT THE KIDS UP
HERE.
[ SNIFFLES ] I'M RESPONSIBLE.
>> NOW, THAT, WE HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH, YOU LITTLE HOMO.
THAT, WE CAN'T FORGIVE.
MNH-MNH.
>> [ SNIFFLES ]
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO, LORD?
>> SAVE...THIS...CAMP.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> GO KICK THE SISTER'S...
AH.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> HOT DOG!
AH.
THERE GOES ANOTHER DISCIPLE.
>> HOT DOG!
I LOVE THE JESUS BUSINESS.
THERE GOES ANOTHER DISCIPLE.
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I LOVE THE JESUS BUSINESS.
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
OH!
[ GASPS ] OH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GASPS ]
AAH! AAH!
AAAAH!
AAH! AAH! AAH!
NO!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GASPS ]
>> WHERE'S DWAYNE?
>> HOLY...
IT'S SISTER MARY CHOPPER!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
YOU SHOULD GET DOWN ON YOUR
KNEES AND START ASKING FOR
FORGIVENESS.
STEALING IS A SIN.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
>> THAT'S ONE BIG...
>> [ CONTINUES LAUGHING ]
>> [ GASPING ]
>> DWAYNE?
HOLD ON, BABY.
YOU TRANNIES DON'T SCARE ME.
>> [ CRYING ]
I'VE BEEN A NAUGHTY GIRL.
[ SOBBING ]
>> YOU'RE LIKE A GIRL!
>> NO!
>> [ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
REVELATION 12:12.
[ LAUGHS ]
"WOE TO THE EARTH AND THE SEA,
FOR THE DEVIL HAS COME TO LIVE
AMONG THEE."
[ LAUGHS ]
[ CRYING ]
UGH!
[ SIGHS ]
"FOR HE IS FULL OF RAGE AND
FURY BECAUSE HIS TIME ON EARTH
IS SHORT!"
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YOU...
CANNOT TELL ME...
WHO I AM!
>> [ Scoffing ] OH.
>> AH.
[ GROWLING ]
>> [ GURGLING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> [ GRUNTING ]
UGH.
OUCH.
>> AAH!
PLEASE, GOD, DO SOMETHING!
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
THE WRATH OF GOD IS UPON THEE.
DEUTERONOMY 7...
SOMETHING.
[ WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> UGH.
>> HYAH, HYAH.
>> [ CHUCKLING EVILLY ]
>> [ GRUNTS ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ GROWLS ]
YOU GOT HELL TO PAY, SISTER.
HYAH!
[ THUD ]
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
HYAH.
>> [ GRUNTING ]
[ GROWLS ]
>> OH, BOY!
>> [ GIGGLING EVILLY ]
>> AAAAH.
AAAH.
[ MUSIC SOFTENS ]
[ HARMONICA PLAYS
"AMAZING GRACE" ]
>> WELL, GUESS YOU ALL LEARNED A
VERY VALUABLE LESSON THIS
WEEKEND.
>> I NEVER DOUBTED YOU FOR A
MINUTE.
>> HOLY...
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S YOU!
>> WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
BELIEVE SO YOU'D STOP ALL
YOUR...
WHY DO YOU GUYS LIKE CAMPING
ANYWAY?
YOU KNOW, BACK IN THE OLD DAYS,
ME AND THE DISCIPLES USED TO GO
CAMPING AROUND JERUSALEM.
TOO MANY SNAKES.
GIVE ME A NICE HOTEL [POPS] AND
ROOM SERVICE.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> GOD BLESS YOU ALL.
"SAINTS GO MARCHING IN."
[ HARMONICA PLAYS "WHEN
THE SAINTS GO MARCHING IN" ]
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
>> WAIT! [ WHIMPERING ]
>> YOUR HAND.
>> J.J.?
DWAYNE?
ARE YOU TAKING THEM WITH YOU?
>> NO. THEY DON'T QUALIFY.
>> WHAT?!
>> COME ON! I'M JUST KIDDING.
LIGHTEN UP.
HEAVEN IS FOR EVERYONE.
>> [ Crying ] OH.
>> EXCEPT YOU.
[ DRUM PLAYS UP-TEMPO
ROCK 'N' ROLL ]
[ THE SMOKING VAGINAS' "WHEN THE
SAINTS GO MARCHING IN" PLAYS ]
>> [ MOUTHING WORDS ]
>> ♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
GO MARCHING IN ♪
♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
GO
MARCHING IN ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE IN THAT NUMBER
♪ WHEN THE SAINTS
GO MARCHING IN ♪
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ OH, WHEN THE MOON TURNS RED
WITH BLOOD ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE IN THAT NUMBER
♪ WHEN THE SAINTS
GO MARCHING IN ♪
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ OH, WHEN THE TRUMPET SOUNDS
ITS CALL FOR YOU ♪
♪ OH, WHEN THE TRUMPET SOUNDS,
♪ LORD, HOW I WANT TO BE HERE
WITH YOU ♪
♪ WITH YOU
♪ OH, OH
♪ SOME SAY THIS WORLD OF
♪ WITH YOU
TROUBLE ♪
♪ SOME SAY THIS WORLD OF
♪ IS THE ONLY ONE WE NEED
TROUBLE ♪
♪ BUT I'M WAITING FOR THAT
♪ IS THE ONLY ONE WE NEED
MORNING ♪
♪ BUT I'M WAITING FOR THAT
♪ WHEN THE NEW WORLD'S
MORNING ♪
REVEALED ♪
♪ WHEN THE NEW WORLD'S
♪ REVEALED
REVEALED ♪
♪ OH, OH
♪ REVEALED
♪ REVEA-EA-LED
[ DISCORDANT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYS ]
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
>> [ LAUGHING ]
[ SIGHS ]
>> FATHER CUMMINGS, ARE YOU
COMING?
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SIGHS ]
...OF A WEEKEND.
[ CHUCKLING ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
...OF A WEEKEND.
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> TAD?
TAD?
I DON'T THINK I'M A VIRGIN
ANYMORE.
BUT I KIND OF LIKED IT.
>> ♪ BUT I'M WAITING FOR THAT
MORNING ♪
♪ WHEN THE NEW WORLD'S
REVEALED ♪
♪ REVEALED
♪ OH, OH
♪ REVEA-EA-LED
♪ REVEALED
[ DISCORDANT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
♪ REVEA-EA-LED
PLAYS ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ OH, WHEN THE RICH
♪ GO OUT AND WORK
♪ OH, WHEN THE RICH GO OUT AND
WORK ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE IN THAT NUMBER
♪ WHEN THE SAINTS
GO MARCHING IN ♪
♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
>> ♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
>> ♪ GO MARCHING IN
GO MARCHING IN ♪
>> ♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
♪ I WANT TO BE IN THAT NUMBER
GO MARCHING IN ♪
♪ WHEN THE SAINTS
♪ I WANT TO BE IN THAT NUMBER
GO MARCHING IN ♪
ALL RIGHT!
[ DRUMS PLAY MARCHING BEAT ]
♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
GO MARCHING IN ♪
♪ OH, WHEN THOSE SAINTS
COME MARCHING IN ♪
♪ THERE'S GONNA BE A...RIOT
♪ OH, WHEN THE SAINTS
COME MARCHING IN ♪
>> [ LAUGHS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> ROCK THIS THING.
>> OH, YEAH!
>> ♪ WHEN THE SAINTS
COME MARCHING IN ♪
♪ WHEN THE SAINTS
GO MARCHING IN ♪