- Sara Lee?
- I'm in here, Mama Wheelis.
I'm goin' out to cut some okrie.
Holler at me when they get here.
It's gonna be real nice,
everybody together again.
It's gonna be livin' hell,
and you know it.
I know it.
Shit, that's Lurlene!
I gotta quit sayin' "shit."
- Lurlene!
- Sara Lee!
Oh, it's so good to see you!
Lurlene, you look so good.
You look younger than me.
Oh, shut up. I do not.
I really appreciate you bringin' Daddy
home from the hospital.
Come on, Tiny Timmy.
Body slam that son of a bitch!
Oh, dear!
Lord, please help him.
He thinks he's watchin'
midget wrestlin' on the TV.
He doesn't even know
who I am, Sara Lee.
All the way down here, he kept
talkin' gibberish about a redhead.
That's Paulena Harlin.
She was that redheaded piece of trash
he had that affair with.
I didn't realize
Daddy was so bad, Sara Lee.
I wish you'd told me sooner.
I didn't think
anything about it at first.
I just thought it was one
of his temporary spells, you know?
I didn't wanna bother no one.
But last week, he started havin'
them progressive strokes.
Dr. Wetzel said
it was the beginnin' to the end.
That's when I called you.
- A week ago.
- I know it, I know it.
But J.D. was in revival, and I just
couldn't leave in the middle of it.
We had two rededications
and three professions of faith.
Well, praise the Lord.
We do, Sara Lee.
I hope you weren't bein' facetious.
I hope I wasn't either,
'cause that sounds like somethin'
I don't wanna be doin'.
I meant I hope
you weren't makin' fun.
No, Lurlene. Gosh!
I been goin' to church pretty regular
myself these days.
Even hit the choir
a couple of times singin' alto.
Get me the shotgun.
I'm gonna kill me a hound.
- What's wrong, Mama Wheelis?
- Just look at me.
That Heinz 57 mutt
of Clarabelle lvy's
tore my knee-highs,
uprooted my tomatoes,
dug a hole the size of Dallas
in my favorite flowerbed.
I am gonna call her
and warn her one more time
to keep that mutt of hers tied up.
Then I'm gonna kill him!
Mama Wheelis,
it's me... Lurlene.
Lord, I ain't seen you
in a coon's age!
Oh, honey!
I'm gonna stop at Bluebell's,
see if Sid'll give me
a discount on a case of beer.
Orville, please, I don't want
you drinkin' while we're here.
Just since when did you start tellin' me
what I could and could not do?!
Marlene, you wait out on the porch.
Woman in a bar ain't proper.
Looky here, Lurlene.
Me and Clarence
are finally gettin' married.
I'm not gonna be
an old maid after all.
Oh, Sara Lee,
I'm so happy for you.
I really do think
he's changed, Lurlene.
I wanted Daddy to give me away,
but in his shape, you know...
It just burns me up to think about
how many times he gave away Evalita.
She's divorced again...
I think it's number six this time.
I don't even know
where she lives anymore.
I had to call Jack
to leave word about Daddy.
Jack is the best husband
Evalita ever had.
Jack says she does call him
every now and again
to check on the girls
since she's lost custody.
I haven't heard from her
since she married that... foreign guy.
I just couldn't bring myself
to go to that weddin'.
Oh, honey, neither could I.
She sent us pictures.
The girl married in white... again.
I don't know
who she thought she's foolin'.
She's about as pure as mud.
Well, I guess we shouldn't judge.
But it is so hard!
- Take a left at the barn.
- Okay.
She had a date
two nights in a row.
She said that Friday night,
she went out with Arthur.
And that Saturday night,
she went out with Ben.
I said, "Arthur and Ben who?"
She said, "Arthritis and Ben Gay."
- How is Mrs. Fenwick?
- Oh, honey, she's dead.
Just eat up with cancer.
- Is that Marlene and Orville?
- No, Mama Wheelis.
Oh, my God,
you're not gonna believe this.
It's Evalita.
Well, spit in the fire
and call the dogs.
I'm a little nervous.
I haven't seen Evalita
in five years.
Count your many blessings.
Name 'em one by one.
Looky here, everybody.
It's Evalita.
And Harmony.
this is my new fiancé...
Harmony Gribowski.
You look real... good.
Harmony, I'm Lurlene.
I'm Evalita's older sister.
Nice to meet you, Lurlene.
Oh, my Lord!
Oh, Mama Wheelis!
Hello, Evalita.
How's one of my grandchildren?
Couldn't be better,
Mama Wheelis.
I'd like you to meet
my new fiancé.
This here is Harmony,
Harmony Gribowski.
I still ain't deaf, Evalita.
Howdy, hippie.
Howdy.
- Hey, Marlene.
- Hey, Clarence.
You lose weight?
- I did.
- I knew it.
- Hey, Orville.
- Hey.
- How's it goin'?
- Fine. Just fine.
Good.
- Asshole.
Shit! Shit!
God, Texas is hot.
It sure is.
Oh, I saw Clarence Hopkins today.
I just had to stop
and say hello.
He hasn't changed a bit.
Me and him are engaged.
That's funny.
He didn't tell me a thing about it.
We picked this out together.
Last of the big-time spenders, huh?
But he's still
the cutest damn thing in Texas.
Yeah, he knows it, too.
And he had the tightest
blue jeans on, and no shirt, girl.
I had a hot flash
just lookin' at that sexy ass of his.
Trash mouth!
I'm gonna check the roast.
Evalita ain't got on nothin'
but her brassiere.
Maybe this'll teach you
not to play that damn radio, Marlene.
- Faster, faster. I need some speed.
- All right!
Dig in. Use your legs.
Take the pressure off your back.
Come on, that's it.
Dig in, girl. Move, move!
- Come on if you're comin'.
- I'm comin'.
- You all right?
- Yes.
If I could run down the street
in a brand-new pair of hose...
Marlene, grab them suitcases.
- Hey, look what the cat drug up.
- Hey, Sara Lee.
- Orville, you look good.
- Hey, Lurlene.
Orville, I'm here. I made it!
- I'll be damned.
- Probably.
Hello, everybody.
I've lost weight.
Nobody gives a rat's ass, Marlene.
Now put this beer in the icebox
and shut up.
You know how I feel
about beer in my icebox.
Hey, Mama Wheelis.
I have lost weight,
in case y'all ain't noticed.
Look behind you
and you'll find it.
I can tell, honey,
and you're pretty as a picture.
- Thank you.
- She's down to a ton.
You behave yourself.
He's just jealous, Mama Wheelis.
He's gained and I've lost
and you know how the heat
affects fat people... they sweat like pigs.
How'd you like it
if I just slapped you silly, huh?
Come on!
Stop that fussin'.
What the hell is that?
I'd like you to meet
my new fiancé.
Nice to meet you, Marlene.
- Oh, likewise, I'm sure.
- Nice to meet you, Orville.
Yeah, right.
Well...
Daddy still alive or what?
He looks pretty bad, don't he?
Have you read the will?
- No, Orville, I haven't.
- Why not?
'Cause it ain't the first thing
that crossed my mind,
like some people I know, Orville.
- You scared me.
- Sorry.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just need to get
some fresh air.
- Shut up!
...don't have Daddy's will.
- Orville, where you goin'?
- Never you mind.
Well, excuse me.
Asshole.
What's Orville
so all fired up about?
He's gone down to Lawyer Pitman's
to look for a copy of the will,
but Lawyer Pitman don't have that will.
- Who does have the will?
- Daddy.
Daddy got it back
from Lawyer Pitman to revise it,
and then he didn't
get back to him
before he took
a turn for the worse.
I think he hid it.
Lurlene, would you please
return thanks?
May we pray?
Dear Lord, we come together
before Thee today
to thank Thee
for Thy bounty and Thy love.
Yes, Lord.
We ask that, as you draw
this family together,
that each one of us will realize
that love conquers all.
- Yes, Lord.
- I love my family, Lord,
and I ask that you will
take greed out of this family
- and replace it with love.
- Oh, Lord... yes, Lord.
Heal our daddy, Lord,
and bless this food
for the nourishment of our bodies,
and our bodies for your service.
Amen.
That was sweet, Lurlene.
- I doubt I'm in it, either.
- In what?
The will.
No, thank you.
I don't eat anything that has a face.
That's not what I've been told.
Here, Harmony.
Double up on those black-eyed peas.
Thank you.
I know for sure that he cut
me and J.D. out at one time.
And who knows
what it says now.
Although I really don't care since
we're financially stable, unlike some.
- Oh, brother.
- What did you say?
Nothin'.
If you have a comment to make,
why don't you just make it out loud?
I just think that Daddy had a right
to do what he did.
I mean, it's a free country,
and you and J.D. did run off
and leave him high and dry
to run the ranch all by himself.
But at least we gave him
five years of hard work.
All you ever gave him
was a lot of grief,
and five or six son-in-laws.
We all promised that we were
gonna get along with each other.
- We all have to try, Sara Lee.
- I'm doin' my part.
Get this. We just cut a record.
- Oh, really?!
- It's actually just a tape.
Well, anyway, a star is born.
It's all because of Harmony.
Lurlene! Mama Wheelis.
Y'all come quick!
Evalita's cut a record.
Lord, I hope I don't
have to go get my garden hose.
You cut a record?
Singin'?
I just went to Hollywood and made
a new movie with Elizabeth Taylor.
I, for one, would love to hear it.
I wouldn't.
Quite frankly, Lurlene,
it probably ain't your kind of music.
It's not that Jesus stuff.
Excuse me, Evalita,
but my musical tastes
are a little more eclectic
than just that "Jesus stuff."
Lurlene sings better
than you do, Evalita.
She used to sing
all them Patsy Cline songs
with Sid Cranford
at the Elks Fraternal Hall.
We've heard this story
all our lives, Mama Wheelis.
Thought maybe you might need
to hear it again.
Well, I don't.
I'm gonna go fix Buford's dinner.
You call me if there's
any more news flashes, hear?
Come on, Lurlene.
I'm gonna go for a little walk.
Get my rice cakes.
- Bye-bye, honey pie.
- Bye-bye, sweet cheeks.
- And he don't mean my face.
- Oh, I'm sure he don't.
Evalita, I don't mean
to get personal,
but just where the hell
did you drag that one up from?
That's a miracle
straight from God, Sara Lee.
- Right after me and Roger busted up...
- Roger?
He was that bronco buster
I lived with for a while
after me and Abdul got divorced.
Oh, you didn't know him.
Anyway, Roger was a nut.
Shoulda been committed
to Big Springs
in a padded cell
if you ask me.
He beat me up.
Threw me outta the trailer house.
I had nothin' to my name
but the clothes on my back
and a buck fifty.
- Told me to get gone or he'd kill me.
- Lord!
So I started hitchhikin'.
- You was hitchhikin'?!
- Sara Lee, I was desperate.
But now I know
it was God's will for my life,
because if Roger
hadn't have kicked me out,
I wouldn't have been hitchhikin',
and I wouldn't have met Harmony,
and Harmony was sent by God.
Evalita, that's the silliest thing
I ever heard.
You could take that theory
from husband one to husband six.
Somehow I don't think it's God's will
that you'd end up with
six husbands before you was 40,
and hooked up with
some hippie named Harmony.
And when did you become
the assistant to Jesus Christ Himself
to know His will for my life?
I have been goin' to church
a little more regularly lately,
and just last week,
Reverend Tuttle himself
preached a real good sermon
on the use and abuse of God's will.
Well, la-ti-da.
Sara Lee's been goin' to church,
so now she's an expert
on the use and abuse
of God's will,
'cause she heard
old fat-ass Revered Tuttle,
who, by the way, had an affair with
our illustrious soloist Mildred Keevner,
preach one of his
boring old sermons.
You wait one minute, missy!
That affair was never proved.
No, I won't wait a minute,
Sara Lee, God damn it.
Every time I come home.
You just hold on, Evalita.
The Lord's name
is sacred in this house.
Please stop.
You're gonna wake up Dad.
That's right.
All of ya just gang up on me.
Some things never change.
We're not ganging up
on you, Evalita.
We just all agree
that the Lord's name
is not to be taken in vain
in this house.
Wake up and smell the coffee,
Mama Wheelis.
This is the 20th century.
The Lord's name is the same
yesterday, today and forever.
Amen!
That affair was never proved.
That's just vicious gossip.
This has nothin' to do
with me sayin' "God damn."
Where is my razor strap?
You think you can
whup me, Mama Wheelis?
- I' m 33 years old.
- No, you're not.
You're 35 years old. I'm 36,
Orville's 38, Lurlene's 40.
That makes you 35.
Okay, so I'm 35.
So I lie, too.
I cuss, I lie, I cheat.
Sometimes I even steal ashtrays
from the motel rooms
where I commit adultery.
But I'll tell y'all somethin'...
I also live,
which is more
than I can say for y'all.
Daddy ain't the only one
dyin' around here.
Correction: Daddy's dyin'.
Y'all are dead.
Good-bye.
I sure have enjoyed
this little family get-together.
Don't go!
- What's wrong?
- My whole family was mean to me.
Honey, don't cry.
- I need a drink, Harmony.
- No, you don't.
We made an agreement.
I don't care. I need a drink
real bad. Just one.
- Let's go to the truck and make love.
- Harmony, I can't.
- Then let's leave.
- I need the money.
- And I need a drink.
- No, you don't.
Let me go.
Who the hell
do you think you are, anyway?
You ain't my daddy, ya know.
Linny Sue, bring me a beer, please.
Linny Sue, we'll watch "Bonanza"
after this.
Buford, I am Lois...
Lois Wheelis, your mother-in-law.
Now, Linny Sue is dead.
Well, we'll watch "Bonanza"
after this, Lois Wheelis.
Oh, Buford.
Bring me another beer, please.
Told ya, Orville, that Lawyer Pitman
didn't have that will.
I've done peed in my chili.
Daddy's mad at me
over Jimbo.
He's cut me clean out.
- Look what he done to you, Lurlene.
- I know.
Imagine your own daddy
cuttin' you out of a will
because the Lord called you
to the ministry.
Lurlene, how is it
that the Lord always calls on you
to do somethin',
'cause He ain't never said shit to me.
If you hadn't put Jimbo
in that home.
Hell, I had to do somethin'.
Marlene spoiled the boy rotten
till I couldn't do nothin' else with him.
He set fire to the back bedroom
smokin' marijuana cigarettes
and sniffin' gasoline.
Daddy wanted to raise
that boy himself.
Like he coulda done any better.
Look what he raised.
- It's a pretty night, isn't it?
- It sure is.
Marlene, are you all right?
I miss my boy, Mama Wheelis.
I just miss my boy so much.
I know, honey. I know.
'Nother drink, please.
Hey, Sid.
Sorry I'm late, Sid.
Somethin' came up.
- Hey.
- What inspired you tonight, anyway?
Need a drinkin' buddy?
You know I do.
We do have customers,
ya know.
I cannot believe you!
You don't give
a flyin' flit about him, do you?
It's just his money.
This is your daddy, Orville...
your very own daddy.
Don't you care
anything about him?
Don't be upset, Sara Lee.
I didn't mean to make you upset.
Heavens to Betsy!
That hippie's playin' "I'll Fly Away."
I'll fly away
I'll fly away, oh, glory
I'll fly away in the mornin'
When I die,
hallelujah, by and by
I'll fly away
Take it, Mrs. Wheelis.
Just a few more weary days and then
I'll fly away
To a land where
joy shall never end
I'll fly away
I'll fly away, oh, glory
When I die,
hallelujah, by and by
I'll fly away
Some glad mornin'
when this life is o'er
I'll fly away
To a home
on God's celestial shore
I'll fly away
I'll fly away, oh, glory
When I die,
hallelujah, by and by
Oh, I'll fly away
I like it the way you kids
sing like that.
Daddy?
Where did Lita go?
But the time has come,
my darlin', to set things right
You'll be harder than my husband
to get along with
Harder than my husband every night
Harder than my husband,
harder than my husband
And I don't want our love affair
to end with a fight
You been like a little angel
how you love me
And I appreciate
the warmth of your embrace
I'll take that.
Paulena.
He's restin' easy.
Sounds like Sid's got himself
a new girl singer.
The Lord's gonna rain His judgment
on that place one of these days.
Mama Wheelis,
if you hate it so much,
why do you come out here
and listen to it?
In the hopes of a cool breeze.
Nothin' else, thank you very much.
- Sis, you wanna dance?
- Take a look at him.
Well, excuse me!
For wantin' a better life
No, Daddy, you can't blame me
Summer sun'll bear on down
and burn you till you're blind
Winter wind cuts like a knife,
too much rain or shine
Daddy, you can't blame me
For wantin' a better life
Get your earplugs out.
Well, I could build me a house
right on down the road
That's far as I'd ever get
Far as I'd ever go
My mama died so young,
lovin' in the rocky ground
Well, Papa, I'll send money home
when I get me a job in town
Daddy, you can't blame me
For movin' away from here,
for wantin' a better life
Wantin' somethin' better than this
Daddy, you can't blame me
You can't blame me
You can't blame me,
you can't blame me
You can't blame me, Daddy
- That was bad.
- And gettin' worse.
We better go, Evalita.
Your father's been askin'
about you.
I think it's time
you deal with that.
Oh, yeah?
I think it's time you minded
your own God damn business.
I guess it is.
Good night, Daddy.
Hurry the hell up, Marlene.
I'm about to bust my bladder
out here.
- I'll be done in a second.
- Come on!
- Morning, Mrs. Wheelis.
- Mornin', Harmony.
Where's Evalita?
I don't know.
What's troublin' you, sonny boy?
My grandmother from Alabama
used to call me that.
Mema Rose.
Evalita didn't come home
last night, did she?
No, ma'am, she didn't.
- Like a cat in heat.
- Good mornin', Harmony.
Good mornin', Mama Wheelis.
- Mornin'.
- Mornin', Marlene.
- Did you sleep well?
- I did.
Thank you very much.
And guess what?!
This is just out of the blue,
but I bet you lost more weight.
You noticed?
One and a quarter more LB's.
Good God, Marlene,
would you learn to strike a match?!
I think I singed my nose hairs!
Damn Herbalean!
It cleanses my system!
Marlene, honey,
why don't you set the table?
Yes, ma'am.
I'll help you.
I'm on Herbalean.
That's how I did it.
I don't know.
I don't think those radical diets
are all that good for you.
I seem to keep the same weight
just by eating healthy.
I don't drink anymore.
All I do now is smoke a little weed.
You smoke marijuana cigarettes?
Not often.
Just every once in a while.
Just one little vice.
I figure with a good diet,
a little wacky tobaccy won't hurt you.
Hey, I want you
to try something.
Ooh, I've always wanted to try
marijuana cigarettes.
No, it's not that.
One day, I was cleanin' out
my boy's room,
and I found this stuff
on the top shelf in the back of his closet.
So I took it down,
rolled it up and smoked it.
I got a little dizzy,
but not much happened.
Then I found a box of catnip.
I thought, "Why does this boy
have catnip... we don't have a cat?"
We have a dog... Bimbo's his name.
Jimbo's my boy, Bimbo's the dog.
Anyway, I found out
that I had smoked catnip.
I coulda killed that boy.
We gotta smoke
the real stuff later.
Try this.
No, thank you, Harmony.
That ain't on my diet.
No, it's, like, 35 calories each.
Okay. Thank you.
Good Lord,
this stuff tastes like Styrofoam.
It's better with
peanut butter and honey.
It'd have to be.
It's like eatin' an ice chest.
Lurlene, it's all yours.
Marlene stunk it up pretty bad,
but I opened up a window.
Fat ass!
- Watch it!
- Sorry, Mama Wheelis.
Looks like at her age,
she'd be hard of hearin', huh?
I heard that.
- Yeah.
- Boy howdy.
- I'm as hungry as a bear.
- And mean as a snake.
Don't start with me, woman,
'cause I ain't in the mood.
You never are.
I lost another pound and a quarter
this mornin', Orville.
Let's all stand up
and do the jig.
- Jealous?!
- Don't talk back to me, woman.
I'll slap the thunder outta you!
- Marlene, help me in the kitchen.
- She'll be right there.
Now listen, woman.
I don't know
what's gotten into you lately,
but I don't want you ever
to talk to me like that again.
You take your hands off me
right this second.
I'm takin' Phil Donahue's advice,
and I'm gonna stand up
for my rights as an equal partner
in this marriage.
Orville, let go of me.
You're hurtin' me.
Let go of me now!
- Marlene, help me scramble the eggs.
- I'm comin', Mama Wheelis.
I'm warnin' you, Orville.
I'm gettin' real tired.
Crazy woman.
Oh, shit.
Morning, Orville.
Did you sleep well?
What?
Yeah. Fine. Just fine.
Mama Wheelis,
don't cook me no breakfast.
Morning.
I have to go down to the bank
and get into Daddy's safe deposit box
and see if there's
a copy of that will
before Orville has a conniption fit.
Honey, you gotta eat breakfast.
It's the most important meal
of the day.
I heard that
on the "Hollywood Squares."
Who was it said that?
Oh, Lord!
So, Orville...
What?
What kind of work do you do?
I work for the city.
He dumps trash.
Would you shut the hell up,
Marlene?!
Jealous.
So you're a sanitation engineer,
so to speak.
- You gettin' smart with me, boy?
- Not at all.
For your information,
it's a damn important job.
This country'd be
a hell of a mess if it wasn't for us.
On top of that, you can find
some good stuff that you can keep.
It's amazing what people throw out.
I wasn't making fun of you.
That's what we call 'em
in California... sanitation engineers.
Really? Sanitation engineers?
Yeah.
I kinda like the sound of that.
- Sanitation engineer, huh?
- Right.
Marlene, where's my coffee?
Sanitation engineer.
Ooh, you're gorgeous.
I am outta here.
- Mornin', everyone.
- Mornin', Lurlene.
Well, I hope I hadn't
cooked this breakfast...
everybody just flits off
without a bite.
You off to the bank,
Marlene on that crazy diet,
Evalita out alley-cattin',
the hippie friend
tankin' up on rice patties.
- Are you hungry, Lurlene?
- Yes, ma'am.
What do you mean,
Evalita's been out alley-cattin' around?
She didn't come home last night.
That's what Harmony said.
Never a dull moment.
You'd think after five husbands
and no tellin' how many in between,
that girl woulda had enough by now.
Well, she is an adult, so I guess
it doesn't concern us, does it?
Besides, doesn't it say in the Bible,
"Judge not lest ye be judged"?
Right. I'm gonna go fix Daddy
his breakfast.
Thank you, Lurlene.
Boy, this is good.
Breakfast is the most important
meal of the day.
Who was that that said that
on the "Hollywood Squares"?
- Oh, shit! Damn it!
- Watch it.
Lurlene, Harmony
was sittin' right out there.
He heard every word
you said about Evalita.
Oh, I had no idea!
Damn hippie queer...
serves him right.
I think he's a nice person,
and we all oughta try
to treat him like family.
Family?
Woman, are you outta your mind?
He's a damn hippie.
Probably a bisexual homo.
Well, he looks like
he's from outer space.
I think he's nice.
Bullshit. He's a damn
hippie pinko Commie...
I've just about
had enough of you.
- Why?
- Don't you talk back to me!
I'm gettin' sick and tired
of that mouth of yours.
You may be big,
but you ain't too big for me
to take my razor strap to you.
What the hell
are you laughin' at?
Hush up... all of ya!
There's a sick man in this house.
He may be dyin'.
You don't give a plug nickel.
So you all just hush up.
You're gettin' on my nerves.
Get to the table, all of ya.
You're gonna eat this breakfast
whether you want it or not.
I'm just gonna take Daddy his tray,
give him his medicine,
and I'll be right back
to eat my breakfast.
Thank you, Lurlene.
Lord, she's so sweet.
I believe if she hadn't been
a preacher's wife,
she'd have made a good nurse.
So much like Linny Sue.
Sara Lee, that's Clarence.
You go out there and tell him
horn honkin' is for callin' the cows.
Oh, my Lord!
Evalita's getting out of
his pickup... staggerin' drunk.
What?!
Time for breakfast.
Daddy?
Daddy!
Dr. Kaufman, report to ICU.
Dr. Kaufman, ICU, please.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hello, pumpkin.
I wanna talk to all my kids.
I made a mistake.
I can't find my will.
He cut me out.
I just know
I've done peed in my chili.
Lita. Where's Lita?
I'm here, Daddy.
I'm here.
- I love you, Evalita.
- Well, I love you, Daddy.
- Sara Lee, where's Sara Lee?
- I'm here, Daddy.
I love you, Sara Lee.
Oh, Daddy, I love you, too.
Where's sister?
Yes, Daddy?
- I love you, sister.
- I love you so much, Daddy.
Orville.
- Orville...
- Daddy...
can you remember
where you put your will?
Look everywhere, Orville.
It could be anywhere.
I don't see no use.
He's mad at me.
I have done peed in my chili.
Will you shut the hell up
about peein' in your chili?!
It turns my stomach.
- Let me help you.
- Okay.
Sure you don't want to go with us?
We're just goin' for a little drive.
Oh, no, thank you.
I gotta get my beauty sleep.
It oughta take any day now.
- Very funny. Get in the car.
- All right, then.
Clean this up.
Mama Wheelis is back.
What in the cat hair
is goin' on here?!
- Nothin', Mama Wheelis.
- Hush up!
Now answer me.
What in the cat hair is goin' on?
Nothin', Mama Wheelis.
You broke
one of Linny Sue's cups.
You oughta be ashamed
of yourself.
- Sorry, Mama Wheelis.
- I'm sorry, too, Mama Wheelis,
but Orville broke that cup.
Orville pinched me.
You're looking for Daddy's will.
To get Daddy's affairs in order.
To get Daddy's affairs
in order, Mama Wheelis.
I don't have a prayer anyway,
'cause I done peed in my chili.
If you say that one more time...
What gives you two monkeys the right
to get Buford's affairs in order?
- We're his children.
- We're his children, Mama Wheelis.
Polly parrot.
Why don't you just keep quiet
if you ain't got
nothin' of your own to say?
I swear, if you two had a brain
between you, you'd be dangerous.
I want you to clean up this mess.
I don't want to see
a thing out of place.
I want you to glue
Linny Sue's cup back together.
Yes, Mama Wheelis.
What the hell
are you all laughin' at?
- Oh, nothin'.
- Oh, nothin' at all.
Whatever it was,
I must've missed it.
What's so funny?
Are y'all laughin' at us?
You two just look like you were kids
gettin' scolded, that's all.
It reminded me of that summer
we went to stay with Mama Wheelis,
and Orville dropped
his little red ball
down the hole of the outhouse.
- I don't think that's very funny.
- I don't, either.
Remember? He paid Evalita a nickel
if she'd go down there and get it.
And she got stuck, so Orville,
you had to go dig her out!
I know the story.
I was there.
Yeah, I was there too,
and I didn't think it was real funny.
I never vomited so hard in my life.
There I was with the hose,
hosin' you down, both of you,
both of you buck naked
and covered with doo-doo
from head to toe.
Oh, my sides!
My sides are achin'!
I used to love to spend the summers
at Mama Wheelis'.
Oh, God, I hated those summers.
I was always the littlest, and y'all
would never let me play with you.
You know why we didn't
let you play with us, don't you, Evalita?
It was 'cause you was
a pain in the ass!
- Watch your mouth, Orville!
- They even say "ass" in the Bible.
You ain't in the Bible.
You're in Lowake.
Orville's right.
You were a pain in the ass.
You were a spoiled little brat.
Daddy just spoiled you rotten.
What are you gettin'
so fired up about?
That was when we was kids.
"Was," Evalita.
We ain't kids no more.
Don't you agree with me?
Ain't it time Evalita just grew up?
What are you talkin' about, girl?
You know damn well
what I'm talkin' about, girl.
Lord, I wish I had me
a roast to tend to. I don't.
You been rode hard, missy,
and many, many times,
and it's startin' to catch up with you.
Just look at that face.
You chisel off that makeup,
and you're lookin' at
nine miles of bad Texas road.
That's enough, Sara Lee.
- You're not Mama, Lurlene.
- I didn't say I was.
Just who the hell is it
you think you are anyway?
You think you can waltz in here
every five or ten years,
and take over the place
and boss everyone else around, huh?
No. l...
You're not Mama, Lurlene,
and don't you ever try to be.
I don't need to listen to this shit.
Oh, yes, you do,
'cause I'm not done with you yet.
The only thing you got
goin' for you, missy,
is that you're willin'.
You're willin' to bed flop
with anything that moves,
and I hate you for it.
That's enough, Sara Lee.
- More than enough.
- Shut up, Orville.
- You're vicious, Sara Lee.
- Yeah, well, I'm honest.
Like hell you are.
I got a question for you,
and I want an answer.
Did you spend the night
with Clarence last night?
- Oh, please!
- Shut up, Lurlene!
This is gettin' good.
Go ahead, Evalita, answer her.
Shut up, Orville!
Did you or did you not
spend the night
with my fiancé Clarence Hopkins
last night?
Well, you know Clarence,
and you know me.
So I guess you got your answer.
Now, if y'all will excuse me,
I'm goin' down to Bluebell's
to get drunk.
Might even get lucky again...
who knows?
You might've pulled the wool
over everybody else's eyes, girl,
but I been around this town, and I know
the truth about you and Clarence.
You little bitch!
- I'm gonna snatch you baldheaded.
- Yeah, right.
Where you goin', girl?
I thought we were all
gonna try to get along.
Wait a dad-burn minute.
That's my car!
I am gonna kick your ass
all the way to Odessa.
Just leave me alone, Lurlene!
Sara Lee, please!
Come on, it's my car!
Damn crazy women.
You bitch!
She better not put a scratch
on my car.
Orville, go to the pantry
and get the flashlight.
There's somethin' in the stonehouse
I want you to help me with.
Is it heavy?
Move that fat bohunkus of yours
now before I take my switch to ya.
- My back's been flarin' up.
- Get!
I'm hungry for love
Like a hobo for food
Like a devil hunts for bad
Like an angel looks for good
I've been oh, so lonesome
Your letters ain't enough
My... hey, just ignore her.
I need to talk to you.
Sure, baby.
I tried so many times... tears, dear
Sweetheart
Here you go.
- I can do it myself.
- Suit yourself.
How could you do it, Clarence?
How could you do this to me?
Do what, baby?
Just don't call me that, okay?
I don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Never mind.
You don't owe me any explanations.
Clarence, I need a big favor,
for old times' sake, okay?
Okay.
What I need...
I need...
Well, I told my whole family
that me and you was gettin' married.
I even bought
a fake engagement ring.
Ain't that funny?
And they bought it, too...
hook, line and sinker.
And then this thing happened
with you and Evalita.
Honey, nothin' happened
with me and Evalita.
Oh, Clarence,
don't play dumb with me, okay?
I just don't wanna eat crow,
especially not served by her.
Just don't sleep with her
anymore, okay?
I mean, tell her she's too old
or she wasn't no good or something.
Sara Lee, I never slept with her
in the first place.
Clarence, that is two stories
I've heard now...
one from you
and one from that Jezebel...
and I sure as hell ain't gonna
place bets on who's lyin'
and who's tellin' the truth.
Lord!
Oh, shit, that's Lurlene!
Hey, sweet thing.
Hey, over here, honey.
Just don't, okay?
Don't worry, baby.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Oh, God, Clarence,
I used to believe that.
I really did.
But I don't anymore.
I gotta go.
Look, we tried awfully hard,
but I'm not gonna try anymore.
And I'd appreciate it
if you didn't, either.
I still love you, Sara Lee.
I still love you, too, Clarence.
So, my sister Vanitta and me
made these dresses.
Hers was pink
and mine was lime green.
All right.
I don't think anybody's home.
- Hello, everybody. We're back!
- Cars are all gone.
You don't suppose Buford died?
- Hello. Turnover-Wheelis residence.
- Why don't you just say hello?
Shut up!
Damn. That was some good shit.
This is Marlene Turnover.
I got a bad case of el munchos.
Me, too.
Fine, Maybelline, just fine.
Maybelline, are you still fat?
Yeah, well, I lost weight.
"Why don't you look behind you
and you'll find it."
I'm sorry, Maybelline.
Somebody's just makin' me laugh.
It's Orville.
Yeah, you know
what a cutup he is.
Yeah.
Shut up, Orville.
The number you have reached
is out of service at this time.
Please check the number
and try again.
This is a recording.
Damn it, I said it was out of order!
Damn, these rice things
ain't gonna cut it.
I'm hungry.
Damn, it's dark in here.
It's in here somewhere.
Could be a rattlesnake's nest in here.
Orville was datin'
ugly old Wilma Burns.
She could bite a hog
through a picket fence.
That's ugly.
He wouldn't even give me
the time of day...
...even though he was
as big as an old barn, too.
Don't ask me why, Harmony,
but I had the biggest crush on him then.
Damn, the pie is good.
So the band starts playin'
Chubby Checker's "The Twist,"
and you should've seen
old Orville.
Do you want a sandwich
of this leftover pot roast?
That'd be weird.
So Orville starts twistin'
and shoutin' and shoutin' and twistin'.
He twisted so hard,
he split the seat
right out of his suit pants.
He was so caught up in The Twist,
he didn't even notice it.
Vanitta saw it first.
When she pointed to Orville,
I about hit the floor...
that big old butt of his
just hangin' out of them suit pants.
He had a hole in his underwear.
I laughed so hard
that I wet my pants.
You didn't.
I sure as hell did.
We had to leave the prom...
didn't get to dance one dance.
You didn't?
Vanitta was so mad at me...
she was drivin'.
God, it was a sight.
That big old hole in his underwear...
you could see his crack.
Marlene, you are a funny woman.
I never smoked
marijuana cigarettes before.
It was a first for me.
And a pretty woman.
They make me talk too much,
though.
They make me horny.
Oh, my stars.
I don't think
you oughta be doin' that.
- Funny and pretty, huh?
- Centered.
- Oh, goodness, and centered?
- And fun.
I can't remember
when I've had so much fun.
Harmony, I don't think you oughta do
this anymore, 'cause I'm gettin' a little...
- Horny?
- Yeah.
No! Confused.
Harmony, I never had anybody
say them kind of things to me before.
Stop, Harmony. We can't do this.
Somebody's gonna catch us.
We can't...
Marlene, I think
I'm falling in love with you.
What?! That's impossible.
It's them marijuana cigarettes.
I don't know what I'm doin'.
You can't.
I got a fat, mean husband
and a kid in reform school.
I know.
Harmony, don't do that now. Stop.
- Run away with me, Marlene.
- I can't. Now you stop it.
- I can't.
- Harmony, stop it. This ain't right.
- It ain't right?
- No, it ain't right,
and Harmony, it ain't moral.
Somehow, I don't think
it's very right or very moral
for you to be miserable
with that lousy son of a bitch
- who treats you like shit.
- We had some good years.
- You're unhappy, Marlene.
- What are you talkin' about? I'm happy.
With me, tonight.
You've only been happy once
since you got here.
That was with me.
Stop it. Stop sayin' them things.
Why? 'Cause they're true?
No, they ain't true.
What about Evalita?
What about her, Marlene?
Evalita doesn't love me.
Evalita doesn't know
what love is.
I want a real woman,
an honest woman, a sincere woman,
a woman capable of giving
and being loved.
And that woman
is right in front of me.
Oh, Harmony, the way you talk.
That's it.
Marlene, come here, pronto.
Great pie. I wish I could bake
like Mama Wheelis.
Well, well.
Well, what do we have here?
A hippie and a hippo.
We was hungry,
so we fixed a little snack.
Little, my ass.
What happened to "get lean
with Herbalean," Marlene?
- Great pie.
- Thank you, Harmony.
- I can have one meal a day, Orville.
- One meal, my ass.
Watch it!
That's enough food
to feed an army.
Harmony was eatin', too.
Yeah?
Great pie.
- You're mean, Orville.
- I ain't mean.
Puttin' my only boy
in reform school
and always makin' fun of me...
you are too mean.
I ain't mean.
I'm just seein'
what's goin' on, that's all.
And you leave Jimbo out of this.
I knew this wouldn't last.
You're gonna blow up
bigger than Lulu on "Hee-Haw,"
and once you start,
you can't stop, and you know it.
Please shut up.
Just leave me alone.
I can hear them hens
down at the beauty shop...
"Oh, honey, look at Marlene.
Lost all that weight,
and now, she's bigger than Dallas."
- I can't wait.
- Oh, God, shut up!
You know, Orville, you never have
a kind word to say to me...
not one kind word.
But you're gonna be sorry one day,
and it's gonna be too late.
Where the hell you think
you're goin'?
I'm goin' out.
Orville, that was mean...
just real mean.
Don't you tell me
how to talk to my own damn wife.
I'm a grown man, Mama Wheelis.
Let go of me!
I can manage very well
myself, thank you.
Fine, but if you throw up
on my leather seats,
you'll clean every bit of it up.
Hey, Lurlene, you know,
there's somethin' I've been wantin'
to tell you for the longest time.
You sing just like Mildred Keevner.
Livin' on the dark side of life
You don't know what's wrong
and what's right
'Cause you're livin' on
the dark side of life
- Marlene?
- What?
What in the hell
are you doin' out here?
Nothin'.
Are you cryin'?
What's wrong with you now?
Nothin'. I'm depressed.
I got just the thing.
You know what I do
when I get depressed?
Well, I sing Christmas carols...
because Christmas makes me happy.
Jingle all the way
- Let me help you with that.
- Oh, yeah.
Just put it
on that table over there.
I been down on my back lately.
So you think Daddy's will
is in that box?
Mama Wheelis said it was.
I'm back.
Thank God you are all right.
I have been worried sick about you.
Oh, I'm fine.
What are you doin'
with Daddy's strongbox?
Mama Wheelis
showed me where it was.
She said the will's in it,
but we can't find the key.
Mama Wheelis, why didn't you
say something to me about this?
It had slipped my mind.
Old people tend to forget.
- Dashing through the snow
- What in the world?!
- In a one-horse open sleigh
- What now?
O'er the fields we go,
laughing all the way
Bells on bobtails ring,
making spirits bright
What fun it is to laugh and sing
a sleighing song tonight
Oh, jingle...
We're drunk.
- No shit!
- Watch it.
I ain't drunk.
I'm high on marijuana cigarettes.
Oh, my Lord!
You are lucky
you didn't get arrested.
But I'll get drunk, too.
No wonder our boy's
in reform school.
I oughta beat
the livin' shit outta you.
I tell you what you oughta do.
You oughta cram this
where the sun don't shine.
You put him there, Orville,
that's why he's there.
You just better watch it,
'cause I'm real tired of you.
There ain't no reasonin'
with a dope addict.
Give it to me.
I wanna give it to you,
all right.
Stop it now!
Here. I just wanted to see
how fast an asshole could move.
You bore the shit outta me, Orville.
I'm washin' my hands
of this whole family.
I'm gonna get drunk now.
You don't need them beers.
Harmony, my very good friend,
would you like a beer?
Excuse me.
I didn't mean to do that.
Well, now...
Ain't this excitin'?
Sittin' around
listenin' to people burp,
watchin' a fool
tryin' to open a strongbox.
Maybe tonight, we can go downtown
and watch fireflies spin around
a streetlamp for entertainment.
No, Evalita. I'm sure you can
sniff out a honky-tonk or two,
if you just put your mind to it.
Be careful, Orville.
- Is the will in this box?
- That's what Mama Wheelis said.
I can open that box.
What?
He's sayin' he can open
Buford's strongbox.
I'll have it open in a second
with this crowbar.
Here, Harmony, open it.
I don't need that.
I need a hairpin.
You havin' a little trouble
there, Harmony?
Not at all.
Oh! That hippie's a crook.
I was, Mama Wheelis.
I did some time, too,
- for burglary.
- Oh, dear.
Lurlene, come help me
hide my jewelry.
And grab the cookie jar.
You don't have to hide your jewelry.
Harmony, I didn't know
you'd been in the pen.
Does that upset you?
What the hell.
Let's just let bygone be bygones...
Yeah, it does.
Evalita, that third husband of yours...
- Dave, Dale, Darrell...
- Darrell.
whatever the hell his name was...
went to the pen up in Huntsville
for writin' hot checks.
- I divorced him, didn't I?
- What the hell do you care?
Maybe Mama Wheelis is right.
I guess I just pick losers.
Excuse me.
Harmony, I'm sorry. I didn't...
I been drinkin'. I'm not myself!
Shit! I shouldn't have said that.
He's been good to me.
You treated him like dirt.
Y'all come around here.
Let's get this show on the road.
Mama Wheelis, he's gone.
I like that boy,
but that diamond brooch
Daddy Wheelis gave me
is worth a fortune.
I hated that old goat,
but I loved that brooch.
He wouldn't have stole
your brooch, Mama Wheelis.
Oh, look. My baby shoes, bronzed.
He kept my second-grade
report card.
Look here. It's an arrowhead
I found and gave to Daddy
on Father's Day
when I was real little.
Daddy's real sentimental, ain't he?
This is that news clippin'
about Linny Sue when she died.
Can we take a shortcut
down Memory Lane
and find the God damn will?
I was ready to tear up, Evalita.
Thanks for ruinin' my moment.
Well, here it is.
I'm so nervous,
I can hardly stand it.
Give me it.
Evalita, this ain't
the time for this.
Okay, okay, it says,
Mama Wheelis and Sara Lee
get the house and...
I can't believe this.
It says Daddy's worth
over $600,000!
Oh, you read it, Sara Lee.
Out loud.
Y'all millionaires yet?
Come on, Sara Lee,
just read it.
He said he made a mistake,
Lurlene.
I'm not in it, am I?
What about me?
I have done peed in my chili.
It's all right. I never expected
anything anyway.
Well, I did.
There goes the motorboat
you wanted.
What's so funny, Marlene?
He's divided everything among
Evalita and Sara Lee...
...and he's crossed out Orville's name,
and written in Jimbo Turnover.
He left my part
to that little sissy?!
That means you, me and Jimbo
get $200,000 each.
Now, he didn't leave me out.
It says right here in number five:
"I leave my daughter Lurlene Sue
Turnover Rogers one dollar."
Anybody want a loan?
That means you'll get a dollar, too,
Orville, even though it don't say it,
'cause I believe it's the law.
A buck?
- This is just awful.
- One measly buck.
I'm just sick over it.
- I have an idea.
Since Evalita feels so awful
about this,
why don't she and Sara Lee
divide their part
- with Orville and Lurlene?
- It ain't that awful.
I'm willin' to give
some of mine away.
I got expenses with my record and all.
I just don't think I can afford it.
I been countin' on this.
Buford oughtn't have
left you a dime.
I tried my best
to talk him out of it.
You shut up, Mama Wheelis!
Don't you ever tell her
to shut up again,
or you'll be sprawled out on that floor
not knowin' what hit you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mama Wheelis.
Well, looky what
the cat drug up.
- My daddy left me a bundle.
- Did he die?
No, not yet, but when he does,
we can make a whole album,
and you can produce it.
It's gonna be wonderful, baby.
I'm such a lucky woman.
I got you and I got my talent,
and I got all that money.
Baby, all you got is the money.
I dumped your things
out on the lawn.
I'm goin' back to California.
Here's your demo tape.
I'm sorry I called you a loser,
but I was drunk.
I'm sober now.
I'm goin' with you, Harmony.
You what?
You what?!
He asked me to go with him,
so I'm goin'.
You're right, Harmony.
All I have is a fat, mean husband,
and a very rich kid
in reform school. I'm goin'.
- I've had just about enough lip.
- I'm sorry!
I'm gonna teach you a lesson
once and for all!
The only way you're goin'
is over my dead body.
You have to sleep sometime.
Let her go now!
Who gives a shit anyway?
It was nice meetin' you, Harmony.
Now, you keep on singin'.
- You've got a nice singin' voice.
- Thank you.
- And be good to her.
- I will.
Bye, Lurlene.
Thanks for always bein'
so nice to me.
I'll be prayin' for you, Marlene.
Good-bye, Mama Wheelis.
I love you.
You be sure to write.
Box 95, Lowake, Texas, 76768.
Bye, Sara.
You take real good care
of yourself, okay?
I hope you and Clarence
get back together.
I hope you know what you're doin'.
This time, I think I do.
Bye.
- I'm sorry, Evalita.
- Shut up.
Just get outta here.
Trash.
I guess that's us.
I ain't goin' to the funeral.
If all he left me
was one measly buck,
then I ain't goin' to his funeral.
- Orville, please!
- I ain't goin'.
- You've got to go. It won't look right.
- I don't gotta do nothin'!
I already said I was gonna
split my part with you and Lurlene.
Then I'll go to your funeral.
I ain't goin' to his.
You gotta go
to your own daddy's funeral.
Marlene used to tie my tie.
I can't even tie my own damn tie.
- I never meant to hurt her.
- I know.
It's all right, Orville.
I tied it. It looks real good.
We love you, Orville.
Come on, now.
We got to practice this song.
I'm ready.
- Oh, dear!
- Oh, my Lord!
Evalita, we have to be
at Daddy's funeral in ten minutes.
- I'm ready.
- You can't go lookin' like that.
The hell I can't.
I can go any way I damn well please.
Shows about as much respect
as that trashy mouth of yours.
I don't need to live my life
by the standards of Lowake, Texas.
You don't live your life
by any standards.
- I've had just about enough.
- It's about time.
If I'm performin',
I'm wearin' my stage clothes.
Evalita, this is the Baptist church,
not the Grand Ole Opry.
Minnie Pearl.
She's the one that said breakfast
is the most important meal of the day
on the "Hollywood Squares."
I ain't goin'.
I just now decided for sure.
Orville, we need your voice.
Buford wanted you to sing...
all of you... like you used to.
We're goin' to sing his favorite,
"Precious Memories,"
just like when we were all kids.
It was his last request.
I'm singin' a solo.
I ain't singin' with y'all.
We're all singin' together.
The service is planned, Evalita.
You can count me out.
I don't sing with amateurs.
You oughta be ashamed
of yourself...
goin' to your own daddy's funeral
dressed like that.
Well, I ain't.
She's trash... pure D white trash.
Quite frankly, I'd be embarrassed
to be seen with you lookin' like that.
God!
It's...
I don't have anything else.
This is all I got.
Leave me alone!
I feel just awful.
Honey, I'd have been glad
to lend her a shawl or an apron.
She ran upstairs
and slammed the door.
Why is it every time she's wrong,
we feel sorry?
I don't know.
We gotta practice this song.
All right, Mama Wheelis,
let's practice this song.
Are you going to help us?
Hell, no.
I guess then that Sara Lee,
Lurlene and me
will just have to sing a trio.
I'll sing alto.
I'll sing soprano.
I'll sing whatever
comes outta my mouth.
Precious memories,
unseen angels
Sent from somewhere to my soul
How they linger ever near me
How the sacred past unfolds
Precious memories,
how they linger
How they ever flood my soul
In the stillness of the midnight
Precious sacred scenes unfold
They unfold
Precious father, loving mother
Fly across the lonely years
Lonely years
And old home scenes
of my childhood
In fond memory appear
They appear
Precious memories,
how they linger
How they ever flood my soul
In the stillness of the midnight
Echoes from the past I hear
I hear
Old time singin',
gladness ringin'
From that lovely land somewhere
Land somewhere
Precious memories,
how they linger
How they ever flood my soul
In the stillness of the midnight...