[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Upbeat music plays ]
>> ♪ Feels so good this
morning ♪
♪ I want to leap before I look
around ♪
♪ I know that I'm falling
♪ I think it's what this life's
about ♪
♪ what you say is infatuation
♪ call it passion
♪ no sin, no crime
♪ in fact, I'm truly grateful
♪ promise of love seems so
alive ♪
♪ let's see
♪ take it outside
and kick the wheels ♪
♪ I'm in
♪ for keeps
♪ I just don't fall this
easily ♪
♪ just don't fall this easily
♪ don't fall so hard
for everyone I meet ♪
♪ you say you're my teacher
♪ it must be time
for my next lesson ♪
♪ I've been trying to reach
you ♪
♪ you want to buy in to my
obsession ♪
♪ let's see
♪ take it outside
and kick the wheels ♪
♪ I'm in
♪ for keeps
♪ I just don't fall this
easily ♪
♪ just don't fall this easily
♪ don't fall so hard
for everyone I meet ♪
♪ I meet
♪ I'm so in love
♪ being in love
♪ I'm old enough
♪ to know I'll be just fine
♪ you called it off
♪ don't have my life over
♪ give myself to walk a bit
♪ I just last forever
♪ I know there's no way
to be free ♪
♪ let's see
♪ take it outside
and kick the wheels ♪
♪ I'm in
♪ for keeps
♪ I just don't fall this
easily ♪
♪ just don't fall this easily
♪ don't fall so hard
for everyone I meet ♪
>> all righty.
For everyone I meet ♪
Two matzo balls just like you
>> all righty.
like it.
Two matzo balls just like you
>> Always taking care of me.
Like it.
You.
>> Always taking care of me.
>> Hey, anything for my most
you.
beautiful customer, huh?
>> Hey, anything for my most
[ tab clicking ]
Beautiful customer, huh?
>> I left you a nice tip today.
[ Tab clicking ]
>> Oh, Leo, you don't have to do
>> I left you a nice tip today.
that.
>> Oh, Leo, you don't have to do
Thank you.
That.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
>> My pleasure.
Thank you so much.
>> See you later, buddy.
>> My pleasure.
>> Thank you.
>> See you later, buddy.
Hold on one second.
>> Thank you.
>> Uh...
Hold on one second.
>> Excuse me. One sec.
>> Uh...
You know, aluminum is not good
>> excuse me. One sec.
for you.
You know, aluminum is not good
>> Waiter?
For you.
Hey, excuse me, buddy.
>> Waiter?
>> Is there something wrong with
hey, excuse me, buddy.
my fork?
>> Is there something wrong with
>> No, just your stock choice's
my fork?
future.
>> No, just your stock choice's
>> Oh. Well, your future
future.
involves topping off my coffee,
>> oh. Well, your future
okay?
Involves topping off my coffee,
[ laughter ]
Okay?
>> [ chuckles ]
[ Laughter ]
Aluminum's stable.
>> [ Chuckles ]
There's just no growth potential
aluminum's stable.
in it.
There's just no growth potential
>> Wait, wait! Hold on a second.
In it.
Hold on, hold on.
>> Wait, wait! Hold on a second.
Back it up.
Hold on, hold on.
>> Unbelievable.
Back it up.
>> That is exactly what my
>> unbelievable.
consultant said last night.
>> That is exactly what my
>> And I bet he charged you more
consultant said last night.
than the $6.95 lunch special for
>> and I bet he charged you more
that.
Than the $6.95 lunch special for
>> Yeah, he did.
That.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, he did.
So, say you were her.
>> Okay.
What would you bet on?
So, say you were her.
>> I would go with...
What would you bet on?
That one.
>> I would go with...
>> [ chuckles ]
That one.
You're kidding, right?
>> [ Chuckles ]
That's nickel stuff.
You're kidding, right?
>> Simitek's about to shake
that's nickel stuff.
hands with them next week.
>> Simitek's about to shake
That means, by Friday, those
hands with them next week.
nickels are gonna be worth
that means, by Friday, those
millions.
Nickels are gonna be worth
>> Can you send a waiter over?
Millions.
>> Wow!
>> Can you send a waiter over?
That's impressive.
>> Wow!
>> You ain't seen nothing yet.
That's impressive.
>> Mike, table 57 is yours.
>> You ain't seen nothing yet.
They need something. Go.
>> Mike, table 57 is yours.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
They need something. Go.
Hold on a second.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
Um, so, um...
Hold on a second.
What are you doing later
um, so, um...
tonight?
What are you doing later
Maybe you want to show me
tonight?
something I haven't seen yet.
Maybe you want to show me
>> Wow! Ha!
Something I haven't seen yet.
Okay.
>> Wow! Ha!
Um, I think I will be at home...
Okay.
With my girlfriend...
Um, I think I will be at home...
>> Oh.
With my girlfriend...
>> ...My very jealous, very --
>> oh.
>> hey, waiter dude.
>> ...My very jealous, very --
>> Yeah, casanova.
>> Hey, waiter dude.
>> It's "mike"!
>> Yeah, casanova.
>> Mike.
>> It's "mike"!
>> Mike Christian, and he's very
>> Mike.
religious.
>> Mike Christian, and he's very
>> Yeah, well, I'd pray to that.
Religious.
[ laughter ]
>> Yeah, well, I'd pray to that.
>> And very busy, okay?
[ Laughter ]
Still waiterless.
>> And very busy, okay?
>> Going, going, going.
Still waiterless.
>> Wait, Mike.
>> Going, going, going.
>> This is ridiculous.
>> Wait, Mike.
Unreal.
>> This is ridiculous.
>> No, no, no.
Unreal.
>> Sir, I apologize.
>> No, no, no.
>> No, I'm sorry.
>> I don't want your apology.
We have a business meeting.
>> He's just a trainee, please.
>> I'll say he's a trainee.
>> Please, let me take your
order. Gentlemen --
>> please, let me take your
>> a trainee, really.
Order. Gentlemen --
Wow.
>> A trainee, really.
[ coughs ]
Wow.
You know what?
[ Coughs ]
I don't feel so good.
You know what?
I think I got to go.
I don't feel so good.
>> If you dare take that tie
I think I got to go.
off, you're fired, okay?
>> If you dare take that tie
Keep it on and clean the table!
Off, you're fired, okay?
>> What seems to be the problem?
Keep it on and clean the table!
>> He wants to get fired,
>> what seems to be the problem?
Mr. lipnick.
>> He wants to get fired,
He's already chased out four of
Mr. lipnick.
our regular customers.
He's already chased out four of
>> I know -- four coffee-only
our regular customers.
customers.
>> I know -- four coffee-only
Those people have been hogging
customers.
that table every day now for a
those people have been hogging
week.
That table every day now for a
I wondered who had the balls to
week.
throw them out.
I wondered who had the balls to
Good business sense, Michael.
Throw them out.
You're my man.
Good business sense, Michael.
>> Thank you.
You're my man.
>> Come here. Let's talk.
>> Thank you.
>> Michael, my granddaughter
>> come here. Let's talk.
delilah is at a conference at
>> Michael, my granddaughter
university hall.
Delilah is at a conference at
Do you think you could pick her
university hall.
up for us?
Do you think you could pick her
>> Absolutely.
Up for us?
>> ♪ yeah, yeah
>> absolutely.
>> although it's rare, at the
>> ♪ yeah, yeah
turn of the last century, the
>> although it's rare, at the
divorce rate grew for a number
turn of the last century, the
of justifiable reasons.
Divorce rate grew for a number
People are alcoholics, drug
of justifiable reasons.
addicts, physically abusive to
people are alcoholics, drug
their spouse or children --
addicts, physically abusive to
these are situations where
their spouse or children --
separation is often best for all
these are situations where
involved.
Separation is often best for all
But divorce and its acceptance
involved.
have changed with the times.
But divorce and its acceptance
On their wedding day, couples
have changed with the times.
often still say, "till death do
on their wedding day, couples
us part," but after time passes,
often still say, "till death do
the initial attraction often
us part," but after time passes,
fades.
The initial attraction often
The perfect spouse all of a
fades.
sudden is a normal person with
the perfect spouse all of a
human flaws.
Sudden is a normal person with
Recurring arguments, attraction
human flaws.
to a co-worker, or simple
recurring arguments, attraction
boredom can lead to
to a co-worker, or simple
irreconcilable differences.
Boredom can lead to
Divorce is a lazy way out.
Irreconcilable differences.
Divorce is a shortcut solution.
Divorce is a lazy way out.
>> Wake up, grandma.
Divorce is a shortcut solution.
It's the 21st century.
>> Wake up, grandma.
That's the way it goes.
It's the 21st century.
[ laughter ]
That's the way it goes.
>> What about children?
[ Laughter ]
Doesn't our future depend on
>> what about children?
them?
Doesn't our future depend on
Divorce can have a devastating
them?
effect on a child, as my case
divorce can have a devastating
studies attest.
Effect on a child, as my case
[ door opens ]
Studies attest.
I can also personally attest to
[ door opens ]
this because I come from a
I can also personally attest to
broken family.
This because I come from a
I was raised by my grandparents,
broken family.
and not that they didn't take
I was raised by my grandparents,
care of me, because they did,
and not that they didn't take
but I still wish that my parents
care of me, because they did,
were there, too.
But I still wish that my parents
>> And your solution?
>> Take it seriously.
Marriage is work.
Marriage is for life.
If you are willing to make the
marriage is for life.
commitment, you have to be
if you are willing to make the
prepared to go the distance.
Commitment, you have to be
>> Excuse me.
Prepared to go the distance.
Um, did you major in sociology
>> excuse me.
or did you major in fantasy?
Um, did you major in sociology
[ laughter ]
Or did you major in fantasy?
You make it sound like a jail
[ laughter ]
sentence without the parole.
You make it sound like a jail
[ laughter ]
Sentence without the parole.
>> Look, buddy, no need to
[ laughter ]
worry.
>> Look, buddy, no need to
From the looks of it, the only
worry.
lifelong commitment you'll have
from the looks of it, the only
is with your right hand.
Lifelong commitment you'll have
>> Ohh!
Is with your right hand.
[ laughter ]
>> Ohh!
>> Shit.
[ Laughter ]
Thank you.
>> Shit.
That's, uh -- that's it.
Thank you.
That's all.
That's, uh -- that's it.
>> Thank God.
That's all.
>> [ clapping ]
[ Door opens ]
>> Honey, slow down.
>> I worked my butt off for
>> honey, slow down.
three years on that thesis.
>> I worked my butt off for
I interviewed hundreds of
three years on that thesis.
couples, and all it takes is a
I interviewed hundreds of
couple of idiots in the audience
couples, and all it takes is a
to make it all seem like a joke!
Couple of idiots in the audience
And you seem to have no opinion
to make it all seem like a joke!
about it.
And you seem to have no opinion
>> Well, if it's one thing I've
about it.
learned from you, it's when to
>> well, if it's one thing I've
keep my mouth shut.
Learned from you, it's when to
>> Okay, then.
Keep my mouth shut.
Fine. Let's -- let's be honest.
>> Okay, then.
I can handle it.
Fine. Let's -- let's be honest.
Tell me the truth.
I can handle it.
>> The truth?
Tell me the truth.
>> Yeah.
>> The truth?
>> Well, I think some of those
>> yeah.
guys had some...
>> Well, I think some of those
Pretty valid points.
Guys had some...
>> Why don't you just admit it?
Pretty valid points.
You don't respect my academic
>> why don't you just admit it?
research!
>> No! It's just thousands of
theses sit in a library
gathering dust.
Theses sit in a library
You know, they change nothing.
Gathering dust.
The world goes on as if they
you know, they change nothing.
were never even written.
The world goes on as if they
>> Yeah, but out of those
were never even written.
thousands, one of those papers
>> yeah, but out of those
had the formula for electricity
thousands, one of those papers
on it.
Had the formula for electricity
>> It did?
On it.
>> So how do you know that mine
>> it did?
won't be that one, huh?
>> So how do you know that mine
I mean, if it could just change
won't be that one, huh?
one mind, it would all be
I mean, if it could just change
worth it.
One mind, it would all be
[ scoffs ]
Worth it.
Why am I wasting my time talking
[ scoffs ]
to you?
Why am I wasting my time talking
What would a college dropout
to you?
care about this stuff anyway?
What would a college dropout
>> Hey, I am a proud dropout,
care about this stuff anyway?
okay?
>> Hey, I am a proud dropout,
College is a waste of time.
Okay?
Four, five, six years of endless
college is a waste of time.
side roads and pointless
four, five, six years of endless
detours.
Side roads and pointless
My theory for life is simple --
detours.
shortcuts.
My theory for life is simple --
>> Shortcuts.
>> You know what?
This has been too much academic
debate for one day.
>> I'm sorry, Mike, okay?
Debate for one day.
I just had a really rough day.
>> I'm sorry, Mike, okay?
[ sighs ]
I just had a really rough day.
>> How about some margaritas at
[ sighs ]
the deck bar?
>> How about some margaritas at
>> [ sighs ]
The deck bar?
>> And then how about a massage
>> [ sighs ]
by the expert hands of a
>> and then how about a massage
Kansas City farm boy?
By the expert hands of a
If the client is not completely
Kansas City farm boy?
satisfied, she can return the
if the client is not completely
massage to the massager.
Satisfied, she can return the
>> Thank God.
>> Hey, babe.
>> Hi, honey.
>> How are you?
>> [ sighs ] Tired.
>> Mm.
>> [ Sighs ] Tired.
>> Hi.
>> Mm.
>> Mm. Hi.
>> Hi.
Look what I brought you.
>> Mm. Hi.
>> Oh, you're sweet, but I'm so
look what I brought you.
icky from the restaurant.
>> Oh, you're sweet, but I'm so
I just -- I really want to go in
icky from the restaurant.
to take a shower.
I just -- I really want to go in
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
To take a shower.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
What's the -- what's the rush,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
huh?
What's the -- what's the rush,
This is a gorgeous evening, huh?
Huh?
>> Ha! It's L.A.
This is a gorgeous evening, huh?
they are all gorgeous evenings.
>> Ha! It's L.A.
>> Yeah, but, um, this is an
they are all gorgeous evenings.
especially romantic evening,
>> yeah, but, um, this is an
isn't it?
Especially romantic evening,
Clear --
isn't it?
>> not so much 'cause we're
clear --
right by the dumpster, and the
>> not so much 'cause we're
trash guy forgot to stop on our
right by the dumpster, and the
street again.
Trash guy forgot to stop on our
So, listen, I'm gonna go in, I'm
street again.
gonna take a shower, and then
so, listen, I'm gonna go in, I'm
maybe I can muster a little
gonna take a shower, and then
romance for you.
Maybe I can muster a little
>> Hold -- hold on.
Romance for you.
>> Okay.
>> Hold -- hold on.
>> What's the rush?
>> Okay.
>> I got to go!
>> What's the rush?
I'm gross.
>> I got to go!
>> Crap.
I'm gross.
>> Aah!
>> Crap.
>> Aah! Aah!
>> Aah!
>> Ohh! Come on!
>> ♪ Do, do do do, do do do
♪ do, do do, do do do
dude, you don't have to leave,
all right?
Dude, you don't have to leave,
You just can't put me on watch
all right?
dog anymore, all right?
You just can't put me on watch
>> [ laughs ]
Dog anymore, all right?
Yeah. I mean, you are more than
>> [ laughs ]
welcome to stay with us whenever
yeah. I mean, you are more than
you want.
Welcome to stay with us whenever
You and Scotty have known each
you want.
other since birth.
You and Scotty have known each
I only barged into your lives
other since birth.
about a year ago.
I only barged into your lives
>> Barging in on me was not
about a year ago.
cool.
>> Barging in on me was not
>> [ chuckles ]
Cool.
>> I know.
>> [ Chuckles ]
I'm sorry, but, you know, you
>> I know.
can't barge in and expect to
I'm sorry, but, you know, you
become one of them in six
can't barge in and expect to
months, either.
Become one of them in six
>> "One of them"?
Months, either.
"Them"?
>> "One of them"?
What -- what does that even
"them"?
mean?
What -- what does that even
Really?
Mean?
Dylan and I are in love.
Really?
Okay?
Dylan and I are in love.
Why you guys so worried about
okay?
this now?
Why you guys so worried about
>> Dude, she's the one who got
this now?
you the lipnick job, remember?
>> Dude, she's the one who got
She just don't want to get fired
you the lipnick job, remember?
when the Christian shit hits the
she just don't want to get fired
jewish fan.
When the Christian shit hits the
>> No. No, I'm not worried about
jewish fan.
that.
>> No. No, I'm not worried about
I am a phenomenal waitress, but
that.
I am worried about you.
I am a phenomenal waitress, but
I mean, if you're really
I am worried about you.
considering marrying Dylan, I
I mean, if you're really
just might think again.
Considering marrying Dylan, I
Her grandparents are very
just might think again.
old school.
Her grandparents are very
I mean, they are
old school.
super-super-religious.
I mean, they are
>> So?
Super-super-religious.
My parents are super-religious.
>> So?
They don't care if I marry a
my parents are super-religious.
jewish girl.
They don't care if I marry a
>> Mike, are you sure? Huh?
Jewish girl.
'Cause growing in punkton,
>> Mike, are you sure? Huh?
Kansas, I doubt anybody could
'cause growing in punkton,
tell jewish from amish.
Kansas, I doubt anybody could
Remember facial hair?
Tell jewish from amish.
If you had facial hair, you were
remember facial hair?
an alien from outer space.
If you had facial hair, you were
True story.
An alien from outer space.
>> Scotty, you can't change my
true story.
mind on this, okay?
>> Scotty, you can't change my
She's...
Mind on this, okay?
[ breathes deeply ]
She's...
She's just made for me.
[ Breathes deeply ]
>> She's made for you.
She's just made for me.
Hey, man, um, what happened to
>> she's made for you.
the Mike I used to know, huh?
Hey, man, um, what happened to
The one who would only take the
the Mike I used to know, huh?
richest dude's daughter to the
the one who would only take the
prom?
Richest dude's daughter to the
Where's he at?
Prom?
Can I see him?
Where's he at?
>> Yeah.
Can I see him?
>> I miss him.
>> Yeah.
>> And what happened to the
>> I miss him.
stock broker who wouldn't even
>> and what happened to the
take a woman out to coffee
stock broker who wouldn't even
without looking at her profile
take a woman out to coffee
first?
Without looking at her profile
>> Ah.
First?
Hmm?
>> Ah.
>> He grew up.
Hmm?
He fell in love.
>> He grew up.
Besides, do not underestimate
he fell in love.
the potential of this
besides, do not underestimate
restaurant.
The potential of this
We are really close to
restaurant.
franchising this.
We are really close to
>> Oh, oh, oh, okay, okay.
Franchising this.
See, I thought -- I thought
>> oh, oh, oh, okay, okay.
amigo was in love with señorita,
see, I thought -- I thought
not the restaurante.
Amigo was in love with señorita,
Amigo in love with señorita, not
not the restaurante.
the restaurante.
Amigo in love with señorita, not
♪ boop ba-da-doop, ba-da-doop
the restaurante.
♪ amigo in love with señorita
♪ boop ba-da-doop, ba-da-doop
♪ not the restaurante
♪ amigo in love with señorita
♪ boop, ba-da-boop, ba-da-boop
♪ not the restaurante
>> Scotty, don't be a schmuck!
♪ Boop, ba-da-boop, ba-da-boop
Besides, I'm thinking about Paul
>> Scotty, don't be a schmuck!
and Elaine in this whole thing.
Besides, I'm thinking about Paul
I mean, how can they say no to a
and Elaine in this whole thing.
guy who is about to
I mean, how can they say no to a
revolutionize their family
guy who is about to
business?
Revolutionize their family
>> Family business?
Business?
[ laughs ]
>> Family business?
You would have to die and be
[ laughs ]
reborn jewish for them to
you would have to die and be
consider you family.
Reborn jewish for them to
>> Oy! Please!
Consider you family.
I could be as jewish as they
>> oy! Please!
wanted me to be!
I could be as jewish as they
[ stomps foot ]
Wanted me to be!
>> [ chuckles ]
[ Stomps foot ]
>> Just wait until you see
>> [ chuckles ]
Jeremy.
>> Just wait until you see
>> Who?
Jeremy.
>> The bicycle guy?
>> Who?
>> Yeah.
>> The bicycle guy?
The lipnicks totally drool over
>> yeah.
him.
The lipnicks totally drool over
Okay? He's straight out of
him.
frickin' "fiddler on the roof."
Okay? He's straight out of
And now that he's back in town,
frickin' "fiddler on the roof."
they're gonna try to set Dylan
and now that he's back in town,
up with him.
They're gonna try to set Dylan
Just wait and see.
Up with him.
[ klezmer music playing ]
>> Sweetheart, we need to buy
more sugar packets.
>> I know.
More sugar packets.
And we're running out of baked
>> I know.
apples.
And we're running out of baked
>> Oh, I thought we had so many.
Apples.
>> No, we don't.
>> Oh, I thought we had so many.
>> What about the halva?
>> No, we don't.
The halva -- chocolate-covered
>> what about the halva?
halva.
The halva -- chocolate-covered
>> Oh, I love it.
Halva.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, I love it.
>> A lot of people like it.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> A lot of people like it.
We're actually not open yet.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> Oh, I'm not a customer.
We're actually not open yet.
I'm family.
>> Oh, I'm not a customer.
>> Would you mind telling me who
I'm family.
you're related to?
>> Would you mind telling me who
>> Look who's here.
You're related to?
Jeremy!
>> Look who's here.
Bubala!
Jeremy!
>> Jeremy!
Bubala!
>> Paul! Ooh!
>> Jeremy!
Bubbie Elaine.
>> Paul! Ooh!
Good to see you.
Bubbie Elaine.
>> Good to see you.
Good to see you.
>> I brought you these -- to
>> good to see you.
congratulate you on delilah's
>> I brought you these -- to
graduation.
Congratulate you on delilah's
>> How nice of you to remember.
Graduation.
>> Where is our beautiful
>> how nice of you to remember.
delilah?
>> Where is our beautiful
>> She's not here now.
Delilah?
But you are -- join us for
>> she's not here now.
lunch.
But you are -- join us for
>> Oh, we have some delicious
lunch.
food here.
>> Oh, we have some delicious
>> There is nothing I would love
food here.
more than grandma's delicious
>> there is nothing I would love
tongue on rye.
More than grandma's delicious
>> Oh! [ laughing ]
Tongue on rye.
>> But, unfortunately, I have to
>> oh! [ laughing ]
run.
>> But, unfortunately, I have to
I'll be back later, though, to
run.
pick up delilah.
I'll be back later, though, to
She doesn't know it yet, but...
Pick up delilah.
I got her tickets to see the
she doesn't know it yet, but...
symphony at the Hollywood bowl.
I got her tickets to see the
>> Wonderful!
Symphony at the Hollywood bowl.
>> Fabulous!
>> Wonderful!
>> Michael, would you put these
>> fabulous!
lovely flowers in some water,
>> Michael, would you put these
please?
Lovely flowers in some water,
He's our new assistant manager.
Please?
>> [ sighs ]
He's our new assistant manager.
>> Hi. Mike.
>> [ Sighs ]
Mike Christian.
>> Hi. Mike.
>> Jeremy.
Mike Christian.
Jeremy jew.
>> Jeremy.
>> Stop it.
Jeremy jew.
[ laughter ]
>> Stop it.
>> Yeah, that's funny.
[ Laughter ]
Uh, Christian is my real last
>> yeah, that's funny.
name, actually.
Uh, Christian is my real last
>> Well, jew's mine, too.
Name, actually.
And if you believe that, I got a
>> well, jew's mine, too.
bridge in Brooklyn I'd love to
and if you believe that, I got a
sell you.
Bridge in Brooklyn I'd love to
[ laughter ]
Sell you.
>> Got it. Yeah.
[ Laughter ]
Uh, Dylan's at the dentist right
>> got it. Yeah.
now, and actually, you know, I
uh, Dylan's at the dentist right
think she has plans later.
Now, and actually, you know, I
>> Really?
Think she has plans later.
I thought you were the assistant
>> really?
manager.
I thought you were the assistant
What, are you her personal
manager.
secretary, too?
What, are you her personal
[ laughter ]
Secretary, too?
>> No, I'm her boyfriend.
[ Laughter ]
>> What?
>> No, I'm her boyfriend.
Wh-what did you say?
>> What?
>> Paul, Elaine, I didn't want
wh-what did you say?
you guys to find out like this.
>> Paul, Elaine, I didn't want
I mean, you guys have taken me
you guys to find out like this.
in, and you've treated me like
I mean, you guys have taken me
family.
In, and you've treated me like
But I guess now is as good a
family.
time as any.
But I guess now is as good a
[ breathes deeply ]
Time as any.
I'm in love with your
[ breathes deeply ]
granddaughter.
I'm in love with your
>> In love?
Granddaughter.
>> [ speaking yiddish ]
>> In love?
>> You're fired! Get out!
>> [ Speaking yiddish ]
>> Paul, let me explain.
>> You're fired! Get out!
>> Out!
>> Paul, let me explain.
>> We don't want to see you. Go.
>> Out!
>> What's going on?
>> Um...There's just one
question I need to ask you
before I leave.
Question I need to ask you
Dylan lipnick, I want to spend
before I leave.
the rest of my life with you.
Dylan lipnick, I want to spend
Will you marry me?
The rest of my life with you.
>> No!
Will you marry me?
>> No! No!
>> No!
>> I'm serious.
>> No! No!
I'm committed.
>> I'm serious.
I need your answer -- yes or no?
>> [ Sighs ]
>> Oh, my God.
Yes!
>> Yes?
>> Yes!
>> Are you serious?!
>> Oh, but --
>> are you serious?!
>> no.
>> Oh, but --
>> This is a sham!
>> No.
Those flowers Jeremy brought for
>> this is a sham!
you.
Those flowers Jeremy brought for
>> Then that's what the invites
you.
will say -- "flowers by
>> then that's what the invites
Jeremy -- Jeremy jew."
Will say -- "flowers by
You know what?
Jeremy -- Jeremy jew."
Jeremy was even kind enough to
you know what?
buy concert tickets.
Jeremy was even kind enough to
>> Yes.
Buy concert tickets.
>> For us.
>> Yes.
>> No!
>> For us.
>> No?
>> No!
>> Yes.
>> No?
>> Delilah...
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> Delilah...
>> ...I want to see you in my
>> thank you.
booth right now.
>> ...I want to see you in my
>> Come on.
>> Oy.
>> You've known this man for
only a few months, and now
you're ready to marry him?
Only a few months, and now
What do you know about him?
You're ready to marry him?
>> I know he's a good man with a
what do you know about him?
brilliant head on his shoulders.
>> I know he's a good man with a
He's a self-directed man with
brilliant head on his shoulders.
ambition and dreams.
He's a self-directed man with
And he loves me to bits,
ambition and dreams.
grandpa.
And he loves me to bits,
What more can I ask for?
Grandpa.
>> Jeremy waited years for you
what more can I ask for?
to finish school.
>> Jeremy waited years for you
At least you could've given it a
to finish school.
try, gone out with him,
at least you could've given it a
something.
Try, gone out with him,
>> He's not my type, grandma.
Something.
He's too...
>> He's not my type, grandma.
>> Too what?
He's too...
>> I don't -- I don't know.
>> Too what?
He's too...
>> I don't -- I don't know.
>> Jewish?
He's too...
Too jewish?
>> Jewish?
Like all those worthless people
too jewish?
in our family?
Like all those worthless people
Like all the generations who
in our family?
suffered so you could have a
like all the generations who
better life?
Suffered so you could have a
Like us, I suppose?
>> Come here, sweetheart.
Listen to me.
I have never seen your grandpa
listen to me.
this hurt.
I have never seen your grandpa
Please, just let it go for a
this hurt.
while.
Please, just let it go for a
Let it be.
While.
All right?
>> They've given up so much to
give me a better life.
And what do I do in return?
Give me a better life.
I crush them.
[ Exhaling sharply ]
>> Okay, so, I want to go
through an authentic conversion,
>> okay, so, I want to go
one that follows the most
through an authentic conversion,
ancient of rituals.
One that follows the most
>> You do understand that this
ancient of rituals.
will require a circumcision,
>> you do understand that this
yeah?
Will require a circumcision,
>> Yes, I do.
Yeah?
>> And you're kidding me, right?
>> Yes, I do.
It's a joke.
>> And you're kidding me, right?
Oh, I get it.
It's a joke.
This is an episode of a reality
oh, I get it.
show, and I'm in it.
This is an episode of a reality
And I bet you my Agent set it
show, and I'm in it.
up.
And I bet you my Agent set it
Max?
Up.
Max, where are you, you little
Max?
rat?
Max, where are you, you little
Max?
Rat?
No?
Max?
>> No.
No?
>> You're serious.
>> No.
All right, I have to explain
>> you're serious.
what it is.
All right, I have to explain
We don't have to take off the
what it is.
whole megillah.
We don't have to take off the
We got to make a cut.
Whole megillah.
But there's gonna be some blood,
we got to make a cut.
there's gonna be a scalpel,
but there's gonna be some blood,
there's gonna be an owie on your
there's gonna be a scalpel,
pee-pee, all right?
There's gonna be an owie on your
I got a question to ask you.
Pee-pee, all right?
On a scale of 1 to 10, how much
I got a question to ask you.
pain can you take it?
On a scale of 1 to 10, how much
>> 8.5.
Pain can you take it?
>> No, no.
>> 8.5.
No, no, no.
>> No, no.
Not 8.5.
No, no, no.
I'm -- I'm more of like a 2.1
not 8.5.
kind of guy.
I'm -- I'm more of like a 2.1
>> You said you were in love.
Kind of guy.
>> And this is your best friend,
>> you said you were in love.
yeah?
>> And this is your best friend,
>> 8.5.
Yeah?
>> Okay.
>> 8.5.
For love.
>> Okay.
>> Hey, kid.
For love.
>> 8.5.
>> Hey, kid.
>> Drink to that.
>> 8.5.
Under strict rabbinical law, I
>> drink to that.
have to tell you, you've got to
under strict rabbinical law, I
ask me three times so I can do
have to tell you, you've got to
it.
Ask me three times so I can do
>> Please?
It.
>> No.
>> Please?
>> Okay! That's all right.
We're gonna do it.
All right.
And I'm gonna sing to you like a
all right.
father would sing to his little
and I'm gonna sing to you like a
jewish boy.
Father would sing to his little
[ singing in hebrew ]
>> Wow! [ chuckles ]
I feel jewish already.
Oh, look!
My foreskin just fell off!
Ha ha!
No, it -- it didn't.
You still have to cut it off.
>> You look jewish a little bit.
Welcome, welcome, my dear
friends.
Good afternoon.
Friends.
Today, we're going to have a
good afternoon.
ceremony which you will never
today, we're going to have a
forget the rest of your life, I
ceremony which you will never
assure you.
Forget the rest of your life, I
We have a young man outside of
assure you.
our shul but with a great deal
we have a young man outside of
of love in his heart, who has
our shul but with a great deal
come here today to express his
of love in his heart, who has
love and admiration for our
come here today to express his
religion.
Love and admiration for our
He wants to be converted in the
religion.
most traditional way -- with our
he wants to be converted in the
oldest ritual, the bris.
>> Rabbi.
>> Are you comfortable?
>> Yeah.
Are you comfortable?
>> I make a living.
Are you confident?
>> Yeah.
>> They're not gonna cut me.
Are you confident?
[ chanting in hebrew ]
[ Singing in hebrew ]
>> Aaaaaaaah!
>> Boychick, how you feeling?
See?
Wasn't so bad.
>> Yeah.
Not so bad.
>> Heimlich.
>> [ chuckles ]
So, we have some oils here
that'll make you feel better.
We have everything from
something that's soothing and
we have everything from
gentle to healing and stinging.
Something that's soothing and
>> How about some wine?
Gentle to healing and stinging.
[ sighs ]
>> How about some wine?
>> You're serious?
[ Sighs ]
All right.
>> You're serious?
>> He's chosen wine.
All right.
>> Wine it is.
>> He's chosen wine.
Don't worry.
>> Wine it is.
>> You're a brave young man.
Don't worry.
>> Oh, yes.
>> You're a brave young man.
Here we go.
>> Oh, yes.
>> Aaaaaah!
Here we go.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
[ Applause ]
>> Mazel tov.
>> Thank you.
Thank you.
>> Mazel tov.
>> Oh. Oh, you came.
Oh, that means so much to me.
Dylan -- Dylan loves you so
oh, that means so much to me.
much, and she was afraid you
Dylan -- Dylan loves you so
weren't gonna accept me and...
Much, and she was afraid you
Thank you.
Weren't gonna accept me and...
>> Who told you this
thank you.
Daniel nudnick was qualified to
>> who told you this
do this?
Daniel nudnick was qualified to
You need to study six mon--
do this?
>> yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
You need to study six mon--
I know. I am studying.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
I just couldn't stay away from
I know. I am studying.
my Dylan that long.
I just couldn't stay away from
>> Excuse me.
My Dylan that long.
>> Oh, uh, Paul?
>> Excuse me.
Let's keep this a surprise,
>> oh, uh, Paul?
between us.
Careful.
[ applause ]
>> Okay, I'll be right back with
some pepper.
Do you need anything else?
Some pepper.
>> Just that.
Do you need anything else?
>> Okay, all right, great.
>> Just that.
>> Hey. Where's Mike?
>> Okay, all right, great.
>> Oh, um, why don't you ask our
>> hey. Where's Mike?
new head manager?
>> Oh, um, why don't you ask our
Proudest jew on the block.
>> Why would you do that?
Hire him as head manager?
No matter what you say or do, I
hire him as head manager?
am never going out with him.
No matter what you say or do, I
>> Well, sorry to hear that, but
am never going out with him.
maybe you should tell him
>> well, sorry to hear that, but
yourself.
Maybe you should tell him
>> Go ahead. Tell him.
>> Look, I know that this might
disappoint you, but will you
please just leave me alone?
Disappoint you, but will you
>> Oy!
Please just leave me alone?
What am I, chopped liver?
>> Oy!
Fine. I'm leaving.
What am I, chopped liver?
I don't need your tsuris.
Fine. I'm leaving.
>> Mike?
I don't need your tsuris.
What is this?
>> Mike?
>> Yesterday was a surprise -- a
what is this?
profound surprise for us, as
>> yesterday was a surprise -- a
well.
Profound surprise for us, as
He put himself through the whole
well.
nine yards, including a
he put himself through the whole
traditional bris.
Nine yards, including a
>> Who knew he was gonna be
traditional bris.
studying hebrew?
>> Who knew he was gonna be
>> You didn't have to...
Studying hebrew?
I can't believe you did all
>> you didn't have to...
this.
I can't believe you did all
>> May I, with your permission?
This.
>> Of course.
>> Oh.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Aww.
>> Mwah.
>> Mwah!
Mazel tov.
>> Mazel tov.
[ laughter ]
>> Aww. Every happiness.
[ Laughter ]
>> It's amazing.
>> Aww. Every happiness.
>> You like --
>> it's amazing.
oh, careful down there.
>> You like --
>> Oh, sorry.
Oh, careful down there.
>> Whew. [ chuckles ]
>> [ Gasps ]
Roger!
>> What happened?
>> Come here!
Come on!
>> What? What?
>> Oh, my God.
You have to see this.
>> What?
Go ahead.
>> No, no, no, no!
You have to read it yourself!
>> Hands are all wet.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
>> Honey, Jesus was jewish.
Gosh. Isn't she beautiful?
>> Well, yeah, but...
I wish he would've told us.
>> Honey, Mike has finally found
somebody he loves.
I'm going.
Somebody he loves.
Are you gonna join me?
I'm going.
>> Of course I'm gonna join you.
Are you gonna join me?
But I'm not joining anything
>> of course I'm gonna join you.
else.
But I'm not joining anything
>> [ laughs ]
Else.
>> So, how many guests so far?
>> [ Laughs ]
>> Our side, we're at 200, plus
>> so, how many guests so far?
you added 49, including the
>> our side, we're at 200, plus
stock-market janitors?
You added 49, including the
>> Oh, good! Yes!
Stock-market janitors?
I love those guys.
Honey, it's getting late.
Don't you have to go home?
>> Yeah.
So, I don't want you to
>> yeah.
misunderstand me.
So, I don't want you to
Feel free -- tell me what you
misunderstand me.
think.
Feel free -- tell me what you
>> What's this?
Think.
>> It's our prenup.
>> What's this?
>> No!
>> It's our prenup.
Hey, guys! Scotty, come here!
>> No!
>> Yo!
Hey, guys! Scotty, come here!
>> You guys, we are like real
>> yo!
celebrities.
>> You guys, we are like real
We are like Brad pitt and
celebrities.
Angelina jolie.
We are like Brad pitt and
Ha!
Angelina jolie.
We have got a prenup.
Ha!
Yeah!
We have got a prenup.
>> This is a -- this is a
yeah!
prenup?
>> This is a -- this is a
>> Yeah.
Prenup?
>> Prenup.
>> Yeah.
This is more like a phone book.
>> Prenup.
>> Wow.
This is more like a phone book.
Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> Okay. I know it's a bit long,
yeah.
but you understand why.
>> Okay. I know it's a bit long,
>> Oh, I know! I know!
But you understand why.
I know.
>> Oh, I know! I know!
Because in our jewish culture,
I know.
before the wedding, we sign a
because in our jewish culture,
thing called a "patuka."
Before the wedding, we sign a
>> A what?
Thing called a "patuka."
>> A "topanga."
>> A what?
A...Bazooka.
>> A "topanga."
Umbutcha.
A...Bazooka.
Tenduka, cambuna, hakuna --
umbutcha.
cadzuki, shiitake.
Tenduka, cambuna, hakuna --
>> It's a ketubah...
Cadzuki, shiitake.
>> Ketubah! Yes!
>> It's a ketubah...
>> ...Mr. Jewish groom.
>> Ketubah! Yes!
And ketubah is just one page.
>> ...Mr. jewish groom.
>> This is way more than one
and ketubah is just one page.
page.
>> This is way more than one
This is...A lot of pages.
Page.
>> Honey, yeah, this is a
this is...A lot of pages.
little...
>> Honey, yeah, this is a
Are you sure this is our prenup?
Little...
It looks more like your thesis.
Are you sure this is our prenup?
>> Just read it and let me know
it looks more like your thesis.
if you want to make any changes.
>> Just read it and let me know
Love you.
If you want to make any changes.
>> I love you.
Love you.
>> Bye.
>> I love you.
>> I love our prenup!
>> Bye.
>> I'm glad.
>> Dude, what are you doing?!
You got to read this shit.
>> [ laughs ]
Dude, how many credit cards do
you sign up for?
You just sign "I agree" without
even reading it.
Come on.
Even reading it.
>> Dude, this is your life we're
come on.
talking about here, not a credit
>> dude, this is your life we're
card, okay?
Talking about here, not a credit
Look, there's an attorney in my
card, okay?
cigar club.
Look, there's an attorney in my
He owes me a favor.
Cigar club.
We'll let him read it first, all
he owes me a favor.
right?
We'll let him read it first, all
Just let him read it.
Right?
>> Dude, it's fine.
Just let him read it.
Look -- "sign here."
>> Dude, it's fine.
>> You're out of your mind.
Look -- "sign here."
>> He's in love.
>> You're out of your mind.
>> I'm in love!
>> He's in love.
>> Love makes you stupid.
>> I'm in love!
>> Like "wow! Stupid!"
>> Love makes you stupid.
>> Love makes me stupid.
>> Like "wow! Stupid!"
>> Yeah.
>> Love makes me stupid.
>> ♪ ooh, ooh
>> yeah.
♪ yeah, yeah
>> ♪ ooh, ooh
♪ picture you with no me
♪ yeah, yeah
♪ picture me without love
♪ picture you with no me
♪ I just can't see you and I
♪ picture me without love
getting old ♪
♪ I just can't see you and I
♪ now picture us old
getting old ♪
♪ still so in love
♪ now picture us old
♪ that is the dream I can
♪ still so in love
picture for us ♪
♪ that is the dream I can
♪ I ain't goin' nowhere
picture for us ♪
♪ I ain't leavin'
♪ I ain't goin' nowhere
for nothin' in the world ♪
♪ I ain't leavin'
♪ I ain't going nowhere
for nothin' in the world ♪
♪ I'm-a stay here
♪ I ain't going nowhere
♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ I'm-a stay here
♪ I want to be the one
♪ I'm stayin' with you
here for the long run ♪
♪ I want to be the one
♪ nothing can fade the love for
here for the long run ♪
you ♪
♪ nothing can fade the love for
♪ I use every single day
you ♪
♪ being your everything
♪ I use every single day
♪ coming with brand-new ways to
♪ being your everything
show you ♪
♪ coming with brand-new ways to
♪ you say I'm headstrong
show you ♪
♪ you think I let go
♪ you say I'm headstrong
♪ oh, baby, ain't enough
♪ you think I let go
forgiveness to make me say
♪ oh, baby, ain't enough
goodbye ♪
forgiveness to make me say
>> ♪ no matter who's gone
goodbye ♪
♪ I always come home
>> ♪ no matter who's gone
>> ♪ 'cause you were made for
♪ I always come home
me, and I'm staying with you ♪
>> ♪ 'cause you were made for
♪ I ain't goin' nowhere
me, and I'm staying with you ♪
♪ I ain't leavin'
♪ I ain't goin' nowhere
for nothin' in the world ♪
♪ I ain't leavin'
♪ I ain't going nowhere
for nothin' in the world ♪
♪ I'm-a stay here
♪ I ain't going nowhere
♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ I'm-a stay here
♪ ooh
♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ yeah
♪ ooh
>> ♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ yeah
>> ♪ ooh
>> ♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ yeah
>> ♪ ooh
>> ♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ yeah
>> ♪ ooh, ooh
>> ♪ I'm stayin' with you
♪ yeah, yeah
>> ♪ ooh, ooh
♪ ooh, ooh
♪ yeah, yeah
♪ ooh ooh
♪ yeah
♪ yeah, yeah
♪ oh
♪ yeah
♪ I'm stayin' with you
>> where are we going?
What are we doing here?
>> Don't worry about it.
Thank you.
>> Honey, what are we doing?
>> Just get the bag.
Come on.
>> Honey, whose house is this?
Wow.
God.
>> Turn it on.
>> Welcome to your new home!
>> Have a very happy married
life, darlings!
>> Have a blast!
Life, darlings!
>> Both: Mwah! Mwah!
>> Have a blast!
>> No.
>> Both: Mwah! Mwah!
>> Yeah.
>> No.
>> No!
>> Yeah.
[ both laugh ]
>> No!
Oh, my God!
[ Both laugh ]
I don't want them watching.
Oh, my God!
>> [ laughs ]
>> Lipnick's.
What the hell kind of name is
that, anyway?
>> It's the name that's gonna
make you money, Rick.
Okay, now, what's the plan of
attack?
V.C.S or angels?
Attack?
>> No, no, no, no.
V.C.S or angels?
I'd go big.
>> No, no, no, no.
On that note, I know you guys
I'd go big.
can't afford a 15% finder's fee,
on that note, I know you guys
so figured I'd make it 10%?
>> 5% is industry standard.
>> [ chuckles ] Come on, Scotty.
>> 5.5%.
>> [ Chuckles ] Come on, Scotty.
>> 8.5%.
>> 5.5%.
>> No!
>> 8.5%.
It hurts.
>> No!
>> Damn. Okay.
It hurts.
Uh...5.5%. Fine.
>> Damn. Okay.
Not a cent less, not a cent
uh...5.5%. Fine.
more.
>> Gentlemen, our board of
directors loves your plan.
However, our c.E.O. Is leaving
town for two weeks, so we'd like
however, our c.E.O. Is leaving
to ask you not to approach any
town for two weeks, so we'd like
other companies until she's
to ask you not to approach any
back, and then we can finalize
other companies until she's
your contract.
Back, and then we can finalize
>> Well, we have two other
your contract.
meetings set up.
>> Well, we have two other
>> We do?
Meetings set up.
Oh.
>> We do?
>> Yeah, we -- we do.
Oh.
>> Two weeks is a long time.
>> Yeah, we -- we do.
Come on.
>> Two weeks is a long time.
She knows the deal.
Come on.
Why not just give us the answer
she knows the deal.
right now.
Why not just give us the answer
>> I wish I could, but she's
right now.
heading to the airport right
>> I wish I could, but she's
now.
Heading to the airport right
>> Is that your c.E.O. Right
now.
there?
>> Is that your c.E.O. Right
>> Yes.
There?
And that's Ms. birch.
>> Yes.
>> Come on.
And that's Ms. birch.
Just let us talk to her for like
>> come on.
one minute.
Just let us talk to her for like
>> 'Fraid I can't.
One minute.
>> Well, we're afraid we'll have
>> 'fraid I can't.
to pursue our other options,
>> well, we're afraid we'll have
then.
To pursue our other options,
>> Give me one minute.
Then.
The gentlemen from the
>> give me one minute.
restaurant are here.
The gentlemen from the
They'd like to speak with you
restaurant are here.
just briefly.
They'd like to speak with you
>> I'm on my way to a business
just briefly.
and golf trip.
>> I'm on my way to a business
I don't have time for this.
And golf trip.
Please just reschedule.
I don't have time for this.
>> Now is not a good time to
please just reschedule.
talk to her.
>> Now is not a good time to
I'm afraid you're just going to
talk to her.
have to wait.
I'm afraid you're just going to
>> Did I hear her say something
have to wait.
about a golf outing?
>> Did I hear her say something
>> Ms. birch is on her way to a
about a golf outing?
financial summit in scottsdale,
>> Ms. birch is on her way to a
Arizona, but all the best deals
financial summit in scottsdale,
are done on the links.
Arizona, but all the best deals
>> You know what?
Are done on the links.
We might just have to go and
>> you know what?
play the back nine with her.
We might just have to go and
>> [ chuckles ]
Play the back nine with her.
I'll see you in a couple of
>> [ chuckles ]
weeks.
>> You know, there actually are
other places we can go.
I think we should look into it.
Other places we can go.
>> Okay.
I think we should look into it.
>> Grandmother's famous recipe
>> okay.
for tongue on rye.
>> It sounded like you said
"tongue."
[ chuckles ]
"Tongue."
>> I did.
[ Chuckles ]
>> It's cow tongue.
>> I did.
>> Oh, cow tongue.
>> It's cow tongue.
Yeah, you know, I'm a diabetic,
>> oh, cow tongue.
so tongue, lips, face, all
yeah, you know, I'm a diabetic,
that's from the neck up, I'm not
so tongue, lips, face, all
supposed to digest it.
That's from the neck up, I'm not
>> Mm. Nice try.
Supposed to digest it.
>> I'm gonna track her down in
>> mm. Nice try.
scottsdale, Arizona.
>> I'm gonna track her down in
I think her comment was a test.
Scottsdale, Arizona.
She purposely said it loud
I think her comment was a test.
enough so that we would hear it.
She purposely said it loud
>> No.
Enough so that we would hear it.
>> Yeah.
>> No.
Look, these big-player types, to
>> yeah.
them, this is all just a game.
Look, these big-player types, to
Why else would they go and do
them, this is all just a game.
business on a golf course?
Why else would they go and do
>> Can you help me?
Business on a golf course?
>> I'm at a loss.
>> Can you help me?
>> So let's play it.
>> I'm at a loss.
Let's play their game.
>> So let's play it.
I'm gonna go to the resort and
let's play their game.
blend in with the millionaire
I'm gonna go to the resort and
crowd.
Blend in with the millionaire
>> Uh, no offense, dude, but
crowd.
that takes some major
>> uh, no offense, dude, but
camouflage.
That takes some major
>> Hey.
Camouflage.
>> Just let me worry about that,
>> hey.
okay?
>> Just let me worry about that,
>> Okay, look, man.
Okay?
>> A last-minute plane ticket,
>> okay, look, man.
though?
>> A last-minute plane ticket,
A five-star executive suite?
Though?
Plus, your blending in would
a five-star executive suite?
cost more than we all can afford
plus, your blending in would
to put together.
Cost more than we all can afford
So, sorry to be a prick, but we
to put together.
all know how your financial
so, sorry to be a prick, but we
adventures turned out in the
all know how your financial
past.
Adventures turned out in the
>> Look, that was a long time
past.
ago, okay?
>> Look, that was a long time
I have learned from those
ago, okay?
mistakes.
I have learned from those
>> I'm not so sure.
Mistakes.
>> Okay. What have we got to
>> I'm not so sure.
lose, other than our own shirts?
>> Okay. What have we got to
Let's see if he can pull this
lose, other than our own shirts?
off.
Let's see if he can pull this
>> Where we gonna get the seed
off.
money?
>> Where we gonna get the seed
What, are we gonna ask the
money?
lipnicks?
What, are we gonna ask the
We can't gamble on their money.
Lipnicks?
We haven't made them any money.
We can't gamble on their money.
It's ridiculous.
We haven't made them any money.
>> Okay. You know what?
It's ridiculous.
Let's just eat.
>> Okay. You know what?
Come on.
Let's just eat.
I've been waiting all day to see
come on.
you try this.
I've been waiting all day to see
>> [ chuckles ]
You try this.
>> Pickle first?
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> Nope.
>> What's this?
>> Open it.
It's our new visa.
Might as well break it in.
>> What if the deal doesn't go
might as well break it in.
through?
>> What if the deal doesn't go
>> At least I'll have a happy
through?
husband.
>> At least I'll have a happy
Happy he at least gave it a try.
Husband.
>> I love you.
Happy he at least gave it a try.
Mmm.
>> I love you.
>> Go get 'em, tiger.
Mmm.
>> Come here.
>> Go get 'em, tiger.
>> ♪ ...Surely find a way
>> come here.
♪ working together day by day
>> here we go.
>> Thank you, my good man.
>> And we never met.
>> Fair enough.
You guys have room for one more?
>> Hi.
[ golf clubs clattering ]
>> Sorry! Just a little --
little tournament stress.
Uh...I'm just gonna -- I'm just
gonna go again.
Yeah.
>> Relax.
Relax.
Eyes on the ball.
Head down.
Feet shoulder-width apart.
Eyes on the ball.
Keep your head down.
Mind on the ball.
Wow.
You are still the same lousy
shooter after all this time.
Nothing's changed.
Shooter after all this time.
>> What?
Nothing's changed.
That's what my friends used to
>> what?
call me back in high --
that's what my friends used to
>> I'm Alex birch.
Call me back in high --
Nice to make your acquaintance
>> I'm Alex birch.
again.
Nice to make your acquaintance
>> Ms. birch.
Again.
Nice to meet you.
>> Ms. birch.
Again?
Nice to meet you.
Alex?
Again?
Alex roverson?!
Alex?
>> [ chuckles ]
Alex roverson?!
It's Alex birch now -- my
>> [ chuckles ]
married name.
It's Alex birch now -- my
>> No way!
Married name.
[ laughs ]
>> No way!
Oh, my God!
[ Laughs ]
How are you?!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
How are you?!
Wow.
Oh!
You haven't changed much.
Wow.
>> Come on.
You haven't changed much.
At least say I lost some of my
>> come on.
baby fat.
At least say I lost some of my
>> Well, yeah, of course.
Baby fat.
I mean...
>> Well, yeah, of course.
Y-you looked great in high
I mean...
school, but...
Y-you looked great in high
You look even better now.
School, but...
>> Thanks.
You look even better now.
You look good, too...
>> Thanks.
Especially on that first tee.
You look good, too...
Wow.
Especially on that first tee.
So, how is it that you ended up
wow.
in L.A. franchising restaurants?
So, how is it that you ended up
>> Oh.
In L.A. franchising restaurants?
Um...
>> Oh.
I was in New York for seven
um...
years playing the market.
I was in New York for seven
I did okay, but then, like
years playing the market.
everyone else, when the market
I did okay, but then, like
crashed, I lost my shirt, so I
everyone else, when the market
decided to move to L.A. and
crashed, I lost my shirt, so I
start fresh.
Decided to move to L.A. and
My buddy Scott askey -- you
start fresh.
remember Scotty?
My buddy Scott askey -- you
>> Mm-hmm.
Remember Scotty?
>> Yeah, he -- he decided to put
>> mm-hmm.
me up until I could get back on
>> yeah, he -- he decided to put
my feet.
Me up until I could get back on
>> Mm. Guess Scotty and I share
my feet.
something -- getting you back on
>> mm. Guess Scotty and I share
your feet.
Something -- getting you back on
It's funny how we ended up being
your feet.
neighbors again.
It's funny how we ended up being
>> Well, I live in the Fairfax
neighbors again.
district.
>> Well, I live in the Fairfax
I'm guessing you're more of a
district.
Beverly hills, malibu girl.
So, Alex birch now, huh?
Wow. That is just...
Is your husband here with you?
>> My ex-husband.
Frankly, I don't know where
>> my ex-husband.
he is.
Frankly, I don't know where
I don't like the word
he is.
"divorcée," so I like to refer
I don't like the word
to myself as a free bird.
"Divorcée," so I like to refer
And you?
To myself as a free bird.
>> Uh, married.
And you?
Four months ago.
>> Uh, married.
>> Congrats.
Four months ago.
Is she here?
>> Congrats.
I'd love to meet her.
Is she here?
>> No. I came alone.
I'd love to meet her.
This is a business trip, after
>> no. I came alone.
all.
This is a business trip, after
Though, given our history, I
all.
don't know if this is such a
though, given our history, I
good idea.
Don't know if this is such a
>> You still haven't forgiven
good idea.
me.
>> You still haven't forgiven
Look, um, maybe I can make it up
me.
to you now.
Look, um, maybe I can make it up
Join me for dinner.
To you now.
I will order something extra
join me for dinner.
special -- corn dogs with a side
I will order something extra
of Mac and cheese.
Special -- corn dogs with a side
>> You remember that?
Of Mac and cheese.
>> You'd be surprised by what
>> you remember that?
else I remember.
>> You'd be surprised by what
Hey, um, I was gonna go to a
else I remember.
club tonight to see some jazz.
Hey, um, I was gonna go to a
You want to come with me?
Club tonight to see some jazz.
>> Yes.
You want to come with me?
Who says no to jazz?
[ Jazz music playing ]
[ Ringtone plays ]
[ Ringing stops ]
>> So...
How many do you want?
>> What?
>> How many franchise branches
>> what?
do you want?
>> How many franchise branches
>> Oh. Um...
Do you want?
Well, our initial roll-out plan
>> oh. Um...
was to have 25 in 5 years.
Well, our initial roll-out plan
>> How about 50 in 3 years?
Was to have 25 in 5 years.
>> What would be the terms?
>> How about 50 in 3 years?
>> If you can stay, we can work
>> what would be the terms?
out the details over the next
>> if you can stay, we can work
few days.
Out the details over the next
>> I don't know what to say.
Few days.
>> You could say no.
[ Soft music playing ]
>> Who told you to change
partners?
Alex, you're supposed to be with
Steve, Mike with Kimberly.
And no head on chest.
>> But she asked my permission.
>> You could say no.
>> Why would I?
I love her.
[ laughter ]
[ Jazz music playing ]
[ Ringtone playing ]
>> Hey, babe.
>> Hi! What's going on?
It's Scott and Dylan.
We've been trying to reach you.
>> What's up, man?
>> Oh. Yeah.
I'm good.
Everything's good here.
Just, uh...Working on the deal.
>> You sound awful.
Are you getting enough sleep?
>> Not really.
Uh, wheelin' and dealin' is --
>> not really.
it is hard work.
Uh, wheelin' and dealin' is --
>> Okay. Wheelin' and dealin'.
It is hard work.
Listen -- I got a couple
>> okay. Wheelin' and dealin'.
questions, man, I wanted to go
listen -- I got a couple
over with you before the
questions, man, I wanted to go
meeting.
Over with you before the
What time is the meeting?
Meeting.
>> It's finished.
What time is the meeting?
>> Damn it!
>> It's finished.
Mike, why didn't you call me
>> damn it!
before you screwed everything
Mike, why didn't you call me
up, man?
Before you screwed everything
>> Dude, chill out, okay?
Up, man?
[ breathes deeply ]
>> Dude, chill out, okay?
I nailed it.
[ Breathes deeply ]
Guess what -- we got
I nailed it.
50 branches.
Guess what -- we got
>> We got 50 branches?
50 branches.
All right, what's the catch,
>> we got 50 branches?
Mike?
All right, what's the catch,
>> No catch.
Mike?
I just got to stay here for a
>> no catch.
couple more days and finalize
I just got to stay here for a
the details.
Couple more days and finalize
>> That's unbelievable!
The details.
That's fanta--
>> that's unbelievable!
how did you talk her into that?
That's fanta--
>> I will tell you all about
how did you talk her into that?
that when I get back.
>> I will tell you all about
>> When are you back?
That when I get back.
>> When are you coming back?
>> When are you back?
I miss you.
>> When are you coming back?
>> Okay, yeah, I miss you, too.
I miss you.
Um, I got to go.
>> Okay, yeah, I miss you, too.
There is a meeting.
Um, I got to go.
It is urgent, okay?
There is a meeting.
I'll talk to you later.
It is urgent, okay?
Bye.
I'll talk to you later.
[ cellphone beeps ]
Bye.
>> Cheers.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
>> We did it.
>> Cheers.
>> Good morning, lazy bum.
>> We did it.
>> Morning.
>> Good morning, lazy bum.
>> Who was that?
>> Morning.
The wife?
>> Who was that?
>> No.
The wife?
Yeah. It -- it was, and Scotty.
>> No.
>> Come on.
Yeah. It -- it was, and Scotty.
Let's beat everyone to the
>> come on.
links.
Let's beat everyone to the
>> I'm not exactly a match for
links.
you.
>> I'm not exactly a match for
I mean, I'm a beginner at this.
You.
>> Remember when you taught me
I mean, I'm a beginner at this.
how to dance?
>> Remember when you taught me
I used to trip all over the
how to dance?
floor?
I used to trip all over the
Well, it's payback time.
Floor?
Come on. Go -- get dressed.
Well, it's payback time.
[ rock music plays ]
Come on. Go -- get dressed.
>> ♪ I didn't see it
[ rock music plays ]
♪ I didn't see it coming
>> ♪ I didn't see it
♪ I can't believe it
♪ I didn't see it coming
♪ it's really stunning
♪ I can't believe it
♪ and now I feel so strong
♪ it's really stunning
♪ it's been way too long
♪ and now I feel so strong
♪ I just remember that I forgot
♪ it's been way too long
about you ♪
♪ I just remember that I forgot
♪ oh, this feelin'
about you ♪
♪ I've been rediscovered
♪ oh, this feelin'
♪ it's got me breathin'
♪ I've been rediscovered
♪ like a teenage lover
♪ it's got me breathin'
♪ and it feels so right
♪ like a teenage lover
♪ better hold on,
♪ and it feels so right
hold on tight ♪
♪ better hold on,
♪ I just remember that I forgot
hold on tight ♪
about you ♪
♪ I just remember that I forgot
♪ I just remembered
about you ♪
♪ oh, you'd come back to me
♪ I just remembered
>> let's go drink.
♪ Oh, you'd come back to me
[ cheers and applause ]
>> Let's go drink.
>> Whoo!
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Come on!
>> Whoo!
>> Let's see what you've got.
>> Come on!
>> All right, here we go.
>> Let's see what you've got.
That's one. That's one!
>> All right, here we go.
>> Yeah!
That's one. That's one!
>> Let's go! Come on!
>> Yeah!
Three.
>> Let's go! Come on!
>> Come on! You got it!
Three.
>> Yeah!
>> Come on! You got it!
Whoo!
>> Yeah!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Whoo!
>> Oh! In your face!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on. You ready?
>> Oh! In your face!
Here we go.
Come on. You ready?
>> Whoo!
Here we go.
>> [ laughs ]
>> Whoo!
>> [ Laughs ]
>> Come on! You can do it!
>> Whoo!
Come on, baby!
>> Come on! You can do it!
>> Aah! Two!
Come on, baby!
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> Aah! Two!
Whoo!
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
>> Aah!
Whoo!
>> One more! One more!
>> Aah!
>> Aaaaaaah!
>> One more! One more!
Aah!
>> Aaaaaaah!
Br-br-br-br-br-br-br-br-br!
Aah!
Here we go! Aah!
Br-br-br-br-br-br-br-br-br!
[ cheers and applause ]
Here we go! Aah!
Whoo!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Yeah!
Whoo!
>> One more! One more!
Yeah!
One more! One more!
>> One more! One more!
>> All: Go, go, go, go, go, go,
one more! One more!
go, go, go, go!
>> All: Go, go, go, go, go, go,
[ cheers and applause ]
Go, go, go, go!
>> ♪ I just remember that I
[ cheers and applause ]
forget about you ♪
>> ♪ I just remember that I
♪ I just remember that I forgot
forget about you ♪
about you ♪
♪ I just remember that I forgot
>> well, if your flight was at
about you ♪
3:00, I could've dropped you off
>> well, if your flight was at
at the airport.
3:00, I could've dropped you off
>> I know, I know.
At the airport.
You got to run.
>> I know, I know.
Tournament's about to start.
You got to run.
>> If you wait until Monday, we
tournament's about to start.
could go together.
>> If you wait until Monday, we
>> I have to report back to my
could go together.
boss before I get fired.
>> I have to report back to my
>> I understand.
Boss before I get fired.
I really enjoyed our time
>> I understand.
together.
I really enjoyed our time
>> Me too.
Together.
I'll see you in L.A.?
Mwah.
[ engine turns over ]
>> Dude, you look like shit.
>> Nice to see you, too.
>> Did you get the l.O.I.
Signed?
>> Not yet.
>> Bro, you know how iffy these
>> not yet.
deals can be.
>> Bro, you know how iffy these
You said you had it in the bag.
Deals can be.
>> Dude, relax.
You said you had it in the bag.
The deal is locked in.
>> Dude, relax.
>> What makes you so sure?
The deal is locked in.
>> I found a shortcut.
You know their c.E.O.,
Alex birch?
Her maiden name is
Alex roverson.
>> Alex...
Alex roverson?
The prom queen who went missing
>> Mm-hmm.
Alex roverson?
>> You got to be kidding me.
>> Mm-hmm.
So, why didn't you get the
>> you got to be kidding me.
l.O.I. Signed again?
So, why didn't you get the
>> Alex is coming to the
l.O.I. Signed again?
restaurant on Friday.
>> Alex is coming to the
I thought it'd be more official
restaurant on Friday.
that way.
I thought it'd be more official
>> Hmm.
That way.
So, if you weren't there closing
>> Hmm.
the deal, what were you doing
so, if you weren't there closing
there the whole time?
The deal, what were you doing
Hmm?
There the whole time?
>> We were just catching up on
Hmm?
things, you know, doing the
>> we were just catching up on
whole p.R. Game with her,
things, you know, doing the
telling her what a great
whole p.R. Game with her,
franchise lipnick's is gonna be.
Telling her what a great
>> Five days is a long time to
franchise lipnick's is gonna be.
talk.
>> Five days is a long time to
Did she tell you why she went
talk.
missing prom night?
Did she tell you why she went
Oh. Okay.
Missing prom night?
You know what?
Oh. Okay.
>> Wait. What are you doing?
You know what?
>> Rick.
>> Wait. What are you doing?
Yeah, look, can you set up the
>> Rick.
backup meetings for fresco and
yeah, look, can you set up the
k.C. And company?
Backup meetings for fresco and
>> Really?
K.C. And company?
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
Okay, thanks, man.
>> Yeah.
>> What are you doing?
Okay, thanks, man.
>> Yeah, I've been doing some
>> what are you doing?
talking, too, myself, all right?
>> Yeah, I've been doing some
Just in case.
Talking, too, myself, all right?
>> Dude, we have a deal.
Just in case.
>> I don't want a deal.
>> Dude, we have a deal.
I don't even think we should be
>> I don't want a deal.
doing business with her in the
I don't even think we should be
first place.
Doing business with her in the
>> Scotty, you worry too much.
First place.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Scotty, you worry too much.
I'm the idiot.
>> Yeah, yeah.
You're the optimist. I forgot.
>> Shit.
Does Alex really live there?
Dude, if I were you, I wouldn't
does Alex really live there?
dare go anywhere near her.
Dude, if I were you, I wouldn't
>> Yeah, Mike, I think you
dare go anywhere near her.
should really reconsider
>> yeah, Mike, I think you
Kimberly.
Should really reconsider
>> Dude, she probably thinks
Kimberly.
you're some millionaire's son
>> dude, she probably thinks
with all those boss shirts
you're some millionaire's son
you've been borrowing from
with all those boss shirts
Scott.
You've been borrowing from
Those boss shirts that I've been
Scott.
borrowing from Scott don't even
those boss shirts that I've been
make Scott look like a
borrowing from Scott don't even
millionaire, dude.
Make Scott look like a
You guys are just jealous.
Millionaire, dude.
I'm an optimist, all right?
You guys are just jealous.
I look at the brighter side of
I'm an optimist, all right?
things.
I look at the brighter side of
Okay?
Things.
Bye-bye.
Okay?
>> You want us to wait?
Bye-bye.
>> No.
>> You want us to wait?
Alex said we'll take her limo.
>> No.
>> [ laughs ]
Alex said we'll take her limo.
>> Okay. Let's go.
>> [ Laughs ]
>> No, wait a sec.
>> I'm here to pick up Alex.
She's expecting me.
Tux, corsage, prom date.
>> You're mistaken, young man.
Miss Alex has left for the
>> you're mistaken, young man.
weekend.
Miss Alex has left for the
>> Ho-ho.
Weekend.
Come on, big guy.
>> Ho-ho.
No, we, uh -- we have a date.
Come on, big guy.
Sir, I mean, it's prom.
No, we, uh -- we have a date.
She -- she can't be gone.
Sir, I mean, it's prom.
She has to be here.
She -- she can't be gone.
So can you call her down here so
she has to be here.
I can talk to her?
So can you call her down here so
>> Are you implying that I've
I can talk to her?
lied to you?
>> Are you implying that I've
>> No. No, no, no.
Lied to you?
Just -- just that there's
>> no. No, no, no.
apparently a misunderstanding.
Just -- just that there's
Is there someone else that I can
apparently a misunderstanding.
talk to, like how about the
is there someone else that I can
driver?
Talk to, like how about the
I mean, he must know her plans.
Driver?
>> I'm the limo driver.
I mean, he must know her plans.
>> What?
>> I'm the limo driver.
How do you guard the house and
>> what?
drive at the same --
how do you guard the house and
>> it's none of your business
drive at the same --
what I do.
>> It's none of your business
Now you need to leave.
What I do.
You can do that the easy or the
now you need to leave.
hard way.
You can do that the easy or the
I strongly suggest the easy way.
Hard way.
Up to you.
I strongly suggest the easy way.
[ gate rattling ]
[ Fingers click ]
>> Where you going?
>> Alex! Alex!
Alex!
>> Give him to me.
>> Alex, come outside!
Come outside right now!
I'm here to pick you up!
Alex!
Unh!
Okay. All right.
Alex!
Ow! Aah!
Alex, come outside!
Alex, I'm here to pick you up!
I have your corsage!
It's purple!
It matches my tie!
Alex!
[ car door closes ]
>> You okay?
[ Car door closes ]
>> Yeah.
>> No! Stop!
>> What?
>> Shit.
Sorry, honey.
I was just having a bad dream.
Hey, wifey.
>> Hi, hubby.
Hi.
>> You're jet-lagged like you
went to Europe or something.
Look at that picture there.
>> Don't worry.
One day, lipnick's is gonna have
>> don't worry.
all the magazine ads.
One day, lipnick's is gonna have
>> I'm not talking about that
all the magazine ads.
one.
>> I'm not talking about that
The one to the right of it.
One.
>> That magazine went out of
the one to the right of it.
business.
>> That magazine went out of
They're gonna be gone within a
business.
month.
They're gonna be gone within a
>> Can you stop talking about
month.
business?
>> Can you stop talking about
I'm talking about family.
Business?
>> Of course.
I'm talking about family.
I'm talking about family, too.
>> Of course.
I am talking about our
I'm talking about family, too.
family's...Future.
I am talking about our
>> Oh.
Family's...Future.
I want to have twins just like
>> oh.
that -- one that looks like you
I want to have twins just like
and one that looks like me.
That -- one that looks like you
Identical twins are so boring.
>> I'm sorry.
>> What do you mean?
>> I kind of wasted your money,
>> what do you mean?
I think.
>> I kind of wasted your money,
I don't think there's gonna be a
I think.
deal.
I don't think there's gonna be a
But there are other companies
deal.
we're gonna go to.
But there are other companies
I know a whole bunch of people
we're gonna go to.
we can talk to.
I know a whole bunch of people
>> Relax.
We can talk to.
You don't have to.
>> Relax.
Let's just be happy with what we
you don't have to.
have.
Mm.
I missed you.
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> How much?
>> A lot.
>> Really?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Hey.
Evening, madam.
Welcome to lipnick's.
Table for two?
>> Just one.
>> Come with me.
Your waitress will be right with
you.
>> I suppose you're Dylan?
You.
>> Yeah.
>> I suppose you're Dylan?
Have we met before?
>> Yeah.
>> Alex -- Alex birch.
Have we met before?
>> Oh. Hi.
>> Alex -- Alex birch.
It's so nice to meet you.
>> Oh. Hi.
>> Nice to meet you, as well.
It's so nice to meet you.
>> Hey, Alex.
>> Nice to meet you, as well.
>> Hey.
>> Hey, Alex.
>> Wow. What a surprise.
>> Hey.
Uh, this is -- this is my wife,
>> wow. What a surprise.
Dylan.
Uh, this is -- this is my wife,
Dylan, this is, uh...Alex birch.
Dylan.
>> I got it.
Dylan, this is, uh...Alex birch.
>> She's the c.E.O. Of
>> I got it.
girthan's --
>> she's the c.E.O. Of
>> I am just an old High School
girthan's --
classmate.
>> I am just an old High School
>> Mm-hmm.
Classmate.
>> Yeah.
>> Mm-hmm.
Mike told me.
>> Yeah.
Um, please make yourself
Mike told me.
comfortable, and welcome.
Um, please make yourself
>> Thank you.
She's beautiful.
[ breathes deeply ]
Why'd you go to fresco?
[ Breathes deeply ]
They're my main competitors.
Why'd you go to fresco?
>> Uh, I -- I talked to, um,
they're my main competitors.
some of the -- some of the --
>> uh, I -- I talked to, um,
some of my partners, and, um...
Some of the -- some of the --
Well, they were -- they were
some of my partners, and, um...
afraid of a conflict of
well, they were -- they were
interest.
Afraid of a conflict of
>> Mike, cut the bullshit.
Interest.
You don't trust me, do you?
>> What's this?
>> Proof of trust.
Cash it anytime you see a red
>> proof of trust.
flag.
Cash it anytime you see a red
So come by my office, sign the
flag.
contract, and let's finalize
so come by my office, sign the
this deal once and for all.
[ Engine turns over ]
>> Would you put that back in
our pocket, Mike?
That's a lot of fucking money.
Our pocket, Mike?
By the way, I think I'm really
that's a lot of fucking money.
starting to like Alex.
By the way, I think I'm really
>> You can't get a better proof
starting to like Alex.
of trust than that check.
>> You can't get a better proof
>> Okay. So what exactly do you
of trust than that check.
know about the divorce?
>> Okay. So what exactly do you
>> Nothing other than the fact
know about the divorce?
that she just had a rough time.
>> Nothing other than the fact
>> Okay, well, I heard
that she just had a rough time.
differently at the reunion last
>> okay, well, I heard
year.
Differently at the reunion last
Apparently, she dumped the guy
year.
after one year and ended up with
apparently, she dumped the guy
most of his money.
After one year and ended up with
>> You know what?
Most of his money.
That's probably just a lot of
>> you know what?
people talking smack.
That's probably just a lot of
>> You know, I don't really
people talking smack.
care, Mike.
>> You know, I don't really
I just want to know.
Care, Mike.
Is there anything between you
I just want to know.
two?
Is there anything between you
Dude, we all worked hard on
two?
this.
Dude, we all worked hard on
>> Damn it, Scott, are you not
this.
seeing the frickin' value in a
>> damn it, Scott, are you not
million-dollar check?
Seeing the frickin' value in a
All those zer--
million-dollar check?
are you kidding me? Really?
All those zer--
>> You know what?
Are you kidding me? Really?
I'm not letting this come
>> you know what?
between us.
I'm not letting this come
I'm just returning it.
Between us.
>> What?
I'm just returning it.
Can you -- can I...
>> What?
Just hold it one last time?
Can you -- can I...
>> Hey.
Just hold it one last time?
There will be plenty to hold in
>> hey.
the future, buddy.
>> Fuck!
>> You.
>> Who are you, sir?
You look familiar.
>> Yeah, so do you.
You remind me of some a-hole
>> yeah, so do you.
back in punkton, Kansas, when I
you remind me of some a-hole
was a kid.
Back in punkton, Kansas, when I
>> Oh, yeah, I remember you.
Was a kid.
Sorry, kid.
>> Oh, yeah, I remember you.
I mean "sir."
Sorry, kid.
I was just doing my job.
I mean "sir."
Come on in.
I was just doing my job.
You still pissed at me?
>> You know, if you'd have been
4 inches shorter back then, I
would have taught you some
manners.
Would have taught you some
>> You know, she was home that
manners.
night.
>> You know, she was home that
>> She lied to me?
Night.
>> I lied.
>> She lied to me?
She cried in her room for days,
>> I lied.
maybe weeks.
She cried in her room for days,
Baby girl was in some major
maybe weeks.
pain.
Baby girl was in some major
Seems boss man had some sort of
pain.
stick up his ass about your
seems boss man had some sort of
family being too -- too common.
Stick up his ass about your
She doesn't like to receive
family being too -- too common.
greetings on her birthday these
she doesn't like to receive
days.
Greetings on her birthday these
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Days.
Today's her birthday?
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa.
>> You didn't know?
Today's her birthday?
Then why are you here?
>> You didn't know?
>> Shit.
Then why are you here?
I should've brought a gift.
Holy shit.
>> I know.
>> Who else lives here with her?
>> Just her.
This way.
No hard feelings, sir?
Carry on.
[ Soft music playing ]
>> Hi.
[ indistinct singing ]
Happy birthday.
>> Thanks.
>> Why don't you come down to
>> thanks.
lipnick's?
>> Why don't you come down to
We'll make you a nice birthday
lipnick's?
meal.
We'll make you a nice birthday
>> I want to be alone, Mike.
Meal.
I think I deserve that.
>> I want to be alone, Mike.
>> Oh, come on.
I think I deserve that.
Don't be like that.
>> Oh, come on.
>> Can you...
Don't be like that.
Never mind.
>> Can you...
>> What?
Never mind.
>> Can you spare, like, three
>> what?
hours for me?
>> Can you spare, like, three
No one else?
Hours for me?
I promise -- no business.
I didn't think so.
>> Okay.
What do you want to do?
Can you hear me?!
Now can you hear me?
>> Yes, I can.
[ chuckles ]
>> Holy cow!
Wow.
This was your husband's?
>> No. It was my family's.
But it's mine now that my dad's
>> no. It was my family's.
passed away.
But it's mine now that my dad's
>> Wow.
Passed away.
>> Actually, I've got some
>> wow.
clothes for you, if you want to
>> actually, I've got some
change.
Clothes for you, if you want to
>> [ chuckles ]
Change.
>> Right through there.
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> [ chuckles ]
>> Hi.
>> Here you go.
Is there anything else I can do
for you, Ms. roverson?
>> No, thank you.
For you, Ms. roverson?
You can go home for the rest of
>> no, thank you.
the night.
You can go home for the rest of
>> Happy birthday.
The night.
>> Thanks.
You know, there's a movie
theater inside, and I have
"superman" all cued up and ready
to go.
"Superman" all cued up and ready
>> "Superman" -- wow.
To go.
That brings back memories.
>> "Superman" -- wow.
>> I know.
That brings back memories.
You watched it two times in a
>> I know.
row.
You watched it two times in a
>> At the drive-in.
Row.
How did you know that?
>> At the drive-in.
>> I was there...
How did you know that?
In the last row...
>> I was there...
Watching you.
In the last row...
I came there because I wanted to
watching you.
say goodbye, and I wanted to
I came there because I wanted to
apologize, but...
Say goodbye, and I wanted to
I wasn't allowed to.
Apologize, but...
I tried every excuse in the book
I wasn't allowed to.
to sneak out of that car and
I tried every excuse in the book
come see you, but the driver
to sneak out of that car and
wouldn't let me.
Come see you, but the driver
My dad's orders.
To superman.
>> Truth, justice, and the
American way.
>> [ chuckles ]
You remember that scene when
he's able to spin the earth
you remember that scene when
backwards?
He's able to spin the earth
>> Yeah.
Backwards?
Sometimes I wish I could spin
>> yeah.
the world back 13 years, you
sometimes I wish I could spin
know?
The world back 13 years, you
>> Me too.
>> I -- I can't.
>> I understand.
>> I can't, but...
>> So, you gonna tell me where
you disappeared to last night?
>> Oh, um...
You disappeared to last night?
I thought I told you.
>> Oh, um...
I went to Alex's office.
I thought I told you.
>> Yeah, Scott told me, but I
I went to Alex's office.
thought that was yesterday
>> yeah, Scott told me, but I
afternoon.
Thought that was yesterday
>> Yeah.
Afternoon.
Yeah. You know what?
>> Yeah.
Yesterday was her birthday, and
yeah. You know what?
I didn't even know.
Yesterday was her birthday, and
Yeah, they had a big beach party
I didn't even know.
for her out at her house in
yeah, they had a big beach party
malibu.
For her out at her house in
I couldn't say no.
Malibu.
I was gonna call you, but --
I couldn't say no.
>> oh, that's fine.
I was gonna call you, but --
Just didn't want you to drink
>> oh, that's fine.
and drive.
Just didn't want you to drink
Just worried about you.
>> We had a very good meeting
with fresco.
You want to know the way I see
it?
All right, look, fresco made a
valid point -- we should start
all right, look, fresco made a
with five branches.
Valid point -- we should start
That way, we all get to bed on
with five branches.
time, we still reach our goal.
That way, we all get to bed on
>> Jesus, grandpa, what are you,
time, we still reach our goal.
80?
>> Jesus, grandpa, what are you,
We need to enter this thing with
80?
a big bang.
We need to enter this thing with
Can't leave room for lots of
a big bang.
little copycat's to start
can't leave room for lots of
popping up.
Little copycat's to start
>> Yeah, I don't even know why
popping up.
we took that meeting today.
>> Yeah, I don't even know why
I mean, we have a better deal at
we took that meeting today.
girthan's.
I mean, we have a better deal at
>> Thank you.
>> Did you fuck her?
>> Scotty.
>> Just checking.
>> Ha!
Ah.
>> Rick, could you give us a
ah.
minute?
>> Rick, could you give us a
Could you give us a minute,
minute?
please?
Could you give us a minute,
>> Got it.
Please?
>> Okay, look, I'm sorry.
>> Got it.
I shouldn't have said that.
>> Okay, look, I'm sorry.
But where were you last night,
I shouldn't have said that.
Mike?
But where were you last night,
Huh?
Mike?
>> Scotty, let's talk business,
huh?
okay?
>> Scotty, let's talk business,
No biases, no conflicts of
okay?
interest.
No biases, no conflicts of
She is giving us the deal of a
interest.
lifetime.
She is giving us the deal of a
>> I never disagreed with that.
Lifetime.
>> And for the record, she did
>> I never disagreed with that.
not stand me up at prom.
>> And for the record, she did
It was her dad, not her.
Not stand me up at prom.
>> Well, what happened to her
it was her dad, not her.
check?
>> Well, what happened to her
Did you return it?
>> Scott, Scotty, scottster...
Do not fuck this up.
Just let's look at it this way.
As long as we're making a pile
just let's look at it this way.
of cash, who really cares who
as long as we're making a pile
fucks who?
Of cash, who really cares who
>> Yeah, uh...
Fucks who?
>> Scotty...
>> Yeah, uh...
No goof-ups.
>> Scotty...
Trust me.
No goof-ups.
Yeah, I promise.
Trust me.
>> Well, I think the proposal is
yeah, I promise.
perfect as is, so I'm signing
>> well, I think the proposal is
off on it.
We have a deal.
>> We have a deal.
>> ♪ I think you know
♪ you know the truth
♪ you can see it in my eyes
>> that's coming up.
♪ You can see it in my eyes
>> That one.
>> That's coming up.
>> ♪ every time I look through
>> that one.
you ♪
>> ♪ every time I look through
[ Both laugh ]
You ♪
♪ it won't be long
[ both laugh ]
♪ a year, maybe two
♪ it won't be long
♪ till I'm coming to you
♪ a year, maybe two
♪ coming home to you
♪ till I'm coming to you
♪ there she is
♪ coming home to you
♪ the woman of the hour
♪ there she is
♪ so naive to all my scheming
♪ the woman of the hour
♪ so unaware of my power
♪ so naive to all my scheming
♪ she'll scratch and scream
♪ so unaware of my power
>> ♪ scratch and scream
♪ she'll scratch and scream
>> ♪ to keep me at bay
>> ♪ scratch and scream
♪ oh, but she can't keep
>> ♪ to keep me at bay
me away ♪
♪ oh, but she can't keep
♪ no, she can't keep me away
me away ♪
♪ you feel the spark
♪ no, she can't keep me away
♪ I know you do
♪ you feel the spark
♪ that embrace of one desire
♪ I know you do
[ Both breathing heavily ]
♪ That embrace of one desire
>> I love you.
[ Both breathing heavily ]
I want to spend the rest of my
>> I love you.
life with you.
I want to spend the rest of my
I feel like my life had passed
life with you.
me by until I saw you again.
I feel like my life had passed
I'm committed, Mike.
Me by until I saw you again.
I'm willing to be in this for
I'm committed, Mike.
the long haul.
I'm willing to be in this for
But it's up to you.
I'll wait until Christmas to
hear your answer.
>> I fuckin' knew it.
You playing with people's lives
again?
You...
Again?
You are a dangerous man to know,
you...
Mike.
You are a dangerous man to know,
>> I know. I'm sorry.
Mike.
[ sighs ]
>> I know. I'm sorry.
What do I tell Dylan?
[ Sighs ]
>> I'm not a freakin' counselor,
what do I tell Dylan?
Mike.
>> I'm not a freakin' counselor,
What kind of question is that?
Mike.
"Do I dump my wife before I
what kind of question is that?
close the deal?
"Do I dump my wife before I
Or do I close the deal, then
close the deal?
dump her?"
Or do I close the deal, then
>> Well, what would you do if
dump her?"
you were me?
>> Well, what would you do if
>> Me?
You were me?
>> I would've taken Kimberly to
>> me?
the prom 13 years ago, okay?
>> I would've taken Kimberly to
That's what I would've done.
The prom 13 years ago, okay?
>> Dude, come on, like...
That's what I would've done.
I really need your help.
>> Dude, come on, like...
You're my best friend.
I really need your help.
>> Why do you keep getting
you're my best friend.
yourself in the same situations
>> why do you keep getting
over and over?
Yourself in the same situations
Hmm?
Over and over?
You got a rich girl on one side
Hmm?
and a poor one on the other.
>> You calling me a gold digger?
>> I'll answer that later.
First, you tell me -- did you
sleep with her or not?
Oh, shit.
Do you love her?
Oh, shit!
>> What do I do?
>> How am I supposed to know?!
Remember, you're the one who
>> how am I supposed to know?!
looks at everything on the
remember, you're the one who
bright side.
Looks at everything on the
[ scoffs ]
Bright side.
Tell you what.
[ Scoffs ]
Do both women. Hmm?
Tell you what.
Do both women, keep the
do both women. Hmm?
franchise, and two helicopters,
do both women, keep the
too, Hmm?
Franchise, and two helicopters,
And I'll stay quiet for life.
Too, Hmm?
Know why?
And I'll stay quiet for life.
'Cause I'm your best -- I'm your
know why?
best friend.
'Cause I'm your best -- I'm your
>> You're drunk. Come on.
Best friend.
>> Let me go.
>> You're drunk. Come on.
You're the one that needs a
>> let me go.
hand.
You're the one that needs a
Finish that.
"Dearest Dylan.
I'm sorry I didn't have the guts
to tell you this in person.
I have so much gratitude for you
in my heart for all the love and
everything you and your family
have done for me.
Everything you and your family
But I haven't lived up to your
have done for me.
love.
But I haven't lived up to your
I have a confession.
Love.
I have fallen in love with Alex.
I have a confession.
Perhaps I've been in love with
I have fallen in love with Alex.
her my entire life.
Perhaps I've been in love with
She was my childhood sweetheart.
Her my entire life.
Until the past few months, to
she was my childhood sweetheart.
me, she was a dream unfulfilled.
Until the past few months, to
I recently found out that I was
me, she was a dream unfulfilled.
her dream, too.
I recently found out that I was
When we reconnected after such a
her dream, too.
long time, we instantly felt
when we reconnected after such a
that nothing between us has
long time, we instantly felt
changed with time.
That nothing between us has
In fact, our love has grown in
changed with time.
the last few weeks.
In fact, our love has grown in
If I deny these feelings, I'll
the last few weeks.
be a lousy husband cheating on a
if I deny these feelings, I'll
loyal, wonderful wife like you.
Be a lousy husband cheating on a
You deserve more.
Loyal, wonderful wife like you.
You deserve better.
You deserve more.
It is with sorrow that I am
you deserve better.
writing this to you to request a
it is with sorrow that I am
divorce...Hopefully one without
writing this to you to request a
too much animosity."
[ Brakes squealing ]
Okay.
>> He's here, he's here.
Mike's here.
>> He's here.
>> Wait, wait, wait!
You can't escape that easily.
Come on over here.
Come.
Come on.
Come in. Zits.
Sit.
So, now that we have our man,
sit.
let me say a few words.
So, now that we have our man,
As you all know, our beloved
let me say a few words.
Mike surprised us very much with
as you all know, our beloved
his unexpected jewishness and
Mike surprised us very much with
his total conversion.
His unexpected jewishness and
And recently, he surprised us
his total conversion.
with his lipnick's franchise
and recently, he surprised us
plan.
With his lipnick's franchise
He's a man of many surprises.
Plan.
So now it's our turn.
He's a man of many surprises.
Time to give Mike the surprise
so now it's our turn.
of his life, and when he hears
time to give Mike the surprise
this, believe me -- he won't
of his life, and when he hears
forget this day so long as he
this, believe me -- he won't
lives.
Forget this day so long as he
So, without further ado, I want
lives.
to announce today...
So, without further ado, I want
That...
To announce today...
I'm gonna be a
that...
great-grandfather!
I'm gonna be a
[ laughing ]
Great-grandfather!
A great-grandpa!
[ Laughing ]
Mazel tov!
A great-grandpa!
And Mike's gonna be a father!
Mazel tov!
Everybody, raise your glass.
And Mike's gonna be a father!
L'chaim! L'chaim.
Everybody, raise your glass.
What a mitzvah.
L'chaim! L'chaim.
Oh, look at them.
What a mitzvah.
What a couple.
Oh, look at them.
Oh, they're so beautiful.
What a couple.
Nice, beautiful jewish children
oh, they're so beautiful.
they're going to have.
Nice, beautiful jewish children
Oh, my.
They're going to have.
Mazel tov.
Oh, my.
Oh, oh, it's so wonderful.
Mazel tov.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, it's so wonderful.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
Oy. You'll have twins, maybe
oh, I'm so proud of you.
quintuplets.
Oy. You'll have twins, maybe
Oh, a bunch of little jewish
quintuplets.
babies running around!
Oh, a bunch of little jewish
>> Holy shit.
Babies running around!
Holy shit.
>> Holy shit.
Scotty.
Holy shit.
[ breathing heavily ]
Scotty.
Scotty, pick up.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Pick up, pick up.
Scotty, pick up.
>> Hey, dude, what's up?
Pick up, pick up.
>> She's pregnant.
>> Hey, dude, what's up?
>> Who?
>> She's pregnant.
>> What?
>> Who?
>> I'm sorry, but with you, I
>> what?
need to ask who.
>> I'm sorry, but with you, I
>> Dylan.
Need to ask who.
>> Holy shit.
>> Dylan.
>> Exactly.
>> Holy shit.
There's more.
>> Exactly.
>> Always.
There's more.
>> I sent an e-mail to her
>> always.
telling her about Alex.
>> I sent an e-mail to her
>> You sent an e-mail?
Telling her about Alex.
That's harsh.
>> You sent an e-mail?
>> Scotty, focus, okay?
That's harsh.
Focus.
>> Scotty, focus, okay?
Help now, judge later.
Focus.
I need you to call your tech
help now, judge later.
guys and ask them how to recover
I need you to call your tech
an e-mail.
Guys and ask them how to recover
>> Don't you know her password?
An e-mail.
>> No!
>> Don't you know her password?
>> Shit.
>> No!
Mike, there's no way to recall
>> shit.
an e-mail.
Mike, there's no way to recall
Trust me.
An e-mail.
>> Shit.
Trust me.
Shit.
>> Shit.
Okay.
Shit.
Okay, Mike.
Okay.
Get it together.
Okay, Mike.
Get it together, Mike.
Get it together.
Aah.
>> There's at least 50
aah.
restaurants here.
>> There's at least 50
>> I never, ever thought we'd be
restaurants here.
able to retire, but if this
>> I never, ever thought we'd be
works out, maybe we can.
Able to retire, but if this
Or at least cut back on our
works out, maybe we can.
hours.
Or at least cut back on our
>> Retire?
Hours.
Oh, sweetheart.
>> Retire?
We're not gonna retire.
Oh, sweetheart.
We're just gonna begin to live.
We're not gonna retire.
>> I got to go.
We're just gonna begin to live.
>> Okay. I'll see you at home.
I'll show them the rest.
>> All right, let's see.
He did this all himself.
[ soft music playing ]
>> ♪ You can say what you want
about me ♪
♪ it doesn't really matter
anyway ♪
♪ all alone here with memories
♪ I'm my own worst enemy
these days ♪
>> sorry.
Didn't mean to wake you up.
>> I wasn't sleeping.
>> I was at the office with
Scott, and then we went to
dinner, and --
>> it's okay.
Dinner, and --
Come on in.
>> It's okay.
I read your e-mail.
>> I'm sorry.
Okay? I...
I wouldn't have sent it if I had
okay? I...
known -- the news earlier.
I wouldn't have sent it if I had
>> So, you would have continued
known -- the news earlier.
to cheat on your wife?
>> So, you would have continued
For how long?
To cheat on your wife?
>> No. No, no.
For how long?
I -- I don't mean that.
>> No. No, no.
I just mean I would've waited
I -- I don't mean that.
for the -- the right time.
I just mean I would've waited
>> The right time.
For the -- the right time.
And when would that be?
>> The right time.
>> Dylan, I am sorry.
And when would that be?
Okay?
>> Dylan, I am sorry.
It's just I'm kind of in a
okay?
corner right now.
It's just I'm kind of in a
She wants to leave by Christmas,
corner right now.
and she wanted an answer before
she wants to leave by Christmas,
then.
And she wanted an answer before
>> Oh.
Then.
Oh, she does, does she?
>> Oh.
[ scoffs ]
Oh, she does, does she?
Okay.
[ Scoffs ]
Well, at first, I was upset.
Okay.
After I calmed myself down a
well, at first, I was upset.
bit, I thought about it.
After I calmed myself down a
I tried to be objective...
Bit, I thought about it.
Tried to understand where you
I tried to be objective...
were coming from.
Tried to understand where you
>> Thank you.
Were coming from.
>> And I've come to a decision.
>> Thank you.
>> The answer is no.
>> And I've come to a decision.
>> What?
>> The answer is no.
>> You heard me.
>> What?
No.
>> You heard me.
>> W-what do you mean "no"?
No.
No to what?
>> W-what do you mean "no"?
>> To a divorce.
No to what?
No.
>> To a divorce.
>> I understand where you're
no.
coming from.
>> I understand where you're
Okay, knowing what we know now,
coming from.
I'm not gonna insist on it right
okay, knowing what we know now,
away, obviously.
I'm not gonna insist on it right
>> No. Not by tomorrow, not by
away, obviously.
Christmas, not by any deadline
>> no. Not by tomorrow, not by
she may give you.
Christmas, not by any deadline
I'm not signing divorce papers
she may give you.
for you ever in my life, period.
I'm not signing divorce papers
Good night.
>> So, you have to go by
Christmas?
>> Look, I understand your
dilemma, Mike.
Just let me go.
Dilemma, Mike.
Be with her.
Just let me go.
I'm not gonna force you into
be with her.
anything.
I'm not gonna force you into
And don't worry.
Anything.
I'm not gonna back out of the
and don't worry.
franchise deal.
I'm not gonna back out of the
>> That's not what I'm worried
franchise deal.
about.
>> That's not what I'm worried
She's pregnant.
>> Wow.
Congratulations.
That's exciting.
You are gonna be a great dad.
I hope your baby gets those
you are gonna be a great dad.
beautiful long eyelashes.
I hope your baby gets those
>> I wasn't ready for this.
Beautiful long eyelashes.
I don't want to lose you again,
>> I wasn't ready for this.
Alex.
I don't want to lose you again,
>> Okay.
Alex.
I can wait.
>> Okay.
How long do you think?
I can wait.
>> I'm afraid it may never
how long do you think?
happen.
>> I'm afraid it may never
>> Okay.
Happen.
Hey, it's all right, Mike.
>> Okay.
I just want you to be happy.
Hey, it's all right, Mike.
It's all right.
I just want you to be happy.
>> No, it's not me.
It's all right.
She said no -- no to the
>> no, it's not me.
divorce -- not now, not ever.
She said no -- no to the
>> Oh, my gosh.
Divorce -- not now, not ever.
She sounds like just like my
>> oh, my gosh.
ex-husband.
She sounds like just like my
He never wanted to let me go,
ex-husband.
either.
He never wanted to let me go,
That bloodsucking leech.
Either.
Should've known better than to
that bloodsucking leech.
sign that prenup.
Should've known better than to
So stupid.
Sign that prenup.
>> Never sign a prenuptial
so stupid.
agreement without reading it
>> never sign a prenuptial
carefully.
Agreement without reading it
There are so many snakes to bite
carefully.
you on the ass that the devil's
there are so many snakes to bite
pitchfork up the wazoo is gonna
you on the ass that the devil's
come as a welcome relief by
pitchfork up the wazoo is gonna
comparison.
Come as a welcome relief by
Scott, how could you not let me
comparison.
read this fucking bible?
Scott, how could you not let me
I would've done it for free!
Read this fucking bible?
And you!
I would've done it for free!
You -- how do you sign this
and you!
thing without giving it to me
you -- how do you sign this
first?!
Thing without giving it to me
All right. All right.
First?!
Here we go.
All right. All right.
Here we go, okay.
Here we go.
Here is the clause that's the
here we go, okay.
killer.
Here is the clause that's the
If you ask for a divorce, you
killer.
have to arrange a formal divorce
if you ask for a divorce, you
ceremony.
Have to arrange a formal divorce
Such ceremony must consist of
ceremony.
the guests attended the wedding
such ceremony must consist of
in the first place.
The guests attended the wedding
It has to take place in the same
in the first place.
wedding venue.
It has to take place in the same
The couple will wear the same
wedding venue.
attire from their wedding day,
the couple will wear the same
and only then is she legally
attire from their wedding day,
bound to sign your divorce
and only then is she legally
application.
Bound to sign your divorce
On top of that, you also have
application.
the burden of explaining your
on top of that, you also have
reasons for your divorce.
The burden of explaining your
The ceremony will be followed by
reasons for your divorce.
a lavish dinner and dancing,
the ceremony will be followed by
which will be paid for...
A lavish dinner and dancing,
By you.
In short, she's a genius.
[ laughing ]
She's got you by the balls.
[ Laughing ]
You're fucked.
She's got you by the balls.
[ laughing ]
You're fucked.
Welcome to the club.
[ Laughing ]
Although I have some good news.
Welcome to the club.
There's a 10% discount on the
although I have some good news.
people attending.
There's a 10% discount on the
[ laughing ]
People attending.
Good luck, buddy!
[ Laughing ]
[ laughing continue ]
Good luck, buddy!
>> Bastard.
[ Laughing continue ]
Con man.
>> Bastard.
He pulled the "I'll be jewish"
con man.
wool over our eyes.
He pulled the "I'll be jewish"
>> You mean your eyes.
Wool over our eyes.
I told you it wasn't a proper
>> you mean your eyes.
conversion.
I told you it wasn't a proper
>> Why would you let that
conversion.
bastard live in your place?
>> Why would you let that
Why don't you kick him out?
Bastard live in your place?
>> Grandpa!
Why don't you kick him out?
How does that help me?
>> Grandpa!
At least I'll have somebody to
how does that help me?
call 911 in case, God forbid,
at least I'll have somebody to
something happens to me in the
call 911 in case, God forbid,
middle of the night.
Something happens to me in the
>> Well, you move in with us.
Middle of the night.
We'll take care of you.
>> Well, you move in with us.
>> Why should you?
We'll take care of you.
It's his responsibility, too.
>> Why should you?
Nowadays, they say, "we are
it's his responsibility, too.
pregnant."
Nowadays, they say, "we are
Why should he have the easy way
pregnant."
out?
Why should he have the easy way
Let him do his share.
Out?
>> Having a baby is a bliss.
Let him do his share.
He doesn't deserve to be any
>> having a baby is a bliss.
part of it.
He doesn't deserve to be any
If I were you, I would kick him
part of it.
so far away that even his shadow
if I were you, I would kick him
couldn't touch that baby.
So far away that even his shadow
>> Enough!
Couldn't touch that baby.
25 years ago, you chased
>> enough!
delilah's father away with the
25 years ago, you chased
same attitude, and what was the
delilah's father away with the
result?
Same attitude, and what was the
He never even showed up for
result?
rachel's funeral.
He never even showed up for
And who suffered the most?
Rachel's funeral.
Delilah.
And who suffered the most?
This child has never even seen
delilah.
her father in her entire life.
This child has never even seen
I'm so sorry to bring this up
her father in her entire life.
now, honey.
I'm so sorry to bring this up
This is not our decision to
now, honey.
make.
>> It's Mike.
Wait, wait, please.
Let me talk to him now.
[ doorbell rings ]
[ Door opens ]
>> Hey, grandpa Paul.
>> Hi.
[ Sighs ]
>> I'm assuming Dylan told you.
>> Yes, she told us.
>> I just want to say I have the
>> yes, she told us.
highest regard for you and
>> I just want to say I have the
elaine.
Highest regard for you and
I think Dylan is a wonderful,
Elaine.
wonderful woman.
I think Dylan is a wonderful,
I truly love her.
Wonderful woman.
I really do.
I truly love her.
It's just, uh, you know,
i really do.
sometimes fate kind of plays
it's just, uh, you know,
tricks on you, and...
Sometimes fate kind of plays
I never thought I'd run into
tricks on you, and...
alex again in the rest of my
i never thought I'd run into
life, but...
Alex again in the rest of my
I did, and, unfortunately, it
life, but...
just kind of...
I did, and, unfortunately, it
Happened at the wrong time.
Just kind of...
>> What do you want from me?
Happened at the wrong time.
>> Dylan is not really of a
>> what do you want from me?
sound mind to listen to me, so I
>> Dylan is not really of a
was wondering if you could talk
sound mind to listen to me, so I
to her and get her to sign these
was wondering if you could talk
papers.
To her and get her to sign these
If you do, we can just avoid the
papers.
whole prenup and just...
If you do, we can just avoid the
Move on.
Whole prenup and just...
>> My granddaughter never cared
move on.
for my advice, even when she was
>> my granddaughter never cared
choosing a spouse.
For my advice, even when she was
But don't be discouraged.
Choosing a spouse.
I'll do my very best to help you
but don't be discouraged.
out with your divorce.
I'll do my very best to help you
Living together after this isn't
out with your divorce.
good for anyone.
Living together after this isn't
Wait.
Good for anyone.
>> And, you know, I will do my
wait.
best to work on the franchise.
[ Door opens ]
Oh. Is this the prenup?
I already have a copy.
>> No, it's the guest list from
i already have a copy.
your wedding.
>> No, it's the guest list from
>> I thought you said you were
your wedding.
gonna help me.
>> I thought you said you were
>> I just did.
Gonna help me.
I'm now officially butting out
>> I just did.
of your lives.
I'm now officially butting out
Good luck.
>> Honey, you're going about
this all the wrong way.
Stop thinking of this as just
your divorce and start thinking
stop thinking of this as just
of this as a celebration of our
your divorce and start thinking
lives together.
Of this as a celebration of our
Start having fun with it, and if
lives together.
you do, then the guests will be
start having fun with it, and if
more likely to come.
You do, then the guests will be
Just think about it.
More likely to come.
How many divorceés will ever
just think about it.
have this kind of an
how many divorceés will ever
opportunity?
Have this kind of an
[ upbeat music plays ]
>> ♪ Free, free, love for sale
♪ I'm free, free
♪ out on bail
♪ out of jail
♪ I'm free, free
♪ and the grass grows greener
♪ out of jail
way up the hill ♪
♪ and the grass grows greener
>> ♪ I'm free, free
way up the hill ♪
♪ cheers to you
>> ♪ I'm free, free
♪ I'm free, free
♪ cheers to you
♪ so are you
♪ I'm free, free
>> good luck.
♪ So are you
>> ♪ and I won't be coming home
>> good luck.
anytime soon ♪
>> ♪ and I won't be coming home
>> ♪ I'm free, free
anytime soon ♪
♪ love for sale
>> ♪ I'm free, free
♪ I'm free, free
♪ love for sale
♪ out on bail
♪ I'm free, free
♪ out of jail
♪ and the grass grows greener
way up the hill ♪
>> every day, every hour you're
on the road.
>> Every day, every hour you're
It's a carmaggeddon for you,
on the road.
dick.
It's a carmaggeddon for you,
>> Don't call him that near my
dick.
school, mom!
>> Don't call him that near my
>> Be quiet.
School, mom!
Mommy and daddy are talking.
>> Be quiet.
>> It doesn't mean you can take
mommy and daddy are talking.
away my day with him.
>> It doesn't mean you can take
>> No?
Away my day with him.
>> No.
>> No?
>> ♪ and I'm free, free, free
>> no.
>> ♪ love for sale
>> ♪ and I'm free, free, free
♪ I'm free, free
>> ♪ love for sale
♪ out on bail
♪ I'm free, free
♪ out of jail
♪ and the grass grows greener
way up the hill ♪
>> ♪ I'm free, free
♪ cheers to you
♪ I'm free, free
♪ so are you
>> [ Laughing ]
♪ So are you
This is hilarious!
>> [ Laughing ]
[ laughs ]
This is hilarious!
Oh, you got to accept this funny
[ laughs ]
gift.
Oh, you got to accept this funny
>> Hi. Come to my divorce.
Gift.
You are coming to my divorce.
>> Hi. Come to my divorce.
Divorce ceremony.
You are coming to my divorce.
Henley's only, okay?
Divorce ceremony.
>> What the fuck?
Henley's only, okay?
Who the fuck are you?
>> What the fuck?
Some high-school friend?
Who the fuck are you?
Some college roommate?
Some high-school friend?
Who the fuck is this, Brad?
Some college roommate?
>> Honey, I have no idea.
Who the fuck is this, Brad?
I swear to God, I don't even
>> honey, I have no idea.
know who this idiot is.
I swear to God, I don't even
>> Brad, it's me --
know who this idiot is.
mike Christian.
>> Brad, it's me --
I'm Dylan lipnick's husband.
Mike Christian.
>> Oh! Oh, yeah!
I'm Dylan lipnick's husband.
>> So you do know him!
>> Oh! Oh, yeah!
Did you just lie to me?
>> So you do know him!
>> I mean -- I don't exactly
did you just lie to me?
know --
>> I mean -- I don't exactly
>> fuck you!
Know --
How dare you fucking lie to me
>> fuck you!
on my fucking wedding day before
how dare you fucking lie to me
my fucking honeymoon?!
On my fucking wedding day before
>> Ohh!
My fucking honeymoon?!
>> Aah!
>> Ohh!
>> So, a young jewish couple
>> aah!
gets successfully divorced, but
>> so, a young jewish couple
the wife says to the judge, "now
gets successfully divorced, but
I have to apply for a get."
The wife says to the judge, "now
And the judge says, "get what?"
I have to apply for a get."
She says, "no, that's the name
and the judge says, "get what?"
for a jewish ceremony which is
she says, "no, that's the name
for a divorce."
For a jewish ceremony which is
And he says, "oh, I understand.
For a divorce."
In other words, you mean like a
and he says, "oh, I understand.
bris."
In other words, you mean like a
She says, "yes, except that in a
bris."
bris, it's one thing.
She says, "yes, except that in a
In a get, you get to get rid of
bris, it's one thing.
the entire schmuck."
In a get, you get to get rid of
[ laughter ]
The entire schmuck."
>> Hey, there.
[ Laughter ]
You and me -- divorce ceremony.
>> Hey, there.
Thanks.
You and me -- divorce ceremony.
Come here.
Thanks.
>> Look what he brings me -- a
come here.
divorce invitation.
>> Look what he brings me -- a
>> ♪ I'm free, free
divorce invitation.
♪ cheers to you
>> ♪ I'm free, free
♪ I'm free, free
♪ cheers to you
♪ so are you
♪ I'm free, free
>> hi.
♪ So are you
I would like to invite you to my
>> hi.
divorce.
I would like to invite you to my
>> Is it true you're actually
divorce.
seeking a divorce from Dylan?
>> Is it true you're actually
>> Uh...No comment.
Seeking a divorce from Dylan?
>> ♪ oh, I'm free
>> uh...No comment.
♪ free
>> ♪ oh, I'm free
♪ free, free
♪ free
♪ cheers to you
♪ free, free
♪ I'm free, free
♪ cheers to you
♪ so are you
♪ I'm free, free
♪ skies are blue
♪ and I won't be coming home
anytime soon ♪
>> you are coming to my divorce.
Anytime soon ♪
Be there.
>> You are coming to my divorce.
Hey, Paul and Amber.
Be there.
Divorce invitation.
Hey, Paul and Amber.
I'll see you there, okay?
>> Oh, my God! It's Mike!
Oh, my God! Mike!
I'm so happy you're here!
I was hoping that you were gonna
come.
I saw you on the cover of that
one magazine.
Is this for me?
One magazine.
>> You're coming to my divorce.
Is this for me?
See you there.
>> You're coming to my divorce.
>> Okay.
See you there.
>> I actually think I'm gonna
>> okay.
bring a plus-one because I
>> I actually think I'm gonna
didn't bring anyone the last
bring a plus-one because I
time.
Didn't bring anyone the last
>> Joseph Armstrong in the
time.
house!
>> Joseph Armstrong in the
>> That's because there wasn't
house!
an open bar, but this time, I
>> that's because there wasn't
think there's going to be.
An open bar, but this time, I
You know what I mean?
Think there's going to be.
>> And I'm done!
You know what I mean?
That's it!
>> According to the prenuptial
agreement, it is incumbent upon
the person who initiated the
divorce to invite all of those
who attended the original
wedding -- minus 10%.
Who attended the original
Mr. Christian has done this
wedding -- minus 10%.
successfully.
Mr. Christian has done this
As decreed in the prenuptial
successfully.
agreement, Mrs. Christian must
as decreed in the prenuptial
sign the divorce petition.
>> Well...
It feels weird to be offering
congratulations to you, Mike.
I didn't think you could pull it
off.
I have never had such a strong
bond with anyone as I have with
you.
Bond with anyone as I have with
I have never been so in love.
You.
And I thought you felt the same
I have never been so in love.
way.
And I thought you felt the same
I guess I was wrong.
Way.
In the past few weeks, I've seen
I guess I was wrong.
how much trouble Mike has gone
in the past few weeks, I've seen
through to get all of you here
how much trouble Mike has gone
today.
Through to get all of you here
He has shown tremendous
today.
persistence to end this marriage
he has shown tremendous
and unite with Alex.
Persistence to end this marriage
Maybe that means she deserves
and unite with Alex.
him more than I do.
>> And now, according to the
prenuptial agreement...
Mr. Christian will reveal his
reasons for a divorce.
>> [ Clears throat ]
Thank you, Dylan.
And thank you, all, for coming
today and sparing your valuable
and thank you, all, for coming
time for me.
Today and sparing your valuable
Getting all you here was no easy
time for me.
task, I can assure you that.
Getting all you here was no easy
It was no fun having doors
task, I can assure you that.
slammed in my face, getting the
it was no fun having doors
evil eye on the street, being
slammed in my face, getting the
spat upon, punched in the face,
evil eye on the street, being
and told I am a horrible person
spat upon, punched in the face,
for deserting my pregnant wife.
And told I am a horrible person
This little...Event was not my
for deserting my pregnant wife.
idea.
This little...Event was not my
It all happened because Dylan
idea.
slipped a little clause in our
it all happened because Dylan
prenup...
Slipped a little clause in our
A clause I never bothered to
prenup...
read.
A clause I never bothered to
Otherwise, I never would have
read.
had to face this shit storm and
otherwise, I never would have
see all of you, but I did.
Had to face this shit storm and
And today, I am a winner...
See all of you, but I did.
[ applause ]
And today, I am a winner...
...A winner not just because I
[ applause ]
got my way, but because I made
...a winner not just because I
the journey.
Got my way, but because I made
I followed through on this.
The journey.
It was a journey of meeting
I followed through on this.
people, talking with them,
it was a journey of meeting
reasoning with some, arguing
people, talking with them,
with others, listening to their
reasoning with some, arguing
pains, their turmoils, their
with others, listening to their
successes, their failures, their
pains, their turmoils, their
mistakes and their regrets --
successes, their failures, their
their life lessons.
Mistakes and their regrets --
Now, I was mad at Dylan for
their life lessons.
making me come here today.
Now, I was mad at Dylan for
I thought she was a selfish,
making me come here today.
stubborn woman...
I thought she was a selfish,
Until I ran into a single mom
stubborn woman...
with five kids who asked me a
until I ran into a single mom
question.
With five kids who asked me a
She said, "what if Dylan had
question.
instigated the divorce?
She said, "what if Dylan had
Would she have to go through the
instigated the divorce?
same hell?"
Would she have to go through the
So, I read the prenup again,
same hell?"
and, sure as shit, she'd have to
so, I read the prenup again,
go through the same hell I did.
And, sure as shit, she'd have to
That's when I realized that this
go through the same hell I did.
clause wasn't evil after all.
That's when I realized that this
It was fair -- to both of us.
Clause wasn't evil after all.
And it was fair to our unborn
it was fair -- to both of us.
child that the parents aren't
and it was fair to our unborn
gonna just walk away from each
child that the parents aren't
other.
Gonna just walk away from each
I realized that this -- this
other.
long journey that I had to take
I realized that this -- this
was the perfect counseling for a
long journey that I had to take
torn, confused man like me.
Was the perfect counseling for a
When I put on this suit today, I
torn, confused man like me.
was reminded how I felt on my
when I put on this suit today, I
wedding day.
I've been thinking a lot about
the word "love" lately.
Love is a...
The word "love" lately.
Powerful emotion.
Love is a...
Love is this...
Powerful emotion.
Indescribable feeling you get
love is this...
when you see someone who you
indescribable feeling you get
know will do anything for you...
When you see someone who you
When you see someone with a life
know will do anything for you...
growing inside of them, a life
when you see someone with a life
you helped create.
Love is sticking it out.
Living with someone day after
day, waking up next to them
living with someone day after
every morning with their bad
day, waking up next to them
breath and their hair matted to
every morning with their bad
one side of their head, and you
breath and their hair matted to
just look at them and you think,
one side of their head, and you
"god, she's beautiful."
Just look at them and you think,
That's love.
"God, she's beautiful."
Dylan, I've given you every
that's love.
reason not to love me...
Dylan, I've given you every
And only one reason to.
Reason not to love me...
I love you.
And only one reason to.
You once said to me, you said,
I love you.
if only your thesis could change
you once said to me, you said,
one person...
If only your thesis could change
It did.
I'm sorry, Alex.
I have to do this.
So, in front of all of you...
I am begging you, Dylan, to
please forgive me for all the
pain that I have caused you.
Please forgive me for all the
Dylan, will you remarry me?
Pain that I have caused you.
>> Both: Yes!
Dylan, will you remarry me?
>> Yes.
>> Both: Yes!
>> Yes, but...
>> Yes.
You're gonna have to work for
>> yes, but...
it.
You're gonna have to work for
>> I promise.
It.
>> [ chuckles ]
>> I promise.
[ cheers and applause ]
[ Upbeat music plays ]
>> Mazel tov!
>> ♪ feels so good this
morning ♪
♪ I want to leap before I look
around ♪
♪ I know that I'm falling
♪ I think it's what this life's
about ♪
♪ what you say is infatuation
♪ call it passion
♪ no sin, no crime
♪ in fact, I'm truly grateful
♪ promise of love seems so
alive ♪
♪ let's see
♪ take it outside
>> all right, now listen up!
♪ Take it outside
Now, all of you who had sex last
>> all right, now listen up!
night...
Now, all of you who had sex last
>> Yeah!
Night...
>> Let's go!
>> Yeah!
Step up!
>> Let's go!
Get your picture ta-- oh!
Step up!
>> All right!
Get your picture ta-- oh!
>> Couple late bloomers.
>> All right!
Couple late bloomers.
>> Couple late bloomers.
Okay, okay.
Couple late bloomers.
>> Uh-oh.
Okay, okay.
>> Oh!
>> Uh-oh.
Oh!
>> Oh!
No kissing and telling, buddy.
Oh!
All right, now...
No kissing and telling, buddy.
Those of you who had sex with
all right, now...
the groom!
Those of you who had sex with
Somebody got to be in with the
the groom!
groom!
Somebody got to be in with the
Sorry, Dylan.
Groom!
Oh!
Sorry, Dylan.
>> Okay, mama.
Oh!
Yeah, come here.
>> Okay, mama.
Rrr!
Yeah, come here.
[ chuckles ]
Rrr!
>> Thanks for playing.
[ Chuckles ]
All right, now, those of you who
>> thanks for playing.
were screwed by the groom.
All right, now, those of you who
>> Yeah!
Were screwed by the groom.
[ crowd ohhs ]
>> Yeah!
>> Aww!
[ Crowd ohhs ]
>> Pick your head up, buddy.
>> Aww!
Pick your head up, buddy.
>> Pick your head up, buddy.
Come on.
Pick your head up, buddy.
Smile about it.
Come on.
It's a celebration.
Smile about it.
All right. All right.
It's a celebration.
A good sport.
All right. All right.
Now, those of you...
A good sport.
Who screwed the groom, big-time.
Now, those of you...
Somebody did.
Who screwed the groom, big-time.
[ crowd "oohs" ]
Somebody did.
[ laughter ]
[ Crowd "oohs" ]
Ohh! Ugh!
[ Laughter ]
Hey! Oh!
Ohh! Ugh!
Okay, all right, hey, um...
Hey! Oh!
>> Hurted me more than it hurted
okay, all right, hey, um...
you.
>> Hurted me more than it hurted
>> Might need some counseling
you.
on
>> might need some counseling
that one.
On
All right, now, those of you,
that one.
who, unfortunately...
All right, now, those of you,
Saw the groom butt naked having
who, unfortunately...
sex.
Saw the groom butt naked having
That was us!
Sex.
[ laughter ]
That was us!
[ Laughter ]
[ cheers and applause ]
That was us!
Get in.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> You know what?
Get in.
>> Michael --
>> you know what?
don't touch him.
>> Michael --
Stay away from him.
Don't touch him.
All right, now, those of you...
Stay away from him.
Who would like to go on a
all right, now, those of you...
honeymoon with the groom,
who would like to go on a
come on down!
Honeymoon with the groom,
>> Yeah, see?
Come on down!
She wants to go.
>> Yeah, see?
>> Here they --
she wants to go.
boy, they --
>> here they --
>> oh! [ laughs ]
Boy, they --
I'm starting to think something
>> oh! [ laughs ]
here.
I'm starting to think something
>> You love it.
Here.
And once you go Mike, you don't
>> you love it.
go anywhere else.
And once you go Mike, you don't
>> There something you want to
go anywhere else.
tell me?
>> There something you want to
>> No. No, there's nothing.
Tell me?
There is nothing.
>> No. No, there's nothing.
>> Okay, just making sure.
There is nothing.
Last but certainly not least --
>> okay, just making sure.
I feel like we all want to do
last but certainly not least --
this -- who wants to go on a
I feel like we all want to do
honeymoon with the bride?
This -- who wants to go on a
That's all of you!
Honeymoon with the bride?
That's everybody!
That's all of you!
>> You're kidding me!
>> No! She's mine!
Unh-unh! No!
Absolutely not!
[ laughing ]
Whoo!
[ Laughing ]
>> Get it, man!
Whoo!
>> ♪ I'm staying with you