Let's go party!
Yeah, baby!
Yeah! Gilly, get out here!
Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go, baby, we got bitches waiting!
Go! Faster! Put the pedal to the metal!
- Party!
- Go! Go! Go!
Yeah, Jake!
Yeah!
- Hey, ladies. We are here.
- You guys are crazy!
- Get ready to party.
- Yeah!
We are here!
Whoa!
Yo, Nathan.
Dude, you're crazy.
Yes, I am.
- You all right, man? Okay.
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Check it out!
- Dude.
Gilly!
Yo, guys, be right back.
What's up, homey? Check it out, man.
Good quality. You like?
Thanks, man. This is hot.
That's right. All right, man. Peace.
Two hundred bucks, man.
Dude, that's criminal.
No, it's a fair price.
I make the best fake IDs in Pennsylvania.
You know what? You should put that
on your college application.
Dude! I can't believe
how mainstream you guys are.
You guys are so mainstream.
I gotta get you some underground...
Yo, heads up. Coming your way.
Here we go again.
Uh-oh. Here she comes.
- Hey, Karen.
- Hi, Nathan.
Watch it.
Watch it? Watch what? You bumped into me.
Billy! Billy, I'm serious! Listen to me.
Billy! Billy!
Come on.
- Is he serious?
- Whoa.
- That was exciting.
- Let's go get drunk.
You ready? Hold it, hold it!
Wait! Ball! Ball! Ball!
Every time!
- All right.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait! Announcement!
A little gift from my dad.
VIP tickets to the first Pirates home game.
Dude, I will drink to that.
- Let's have a good night, boys!
- Let's toast! Let's do it!
- A great night!
- Yeah!
Whoa!
Look at this guy. Hey, wake up.
Look, whoever you are,
you gotta get out of here.
My parents will be home in an hour.
All right, girls, we have to hurry up.
My parents will kill me.
Trish, do you have any more bags?
You know, you really don't have to
help me pick up all this stuff.
It's okay. It's the least I can do.
If my parents see you here,
they might get really pissed at me, though.
Yeah. Mine, too.
Perfect timing.
- All right, get those mitts on.
- Wake up.
Can't believe you're making me fight
hungover.
You wanna drink like a man?
Let's see if you can fight like a man.
Come on, let's go!
Hit me.
Come on! Hit me! It's not patty-cake.
Punch me! Here!
Move your feet!
I'm right here. Knock my head off. Come on!
Come on, Son!
Hands up!
My boys.
Hands up! Come on!
This is bullshit.
I'll tell you what's bullshit.
Bullshit's getting so drunk
that you can't defend yourself.
You can't watch your back.
That's bullshit, Son.
Come on! Turn around! Move! Let's go!
- Kevin!
- What?
Bet you're glad you went last night now.
Doesn't taste as good on the way out
as it did on the way in, I'll bet, huh?
See, this is what I call a party.
You wanna hurt me, Nathan?
Don't get mad, get even.
Don't lose control.
Think about it. Clear your head now. Focus.
Bear hug? That's all you got?
Come on. Your mother hits harder than that.
Show me something.
You're so slow!
Come on! Pay attention! Come on.
Use your head, Nathan. Think!
You better show me something soon, Son,
or you're gonna go down.
Come On!
I thought we were boxing.
You always said the person
that ends the fight was the winner.
Do I look like I'm done?
You want to play with no rules?
You better be careful
what you let out of the box.
Come on. Get up!
That wasn't that hard, Nathan.
What's the matter? Come on. Use your anger.
Think about it. Keep control.
Look for an opening. What are you gonna do?
You can't punch me. You can't kick me.
What are you gonna do?
Come on!
Is that all you got?
You gotta get me off balance.
Gonna dance all day?
You gonna show me something?
Good shot.
Now we're talking.
I'm bigger than you,
but you can take me, Nathan. Come on!
Wait till you get old.
Hey, guys. Guys!
Kevin!
- You got me!
- Finish me off! Take me...
Enough!
What? We're just working out.
You look like you're
trying to kill each other.
Nah! No, we're good. Right, Nate?
Good job, Son.
You...
God, you smell like beer.
Can I take a shower?
I just don't went to get
a phone call one night
that you wrapped your
motorcycle around a tree.
I wasn't even driving.
Hey, you were out all night. You didn't call.
You're grounded for a week.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Why? Do you not trust me?
After last night, not so much.
Did you ever hear that phrase,
"Trust needs to be earned"?
- ... He doesn't do yoga.
- Whoa!
- He did yoga before.
- He did not do yoga.
- Tell him.
- You went to a yoga class?
- Mom took me.
- You're serious?
See? And you were in pain the next day.
- Admit it. Tell him.
- When did you take him to yoga?
You didn't ask me about taking him to yoga.
I have to ask you everything that I do?
No. If you believe in
secret lives in this house,
I didn't get the memo.
Your dad needs yoga. Tell him.
He has more important things
to do with his day.
You really do need yoga.
- It's good for your mind.
- What's yoga for?
- Your body. Your spirit.
- Tell me a practical application for yoga.
- You could use some.
- That'll happen
the day I take up basket-weaving.
Hey, Nathan, you're on clean-up duty.
Come on. Your mother cooked.
I worked all day.
- What did you do?
- That's right.
Are you going to spin me? Whoa!
You got it.
You've gotten better and better,
you know that?
You always have new problems.
- It's always my fault.
- What is it now?
It's every single time, Billy!
Because it's
mostly your fault, Karen!
- It's always my fault!
- Have you thought about that?
All you think about is football.
If you're so over this,
then just get out of here!
- You know what? I will get out of here.
- I don't need this.
You're in high school, Karen.
I could have any girl I want in college.
God!
What are you looking at, freak?
Sometimes I do feel like a freak.
I walk around like everybody else.
But inside I just feel different.
Like I'm a stranger in my own life.
Or I'm sitting at the breakfast table
with my parents,
and I'm just like,
"Who are these people?"
Don't you think
everybody feels that way growing up?
Do they all go to a shrink?
Not everyone has insomnia
and impulsivity and rage issues, Nathan.
I used your technique.
Last night, this guy snapped at me,
and I had this overwhelming urge
to run across the street
and smash his face in.
But you contained it.
Yeah. I put the anger away.
I chilled. It wasn't worth it.
That's great, Nathan.
Do you realize we probably would have
been having this discussion
in juvenile court a year ago?
You're making progress.
But I still have the dreams.
When was the last one?
Two nights ago.
Any new details?
It was mostly the same.
I see the woman standing there.
She starts singing to me.
I think it's a lullaby.
Then comes the attack.
And then it's over.
Nathan, some dreams are based in reality,
but others are
our mind's way of handling anxiety
just by pushing it
deep into your subconscious.
That's not necessarily a bad thing.
Don't most psychiatrists want to
unearth these things?
I'm not most psychiatrists.
Our time is up.
- Have a good week, Nathan.
- Thanks.
Go, Talbots, go!
- I think you won that match.
- Definitely.
You know what?
You guys are both dicks, okay?
I don't know how y'all convinced me
into joining the wrestling team.
- It was your idea.
- "It's fun, Gilly, it's fun. "
You know what? It's probably a lot of fun
when you out there kicking ass,
but let me tell you, it's a lot less fun
when you getting the smack down.
Come on, Nathan. Come on!
- You got this! You got him!
- Hold on! Hold on!
You got him! Take him down! Take him!
Damn!
Pin him down, man.
You got this! You got this!
Keep him pinned!
Game over!
Yeah, sure.
It's easy when your guy
just rolls over for you.
Come on, he didn't even put up a fight.
- Could you take him?
- Yeah, probably.
Whoa.
You joining the militia group or something?
So I go to the gun range three to
four times a week to blow off steam.
I'm a virgin. What else am I gonna do?
True.
- He was there, right?
- He was there, but he hasn't called me back.
Here we go again. You look at her.
She glances back at you.
You both totally dig each other.
And yet nobody pulls the trigger.
Grow a pair and make that happen, man.
You act like you're afraid to talk to her.
I'm not afraid.
- I don't wanna go to class.
- Me neither.
- Then do something.
- Fine.
Watch.
Hey.
Karen.
- Smooth.
- Yeah.
All I'm asking is that you do
the minimal amount of work in this class
to give yourself the illusion
that you're actually learning something,
and to give me a modicum of self-respect,
like I'm actually teaching a class.
It's called sociology.
The study of society.
People. Besides yourselves.
You're going to choose
one of these topics on the screen
to be the subject
of your 10-page research paper.
You should know
that your 10-page research paper
is going to constitute 75%
of your midterm grade.
Yes, yes, I know, I know, I know.
Your lives have been ruined.
But you know
what Mr. Miles is gonna do for you?
I'm going to assign you a partner,
so that you can learn
to share responsibilities,
to share the work load.
Ernesto, you're gonna work with Susan.
Nathan, meet Karen.
Gilly, you're gonna be working with Sean.
And let's see, Ladislav and Mohammed.
Romeo, Juliet.
- Hey, Mrs. Harper.
- Hey, how are you?
I'm not doing all the work for you
on this research paper.
You got that?
Got it.
You still like games.
When was the last time you were here?
You had a bunk bed.
Wow.
Hey.
Kids want something to eat or drink
or some more pillows to sit on the floor?
Mom.
Okay. You want the door open or closed?
Close it. Please.
Okay.
Uh, well, we should probably get to work.
Says here over 2,300 Americans
are reported missing every day.
I found a website for missing kids here.
They have height, weight, age,
favorite foods, medical reports.
Check it out.
Wow.
Last place they were seen.
People they were affiliated with.
Everything.
Yeah.
I'll send you this link.
What was that story I heard about you
waking up in your underwear
on the lawn after that party?
Just a practical joke.
- Right.
- Not worth explaining.
And I had pants on. Yeah.
I thought your boyfriend
was gonna take a swing at me that night.
He's not my boyfriend.
Hmm.
What'd you say to him anyway
to make him back off so quickly?
I told him that
you'd kick him in his big fat head
and embarrass him in front of everyone
if he didn't stop acting like a dick.
How'd you know
I would have kicked him in the head?
How long have we lived
across the street from each other, Nathan?
Hey, check this out.
What is it?
I found this site that shows you mock-ups
of what missing kids might look like today.
And if you recognize a person,
you can click on their childhood pics.
Check out this guy!
Jason Statham meets Justin Bieber.
Seriously!
Uh, next.
Oh.
Ryan Seacrest meets...
- Lady Gage.
- Whoa!
Next.
Matt Damon meets...
you.
That doesn't look like me.
Nope. You're right.
It's definitely not you.
This kid's too cute.
- Could you send me a link to that site?
- Yeah.
My uncle's coming to check up on me
'cause my folks are out of town.
When did you want to start outlining?
How about I come over in an hour?
Yeah, yeah, awesome. Bye.
Weird.
You're gonna put me off my food now.
Marlin and Lorna Price?
So the lemon and then the capers.
- Sauté it a bit.
- Hey, what's goin' on?
Hey, where do you think you're going?
What?
Come here.
Did you forget you were grounded?
Nathan. Your mother said get over here.
Get over here.
What's up? Are you going to Karen's?
- Yeah, it's for a school project.
- What project?
It's on websites.
- Can I go?
- And you have to get it done tonight?
- And it has to be finished?
- Pretty much.
- For school?
- For school.
- If it's for school, right?
- Right.
- He's still grounded.
- Right. Okay.
It's work.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Be quick.
- Understood.
- Be back for dinner.
Deal.
- Bye.
- And behave yourself.
Our little boy.
I can't believe I just agreed to that.
God, Karen.
I remember when she was just a child.
She's kind of hot now.
- She's sweet. And kind.
- Sweet. Did I... I meant kind.
- And he's a good boy.
- Yeah.
All right, I see the resemblance, but I
really don't think this is you, Nathan.
Okay, good. Tell me why.
First of all,
this kid's three-and-a-half years old.
Don't we all look the same at that age?
Yes. But we have the same exact chin.
Coincidence.
Fine. Explain this.
Okay. It's a similar shirt.
Not just the shirt.
The stain on the left shoulder.
Here. Look.
Holy shit.
Online contact.
Steven Price.
My name is Marisa.
Marisa?
Nathan...
Possibly.
Can you tell me more?
I mean, I don't get it.
Don't you think it's weird that
she wants to know what your address is?
Why does it matter where you are now?
You could just be tipping them off.
It's really suspicious to me, Nathan.
It doesn't feel right.
Don't you think you should
talk to your parents about this?
Mr. Kozlow.
You wanted me to notify you immediately
if the website got a hit.
And if anyone ever finds out,
then you're gonna get in trouble
'cause it's probably a false accusation.
And then I'm gonna get in trouble
because now I'm involved, too.
Don't you think it's weird?
Maybe this is all just a mistake.
You could be adopted.
You know, dropped on a doorstep.
You never know.
If I were adopted,
why would my picture
end up on a missing persons website?
A better question would be
if this is for real, then who are
those people living in your house?
We're gonna
be out there, We're gonna dive...
He's gonna wanna dive with us, okay?
We need you to study. All right?
Rigging. How weather changes.
There'll be times your
mother and I are asleep.
You got to take the helm.
Our lives will be in your hands.
I don't wanna make this sound too ominous,
but it's dangerous out there.
The ocean is a big scary beast, man.
What you got there?
Um...
I lost my driver's license.
Need this to get a new one.
That what's really going on?
Yeah, what else would be going on?
You're not getting a fake ID?
No.
- What's going on, man?
- Oh, man.
- I don't know.
- Must be losing my mind.
My parents are too boring to be psychos.
Hey, you never Know, man.
Now here's you at two years old.
Three-ish.
Five.
Nice. Nice.
Whoa, whoa, wait a second.
Okay. You see this picture of you
when you were five?
- Yeah, why?
- It's cropped weird.
Slight outline of a person's shoulder.
Clearly zoomed in a touch,
like someone didn't
wanna be seen in this picture.
Any more photographs
of you when you were younger?
Those are the ones that are questionable.
Not really.
Just a ton more of me by myself.
A few family photos
is all you have from your childhood?
All that I could find.
Nathan, I've got a million
embarrassing family photos.
Enough to make me wanna vomit.
And you're telling me all you have is two?
What? You're too cool to say hi now?
Hi.
Teenagers.
Hi, bud.
What you looking at?
Your baby shirt.
Are you my mother?
You are my son.
You don't understand, baby.
It's complicated.
Answer me.
Are you my mother?
No, Nathan. I'm not.
We wanted to tell you for so long
and we just couldn't.
Go ahead. Tell me. All of it.
Kevin's a part of this. I gotta go.
Sweetie, don't judge us
so quickly, all right?
You don't know.
I love you.
You're what's made us a family.
I love you and you're my son.
Nothing's gonna change that.
Don't.
I'm so sorry.
Don't hate me, okay?
Gotta go get your dad.
- Yeah?
- Hey. I heard you pull up, so...
Karen, it's true. My mom just admitted it.
What? God, Nathan, you must be
freaking out. I'll be over in a minute.
Okay, come in the back door.
I'm so sorry.
- Ms. Harper?
- Yes.
- How are you this evening?
- Fine, thank you.
We're investigators with the
Bridgewater Juvenile Justice Department.
It's about your son Nathan.
I have a couple questions for him.
May we come in for a moment?
Wait, wait, wait!
Kev!
Where is he? Where is he?
Tell us where he is.
You can't have my son!
Who are you?
Get it started. I'll get the kid.
Mara.
Go, Nathan, go! Go now!
No, Son. Run!
And don't stop!
Karen.
Hey. Get in the house.
Come on, move.
It's going to be all right.
You're gonna be fine.
You won't even feel this.
Such a waste, you know that?
Hey!
Who are you?
Who are you? Answer me! Answer me!
Nathan, stop.
You killed my parents!
Stop. Stop.
I'll tell you what you need to know.
But I'm not dying here.
There's a bomb in the oven.
What?
Oh, my God!
Dive!
Sir, you're next.
DR Pedway...
Thank you, sir. Have a nice day.
- How bad is it?
- I don't know. It hurts.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
We need a doctor. Anybody?
We need a doctor, please.
Hello? Hello?
- 911.
- What's your emergency?
My parents were just murdered.
And I think the people who did it
are after me, too.
What's your location, sir?
I'm at a hospital.
Vassar Brothers Hospital.
But my parents were killed
at 2009 Clearwater Drive.
Please hold.
Hold? What do you mean, "Hold"?
Clearwater Drive.
I'm Slade McKassen- Topping our news,
a dramatic fire in suburban Bridgewater
believed to have been caused by a gas leak.
There have been
no reported injuries at this time.
Police say the residents were out of town
at the time of the incident.
We'll have more later on in our broadcast.
Nathan?
Nathan, are you there?
- Yes.
- Are you okay?
I'm shaken up a bit, but...
Wait. How'd you know my name?
My name's Frank Burton.
- I work for the CIA.
- The CIA?
Why am I talking to the CIA?
I need to know if you're okay.
Am I okay?
I just saw my parents get murdered
in front of my eyes.
Have you spoken to anyone
since the incident?
- Beside Karen Murphy?
- No.
Good. Don't talk to anyone.
Don't contact anyone.
Stay right where you are.
There'll be two men
coming to find you shortly.
One's wearing a red flannel shirt.
They're there to help you.
Nathan, you have to trust me.
Trust needs to be earned.
Nathan? Nathan?
Why am I talking to the CIA?
- Are you okay?
- Am I okay?
I just saw my parents get murdered
in front of my eyes.
Yeah?
They're at Vassar Brothers Hospital.
It's about 10 minutes away.
One of the ER doctors
will come check on you soon.
I want the video feeds from every
security camera in that hospital.
Put this On.
What?
Dr. Bennett? What are you doing here?
There's no time to explain, Nathan.
We've gotta get out of here.
Put that on. Walk behind me.
Cover your face from the cameras.
What do you have
to do with all this?
I'm a friend of your father's.
My father was just killed.
I'm talking about your real father.
- Wait.
- What?
Karen.
There's no time. I came for you, Nathan.
I'm not leaving without her.
They're here already.
- We're on site.
- Where's my surveillance video?
- Hey.
- Hi.
It's okay. She's my...
Doesn't matter. Let's go.
Yeah.
I'm looking for these two teenagers.
My nephew and his girlfriend.
They run away.
Go fast.
Faster.
Come on.
Left! Take the exit! Go left!
- We're in.
- Where are you, Nathan?
- Where is it?
- Over here.
I hate balloons.
We've got a hit.
We have a visual on the target.
Garage. Second floor.
Stop!
- Target is fleeing.
- Westbound. Late model silver BMW.
- We 're in pursuit.
- Stay on him.
- MALE AGENT 22 Sir.
- What?
FaceRec got another hit.
You should take a look.
You can kiss your pension goodbye, Geri.
Nathan.
There'll be time for you
to deal emotionally with all of this,
but right now,
you have to get your shit together.
Who are you really?
Agent Brock, target is proceeding south.
I'm one of your keepers, Nathan.
I'm put in place to look after you.
Just like Mara and Kevin were.
They died protecting you.
This is crazy.
Call the police or something.
I already tried.
I dialed 911 back at the hospital,
and some guy came on the line
saying he was with the CIA.
- Frank Burton.
- Burton? I work for him.
- What?
- Or I did.
He can't be trusted.
There were only four of us
who knew your identity.
Mara, Kevin, me and Burton.
Two of us are dead.
Until I can get in touch with Martin,
we have to consider Burton unreliable.
Target heading
west over the Fourth Street Bridge.
Here. 4-3-1-1 Clarendon Boulevard.
Apartment 2. Arlington, Virginia.
Memorize the address.
Find your way there and just sit tight
until someone contacts you.
What? We're just supposed to
wait for someone?
It's the arrangement I made with your father
in case something like this ever happened.
Who is my father? Who were my real parents?
She has heard too much already.
- What?
- Are you serious?
As soon as you can, dump those clothes.
Agent Brock,
we 're recalculating the coordinates.
Now in less than 20 seconds,
we're gonna hit a soft curve
just before the bridge.
I'm gonna slow down
just enough for you to jump out.
- Jump? What?
- Their field of vision will be obscured.
It's 30 feet down to the river.
- Dr. Bennett, this is insane.
- Fifteen seconds.
And remember, from now on,
do not trust anybody
except Martin Price and Paul Rasmus.
I don't even know these people.
I need answers.
You've been looking for answers
your whole life.
You just didn't know what questions to ask.
You can do this, Nathan.
Now you have 10 seconds to open that door.
After you jump, I will create a diversion.
I don't know if I can handle this.
Five seconds. Leave the girl.
You're better off alone.
- Where am I supposed to go?
- Just trust me.
Take a breath.
- Jump! Now!
- It's going to be okay.
Ready... Jump!
Get out of here!
One lousy state trooper?
That's all you could get?
- Don't lose that kid.
- We're on it, chief.
Come on. Let's go.
All right, we have to get in the river.
- What? Why?
- Because he'll try and track us.
Right here.
Watch your feet.
Behind here.
Was Nathan Price in the Vehicle?
I want confirmation!
Okay, sit down. Relax.
You stay right here.
I'm gonna be right back, okay?
Stay.
Hey. Come on.
It's okay.
You were crying in your sleep.
- I was dreaming about...
- I know.
You don't have to say it.
I have to get you home.
Nathan, I can't go home.
You'll be safe there.
I won't be safe there! We're not safe here!
We're not safe anywhere.
Come on. Let's go.
- Where are we gonna go now?
- Just walk.
I can't go back there, Nathan.
Don't you understand?
My parents are in Italy.
And even if they were home,
they can't protect me.
What are we supposed to do? Call 911 again?
Look. Whoever these people are,
whatever they want,
they're after me, not you.
I think they'll leave you alone.
Do you really believe that?
Or are you thinking about what
your therapist said back in the car?
- Your chances are better alone.
- No.
Of course not.
It's just, suddenly
everyone around me is dying, Karen.
And I don't want anything to happen to you.
We have to stick together, Nathan.
Who else are we gonna trust now,
except for each other?
Come on.
All right, here's the latest intel
we have on Martin Price's current mission.
Ten days ago, Martin Price obtained
a high-value piece of intel.
Specifically, a list of 25 encrypted names,
US politicians and intelligence officers,
all of whom had sold state secrets
at one time or another.
The list was stolen from this man.
Nikola Kozlow.
Ex-Serbian Secret Service.
Now, freelance intel broker and operative.
He wants it back. Badly.
Yesterday, there was
an attack on the residence
where Martin's son Nathan lived.
Two of our undercover agents were killed.
The attackers were hired guns. Btrava.
Connections tracing them
all the way back to Nikola Kozlow.
Martin Price is the agency's
most valuable black ops agent.
Keeping his son Nathan safe from Kozlow
is our top priority.
How did Kozlow find Martin's son?
We think he discovered
the existence of the boy
a couple of years ago
through a cyber attack.
He's been phishing ever since
with fake missing persons websites.
One of his traps finally worked.
Nathan Price is the bargaining chip.
How so?
If Kozlow gets to the kid before we do,
he gets the list off Martin.
What do I need to know
that you're not telling me?
The boy escaped from us last night
with some help from a veteran operative.
Geri Bennett.
Her vehicle was empty when we got there.
No sign of her. No sign of the kids.
Frank.
Get this situation under control
before things get any messier.
- Hey, can you take us to Virginia?
- Get in.
- It's crunch time, Frank.
- Yeah, where the hell is Martin?
Last contact we had
was the Peshawar drop two days ago.
He's vanished since then.
- The fastest he can make it back here...
- Is about 36 hours,
which is how long we've
got to find this kid.
Track the girl. Track his friends.
Track anyone they've ever spoken to.
Put out an alert to all overseas stations.
Get a fix on Nikola Kozlow.
If they can't locate him,
that means he's probably already here.
So we can add him
to our list of headaches as well.
Clarendon Avenue. This is the street.
Hello?
"Lorna Price. 1-7-9-3-7 Calvary Road. "
"G-3-7-7."
What is it?
- I know this woman.
- Who is she?
I think she's my mother.
This must be Martin Price's apartment.
I'm gonna call my uncle.
Let him know I'm still alive.
- Hello?
- Uncle Danny?
I'm sorry,
I must have dialed the wrong number.
Karen? Karen Murphy, is that you?
Who is this?
Someone who's trying to help
you and Nathan.
How do you know my name?
You're in danger, Karen.
There are other people trying to find you.
- Who is this?
- Nathan?
Listen to me, Nathan,
we're going to find you.
You can't hide from us.
For your own safety...
Let's go.
Kids.
Thanks.
This address could be 15 years old.
You know the chances
of finding your mother living there are...
I know. But it's all we have.
- This is an odd address.
- Look at the numbering.
G-3-7-7.
That's her plot number.
You know what's messed up?
I never knew either one of my mothers.
The one who raised me,
I had no clue who she really was
or what she sacrificed for me.
And Lorna Price.
All she was, was a face in a dream.
Now she has a name.
But she's still a dead end.
Nathan, maybe she's not a dead end.
These flowers are fresh.
I'll handle this.
- Hello.
- Hi. How can I help you?
My brother and I just came
from visiting our mother's grave
and we saw that some flowers
had been delivered there recently.
Is there any way you could check
and see who sent them?
We came a really long way to visit her.
Couldn't you just help out
with this little favor?
- Okay. What's the name?
- Lorna Price.
Okay, so the flowers came
from Omaha, Nebraska.
A Mr. P. Rasmus.
It looks like it's going to be
a longstanding order.
Do you have an address for that?
SIGNIT just got a hit
on a name Lorna Price.
Came from a computer
in a place called Calvary Cemetery.
Calvary Cemetery.
The CIA is mobilizing
a strike team out of Pittsburgh.
Dr. Bennett said we could
trust Paul Rasmus.
We have to find him.
You want to drive to Nebraska?
No. We've probably been
in this car too long already.
- We need to ditch it.
- What then?
We'd never even make it
through airport security.
They know our names, our faces.
I know. I have another plan.
Tuscarora Pike. Route 15.
You're very close to them.
- Dude.
- Hey, man.
These guys came to my house
asking questions.
I had to sneak out back.
This is some deep, deep shit.
Did you bring what I asked for?
Yeah, three different IDs
in three different states.
- Yeah, that works.
- Karen.
I went through all your Facebook photos.
I chose the one of you
from that pep rally last month
'cause I thought you
looked really good in it.
- But I could use the one from the beach...
- These will be fine.
- Thanks, Gilly.
- Cool.
Let's move. We should get going now.
This isn't safe for any of us.
I'm sorry about your parents.
Listen, if there's anything else
I could do for you,
if you need cash or...
We're okay.
See you, Gilly.
- Thanks, man.
- See you.
Tell me when you have him.
Amtrak train 29, the Capitol Limited
from Pittsburgh to Omaha
is now boarding on track seven.
Step this way, please.
- Thank you. Enjoy your trip.
- I will.
Capitol Limited, Pittsburgh to Omaha...
- Is now boarding on track 7.
- Go ahead.
- Have a nice trip.
- Once again, Amtrak train 29
now boarding on track 7.
Good thing it's only one night.
Mmm-hmm.
Do you remember that summer when
our families were both
staying at Canadohta Lake?
After eighth grade.
In the boathouse, we
skipped the canoe trip.
Yeah. I remember.
Kind of.
When we came back to school that year,
how come you never asked me out?
I don't know.
I just thought summer was summer and...
Are we gonna die, Nathan?
No.
I won't let that happen.
- Wow.
- What?
That's better than middle school.
That's 'cause I know what I'm doing now.
And no braces, either.
We should get some food.
Yeah. I'm starving.
I'll go.
Okay.
I'll knock twice before keying in.
All right.
I'm on a train, heading south of the city.
Very good.
We're coming up on the Cincinnati station.
We'll be waiting at the next stop.
I'm so hungry.
He might like that.
Shut up!
Tell me what room he's in.
No, no, no.
Pretty fingers.
Tell me the room. Now.
You're gonna play some more, huh?
You little man.
Come on, Nathan! Use your anger.
Think about it. Keep control.
Come on, Nathan! Do something!
You're gonna go down here!
What can you do? Focus.
Think about it. Think.
Think about it.
Come on.
Hey, hey!
Watch it.
Hold on. I need to catch a breath.
Okay.
He really is Martin's fucking kid.
They can't have got very far on foot.
Let's round them up. Wrap up this thing.
I didn't get it until now.
All that time spent training,
wrestling, sparring.
He was preparing me. For this moment.
A few days ago,
we were just a couple of high school kids.
Already feels like a lifetime ago.
Because it was.
Agent Burns,
we have a visual on the target.
Going south on Route 51.
- Come on.
- Kid!
Give it up, kid!
Nathan! Nathan! Nathan!
Come on, why are you running?
Look around.
Is anybody pointing a gun at you?
We're not threatening you.
If you're really the CIA,
what's my real name?
Nathan Price.
Steven. Steven Price.
Steven's your middle name.
They argued about it,
but your mom thought Nathan was better.
- How do you know that?
- I was at the hospital
the night you were born, Nathan.
What do you want?
I'd like to get out of
this dirt, for starters.
You kids, you been on the run
for what, 22 hours? Gotta be hungry.
How about I buy you a burger
and a milkshake?
You must have been hungry.
Karen, could I have
some alone time with Nathan?
Agent Burns will help you
tend to those bruises.
Come sit over here.
You must have a lot of questions.
Who killed my parents?
- You mean Mara and Kevin?
- Yes.
His name is Nikola Kozlow.
He's an independent black ops agent.
Like...
- Like my father?
- Yes.
But Kozlow works for the bad guys.
Martin is...
Was one of us.
The woman you know as Dr. Bennett
trained him.
Lorna, too.
Whose idea was it to put me in
foster care, or whatever you wanna call it?
When your mother died...
To be honest, we weren't sure
whether Martin was gonna crack or not.
He was in no condition to raise a child.
He realized that.
I told him I would make sure you were safe,
so Martin could carry on
doing what Martin does.
What exactly is that?
It's a messy world, Nathan.
People like Martin and Kozlow
are just two sides of the same coin.
Listen, kid.
The world you've just been dropped into
is a world very few people get to see.
You're getting a glimpse
behind the curtain.
What we're engaged in here is a polite war.
It's not about bullets and bombs,
borders or territories.
The currency of this war is information.
Zeroes and ones, Nathan.
Data. And that's what Kozlow's after.
What does Kozlow want from me?
Martin recently stole
something very valuable from Kozlow
and he wants it back.
If Kozlow gets you, it puts your father
in a very compromised position.
Why should my father
suddenly start caring about me now?
Nathan, you don't know
the first thing about your father.
I know he scares the shit out of you.
Mmm.
Byers, report. Torres, report.
Torres, report.
This thing that Kozlow wants so badly,
what my father stole, what is it?
To the naked eye, it's a sequence of
meaningless numbers and letters.
It's actually an encrypted
list of 25 people
who have sold or traded state secrets.
Do you have any idea how valuable that
kind of information is, Nathan?
Your name's on that list, isn't it?
You have a vivid imagination.
That's a very dangerous thing.
Go! Go! Go!
Drop!
- Get down!
- Stay down!
Get behind something solid.
Stay here and keep your heads down.
Stay down!
Come on.
Nathan? Nathan?
What the hell is going on, Nathan?
My parents' murder,
everything we've been through,
it's all about a damn list.
- What list?
- A list of names my father stole.
This guy Kozlow came after me, thinking
he'd force my father to give it back.
The crazy part is I've had it all along
and didn't even realize it.
It's in the phone
I picked up back at the apartment.
Martin must have
texted it to himself for safekeeping.
Jesus, Nathan,
why didn't you give it to the CIA?
Because Dr. Bennett was right about
not trusting Burton.
We're on our own.
Where'd you get that phone?
The guy on the train who attacked us.
Hello?
Convenient thing with cell phones,
they can be turned into
listening devices, as well.
- Kozlow.
- You have something that belongs to me.
Now it's time to give it back.
What use is it to you?
Don't be a foolish boy.
Hand it over and you'll be left alone.
What kind of guarantee can you give me?
I can guarantee this.
If you don't surrender that list,
I will be killing every friend you have.
Jake, Gilly, neighbors.
Even your boring teachers.
And when I'm finished,
you'll be responsible for the death
of every friend you have on Facebook.
But I think it's one person in particular
you don't want to see get hurt.
Am I right, Nathan? Her parents arrive
on Alitalia flight 4-4-9
tomorrow afternoon at 3:20 p. m.
If I don't have the list by then,
they're dead.
You can tell her all about
what it's like to lose your parents.
It's a feeling you must know by now.
Am I right, Nathan? Or am I right?
Okay. Okay.
So, how do you propose we do this?
Simple. I give you a time and a place.
No. I'll pick the time and place.
Somewhere public.
Someone backtracked our signal!
Let's go, guys!
Don't move!
Good.
I'm only sorry
there weren't more of them there.
Yes, sin Another thing.
- What?
- We found a digital record.
- Nathan Harper has the list.
- No, no, no!
He's on his way to meet with Kozlow
to hand it oven.
Where?
- Were you followed?
- No, I don't think so.
I took my 80-year-old neighbor's car.
Can't you tell it smells in here?
Did you do what I asked?
- Did you?
- Yeah, man, just like you said.
Patio section. VIP access only.
It's under 23D.
- Thanks, man.
- Good luck.
I wish there was another way.
So do I.
I assure you,
I have the situation under control.
Do you have the boy?
No.
- Do you have the list?
- No, but...
Then you don't have things
under control, Frank.
- Hello?
- Hello, Nathan.
- Who is this?
- It's me.
I need you to turn around
and walk out of that stadium, now.
Martin?
You sure have grown.
I know veteran agents
who couldn't have handled
what you've been through
in the past 24 hours.
But you can't go in there.
Kozlow will take the list and he will kill you.
Not if I kill him first.
You're not ready for that.
- I've made it this far, haven't I?
- You don't need to do this.
I'm on my way. Just trust me, Nathan.
Give me a chance.
- You had 15 years, Martin.
- Nathan, this is not the time for that.
- I'm done waiting.
- Right now, you need to hear me out.
- Nathan?
- The ticket's at the foot of the statue.
Ticket. Please have your tickets ready.
Thanks.
Well?
Where is this kid?
Burns, do you have anything yet?
Nothing yet, Frank.
Where are you, kid?
Excuse me.
- Watch it. Get up.
- Hey!
Jerk!
Popcorn?
I don't understand this game at all,
but I like popcorn.
I'm glad you're enjoying yourself.
What happened? What did I miss?
You got my list?
How do I know you won't kill me
once I give it to you?
You don't trust me?
You murdered my parents.
They weren't your real parents.
I can tell you all about your real parents,
but I'm not so sure
you want to know the truth.
What truth?
Martin was, as they call, a Class 5,
which means he had the authority
to break the Geneva Convention.
To kill women, children, whatever was
necessary to accomplish his mission.
But your mother, on the
other hand, so loyal.
She wouldn't give up Martin's location
even to save her own life.
You killed her.
Wasn't my intention.
She was a stubborn woman.
Do you remember, Nathan?
You should. You were there, too.
Paris, 1995.
Nathan, think.
It's a funny thing, the human mind.
I'm trained to pay attention to details,
from the hair on your neck
to the location of
every security camera in this stadium.
But in that hotel room,
I made one tiny, colossal mistake.
I forgot to check under the bed.
The bed.
Nathan.
GO! GO! GO!
Is this what you're looking for?
Now we have to give me
what we agreed upon, right, Nathan?
Hey!
Frank? I have location on Nathan.
- Where is he?
- The seats above the visitors' box.
And moving fast.
Excuse me. Sorry!
- Hey.
- Hey!
Hey!
I'm sorry.
- Martin?
- You're alive. That's good. Where are you?
In a shop on the upper level.
Listen to me. I need you to lead him
outside to the south parking lot.
If I do that, I'm dead.
If you stay where you are,
you're dead for sure.
- Lead him outside. Trust me.
- Why should I?
Because I'm here, Son.
- Hey!
- Watch it!
Come on, Martin.
Nathan!
Stop, I'll shoot!
It's over, Nathan.
Trust me, Nathan. I'm here, Son.
You're not as good as your father, Nathan.
You sure about that?
Martin!
Nathan? I'll take that.
You're just like your dad, huh?
Let's go.
I told you
we had the situation under control, sir.
- I have it.
- Good work. Let me see it.
- It's still encrypted, sir.
- That's all right.
Let me get it to the lab and I'll make sure
you have the decrypted file
on your desk first thing in the morning.
That's funny.
Martin said that would be the first sign.
- You talked to Martin?
- He said that
you'd insist on overseeing
decryption yourself,
to give you a chance
to take your name off the list.
Come on, Frank.
We got a long debriefing ahead of us.
Let him go.
He's family.
I'm sorry. For everything.
I'll See you soon.
- Martin?
- Mmm-hmm.
Give the phone to my kid, Frank.
He wants to speak to you.
You're very brave, Nathan.
I handled things with Hudson.
You and Karen won't have to
worry about the agency from now on.
Where are you?
I'm right here. Watching from a distance.
Like I always have.
All I ever wanted was to keep you safe.
Make sure you didn't get hurt.
But I failed.
I'm sorry, Nathan. I truly am.
When can I see you?
Why don't you come out here
and talk to me in person?
I'd like that. More than you can imagine.
- But it's not possible.
- Why not?
I made certain choices a long time ago.
I have to live with the consequences of
those choices, but you don't have to.
Well, then it's up to me.
I want to meet you.
You don't understand the risk.
I don't care about the risks.
You remind me of your mother.
Martin?
Dad?
Nathan.
I'm your father,
but I'll never be your dad.
I lost that chance a long time ago.
I don't know
if you can understand my reasons.
Maybe someday you will.
But you're the only family I have left.
You're leaving me all alone.
You're gonna be all right.
Sorry, Son.
Goodbye, Nathan.
Nathan.
Dr. Bennett?
Hello, Nathan.
Hi.
Call me Geri.
- I can't believe you're alive.
- Me?
What about you guys?
How are you doing with all of this?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
It's for your own protection.
I know.
But where do I go from here?
Your father wanted me to talk to you about
making arrangements for a new home.
- Nothing can replace Kevin and Mara.
- I know that.
But we thought maybe you'd want to consider
coming to live with me
until you finish high school.
Then you have college and...
You know, whatever else you want to pursue.
How does that sound?
Yeah, that sounds good.
- Okey-dokey.
- So, shall we get out of here?
Not quite yet.
I'll make sure he gets home all right.
Oh!
I see. Okay. That's cool. I'll just...
- You know, I'll be here.
- All right.
And, Nathan,
about a certain young lady, I was wrong.
You should hold onto her.
Yeah.
She's worth it.
Sorry we missed the game.
You can take me to another one.
It's a date.
So, you mean this isn't going to be like
eighth grade after the
boathouse between us?
You know what the problem was
back in eighth grade?
I just wasn't ready for you yet.
Mmm. So I had to wait four years
for you to ask me out?
Yeah.
But you gotta admit,
it was one pretty exciting first date.
Definitely.