So he sat on a chair  go
Frank, I need you to do what he
Listen buddy,
I just say this once
Q2 him I really, really, but the
is not smooth
Department has invested a problem
And the loss of investments,
so I can feel better
is to kill someone
Hey! Lance Geverty, bloody career of trafficking in cocaine
I mean, look at what has happened in Pablo
Escaba view
Things like that should not
I moved to the City of Angels to pursue
dream
Like anything else, there are crossroads
I have pursued dreams of others,
guys partying, actor, director, editor
With the hope to improve the position
chain business
But most of them are unaware of the law
yourself playing games
The game begins with the following tricks
The smugglers
The only person can make this dream
First, we opened one strip bar, plenty of investors
more you get good feedback,
more people will be lining up to go on
Then to the drug, mass
large with numerous opportunities
Master  yourself, do not take taxes,
we turn it into your own kingdom
1 paradise with white sand and beautiful girl
But it was not enough
I need to go back to reality ,
to not like zombies
out only at night to make up the
belly and little cash
I find them adorable,
neighbor does not stick to medicine
Still living with their parents, hardworking college
Hot on the bed,
does not disappoint me
He really loves me.
I am a dream, that my berth
A sweet charm of reality
I call her Ashley
And for the future, I need to make sure that Eddie and I
can make this campaign
Boy, does nothing for me?
What the hell is this? Where is my money?
There is only that much, and all that
No missing. Where is my money?
That's gone
End already?
Wait 1 bit
I love
Hi, honey, yeah
okay to eat tonight, 2 people.
Of course, I like it
Ok, I love you. Goodbye
All right, nowhere did I say that?
Oh, that's right.
Where is my money?
I swear it already
He dog  this, no money?
- Where's the Money?
- That's it, just barely making it
I do not add up
He can only cry
I do not claim to be,
I have to tell Frank that
Do not mention that Frank ,
I do not want any trouble here
I have to tell Frank that
I'm trying to help him but
Do you help? You are helping the stars?
Help something that helps?
I just say this once,
you go where the money for me.
Got that? Good boy.
Now go away.
Do not you tired of this job
little star?
Yeah
Just called him back he ran to asses
He's playing you, you know.
He is the son of a bitch that Eddie
- Okay, come on
- New England's misery
He played right in front of him
- And he laughed all the way there
- Get out of here
- Okay that, calm
- No, he is not respected at all
He was just telling the truth only Tony
We have a chance  earn that much money
Talk to Max,
see how the he
- The only way to make only 1
- not where he
Yes, he'll listen to me
I do not think we're going to sell it?
We will bring more money into your pocket
more to him that what Max
-
I know that - I do not know
I want to do the star idiot?
Okay, Eddie, we know that
Come on, Tony, you say?
I'll talk to him
- Really?
- Yes
- Really, told you
Okay kids
crazy Scottish guy
- You think he's going to say it?
- No
I have to say is true  6 o'clock,
I know my family right now that
I know, I know
Traffic jams horrible, I'm sorry
No, I was glad he came and . Come
Wait, Me have a deal?
They're sitting there waiting for him to eat star?
Yes, that's right
-
Ok - I am worried you?
- What? I do have.
- Yes.
- Yeah, I was so worried.
- Come on, it's okay.
Do not worry about that.
Everyone, this is Frank
- Good evening.
- Everybody all right, sir?
- I sit down.
- Yes.
Please enable.
Thank you.
1 little slip slightly chairs.
- This is it.
- What's up?
Well?
- Every well?
- Is it
- Look like?
- That's what I'm talking about
Want a drink instead?
Yeah, I'll get 1 less, you need anything?
Well, why not?
I really appreciate  he had
to do with this case
This was our first ever
when it comes to the Academy
- Really?
- Yes, it is true that yesterday for legendary
- there must also be a
40 - 48, a total that
Local police will want to investigate this
- I need to field first?
- No need to rush
No sign of resistance
Surely someone has  here
There are little wrestling.
Confirm  2. Time of death: 6 pm
6:30 am
- first murder you?
- Yes
Withstand blood right? Being.
He ​​held my breath while I'll buy burgers.
Really.
Who killed you?
Do not know what they are related to the police right
.
- I was the first to here?
- Yes.
- Why do you think we are we have the money?
- We wear that Rolex.
- What else?
- It has no furniture whatsoever.
Only the first two corpses pile of drugs.
No witnesses,
no one knows who the killers are.
- There are theories that do not?
- Probably not the violence then.
Make this transaction failures.
- What is the right sensitivity.
- Thank you, from time to concern us.
- Two people wanted me so that coming?
- Federal Police will investigate the incident.
They're leaving.
If you have any useful information for the investigation
Please call us.
If not, do not impede the process of investigation.
- Boy, you just have a driving license you?
- Beverly, come on.
Even the diapers, kid.
What the hell!
Hey.
Come asshole.
- Why you kill 2 kids it?
- Not me.
- Bullshit.
- I happened to be alone.
- Is there anyone killed 2 kids?
- I do not know.
I have to patrol duty in there.
I saw him run, that's all.
Good?
What's up?
This guy wanted to attack me.
So I feed him 2 rounds.
- I heard four gunshots that.
- I'm not very good at counting.
- I want a report.
- The person that investigation, reporting to walk away.
- Freeze.
- God, I'm here.
Franky...
Fool.
He ​​almost got hit by it.
- Do not hear me yell it?
- The name of this nerve.
What, are you going to shoot police it?
Do not shoot the police, he crazy?
Out goes.
- You're a real liver.
- He timed it.
- Open it.
- What?
Open it.
Fuck that.
Verse Where do you find so much?
I can not believe.
- This is the genuine goods.
- Coming soon before Christmas.
He wants how much?
- For me.
- Uh huh.
Frank.
He wanted to share how?
- I kill them then.
- Why?
You just said you killed him?
Eddie  Well, you do not wear fur.
So too cruel.
I like that fur.
- Fascinating too.
- Yeah. Shelves him go Eddie.
- Give him the remote.
- No, you're supposed cartoon. - Give it.
- I'm watching that.
- Leave the room now.
Bastard.
- Two people are not turned away, huh?
- Loudmouth bastard.
No different women.
Do you think it's funny how Frank?
- I do not laugh about it.
- Madsen Why did you kill?
- He is the source of it.
- Do not talk anymore.
- I need to remove brokers.
- Yeah.
I told you.
I have said many times before that.
I will seek cooperation, more money.
There is nowhere confusing you?
Well, I was trying to tell him, but he did not hear
.
- Should he kill him?
- He does not respect me.
Well, he does not respect him.
Why not say soon.
That's better then, Frank.
You know they will look to me?
No, not us.
Which is his only.
I did not kill anyone. As you do so.
Do not want to eat apples?
Or something well?
Frank... that they will kill you.
They do not kill, I die.
I will not live my life in my first hole in it.
I work we need to do.
Now what?
I will adventure. Quickly
disperse some of this...
When they see the money we earn, they will be replaced by Franky
Madsen and Tony and Eddie.
He killed all star Tony?
Course. Buy 1 get 1 free that.
Frank, crazy map.
God.WWW.SUBTITRARI.PRO
Eddie, come on.
If done right, climb to the top.
There will be the day they catch us.
There will be a next  find you again, but
did everything possible before.
I will not die... someday.
But I will not die an anonymous way.
I will never be nameless.
I was royalty there.
I am a descendant of kings.
That is it, this is the new Eddie.
Okay, listen.
All listen to me.
- Heck he is, Frank.
- Come on, cheer up going. Look at that view.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Those dogs. Investigating What okay.
Los Angeles.
How to call me so early?
I have no idle as you.
- What, still do not believe me?
- I do not trust anyone.
Some people will not like that.
- What say you?
- I said he was not wrong at all.
- There will be other days he was the only prick.
- Threatening me?
- Just a little advice for him alone.
- I advise you, sucking throat again.
Ferns which make regular payments to me.
Do not they know that you own.
- Why?
- I went to check.
The name Reiley real problem.
A few months ago we have sent people to check
his place. Look.
Nothing looks suspicious?
Dispelling , it does not matter now.
Where's Department to the other?
- Focusing on services that go, ok?
- I understand.
Alo?
Hi, honey. Yes, he is only resting.
No, he did not forget. 7am right?
Well, 6h. I, honey, I promise to you.
Yeah, I love you.
- Damn.
- There are people in trouble.
- Well, I was late already.
- I do not know, Frankie.
I do with her?
She  serious relationship only after the loss, a healthy girl
is genuine.
She finished? She is the only
certainly in my lifetime.
As a woman I want
format and with a family wedding.
- We're his family that.
- You think I want to live here all his stars?
Just to have the opportunity, I will take her...
Buy a farm.
- Farm?
- Born a team.
How can I help him  that.
No Where.
Let me say clearly.
- You make my take.
- No, my soldier is killed by it.
You do not have the money right?
You can earn more money, huh?
It's not my fault, it
is only an unfortunate accident.
Yes, it is bad luck.
I asked him that. No.
I beg you, I can not get kicked out like
. No way.
Stand up and fucking .
Putting the hell out of it.
Search on for my rows.
This is a commercial industry, and like every other industry
, it also has its own rules.
Nervous names, we selfish, stupid guys...
it's easy to trick goal.
I have to calm down, play by the rules,
market research and customer insights.
I have to minimize risk and maximize
profit.
It is very basic laws, and also the
th most or forgotten.
To be frank, this is
industry worth billions.
Part of it is perfectly legal:
psychological treatment, medical care, prisons...
Only a small fraction of them are off to.
Less than 20%.
My question is:
eradicate this sector worth it?
I do not think so,
I support that government.
Without drugs, people are entitled to some people thought
would lose my job?
Government wants to increase the number of people
unemployment benefits?
Of course not. They just take advantage of it
to emphasize the fear among the people.
Corporations  opium traffickers smuggle drugs
in Mexico, the Russian mafia...
The message is very simple indeed.
Be careful with foreign men.
Yes, the United States.
Why
who can forget his roots?
By the way, who do not know the plant industry
opium growing pharmaceutical industry is the most you?
Yes. It was such garbage.
unrelated to morality or law.
Only economy is important here.
This is a commercial industry,
better than Wall Street.
Hope they sell, and I sell dreams.
Most of the time, I sold the dream
for those hoping to sell it.
Those are the people I do business,
Where to chew guys lip syncing.
We control this world.
At least I think so.
This place is great right .
But it will not make you forget everything where
Frank.
Why do I always scolded you?
Franky, he disappeared for a week there.
Where were you?
You know what you have not? Why
everything with him always the secret?
How can you believe him when he does not trust me
?
Yes, you're right. What he is doing...
Club  what there... Money is very stable, but it is not good for
a relationship.
Do you think so?
- I want to sell the club.
- No, do not.
- I do not want him to.
- Listen.
I want to do that.
I do not want to do this again, Ashley.
I want out of here and start over.
1 and buy horse farms.
Mews stars?
I do not want to live on the farm.
- Then I'll buy something else.
- Softly.
Yeah, I promise. But...
When he saw his family...
- I think that it's a bit boring.
- It was great.
Wonderful. He wants...
Franky us she wanted...
- They will have the same nose you.
- And his eyes.
Definitely like his right eye.
I get married.
Stars Are you serious?
Ask the children
a more dignified way to another day off.
Also.
- To not partying? Get in the car.
- What do you have?
There are things that are delicious.
- For a little baby?
- I do not want to inhale smoke at all.
- Come on.
- No, I only take cash only.
Come on, do it, do it.
- Get your hands.
- Come on.
Come on.
- Fool.
- Fuck off.
- As a guy, huh? - Yeah. Back then,
talk to him, bring him here.
Okay.
- Hey you.
- Hey.
I have a few questions to ask.
Back to the car over there.
Why did you do that?
- Damn.
- There are a few questions you need answered here.
- Bastards.
- Want to try me?
Now that clear?
- Know this guy?
- Dead guy.
's Right. Because who do you?
A guy that Eddie. Loud, partygoers.
- Find him where?
- He or take a bar in Madison 5.
- Thank you. - Do not get him done?
- All right, let's go.
God, then threw slide!
But almost hit it.
Is a little late.
Hey.
This is the lady asked him.
- She said to try it again.
- Well, is not it hot tonight.
For her, the princess.
God, again. Slide again.
Eddie, that's enough. Separated
my tank almost empty already.
What relation to me?
Calm down, it would be injured.
He just told me to calm you?
- I just remind you. - No, says
the get go. Do not tell me to calm down.
Understand? I'll buy it off the bar, and for his
toilet cleaning.
Now bring more drinks here.
Take out any. Come here, baby.
Maxell, he in it?
Alo ?
Do you see anything?
Here too quiet.
Do not know how to silence it?
Well, I'm sorry.
If anything, I'll let you know soon.
Thank you, I will not make you disappointed.
- You need anything, just call me.
- Hot dog also.
- Really?
- No. Stay where you are going.
Sit back a bit.
- Hi.
I think she is very different.
She has a real job.
Yes, as a civil servant.
There right?
You do not have to get up early?
Let me guess...
Lawyer?
Accountant.
I know that. What is also approximate.
Almost right.
- Why are you here?
- Is due to my boyfriend.
- I do not want to cry anymore.
- So here she is right.
Yeah. This is the stage of my revenge.
I'm looking  1 guy named Eddie. The Scotland.
I am the type of person who will annoy her boyfriend that
.
- I'm exaggerating only.
- I said that right. - Maybe.
Eddie!
- There is gunfire.
- Get inside.
Come here.
Freeze. Back.
There are no weapons, huh?
Good.
Freeze.
- You did good.
- Thank you.
Stand up. Okay, let's go.
Freeze , Eddie.
Some people want to talk to you then.
Damn.
Good? Are you okay?
Need some rest?
Let me give you rest.
I will give a maniac like you
a little break.
Damn, I want to play, huh,
want to try me?
For you know the hand.
Seeing stars? Coffee yet?
Under this huh?
Not okay?
Alright kid?
Fool like pigs.
- Game over.
- I will not do that Eddie.
Shut away.
1 more step, I'll shoot this guy out
crushed skull.
Just do it. I have 3 people.
Put ​​the gun down Eddie.
- Do not act so foolish.
- Try before know.
Damn.
Wait I was ready instead.
Bitch.
- Hey.
- What?
Wait.
- Eddie, why?
- Where you're not home.
- Are you sure? - Eddie, in addition to alcohol with 2
This girl is waiting for him.
Where you're not home.
Maybe I'll stay.
- But not for long.
So tomorrow I have to go to school anymore. - Yeah.
- Yes, really.
- I believe you that.
- Teachers coming very soon.
- Yes.
This... to remove the new.
Franky? Why are not you listening?
Do not you know knock it?
As Eddie.
- She sure was a cop right?
- They do not wear uniforms, but with guns...
And they ask a lot. You think what?
- Star federal police?
- I guess. I do not know.
Think to Kathy, Eddie is now located?
- I do not know. Why do not you go find him go.
- Go to the club alone.
No, do not go anywhere. Are you crazy?
Full Time Police that spot.
They do not care where you Kathy.
Fuck .
- I will be with her.
- Who is she?
- What is this?
- She is my friend. - Her friend?
And you bring her here? She crazy star?
She saved my life.
I have not done anything for me?
What is it Frank?
Wait.
- I want to go home.
- I will go to the club. I took the car to go.
I'm sorry. I'll call you later.
- I please hear me. - Whatever.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Ashley, please do it. Do not seem like that.
Why?
I want you to be excited
2 girls sitting in the living room to the stars?
They are not related to him.
I know that they are people of Eddie.
Why would you want to stay with you, Frank?
His life, his friends...
Nothing like you.
Ashley, Ash...
Hey, they go that way.
- Eddie.
- You should understand these things
's business entirely.
Do not be afraid, Frank. On the go.
- What the hell is Eddie?
- Calm down son.
- Calm? Who are you?
- Frank, calmly.
Yeah, Frank slowly.
And not raise your voice.
- Fuck off. - Frank, calm down.
- Who is this guy right Ed?
Do not need violence that.
Just slowly stop talking.
Do you feel threatened, do not you?
Do not thoughtful.
Use your brain that thought away.
A chair for him to go.
Frank, do as he asked.
Listen, I have little trouble.
I enjoyed the two. It's there.
But I'm not happy.
Goods have been taken away.
And when I lose something,
I feel better if someone is killed.
Wait a minute. Before he came in,
I said we'll take his goods, sell it and get money
fill his pockets.
- Lots of money.
- Shut up.
There is a further problem.
I have 2 partners.
We are fed bullets to the head.
It's true that the real issue.
Listen, I can not make the dead live again...
But I can replace them.
More importantly, I can replace them.
You think you do it?
We were able to complete it.
This is because his buddies makes me angry.
You have to teach him how to behave, Eddie.
Listening to clarify this.
You'll have to sell my stock for 2 days.
No, I'll come back and kill you
with him.
- Clear?
- I get it.
Good.
2 single day that Eddie.
Two days.
Do not let me down.
Come .
Two days. There are two days.
- Is true or real.
- Or rather what this story?
I was alive, Frank.
His plan and effectively.
- You know...
- Why?
Stand up to.
- Hands are you okay?
- And he admits it.
- Then of course. - Home or good.
- And you like it that actor.
- Hey, it's okay with that?
- Damn.
Our plan  success then! Congratulations
.
Counting enough away.
Time differentiation.
Does anyone want to try?
I see?
Let's do it.
As for anything else?
Not much but it is enough to catch them then.
To me were Maxwell.
And Royce agent, why?
- She was waiting outside with a detailed report.
- Royce.
She does nothing for me?
I have infiltrated their group is
and build trust.
I was discussing business with Eddie.
Good.
I heard she had sex with one girl in it?
Tell me that.
It is in that report your boss.
Okay, I'll read it carefully.
I believe we have enough evidence thrown them in jail.
- I agree, we should do just that.
- It is easier to use?
If it fails to do from the first stars?
Maybe we should not hurry it.
But really, sir, we're not necessarily hiding anything
. They operate very intense.
Okay Maxwell. Please send 1 team closely monitored.
If nothing happens within 2 weeks, we will break into.
But no one is doing anything before.
I do not care what her actions. Got that?
- Yes, sir.
- Yes.
Okay, going to finish it.
- Beverly.
- Why?
He said what? I was paired up with someone?
Evan, you know the job is 1.
- I have no such right?
- There is not?
- I'm just worried about me.
- Yeah, ok...
- I know what you're doing.
- This is very dangerous,
I do not want you to stick to sprinkle
mess and can not get out.
You know how when he first met you before that.
Beverly, think carefully away.
You know, if he can not refrain from personal emotions
Job
then maybe we should think about this relationship.
O.
Frank, I like him, but I do not have time
to the day where...
I'm here to discuss the story, you hear me?
Heard you were always stocked, so I'll take half of
characters.
Half a sign huh?
Yes, I am now expanding the business.
Out around the corner this.
- What are you doing?
- Why?
- I have to say I was star juicer?
- No, you're playing the game, and I'm hungry too.
- How dare you do that? - What are you doing?
- God, he also took another chocolate ice cream?
Only 1 bit that, but why are you so angry right?
- Calm down.
- Do not have to spend a map that people would rather not.
- Where Is Your Storage?
- I did not have one yet, I make it.
English drinking straight from the jug stars?
- Disgusting go.
- Depending on how you think.
Why would you do something so big?
Smoke a little bit and then go play the game and calm.
Everything's alright that.
- Really? I get in it?
- No.
- Why not? - You can not just take half
Register here Heroin available. Is this where the level 3.
I took it to go right? Under the seat you?
- But there will be tomorrow, 15 thousand semi signing.
-15 Thousand? Are you crazy?
Several other place full with 10 thousand only.
So by buying some other place to go.
Okay, tomorrow I'm going through. But there is no
samples?
Why are you laughing ? Prestige is doing that, I'm not sure
good restaurant instead.
This is my career, you know?
I understand, the better he should have known better, because he will not have
samples anywhere.
Okay, whatever, I'll be back tomorrow.
- Yeah. Stay away from my refrigerator.
- Where do I have to close.
- I saw him driven to it.
- There was little trust as your brother.
BLT. That's his code.WWW.SUBTITRARI.PRO
Fuck off.
Damaging people's screens.
- Baby I go somewhere?
- Fuck off. - Why are you so?
- Crazy guy.
- Come on.
Hello.
- You're late Scott.
- Do not call me that, too rural. I've said many times before?
- Shut up Scottie. Can you believe I should know?
- I do not need this head start.
Did I say I know where to get paid right?
- What are you doing?
- I'll catch you.
- For possessing banned substances.
- TB go. - Listen.
I do not care about you or your name.
If you do not want to just point out
then perhaps you should think twice before.
Now you have the choice.
To be the only guy alive or dead?
- Okay. Calm down.
- I will ask only one time.
Who's going shipping?
- Enough all right?
- Yeah.
Do not ruin it.
This is a map of the apartment.
I'll be here. When have any of what happened, we started to move
here.
Please remember, that anyone run out
Must  arrested, okay?
The 4 and 5 will be in bedrooms 2 and 3.
Team 1 and 2 bedroom 1 will take care of now.
Go.
Frank, are you all right?
I'm fine.
He's in there too long.
What's wrong?
You okay honey.
Come on.
- I do not think it's a good idea.
- I'm mad at you?
At dinner he worried that too.
- If not why do you want to do?
- Come on Ashley, you know...
This  him much stress.
- I know.
- So you want to go home with you?
Can.
Very funny, Frank.
Why not take it to talk?
I love this place.
Ever since that cheesy god?
The confessed to me?
Lm away. I have something to tell you.
Say.
I will quit.
Course.
Kidding?
Really?
Why would you want to quit?
Frank, he just killed two guys.
1 So great bargain.
I want to star?
I do not.
I know. I also do not want him to do so.
That's what I want to say to him.
I just went over.
What happened?
Nothing. Just...
I do not like this future.
I ruin the nostalgic,
do crazy things.
I do not know. It's as if I do not leave now
I'll do something stupid.
It's time to put this back then.
Favor but I still do not understand.
Do you want to come back as this honest?
- Is the goal.
- It will ruin our friendship.
- I know what will happen right?
- What's that?
I think I will visit,
dressed as Santa's bringing gifts for his children...
Then they will call me uncle.
Then will come when trouble occurs, Frank.
Since we will no longer be the same again.
So, why do not you try doing what I'm doing?
So I'm doing a very good job of this already.
You too.
This is the end. Why I will withdraw.
I was very disappointed.
Do you remember when he asked me to do the same.
He had left  all in the mind.
He ​​is the latest build.
What do you want from me? I owe you.
I wish he
carefully recalculate his plan to not regret later.
What are you talking about? I have no plan at all.
Sometimes his actions will lead him to the path 1
What can I say?
Good luck, Frank.
Thank you.
Good luck.
But if something happens I will not run
Dum cleans you.
In the legal world, when he became a suspect
1 business ngech he just went bankrupt.
You could lose the license, reputation, property
. At most take home.
In my profession, often lose their lives.
So have a plan B is very important.
1 exit strategy.
My escape is Ashley.
Being alive  1
normal life free from all this.
I've always saving money.
Soon, I will be able to retire.
Maybe I'll remember, but once
action and excitement, but I will live.
And there may be more children.
1 3-bedroom house with a lawn,
and 1  pool. Where in the suburbs.
That would be my blessing.
Thank you. As my paradise.
Listen  Frank, I'm sorry, I did not
lately sympathize with him.
- I know you have much to worry about in the beginning...
- Do not. Do not apologize.
Okay?
Summary neck you got you, you bastard.
- How are you boss?
- How you doing?
Fine. I in?
No, sorry, I was not invited.
Have fun.
Calm down, I know she's not all flowers.
Respect each other at all.
- Hey, no offense intended...
- Did you say that?
I am Jack Reiley.
- Jack is my name.
- Okay.
Why not go somewhere else to play?
He is Frank right?
What about the police?
Yes.
Now I'm off work then.
Really?
It's just work.
I guess.
- So Reiley police...
- As inspection.
Really?
- How do you know me?
- I have inquired around here.
I want to meet you.
Then he met  Time.
What's this?
I have enough all you know?
- Money, women.
- I own the little brother to us, okay?
Come on.
- Hey!
- Mongolia's beautiful.
If I will not choose to become a police officer.
Then discarded.
Maybe I should, but I kept thinking.
Pension...
This place burns hot right hands.
Everything I do is for dinner only.
Nor  aristocratic anything.
Yeah, amazing really. You buy from?
- Not mine.
- Not it?
Mind if I take always?
I used to get that good of friends
1. Maybe you know him.
- I do not think so.
- Maxson?
Not it? Do not remember anything?
Anyway he also died.
Why do not always go to?
He ​​made me fall inspired too.
Why? I think I caught him coming stars?
Why would I do that?
I know everything about him.
I know where you live, what time you wake up.
Knowing the toilet when he went.
And the beautiful girl he had met before coming here
- I talk too much.
- I'm going on the subject.
I did not say anything.
I keep what I know about her.
So what do you want? As you.
Power, women, money.
My money .
Think of it as insurance policies.
- He is one dirty cop.
- I'm one smart cop.
Yeah, I get it.
- How much?
- This is where we can negotiate.
Yes, we will negotiate.
Do you think? 100?
Yes.
$ 1,000.
What are you talking about? $ 1000...
Only cheap prostitute alone.
1 Police Act is much more expensive, huh?
To see, how much will this cost?
Dear inspector, for his mouth shut?
Do not be stupid!
Damn!
Do you have that?
Jourdan come on!
Go Here  asshole.
This boss. Handling it.
I just think...
Will tell you...
're Fooling here... I asked for it?
Bastard!
It's a cop, Johnny!
As one dirty cop, cops
so why are you here?
Frank  What is this? Who is this guy?
As police. He wants to make money.
Understand what I mean?
Cash it? I do not owe him anything.
Yes.
U You want my money?
I will give you money.
Bring money back.
Okay.
Here's your money.
- British police à you.
- Frank,
- Let us condemn him to go there.
- You girlfriend to threaten me?
Huh?
Take the first step out of here.
Damn .
Music  Open again.
Time to go dancing.
Beverly me okay?
I have no control over the situation?
There...
This...WWW.SUBTITRARI.PRO
He had dirty cops shoot man tonight.
- Reiley it? - Yes.
- Can kill him? - No.
I do not know, but...
- I could have stopped it.
It can end here. - No, do not do it.
- Do not do it. - I dipped too deep already.
- I can not do that this time.
I can not draw them out.
The health of children is to do?
I just need to see you...
I just...
I need to know you're doing the right thing here.
Okay?
OK, but when you find yourself losing control,
Just forget about the case and walked away.
Yes.
Everything will be alright.
Promise me you'll be there when
done something right?
I promise. Careful.
Yes.
So Frankie, threatening him as well.
To him is not good.
I want to go to Mexico too.
What about you?
Um...
I like Mexico.
Let me make this clear,
He robbed,
then they took his gun and shot him in the hand.
What are you doing in this place?
That's where they put me.
So he kidnapped again.
Tell me how many names?
3.
- 3? White, black or latin?
- I have already said in the report.
Jack, with cocaine in his blood.
And 1 more cocaine in his jacket pocket.
I do not have any explanation, he also vowed
not tell me about the guy robbed.
If you have addiction problems, the Department can help you.
- Reiley Damn, he should tell me.
- The report is enough.
Okay, if you insist.
- He is suspended without pay indefinitely.
- She can not do that.
We know each other 20 years ago,
before she went next door to the boss.
I find it difficult to do much less then.
Deborah Sorry, I did not mean it.
I just need a few more days.
I am doing one big case,
then everything will be clear only.
Ministry of Internal Affairs is investigating him that Jack.
I do not like him, but the superior data
eyeing him too. I give up then.
If I were you I would make one good lawyer.
Since losing his gun and badge to put here.
Kidding me?
Look like I'm kidding?
I want to know who has a gun to rob
police, shot in his hand
- And then still alive to tell.
- Life is full of crazy but, just look at him.
You know what I think?
I think I know who had shot him.
We also know he will not open up.
So stick your hand eczema is also available now.
I do not care what you think.
- I can not remember why I made the police?
- I shall have stars?
Maybe he likes head 80 thousand 1 year,
wandering around the city running them shot in the butt
- Work that.
- You're so weird.
Every self-righteous.
You think you are making a difference how?
No, he did not clean up the drug.
Once started 1 month 3 months others emerge.
True work is this funny. Look around to see.
Look at the truth. Although the initial goal of
he is, he is only failure.
I just want to make enough to retire.
Escape to the tropics this place somehow.
Anywhere except here.
My first case...
There is also one addict mother.
She was a seizure, but the crying baby
stirring constantly.
The bitch is positive that coach inserting
rag into her mouth to figure it shut.
When I arrived, the child was dead, his mother is
overdose is that I can not do anything.
In the beginning, my goal is
save the world, but after 20 years,
I just want to stop people like him to
Costa Rica. I've seen so many guys before.
1 someday he'll loopholes,
and I'll catch him.
I do not remember Mike?
Captain  guy with a towering voice?
- In this animation.
- Which one?
Sam chase the box.
And the box with its feet.
Sammy Sam kept banging rumbling.
And the answer box.
But wearing sexy clothes in front of the door.
- Hi.
- She is the girlfriend of Frank?
Then it says: "Sorry, Sorry".
I'm looking for pink bunny big belly.
- Yes - I'd like to meet her.
- Then he hit a game boy.
Where are we going?
He ran to the door and tried to keep calling:
"It is not in the"
Damn, come back here!
Where you going to run?
Mom!
Boom!
First it always explodes!
"Should I not run this way?"
- "It is not in the house.'s Not in the"
- So that Sam still believe.
You crazy star?
- What is She?
- Sam should run to the door...
Back to the door opposite...
Boom... to the surface again!
Until then, Sam staggered around the matted surface.
Cosmetic surgery will not be saved.
Step back, do not let it show...
"It is not in the"
I'll believe you this time.
So I'll believe you.
Sam I like this version too.
Thank chefs okay.
What happened ?
- He overslept.
- You think so? I'm sorry.
- Have you seen anything?
- Yes.
1h37, Royce and two female agents to the suspect.
1 blonde, 5'7 and the other 5'2,
Black hair. At 2h23 1 of the grocery store and then return
. Alright.
There is good news?
- Okay, okay trying to keep awake.
- Yes.
- Listen to go.
Do you remember when your  still in school and I have to imagine
not dream home?
What I was dreaming?
I imagine it like?
Actually, I do not have class,
I do not go to school much.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
So let's play it, if I have to imagine now
I think?
I do not know, I prefer animals.
Why?
I want to eat cat ,
wanted to save all the dogs and cats in the world. And Turtle.
- Turtle it?
- I know. It's funny.
It's cute.
- I want to open one farm animal rescue 5 stars.
- It was stupid. - Not at all.
This terrible at animal shelters is that they do not clean up
and to them in an extremely dirty. It is a sin.
I want to have one farm animals 5 stars, no fertilizer.
There are TV  cat. So they do not suffer from depression, who also fun.
- What is it?
- I do not know.
Opening grow.
- Well done Henry.
- Yes, he caught sight Royce and girlfriend.
- She is beautiful too.
- Shut Walter.
My boss, consider this.
- Give up on the screen.
- Okay, what?
As Reiley.
Keep going.
- Please...
- Shut up.
Okay, I'll stay away opening.
Step back, let's go inside.
Do not joke with me.
Shut up.
He said, "Why do you put oil on my hair?"
- Frank.
- What do you think of him or more stars?
- Frank, drug trafficking continues to go.
- Ridiculous.
How can you... The characters, plot,
everything is funny.
- Do not make me... Okay I give up.
- Damn, the door opened again.
Kathy!
- I told her this yet?
- Not yet.
- Come here.
- Kathy.
Sat down.
Stop that noise.
We will carry on.
Support Team will soon have to. Tell them to hurry up.
I have to pee.
Every time the door is open heart.
Do not move! Go back, put his hands on his head.
Right back.
Damn!
Do not move!
This is the police!
- Do not play stupid Maxwell!
- No hiding place Reiley.
- I can not get away, put the gun down!
- View me this.
We need reinforcements now!
- Put the gun down!
- No way.
Put ​​the gun down! Put the gun down now!
Maxwell Go to hell!
Just stay there.
For her go!
This bastard! You shot my hand!
Okay honey, I'll take care of it.
I swear that you dare hurt her...
You dare  shoot me?
For her go!
- Shoot a try!
- Let her go!
Ashley!
Now does anyone win?
Move back Maxwell!
Where you no longer exits.
And dare take his gun again?
I will kill it!
Stay away!
Careful!
Do not move!
Stay there!
Do you hear me?
I know, I know. Do not tell.
Do not, do that...
Agent Royce here, where is the relief?
Look at me. Just do what I say.
Just follow, will be okay.
Come on, get up.
Okay, let's go.
I catch her then.
Keep going.
Stop.
Go away, go away from here.
Go away.
So you will not come to Costa Rica where eh.
Bastard.
I've calculated everything.
But I fail.
Is my fault.
I should have known before.
I said "I would rather do business with sharks
rather than with fools."
At least I know what they want.
I understand the way they used to sabotage me,
With idiots, you can not measure.
I would rather do business with flood debris of this world rather than
Flood said police are not corrupt control addiction.
Supposed to kill him when I get a chance.
Now Ashley, Eddie,
the girls...
Dead already.
Money and all.
Plan A fails.
Plan B as well.
Maybe it's time to start planning C