FOUR? THEY'RE CRAZY.
I SHOULD JUST GET UP
AND WALK OUT RIGHT NOW.
OKAY, CALM DOWN.
HONESTLY, WE PUT
A SOLID OFFER
ON THE TABLE.
MY CLIENTS ARE SELLING
FOR FOUR,
LEAVING HALF A MILLION
IN EQUITY.
NOW, THIS IS THE DEAL.
NO. NO.
RICHARD,
PLEASE SIT DOWN.
[SILENT]
[RICHARD SIGHS]
I'LL SHOW THIS TO MY CLIENTS.
DON'T KNOW IF IT'LL FLY,
BUT WE'LL SEE.
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING
IN THERE? ANYTHING
I CAN DO?
LISTEN. WHEN
BILL AND NORA LEAVE,
I WANT YOU TO
POP YOUR HEAD INTO
THE CONFERENCE ROOM
AND I WANT YOU TO SAY
THESE EXACT WORDS--
"YOUR CLIENTS ARE LEAVING."
SURE. ANYTHING ELSE
I NEED TO KNOW?
NO, NOT YET.
HMM.
WELL?
3.5 MILLION.
WE ALREADY CAME DOWN
FROM FOUR.
WE'LL ONLY BREAK EVEN IF WE
AGREE TO THREE AND A HALF.
DO YOU TRUST ME?
WE KNOW YOU'RE WORKING
AS HARD AS YOU CAN
TO CLOSE THIS DEAL,
BUT THAT RICHARD GUY
IS TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF US.
I KNOW. THAT'S
WHY IF YOU TRUST ME,
I WANT YOU TO DO EXACTLY
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO TELL YOU.
IN 10 MINUTES I NEED
FOR YOU TO GET UP,
WALK OUT OF THIS OFFICE,
PAST THE CONFERENCE ROOM,
AND OUT THE DOOR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF NEGOTIATING.
TRUST ME.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER
DONE SOMETHING WITHOUT
KNOWING THE OUTCOME?
WAIT 10 MINUTES
AND GO HOME.
THE NEXT TIME
YOU'LL HEAR FROM ME
WILL BE ME CALLING
TO CONGRATULATE YOU.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND NOW?
NOT REALLY.
BILL, LET'S JUST DO
WHAT SHE ASKS.
'KAY. 10 MINUTES.
LET ME CALL YOU BACK.
WELL?
DO WE HAVE A DEAL OR NOT?
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU
AND THIS PAPER?
CAN'T YOU SPEAK?
WHAT DID THEY SAY?
DO WE HAVE A DEAL OR NOT?
YOU'RE CRAZY!
NO, THEY'RE CRAZY!
4.2 MILLION?
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
WE MADE A FAIR OFFER AND
THEY'RE GOING UP IN PRICE?
THEY'RE TIRED OF
THIS BACK AND FORTH,
PUSH AND PULL.
AND THEY SAID IF YOU DO NOT
AGREE TO IT IN 10 MINUTES,
THE DEAL'S OFF THE TABLE.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
3.7 MILLION
IS A LOT OF MONEY.
I MEAN, WHO'S GONNA
WALK AWAY FROM THAT?
YOUR CLIENTS?
THEY'RE LEAVING?
THEY'RE WALKING OUT
OF THE BUILDING RIGHT NOW.
WELL, I GUESS THAT MEANS
THE DEAL'S OFF.
WHAT? AFTER ALL THE TIME
AND WORK I PUT INTO THIS?
GO. GO GET THEM.
AS I EXPLAINED, THEY TOLD ME
IF I DIDN'T COME BACK,
- THEY WERE WALKING.
- MEGHAN, YOUR CLIENTS
ARE LEAVING.
OKAY, FOUR. FOUR,
AND WE GO TO CLOSE TODAY.
- NOW WOULD YOU PLEASE GO
GET THEM BEFORE THEY LEAVE?
- TELL MY CLIENTS
I'LL SEND THE PAPERWORK
OVER THIS AFTERNOON.
OKAY.
IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE.
THANK YOU.
AND CONGRATULATIONS
ON A GREAT BUY.
I JUST CLOSED
THE SMITH'S DEAL.
GOOD. IT'S ABOUT TIME.
NO, I DON'T LIKE ANY OF IT.
REDO IT.
YOU, COME WITH ME.
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE I WANT
YOU TO MEET IN MY OFFICE.
MEGHAN, I WOULD LIKE
TO INTRODUCE YOU TO
THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS,
KANA AND HOSHI YAKAMOTO.
GENTLEMEN, THIS
IS MEGHAN DOHERTY.
KONICHIWA.
[SPEAKS JAPANESE]
SHE WILL BE HEADING
YOUR CASINO PROJECT.
MR. WHITAKER, WE HAVE
A LOT RIDING ON OUR DEAL.
I UNDERSTAND. MEGHAN IS
MY TOP INVESTMENT BANKER
HERE AT THE FIRM.
WE'VE REVISED
OUR BUSINESS PLAN
TO INCLUDE PHOTOS
OF THE EXTENDED LAND
IN THE MOJAVE.
I HAVE BEEN ANTICIPATING
THESE PLANS FOR A FEW
WEEKS NOW.
AND FOR OUT
NEXT MEETING, WE'LL
HAVE AN OUTLINE IDENTIFYING
RISKS, AND FACTS
UNDERLINING YOUR INVESTMENT.
NOW, THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
TO SAY THE LEAST.
[LAUGHS]
YOU HAVE YOUR WORK
CUT OUT FOR YOU NOW.
SO, ARE WE ALL
SET FOR TONIGHT?
THE DECORATIONS ARE UP.
THE CATERERS START SERVING
AT 8:00.
EVERYONE KNOWS TO BE
AT YOUR HOUSE BY 7:00
OR DIE BY THE HANDS
OF MEGHAN DOHERTY.
AND VALENTINA
KNOWS NOTHING?
SHE THINKS
WE'RE DOING SUSHI.
[MAN ON SPEAKERPHONE]
I HEAR YOU'RE TRYING TO CLOSE
ON THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS
CASINO THING, RANDOLPH.
YOU THINK SO, AL?
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
YOU'VE BEEN TRYING TO SQUEEZE
OUR COMPANY FOR YEARS NOW,
AND IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
WE'RE NOT GIVING IN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SHOW OFF
MY NEW OUTFIT TONIGHT.
LIKE ALWAYS.
ARE YOU IMPLYING
THAT I'M SELF-CENTERED?
MMM, THAT'S RIGHT.
THE SAME SELF-CENTERED FRIEND
WHO STUCK MY NECK OUT
TO GET YOU A JOB AT THE FIRM.
HOW QUICKLY WE FORGET.
[AL] JUST REMEMBER ONE THING,
RANDOLPH.
I AM IN FIRST POSITION
ON EDEN GRAHAM'S MOJAVE LAND.
AND I WILL FORECLOSE
ON SATURDAY,
AND WHEN I DO, THE YAKAMOTOS
WILL BE KNOCKING ON MY DOOR.
[BUZZING]
THAT'S THE OFFICE.
HOLD ON. HELLO?
MEGHAN,
I NEED YOU HERE TONIGHT.
TONIGHT?
[WHISPERS] IT'S
VALENTINA'S PARTY.
SIR-- ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE THERE
BY 6:00 PM, SIR.
I'LL HAVE TIME TO STOP
AT JASON'S OF BEVERLY HILLS
BEFORE I MEET WITH WHITAKER.
I WANT TO GET VALENTINA
SOMETHING SPECIAL.
SO WHAT'S NEW
AT THE FIRM?
I CLOSED A BIG ONE TODAY.
YOU DID? CONGRATULATIONS!
HOW'S YOUR CAR DEALERSHIP
GOING?
- DEALERSHIP IS GREAT.
- THAT'S GORGEOUS. I HAVE
TO GET A GIFT FOR MT FRIEND.
AH, THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
ANY INTERESTING OPPORTUNITIES
YOU CAN THROW MY WAY?
YEAH. ONE OF MY CLIENTS IS
THINKING OF OPENING A CHAIN
OF AUTOMATIC CAR WASHES.
THAT SOUNDS INTERESTING.
I KNOW I DID REAL WELL
INVESTING IN
THE LAST EXOTIC CAR
BUSINESS YOU GOT ME TURNED ON
SO HOW MUCH?
FOR YOU, 8,000.
THAT'S RETAIL.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
OKAY, I'LL DO 7,500.
OKAY. 7,000.
BUT THAT'S IT.
DEAL.
- HOW MUCH FOR THAT ONE?
- NORMALLY IT'S 2,000,
BUT
FOR YOU, 1,500.
COULD YOU BOX THAT ALSO?
SURE. SO HOW'S THE FERRARI?
FAST.
YOU KNOW,
THAT'S THE ONLY CAR
I DON'T HAVE
IN MY DEALERSHIP,
SO IF YOU EVER WANT TO GET
THAT THING OFF YOUR HANDS,
LET ME KNOW.
LET GO OF MY PRIDE AND JOY?
NEVER.
JASON, YOU KNOW BETTER
THAN TO ASK ME THAT.
[WHITAKER] THE MOJAVE DESERT.
5,000 ACRES OF THE MOJAVE
DESERT.
WE ARE GOING TO BUILD
A CASINO RESORT,
INCLUDING AN
18-HOLE GOLF COURSE
AND A COUNTRY CLUB.
SO WHAT'S THE CATCH?
WELL, GRAEME MINISTRIES
OWNS 1,000 ACRES
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS
ARE GOING TO NEED
THIS ONE PIECE OF LAND
TO BUILD THEIR VISION UPON.
NOW, THIS LAND IS ALREADY IN
FORECLOSURE,
BUT THE OWNER,
MR. EDEN GRAHAM,
IS NOT COOPERATING.
AND SO, THIS LAND
IS GOING TO
GO TO AUCTION
NEXT SATURDAY.
THAT DOESN'T GIVE
US MUCH TIME.
I KNOW. THIS GUY
ABSOLUTELY REFUSES
TO SELL.
THEREFORE I NEED YOU
TO DRIVE UP TO THE MOJAVE,
AND MEET WITH
MR. EDEN GRAHAM.
MEGHAN, YOU
CLOSE ON THIS DEAL,
AND WE'LL ENJOY
A CELEBRATION TOGETHER.
MY DREAM WILL BE REALIZED
AND GUESS WHO WILL BE
IN LINE TO FILL MY SHOES?
HI!
VALENTINA.
I'M SORRY I MISSED
YOUR PARTY.
NO, YOU DIDN'T MISS IT.
YOU'RE HERE NOW,
AND THIS IS
HOW IT SHOULD BE,
THREE BEST FRIENDS,
ENJOYING EACH OTHER.
I KNEW WHEN WHITAKER
CALLED YOU TO HIS OFFICE
IT WOULD BE A LATE NIGHT.
WE ALL KNEW THAT.
WE DECIDED
TO WAIT FOR YOU.
OH, GUYS,
YOU ARE SO SWEET.
OH, I'M ACTING AS IF
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY. HERE.
OH MY, LOOK
AT THIS BRACELET!
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL!
OKAY, OPEN.
OKAY!
OH!
DO YOU LIKE IT?
I LOVE IT!
OH, THANK YOU.
LOOK WHAT ADAM GOT ME.
THAT IS GORGEOUS!
YOU MUST HAVE SPENT
YOUR ENTIRE PAYCHECK
ON THAT.
NOT ALL OF IT,
BUT, YEAH, MOST.
[PHONE BUZZES]
HI, MOM.
I FINALLY CAUGHT YOU.
LET ME TALK TO HER.
MOM, I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
A CALL BACK TOMORROW.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
CALL ME BACK YESTERDAY.
GOOD NIGHT. I LOVE YOU.
SHE HAS
THE WORST TIMING.
HMM.
[MEGHAN] I HAVE THE BIGGEST
DEAL OF MY LIFE AND SHE CALLS
TO CHIT CHAT?
DON'T BE SELFISH.
IT'S YOUR MOTHER.
YOU CAN'T TAKE TWO MINUTES
OF YOUR TIME?
TWO MINUTES WILL
TURN INTO TWO HOURS.
I JUST HAVE SO MUCH ON MY MIND
WITH THE YAKAMOTO ACCOUNT.
MEGHAN, EVER SINCE
I'VE KNOWN YOU,
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT IS MONEY
AND YOUR CAREER.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
WHEN YOU TURN 60?
YOU'RE GOING TO WISH THAT
SOMEONE WOULD CALL AND VISIT
YOU.
AND GUESS WHAT? YOU ARE
GOING TO BE ALL ALONE.
YOU ARE JUST AS OLD AS I AM.
BUT I LOVE MY FAMILY.
AND ONE DAY I PLAN TO
SETTLE DOWN AND HAVE
CHILDREN OF MY OWN
SO THAT WHEN I GET OLD
I'LL HAVE SOMEONE TO LOVE ME.
LOOK AT YOU! YOU DON'T DATE
AND YOU HAVE NO FRIENDS
OUTSIDE OF ADAM AND ME.
IT'S LATE, AND
I HAVE TO PREPARE
FOR THE BIGGEST
PRESENTATION OF
MY LIFE TOMORROW.
[ADAM] THAT'S RIGHT.
BIG PRESENTATION.
I'LL GO GET MY COMPUTER
SO I CAN ASSIST.
YOU KNOW THAT I'M RIGHT.
LET ME GOOGLE "GOD'S COUNTRY"
AND SEE WHAT
WE'RE WORKING WITH.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
"GOD'S COUNTRY IS NOT
JUST A GETAWAY.
IT'S A SAFE HAVEN FOR
THOSE WHO NEED A BREAK,
IN THE MIDDLE OF 1,000 ACRES,
WE OFFER THE BEST HIKING,
CAMPING--
RUN BY MINISTER EDEN GRAHAM,
SECOND GENERATION--
[WHISPERS]
GOOD NIGHT.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS, THUDS, GRUNTS]
STUPID SHOE!
HAVE THEY MADE IT?
MEGHAN, WHERE ARE YOU?
THEY ARE HERE NOW.
- OKAY.
- AND MR. WHITAKER IS WALKING
THEM INTO THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU WAKE ME?
- I'VE BEEN CALLING YOU
ALL MORNING.
I HAD RESEARCH PUT SOMETHING
TOGETHER. IT'S ON YOUR DESK.
OKAY. OFFER THEM COFFEE, TEA,
SOMETHING TO DRINK.
STALL THEM.
YOU WANT ME TO GO
INTO THE CONFERENCE ROOM?
- BUT I--
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THESE QUESTIONS!
JUST DO IT!
OKAY.
[HONKS HORN, TIRES SCREECH]
WHO DO YOU LIKE BETTER?
YOU LIKE MATSUI OR ICHIRO?
UH, MEGHAN IS A COUPLE
OF MINUTES AWAY.
SHE ASKED ME TO OFFER YOU
SOMETHING TO DRINK.
COFFEE? WATER? TEA?
TELL MS. DAUGHERTY WE PREFER
HER PRESENCE
INSTEAD OF DRINKS.
BUT SINCE YOU'RE HERE,
BRING ALL OF THE ABOVE.
YES, SIR.
ANYWAY, MY FAVORITE PLAYER
IS HIDEKI MATSUI.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR YOU.
I STALLED AS LONG AS I COULD.
HERE'S YOUR MATERIAL.
OH, UH--
GENTLEMEN.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
SHALL WE GET DOWN
TO BUSINESS?
WE'VE IDENTIFIED
YOUR PROSPECTUS
AND HAVE DONE AND EVALUATION
KEEPING IN MIND
THE GROWTH RATE
OF
THE SURROUNDING MOJAVE AREA.
WE SEE YOUR CASINO NOT ONLY
AS GAMBLING FOR ADULTS,
AND WE BELIEVE YOU HAVE
AN ENTERTAINMENT PORTAL.
WE SEE THE PROFIT POTENTIAL
AT A CAPTURE OF 40% LIFT
ANNUALLY.
YOUR INVESTMENT OVER
THE COURSE OF 10 YEARS
WILL YIELD AN
ANNUAL $2 MILLION,
WHICH BY YEAR EIGHT, FROM
YOUR PROFIT, YOUR INTEREST,
AND NEIGHBORING LEASES,
YOUR INVESTMENT WILL BE
PAID BACK IN FULL.
WE AT WHITAKER AND ASSOCIATES
WOULD LOVE TO TEAM UP WITH
THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS
TO TURN THE MOJAVE DESERT
INTO ONE OF AMERICA'S
MOST IMPRESSIVE CASINOS.
WHITAKER AND ASSOCIATES
IS THE MOST QUALIFIED
FINANCIAL ORGANIZATION
TO BRING YOUR ASTONISHING
VISION TO REALITY.
THANK YOU.
[BROTHER] EXCELLENT.
[BROTHER #2] VERY GOOD JOB.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
ARIGATO.
I'M SORRY. COULD SOMEONE
TRANSLATE FOR ME?
- [CHUCKLES]
- I JUST COMPLIMENTED
MS. DOHERTY
ON HER PRESENTATION.
EXCELLENT.
DID YOU SEE THE LOOK
ON THEIR FACES?
I DID.
WE REALLY WON THEM OVER.
YOU KNOW, MEGHAN,
I DON'T HAND OUT
COMPLIMENTS TOO EASILY,
BUT YOU WERE OUTSTANDING
TODAY AND I MEAN THAT.
BUT BEFORE WE START
BLOWING OUR OWN HORN HERE,
WE STILL HAVE SOME
UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
WALK WITH ME TO MY CAR.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S NOT
WASTE ANY TIME WITH THIS.
I WANT YOU TO GET UP THERE
AS EARLY AS TOMORROW.
HAVE YOU ASSISTANT CALL AHEAD
AND SET UP A MEETING WITH
GRAHAM.
AND MEGHAN,
DO NOT PULL ANY PUNCHES
WITH THIS GUY.
LET HIM KNOW
THAT YOU MEAN BUSINESS,
THAT NOTHING,
AND I MEAN NOTHING,
WILL STOP WHITAKER AND
ASSOCIATES FROM CLOSING
THAT DEAL.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CAN FEEL IT.
GOD IS ON OUR SIDE,
SO YOU CLOSE THIS.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
HELLO?
I THOUGHT MAYBE I'D
HAVE A CHANCE TO SPEAK
WITH MY ONLY CHILD.
BUT SHE'S ALWAYS TOO BUSY
FOR HER ONLY MOTHER.
SORRY, MOTHER.
I'VE BEEN SWAMPED AT WORK.
WELL, IT MUST BE GOING WELL.
I RECEIVED ANOTHER CHECK
IN THE MAIL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
EVERY WEEK THE CHURCH
HANDS OUT FOOD DONATIONS
TO SENIOR CITIZENS.
SO I'M HEADED ON OVER
TO THE RETIREMENT HOME,
WHICH IS WHERE I'LL BE
LIVING IN A COUPLE OF YEARS.
MA, COME ON. YOU
MAKE ME FEEL SO GUILTY.
WELL, YOU SHOULD.
WHAT HAS IT BEEN, ALMOST SIX
MONTHS SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS COMING
WEEKEND IS.
NO, MA, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THIS COMING WEEKEND IS.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY, MEGHAN.
LISTEN, PASADENA IS NOT
THAT FAR FROM LOS ANGELES,
SO I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ANY
EXCUSES, AND I DON'T WANT
ANOTHER CHECK FROM YOU.
I WANT TO BE WITH
MY DAUGHTER ON MY BIRTHDAY.
OKAY, MA, I WILL BE WITH
YOU ON YOUR BIRTHDAY.
I PROMISE.
CROSS YOUR HEART?
CROSS MY HEART.
HA! OH, I'M SO EXCITED
I'M GONNA SEE YOU FINALLY!
I LOVE YOU.
LOVE YOU TOO, MOM.
[GROANS]
ALL RIGHT.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
HELLO, ADAM.
MEGHAN, HEY.
MR. WHITAKER ASKED ME
TO GET YOU ON THE PHONE.
- HOLD THAT NOTE.
- YOU GET MEGHAN
ON THE PHONE YET?
- WHAT DOES HE WANT
TO TALK ABOUT?
- YES, SIR.
- ADAM, WAIT--
- HELLO, MEGHAN. YOU'RE
HEADING UP THERE, I HOPE.
YES, SIR. I SHOULD BE THERE
IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
GOOD. LISTEN TO ME.
THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS ARE
SCHEDULED TO FLY
BACK INTO TOWN
THIS THURSDAY
TO FINALIZE EVERYTHING.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
I AM DEPENDING ON YOU
TO TAKE CARE OF THIS.
DON'T PLAN. DO IT.
YES, SIR. I PLAN TO.
CALL ME THE SECOND YOU HAVE
YOUR MEETING WITH GRAHAM.
DO NOT LEAVE HIS SIDE WITHOUT
SIGNING THOSE DOCUMENTS.
BYE.
[GROANS]
"CLOSE IT."
I'LL CLOSE IT.
I'LL SHOW HIM.
I'LL MAKE PARTNER
AND FORCE HIM TO RETIRE.
WHERE AM I?
OKAY--
I'LL FIND IT.
[SIGHS]
[MOTOR STOPS]
WHOO!
PARIS HILTON AIN'T GOT NOTHIN'
ON YOU, GIRL!
DA-DA-DA-DA!
I'M SORRY, MA'AM--
DON'T TOUCH THE CAR!
MA'AM, IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
THAT A FERRARI PULLS UP.
HOO!
[DOOR CLOSES]
HEY, MY NAME IS LENNY.
I'M ONE OF THE COUNSELORS
HERE.
- OKAY--
- I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T
GET YOUR NAME.
I DIDN'T GIVE
MY NAME TO YOU.
LISTEN, I'M LOOKING
FOR MR. GRAHAM.
IS HE AROUND?
MR. GRAHAM IS ALWAYS AROUND.
WELL THEN, CAN YOU
GET HIM FOR ME?
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
HEY, UH, MR. GRAHAM,
THERE'S A WOMAN OUT HERE
WITH A FERRARI.
[GROANS]
[WALKIE TALKIE BEEPS]
REALLY? WHERE'S SHE FROM?
MY NAME IS DOHERTY.
WHERE--
WHERE IS SHE FROM?
MRS. DOUBTFIRE, HE WANTS
TO KNOW WHERE YOU'RE FROM.
DOHERTY.
MY NAME IS DOHERTY.
HUH?
I'M FROM WHITAKER
AND ASSOCIATES.
WHITAK-- OH, JUST--
HUH?
- I'M SORRY, MA'AM.
I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU'RE--
MR. GRAHAM,
THIS IS MEGHAN DOHERTY.
I'M WITH WHITAKER
AND ASSOCIATES.
MY ASSISTANT
CALLED YESTERDAY.
HELLO, MR. GRAHAM?
MR. GRAHAM?
MA'AM. MA'AM.
WHAT?
MA'AM!
IF YOU WANT TO TALK
TO MR. GRAHAM,
YOU HAVE TO PUSH
THAT BUTTON RIGHT THERE.
WHERE IS HIS OFFICE?
[GROANS]
INCOMPETENT PEOPLE.
OOH, THAT'S A NICE RIDE!
HOO!
[WHISTLES]
ONE FANCY AUTOMOBILE.
MR. GRAHAM.
WHAT?
NO, GIVE ME A HUG.
THERE WE GO.
MS. DOHERTY?
DOHERTY. MEGHAN DOHERTY.
- GOOD TO MEET YOU.
THIS IS PASTOR TINSLEY.
- HOW DO YOU DO?
- PASTOR TINSLEY,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- BREATHTAKING.
PASTOR TINSLEY'S CHURCH
IS GONNA BE OUR GUEST
ALL THIS WEEK AT CAMP.
MR. GRAHAM, IS THERE SOMEPLACE
WE CAN SPEAK IN PRIVATE?
WELL, SURE.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
AHEM.
HAVE A SEAT.
I NEED TO GET RIGHT
TO THE POINT.
AS YOU KNOW, WE'RE
THE LENDER IN SECOND
POSITION ON YOUR PROPERTY.
MR. WHITAKER SENT ME DOWN HERE
TO DISCUSS YOUR PROPERTY
IN ITS CURRENT STATE.
YOU'RE IN FORECLOSURE,
SET TO GO TO AUCTION
THIS SATURDAY.
SINCE WE DON'T WANT TO RISK
ANYONE ELSE ATTEMPTING TO BUY
YOUR PROPERTY,
I'M HERE TO MAKE YOU AN OFFER
AND CLOSE ON THIS DEAL TODAY.
HMM. IT'S FUNNY--
I SPOKE TO ONE OF YOU
PEOPLE THE OTHER DAY.
NOW WHITAKER'S SENDING
SOMEBODY DOWN HERE
TO PATRONIZE ME?
MR. GRAHAM, I AM NOT
PATRONIZING YOU.
I'M HERE TO MAKE YOU
A SERIOUS CASH OFFER,
AN OFFER I KNOW
IS MORE THAN FAIR.
LOOK, YOU'RE BEHIND
IN MONTHLY PAYMENTS,
BEHIND ON YOUR TAXES.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO HELP.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SIGN
THE POWER OF OWNERSHIP
OVER TO US
- AND WE CAN
HANDLE THE REST.
- MS. DOHERTY,
I MAY BE A LITTLE LATE
PAYING THIS MORTGAGE,
BUT I SERVE AN ON-TIME GOD,
AND HE WILL DELIVER US
FROM THIS FINANCIAL HOLD
YOUR BANK HAS ON US.
- MR. GRAHAM--
- DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS PLACE?
OR ARE YOU JUST DOWN
HERE TO EARN A COMMISSION?
I'M HERE TO DO YOU A FAVOR.
FOLLOW ME.
[LAUGHS]
I'D LIKE TO TAKE YOU ON
A LITTLE TOUR OF THE CAMP.
A TOUR IS NOT GOING TO CHANGE
THE POSITION YOU'RE IN.
COME ON. WHAT DO YOU
HAVE TO LOSE?
[MOTOR STARTS]
HMMM.
I'M SECOND-GENERATION
LAND OWNER OF GRAHAM HOLDINGS.
MY DAD WAS A MINISTER.
I USE THIS LAND
TO GIVE BACK TO GOD,
FOR ME REBELLING AGAINST
HIS RIGHTEOUS WAYS WHEN
I WAS A KID.
LOOK AT IT.
I LOVE THIS LAND.
THERE'S NO PLACE LIKE IT.
OUR MINISTRY HAS TAKEN
A BIG HIT, JUST AS I'M
SURE RESIDENTIAL HAS.
CHURCHES CAN'T TITHE
THE WAY THEY USED TO
OR PAY EXTRAS FOR THE KIDS,
AND THAT TRICKLES DOWN
TO PEOPLE LIKE US.
MEGHAN YOU CAN TELL WHITAKER
I HAVE TO DECLINE HIS OFFER.
LISTEN, THE DEAL
IS THE DEAL.
YOU CAN PRAY TO YOUR GOD
ANY TIME, DAY OR NIGHT,
BUT IT'S NOT GONNA STOP
THE FACT THAT OUT BANK
IS GONNA TAKE THIS PROPERTY.
TAKE ME BACK TO MY CAR.
MEGHAN, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'D BE WILLING TO PUT MY FAITH
THAT GOD WILL COME THROUGH
AND THIS WILL ALL BE
WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE.
IF YOU'LL JUST STAY HERE
FOR SIX DAYS.
SEE WHAT IT IS WE DO HERE.
WATCH GOD'S BLESSINGS UNFOLD.
AND THEN IF BY SOME CHANCE
YOU DON'T SEE WHY THIS LAND
IS SO IMPORTANT,
I'LL SIGN YOUR DEAL BEFORE
THE LAND GOES TO AUCTION
SO YOU CAN GET YOUR
BIG COMMISSION CHECK.
LISTEN, TAKE THE CHECK,
GATHER YOUR CHRISTIAN FOLK,
AND GO BUILD A CHURCH
IN A NEW LOCATION.
NEAR A CITY WHERE
PEOPLE ACTUALLY LIVE.
MS. DOHERTY,
I KNOW AS LONG AS I
DON'T PUT MY SIGNATURE
ON THAT DOCUMENT,
I HAVE A FIGHTING
CHANCE TO KEEP WHAT'S
RIGHTFULLY MINE.
NO, IT'S NOT OVER
TILL GOD SAYS IT'S OVER.
AND GOD HASN'T
TOLD ME ANYTHING.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, WHY WOULD ME STAYING HERE
FOR SIX DAYS
MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE IN WHETHER
OR NOT YOU SIGN THIS DEAL?
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SEE
WHAT WE DO HERE WITH
YOUR OWN EYES.
MAYBE THEN YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
WHY I'M WILLING TO PUT MY
FAITH IN GOD
AND FIGHT TO KEEP
THIS PLACE OPEN
TO HELP PEOPLE IN NEED.
TO YOU, THIS IS JUST
ANOTHER BUSINESS DEAL.
THIS IS MY WHOLE LIFE.
IF IT'S MORE MONEY YOU WANT,
LET ME CALL MR. WHITAKER.
LET'S UP THE OFFER.
YOU HAVE MY OFFER.
SIX DAYS AND I'LL SIGN. THAT'S
MY PROMISE TO YOU AND TO GOD.
ONE CONDITION. THE DEAL
REMAINS BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYBODY ELSE.
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE
AROUND HERE TO JUDGE
OR TREAT YOU
ANY DIFFERENTLY THAN
THE REST OF THE GUESTS.
ALL RIGHT.
DEAL.
OKAY.
I JUST NEED
TO MAKE A FEW CALLS.
[BEEPING]
MEGHAN.
[GASPS]
YOU SCARED THE LIVING
DAYLIGHTS OUT OF ME.
SORRY. WE HAVE A CAMP
MEETING IN FIVE MINUTES.
ABOUT THIS DEAL,
I NEED TO GO AND MAKE
A CALL TO MY OFFICE.
I NEED TO GO HOME AND
GET SOME EXTRA CLOTHING,
BECAUSE THE ONLY CLOTHING
I HAVE IS WHAT I'M WEARING.
NOW, DO YOU HAVE A PHONE
IN YOUR OFFICE I CAN USE?
FIVE MINUTES. AND YOU
CAN LEAVE ALL YOUR STUFF
IN THE CAR.
NO ONE'S GONNA MESS
WITH IT. FIVE MINUTES.
[PHONE BEEPING]
HASN'T ANYONE EVER TOLD THEM
THAT STARING ISN'T POLITE?
MEGHAN, LISTEN,
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN MY
CHURCH'S CONGREGATION?
YOU CAN BE
OUR SPECIAL GUEST.
MAYBE YOU COULD TEACH MY KIDS
A LITTLE SOMETHING ABOUT
WHATEVER IT IS THAT YOU DO.
THEY LOVE YOUR CAR.
SURE. WHATEVER YOU SAY.
AWESOME. THANK YOU.
[BEEPING]
I GUESS SOMEBODY DIDN'T GET
THE MEMO ABOUT APPROPRIATE
ATTIRE.
I'M JACOB. EVERYONE
AROUND HERE CALLS ME JAKE.
WELL, JACOB, YOU CAN
KEEP YOUR SMART COMMENTS
TO YOURSELF.
LOOK, I JUST SAW YOU WALK
IN HERE WITH MY FATHER,
AND I CAN TELL BY THE
WAY THAT YOU'RE DRESSED
THAT YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY NOT ONE
OF THE CHURCH GROUP LEADERS.
SO, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
I'M HERE FOR THE SAME REASON
AS EVERYONE ELSE.
ENLIGHTENMENT.
NOW I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU ARE, BUT--
I'M SORRY, DID YOU JUST SAY
THAT WAS YOUR FATHER?
YEAH. I RUN THIS PLACE
WITH MY PARENTS.
I'M THE HEAD COUNSELOR HERE.
SORRY. MEGHAN DOHERTY.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
WELCOME TO GOD'S COUNTRY.
I WANT YOU TO SHAKE AWAY
ALL THE WORRIES OF YOUR
DAY-TO-DAY RAT RACE
AND PEER PRESSURE, AND
ESPECIALLY VIDEO GAMES,
SOCIAL NETWORKING, AND UH--
[PHONE BEEPS]
TEXTING.
[CLEARS THROAT]
YOU'RE HERE TO RELAX,
MAKE FRIENDS,
AND MOST OF ALL, DISCOVER
THAT REAL INNER LOVE OF SELF
AND GOD'S SPIRIT.
BEFORE WE BEGIN, I WANT YOU
TO TURN TO THE PERSON
TO YOUR RIGHT AND LEFT,
AND GIVE THEM A BIG
WELCOMING HUG.
HEY.
OH!
OKAY.
OH MY--
[GIRL SQUEALS]
[GRAHAM LAUGHS]
MEGHAN, I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
MY BETTER HALF OVER HERE
FOR ALMOST 25 YEARS NOW,
CAROLINE.
SHE'S SORT OF THE MOTHER HEN,
CARETAKER OF THE CAMP.
SO IF YOU GET SICK, BITTEN,
OR JUST PLAIN HOMESICK,
SHE'S--
HONEY, STOP IT.
BITTEN?
HE'S JUST PULLING YOUR LEG.
IF IT WAS THE SUMMER TIME,
YES,
BUT IN THE COOLER MONTHS
WE DON'T HAVE THAT PROBLEM.
GOOD TO KNOW.
OH, HEY, MEGHAN,
THIS IS GERI.
- SHE'S ONE OF THE COUNSELORS
HERE. YOU GUYS SHOULD--
- HI.
ARE YOU A MODEL?
YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
I KNOW YOUR FEET MUST BE
KILLING YOU IN THOSE
HIGH HEELS.
GERI, GO FETCH MEGHAN
A PAIR OF YOUR BOOTS.
- NO.
- THEY'LL PROBABLY
BE A LITTLE TOO BIG,
BUT THEY'LL GIVE YOUR FEET
A MUCH NEEDED REST.
JUST SHOW ME TO MY ROOM
SO I CAN GET ON MY LAPTOP
AND MAKE A FEW CALLS,
AND I'LL BE AWESOME.
[ALL LAUGHING]
MEGHAN, YOU'RE KIND OF MISSING
THE POINT OF WHAT WE DO HERE
IN GOD'S COUNTRY.
AND THAT IS--
OFF THE GRID.
HERE YOU GO.
ANYWAY, WELCOME ABOARD.
GRUDGE MATCH. PING PONG.
LET'S GO. WANT TO WATCH?
I'M GONNA WATCH.
THOSE ARE FOR YOU.
I'LL TAKE YOU
TO YOUR TRAILER.
YOU'RE GONNA WANT THOSE.
I'M NOT WEARING THEM.
MY TRAILER?
[PAINED GROAN]
WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS YOUR LIVING QUARTERS.
SORRY IT'S NOT
THE PLAZA HOTEL.
I AM NOT STAYING IN THAT.
WELL,
IT'S STAY IN THAT TRAILER,
OR IN THE HOUSE WITH ALL
HERE OR THERE.
WHAT HAVE I GOTTEN
MYSELF INTO?
GROSS!
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
GET OFF!
[COYOTE HOWLING]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
STALKING ME?
NO, I JUST CAME BY
TO SEE IF YOU WERE OKAY.
I AM NOT OKAY!
I HEAR THESE THINGS
HOWLING AT ME AND
THERE WAS THIS BIG BUG--
WAIT. A BUG?
YES! ARE YOU LAUGHING AT ME?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HEY, MOM?
[WALKIE TALKIE BEEPS]
YEAH, HONEY.
CAN YOU SEND GERI TO
TRAILER NUMBER ONE, PLEASE?
WHAT'S UP, JAKE?
IT'S MEGHAN.
AND A BUG.
IT WAS A BIG BUG.
BIG.
SORRY. A BIG BUG ATTACKED HER,
AND NOW SHE REFUSES TO GO
TO THE TRAILER.
YOU WANT ME TO SEND SOMEONE
TO STAY WITH HER?
- AFFIRMATIVE.
-  OKAY, HONEY. I'LL TELL GERI.
BYE BYE.
THANKS.
IT WAS A BIG, BIG BUG.
IT'S ALL CLEAR.
HI AGAIN.
ARE YOU ALWAYS SO PETULANT?
OH.
THEY ACTUALLY SAID THAT YOU
NEEDED A LITTLE HELP OUT HERE
SO WE'RE GONNA BE
ROOMMATES NOW.
I HOPE THAT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT TOO ADJUSTED
TO THE WILD, HUH?
- THAT'S OKAY.
- WELL, NOW YOU HAVE
YOUR BODYGUARD.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
OKAY, THIS IS FOR YOU.
WHAT IS THIS?
MR. GRAHAM SAID THAT YOU
NEEDED SOME CLOTHES TO WEAR,
SO I JUST BROUGHT YOU
SOME OF MY OWN.
I'M NOT WEARING THAT.
WE DON'T GET ANY SIGNALS
OUT HERE.
WHAT, ARE YOU GUYS
IN THE 1800's?
HOW DO YOU
LIVE LIKE THIS?
LIVE LIKE WHAT?
LIKE THIS. NO CELL PHONE,
WI-FI.
WHAT ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE PROVING?
WE'RE NOT TRYING
TO PROVE ANYTHING.
WE'RE ACTUALLY JUST
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
WHAT?
HEY, MEGHAN.
DO YOU MIND IF WE JUST SAY
A QUICK PRAYER BEFORE WE
HEAD IN FOR THE NIGHT?
PRAY ON.
OKAY.
[PHONE RINGING]
YOU'VE REACHED MEGHAN DOHERTY.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
MEGHAN, BET YOU WRAPPED
GRAHAM AND THOSE DOCUMENTS
AROUND YOUR
LITTLE FINGER TODAY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR
ABOUT IT. CALL ME.
[GERI] MEGHAN, WAKE UP!
MEGHAN. MEGHAN. MEGHAN.
WAKE UP, SLEEPYHEAD!
[MEGHAN SNORES]
♪ RISE AND SHINE
♪ AND KICK OUT
THE GLORY, GLORY  ♪
WHAT TIME IS IT?
IT'S 6:00.
6:00 A.M.?
YEAH.
COME BACK AT 10:00 A.M.
I DON'T DO BREAKFAST.
GERI, WHERE'S MEGHAN?
SHE WOULDN'T GET UP.
JAKE, WILL YOU ASK PASTOR
TINSLEY TO START THIS
MORNING'S PRAYER SERVICE?
YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
THANKS. BE RIGHT BACK.
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL, HOW'S
EVERYBODY DOING TODAY?
[CLANGING]
[SCREAMS]
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
WE'RE HAVING PRAYER
BEFORE BREAKFAST
AND YOU HAVE TO JOIN
YOUR ASSIGNED GROUP.
LISTEN. I'M TIRED. I
AM NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
AND I HAVE AGREED TO
STAY HERE FOR SIX DAYS.
[YAWNS]
YOU AGREED TO BE PART
OF THE JOURNEY.
BEING PART OF THE JOURNEY
MEANS TAKING THE JOURNEY.
NOW IF YOU DON'T SHOW UP
FOR YOUR ASSIGNED GROUP,
OUR AGREEMENT'S OFF.
YOU CAN GET BACK IN YOUR
FANCY CAR AND DRIVE BACK
TO LOS ANGELES TODAY.
OKAY. I GET YOUR
POINT. LET ME JUST
GO TAKE A SHOWER--
NO TIME FOR THAT.
YOU GOTTA MEET YOUR GROUP.
BREAKFAST IS IN 15 MINUTES.
GET UP,
THROW SOME WATER ON YOUR
FACE, I'LL SEE YOU OUT HERE.
JAKE, DO WE KNOW
WHERE YOUR FATHER IS?
THERE SHE IS.
MEGHAN, I THOUGHT WE COULD
ALL SIT DOWN TOGETHER,
AND EAT AS A FAMILY.
LET'S BOW OUR HEADS
IN PRAYER.
AND JESUS SAID UNTO THEM,
"I AM THE BREAD OF LIFE,
HE THAT COMETH TO ME
SHALL NEVER HUNGER
AND HE THAT BELIEVETH
ON ME SHALL NEVER THIRST.
[ALL] AMEN.
AMEN.
NOW WE CAN EAT.
ALL RIGHT, GANG, REMEMBER
THIS IS A CONTEST
SO THERE ARE SPECIAL
REWARD ACTIVITIES
FOR THE GROUP THAT
PULLS TOGETHER AND
DOES THE BEST JOB.
THE FIRST ACTIVITY IS
A TWO-MILE HIKE UP TO
THE TENNIS COURTS.
LENNY, IT'S ALL YOU, BUDDY.
WAIT.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I AM NOT DRESSED
FOR A TWO-MILE HIKE
OUT IN THIS JUNGLE.
I'D ACTUALLY BE MORE
WORRIED ABOUT THE SNAKES.
[LAUGHS]
COME ON, I'M JUST
KIDDING WITH YOU.
I GOT YOUR BACK.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
OKAY, LET'S GO FOR A HIKE!
[ALL CHEER]
[BEEPING]
[PHONE RINGING]
YOU'VE REACHED MEGHAN DOHERTY.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
HOLA, MEGHAN, YOU'VE BEEN
GONE FOR TWO DAYS NOW.
WE ALL KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
WORKING ON A A BIG DEAL
YOU STOP COMMUNICATING,
BUT YOU MISSED OUR WEEKLY
FACIAL APPOINTMENT TODAY,
AND THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
OKAY, CALL ME. BYE.
GROUP THREE, WE'RE HERE,
AND YOU MIGHT NOTICE
THAT THERE ARE
NO TENNIS RACKETS. BUT,
WE DO HAVE THESE.
OH, NO.
IT IS BAD ENOUGH
THAT WE HIKED TWO MILES,
AND NOW YOU EXPECT US
TO WORK?
COME ON. IT'LL BE FUN.
YOU'LL HAVE FUN.
WE'RE GONNA
CLEAN THIS PLACE UP.
WE'RE GONNA GET IT NICE
AND BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT IS FUN ABOUT HIKING TWO
MILES TO CLEAN A TENNIS COURT?
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE WORK.
IT'S ABOUT US
WORKING TOGETHER
AS A TEAM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT I'M HEARING.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE BRAINWASHED.
[GROANS]
OKAY.
WE'LL START ON THIS END,
AND WE GOTTA
WORK OUR WAY BACK.
LET'S DO IT!
HEY, MEGHAN.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
NO. WHAT DO KIDS LEARN
FROM HIKING TWO MILES
UP TO A TENNIS COURT
COVERED IN WEEDS,
AND GUESS WHAT? HERE ARE SOME
GLOVES AND SHOVELS AND LET'S
CLEAN THE TENNIS COURT
AND LEARN ABOUT
THE GOOD LORD.
HMMM.
- CALM DOWN.
- I AM NOT     GOING TO
CALM DOWN!
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SIGN THIS DOCUMENT?
JUST GIVE UP ALREADY.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO
TO SAVE THIS LAND.
I GET IT THAT YOU ARE A MAN OF
GOD AND YOU LIVE OFF THIS AND,
BUT I DON'T SEE
A MIRACLE THAT'S GONNA
COME OUT OF THE SKY
AND SAVE THIS PLACE!
YOU DONE?
NO. DO YOU WANT
MORE MONEY?
'CAUSE IF YOU WANT
MORE MONEY, I COULD
GET YOU MORE MONEY.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT?
MS. DOHERTY--
WE HAVE AN AGREEMENT.
I PLAN TO STICK TO MY END
IF YOU STICK TO YOURS.
NOW IF YOU DON'T
GET BACK TO YOUR GROUP,
DEAL'S OFF.
OH!
WELL, WELCOME BACK!
[BLOW DRYER BLOWS, STOPS]
I NEED A FACIAL
AND A MAKEOVER SO BAD.
WOW, YOU LOOK SO
DIFFERENT.
YOU LOOK REALLY PRETTY
WITHOUT MAKEUP.
[GROANS]
OH, MY BODY HURTS SO BAD.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD A FACIAL
OR--?
[LAUGHS] NO.
NO.
SIT RIGHT THERE.
'KAY.
YOU HAVE PRETTY HEALTHY SKIN.
YOU SHOULD TAKE CARE OF IT.
OH, I WASH IT WITH SOAP.
SOAP?
SOAP IS THE HARSHEST THING
ON A LADY'S SKIN. HUH-UH.
MY FRIEND VALENTINA AND I,
WE GET A FACIAL ONCE A WEEK.
OH.
I FEEL LIKE MY
FACE IS CRACKING.
WANT TO SEE?
[GIGGLES]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
GOOD MORNING!
[GROANS]
WHAT TIME IS IT?
5:45.
[GROANS]
WHY DO WE HAVE TO GET UP
SO EARLY?
"EARLY TO BED, EARLY TO RISE,
MAKES A GIRL HEALTHY, WEALTHY,
AND WISE."
ALL RIGHT, I KNOW THAT'S
NOT IN THE BIBLE.
HOW DID YOU SLEEP? GOSH,
LAST NIGHT WAS SO SPECIAL.
JUST, IT WAS LIKE ALMOST
LIKE I HAD A SISTER.
OW!
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT FEELS LIKE SOMEONE'S
POURED CONCRETE DOWN MY BACK.
- OH NO!
- LISTEN, WHY DON'T
YOU JUST GO AHEAD
AND TELL MR. GRAHAM
THAT I CAN'T GET OUT OF BED
BECAUSE MY BACK HURTS.
JUST GO AHEAD.
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[DOOR SHUTS]
HELLO, MEGHAN?
MY DAD ASKED ME
TO COME CHECK ON YOU.
[KNOCKING]
MEGHAN, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M GONNA COME IN.
ARE YOU DRESSED?
OW! OW!
OW! [GROANS]
ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, I'M ALL RIGHT.
I JUST STRAINED MY BACK
FROM PULLING WEEDS YESTERDAY.
I THOUGHT I HAD SOME
IBUPROFEN IN THE CAR.
WELL COME ON, LET'S
GET YOU SOME ASPIRIN.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO KNOW
WHERE THERE WOULD BE A PHONE
I COULD USE.
YEAH, WELL, THE ONLY PHONE'S
IN MY FATHER'S OFFICE.
OTHER THAN THAT THE CLOSEST
PHONE'S ABOUT 10 MILES AWAY
IN THE NEAREST TOWN.
I COULD ASK HIM IF YOU LIKE.
OH. OH, NO.
I GUESS I COULD DRIVE
YOU TO TOWN IF IT'S
THAT IMPORTANT.
YES, IT IS THAT IMPORTANT.
JUST FAR ENOUGH UNTIL
I GET SOME CELL SIGNAL,
- AND THEN I COULD
MAKE THE CALL.
- YEAH, SURE.
COME ON. WE'LL TAKE MY CAR
AND WE'LL BE
BACK BEFORE LUNCH.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
[GROANS]
WHERE ARE
YOU GUYS HEADED?
SHE NEEDED TO MAKE
AN IMPORTANT CALL
AND USE THE PHONE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BOTHER YOU.
IS THAT RIGHT, MEGHAN?
YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU OKAY?
[SIGHS]
YEAH. ALL OF A SUDDEN
I JUST FEEL SICK.
MAYBE CAROL CAN HELP YOU
WITH HER SUDDEN SICKNESS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
I'LL BE OKAY.
I JUST NEED TO
SIT DOWN AND REST.
RUN! RUN!
[ALL CHEERING, ROOTING]
WE WOULD HAVE WON
IF I DIDN'T HAVE TO RUN
TWO LEGS OF THE RACE.
YEAH, WHAT'S HER PROBLEM?
SHE SCARED OF BREAKING A NAIL?
SO HOW DO YOU FEEL?
I STILL FEEL A LITTLE DIZZY.
I UNDERSTAND IF YOU
WANT TO LEAVE, BUT--
I WASN'T TRYING TO LEAVE.
I WILL BE HERE
UNTIL NEXT SATURDAY,
'CAUSE WE AGREED
THAT YOU WOULD SIGN THAT DEED.
AND I'LL BE HERE TO
PERSONALLY HAND IT TO YOU.
IT SURE LOOKED LIKE YOU
WERE TRYING TO LEAVE TODAY.
I WASN'T TRYING TO LEAVE.
I WAS MAKING A CALL.
A JOB IS AT STAKE
AND I NEEDED TO LET
MR. WHITAKER KNOW
IT'S TAKING A LOT LONGER
THAN I THOUGHT.
MEGHAN, THE POINT IS
TO LEAVE THAT BEHIND.
YOU BEING HERE
IS ABOUT RESTING
AND GETTING IN TOUCH
WITH GOD.
CALLING WHITAKER
IS NOT GONNA CHANGE THAT
OR SPEED UP THE PROCESS.
YOU ARE JUST SO IN CONTROL.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE
FIGURED OUT?
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO KNOWS
HOW BAD THINGS
ARE AROUND HERE.
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOWS THAT THIS MAY BE
THE LAST WEEK
THIS PLACE IS IN BUSINESS.
I WONDER HOW YOUR FAMILY
WOULD FEEL IF THEY FOUND OUT.
YOU THREATENING ME?
[PHONE RINGS]
YOU'VE REACHED MEGHAN DOHERTY.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
MEGHAN, HEY, IT'S ME.
I'VE BEEN CALLING
FOR THREE DAYS NOW.
NO ONE AT GOD'S COUNTRY
IS ANSWERING THE PHONE.
SO, IF YOU HAD CLOSED
THE DEAL YOU WOULD HAVES
CALLED BY NOW, RIGHT?
I'M REALLY GETTING WORRIED.
HOLA, MEGHAN,
SOY YO.
IT'S VALENTINA.
I WISH YOU WOULD JUST
PICK UP THE PHONE.
WE ARE ALL TRYING
TO LOCATE YOU.
I REALLY HOPE THAT
YOUR NOT CALLING HAS ANYTHING
TO DO WITH OUR DISCUSSION
THE OTHER NIGHT.
I'M SO SORRY.
I MISS YOU.
PLEASE, JUST,
JUST CALL ME BACK OR,
OR CALL ADAM, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
BYE.
[SINGING CAMPFIRE SONG]
♪ GOTTA LOVE IT IN GOD'S
COUNTRY...  ♪
NICE!
[CLAPPING]
YOU KNOW WHAT, I WAS
JUST THINKING SOMETHING.
WHEN I WAS A KID GROWING UP
IN CALIFORNIA,
ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT I REMEMBER THE MOST
WAS SPENDING THE HOLIDAYS
TOGETHER WITH MY FAMILY.
AND EVEN THOUGH WE WERE
ALL PACKED IN THERE--
IT WAS A TINY LITTLE
TWO-BEDROOM HOUSE--
I WAS THE RUNT-
RIGHTFULLY SO!
I SLEPT ON THE FLOOR.
I HAD MY BROTHER HERE,
I HAD MY SISTER HERE.
COUSINS EVERYWHERE.
I NEVER FELT CROWDED.
NEVER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I FELT?
I FELT LOVE.
I FELT TOGETHERNESS.
I JUST DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING THAT CAN REPLACE
THAT FEELING,
THAT FEELING OF BEING
TOGETHER WITH YOUR FAMILY.
AMEN.
I THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
TAKE A LITTLE MOMENT HERE
TO REALIZE HOW LUCKY WE ARE
TO BE HERE WITH EACH OTHER.
AMEN.
ALL RIGHT.
[CAMPFIRE SONG CONTINUES]
[PEOPLE TALKING, LAUGHING]
I'M SORRY IF I GOT YOU
INTO ANY TROUBLE THIS MORNING.
NO, YOU DIDN'T GET ME
INTO ANY TROUBLE.
I DO HAVE A QUESTION
FOR YOU.
WHAT'S GOING ON? WHY IS
MY FATHER
HOVERING OVER YOU LIKE
MOTHER OVER A NEW BORN BABY?
WHEN I CAME HERE I TOLD
HIM THAT I NEEDED HELP.
AND SO HE AGREED TO HELP ME
AND TREAT ME LIKE EVERYONE
ELSE.
I'M NOT BEING NOSY,
BUT HELP YOU WITH WHAT?
DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT
A DRUG ADDICT OR ANYTHING.
I'M A WORKAHOLIC.
AND SO IT'S WORK THAT
I THINK ABOUT ALL THE TIME
AND HENCE I'M
UP HERE FOR REST.
HENCE, NO CELL PHONES,
NO COMPUTERS,
NONE OF THAT STUFF.
THAT'S WHAT YOUR DAD'S
BEEN HELPING ME WITH.
YEAH, WELL, HE CAN BE
BULLHEADED AND STUBBORN
SOMETIMES.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
HOW'S YOUR BACK?
YOU KNOW, IT'S--
IT'S STILL A LITTLE TIGHT
BUT I THINK THE ASPIRIN
HAS HELPED EASE THE PAIN.
[BOTH]
SO WHAT DO YOU--
[BOTH LAUGH]
SO TELL ME ABOUT JAKE.
I'VE BEEN A COUNSELOR HERE
SINCE MY PARENTS OWN AND
RUN THE PLACE.
I LEFT FOR A COUPLE
OF YEARS TO GO TO
COLLEGE AND BUSINESS SCHOOL
AND THEN I CAME BACK
TO HELP MY MOTHER AND
FATHER RUN IT.
WHERE DID YOU GO
TO BUSINESS SCHOOL?
HARVARD.
YOU WENT TO HARVARD
BUSINESS SCHOOL?
YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE
WORKING AS A COUNSELOR?
WHO NEEDS WALL STREET? I CAME
HERE TO LEARN HOW TO BUILD
THE PERFECT BONFIRE.
PLUS I MAKE
ONE HECK OF A SMORE.
LISTEN, DO YOU
WANT TO COME WITH ME?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO SHOW YOU.
OKAY.
SO, THIS IS MY VISION.
I WANT TO BUILD
A CHRISTIAN COLLEGE WITH
FULL STUDENT HOUSING.
THE CAMPUS WILL BE A STATE
OF THE ART COLLEGE WITH
FULL ACADEMIC CURRICULUM.
AND THE STUDENTS, THEY
CAN EARN COLLEGE CREDIT
AND THEY CAN EARN SCHOLARSHIPS
BY WORKING AT THE CAMP
DURING THE SUMMER.
THIS IS A DAY CARE CENTER
FOR SINGLE MOTHERS THAT
WANT TO ATTEND THE COLLEGE.
THIS IS STUDENT HOUSING,
AND LOOK AT THIS.
THAT'S THE STUDENT ACTIVITY
CENTER.
I'M IMPRESSED.
DOES YOUR FATHER
KNOW ABOUT THIS?
YEAH, OF COURSE HE DOES.
WE SPENT THOUSANDS
PUTTING TOGETHER
A BUSINESS PLAN WITH
SOME REALLY SOLID PROJECTIONS.
AND WE CAN GET STATE FUNDING,
TAX RELIEF.
I'M TALKING ABOUT BUILDING
AN ENTIRE INFRASTRUCTURE HERE,
I MEAN ELECTRICITY, SEWAGE,
WATER, PAVING A ROAD THAT GOES
ALL THE WAY TO THE HIGHWAY.
I'M SORRY. AM I BORING YOU
WITH THIS?
NO! NO.
SO WHY HAVEN'T YOU
PUT THIS PLAN INTO ACTION?
GRAHAM ESTATES IS
A NONPROFIT ORGANIZATION.
IT RAISES MOST OF OUR MONEY
THROUGH CHURCH OFFERINGS.
WITH THE ECONOMY HITTING
ALL CHURCHES, BIG AND SMALL,
IT'S PUT OUR ENTIRE
ORGANIZATION INTO FLUX.
WHAT WE NEED IS
A VENTURE CAPITALIST
TO INVEST,
BUT SO FAR EFFORTS
HAVE FALLEN ON DEAF EARS.
OUR VISION IS
NOT THEIR VISION.
MY FAMILY--
WE REALLY BELIEVE IN HELPING
THOSE WHO NEED HELP.
IT'S GOD'S WAY.
[HOSHI YAKAMOTO]
PAPERWORK LOOKS GOOD.
WE ARE READY TO MOVE FORWARD
WITH WHITAKER AND ASSOCIATES.
MR. WHITAKER, ONE QUESTION--
WHERE'S MS. DOHERTY?
HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING?
NOTHING. ADAM, I'M WORRIED.
- MY BROTHER THINKS
SHE'S VERY IMPRESSIVE.
- [PHONE RINGS]
IT'S BEEN FOUR DAYS!
OKAY, HOLD ON.
YES.
MS. DOHERTY?
VALENTINA HASN'T
HEARD ANYTHING.
...AND SHE IS. SHE IS
VERY IMPRESSIVE INDEED,
- AND RIGHT NOW SHE'S AWAY.
SHE'S HANDLING...
- UH--
...SOME VERY DETAILED
BUSINESS...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
OR HOW TO REACH HER.
WHY DOESN'T SOMEONE JUST
DRIVE DOWN THERE AND MAKE
SURE SHE'S ALL RIGHT?
- UH...
- ...I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT
EVERYTHING IS GOING TO PLAN,
AND THE CLOSING WILL
TAKE PLACE ON TIME.
HOW'S THE WEATHER
OVER THERE, HOSHI?
MR. WHITAKER DOESN'T WANT
TO GO DOWN AND INTERFERE.
HE'D PREFER FOR MEGHAN
TO CALL IN.
SHE'S WORKING ON SOME
REALLY BIG DEAL FOR THE FIRM.
I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT IT,
THOUGH, OTHER THAN IT'S
WORTH A LOT OF MONEY.
FORGET WHITAKER AND HOW MUCH
MONEY THIS DEAL IS WORTH.
WHAT IF SHE'S IN TROUBLE?
WHAT IF SHE NEEDS OUR HELP?
- UH--
-  ANYTHING COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO HER.
YOU GET ON THAT PHONE
AND CALL THE STATE POLICE
AND PLACE A MISSING PERSONS
REPORT.
DON'T JUST SIT AROUND
AND DO NOTHING.
YOU HEAR ME?
OKAY, WELL, LOOK, MR. WHITAKER
SAYS IF SHE DOESN'T CALL IN
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS,
HE'LL GO DOWN THERE HIMSELF.
ALL RIGHT? I GOTTA GO, THOUGH.
OKAY, BYE.
YOU CAN'T KEEP
PUTTING THIS OFF.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW. WE'VE TRIED
HER CELL MANY TIMES.
THERE'S NO ANSWER.
ADAM, OUR FRIEND IS MISSING.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO CALL 911, I WILL.
YOU DECIDE.
IF I CALL 911 AND SHE'S OKAY,
I RISK BLOWING HER DEAL
AND MY JOB.
[CHEERING, CLAPPING]
HOW'S YOUR BACK?
MY BACK'S DOING GOOD.
HEY, MEGHAN, I COULD
USE YOUR HELP ON THIS PULL.
NO!
COME ON!
YOU CAN DO IT.
[CLAPPING]
MEGHAN!
MEGHAN! MEGHAN!
OH, WAIT A SECOND.
LET ME PUT MY HAIR UP.
BRING IT ON, BLONDIE!
YOU'RE GOIN' DOWN!
YOU'RE GOIN' DOWN.
YOU GOT NOTHING.
[ADAM] GRAB YOUR ROPES,
EVERYBODY!
ON YOUR MARKS,
GET SET,
PULL!
[SQUEALS]
[JAKE] BRING IT ON!
OKAY, COME ON, COME ON!
ONE, TWO THREE!
COME ON, GUYS!
PULL!
ONE, TWO THREE! PULL!
PULL HARDER!
COME ON GUYS!
HERE WE GO!
ONE, TWO THREE! PULL!
YOU DID
A GREAT JOB!
MEGHAN, HE HAS NEVER LOST!
THAT IS AMAZING!
VICTORY, BABY!
VICTORY!
GREAT JOB.
SO THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT.
WOW.
THIS IS YOUR REWARD
FOR WINNING AT TUG-OF-WAR.
[MEGHAN] YOU DIDN'T
LET ME WIN, DID YOU?
TRUST ME WHEN I TELL YOU THIS.
I LOVE TO WIN TOO MUCH
TO ALLOW YOU TO WIN.
OKAY, I-- I HAVE TO GO.
[TO HERSELF] STAY ON TASK...
- WAIT.
- ...IT'S NOT PERSONAL.
IT'S BUSINESS...
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
CAN YOU TAKE ME BACK
TO CAMP?
MEGHAN, SO,
I SPOKE TO A GUY
OUT AT GOD'S COUNTRY,
AND HE SAID THAT A MEGHAN
DOUBTFIRE WITH A FERRARI
HAS BEEN OUT THERE
FOR THE PAST FIVE DAYS.
SO WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
WHAT HAVE THEY DONE TO YOU?
LOOK, I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE YAKAMOTO DEAL.
BUT IF I DON'T HEAR FROM YOU
BY THE END OF THE AUCTION,
I'M CALLING THE POLICE.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO
FOR A LIVING?
- I'M IN REAL ESTATE.
- OH, REAL ESTATE.
THAT SOUNDS INTERESTING.
I WANT TO MAJOR
IN CIVIL LAW.
MY FATHER'S A LAWYER, SO
I GET TO SEE HOW HE HELPS
PEOPLE OUT OF TIGHT SPOTS.
I CAN NEVER SEE YOU
AS A PERSON WHO WOULD
MAJOR IN LAW.
WHY, 'CAUSE I'M NOT
ALL GLAMOROUS LIKE YOU?
I ALWAYS WANTED TO FIT IN
WITH THE GIRLS, YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST, I HAVE
FOUR BROTHERS.
IT'S JUST EASIER
TO PLAY ROUGH, YOU NOW?
I HAVE AN IDEA. LISTEN,
WHY DON'T YOU COME
TO LOS ANGELES
FOR A WEEKEND WITH ME?
REALLY?
YEAH, WE CAN,
WE CAN GO SHOPPING,
AND--
WE COULD FIND YOU A NEW
HAIR STYLE.
HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
WE COULD HAVE SOME GIRL TIME?
YOU KNOW, JUST DO
A BUNCH OF GIRL THINGS.
I WOULD LIKE THAT.
YEAH?
SOUNDS LIKE
SOMETHING MY MOTHER
AND I WOULD
HAVE DONE TOGETHER.
OH. WHERE'S YOUR MOTHER?
SHE DIED LAST YEAR.
I'M SORRY.
MY FATHER DIED WHEN
I WAS ABOUT YOUR AGE.
I DID EVERYTHING
WITH HIM, AND THEN
WHEN HE DIED I JUST LOST
INTEREST IN EVERYTHING.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU SEEM
TOO NICE TO BE A LAWYER.
ALL THE LAWYERS I KNOW
ARE JUST RUTHLESS.
THERE'S GOOD AND BAD IN
EVERYTHING AND EVERYONE.
I WANT TO BE A LAWYER
SO I CAN--
SO I CAN FIGHT FOR
THE PEOPLE THAT CAN'T AFFORD
TO FIGHT FOR THEMSELVES.
YOU KNOW, FOR EXAMPLE,
SAY THERE'S THIS BIG BANK
THAT LOCKS AN ELDERLY COUPLE
INTO A BAD MORTGAGE,
AND THEN TRIES TO EVICT THEM
FROM THEIR HOME FOR THE MONEY
'CAUSE THEY'RE GREEDY.
THAT'S WHEN I WOULD SWOOP IN--
SUPERLAWYER EXTRAORDINAIRE,
COMING IN, SAVING THE DAY,
SAVING THE ELDERLY COUPLE,
PUNISHES THE BANK,
DOES THE RIGHT THING,
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK
IT'D BE GREAT.
[GERI] I KNOW THIS VERSE ON
GREED. ISAIAH 56:11.
"YEAH, THEY ARE GREEDY DOGS
WHO CAN NEVER HAVE ENOUGH.
THEY ARE SHEPHERDS
THAT CAN NOT UNDERSTAND."
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
WHERE ARE YOU, MEGHAN?
THIS IS WHAT
I WAS TALKING ABOUT, JAKE.
LUKE 10:23.
"BLESSED ARE THE EYES
THAT SEE WHAT YOU SEE."
- HOW ARE YOU DOING
THIS MORNING?
- GREAT. GOOD TO SEE YOU.
YEAH?
HEY, JAKE.
THE TRUCK. WHERE IS IT?
RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE OFFICE.
YUP.
KEYS INSIDE?
THANKS, MAN.
[EDEN] COME IN, MEGHAN.
- EDEN?
- HI, MEGHAN.
HAVE A SEAT.
I HAVE A CONFESSION TO MAKE.
MR. WHITAKER DIDN'T SEND ME
DOWN HERE JUST
TO MAKE AN OFFER.
THERE'S A PAIR OF BUSINESSMEN,
THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS,
AND THEY'RE HERE
TO DEVELOP THE LAND.
THEY WANT TO TURN IT
INTO A CASINO AND RESORT.
IT'S A $100 MILLION DEAL
AND I DON'T SEE ANY WAY
THAT YOU COULD STOP IT
FROM HAPPENING,
ESPECIALLY SINCE TOMORROW
IS THE AUCTION.
THANKS FOR
THE INFORMATION, MEGHAN.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO DO BUT PRAY.
WILL YOU STOP IT?
RIGHT NOW IS THE DECISION!
MR.
WHITAKER IS GONNA COME DOWN
THE ROAD ANY
SECOND NOW AND JUST
SHUT DOWN
THE ENTIRE OPERATION,
INCLUDING ME.
I GET IT. I UNDERSTAND.
THERE IS SOMETHING REALLY
SPECIAL ABOUT THIS LAND.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE PROACTIVE.
JAKE SHARED WITH ME THE ENTIRE
VISION YOU HAVE TO BUILD
A CHRISTIAN COLLEGE.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIND SOMEONE
TO INVEST IN IT,
TO PAY UP THE DEBT,
TO BUY THIS
LAND SO YOU CAN PUT THIS CAMP
I'VE TRIED EVERYTHING.
I'VE CALLED EVERYONE
I KNOW WITH MONEY
THAT COULD MAYBE BAIL ME OUT,
BUT SO FAR, NO ONE.
ALL I HAVE LEFT IS
MY FAITH IN GOD.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
THAT'S ALL I HAVE LEFT.
BUT WHAT ABOUT JAKE
AND EVERYONE ELSE?
JAKE TRUSTS YOU.
HE TRUSTS THAT
YOU AND HIM ARE GONNA
COMPLETE THIS VISION.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT. YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THE WHOLE SITUATION.
YEAH. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GONNA TELL MY FAMILY
TONIGHT.
IT'S NOT FAIR T HIDE THINGS
FROM THE ONES YOU LOVE.
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
THEY HAVE THE RIGHT TO KNOW.
OKAY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
NO. I WANT YOU
TO COME WITH ME.
CAN I HAVE YOUR
ATTENTION, EVERYONE?
IN JOHN CHAPTER 8,
THE PASSAGE STATES,
"THEN YOU WILL KNOW
THE TRUTH, AND THE TRUTH
WILL SET YOU FREE."
WELL, I HAVE A CONFESSION TO
MAKE ABOUT GOD'S COUNTRY.
WE'RE IN FORECLOSURE.
AND AS OF SATURDAY
WE WILL BE NO MORE.
THE LAND WILL GOT TO AUCTION
TO THE HIGHEST BIDDER.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS,
THEY MADE US AN OFFER,
AND WITH THE MONEY,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO
START OVER IN A NEW CITY.
SURE WE CAN START OVER
IN A DIFFERENT CITY,
BUT I LOVE THIS LAND.
WAIT. WHY CAN'T JUST CALL
THE BANK AND ASK THEM TO WORK
SOMETHING OUT WITH US?
BECAUSE I AM THE BANK.
AND MY BOSS WON'T
BAIL YOU OUT OF DEBT.
THERE ARE SOME BUSINESSMEN AND
THEY HAVE MADE A VERY LARGE
OFFER FOR THE LAND-- JAKE!
YOU LIED TO ME.
I DIDN'T LIE TO YOU.
- I JUST DIDN'T
KNOW HOW TO TELL YOU.
- LYING AND NOT TELLING
ARE THE SAME THING TO ME.
[SOBBING]
JAKE, WAIT.
IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
YEAH? AND WHOSE FAULT IS IT?
YOU HID THIS FROM ME!
WHAT ABOUT THE COLLEGE?
WHAT ABOUT THE VISION
THAT WE HAD?
SON, I KNOW--
KNOW WHAT?
THAT WE'RE LOSING EVERYTHING
THAT WE'VE WORKED FOR AND YOU
DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH RESPECT
FOR ME OR THE WORKERS
TO TELL US?
MEGHAN, HOW COULD YOU
DO THIS TO US?
GERI, IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
SHE WAS JUST DOING HER JOB.
EDEN, HOW DID
ALL THIS HAPPEN?
I TRIED EVERYTHING
I COULD TO STOP THIS.
BUT UH, OUR TIME IS SHORT.
I MEET WITH MS. DOHERTY
TOMORROW
TO FINALIZE
THE PAPERWORK.
SO, UM,
LET'S ENJOY THE REST
OF THE CAMP.
PASTOR, COULD YOU LEAD US
IN PRAYER?
SURE.
DEAR HEAVENLY FATHER,
WE ASK FOR YOUR GUIDANCE
AND YOUR WISDOM,
AND THAT YOU MAY POUR
YOUR BLESSING UPON YOUR WORK,
YOUR LAND, AND YOUR PEOPLE.
IN JESUS' NAME WE PRAY.
[ALL]
AMEN.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M SORRY.
[MOTOR HUMMING]
HEY.
YOU KNOW, AS LONG
AS I CAN REMEMBER,
THIS HAS BEEN MY SPOT TO COME
AND GET AWAY FROM THE WORLD,
CLEAR MY MIND FROM
ANY WORRIES, DOUBTS,
FEARS.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO MISLEAD
YOU WHY I WAS HERE.
I'M JUST DOING MY JOB.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
RIGHT? LIKE,
WHO DRIVES UP HERE
IN A FERRARI?
IT'S GOTTA BE
A BANKER OR A LAWYER,
SOMEBODY SELF-ORIENTED.
YEAH, THAT WOULD BE ME.
I WAS EXACTLY THAT PERSON
YOU JUST DESCRIBED WHEN
I CAME HERE.
I WAS ON A MISSION
TO CLOSE ON THIS DEAL
AND GET BACK IN TIME
TO HAVE DRINKS WITH
MY FRIENDS IN THE CITY.
BUT SOMETHING CHANGED.
AFTER SEEING ALL THIS,
AND YOU SHARING YOUR--
YOUR VISION WITH ME,
AND MEETING EVERYONE,
I UNDERSTAND WHY
YOUR FATHER
DOESN'T WANT TO PART
WITH THIS LAND.
THIS REALLY IS GOD'S COUNTRY!
LOOK, I KNOW I CAN'T
BLAME YOU,
BUT I DON'T
HAVE TO LIKE IT.
[CRYING]
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
I FEEL SO BAD.
DON'T. I REALIZE THAT YOU
WERE JUST DOING YOUR JOB.
AND THAT I NEED TO FORGIVE
LIKE JESUS WOULD HAVE.
DO YOU WANT
TO FORGIVE ME?
YES. YES, I DO.
I REALLY ENJOYED
WHAT WE SHARED TOGETHER.
AND I LEARNED THAT THERE'S A
LESSON IN EVERY PART OF LIFE
AND IT IS NOT YOUR FAULT
THAT THIS CAMP IS BROKE.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT JAKE
AND EDEN AND CAROLINE
HAVE TO DEAL WITH.
SO--
I'M GONNA GO FOR A WALK.
WANT ME TO COME
FOR A WALK WITH YOU?
I'D RATHER BE BY MYSELF.
I JUST-- I HAVE
A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
YOU'VE REACHED MEGHAN DOHERTY.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
[ADAM] MEGHAN,
WHITAKER'S FURIOUS.
HE PLANS TO COME OUT THERE
IF YOU DON'T CALL IN.
YOUR JOB'S AT STAKE.
I HOPE YOU'RE DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
[MEGHAN] I SHOULD JUST CLOSE
THE DEAL AND WALK AWAY.
THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO. YOU'VE DONE IT
A MILLION TIMES BEFORE
AND IT'S GOTTEN YOU A FERRARI,
A HOME OUT IN THE HOLLYWOOD
HILLS,
I MEAN,
WHAT MORE DO YOU NEED?
WHO CARES IF I'VE TAKEN AWAY
EVERYTHING THAT
THEY CARE ABOUT?
POW!
WHEN HAVE I EVER
CARED BEFORE?
MEGHAN, JUST STAY ON TASK.
IT'S NOT PERSONAL. IT'S--
IT'S BUSINESS.
HEY, PASTOR TINSLEY!
MEGHAN.
HOW DO YOU FEEL TODAY?
CONFUSED.
OKAY, I'M LISTENING.
YESTERDAY I FELT SO BAD,
AND--
TODAY IS THE LAST DAY,
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE
THE EXECUTIONER.
YOU'RE A GOOD SERVANT.
THAT'S ALL GOD WANTS US
TO BE IS GOOD SERVANTS.
I GUESS I'VE JUST
BEEN EXPERIENCING THIS
OVERWHELMING AMOUNT OF GUILT
THESE LAST FEW DAYS.
IF IT'S GOD'S WILL,
THEN IT'S HIS WILL.
YOU'RE ONLY HIS MESSENGER.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THERE'S
SOMETHING THAT I SHOULD DO.
IF THIS IS GOD'S WILL
THEN IT'S HIS WILL.
GOOD LUCK.
EVERYBODY READY?
HEY! JAKE! JAKE! JAKE!
JAKE, LISTEN. GRAB
YOUR TRUCK AND COME WITH ME.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO EXPLAIN.
JUST FOLLOW ME.
LISTEN, JAKE,
I KNOW YOU DON; T TRUST ME,
BUT I HAVE AN IDEA.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH
OF YOUR IDEAS, OKAY?
WHY SHOULD I TRUST YOU?
YOU STANDING HERE MAD AT ME
IS NOT GOING TO
SAVE THIS LAND.
LET'S GO TO YOUR ROOM.
GET YOUR BUSINESS PLAN.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
IF YOU DON'T TRUST ME,
THEN TRUST GOD.
COME ON.
COME ON! COME ON! COME ON!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
MEGHAN, OH MY GOD!
WHERE ARE YOU? WE'VE
BEEN WORRIED SICK!
ADAM, I'M FINE.
TELL WHITAKER NOTHING, OKAY?
I CAN'T JUST DO THAT.
LOOK, YOU FELL OFF
THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
WE ALL HAVE QUESTIONS.
CALL JASON AND TELL HIM THAT
I AM ON MY WAY BEARING GIFTS.
OKAY, MY FRIEND?
YEAH, OKAY.
MY CAR.
TAKE IT. IT'S YOURS.
JASON, YOU TOLD ME IF
I HAD A GREAT OPPORTUNITY,
YOU WANTED IN.
WHAT IS IT?
THIS IS IT.
IT'S THE FUTURE.
I HOPE YOU HAVE
YOUR CHECK BOOK.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
HELLO.
[HOSHI YAKAMOTO]
MR. WHITAKER, WE CAN NO
LONGER WAIT.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID THE DEAL
WOULD BE CLOSED BY TODAY.
HOSHI, RELAX.
I GAVE YOU MY WORD. YOU
KNOW HOW THESE LAWYERS WORK,
GOING OVER ALL THAT PAPERWORK.
IT TAKES SOME TIME.
I UNDERSTAND THAT,
MR. WHITAKER.
BUT WE HAD A DEAL.
AND WE AGREED UPON A DEADLINE.
YEAH, BUT--
I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR CALL.
[MURMURING]
ALL RIGHT, GATHER AROUND,
FOLKS.
WE'RE GONNA START THE AUCTION
IN ABOUT FIVE MINUTES.
NOW, WHAT YOU'RE GONNA BE
BIDDING ON IS 1,000 ACRES
OF GOD'S COUNTRY.
PLEASE, SERIOUS BIDDERS ONLY.
INCLUDES THREE NICE TRAILERS,
LOVELY LITTLE LOG CABIN,
AND A PRIVATE LAKE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL START
THE BIDDING AT 75,000.
[TRUCK SCREECHES]
WAIT!
- 1,000 ACRES OF--
- NO NO NO NO! WAIT WAIT
WAIT WAIT!
I GOT IT. I GOT THE PAYMENT.
HERE YOU GO.
I'M WITH
WHITAKER AND ASSOCIATES
AND I HEREBY PRESENT TO YOU
TO RESTORE THE LAND
INTO GOOD STANDING.
EVERYTHING SEEMS
TO BE IN ORDER.
SORRY, FOLKS,
NO AUCTION TODAY.
THANKS.
MEGHAN, I HOPE THAT SMILE IS
BECAUSE
WHITAKER AND ASSOCIATES
NO.
WE HAVE A NEW PARTNER.
GOD'S COUNTRY'S GONNA SURVIVE,
SO WE CAN CONTINUE TO
SAVE LIVES AND GIVE BACK.
DO YOU THINK THE WORLD NEEDS
ANOTHER CASINO
TO TAKE PEOPLE'S
WHY COULDN'T YOU
BUILD SOMETHING
THAT GIVES BACK TO MANKIND?
MEGHAN, YOU GOTTA
BE KIDDING ME.
NO, I'M NOT, SIR.
AFTER SPENDING TIME HERE
AND SEEING WHAT THIS LAND
WAS REALLY ABOUT,
I REALIZED I COULD NOT BE
A PART OF BUILDING A CASINO
OUT HERE.
THERE ARE SO MANY OTHER PIECES
OF LAND IN THIS VAST DESERT
WHERE
THE YAKAMOTO BROTHERS CAN
BUILD THEIR CASINO ON.
THIS LITTLE
PIECE OF LAND, THIS
IS TOO VALUABLE,
TO THIS CAMP,
TO THESE PEOPLE,
AND NOW ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE FIRED.
I KNOW.
MEGHAN, I TRUSTED YOU
TO COME UP HERE
AND DO THE RIGHT THING!
AND YOU CROSSED ME?
I DID DO THE RIGHT THING,
AND IT TOOK BEING UP HERE
AT GOD'S COUNTRY AND THIS LAND
TO FINALLY REALIZE THAT.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
WE HAVE A COLLEGE TO BUILD.
[MEGHAN LAUGHS]
MAN, I CAN NOT
BELIEVE YOU GOT RID
OF THAT SWEET RIDE.
LISTEN, I'M GONNA BE IN LOS
ANGELES IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
MAYBE I CAN COME DOWN
THERE AND WE CAN HANG OUT.
PROMISE.
YES.
OH, STOP IT.
I'M GONNA GO GET THE TRUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M REALLY GONNA MISS YOU.
I TOLD YOU I WANT YOU
TO COME HANG OUT WITH ME.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE
JUST SAYING THAT NOW.
PROMISE.
YOU'RE SPECIAL.
THANK YOU.
MEGHAN, WE'RE TRULY
GONNA MISS YOU.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
I DIDN'T. HE DID.
YOU READY TO GO?
I AM.
SO, PARTNER, YOU READY
TO TAKE ME BACK TO THE HUSTLE
AND BUSTLE OF CITY LIFE?
YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALWAYS
WELCOME TO STAY HERE.
YOU CAN TEACH BUSINESS
FINANCE AT THE COLLEGE.
TRUST ME. I'LL BE BACK
TO CHECK ON MY NEW VENTURE.
ESPECIALLY SINCE
I'M OFFICIALLY UNEMPLOYED.
YEAH, WELL, I HOPE BUSINESS
ISN'T THE ONLY REASON
YOU COME BACK.
- HOW ABOUT I BUY YOU DINNER?
- [MEGHAN] YOU KNOW, I KNOW
A GREAT SUSHI PLACE.
[MEGHAN] HEY, DO YOU HAVE
ANY PLANS TOMORROW?
WHY? WHAT DO YOU
HAVE IN MIND?
[PHONE RINGS]
HELLO? MEGHAN!
OH.
WELL, I CAN'T SAY
I'M NOT DISAPPOINTED.
WELL, I KNOW THAT YOU'RE BUSY.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
MEGHAN, CAN YOU WAIT A SECOND?
THERE'S SOMEONE AT THE DOOR.
BE RIGHT BACK.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
OH!
YES?
HI. I HAVE A DELIVERY
FOR A MS. EMMA DOHERTY.
THAT'S ME.
GREAT. THESE ARE FOR YOU.
OH, THANK YOU.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
BYE.
YOU TOO.
OH, MEGHAN.
OKAY, I'M BACK.
I JUST RECEIVED THE FLOWERS.
HOW BEAUTIFUL! THANK YOU.
AT LEAST YOU DIDN'T
FORGET ABOUT ME.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
AGAIN? PLEASE HOLD.
OH!
SURPRISE!
OH, MY GOD! MEGHAN!
OH, SWEETHEART!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MOM.
OH! THANK YOU.
COME IN.
OH MY GOD!
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- THANK YOU!
THIS IS JAKE.
HI, I'M JAKE.
HI!
YEAH, I KNOW!
COME IN!
OH, SWEETHEART,
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THIS!
HEY, COME ON!
I WAS SO SURPRISED!
I JUST COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
I ACTUALLY GOT YOU
A LITTLE SOMETHING.
JAKE, THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY SWEET OF YOU.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
YOUR DAUGHTER'S VERY
IMPORTANT TO ME
IN THE LITTLE TIME
I'VE KNOWN HER.
THAT'S SO SWEET. THANK YOU.
[MURMURING]
YAY! CAKE!
OH, LOOK AT THAT!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MOM.
YOU THINK IT'S BIG ENOUGH?
[ALL LAUGH]
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
OH!
HEY, YOU MEAN
THE WORLD TO ME.
THANKS, SWEETIE.
OKAY, NOW BLOW OUT
YOUR CANDLES.
OKAY. READY?
[MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC ENDS]