I want it with you.
I could be in your hotel
in 10 minutes.
10:00 tonight?
Yes, of course.
I come when you want,
You know.
I'm here for you.
I want to feel you in me.
I want you to fuck me.
I may be coming soon.
No, I understand.
On this evening.
George?
This is Lucy. Hello.
I miss you.
If you arrived?
I'm home in bed
and I think of you.
I kept thinking about you.
I want to feel you in me.
I do not want to wait.
You want what?
Tell me.
I want to.
I arrived a few minutes.
You know what I want.
Yes, you have told me.
I never do.
You just do not want?
With you, though.
I do not know how to say it, but...
You're not like all the others.
I feel these things with you.
I do not feel normal.
There.
Touch me.
You see.
You really missed.
It will be 500 this time, okay?
Good.
Lucy, Bob.
I'm late.
I am in the Goodwin Hotel.
Remember me.
Claire, Mrs. Peña
nurses.
Phone me as soon as possible.
It is very important.
Home care "Rosemont."
Ms. Peña, please.
- Who is calling?
- Claire Dolan.
One moment, please.
Ms. Peña to the device.
I've got bad news.
Your mother died.
I'm sorry.
When she died?
At 10:52 this morning.
He suffered?
No, he went very quickly.
Lucy?
One moment, please.
I for one second.
I gotta go.
I have a promise.
I came.
If you want to
left in his room
Come quickly.
I am now.
This is going to go?
Ira. Thank you.
Are you sure?
I must leave you.
At what time it was.
Sorry I made you wait.
I gotta go.
I have a promise.
It was great.
Call me when you get back.
I want you again.
Promised.
I will miss you...
This will be a long time?
I have a very important undertaking.
Minutes.
On behalf of Mr Roland Cain
that the invoice was issued.
Is that true?
I would prefer to resolve itself.
They send the bill?
Yes, please.
Would you tell Mr Cain
death?
Like you?
No, I do it myself.
Not to be told.
I want to tell her own.
I understand.
No one contacted.
Can you see
in the image?
I do not want weird.
This copy for you.
I will try
managing your mom?
Will not be long.
4000, right?
$ 1,000 interest for a week.
Rest for your debt.
Beautiful, yes?
Very nice.
Hungary.
That just happened.
And your mother?
He was fine, thank you.
He likes his room?
I want him to be the best.
I was there Thursday.
I'm sure
He has his own room.
He talks about you?
I understand.
He absorbed
by your visit.
That's right, mother.
I'm happy.
He deserves to be happy.
Convey my regards to him
and tell him that I think about it
when you see it.
Do you?
Of course, thank you.
It makes me happy.
Be careful, Claire.
Yes, thank you.
Grant him eternal rest,
Dear God,
and your light
the light forever.
I hope he rest in peace.
Amen.
May his soul
and that of all the missing
rest in the grace of God.
Peace of God
that passes all understanding,
Guard your heart and your mind
the love of God
and His Son, our Lord,
Jesus Christ.
May God Almighty bless you,
Father, Son and Holy Spirit.
He is in heaven.
Have faith in God.
Thank you very much, Father.
God bless you.
I buried my mother today.
A drink?
Okay.
You drink?
A Johnny Walker, sec.
Boy, two Johnny Walker.
Without ice.
Double contrast.
A double for women.
Other.
Another woman.
I've never seen here.
I have not been here.
What's your name?
Clear.
This is a beautiful name.
You're a beautiful woman.
I like you.
I want it with you.
Boy, the same thing.
It is for me.
You are attractive.
And if we go
in a more quiet?
Anyone?
You're really beautiful.
If we are going home?
Let's go.
You got something to drink?
Dress up and transmit.
- How?
- Go!
Gross! You understand?
Fuck you!
Bitch!
This is 2500.
And your mother?
He was good, thanks.
You go back to see it?
Yes, he asked me
thank you for the room.
Sorry.
Never mind, do not worry.
- An accident.
- This is my fault.
It was an accident, Claire.
What is it?
How?
You look nervous.
No, it was fine.
Show your hands.
I just had a little cold.
Ever shake my hand.
You're lying to me?
Why?
I work, there.
When you see your mother?
Last night.
He likes his room?
What did she say?
We were lucky
to have such generous friends.
Having their own room
it was good, the lack of
Privacy she weighed.
And he sends greetings.
I'm happy to help.
You look tired.
Try to relax.
I will try. Thank you.
Be careful, Claire.
Yes. I will rest tonight.
Thank you.
Leave a message after the beep.
Your take.
Claire?
Are you there?
Lost?
You from?
Leave me.
If not?
You feel alone?
- No
- I do.
I need company.
You do.
Very funny.
You're wrong.
Really? I do not think.
I do.
You have asked your opinion?
What name do not you?
- Never mind!
- I prefer it.
Prettier than you.
I do not care.
Really? You will leave
go first?
Mary?
Claire Dolan is thy cousin.
Already a century.
How are you?
My mother recently passed away.
He has a brain tumor.
I'm sorry.
How old is he?
58.
I am in Newark.
I think we can see.
Excuse me.
Do not leave...
You say?
I'm in Newark
and I saw you.
Come tomorrow.
I gave my address.
I have it, it is in the directory.
Two hours, that you okay?
Perfect.
How are you?
Good. "I have a 3 year old daughter
'M is not that bad.
This is incredible.
His name?
Siobhan.
I gotta go.
See you tomorrow without fail?
Without error.
Tomorrow, then.
... Who knows what could happen...
... She is beautiful...
... You know?
... Three hours in the morning...
... They had been drinking all night...
... He asked for it...
I like my natural color,
but I want to try the more clearly.
Too late to go back,
now.
You would be awesome.
If it is not fun you are,
We take your color.
Claire, the call for you.
Are you sorry?
Lucy?
You are responsible for
or waiting for someone?
I am alone.
Want to dance?
I love to dance.
- So?
- Sorry to be late.
What the head! Ms Raynor
awaits you. Do not repeat.
Did you set the
and treatment of Mrs. Raynor.
Immediately.
He is cute...
What's his name?
Sadie.
He was so small.
Michelle, we will.
You down?
I do not know what a.
It was not connected.
He returned, he said nothing.
He ate, he said nothing.
He sees information
he went to bed.
He said nothing.
And it does not get better.
I do not know...
Still far away from me.
Color "pearl"
I am okay?
Your opinion?
Pardon?
"Mother," I am good?
your mascara runs.
Pardon?
You feel good?
It does not go.
Are you sorry?
Cathy will solve your nails.
What do you do?
I drive a taxi.
Do you like it?
It works.
You work for a company?
No, the taxi was mine.
My beauty.
In the show South Park Street.
Do you like it?
I went.
I'm late.
I gave my phone number.
I have.
I noted
when you are asleep.
I often work
near Royalton.
You can find me there.
I'll call you.
Look at me.
Where your money?
On the coffee table.
I brought your clothes.
Please,
and put their makeup.
Please.
Put yourself in the light.
I'm really sorry
to your mother.
It was a good woman.
I will miss him.
You friend Roland?
- What is your name?
- Lucy.
He says Claire.
This is your real name?
From where in Ireland your home?
Dublin.
I went there last year.
The people are very friendly.
I do not know,
They invited me to eat at home.
They share a moment
short but intense
they live with me.
This is embarrassing
for me than for you.
Maybe I can help you.
How?
What
do you want?
You do not know, eh?
Why are you doing this?
To make you happy.
We do not know.
You do not really want.
Debt?
It was not.
I understand.
For the money, I do things
I hate it.
The tear-strip in.
I'm learning to promote,
to protect me.
The worst
I always wondered,
I'd put that
in this situation.
I do not know what is inside me
which led me to accept these things.
I think long
different, much worse.
I have anyone to
turn to find my bearings.
It took many years to tell me
I'm not a monster.
Many people do things
the tears,
they hate.
You understand?
Just try not to think about.
Zac are you?
My name is Lucy.
I am a friend of Cain.
He asked me to contact you,
I would love
caring for you.
Do you want me to come?
It's free.
Cain said
than you.
I really would love to meet you.
I want to please you.
I'm 27, I'm 1.72 m.
Brown eyes
and brown hair.
I think I'll humor you.
I'm happy
to change the color.
At 7:00?
At what time it was.
Lucy, Mark. It is 07:10.
Remember me. You got my number.
I want to see you.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere, I do not care.
Excuse me.
Maybe I got sick,
You work.
It was not. Do not worry.
You okay?
I just want to see you.
What is it?
I went to the last hotel
I was told that you go.
Where you live,
now?
Stop.
- Now.
- Where are you?
"I must go.
I call.
I can take you anywhere you want!
I'll call you.
How did you find me?
Can I come?
You live here
old?
You live here?
Claire is your name?
- And your name?
- Dolan.
- What do you do in Newark?
- How did you find it?
I followed the cab yesterday.
I see you left this morning,
I have followed
to Parke Hotel.
I waited a few hours,
I do not see you.
I'm tired of waiting.
I moved here a little earlier,
You do not have.
You're a pimp?
I owe someone money.
Okay?
You enjoy?
This can not be seen?
I have enjoyed.
Okay?
Okay.
I can not accept it,
I have to work.
You have received a check?
I told her Friday.
We will fix.
I'll call you.
We try to organize.
I gotta go.
Tell Angela
I see you tomorrow.
Lucy, Aaron.
I want to see you.
I'm in Cornwall
Room 227. See you soon.
I'm John Williams
a friend Jed.
He told me to contact you...
No
Not that.
That's it.
This is Claire.
I do not know whether in your home
in Newark.
Call me
when you receive this message.
I miss you.
Do not go.
I want to talk.
Talk about what?
I feel you're worried
I was not supposed to.
Is that all?
If there is something
You want me to say...
Like it?
If ever you disturb something,
You can talk to me.
I'm here for you.
Everything is good.
Okay, with your mother?
Is there anything else?
This is for you.
Do not tell your mother.
Buy it alone.
Thank you, Elton.
See you soon!
Sorry too late.
- And a job?
- It.
You're long gone?
One hour.
Just coffee, thanks.
You are beautiful.
I want you to take it.
It is committed to you for nothing.
I want to help pay
Your debt.
... Heather... velar
always ready to kiss
tell you that the pants down.
Even as he called
grandmother!
Everything you would expect:
She will suck, lick your ass.
You can fuck,
it was good.
It has been two days
we see thee not.
I'm sick. Influenza.
- There is an epidemic.
- You have a customer.
Over.
Seven hundred.
Thousands.
I "clean".
And if I really was not?
I took the risk.
Your take.
Thousands of dollars are not any.
I do not ejaculate in you
if you want.
I just want to feel.
You are very beautiful.
Sorry, I'm not interested.
So what?
I do not waste my time!
No problem.
Pardon?
I said "No problem".
Out, bitch!
And work?
That's okay.
And you?
I want a child.
Are you sure?
I understand.
Really?
It happens.
I want to feel you in me.
I love you.
I also love you.
Stop there.
This is $ 17.50.
You pay before you start!
I will pay you.
- Before Download!
- Fuck!
You think I'm not going to pay you?
Why? Would not be?
Open, I'll pay you!
Cutting machine!
Keys!
If you see me, you die.
Money!
All the money, or you die!
Fuck you get it?
I give everything.
Do not kill me!
Gun it.
Gun it!
Please...
Close your eyes!
I do not mind?
I have to call.
Do not worry.
I'm glad to see you.
You okay?
This is for Siobhan.
A place of paint.
I hope she likes.
I was told that it's like
a lot.
She will love. Thank you very much.
Where are you?
I returned to New York
Not yet.
Why?
Claire?
Not long.
- You okay?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
You are pregnant, right?
That's why you go?
You're going to keep it?
So, congratulations!
I'm happy for you.
Better
I will let you work.
I will miss you,
and Siobhan also.
He claims you.
Kiss her for me.
I'll come find you.
Every 8 or 15 days.
You will always be accepted.
If you need something,
call me. You hear?
Promised.
You look tired.
How long have you saved?
Two, three years maybe?
What you will do
when you are broken?
Brader your cat to $ 20 a shot?
You're not the novice.
You do not have to leave
You take
and attack you like that.
Use your head.
I have to go some day.
One thing I have to face.
What?
A value for the finish.
I should
2 days, not more.
He fell sick, I know.
I'll be there for you promise
doctor.
I'll call you.
I go back whenever I can.
Enter.
Peter?
I'm Eva.
Wait
old?
No, I've just arrived.
You drink something?
I will.
Where are you from?
Budapest.
You are here
since when?
9 weeks.
You have a beautiful face.
- What do you like best?
- How?
Total? Anything else?
I can do anything.
What is it?
- Kiss, you love it?
- You, I like you.
Would you like to kiss?
You like?
Whatever.
- But what?
- You suck.
Why?
I want you to suck.
You like it?
I waited.
I repeat, listen.
Even if he must,
it will never stop.
I know
since he was 12 years old.
I already knew
it sucks.
He was born to a prostitute, whore she will die.
I was offered a drink.
Two whiskey.
Difficult, but try to accept
I said.
Your life will be happier.
It is time for you to take control.
You're not children.
Four hundred, according to the agreement.
- A tape?
- A good idea.
Leave open.
- It is not too cold?
- No, it's nice.
I ask this.
You live in New York?
I was thinking about leaving.
Maybe Seattle.
You have money?
Ira.
Take, for babies.
You're going to keep it?
As results
can be complex
and make... doubt.
Uncertainty.
I'm sure.
I'm happy.
You give a very good mother.
Take the money.
Gift.
Accept it.
Thank you, but I do not want to...
It is very touching me.
I do not want.
I do not understand.
But if you do not want my help,
no problem.
Up to you.
I'm not talking in general
I feel...
But know that death
angry mom
and I share your pain.
If I can do anything
for you or your child,
I hope you will give me a sign.
Sure.
I hope.
Be careful, Claire.
Do not worry.
Do not stop!
We were flying
Chicago at 16:50...
Other Seattle to 17.05.
The next flight
leaves for Phoenix at 18:00.
One way ticket to Chicago.
Sure. Your name?
Claire Dolan.
You specify how?
In cash.
It makes you $ 472.
Hi, Lucy.
You work here?
I want to see you.
You're wrong.
I still know who I love.
Pardon?
Sorry. You look like
someone I know.
I said,
you're wrong.
My name is Claire Dolan.
I saw your ad.
The place is always free!
My name is Claire Dolan.
This is about jobs
Babysitting.
What time is it suitable?
I will try again later. Thank you.
You see her face...
How beautiful.
The beating heart.
Spine.
Leg... and penis.
These boys.
I can not believe it.
Elton?
Roland!
- What brought you to New York?
- We walk.
This is your wife?
Hello, Roland Cain.
Madeline Garrett.
You take
Your husband's name.
I also
I'm all for tradition.
Even if, sometimes,
cause problems.
True enough.
- How many months?
- September
Wonderful, congratulations.
I had my fourth
5 months ago.
That was a bad boy.
- Name?
- Jack.
Nice name.
This is my grandfather.
This was the first?
Who is better!
It changes lives.
This will make the other person.
We'll start with this one.
You'll see.
Men?
daughter of A.
Do not become angry.
I know.
I can?
Please.
Motherhood suits you.
You are beaming.
You know where?
It is well known in another life.
Time passes so quickly.
I gotta run.
Nice to meet you.
You're lucky, you have a beautiful woman.
You can show your daughter
one day my son!
A good idea.
Be careful.
Do not worry,
everything will be okay.