[MALE INTERVIEWER]
YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
I'M 63 YEARS OLD.
I'M LIKELY TO SKATE MY WAY
TO THE GRAVE,
BUT I HAVE THREE YOUNG CHILDREN
WHO ARE ALL ENGINEERS,
AND I WORRY ABOUT
THEIR ABILITY TO WORK
IN AMERICAN MANUFACTURING
DOWN THE ROAD...
[MACHINERY CHUGGING]
[MAN]
I THINK THAT THE WATER'S
GOING TO GET HOTTER AND HOTTER,
AND IF THERE IS NO EVENT
TO WAKE PEOPLE UP,
I THINK CHINA CAN JUST OWN
MORE AND MORE AND MORE
AND MORE OF OUR DEBT,
AND EVERYTHING'S FINE
UNTIL THAT MAGICAL MOMENT
WHEN IT'S NOT,
AND ALL THE SORRIES
IN THE WORLD
AREN'T GOING TO MAKE THAT
ANY DIFFERENT.
[MALE NARRATOR]
THE FILM YOU ARE ABOUT TO SEE
ADDRESSES ONE OF
THE MOST URGENT PROBLEMS
FACING AMERICA--
IT'S INCREASINGLY DESTRUCTIVE
TRADE RELATIONSHIP
WITH A RAPIDLY RISING CHINA.
AS YOU WATCH THIS FILM,
IT IS IMPORTANT TO ALWAYS
DISTINGUISH CLEARLY
BETWEEN THE GOOD AND
HARDWORKING PEOPLE OF CHINA
AND THEIR REPRESSIVE
COMMUNIST GOVERNMENT
NOW VICTIMIZING BOTH AMERICAN
AND CHINESE CITIZENS ALIKE.
I'M HERE TO BUY ME
A BIG-SCREEN TV,
MY FIRST BIG SCREEN, MAN,
40 INCH, FOR 265.
[INTERVIEWER]
WHERE'S THAT PRODUCT MADE?
PROBABLY IN CHINA.
CHINA.
THIS IS MADE IN CHINA.
[INTERVIEWER]
DO YOU KNOW HERE THAT BIKE
WAS MADE?
NO, BUT I KNOW IT'S HUFFY.
WHERE WERE THESE PRODUCTS MADE?
DO YOU KNOW?
PROBABLY FROM CHINA WHERE
EVERYTHING ELSE IS MADE.
OH, THIS [BLEEP]
IS MADE IN AMERICA.
[MAN]
WELL, AMERICAN IS BETTER.
SO IS THIS AMERICAN?
I'M NOT SURE IF IT IS AMERICAN,
BUT HOPEFULLY IT IS.
[MAN #2] YEAH,
I THINK I GOT A GREAT DEAL.
YOU CAN'T BEAT 300 BUCKS
FOR A 46-INCH TV.
TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DIDN'T EVEN COME HERE
EXACTLY FOR THIS,
BUT I SEEN IT AND COULDN'T
PASS UP THE DEAL, MAN.
FOR, YOU KNOW, $200, YOU CAN'T
REALLY, YOU KNOW, BEAT THAT,
SO THEY TOLD ME IT WAS 200,
AND NOW THAT'S IN MY--
IT'S IN MY CART NOW.
DID YOU SEE WHERE IT WAS MADE?
OH, YEAH,
IT WAS MADE IN CHINA.
HEY, I'M FINE WITH IT,
YOU KNOW.
IF THE AMERICAN PEOPLE CAN'T
PROVIDE ME WITH WHAT I NEED,
I GOTTA GET IT FROM CHINA.
HEY, IT IS WHAT IT IS,
YOU KNOW,
I'M JUST BEING TRUTHFUL.
DON'T HATE ME.
SO HOW DO YOU FEEL
WHEN AMERICANS BUY
CHINESE PRODUCTS?
I FEEL REALLY BAD BECAUSE
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS IS
IT'S NOT JUST AMERICA
IS BUYING UP CHINESE PRODUCTS.
IT'S THAT AMERICAN PEOPLE
ARE LOSING THEIR JOBS.
I WAS LAID OFF THREE TIMES
WITHIN SIX MONTHS
UNTIL I WAS PERMANENTLY
LAID OFF.
I GRADUATED
WITH MY BACHELOR'S IN 2004.
I'VE BEEN OUT TRYING
TO USE THAT OF COURSE
BECAUSE I SPENT
A LOT OF MONEY GOING TO SCHOOL,
AND I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO FIND ANYTHING.
CHINA, I THINK, IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR WIPING OUT A GOOD DEAL
OF THE MANUFACTURING
THAT WE HAVE, OR HAD,
IN NORTHEAST OHIO.
AND I THINK THAT IS CONTINUING
AS THEY CONTINUE TO MANIPULATE
THEIR CURRENCY,
AS THEY CONTINUE TO NOT HAVE
THE LEVEL OF WORKPLACE SAFETY
OR ENVIRONMENTAL
OR HEALTH STANDARDS
THAT WE HAVE HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
SO WE'VE SEEN OUR WHOLE
MANUFACTURING BASE
UPROOT AND REPLANT
IN A PLACE WHERE YOU CAN COMMIT
CRIMES AGAINST WORKERS
AND JUST GO OUT
TO DINNER THAT NIGHT.
SO WHEN A LARGE COMPANY
DECIDES TO MOVE ITS PRODUCTION
OFF SHORE
AND IT CLOSES A FACTORY
IN A CITY OR A
TOWN IN THE UNITED STATES,
THAT BASICALLY LEAVES--
IT'S LIKE A BLACK HOLE.
SUDDENLY THAT FACTORY
JUST DISAPPEARS,
AND EVERYTHING ELSE
GOES DOWN WITH IT.
JOBS DISAPPEAR,
AND THE WAY THE ECONOMY'S
GOING RIGHT NOW,
IT'S TOUGH TO FIND A JOB.
I JUST RECENTLY FINISHED
GRADUATE SCHOOL,
AND EVEN COMING OUT WITH THAT,
IT'S STILL HARD TO FIND ONE.
SOME OF THE WORKERS
AT COMPANIES,
LITERALLY THEIR LAST ACT
AT THE FACTORY
WAS TO UNBOLT THE MACHINE
AND LOAD IT UP
TO BE SHIPPED OFF TO CHINA.
I EVEN TALKED
TO A FELLA DOWN THERE.
THEY WANTED TO SEND HIM
OVER TO CHINA
TO TEACH THE PEOPLE
HOW TO RUN THE MACHINES THAT
THEY WERE SHIPPING OVER THERE.
HE WAS 63 YEARS OLD.
HE SAID, "I ONLY GOT
TWO MORE YEARS TO GO,
AND I CAN RETIRE,
SO I'M NOT GOING TO BOTHER
DOING IT."
HE SAID,
"BAD ENOUGH THEY TOOK MY JOB.
NOW THEY WANT ME TO SHOW THEM
HOW TO DO IT, TOO."
PEOPLE WHO WERE SUPPLYING
THAT PLANT WITH MATERIALS,
EQUIPMENT,
MAINTENANCE SERVICES,
EVEN THE ACCOUNTING FIRMS,
DESIGN FIRMS, R&D FIRMS,
AND THEN ALL THE OTHER SERVICES
AROUND IT, LIKE RESTAURANTS,
WHAT HAPPENS TO THEM?
THEY'RE DOOMED.
THEY GO DOWN WITH IT.
THEY CAN'T FOLLOW THAT COMPANY
OFFSHORE TO SHANGHAI.
IT'S DIFFICULT TO BE UNEMPLOYED
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A MORTGAGE
AND YOU HAVE YOUR REGULAR BILLS
YOU HAVE TO PAY.
YOU HAVE TO PAY FOR A CAR,
AND YOU HAVE TO PUT FOOD
ON THE TABLE,
AND WHEN YOU HAVE
JUST A SMALL AMOUNT OF MONEY
FROM THE STATE COMING IN,
SOMETIMES IT'S HARD TO MAKE IT.
I'M TRYING TO GET FOOD.
LIKE, THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
I MEAN, THIS IS NOT JUST
AN UNEMPLOYMENT LINE.
THIS IS FOR PEOPLE
WHO ARE HUNGRY,
AND I'M HUNGRY.
AND IT JUST REALLY IS UNFAIR
THAT BEING IN A COUNTRY
AS GREAT AS THE UNITED STATES
TO HAVE OUR PEOPLE STRUGGLING
THE WAY THEY ARE
TO NOT FIND WHAT IS JUST
COMMON-- YOU WORK.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
AND FOR THEM NOT TO FIND THAT
MONTH AFTER MONTH AND MONTH,
IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE SENSE
TO ME.
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S THE PRESIDENT.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S THE--
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW
WHO TO POINT THE BLAME TO.
IF WE TALK ABOUT WHO'S TO BLAME,
I THINK PARTIALLY
OUR OWN GOVERNMENT.
OUR GOVERNMENT
SHOULD BE DOING SOMETHING.
THEY COULD HAVE STEPPED IN,
I THINK, A LONG TIME AGO.
PLEASE HEAR US,
AND PLEASE UNDERSTAND
THAT COMPANIES
LIKE THIS ARE SPECIAL.
SMALL COMPANIES
ARE WHAT MAKES AMERICA,
AND UNLESS SOMEBODY
DOES SOMETHING
ABOUT UNRESTRICTED IMPORTING,
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE
THE REST OF US, TOO.
WE'VE NEVER HAD A REALLY BIG
AND HOSTILE COUNTRY
COME INTO OUR MARKETS.
MOST OF THE INTERNATIONAL
COMPETITION WE HAVE FACED,
FROM JAPAN, FROM GERMANY,
FROM THE REST OF EUROPE,
HAS COME WITHOUT A SENSE
THAT BEHIND IT WAS A GOVERNMENT
THAT HAS SOUGHT CONFRONTATIONS
WITH THE UNITED STATES
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
THE WTO-- IT'S NOT BASED HERE.
WHO IN THE UNITED STATES
IS ON THE WTO?
DOES ANYBODY KNOW?
IN 2001 CHINA JOINED THE WTO--
THE WORLD TRADE ORGANIZATION--
WITH THE STRONG SUPPORT
OF A DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENT
AND A REPUBLICAN-CONTROLLED
CONGRESS.
BEFORE THE INK WAS DRY
ON THIS FREE TRADE AGREEMENT,
CHINA BEGAN FLOODING
AMERICAN MARKETS
WITH ITS ILLEGALLY SUBSIDIZED
AND VERY DANGEROUS EXPORTS
WHILE THE BIG
MULTINATIONAL COMPANIES
THAT HAD LOBBIED
HEAVILY FOR THE AGREEMENT
RAPIDLY ACCELERATED
THE OFF SHORING
OF AMERICAN FACTORIES
AND AMERICAN JOBS TO CHINA.
TODAY, AS A RESULT OF THE
BIGGEST POLITICAL SHELL GAME
IN AMERICAN ECONOMIC HISTORY,
CHINA HAS STOLEN THOUSANDS
OF OUR FACTORIES
AND MILLIONS OF OUR JOBS,
MULTINATIONAL CORPORATION
PROFITS ARE SOARING,
AND WE NOW OWE
OVER $3 TRILLION
TO THE WORLD'S LARGEST
COMMUNIST NATION.
THIS WAS NOT HOW IT WAS
SUPPOSED TO TURN OUT--
[MAN]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES.
...WHEN WILLIAM
JEFFERSON CLINTON
WAS SELLING CHINA'S ENTRY
INTO THE WORLD TRADE
ORGANIZATION
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
IF YOU BELIEVE IN A FUTURE
OF GREATER OPENNESS AND FREEDOM
FOR THE PEOPLE OF CHINA,
YOU OUTTA BE
FOR THIS AGREEMENT.
IF YOU BELIEVE IN A FUTURE
OF GREATER PROSPERITY
FOR THE AMERICAN PEOPLE,
YOU CERTAINLY SHOULD BE
FOR THIS AGREEMENT.
IF YOU BELIEVE IN A FUTURE
OF PEACE AND SECURITY
FOR ASIA AND THE WORLD,
YOU SHOULD BE
FOR THIS AGREEMENT.
THIS IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
IT'S AN HISTORIC OPPORTUNITY
AND A PROFOUND AMERICAN
RESPONSIBILITY.
IN PUSHING FOR CHINA'S ENTRY
INTO THE WTO,
PRESIDENT CLINTON EMBRACED
A DOCTRINE DATING BACK
TO PRESIDENT RICHARD NIXON,
KNOWN IN WASHINGTON CIRCLES
AS THE "POLICY OF ENGAGEMENT."
[FILMSTRIP NARRATOR]
PEKING-- HISTORIC SITE
FOR AN UNPRECEDENTED MEETING
BETWEEN EAST AND WEST.
PRESIDENT AND MRS. NIXON
ARRIVE
AND PREMIER CHOU EN LAI
IS ON HAND
TO EXTEND AN OFFICIAL WELCOME
TO THE PRESIDENTIAL COUPLE.
IT'S MR. NIXON'S INITIAL MOVE
TOWARDS HIS SELF-PROCLAIMED
GOAL-- A GENERATION OF PEACE.
[NARRATOR]
HERE, PRESIDENT CLINTON
OFFERS HIS OWN VISION
OF THE GOAL OF ENGAGING CHINA.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT'S RIGHT
TO CRACK DOWN ON PEOPLE
FOR THEIR RELIGIOUS VIEWS
OR THEIR POLITICAL EXPRESSION
OR BECAUSE THEY WANT TO BE
IN AN ASSOCIATION
LIKE THE FALUN GONG.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S RIGHT,
BUT I DON'T BELIEVE
THAT WE WILL HAVE
MORE INFLUENCE ON CHINA
BY GIVING THEM
THE BACK OF OUR HAND.
IN MASTERFULLY ARGUING
FOR CHINA'S ENTRY INTO
THE WORLD TRADE ORGANIZATION,
PRESIDENT CLINTON
PROMISED THE BRIGHTEST
OF FUTURES
FOR BOTH AMERICAN WORKERS
AND AMERICAN MANUFACTURERS.
ECONOMICALLY, THIS AGREEMENT
IS THE EQUIVALENT
OF A ONE-WAY STREET.
IT REQUIRES CHINA
TO OPEN ITS MARKETS
WITH A FIFTH
OF THE WORLD'S POPULATION,
POTENTIALLY THE BIGGEST
MARKETS IN THE WORLD.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
CHINA WILL AGREE TO PLAY
BY THE SAME OPEN
TRADING RULES WE DO.
NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
OUR COMPANIES
WILL BE ABLE TO SELL AND
DISTRIBUTE PRODUCTS IN CHINA
MADE BY WORKERS
HERE IN AMERICA.
AND BY ECONOMICALLY
ENGAGING CHINA,
BOTH DEMOCRATS
AND REPUBLICANS ARGUED,
THIS WOULD ULTIMATELY
DEMOCRATIZE THE CHINESE DRAGON
AND FREE THE CHINESE PEOPLE.
WE HAVE WAGED
AN INTENSE BATTLE
IN SUPPORT
OF AN IMPORTANT PRINCIPLE,
AND THAT IS FREEDOM.
AND THE PEOPLE OF CHINA
AND THE CITIZENS
OF THE UNITED STATES
WILL BENEFIT ENORMOUSLY.
AFTER THE VICTORY VOTE,
THE REPUBLICAN HOUSE
MAJORITY LEADERS
WOULD CELEBRATE
THE BI-PARTISAN VICTORY
WITH THE CRACKING OPEN
OF A CEREMONIAL
FORTUNE COOKIE.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD
AT THESE THINGS.
WHOA.
[SPECTATORS LAUGHING]
IT'S GOT A LOTTERY NUMBER.
NO.
IT SAYS NEW AMERICAN PROVERB--
NEW PROSPERITY AWAITS YOU
BECAUSE NORMAL TRADE RELATIONS.
YEA.
IT'S A CONFRONTATION
OF WORLD VIEWS
THAT WE WILL WIN,
AND I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO THE FUTURE.
SO JUST WHAT HAS AMERICA'S
FUTURE LOOKED LIKE
SINCE CHINA JOINED THE WORLD
TRADE ORGANIZATION IN 2001?
WE ARE IN A TRADE WAR
AND STEALING, LYING,
AND CHEATING
ON THE PART OF THE CHINESE
IS ALL PART OF IT.
FREE TRADE'S GREAT STUFF
IF YOU CAN GET IT,
BUT WHAT WE HAVE WITH CHINA
IS NOT FREE TRADE.
FOR CHINA TO SELL SOMETHING
AT 1/10th THE PRICE
OF WHAT IT WOULD COST
IN THE UNITED STATES TO PRODUCE,
THEY ARE CHEATING MONUMENTALLY,
IN A MAJOR,
MASSIVE SORT OF WAY.
ON EVERYTHING.
WHEN CHINA JOINED THE WORLD
TRADE ORGANIZATION IN 2001,
IT PROMISED TO STOP CHEATING
AND PLAY BY FAIR TRADE RULES.
THAT MEANT ABANDONING UNFAIR
TRADE PRACTICES
LIKE CURRENCY MANIPULATION,
ILLEGAL EXPORT SUBSIDIES...
AND ABUSING ITS WORKERS.
INSTEAD,
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
HAS USED THESE WEAPONS
OF JOB DESTRUCTION
TO LAUNCH A SUSTAINED
AND DEVASTATING ATTACK
ON AMERICA'S FACTORIES
AND JOBS
WHILE FLOODING OUR MARKETS
WITH DANGEROUS PRODUCTS.
THERE'S NO QUESTION
THAT A LARGE PART OF CHINA'S
COMPETITIVE ADVANTAGE
HAS COME FROM
ENVIRONMENTAL NEGLECT.
BUT THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT'S
WILLINGNESS TO USE POLLUTION
AS A COMPETITIVE EDGE
HAS COME AT A VERY HEAVY PRICE.
[MAN]
CHINA HAS THE MOST DEGRADED
ENVIRONMENT IN THE WORLD.
SIXTEEN OF THE WORLD'S
20 DIRTIEST CITIES
ARE LOCATED
IN THE PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC.
LESS THAN ONE PERCENT
OF THEIR URBAN AIR
MEETS THE AIR QUALITY STANDARDS
SET BY THE EUROPEAN UNION.
IT'S DIFFICULT TO THINK
ABOUT WHAT IS HAPPENING,
PARTICULARLY TO THE LUNGS
OF CHILDREN BREATHING AIR
LIKE THAT.
[McCORMACK]
IN ONE FELL SWOOP,
YOU CAN MOVE YOUR PRODUCTION
TO CHINA
AND NOT HAVE TO DEAL
WITH A HUNDRED YEARS
OF REGULATIONS
THAT WE'VE PUT INTO PLACE TO
PROTECT OUR WORKERS,
TO PROTECT OUR SOCIETY,
JUST BY MOVING
YOUR PRODUCTION TO CHINA
BECAUSE THEY DON'T HAVE ANY.
THEY HAVE WHAT WE HAD
PROBABLY IN 1910.
THE MOST TRAGIC STORY
IS THE "CANCER VILLAGES"
BECAUSE OF TOXIC METALS
IN THE SOIL,
BECAUSE OF THE POLLUTION,
BECAUSE MANUFACTURERS
HAVE NOT BEEN FORCED
TO CLEAN UP THEIR PLANTS,
AND SO ESSENTIALLY WHAT WE HAVE
IS THE WORLD'S
MOST DEGRADED ENVIRONMENT.
WHETHER YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
HEAVY METALS POLLUTION,
AIR POLLUTION,
WATER POLLUTION,
CHINA'S GOT IT ALL.
AND PARTICULARLY
FOR HEAVY INDUSTRIES
LIKE CHEMICALS OR STEEL,
THE ABILITY TO WANTONLY
POLLUTE IN CHINA
ADDS UP TO
A HUGE COST ADVANTAGE
IN THE GLOBAL MARKETPLACE.
[MAN] IF A COMPANY
LIKE BAO STEEL IN CHINA
IS ALLOWED TO DUMP POLLUTION
INTO THE YANGTZE RIVER
WHEN, SAY,
A UNITED STATES STEEL COMPANY
IS NOT ALLOWED TO DO THE SAME
IN THE OHIO RIVER,
THAT'S GOING TO BE A SOURCE
OF COMPETITIVE ADVANTAGE
FOR THE CHINESE
BECAUSE POLLUTION CONTROL
COSTS MONEY.
IT PROVIDES THEM
AN ECONOMIC ADVANTAGE
IN ENVIRONMENTAL COSTS OF
APPROXIMATELY $40 A STEEL TON,
OR REPRESENTS ABOUT
5% OF THE COST OF PRODUCING
THAT STEEL.
[INTERVIEWER]
IS A 5% COST ADVANTAGE
SIGNIFICANT?
IN THE STEEL INDUSTRY
A 5% COST ADVANTAGE IS GREATER
THAN OUR PROFITABILITY.
AND HERE'S THE ULTIMATE IRONY--
THE MORE WE ALLOW
OUR AMERICAN MULTINATIONALS
TO OFFSHORE PRODUCTION
TO CHINA,
THE MORE TOTAL
GLOBAL POLLUTION WE CREATE
AND A GOOD BIT OF THAT
COMES RIGHT BACK TO AMERICA
BY WAY OF THE JET STREAM.
CARBON EMISSIONS IN CHINA
PER THOUSAND DOLLARS OF GNP
ARE SEVEN TIMES WHAT THEY ARE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
THAT LEADS TO CARBON EMISSIONS
AND PARTICULATE MATTER
FALLING ALL ALONG THE COAST
OF THE UNITED STATES.
25% OF THE PARTICULATE EMISSIONS
FALLING IN CALIFORNIA
ARE FROM ASIA IN GENERAL
AND CHINA IN PARTICULAR.
[WOMAN]
THEY'RE GOOD AND BAD REASONS
WHY GOODS ARE CHEAP
IN THE INTERNATIONAL ECONOMY.
THE GOOD REASON IS THAT
SOMEBODY IS A GOOD PRODUCER,
THAT THEY'RE QUICK,
THAT THEY GET THE PRODUCT
TO MARKET,
THEY HAVE GOOD TECHNOLOGY,
THAT THEIR WORKERS ARE
EFFICIENT AND WELL-TRAINED.
THE BAD REASON IS THAT
THE WORKERS ARE TREATED
LIKE DIRT.
WHEN THE WORKERS IN CHINA
ARE BEING ABUSED,
THEN WORKERS IN AMERICA
HAVE A TOUGHER TIME COMPETING
AGAINST THEM.
[McCORMACK]
AS AN EMPLOYER IN CHINA,
DO YOU HAVE ANY REGULATIONS YOU
HAVE TO DEAL WITH,
LIKE OSHA, LABOR REGULATIONS?
DO YOU HAVE TO PAY EVEN SOCIAL
SECURITY OR MEDICARE?
DO YOU HAVE TO PROTECT
YOUR WORKERS IN DIFFICULT
OR UNSAFE CONDITIONS?
NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YOU GO TO PRISON IF YOU TRY
TO FORM A LABOR UNION.
FREEDOM OF ASSOCIATION,
THE RIGHT TO ORGANIZE
AND BARGAIN COLLECTIVELY,
ARE COMPLETELY ABSENT
IN CHINA TODAY.
THERE'S NO EQUIVALENT TO OSHA,
OCCUPATIONAL SAFETY
REGULATIONS--
AND THEY LOSE ABOUT 130,000
MEN AND WOMEN TO--
AND THAT'S THE ONES
THEY REPORT ON--
TO ACCIDENTS PER YEAR
THAT MANY OF WHICH
COULD BE PREVENTED
WITH GOOD PROTECTION.
THEY DON'T COMPLY WITH
THEIR OWN CHILD LABOR LAWS,
PRISON LABOR LAWS,
HEALTH AND SAFETY LAWS,
MINIMUM WAGE LAWS.
WELL, THERE'S A DR. LEE,
WHO LIVES IN NEW JERSEY,
WHO WAS ACTUALLY
AN AMERICAN CITIZEN,
AND HE WAS IN CHINA,
AND HE WAS ARRESTED
AND KEPT IN ONE OF THEIR WORK
CAMPS FOR THREE YEARS.
WHEN HE WAS FINALLY RELEASED,
THANKS TO PRESSURE
FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE,
HE CAME BACK TO NEW JERSEY,
AND HE WAS IN A STORE,
AND HE SAW THESE BIG SLIPPERS
THAT HE'D MADE
IN THE WORK CAMP.
HOW CAN WAL-MART,
OR ANYONE ELSE
IN THE UNITED STATES,
ALLOW PRODUCTION FACILITIES
IN CHINA
TO SELL GARMENTS, CHOPSTICKS,
CHRISTMAS DECORATIONS
THAT ARE MADE
IN FORCED LABOR CAMPS?
[WU] YOU CAN GO TO CHINA,
GO TO EVERY PRISON CAMP.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT
ARE THE PRISONERS DOING.
EVERYBODY VERY BUSY.
IT'S NOT ALL ABOUT CHINA
CURRENCY MANIPULATION,
BUT A LOT OF IT IS.
CHINA MANIPULATES ITS CURRENCY
BY ILLEGALLY PEGGING
THE VALUE OF THE CHINESE YUAN
TO THAT OF THE U.S. DOLLAR
AT A RATE FAR BELOW
MARKET VALUE.
MOST ECONOMISTS WOULD SAY
THAT CHINA GETS ANYWHERE
FROM A 25 TO 40 CENT ADVANTAGE
FOR EVERY DOLLAR.
SO IT'S LIKE HAVING
A TARIFF ON GOODS COMING
FROM THE UNITED STATES
OF 40 OR 50%
BY THE AMOUNT THAT THEY'RE
UNDERPRICING THEIR CURRENCY.
IT ALSO GIVES THEIR EXPORTS
TO THE UNITED STATES
A SUBSIDY OF 40 OR 50%
TO CAPTURE OUR MARKET
AND KNOCK OUT
DOMESTIC INDUSTRIES
THAT MIGHT BE COMPETING
WITH THEM.
SIMPLY, AN UNDERVALUED CURRENCY
MAKES CHINESE COFFEEMAKERS
$10 A PIECE
INSTEAD OF 15 OR 20.
AND IT MAKES AMERICAN CARS
IN CHINA $30,000 INSTEAD OF 25.
IN OTHER WORDS,
CHINA'S MANIPULATED CURRENCY
ACTS AS A HUGE SUBSIDY
TO CHINESE EXPORTS TO AMERICA
AND AN EQUALLY
BIG TARIFF BARRIER
BLOCKING AMERICAN EXPORTS
TO CHINA.
THE RESULT--
MORE JOBS IN CHINA,
FEWER JOBS IN AMERICA,
AND A HUGE AND CHRONIC
AMERICAN TRADE DEFICIT
WITH CHINA.
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
DOES NOT DENY THIS.
CHINESE OFFICIALS THEMSELVES
SAY THAT THEY FIX THE VALUE
OF THEIR CURRENCIES
TO HELP CHINESE WORKERS.
WHEN PREMIER WEN JIABAO WAS IN
THIS COUNTRY RECENTLY,
HE SAID, "IF WE ALLOW
THE CURRENCY TO FLOAT,
CHINESE COMPANIES
ARE GONNA GO BANKRUPT."
OKAY, BUT WHAT ABOUT
AMERICAN WORKERS?
[REP. RYAN]
THEY'RE CHEATING
ON THE INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
BY JUST FLAT OUT PIRATING
STUFF FROM THE UNITED STATES.
YOU DON'T WANT CHINA TO GET
THEIR HANDS ON YOUR LATEST PIECE
OF TECHNOLOGY, WHATEVER,
BECAUSE THEY WILL COPY IT,
AND THEY WILL TURN AROUND
AND PRODUCE IT.
MOST FAMOUSLY,
COPYRIGHT PIRATES IN CHINA
ARE STAMPING OUT DISNEY DVDS.
THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY KNOWS OF.
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT
IS THE THEFT OF THE BLUEPRINTS,
FOR EXAMPLE,
FOR HIGH TECHNOLOGIES.
I MEAN, I HEAR ALL THE TIME
ABOUT AMERICAN COMPANIES
WHO FIND THEMSELVES COMPETING
IN THE MARKETPLACE
WITH A CHINESE PRODUCT,
AND THEY TAKE IT APART,
AND THEY FIND THEMSELVES
LOOKING IN THE MIRROR
BECAUSE THE CHINESE
HAVE JUST STOLEN THE PLANS
OF THEIR OWN PRODUCT.
AND ONE OF AMERICA'S
HIGHEST TECH COMPANIES
HAS CERTAINLY EXPERIENCED
THIS KIND OF PIRACY FIRSTHAND
AND A SCHOOL OF VERY HARD
KNOCKS AT THE HANDS
OF THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT.
[CHANG] GOOGLE CAME
INTO THE CHINESE MARKET
AND OF COURSE, IT ENDED UP
WITH A DOMINANT MARKET SHARE.
BUT BEIJING WANTED BAIDU,
A LOCAL COMPANY,
TO BE ABLE TO OUTPACE GOOGLE.
WHAT BEIJING DID
WAS IT HACKED GOOGLE'S NETWORK,
IT STOLE ITS SOURCE CODE,
AND NOW BAIDU HAS MORE THAN 75%
OF THE CHINA SEARCH MARKET.
THIS SHOWS THAT BASICALLY
BEIJING WANTS THE LOCAL
COMPANIES
TO BE THE NATIONAL CHAMPIONS.
BUT SOMETIMES CHINESE PIRATES
AREN'T CONTENT JUST TO STEAL
THE INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
OF AN AMERICAN CORPORATION.
SOMETIMES THEY JUST TAKE
THE WHOLE COMPANY.
SO FELLOWES IS A COMPANY
THAT MAKES SHREDDERS--
PAPER SHREDDERS--
AND THEY MOVED--
LIKE EVERYBODY--
THEY MOVED THEIR PRODUCTION
TO CHINA.
THEY HIRED A COMPANY TO RUN
THEIR PRODUCTION FOR THEM,
AND SUDDENLY, ONE DAY,
THEIR EMPLOYEES WERE LOCKED OUT
OF THEIR OWN PLANT.
SO FELLOWES WENT FROM HAVING
A LARGE PRODUCTION BASE
IN CHINA ONE DAY
TO THE NEXT DAY, THEIR PARTNER
SUDDENLY SHUT THEM OFF,
SHUT THEM DOWN.
THE MORAL
OF THE FELLOWES STORY IS,
YOU BETTER BE VERY CAREFUL
WHEN YOU MOVE YOUR PRODUCTION
TO A COMMUNIST COUNTRY.
IT MAKES NO SENSE THAT CHINA,
WHO PRODUCES 45%
OF THE STEEL IN THE WORLD,
HAS HIGH MANUFACTURING COSTS
YET SELLS STEEL
AT THE LOWEST COST IN THE WORLD
AND IS GROWING
AT A RATE OF 7 OR 8%.
THIS GROWTH
FROM A HUNDRED MILLION TONS
TO 700 MILLION TONS,
GROWING BY 50 MILLION TONS
PER YEAR,
IS ALL DUE TO STATE SUBSIDIES.
THE PROBLEM
IS THAT AMERICAN COMPANIES
CANNOT COMPETE
BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT COMPETING
WITH CHINESE COMPANIES.
THEY ARE COMPETING
WITH THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT.
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
IT MOST CERTAINLY WILL RESULT
IN MORE UNEMPLOYMENT
IN THE U.S.
AND TO THE ADVANTAGE OF CHINA.
WE'RE CHUMPS.
SO JUST HOW BIG OF A CHUMP
HAS AMERICA BEEN
FOR SUPPORTING CHINA'S ENTRY
INTO THE WORLD TRADE
ORGANIZATION IN 2001?
IT'S LIKE WE'RE IN THE
SUPER BOWL OF GLOBALIZATION,
AND IN FACT
WE'RE BEING TAKEN APART.
AND IN THIS SUPER BOWL
OF GLOBALIZATION,
WHEN YOU TALLY UP THE SCORE
ON HUMAN RIGHTS ABUSES
AND CONSIDER
THE PLIGHT OF TIBET,
THE TORTURE OF THE FALUN GONG,
AND THE CRUSHING OF RELIGION
AND DEMOCRACY,
THIS MUCH IS CLEAR.
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
IS THE WORLD'S WORST HUMAN
RIGHTS ABUSER
ON THE PLANET TODAY.
AND WHEN YOU TALLY UP THE SCORE
ON CHINA'S RAPID MILITARY
BUILDUP,
THIS, TOO, IS CLEAR...
[CHANG]
CHINA IS THE ONLY MAJOR NATION
IN THE WORLD
THAT IS PREPARING
TO KILL AMERICANS.
AND OF COURSE,
WHEN YOU COUNT THE JOBS LOST
AND FACTORIES GONE
AND MILLIONS OF AMERICANS
OUT OF WORK--
AMERICAN MANUFACTURING
HAS BEEN IN AN ABSOLUTE CRISIS
OVER THE LAST DECADE.
51/2 MILLION
MANUFACTURING JOBS GONE.
57,000 MANUFACTURING FACILITIES
CLOSED IN THIS NATION.
SO YOU'RE IN A MASSIVE
JOBLESS RECOVERY.
YOU'VE GOT 28 MILLION
WOMEN AND MEN
WHO ARE IN VARIOUS STAGES
OF UNEMPLOYMENT,
TWICE THE OFFICIAL NUMBER.
WHEN YOU TALLY UP
ALL THESE SCORES,
IT'S CRYSTAL CLEAR
THAT CHINA'S ENTRY
INTO THE WORLD TRADE
ORGANIZATION
HAS BEEN BOTH A LOSING,
AND A VERY DANGEROUS,
PROPOSITION--
EVEN AS AMERICA HAS ALL
BUT COMPLETELY SURRENDERED
ITS MANUFACTURING BASE
TO CHINA.
WE DON'T MAKE A SINGLE CELL
PHONE IN THE UNITED STATES,
NOT ONE IS MADE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
[MAN]
THERE IS NOT A SINGLE MODERN
FLAT PANEL DISPLAY FACTORY
IN THE UNITED STATES.
DOES THAT MATTER?
ARE FLAT PANEL DISPLAYS
IMPORTANT FOR MILITARY
APPLICATIONS?
I THINK SO.
THEY'RE WIDELY USED.
EVERY AIRPLANE,
EVERY HELICOPTER HAS THEM.
THE UNITED STATES RIGHT NOW
IS UNABLE TO PUT A SINGLE
MILITARY AIRCRAFT INTO THE SKY
WITHOUT USING COMPONENTS
BUILT BY POTENTIAL ADVERSARIES.
WE PRODUCE ABOUT $3 BILLION
WORTH OF PRINTED CIRCUIT BOARDS
IN THE UNITED STATES.
CHINA PRODUCES
ALMOST $20 BILLION.
MACHINE TOOLS,
WE PRODUCE $2.7 BILLION.
CHINA'S CONSUMPTION
WAS 10 TIMES THAT AMOUNT.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A MACHINE TOOL INDUSTRY,
DO YOU HAVE AN INDUSTRY?
IT'S, YOU KNOW, A BASIC
COMPONENT OF AN INDUSTRIAL
ECONOMY.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THOSE
GREEN INDUSTRIES
THAT SOME OF OUR POLITICIANS
SAY WILL CREATE
THE JOBS OF THE FUTURE?
[PRESIDENT BARACK OBAMA]
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
WHY WE'RE ACCELERATING
THE TRANSITION
TO A CLEAN ENERGY ECONOMY
AND DOUBLING OUR USE OF
RENEWABLE ENERGY SOURCES
LIKE WIND AND SOLAR POWER,
STEPS THAT HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO CREATE WHOLE NEW INDUSTRIES
AND HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS
OF NEW JOBS IN AMERICA.
BUT HERE'S THE GRIM REALITY.
WE PRODUCE 4% OF THE WORLD'S
GLOBAL OUTPUT OF SOLAR.
ONE OF THE THINGS HAPPENING
IN THE MARKET RIGHT NOW
IS IT'S BEING SWAMPED
BY LOW-COST MULTI-CRYSTALLINE
AND POLYCRYSTALLINE SILICONE
SOLAR CELLS FROM CHINA.
WE DON'T MAKE COMPUTERS.
WE DON'T MAKE PRINTERS.
WE IMPORT 99% OF OUR SHOES.
MASS-PRODUCED
CONSUMER PRODUCTS--
WE BASICALLY
DON'T MAKE THEM ANYMORE.
BUT IT'S NOT JUST MASS-PRODUCED
CONSUMER GOODS
WE ARE LOSING TO CHINA.
SOME OF OUR VERY BEST PAYING
MANUFACTURING JOBS
ARE ALSO NOW QUITE LITERALLY
BEING SHANGHAIED.
[MAN]
BOEING, AT ITS PEAK IN
THE SEATTLE-EVERETT AREA,
HAD ABOUT 50,000 EMPLOYEES.
THAT WAS NO MORE THAN
FIVE YEARS AGO.
20,000 OF THOSE JOBS
HAVE NOW MOVED TO CHINA
IN JUST THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
[McCORMACK]
APPLE EMPLOYS 26,000 PEOPLE
IN ITS DESIGN
OF MAKING NEW PRODUCTS.
IT EMPLOYS, THROUGH FOXCONN,
700,000 MANUFACTURING WORKERS
IN CHINA.
THEY'RE AN AMERICAN COMPANY.
THEY'RE HEADQUARTERED HERE.
ALL THEIR JOBS
ARE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
AMERICANS NEED THOSE JOBS,
BUT THEY ALL EXIST IN CHINA.
EVERY ONE OF THOSE
MANUFACTURING JOBS
EXISTS IN CHINA.
THESE ARE JOBS THAT COULD VERY
EASILY BE IN SILICON VALLEY,
IN OREGON, NORTHERN CALIFORNIA,
IN GENERAL ALONG THE COAST
FOR WHICH THERE ARE
WELL-TRAINED AND VERY
INTERESTED WOMEN AND MEN
WHO WOULD TAKE THEM
IN A HEARTBEAT.
AND EVEN WHITE-COLLAR WORKERS
ARE NOW IN CHINA'S CROSS-HAIRS.
[MAN]
THE WHITE COLLAR WORKER
UNDERSTANDS
THAT CHINA IS NOW MOVING UP
IN THE FEEDING FRENZY TO,
FOR EXAMPLE, SOFTWARE
AND OTHER KINDS OF PRODUCTION.
THEY'RE MOVING AWAY
FROM JUST PROCESS TECHNOLOGY
UP TO MORE REALLY
INTELLECTUAL TECHNOLOGY.
NOW, IT'S NOT A VERY BIG PART
OF THEIR ECONOMY,
BUT YOU CAN LOOK
IN THE UNITED STATES.
IT'S HAVING
A DEVASTATING EFFECT.
IF THE JOBS FOR PRODUCTION
MOVE TO CHINA,
THE SUPPORT JOBS
FOR WHITE COLLAR,
TO A BIG DEGREE,
WILL MOVE TO CHINA.
MEANWHILE, OUR RAPIDLY
ACCUMULATING CHINESE DEBT
HAS BECOME A NATIONAL JOKE,
LITERALLY.
...AND TO ALLOW THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT TO DEFAULT.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
I'D SAY CHINA IS MAD
AT PRESIDENT OBAMA
FOR MEETING
WITH THE DALAI LAMA.
I MEAN, COME ON.
OBAMA DOESN'T
OWE THEM ANYTHING.
EXCEPT LIKE $14 TRILLION.
AND THAT DEBT REPRESENTS
A VERY REAL CLAIM
ON AMERICAN ASSETS.
...AND THEN CHINA WOULD BACK
A TOW TRUCK UP TO KANSAS
AND DRAG IT OFF
TO GUANGDONG PROVINCE.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
I FIND IT IRONIC
THAT THE CORNER OF CAPITALISM,
THE J.P. MORGAN BUILDING
DOWN ON WALL STREET,
IS NOW OWNED
BY A CHINESE COMPANY.
AS FOR THAT HOPE
THAT ECONOMIC ENGAGEMENT
WOULD LEAD TO A MORE FREE
AND DEMOCRATIC CHINA,
GEORGE BUSH, SENIOR.
REMEMBER HIM.
HE WAS THE AMBASSADOR
TO CHINA WAY BACK WHEN.
AND SO HE LIKED CHINA.
HE LIKED THOSE GUYS OVER THERE.
THINGS ARE GOOD IN CHINA.
ECONOMIC GROWTH IN CHINA
HAS NOT LED TO ITS
BECOMING MORE DEMOCRATIC.
IT HAS LED TO
A MORE SOPHISTICATED,
BETTER-FINANCED FORM
OF AUTHORITARIANISM.
AND IRONICALLY ONE OF THOSE
MEASURES OF REPRESSION
HAS BEEN THE INTERNET ITSELF,
WHICH WAS SUPPOSED
TO SET CHINA FREE.
[McCORMACK]
CHINA IS LESS FREE TODAY
THAN IT WAS WHEN THEY
ENTERED THE WTO.
CHINA HAS 50,000 INTERNET POLICE
WHO ARE TRACKING EVERY DAY
THEIR CAPABILITIES,
WHO'S SAYING WHAT,
TO BE ABLE TO TRY AND KEEP
THINGS LIKE TIANANMEN SQUARE,
DEMOCRACY, FREEDOM,
AND THOSE TERMS
OFF THE INTERNET.
AND THESE CYBER COPS
HAVE HAD PLENTY OF HELP
FROM AMERICAN COMPANIES
IN BUILDING
THE GREAT FIREWALL OF CHINA.
[REP SMITH]
GOOGLE, YAHOO, CISCO,
AND THE CAPABILITY
THEY HAVE SOLD TO CHINA,
ESPECIALLY
FOR ITS SECRET POLICE,
HAS ENABLED THEM TO SEARCH,
APPREHEND, DISCOVER
THE WHEREABOUTS,
GET CACHES OF NAMES,
PARTICULARLY ONLINE
WHERE IF YOU SEND YOUR EMAILS
TO OTHER PEOPLE,
THEIR IP ADDRESSES QUICKLY
YIELD TO WHAT THEIR
PHYSICAL ADDRESSES ARE,
AND THEY'RE THEN
APPREHENDED AND ARRESTED.
PERHAPS THE MOST SHAMEFUL
ANSWER TO THAT QUESTION
MAY BE FOUND IN YAHOO'S ROLE
IN THE JAILING OF A CHINESE
CITIZEN NAMED SHI TAO.
HERE'S A GUY, A JOURNALIST,
WHO SENT INFORMATION TO AN NGO
ABOUT WHAT THEY
COULDN'T SAY OR DO
AS THE TIANANMEN SQUARE
REMEMBRANCE DAY WAS COMING UP
OR DAYS AND HE SENT IT
TO A NEW YORK NGO.
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT KNOCKED
ON THE DOOR OF THE YAHOO PEOPLE,
ASKED FOR THE INFORMATION,
THEY JUST COUGHED IT RIGHT UP,
AND SHI TAO GOT TEN YEARS
FOR THAT.
AS FOR THOSE FALUN GONG
PRACTITIONERS
AND OTHER DISSIDENTS SINGLED
OUT BY PRESIDENT CLINTON...
I HAD A HEARING
ON THE FALUN GONG,
AND HOW THEY'RE THROWING
THESE PEOPLE IN JAIL
BY THE THOUSANDS,
AND THEY'RE HARVESTING ORGANS.
THE WAY IT WORKS IS THAT IF
SOMEBODY GOES-- WANTS A LIVER,
SAY,
THEY FLY TO SHANGHAI,
AND THEY PROBABLY GO CHECK
INTO THE NUMBER ONE PEOPLE'S
HOSPITAL IN SHANGHAI.
A MILITARY SURGEON,
PROBABLY IN UNIFORM,
ONE I'M THINKING OF,
COMES UP AND DOES
THE [UNINTELLIGIBLE] TESTS
AND THE BLOOD TEST AND SO ON.
THEN HE-- HE OR SHE--
LOOKS ON THE COMPUTER LIST
AND SAYS,
"OH, THERE'S A MATCH OUT
IN WORK CAMP 400."
THE POOR VICTIM,
WHO MATCHES
WHAT YOUR ORGANS NEED,
IS DRAGGED
INTO A SORT OF HOSPITAL,
GIVEN A LIGHT ANESTHETIC
IN MOST CASES,
AND NEVER WAKES UP
BECAUSE THEY TAKE
NOT JUST ONE KIDNEY.
THEY TAKE BOTH KIDNEYS,
THE LIVER, HEART, EVERYTHING,
AND THEIR BODY IS THEN BURNED,
AND THE PEOPLE'S
LIBERATION ARMY
FLIES THE ORGAN TO SHANGHAI
FROM WHEREVER
THE CAMP HAPPENS TO BE,
AND YOU'RE TOLD
YOU'RE GETTING THE ORGAN
FROM A CONVICTED
MURDERER OR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, THIS IS
A GROTESQUE TALE
OF THE WORST KIND
OF OPPRESSION AND GHOULISHNESS
ON THE PART OF RULERS
OF A COUNTRY.
AND HERE IS WHAT
TOO MANY AMERICAN POLITICIANS
SEEM TO HAVE SUCH
A HARD TIME UNDERSTANDING.
WEI JINGSHENG TOLD ME,
IN BEIJING RIGHT BEFORE
HE GOT RE-ARRESTED,
"YOU AMERICANS
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
"WHEN YOU CODDLE DICTATORSHIP,
"WHEN YOU KOWTOW
AND YOU CARRY THE DICTATORSHIP
AROUND ON A PILLOW,
"THEY BEAT US MORE
IN THE LAOGAI.
"WHEN YOU'RE TOUGH,
PREDICTABLE,
TRANSPARENT ON HUMAN RIGHTS,
THEY BEAT US LESS."
BUT AT LEAST ENGAGING
CHINA ECONOMICALLY
HAS MADE THE RULING COMMUNIST
PARTY MORE PEACEFUL, RIGHT?
CHINA'S MILITARY POWER
IS STRENGTHENING
VERY, VERY RAPIDLY.
THEY ARE BUILDING UP THEIR
MILITARY CAPABILITIES
IN HARD WEAPONS
AS WELL AS IN CYBER SECURITY.
CHINA HAS A POPULATION
WHICH IS ABOUT FIVE TIMES
THE SIZE OF THE UNITED STATES,
AND THAT MEANS THAT
IF THEY HAVE A COMPARABLE
LEVEL OF DEVELOPMENT,
THEY PROBABLY WILL END UP
WITH A MILITARY
FIVE TIMES LARGER.
AND I DON'T CARE WHAT KIND
OF TECHNOLOGICAL EDGE WE HAVE.
IT WOULD BE
VERY DIFFICULT TO PREVAIL
OVER AN ADVERSARY
THAT IS FIVE TIMES LARGER.
[REP. ROHRABACHER]
WHAT CHINA IS BUILDING
IS JUST NOT A MASSIVE FLEET
OR A MASSIVE GROUND ARMY,
BUT IT'S DEVELOPING A MODERN,
WELL-EQUIPPED,
TECHNOLOGICALLY
CAPABLE MILITARY.
AND IN SOME CASES,
IT NEED NOT BE CHINA
PULLING THE TRIGGER...
[MAN SPEAKING FARSI]
...MAHMOUD AHMADINEJAD!
...OR LAUNCHING THE MISSILES,
AS THE CASE MAY BE.
[RICHARD FISHER]
WE ARE ON THE ONSET
OF AN AGE OF NUCLEAR TERRORISM.
WE SEE PAKISTAN CRUMBLING
WHILE IT BUILDS MORE AND MORE
NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
WHY DOES PAKISTAN
HAVE NUCLEAR WEAPONS?
WHY DOES IT HAVE THE MISSILES
TO DELIVER THEM?
BECAUSE OF CHINA.
WE'VE BEEN IN A NEAR
30-YEAR DIALOGUE
WITH THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
TRYING TO ARREST THIS BEHAVIOR
THAT IS SUPPORTING NOT
ONLY PAKISTAN'S,
BUT NORTH KOREA'S AND IRAN'S
FUTURE NUCLEAR CAPABILITIES.
CHINA REFUSES
TO LISTEN AND RESPOND.
WHEN A NUCLEAR BOMB
GOES OFF ON SOME HIGHWAY
EITHER INSIDE
OR OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY,
CHANCES ARE A LOT OF THOSE
COMPONENTS ON THAT BOMB
ARE GOING TO SAY
MADE IN CHINA.
I HAD MY CHILDREN'S THOMAS
THE TRAIN SETS RECALLED
BECAUSE OF THE INK ON
THE RED ONES WAS LEAD POISONED.
THEY'RE NOT ONLY RUINING
OUR ECONOMY.
THEY'RE POISONING
OUR CHILDREN WITH THE TOYS
THAT WE GIVE THEM.
I WANT TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT WHAT PRODUCTS I BUY
BECAUSE I WANNA KNOW THAT
THEY'RE SAFE AND THEY'RE GOOD.
I WANT TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT WHAT PRODUCTS I BUY
BECAUSE I WANNA MAKE SURE THAT
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE PRODUCING
THOSE
ARE BEING TREATED PROPERLY.
AND I WANT TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT THE PRODUCTS I BUY
BECAUSE I WANNA MAKE SURE
THAT THE PEOPLE
IN MY COMMUNITY
ARE PEOPLE WHO ARE ABLE
TO HAVE JOBS AT A DECENT WAGE.
AND ALL OF THOSE THINGS
ARE TIED TOGETHER.
[PETER NAVARRO]
EVERY TIME A CONSUMER
WALKS INTO A WAL-MART,
THE FIRST THING
THEY HAVE TO DO
IS TO BE AWARE ENOUGH
TO LOOK FOR THE LABEL.
THEN, WHEN THEY PICK UP
THAT GOOD AND IT SAYS
"MADE IN CHINA,"
I WANT THEM TO THINK,
HMPH. IT MIGHT EITHER
BREAK DOWN OR IT COULD
KILL ME, NUMBER ONE.
THIS THING, IF I BUY IT,
MIGHT COST ME OR SOMEONE
IN MY FAMILY OR MY FRIENDS
THEIR JOB.
LASTLY, HEY, IF I BUY THIS,
THAT MONEY IS GOING TO GO OVER
TO HELP FINANCE
WHAT IS ESSENTIALLY THE MOST
RAPID MILITARY BUILDUP
OF A TOTALITARIAN REGIME
SINCE WHEN?
THE '30s.
I MEAN, MAKE NO MISTAKE
ABOUT THAT.
91% OF EVERY PRODUCT
IN A WAL-MART STORE
IS MANUFACTURED IN CHINA.
WAL-MART SPENT $50 BILLION
IN CHINA TWO YEARS AGO.
IF WAL-MART WERE A COUNTRY,
THEY WOULD BE CHINA'S FOURTH
LARGEST TRADING PARTNER.
WHEN AN AMERICAN GOES
INTO A WAL-MART
AND BUYS A PRODUCT
MADE IN CHINA,
THAT PERSON
IS THINKING JUST PRICE.
IF YOU'RE A PERSON ON A PENSION
SHOPPING AT WAL-MART,
YOU KINDA LIKE
THE GREAT WALL OF MART.
BUT WHAT THEY REALLY NEED
TO THINK ABOUT
IS HOW THAT PRODUCT GOT THERE.
IT GOT THERE BECAUSE
YOU HAVE A PREDATORY SYSTEM
WHICH IS REALLY TRYING TO
UNDERCUT AMERICAN MANUFACTURERS
AND THEREFORE AMERICAN WORKERS.
[INTERVIEWER]
AND WHEN CONSUMER
GOES INTO WAL-MART
AND PICKS UP
A GOOD MADE IN CHINA,
WHAT DO YOU WANT THEM
TO THINK ABOUT
BEFORE THEY GET
TO THE CASH REGISTER?
THINK ABOUT YOUR RELATIVE
THAT JUST GOT LAID OFF
OR THE FACTORY
THAT JUST GOT SHUT DOWN.
THINK ABOUT THE SCHOOL
THAT IS DOING WITH LESS
BECAUSE THE MANUFACTURING BASE
HAS GONE
AND THE TAX BASE HAS LEFT.
THINK ABOUT THE LOWER INCOME
THAT YOU'RE RECEIVING NOW
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT MAKING
PRODUCTS,
AND WE'RE NOT BUYING
OUR OWN PRODUCTS.
WHEN AMERICANS BUY A PRODUCT
FROM WAL-MART,
I WANT THEM TO REMEMBER
THE CHILDREN, THE FAMILY,
THE WORKERS WHO HAS EARNED
VERY, VERY LITTLE
FROM THOSE PRODUCTS.
THIS IS NOT JUST
AN ECONOMIC MATTER.
THIS IS A SECURITY MATTER
BECAUSE THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
HAS MADE IT CLEAR
THAT IT WANTS TO UNDERMINE
AMERICA'S ROLE IN THE WORLD.
SO, YEAH,
THINGS ARE CHEAP AT WAL-MART,
BUT WE HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
THE CONSEQUENCES.
BUT EVEN IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO CONSIDER
THE BROADER ECONOMIC
OR NATIONAL SECURITY
CONSEQUENCES
OF CONSUMING GOODS
MADE IN CHINA,
YOU MAY AT LEAST WANT TO THINK
ABOUT YOUR OWN PERSONAL SAFETY
AND THAT OF YOUR FAMILY.
[MORICI]
IF YOU PUT IT IN YOUR MOUTH
OR THE HANDS OF A CHILD,
DON'T BUY IT FROM CHINA.
OVER THE LAST FIVE YEARS,
WE'VE HAD A NUMBER OF SCANDALS
INVOLVING CHINESE PRODUCTS.
AND THESE PRODUCTS HAVE KILLED
PEOPLE NOT ONLY IN CHINA,
BUT ALSO IN THE UNITED STATES.
DO YOU WANT TO BUY PIPE
FOR YOUR RESIDENTIAL COMMUNITY
THAT'S GOING TO PUT ALL
THE WATER INTO EVERYBODY'S
HOUSES
THAT IS TAINTED
WITH ARSENIC AND MERCURY
SO THAT IT'LL LEACH OUT
INTO YOUR WATER
SO THAT WHEN YOU TURN
ON YOUR SPIGOT IN YOUR HOUSE,
YOU'RE SUDDENLY, YOU KNOW,
CONTAMINATING YOURSELF
BECAUSE THAT PIPE WAS MADE
CHEAPER IN CHINA?
GOODYEAR TIRE
OUTSIDE OF MONTREAL,
IT CLOSED ABOUT FOUR YEARS AGO
AND PUT 850 PEOPLE OUT OF WORK,
MOVED THE PRODUCTION TO CHINA
BECAUSE THEY COULD MAKE TIRES,
I THINK, IT WAS
FOR $4 A TIRE CHEAPER
AND NOT LONG AFTER
THEY STARTED UP IN CHINA,
THE TRANSPORTATION AGENCY
IN THE U.S.
SAID THE TIRES BEING
PRODUCED THERE WERE UNSAFE.
I MEAN, IS THIS WHAT CORPORATE
AMERICA OR CORPORATE CANADA
THINKS IS THE WAY THEY SHOULD
BE CONDUCTING THEMSELVES?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WE'RE IMPORTING
A LOT OF THEIR APPLES.
THEY SPRAY THEM WITH ALAR,
YOU KNOW.
THAT'S ILLEGAL
IN THE UNITED STATES.
YOU WANT DDT ON YOUR APPLE?
BUY IT FROM CHINA,
AND WE'RE BUYING
A LOT OF APPLES FROM CHINA.
WE'RE BUYING EVERYTHING
FROM CHINA,
AND THEY'RE NO ENVIRONMENTAL
CONTROLS.
[WOMAN]
THERE IS A RISK OF SUFFOCATION,
THAT KIDS CAN GET TRAPPED
AND DIE.
[WOMAN #2]
THEY TOOK HIM TO THE HOSPITAL
WHERE THEY PRONOUNCED HIM DEAD.
[WOMAN #3]
...MASSIVE RECALL OF A MILLION
OF MATTEL'S FISHER-PRICE TOYS.
A RECENT BATCH MADE IN CHINA
CONTAINS TOXIC LEVELS
OF LEAD PAINT.
[MAN]
THE EYES OF THOSE TEDDY BEARS
CAN LOOSEN AND FALL OUT,
IMPOSING A CHOKING HAZARD
TO YOUNG CHILDREN.
[MAN #2]
ACCORDING TO THE STATE MEDIA,
DOZENS OF BABIES HAVE DEVELOPED
KIDNEY STONES IN RECENT DAYS.
[MAN]
THOUSANDS OF PETS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY
DIED AFTER EATING
TAINTED PET FOOD.
THAT LED TO
A MASSIVE PET FOOD RECALL.
[MAN #3]
MY WIFE BONNIE DIED
IN DECEMBER
AFTER RECEIVING HEPARIN
THAT WAS LATER RECALLED BY
BAXTER.
MY SON RANDY
DIED A MONTH LATER
UNDER THE SAME CIRCUMSTANCES.
[WOMAN #4]
SOME BRANDS HAVE BEEN FOUND
TO CONTAIN A TOXIC CHEMICAL
USED IN ANTIFREEZE.
[MAN #4]
PORK FROM PIGS
FORCE-FED WASTEWATER.
[MAN #5]
IF IT COMES FROM CHINA,
AND THE PRICE
IS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE,
THEN IT PROBABLY IS.
IT IS VERY DIFFICULT
FOR ANY COUNTRY
TO PROTECT THEIR CITIZENS
FROM CHINESE PRODUCTS.
THE REAL PROBLEM HERE
IS THAT YOU HAVE A POLITICAL
SYSTEM
THAT DOES NOT PUNISH
MANUFACTURERS
FOR BAD PRODUCTS.
AND IT'S BECAUSE
IT'S THE NATURE
OF THE POLITICAL SYSTEM.
THE COMMUNIST PARTY DOES NOT
ALLOW INDEPENDENT PROSECUTORS,
DOESN'T ALLOW A FREE PRESS,
DOESN'T ALLOW PEOPLE TO
COMPLAIN ABOUT BAD PRODUCTS.
LET'S TAKE FISH.
THERE ARE 3.5 MILLION
FISH FARMS IN CHINA.
THE FISH ARE RAISED
IN CONTAMINATED PONDS.
THEY ARE FED
ALL KINDS OF HORMONES,
AND THE BIGGEST MARKET
FOR THAT FISH
IS THE UNITED STATES.
85% OF THE TILAPIA
COMES FROM CHINA.
MOST OF OUR SHRIMP
U.S. FDA ONLY HAS THE ABILITY
TO INSPECT ONE PERCENT
OF THE FISH COMING
INTO THE UNITED STATES.
65% PERCENT
OF THE ONE PERCENT THEY REJECT.
THEY DON'T HAVE THE AUTHORITY
TO CONFISCATE THE FISH,
SO IF THE SHIP COMES
INTO CHARLESTON
AND GETS REJECTED,
THEN IT GOES TO MIAMI
OR NEW ORLEANS
OR SOME OTHER PORT
AND EVENTUALLY
THE FISH GETS IN.
AND BECAUSE OF SUCH DANGERS,
AMERICANS ARE BECOMING
MORE AND MORE AWARE
OF THE MADE-IN-CHINA LABEL
BUT THAT DOESN'T ALWAYS
GUARANTEE ONE'S SAFETY,
OR CONVENIENCE.
I PERSONALLY DO LOOK
AT THE LABELS OF
WHERE THINGS ARE MADE,
BUT SOMETIMES
I GO TO BUY THINGS,
AND IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO FIND SOMETHING
THAT ISN'T MADE IN CHINA.
WELL, MY WIFE'S A GOOD
CARD-CARRYING LIBERAL.
SHE BELIEVES IN ALL
THE WORTHY CAUSES IN THE WORLD
AND ALL THAT SORT OF THING,
AND SHE'S AN INTELLIGENT
WOMAN I WANT TO SAY
FOR THE RECORD.
LITTLE BY LITTLE I REALIZED
THAT CHINA WAS GETTING
TO WHERE IT WAS
AND THE UNITED STATES
WAS GETTING TO WHERE IT WAS
BECAUSE THERE WAS ALL THIS
CURRENCY MANIPULATION,
AND IT JUST SEEMED LIKE
THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT
WAS NOT DOING A WHOLE LOT
IN THE NAME
OF INTERNATIONAL TRADE
TO TRY TO STOP
WHAT WAS GOING ON IN CHINA,
WHICH WAS ABLE
TO LURE A LOT OF JOBS.
SOME MONTHS AGO,
SHE DECIDED TO THE BEST
OF HER ABILITY,
SHE WASN'T GOING TO BUY
ANYTHING MADE IN CHINA.
SO OUR MICROWAVE OVEN FAILED.
WE DON'T HAVE
A NEW MICROWAVE OVEN
BECAUSE SHE COULD NOT FIND ONE
THAT WAS NOT MADE IN CHINA.
WHEN I WENT TO LOOK
FOR A MICROWAVE
OR FREE-STANDING MICROWAVE,
THERE WAS NOTHING
THAT WASN'T MADE IN CHINA.
I WENT TO FIVE DIFFERENT STORES
FROM HIGH-END HARDWARE STORES
TO LOW-END DISCOUNT PLACES.
NOTHING WAS AVAILABLE
THAT WASN'T MADE IN CHINA,
AND MY EXPERIENCE
WITH THINGS MADE IN CHINA
WAS THAT THEY WEREN'T HEALTHY,
YOU NEVER KNEW
WHAT WAS IN THEM,
THEY DIDN'T WORK FOR VERY LONG,
AND THEY BROKE DOWN
IF THEY WORKED
IN THE BEGINNING.
SO I THEN DECIDED
I JUST WASN'T GOING TO BUY
ANYTHING THAT WAS MADE
IN CHINA.
SO WE JUST DO NOT HAVE
A MICROWAVE ANYMORE.
RIGHT AROUND THE SAME TIME,
WE HAD AN UNDER-A-COUNTER
ELECTRIC UNIT FOR HEATING
IN ONE OF THE ROOMS
AND THE SAME THING HAPPENED.
YOU COULDN'T GET
ANY ELECTRIC BASEBOARD
THAT WASN'T MADE IN CHINA.
AND I THOUGHT WELL MY LAST ONE
WAS MADE IN AMERICA.
I HAD IT FOR 23 YEARS.
IT WORKED GREAT.
NOW I COULDN'T FIND IT.
AND I JUST GOT
COMPLETELY DISCOURAGED
THAT NO AMERICAN MANUFACTURERS
WERE COMING IN TO PRODUCE
QUALITY PRODUCTS OVER HERE.
AND THAT'S THE DILEMMA
WE NOW FIND OURSELVES IN.
AS CHINA HAS USED ITS WEAPONS
OF JOB DESTRUCTION
TO SO THOROUGHLY CAPTURE
OUR MARKETS,
WE ARE LEFT WITH FEW
CHOICES OTHER THAN
TO BUY FROM CHINA.
BUT THE MORE WE BUY FROM CHINA,
THE MORE RISKS
OUR FAMILIES FACE
FROM DANGEROUS
CHINESE PRODUCTS.
AND THE MORE JOBS WE LOSE.
AND BECAUSE THIS IS TRUE,
WE NOW MUST ALSO CONFRONT
THIS MUCH BIGGER TRUTH.
[MAN]
WE IMPORT A LOT OF STUFF
FROM CHINA,
BUT A LOT OF IT
WE DON'T PAY FOR.
I MEAN, WE'VE GOT NO GOODS TO
SHIP IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION,
SO WE JUST SHIP
BUNDLES OF DOLLAR BILLS,
BETWEEN TWO AND THREE TRILLION
DOLLARS IS AVAILABLE
TO BUY UP PIECES OF AMERICA.
IN OTHER WORDS,
WE'RE LIVING BEYOND OUR MEANS.
WE HAVE AN ARTIFICIALLY HIGH
STANDARD OF LIVING.
WE'RE CONSUMING
MORE THAN WE CREATE.
THAT'S
A VERY DANGEROUS SITUATION,
AND ESPECIALLY IF
YOUR PRINCIPLE CREDITOR
IS A NATION LIKE CHINA.
SO JUST EXACTLY HOW
DID WE IN AMERICA
ALLOW OURSELVES TO BE BACKED
INTO SUCH A DANGEROUS
CHINESE CORNER?
WHEN YOU LIVE IN A DEMOCRACY,
IT'S ALWAYS SUBJECTED
TO BEING HIJACKED,
AND OUR DEMOCRACY
HAS BEEN HIJACKED
BY THE MULTINATIONAL
CORPORATIONS.
THE CORPORATE RESPONSIBILITY
IS TO ITS SHAREHOLDERS,
AND IT OFTEN HAS A LEGAL
FIDUCIARY RESPONSIBILITY
TO ITS SHAREHOLDERS.
THE GOVERNMENT
HAS A RESPONSIBILITY
TO THE PEOPLE
AND THE NATIONAL INTEREST.
THOSE ARE NOT NECESSARILY
THE SAME.
U.S. MULTINATIONAL CORPORATIONS
KNEW EXACTLY
WHAT WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE
ANY PLANS
TO INCREASE EXPORTS
TO CHINA
AFTER CHINA JOINED THE WTO.
THEY HAD PLANS TO MOVE
PRODUCTION TO CHINA,
BUT THEY WERE, I'D SAY,
DISHONEST OR DISINGENUOUS
BECAUSE THE WHOLE RHETORIC
AROUND CHINA JOINING THE WTO
WAS ABOUT FREE TRADE
AND OPENING MARKETS
AND ENGAGING WITH CHINA.
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
OUR COMPANIES
WILL BE ABLE TO SELL AND
DISTRIBUTE PRODUCTS IN CHINA
MADE BY WORKERS
HERE IN AMERICA.
WHEN IN FACT IT WAS REALLY
SELF-INTEREST AND PROFIT MOTIVE
ON THE PART OF U.S.
MULTINATIONALS
THAT DROVE THAT DEBATE.
AND U.S. CHINA COMMISSIONER
AND BUSINESSMAN DAN SLANE
KNOWS FIRSTHAND
JUST HOW THIS OFFSHORING
SHELL GAME IS WORKING,
SINCE CHINA JOINED THE WORLD
TRADE ORGANIZATION IN 2001
AND BEGAN FLOODING
AMERICAN MARKETS
WITH ILLEGALLY
SUBSIDIZED EXPORTS.
I HAD A PLYWOOD MANUFACTURING
FACILITY IN BOWLING GREEN,
KENTUCKY,
SELLING PLYWOOD
TO FURNITURE MANUFACTURERS
IN THE UNITED STATES.
IN 2002, ALL OF MY COMPETITORS
WERE MOVING TO CHINA.
ESSENTIALLY,
I HAD TWO CHOICES--
I SHUT THE COMPANY DOWN,
OR I MOVED IT TO CHINA.
AND I OPENED UP
THREE FACTORIES IN CHINA
AND DELIVERED TO THE CUSTOMER
IN THE UNITED STATES
50% CHEAPER
THAN I COULD MAKE IT
IN BOWLING GREEN.
AND SLANE'S NEW FOUND
COMPETITIVE EDGE
WAS ALL DUE TO CHINA'S
ILLEGAL WEAPONS
OF JOB DESTRUCTION.
MANIPULATING THE CURRENCY
WAS A HUGE HELP FOR ME,
BECAUSE IT KEPT
OUR PRICES DOWN.
I HAD NO ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUES;
AND THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
WAS THAT I COULD SELL
MY PRODUCT AT COST
AND EVERY MONTH THE CHINESE
GOVERNMENT
WOULD SEND ME A CHECK
FOR 17% OF MY EXPORTS,
AND THAT WAS MY NET MARGIN
AND MY PROFIT.
SO WAS SLANE WRONG TO OFFSHORE
HIS FACTORIES TO CHINA?
THIS INTERCHANGE
WITH U.S. CHINA COMMISSIONER
AND MULTINATIONAL CORPORATION
LOBBYIST WILLIAM REINSCH
OFFERS SOME PERSPECTIVE:
IT'S NOT GENERALLY REGARDED
AS THE JOB OF A LARGE AMERICAN
COMPANY TO SUBSTITUTE ITSELF
FOR THE GOVERNMENT.
WHAT MOST OF THE COMPANIES
WANT TO DO
IS TO--
THEY WANT TO BE CONSISTENT
WITH GOVERNMENT--
WITH U.S. LAW
AND U.S. PRACTICE.
IF THE GOVERNMENT TELLS THEM
THAT THEY WOULD LIKE THEM
TO DO SOMETHING,
THEY GENERALLY DO IT.
[INTERVIEWER]
SO THEY DON'T HAVE ANY
RESPONSIBILITY PER SE
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
OTHER THAN OBEYING THE EXISTING
LAWS AND REGULATIONS.
IS THAT FAIR?
WELL, WHAT RESPONSIBILITY
WOULD YOU LIKE THEM TO HAVE
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
OTHER THAN TRYING TO BE
GOOD CORPORATE CITIZENS
AND TO BE PROFITABLE?
WOULD YOU DEFINE
A GOOD CORPORATE CITIZEN
AS A COMPANY THAT MOVES
ITS FACTORIES OVER TO CHINA
AND CREATES MASSIVE
UNEMPLOYMENT IN THE MIDWEST?
IS THAT GOOD CORPORATE
CITIZENRY?
WELL, I THINK THAT
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK--
YOU'D HAVE TO LOOK AT--
YOU'D HAVE TO GO CASE BY CASE.
AND IN DAN SLANE'S CASE?
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN MYSELF
AND GENERAL ELECTRIC
IS THAT I HAD NO CHOICE.
I EITHER MOVE TO CHINA,
OR I SHUT THE COMPANY DOWN.
I COULDN'T COMPETE.
JEFF IMMELT
AT GENERAL ELECTRIC
DOES HAVE A CHOICE.
HE CAN SACRIFICE SOME PROFITS,
KEEP HIS TECHNOLOGY,
AND IN THE LONG TERM
BE MUCH BETTER OFF
MANUFACTURING
IN THE UNITED STATES.
CONGRESSMAN TIM RYAN
UNDERSTANDS THIS DISTINCTION
BETWEEN SMALL DOMESTIC
MANUFACTURERS
AND THE BIG, WELL-HEELED
MULTINATIONALS
BETTER THAN MOST.
THERE'S A HUGE DIVIDE HERE
BETWEEN THE MOM AND POP
TOOL AND DIE MAKER
THAT HAS BEEN
IN YOUNGSTOWN, OHIO
FOR A HUNDRED YEARS
AND THE GLOBAL CORPORATION
THAT'S INVOLVED IN THE GLOBAL
FINANCING OF ALL OF THIS STUFF,
THE GLOBAL MANUFACTURING,
AND NOT REALLY CONCERNED
WITH ANY ONE COUNTRY.
THEY'RE CONCERNED WITH
HOW THEY CAN BEST DO BUSINESS.
AND ONE OF THE BIGGEST
OBSTACLES
TO PASSING TOUGH LEGISLATION
THAT WOULD STOP CHINA'S
UNFAIR TRADE PRACTICES
IS THE LACK OF POLITICAL CLOUT
OF AMERICA'S
DOMESTIC MANUFACTURERS.
AND TO GO CHASING DOWN AFTER
ALL OF THE POLITICAL RHETORIC
OF DEALING WITH THIS ISSUE
AND THAT ISSUE
AND RUNNING TO ALBANY
OR RUNNING TO WASHINGTON, D.C.
AND SETTING UP MEETINGS
AND STUFF,
IT'S TOO COSTLY,
IT'S TOO TIME-CONSUMING,
AND IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH BUILDING DRUM-AND
BARREL-HANDLING EQUIPMENT
AND HELPING THIS COMPANY
TO BE SUCCESSFUL.
AND THAT'S THE ISSUE HERE.
THEY DON'T HAVE LOBBYISTS
DOWN HERE.
THERE'S VERY FEW ORGANIZATIONS
THAT REALLY REPRESENT
THE SMALL AND MID-SIZED
MANUFACTURERS.
I CAN THINK OF ONE OR TWO
THAT REALLY DO A GREAT JOB,
BUT THEY DON'T HAVE THE IMPACT,
THE CAMPAIGN CONTRIBUTIONS,
THE CORPORATE INFLUENCE
THAT SOME OF THE BIG DOGS HAVE.
AND JUST WHO
IS ONE OF THE BIGGEST DOGS
ON THE CAPITOL HILL
LOBBYING BLOCK?
BEHIND ME IS THE HEADQUARTERS
OF THE NATIONAL ASSOCIATION
OF MANUFACTURERS,
WHICH UNFORTUNATELY
HAS BECOME A MAJOR MISNOMER
IN RECENT YEARS,
BECAUSE THE NAME
REALLY SHOULD BE
THE NATIONAL ASSOCIATION
OF MANUFACTURING THINGS
SOMEPLACE ELSE.
IF YOU GO BACK AND YOU LOOK
AT THE NATIONAL ASSOCIATION
OF MANUFACTURERS' MEETINGS
IN WHICH THEY WERE TALKING ABOUT
ENDORSING OR
NOT ENDORSING THE RYAN-MURPHY
CHINA CURRENCY BILL,
YOU WILL SEE THAT THERE
WAS A HUGE SPLIT
WHERE THE SMALL AND MEDIUM-SIZED
MANUFACTURERS ENDORSED THE BILL.
BUT THE 20% OF THE MEMBERSHIP
THAT GIVES 80% OF THE DUES
DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE RYAN-MURPHY
CHINA CURRENCY BILL.
BRIAN O'SHAUGHNESSY
IS THE CHAIRMAN
OF REVERE COPPER,
A COMPANY FOUNDED
BY NONE OTHER THAN PAUL REVERE
AND THE OLDEST MANUFACTURER
IN AMERICA.
AND O'SHAUGHNESSY HAS BEEN
ON THE INSIDE
OF THE NATIONAL ASSOCIATION
OF MANUFACTURERS
WHEN IT HAS OPPOSED BILLS LIKE
THOSE OFFERED UP BY TIM RYAN
TO STOP CHINA'S
CURRENCY MANIPULATION.
I STOOD UP BEFORE A GROUP
OF 300 OF THE MOST POWERFUL CEOs
IN THIS COUNTRY,
AND I TOLD THEM,
AS WE CONSIDER N-A-M SUPPORT
OF THIS BILL,
I THINK THOSE OF YOU
WHO HAVE FACILITIES IN CHINA,
I THINK YOU SHOULD RECUSE
YOURSELF FROM VOTING.
YOU'RE CONFLICTED.
YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN YOUR COMPANY
AND YOUR COUNTRY,
AND YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WELL, I WAS SHOT DOWN
IN FLAMES.
BY ALL INTENTS AND PURPOSES,
A LOT OF THESE COMPANIES
ARE NOT AMERICAN COMPANIES
ANYMORE.
[SLANE]
GENERAL MOTORS TAKES TARP MONEY
AND OPENS UP FACTORIES
IN CHINA.
CATERPILLAR TRACTOR
SHUTS DOWN PLANTS IN PEORIA
AND OPENS UP THREE FACTORIES
IN CHINA.
GENERAL ELECTRIC AND BOEING
ARE ESSENTIALLY TRYING
TO BECOME CHINESE COMPANIES.
LOOK AT COCA-COLA.
AMERICAN-SOUNDING COMPANY,
ISN'T IT?
HOW AMERICAN CAN YOU GET
OTHER THAN REVERE OR COCA-COLA?
THE PRESIDENT OF COCA-COLA
IS FROM SOUTH AFRICA.
THE CHAIRMAN IS FROM TURKEY.
NOW, YOU WANNA ASK THEM
WHAT AMERICA'S INTERNATIONAL
TRADE POLICY SHOULD BE?
YOU SHOULDN'T LISTEN TO THEM.
WHILE COCA COLA'S EXECUTIVE
SUITE MAY LOOK LIKE
THE UNITED NATIONS,
IT IS PURE BRED AMERICAN
CEOs
FROM COMPANIES LIKE CISCO,
FORD, IBM,
HONEYWELL, MOTOROLA, INTEL,
AND APPLE
THAT KEEP SENDING
SO MANY OF OUR JOBS TO CHINA.
[MCCORMACK]
WE DESIGN THE iPAD. GREAT.
WE GET THE PROFITS
FROM THE iPAD. FINE.
WE DON'T GET THE JOBS.
PROFITS VERSUS JOBS.
THAT'S A CONFLICT
RALPH GOMORY SEES
AS THE ROOT OF AMERICA'S
OFFSHORING PROBLEM.
THEY ARE PURSUING
MAXIMIZING PROFIT.
THAT'S THEIR GOAL.
THE COUNTRY IS LOSING
THE WAGE BILL.
AND ITS GOAL IS TO HAVE WAGES.
WHAT THEY'RE DOING IS RIGHT
FOR THEIR SHAREHOLDERS
AND THEIR CONSTITUENTS,
BUT IT'S NOT RIGHT
FOR THE PEOPLE OF AMERICA
WHO ARE UNABLE TO FIND WORK
TODAY.
THE PROBLEM WITH OUR SYSTEM
IS THAT IT IS EVERYTHING IS
SHORT TERM
SO WHEN YOU TALK TO A CEO
AND YOU SAY TO A CEO,
AN AMERICAN CEO,
"DO YOU REALIZE THAT THEY'RE
GOING TO TAKE YOUR TECHNOLOGY
AND THEY'RE GOING TO BE
YOUR COMPETITOR?"
THE CEO SAYS,
"YES, BUT I ONLY HAVE THREE OR
FOUR YEARS TO GET MY STOCK UP
SO I CAN GET MY BONUS,"
AND THEY KICK THE CAN
DOWN THE ROAD,
AND IT'S THE NEXT GUY'S PROBLEM.
THIS WILL END BADLY
FOR ALL OF US,
BUT EVERYBODY
IS SO SHORT TERM IN THINKING
AND IN THEIR TENURE
THAT THEY'RE WILLING
TO TAKE CHANCES
THAT ARE RIGHT FOR TODAY
THAT THEY PROBABLY KNOW
IN THEIR MINDS
IS LONG TERM BAD
FOR AMERICA TOMORROW.
IRONICALLY,
NOBODY UNDERSTOOD THIS GROWING
DIVERGENCE
BETWEEN CORPORATE INTERESTS
AND THE COMMON GOOD
BETTER THAN CANDIDATE
BILL CLINTON
DURING THE 1992 ELECTIONS.
YOU MUST DO YOUR PART.
YOU MUST BE RESPONSIBLE.
AMERICAN COMPANIES MUST ACT
LIKE AMERICAN COMPANIES AGAIN,
EXPORTING PRODUCTS NOT JOBS.
BUT SUCH CORPORATE
IRRESPONSIBILITY
WASN'T ALWAYS THE AMERICAN WAY.
CORPORATIONS
USED TO THINK THEY HAD
A STAKEHOLDER THEORY.
IN OTHER WORDS, THEY HAD A
RESPONSIBILITY TO THE NATION,
TO THEIR COMMUNITY,
TO THEIR WORKERS,
AND TO THEIR SHAREHOLDERS.
SOMETHING MORPHED IN OUR OWN
SYSTEM ABOUT 20, 25 YEARS AGO
WHERE SHAREHOLDER VALUE
BECAME THE END-ALL AND BE-ALL,
AND THEN THE CEOs TIED
THEIR OWN COMPENSATION
TO SHAREHOLDER VALUE,
AND THEN OTHER COUNTRIES
FIGURED OUT
HOW TO INCENTIVIZE THEM
TO INCREASE SHORT-TERM
SHAREHOLDER VALUE
BY TRANSFERRING PRODUCTION,
MANUFACTURING, R&D THERE.
AND WE CAN NEVER FORGET
THAT WHEN CHINA MANIPULATES
CURRENCY,
WHEN CHINA PROVIDES ILLEGAL
SUBSIDIES OF ALL SORTS
FOR MANUFACTURING,
FOR THE ACT
OF EXPORTING ITSELF,
THESE U.S.-OWNED COMPANIES
BENEFIT.
THEY LIKE THE STATUS QUO,
THEY WANT TO PROTECT IT,
AND THEY HAVE PAID
A LOT OF MONEY FOR IT.
MONEY AND THE POWER OF
AMERICA'S MULTINATIONAL
CORPORATIONS
IN INFLUENCING
CHINA TRADE POLICY--
THAT'S SOMETHING TWO MEN
FROM TWO DISTINCTLY
DIFFERENT WORLDS
CAN AGREE ON.
I LIVE IN THAT WORLD.
I'VE WATCHED THOSE DOLLARS GO.
CAMPAIGN LAWS ALLOW THEM
TO SPEND UNLIMITLESS
AMOUNTS OF MONEY.
IT'S A TSUNAMI.
BUT TO FORMER WHITE HOUSE
ADVISOR JARED BERNSTEIN,
IT'S MORE THAN JUST MONEY
AND POLITICS DRIVING
OUR JOBS OFFSHORE.
IT'S ALSO THE PREVAILING
FREE MARKET VIEW
IN THE OVAL OFFICE,
REGARDLESS OF POLITICAL PARTY.
I THINK THAT THERE IS
A DEEPLY EMBEDDED VIEW
THAT I DO NOT THINK
IS WHOLLY WRONG,
THAT CAPITAL MUST BE HAPPY
IF WE ARE GOING TO HAVE
A SUCCESSFUL ECONOMY.
AND NO MULTINATIONAL COMPANY
HAS BEEN HAPPIER
TO MOVE ITS CAPITAL OFFSHORE
THAN GENERAL ELECTRIC,
BUT THIS IS TRULY
A FOOL'S GAME.
[SLANE]
THE CHINESE HAVE NO INTENTION
OF TURNING OVER
THEIR DOMESTIC MARKET
TO FOREIGN COMPANIES.
ONCE THEY'RE ABLE
TO MASTER THE TECHNOLOGY,
THEY ARE GOING TO MAKE IT
VERY DIFFICULT
FOR FOREIGN CORPORATIONS
TO MAKE A PROFIT.
WHEN I GO OUT AND DO SPEECHES
TO CORPORATE AUDIENCES ON CHINA
AND THEY WANT ME TO TALK
ABOUT STRATEGY,
IT'S LIKE.
"HEY, YOU'RE GOING OVER
TO CHINA.
"YOU'RE GIVING
THEM YOUR AVIONICS
"SO YOU CAN PARTICIPATE
IN A REGIONAL JET GAME IN CHINA,
"AND TWO OR THREE
OR FIVE YEARS FROM NOW,
"YOU'RE GOING TO TRY TO SELL
YOUR REGIONAL JETS IN EUROPE,
"AND YOUR BIGGEST COMPETITOR
IS GOING TO BE THAT CHINA GUY.
HOW STUPID IS THAT?"
WHAT'S HAPPENING UNFORTUNATELY
IN THE UNITED STATES
IS WAY TOO MANY OF OUR
MULTINATIONAL CORPORATIONS,
NOT ONLY THEY'RE SHIFTING
THEIR MANUFACTURING OVERSEAS,
BUT ALONG WITH IT
GOES THEIR TECHNOLOGY,
THEIR INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY.
AND WHILE MANY OF US ARE
CONCERNED, DEEPLY CONCERNED,
ABOUT THE LOSS OF JOBS,
WE'RE JUST AS CONCERNED
ABOUT THE LOSS OF
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY.
THAT'S SORT OF THE FUTURE
OF AMERICA.
THE THING IS
NOBODY HAS REALLY LOOKED
AT ALL THE INDUSTRIES
THAT HAVE BEEN LOST.
IT'S VERY HARD TO GET
INFORMATION ON THE INDUSTRIES
THAT ARE GONE,
OR THAT ARE JUST ABOUT GONE,
BECAUSE THE GOVERNMENT
DOESN'T KEEP TRACK OF ANY DATA.
THEY DON'T FOLLOW INDUSTRIES.
THEY HAVE NO MARKET ANALYSTS
WHO FOLLOW SPECIFIC INDUSTRIES,
SO NOBODY KNOWS WHAT'S HAPPENED
WITH ALL OF OUR INDUSTRIAL
CAPACITY THAT'S VANISHED,
OR IS IN THE PROCESS
OF VANISHING.
THE NEXT THING YOU SEE
IS YOU'RE NOT DOING ANY WORK
OVER THERE YOURSELF.
THE CHINESE ARE DOING IT
FOR YOU ENTIRELY.
AND WE SEE THAT.
THE TWO MID-RANGE AIRCRAFT
IN THE WORLD
ARE THE AIRBUS 319
AND THE BOEING 737.
FIVE YEARS FROM NOW,
THE CHINESE HAVE ALREADY TOLD
BOTH COMPANIES,
THEY WILL NO LONGER BUY
EITHER AIRCRAFT.
THAT MID-RANGE AIRCRAFT,
THE ONE THAT IS DOMINATE
THROUGHOUT ASIA,
WILL BE ENTIRELY
MANUFACTURED IN CHINA
UNDER A CHINESE MARK OR NAME
USING TECHNOLOGY
THAT THEY TOOK
FROM AIRBUS ON THE ONE HAND
AND BOEING ON THE OTHER.
? LOOK AROUND ?
? TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE ?
? EVERY DAY MORE PEOPLE
IN THE STREET ?
? TOO BAD ?
? THEY SENT OUR JOBS AWAY ?
? IN CHINA
THEY'RE NOT WORKERS,
THEY'RE JUST SLAVES ?
? PEOPLE, WAKE ?
? IT'S A WORLD
OF TRADE AND GREED ?
? AND THE CEOs GET RICHER ?
? AND OUR JOBS ALL MOVE
OFF SHORE ?
? OH-OH-OH-OH ?
THE SOVIET UNION
COULD MAKE AN UNBELIEVABLE
INTERCONTINENTAL BALLISTIC
MISSILE,
BUT THEY COULDN'T MAKE
A LOAF OF BREAD.
NOW, WE CAN MAKE
A STEALTH FIGHTER,
BUT WE CAN'T MAKE
A PAIR OF SHOES.
YOU CAN'T BE A WORLD POWER
IF YOU DON'T MAKE ANYTHING
BUT HOT AIR,
AND WE'RE
WELL ON OUR WAY TO THAT.
YOU CAN'T HAVE SUSTAINABLE,
LONG-RUN ECONOMIC GROWTH
AT ROBUST LEVELS
IN THE ABSENCE
OF A MANUFACTURING BASE.
LESS THAN NINE PERCENT
OF AMERICAN WORKERS
ARE NOW IN
THE MANUFACTURING SECTOR.
WE AS A COUNTRY CAN'T SURVIVE
INTO THE LONG TERM
WITH UNDER 25%
OF OUR WOMEN AND MEN
MAKING THINGS.
MANUFACTURING JOBS
HAVE A HIGHER MULTIPLIER
THAN SERVICE INDUSTRY JOBS.
THAT IS TO SAY,
EVERY ONE MANUFACTURING JOB
THAT YOU BRING INTO A COMMUNITY
ULTIMATELY SUPPORTS
HALF A DOZEN OTHER JOBS.
IF YOU ARE HONEST
ABOUT HOW JOBS HAVE EVOLVED
IN THE UNITED STATES,
SMALL BUSINESSES AROSE
ONLY WHEN THERE
WAS A STABLE MANUFACTURING BASE
PUT UNDER THEM.
MY MOTHER, AND MANY MOTHERS
OF YOURS, I'M SURE,
UP ON THE COMMISSION,
THEY GAVE THEMSELVES
HOME PERMANENTS.
IT WAS ONLY WHEN THERE WAS
A STABILITY OF MIDDLE-CLASS
INCOMES
THAT YOU HAD BEAUTY PARLORS
AND NAIL SALONS
AND PIZZA PARLORS
AND MCDONALDS
AND ALL OF THE THINGS WE THINK
OF AS SMALL BUSINESS.
EVERY ONE MANUFACTURING JOB
THAT YOU BRING INTO A COMMUNITY
ULTIMATELY SUPPORTS
HALF A DOZEN OTHER JOBS.
THOSE MANUFACTURERS
PROVIDE THE GOOD-PAYING JOBS
IN OUR COMMUNITY,
AND IT'S THE JOBS THAT
A FATHER OR MOTHER CAN
WORK AT THE FACTORY,
RAISE THEIR FAMILY,
HAVE SOME HEALTH CARE,
HAVE A SAFE PENSION,
DONATE A LITTLE BIT OF MONEY
INTO THE BASKET IN CHURCH ON
SUNDAY,
VOTE FOR THE SCHOOL LEVY,
VOTE FOR THE POLICE
AND FIRE LEVY,
TO HELP BUILD
STRONG COMMUNITIES,
AND WHEN THOSE FACTORIES
GOT WIPED OUT
AND THEY WENT FROM
200 TO 30 PEOPLE,
IT BECOMES VERY DIFFICULT
FOR THESE COMMUNITIES
TO SUSTAIN THEMSELVES.
ULTIMATELY
THE MOST IMPORTANT REASON
WHY AMERICA MUST RESTORE
ITS MANUFACTURING BASE
IS TO HOLD ON TO THE
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT,
THE R&D.
THAT IS THE TAP ROOT OF ALL OF
THE TECHNOLOGICAL INNOVATIONS
WE WILL NEED TO CREATE
NEW JOBS IN NEW INDUSTRIES.
MANUFACTURING IS THE ORIGIN
OF 70% OF U.S. R&D.
THAT'S TRUE EVEN TODAY.
YOU CAN'T DO YOUR R&D HERE AND
DO YOUR MANUFACTURING THERE.
YOU CAN'T MOVE YOUR
MANUFACTURING OVERSEAS
AND NOT MOVE YOUR TECHNOLOGY
AND ALL YOUR ENGINEERING.
IT'S NICE TO DO R&D AND COME UP
WITH A SUPER-DUPER DESIGN
OR A NEW PRODUCT,
BUT IF YOU CAN'T MAKE IT,
WHAT'S THE SENSE OF DOING
THE R&D?
WHEN WE SAY WE'VE KEPT OUR
TECHNOLOGY OR OUR I.P.
BUT WE'VE MOVED
OUR MANUFACTURING,
THAT'S JUST NOT TRUE.
IT'S AN IMPOSSIBLE FEAT.
THEY'RE TOTALLY COUPLED.
SO AS MANUFACTURING
HAS MOVED OFF SHORE,
R&D HAS GONE RIGHT WITH IT.
SO AS WE MOVE MORE AND MORE
MANUFACTURING OVER TO CHINA,
AND PEOPLE CAN RE-ENGINEER
AND UNDERSTAND HOW
THINGS ARE MADE,
WE ARE TEACHING THE COUNTRY
HOW TO COMPETE WITH US,
AND ULTIMATELY THEY ARE.
SO THAT THE NEW PRODUCTS,
THE NEXT CUTTING EDGE PRODUCT,
IS BEING DEVELOPED THERE
WHERE THE MANUFACTURING'S
GOING ON IN CHINA
RATHER THAN HERE WHERE
THE MANUFACTURING WAS
AND NOW IS NO LONGER.
? THERE'S NO OTHER WAY
AROUND IT ?
? WE CAN'T MAKE IT
ON OUR OWN ?
? ALL THE JOBS WENT TO CHINA ?
? NOW I'M LOSING MY OWN HOME ?
WE NEED TO CHANGE COURSE.
WE NEED DEFINITIVE U.S. ACTION.
WE NEED TO SHOW THE CHINESE
THAT THERE ARE LIMITS,
THAT THEY HAVE TO BE
RESPONSIBLE CITIZENS,
AND THAT IF THEY'RE NOT
THERE ARE CONSEQUENCES.
I LIKE THE IDEA OF DOING
BUSINESS WITH CHINA.
THERE ARE A FEW PEOPLE
OVER THERE.
BUT, IT SHOULD BE,
IT MUST BE ON OUR TERMS.
IF IT'S NOT ON OUR TERMS,
THEN IT'S ON THEIR TERMS,
AND IF IT'S ON THEIR TERMS,
THEY DON'T HAVE OUR BEST
INTERESTS IN MIND.
PEOPLE SOMETIMES SAY
THAT WE CAN'T STAND UP TO THE
CHINESE ON ANY OF THESE ISSUES
BECAUSE WE RISK STARTING
A, QUOTE, "TRADE WAR."
MY MESSAGE
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
IS THAT WE ARE ALREADY
IN A TRADE WAR.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH TAKING
CHINA TO TASK?
THEY PIRATE OUR TECHNOLOGY.
THEY PIRATE OUR
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS.
THEY COUNTERFEIT
OUR GOODS AND SERVICES,
AND NO ADMINISTRATION
HAS THE BACKBONE
TO STAND UP TO THEM.
IT'S BEEN DISMAYING
FOR ME TO SEE
A SUCCESSION
OF ADMINISTRATIONS,
BOTH REPUBLICAN
AND DEMOCRATIC,
UNABLE OR UNWILLING
TO TAKE ON
THE CHINA TRADE IMBALANCE,
AND I WOULD SAY PART
OF THAT IS THE VERY COZY
RELATIONSHIP
THAT ANY WHITE HOUSE HAS
WITH THE BIG MULTINATIONAL
CORPORATIONS
AND WITH
THE INTELLECTUAL ELITE
THAT HAVE TAKEN
A VERY SOFT VIEW
ON THIS ISSUE,
SO I THINK BOTH DEMOCRATIC
AND REPUBLICAN ADMINISTRATIONS
HAVE FAILED US IN THE SAME WAY.
SO HOW DO WE THE PEOPLE
OVERCOME THE POWER
AND INFLUENCE
OF THE BIG MULTINATIONAL
COMPANIES
AND THE DEADLY INERTIA
OF OUR POLITICAL LEADERSHIP
TO BRING ABOUT
LONG OVERDUE CHANGES
IN THE U.S.-CHINA
TRADE RELATIONSHIP?
IT ALMOST TAKES A MOVEMENT,
A TEA PARTY
THAT'S DIFFERENT THAN--
THAT'S COMPLETELY DIVORCED
OF LEFT OR RIGHT.
IT'S VIRTUALLY A TEA PARTY
THAT DIFFERENTIATES
BETWEEN RIGHT AND WRONG,
WHICH IS VERY MUCH DIFFERENT
THAN LEFT OR RIGHT.
I THINK THIS CAN ONLY HAPPEN
WHEN THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
REALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT IS HAPPENING TO US
AND BEGIN TO DEMAND
THAT THEIR CONGRESSMEN
AND SENATORS REALLY--
AND THE NATIONAL GOVERNMENT--
TAKE ACTION IN THESE AREAS.
I THINK THAT AT EVERY LEVEL,
PEOPLE COULD BOYCOTT
TO SOME EXTENT,
AND THERE WOULD BE A SHOT
HEARD AROUND THE WORLD.
IT'S GOT TO BE A WHOLE
COMMUNITY EFFORT
BY THE CITIZENRY,
BUT WE DO NEED TO CREATE JOBS.
IT DOESN'T ALWAYS HAPPEN
ACCIDENTALLY.
HERE'S THE MESSAGE
THAT NEEDS TO BE DEVELOPED.
YOU KNOW, LOOK.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THIS WAY.
THIS IS AN ECONOMY
AND A GLOBAL ECONOMY
THAT HAS BEEN MADE
BY POLICY CHOICES,
POLICY CHOICES
THAT REALLY DO BENEFIT THE RICH
AND THE MULTINATIONALS.
THEIR INTERESTS
NO LONGER COINCIDE
WITH THE INTERESTS
OF THIS COUNTRY,
SO WE HAVE TO DO WHAT'S BEST
FOR THIS COUNTRY.
THEY'LL DO WHAT'S BEST
FOR THEIR COMPANY,
BUT WE HAVE TO DO WHAT'S
BEST FOR THIS COUNTRY.
AND THAT MEANS
ALL OF US COMING TOGETHER,
BUILDING AN ECONOMY
THAT REALLY DOES WORK
FOR EVERYBODY.
SO HOW DO WE BUILD
SUCH AN ECONOMY?
WE HAVE TO DECIDE AS A NATION
THAT WE WANT MANUFACTURING,
THAT WE WANT PROSPERITY
AND THE GOOD JOBS AND INCOME
THAT COME WITH MANUFACTURING.
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS
TO ME IS FLINT, MICHIGAN,
DAYTON, OHIO,
AND BUFFALO, NEW YORK.
IF YOU DON'T REESTABLISH
THE MANUFACTURING BASE
OF THIS COUNTRY
ROUGHLY AT THE LEVEL
OF 20 TO 25% OF WORKERS,
AND THE MOST IMMEDIATE WAY
TO DO THAT IS TRADE REFORM
WITH CHINA.
THE BEST JOBS PROGRAM
IS TRADE REFORM WITH CHINA,
AND THE ARGUMENT
IS PRETTY SIMPLE.
THE GROSS DOMESTIC PRODUCT
GROWS WITH ONLY FOUR THINGS--
CONSUMPTION, INVESTMENT,
GOVERNMENT SPENDING,
AND NET EXPORTS.
AND WHEN YOU RUN
A TRADE DEFICIT,
THE SIMPLE MATH OF THAT
IS THAT'S A NEGATIVE
IN TERMS OF GROWTH.
I THINK THE NUMBER ONE THING
THAT THE UNITED STATES
HAS TO DO
IS TO MOVE TO SAY WE ARE
GOING TO BALANCE OUR TRADE.
LOOK, IF WE HAD
HAD BALANCED TRADE,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE HAD
A DECADE OF A DRAG ON GDP
THAT AMOUNTED TO ALMOST
A POINT PER YEAR,
SO OF COURSE
WE WOULD BE BETTER OFF.
NOW, PEOPLE SAY,
"HOW DO YOU DO THAT?"
I'M A YOUNG GUY
WHEN PRESIDENT KENNEDY SAID,
"WE'RE GOING TO THE MOON."
HE DIDN'T HAVE A CLUE
HOW TO GET TO THE MOON,
BUT WE SET IT
AS A NATIONAL GOAL
AND WE FIGURED OUT
HOW TO DO IT
BECAUSE WE'RE A SMART,
CREATIVE PEOPLE.
AND IF WE ARE TO TRULY
BALANCE OUR TRADE,
WE CANNOT DO IT BY BOOSTING
EXPORTS ALONE.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS,
"LET'S EXPORT MORE."
WE'RE NOW EXPORTING
MORE THAN $100 BILLION A YEAR
IN GOODS AND SERVICES
TO CHINA.
BUT IT ISN'T EXPORTS
THAT MATTER.
IT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN IMPORTS AND EXPORTS.
EXPORTS ARE GREAT,
BUT IF YOUR IMPORTS GROW MORE
RAPIDLY THAN YOUR EXPORTS,
THERE'S A DRAIN ON DEMAND
FOR WHAT AMERICANS MAKE,
WE GET MORE UNEMPLOYMENT,
AND THE ECONOMY SINKS
INTO THE KIND OF MESS WE'RE IN.
IF YOU LOOK AT AMERICA TODAY,
WE HAVE A VERY FAST-GROWING
EXPORT SECTOR,
AND PEOPLE TALK ABOUT
HOW WE'RE GOING TO COME BACK
WITH EXPORTS.
THAT'S JUST ALL SILLY.
AMERICA'S GOING TO COME BACK
FROM "IMPORT SUBSTITUTION."
WE DON'T HAVE TO TAKE
OVER THE WORLD IN EXPORTS.
WE SIMPLY NEED TO GET BACK
OUR MARKET HERE.
IN FACT AMERICAN CONSUMERS
AND CITIZENS
SEEM TO BE FAR AHEAD
OF OUR POLITICIANS
WHEN IT COMES TO UNDERSTANDING
BOTH THE DANGERS WE FACE
AND THE NEED
FOR FUNDAMENTAL CHANGE.
WE'RE A SUBSIDIARY OF CHINA
AND GETTING WORSE AND WORSE
BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING
TO OWN US PRETTY SOON.
NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE IT
BOTH WAYS.
WE EITHER WANT THE JOBS,
THE MANUFACTURING,
EVERYTHING HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES,
AND WE'RE GONNA BUY IT,
BUT YOU GO
TO THE STORE AND YOU LOOK
FOR THE CHEAPEST THING,
WHICH USUALLY COMES FROM CHINA.
I DO BUY CHINA STUFF,
BUT I PREFER TO BUY
AMERICAN THINGS.
[INTERVIEWER]
WHY?
I THINK IT'S BETTER JUST
TO SUPPORT THE ECONOMY HERE
RATHER THAN-- YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN BUY CHEAPLY IN CHINA,
BUT I THINK IT'S BETTER
FOR OUR ECONOMY IF WE BUY HERE.
WE'VE ALSO GOT TO LOOK
AT OUR PRINCIPLES, TOO.
LOOK HOW THEY'RE LIVING.
IS THAT WHAT WE WANT TO SUPPORT?
WE OPEN UP OUR MARKETS
TO EVERYBODY,
AND I THINK THAT IF THAT'S
HOW IT'S GONNA BE,
IT NEEDS TO BE
A TWO-WAY STREET,
AND I THINK POLITICALLY,
OUR SYSTEM HAS NOT SUPPORTED,
YOU KNOW, THE AMERICAN WORKER,
THE AMERICAN PRODUCT
FROM THAT STANDPOINT.
AND PERHAPS THE BIGGEST REASON
OUR POLITICIANS ARE FAILING US
IS BECAUSE THEY HAVE TRULY
FORGOTTEN
THE PROPER ROLE OF GOVERNMENT.
I USED TO DEBATE
A COLLEAGUE OF MINE,
MY COUNTERPART
FROM THE CHAMBER OF COMMERCE,
AND HE USED TO SAY TO ME,
"YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT MY JOB TO
PLAY SANTA CLAUS TO THE WORKERS
"OR TO PAINT MY COMPANY GREEN.
IT'S MY JOB TO MAKE MONEY
FOR THE SHAREHOLDERS,"
AND I AGREE WITH THAT.
THAT IS THE JOB OF CORPORATIONS,
BUT IT IS GOVERNMENT'S JOB
TO MAKE SURE THAT COMPANIES
ARE DOING THAT
WITHIN A FRAMEWORK
THAT MAKES SENSE.
I THINK THE FIELD
THAT WE'RE PLAYING ON
NOT ONLY NEEDS TO BE LEVEL,
BUT I THINK EVERYBODY
NEEDS TO BE ON ONE FIELD.
WE'RE NOT EVEN ON
THE SAME FIELD AS THE CHINESE.
WE ARE PAYING VERY GOOD WAGES.
WE ARE PROVIDING HEALTH CARE
TO OUR EMPLOYEES.
WE ARE IN A REGULATED BUSINESS
AS FAR AS WORKPLACE SAFETY
FOR OUR EMPLOYEES.
WE PAY OUR TAXES GLADLY,
AND WE CANNOT COMPETE
WITH A NON-REGULATED WORKPLACE
THAT PAYS THEIR EMPLOYEES
PENNIES
AND ARE ALLOWED TO IMPORT
THEIR GOODS
INTO THIS COUNTRY
WITH NO RESTRICTIONS.
WHAT IS THE ALTERNATIVE
FOR AMERICA?
SAY EVERYBODY-- ALL OF OUR
WORKERS SHOULD TAKE A 50%,
60% PAY CUT
AND THEN WE'LL
REALLY TAKE ON CHINA?
WE'LL BE-- WE'LL GET THEM.
OR, YOU KNOW, HAVE DIRTIER AIR
OR HAVE THE CUYAHOGA RIVER
CATCH ON FIRE AGAIN
BECAUSE THERE'S SO MUCH
POLLUTION GOING IN.
IS THAT REALLY HOW WE'RE
GOING TO COMPETE WITH CHINA?
I THINK IT'S
THE COMPLETE OPPOSITE.
I THINK WE REINVEST
BACK INTO OUR WORKERS.
I THINK WE JUMPSTART
THE MIDDLE CLASS,
AND I THINK HAVE POLICIES
IN PLACE
THAT WOULD ENCOURAGE
MANUFACTURING BACK HERE
TO PUT THOSE GOOD JOBS
IN PLACE HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
BUT EVEN IF WE ULTIMATELY SOLVE
OUR ECONOMIC PROBLEMS,
THERE WILL STILL BE VERY
DIFFICULT CHALLENGES AHEAD
IN THE U.S.-CHINA
RELATIONSHIP.
IF TENSIONS DO RISE,
WE MUST ALWAYS REMEMBER THIS--
THERE'S A REAL DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN THE CHINESE PEOPLE
AND THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT.
MOST OF THE CRITICISMS
THAT WE HAVE ARE OF
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT,
THE ACTIONS THAT THE CHINESE
GOVERNMENT HAS TAKEN
WITH RESPECT TO TRADE POLICY
AND WORKER RIGHTS REPRESSION,
AND THE CHINESE PEOPLE SUFFER
FROM A LOT OF
THOSE SAME POLICIES.
WE NEED TO UNDERSTAND
CHINA BETTER.
WE HAVE THIS SORT OF
GLOWY VIEW OF THE TRAJECTORY
OF CHINA'S HISTORY,
BUT WHAT WE HAVE SEEN,
ESPECIALLY OVER
THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS,
IS A CHINA THAT IS MOVING
IN THE WRONG DIRECTIONS
ON EVERYTHING.
AND IT'S NOT JUST
HUMAN RIGHTS.
IT'S ITS RELATIONS
WITH ITS NEIGHBORS,
ITS ECONOMY, YOU NAME IT.
THIS IS A COUNTRY
THAT IS GOING BACKWARDS
IN ALL PHASES.
I HEAR PEOPLE
REFERRING TO THE PRC
OR THE PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC.
WELL, LET'S BE HONEST.
AS SOON AS WE ACCEPT THAT
PHRASE,
WE'RE JOINING CHINA
IN THEIR REALITY DISTORTION
FIELD.
IT'S A LIE.
IT IS NOT THE PEOPLE'S,
AND IT IS NOT THE REPUBLIC.
STOP SAYING THAT.
IT'S COMMUNIST CHINA.
WE'VE GOT TO SPREAD THE WORD
THAT THERE'S DANGER OUT THERE,
AND WE NEED TO CHANGE
OUR POLICIES.
WE CAN NO LONGER AFFORD
TO TREAT A COMMUNIST
DICTATORSHIP IN CHINA
AS WE WOULD TREAT ANY
OTHER DEMOCRATIC INSTITUTION,
BECAUSE THEY HAVE TREATED US
LIKE FOOLS FOR DOING THAT,
AND THAT'S BECAUSE
WE HAVE BEEN FOOLS.
? LOOK AROUND ?
? TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE ?
? EVERY DAY MORE PEOPLE
IN THE STREET ?
? SAID I USED TO WORK
IN A FACTORY ?
? RIGHT NOW I'D WORK
FOR ANYTHING ?
? OH-OH-OH-OH ?
? IT'S NOT ME ?
? BUT MY FAMILY
I WISH TO FEED ?
? NOT MUCH ?
? WE GOT SIMPLE NEEDS ?
? TOO BAD ?
? THEY SENT OUR JOBS AWAY ?
? IN CHINA
THEY'RE NOT WORKERS,
THEY'RE JUST SLAVES ?
? PEOPLE, WAKE ?
? IT'S A WORLD
OF TRADE AND GREED ?
? AND THE CEOs GET RICHER ?
? AND OUR JOBS
ALL MOVE OFF SHORE ?
? OH-OH-OH-OH ?
? MY OLDEST SON ?
? HE GOT A COLLEGE DEGREE ?
? HE DREAMED ?
? OF RUNNING A FACTORY ?
? NOW HE'S BACK HOME ?
? JUST LIVING WITH ME ?
? AND THERE'S NO BRIGHT FUTURE
MY BOY CAN SEE ?
? SIXTEEN HOURS ?
? SEVEN DAYS A WEEK ?
? OF UNIONS ?
? AND FREEDOMS
THEY CANNOT SPEAK ?
? GOTTA RISE ?
? GET UP OFF YOUR KNEES ?
? BEFORE THEY BUY UP ?
? ALL OUR DREAMS ?
? WE GO TO THE STORE
AND SPEND OUR MONEY ?
? SEND ALL OUR
DOLLARS OVERSEAS ?
? THIS AIN'T THE LAND
OF MILK AND HONEY ?
? THIS IS THE LAND
OF TRADE AND GREED ?
? WE GO TO THE STORE
AND SPEND OUR MONEY ?
? SEND ALL OUR DOLLARS
OVERSEAS ?
? THIS AIN'T THE LAND
OF MILK AND HONEY ?
? THIS IS THE LAND ?
? OF TRADE AND GREED ?
AND THIS WHOLE NOTION
THAT WHAT'S GOOD FOR
MULTINATIONALS
IS GOOD FOR AMERICA,
THAT'S COMPLETELY WRONG.