Before man, before moon, before history,
In a world made of magic and mystery,
Gods and Titans, lightning and bone,
Fought to possess the Chronos stone.
For he who held the stone held the world,
And into darkest earth the Titans were hurled.
And Zeus, the thunder in his throne,
Zeus became the ruler of them all.
Come with me,
across the sea of time.
across the sea of time,
Where creatures never seen before,
The Gorgon and the Manticore,
The Centaur 'neath the silver tree,
Across the sea of time.
Come with me, across the sea of time.
Come with me, across the sea of time,
Where man and god meet in the dawn,
Where gods are kings and men are pawns,
And no man born is truly free,
Across the sea of time.
Zeus descended from the sky,
The lightning by his side,
Love like thunder in his heart,
To take a mortal bride.
And from their union came a son,
Half human and half god,
With twice the strength of mortal men,
To walk…
…where heroes trod.
Come with me, across the sea of time,
When men have fallen to their knees,
And all the gods ignore their pleas,
The name they call is Hercules,
Across the sea of time,
- Time.
- Hercules.
- Across the sea of time.
- Time.
- Hercules.
- Across the sea of time.
- Time.
- Hercules.
- Across the sea of time.
Hmm, must've been something he ate.
- Thank you, Hercules!
- Hooray for Hercules!
- Ha-ha-ha!
Destroyed the monster!
Huh! Thank you. Wow, that was fantastic!
Nice job with the monster.
No sweat.
Where were you, anyway?
Hey, I got here as soon as I could.
I would've jumped in, but, well, you
looked like you were doin' okay.
Thanks, buddy.
Hercules, Hercules! Do ya like fish?
Well, sure I…
And there's plenty more where that came from.
Free fish any time you want.
A lifetime supply.
Thanks, but I think this is a lifetime supply.
Come back anytime, Hercules. You're the best.
"Oh, Hercules, you're the best! How can we ever
repay you?! What can we ever…"
Here…
…have a fish.
More fools to rob!
Monsters, highwaymen. What's next? Satyrs?
Nice place, huh?
Yo, baby!
You talkin' to me?
Why don't you and your little friend
give yourselves a thrill?
Thanks, don't mind if we do.
Come on, Gabrielle.
You guys asked for it.
We've, uh, had our eyes on you for,
uh, quite some time.
I've had my eyes on you, too.
Ya have, huh?
Who wouldn't notice such handsome, distinguished
satyrs with such a large bag of gold?
Knock it off, hair-ball!
This gold, it didn't, by any chance, come from…
the purses of innocent travelers
on the road to Corinth, did it?
What if it did?
Hmm. Well, if it did, I'd just have to…
…take it back.
Hey, give me that. It's ours.
Sorry, I don't think so.
You can't just walk in here and take our gold.
You're welcome to try and stop me, goat-breath.
Bravo!
Ares.
Ah, Xena, I love watching you work.
Thanks, but the mighty God of War doesn't come
down from Mount Olympus to a dive like this just
to see the floor show.
You know me too well.
That's for sure.
Actually, there is something you can do for me.
And, as usual, my answer is "No".
It concerns your… friend, Hercules.
My "friend"? Don't you mean your brother?
Half-brother. I just thought you should know…
…he's in grave danger.
He's on his way to Thebes.
Isn't that where his mother lives?
Yes…
…but he must never get there. He's walking right
into a trap. Only you can stop him.
Why should you care what happens to Hercules?
You know what they say, blood is thicker than nectar.
I don't believe you.
This is one of your tricks.
Xena! Frankly, I'm offended.
You gods sit up there on Mount Olympus and
think you can play with us mortals like we were
toys!
Well, I'm no toy.
Ya got that?
It was… it was nice talkin' to you.
We've gotta go.
Don't you think that he might've been telling the
truth for a change?
Sorry.
Ares has tried everything to draw me back into
his world of destruction.
He's threatened me,
tempted me,
framed me for a crime I didn't commit.
So, now he's trying the sincere approach.
If Ares doesn't want Hercules to
go up to Thebes,
then it's probably the best place
for Hercules to be.
This is hot work!
What are you complaining about? I'm the horse.
I'm so hungry, I could eat that rotten fish.
Don't worry. When we're through, mother
will fix us one of her special…
What is it? What's wrong?
Zeus!
Mother! Look out!
Mother!
No!
Hercules! Calm down!
How can I calm down when Zeus has kidnapped
my mother?!
Well are you, are you sure he kidnapped her?
Are you crazy? You saw it!
Yeah, but, well,…
she didn't look like she was putting
up much of a fight.
What do you mean by that?!
Nothing! I…
look, I know how you feel about Zeus,
but, I mean,
after all, he is your father.
Don't remind me!
Sorry.
Where are you going now?
To bring her back.
You…you mean you're…you're…you're going
to…to Mount Olympus?
That's right. And don't try to stop me.
Are you kidding?! I'm comin' with ya!
Wow, Mount Olympus, the home of the gods.
How come you don't go there more often?
I mean, I know you hate that side of
your family, but,
after all, Mount Olympus,
it's gotta be fabulous.
Whoa! What the…
Oh, boys!
Geronimo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Hey, bro. Iolaus.
Hello, Aphrodite.
Wow!
Did you see that three-sixty?
Not too shabby, huh?
Yeah, it was great.
Listen, I don't really have time
to stand around discussing shell technique?
Uh, better close that thing, Iolaus. You're
tongue's getting all dusty.
Hey, Hercules, hang on.
Look, I know you're bummed about your mom.
What do you care? I mean, she's not your mother.
Look, you may think you're mad about Zeus taking
Alcmene, but you've got nothing on Hera.
How dare he bring that floozy up here?
Who does
he think he is? That…
that…
All I asked you to do…
…was stop Hercules from being there when I
went to get his mother.
A rather simple request,
I would've thought.
Yes, Father. See I asked this mortal
to help me, but I
You asked a mortal to help you?!
Who, may I ask?
Xena.
Xena? You'll use any excuse to get close
to her, won't you?
Father, you of all gods, must understand that,
well, some mortal women can just…
Enough!
I doubt that there's anything you can tell
your father about mortal women.
Leave us.
It is well for a mother to know where the
loyalties of her children lie.
I guess he told you.
Shut up, Artemis.
What is it with you and that Xena?
She brings you
nothing but trouble.
One of these days, Xena will come through for
me.
Just you wait and see.
You should live so long!
Get it? You're an immortal?
How could you do it?
How could you bring a mortal
to this sacred place, especially that mortal?
I don't see that this is any of your concern.
Where is she?
Where did you put her? In the
servants' quarters?
Some plush chamber of her
very own?
Or perhaps the trophy room?
Enough!
Remember to whom you are speaking!
I am Zeus, King of the Gods!
King of the Gods!
But for how long?
Come on, Hercules you heard her!
It's crazy to go
up there if Hera's on the warpath!
You know how
much she hates you!
Iolaus, it's very simple.
My mother's there, and I
have to get her back.
You don't have to come if
you don't want to.
True.
I could just, uh, hang out down
here with you,
keep you from getting lonely.
As if!
Be good, Iolaus. Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
Ah, that's no fun. She's your sister.
So, Aphrodite, looks like it's just you and me.
Ah, you mortals might have to put up with these
natural disasters, but I don't.
Toodles!
The Chronos stone.
Hang on! I'll get you!
Hercules! It's closing!
Gabrielle! Look out!
Thanks.
Look at them.
Nothin' like a natural disaster to
bring out the bad guys.
Come on.
I think that belongs to the nice lady.
Back off, low… lives.
Make us.
If I must.
Xena! Look out!
Hang on, kid. I'll getcha.
Gabrielle! Look out!
Get outta my way!
Take that!
Help!
Gotcha!
Good work, Iolaus.
Let me pass in peace, little man.
My quarrel is not with mortals,
but with the gods who imprisoned
me beneath the earth.
If I let you pass,
do you pledge to leave the mortal world alone,
and take your fight to Mount Olympus?
You have my word.
Go.
Who's Mr. Big?
His name is Porphyrion.
He's a Titan.
A Titan?!
Hello.
No more stealing…
…or you'll wish he had squashed
you like a bug.
Y…yes, ma'am.
Xena, look!
The ancient prophecy has come true at last.
The Titans have escaped from
their prison in Tartarus.
Do you, do you think they'll come here?
Of course, they'll come here. They want revenge.
But we will beat them, right?
I mean this prophecy,
it does say we win in the end.
The source of our power is the Chronos stone,
which we won from them many years ago
and with which we could easily defeat
them again.
But, as you can see, the Chronos stone is gone.
That evens the odds considerably.
Should be quite a battle.
A bit soon to celebrate, isn't it?
Ya haven't even
met the Titans, yet.
Hera!
Where's the Chronos stone? What have
you done with it?
Why suspect me?
Perhaps your mortal took it. You
can't trust them, you know.
What a predicament! The Titans are coming,
and no Chronos stone to protect you.
I have it! A champion of mortal blood
can defend you from the big, bad Titans.
Doesn't the prophecy say that?
You could ask your son, Hercules, to help you,
if you hadn't just kidnapped his mother.
Thank you, Hercules.
There, everything seems to be under control, here.
I'd better get going.
Thanks, bro.
I think you're losing your technique.
Hercules, I know you're mad at Zeus and all, but
you gotta help us! The Titans are coming!
I know. I met one of them.
You let him go?!
But you gotta stop 'em down here,
before they reach Mount Olympus!
Come on, be
our champion, please?
Sorry, if I fought the Titans here,
innocent people might get hurt.
Besides. I'm not sure I'm on your side.
Great.
Thanks for nothin'.
So that's it?
You're just gonna let the gods down?
They'll find their champion.
That's right. You're not the only hero on Earth.
Is there nothing that Xena can't do?
What're you doing here?
I came to laugh at you. Don't you ever learn?
Ya have to admit, she's perfect for the job.
Yeah, but, she'll never do it.
If I explain to her what's at stake…
She'll think you're lying to her like you always do.
She'll denounce the gods like she always does.
She might even kick your butt while she's
at it. Should be fun to watch.
Yeah, you're right.
Here, I'll show you how to deal with a mortal.
How many more?
Quite a few.
Word of your healing has gotten around.
Gabrielle?
Are you all right?
Of course,
No-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Gabrielle!
Sorcery!
Now, what?
We wait.
This is the hour of our rebirth!
And we shall take
our vengeance on the gods of Olympus who
imprisoned us so long ago.
We'll blow 'em away, won't we, Mnemosyne?
We'll make them burn!
Cool off, you two.
I have waited too many years, in the
bowels of the Earth, to waste time now.
What is our plan?
Simple, we will attack Mount Olympus, regain
the sacred stone of our father, Chronos,
and rule the universe!
Is this the stone you seek?
Stand back.
While I have the stone, you are in my power.
Understand? You work for me.
Don't fret. You
shall rule the universe,
under my command.
Gabrielle.
I'm so sorry.
This is the work of the gods.
It's aimed at me, not you.
If only I knew you could understand.
I'll make thinks right, Gabrielle, I promise.
Hey, calm down.
You can do it, I know you can.
Come on, Gabrielle, go for it.
I'm starting to think this wasn't such a good
idea-a-a-a-a-a!
Fly, Gabrielle, fly!
Yes! Ya did it!
Huh?! Aphrodite, why aren't you ready
for battle?
I'm sending out a calming aura to neutralize the
bad Titan vibes.
And if that doesn't work, I plan to
hide in my shell.
Shh. What's that?
Of all the tricks you've ever played on mortals this
was the lowest.
It wasn't me. She did it.
Just because I refuse to help in this plot against Hercules…
This has nothing to do with Hercules.
It's the Titans.
If you help us defeat them, I'll turn
your friend back into a human.
And next time, try asking first.
Ya hanging in there?
Yeah, but I can see why the gods aren't bothered
by pesky drop-in guests!
Whoa! Not another Earthquake!
It's the Titans.
Gabrielle!
Thanks.
You're not really welcome.
This is gonna be harder than I thought.
Oh, baby, that's what I like.
Hercules. It's about time.
Looks like the party started without me.
Unfortunately, I can't stay.
But… but…
Aphrodite!
I'm going to crush your skull like an egg.
Sorry, no time.
I never thought I'd see you help
me out of a tangle.
Looks like you're havin' a bad hair day.
Mother!
I have no fight with you.
You let me go in peace.
I return the favour.
Hercules!
Iolaus, I have to get my mother to safety.
Go ahead! I'm gonna stay and fight!
Not me. I'm outta here.
No! Let me go!
Come back, you cowards!
Run, my family, like the frightened
little animals you are.
Yes, like frightened little animals.
You have chosen the wrong side on which to
fight today.
It ain't over 'til it's over, big boy.
You mean to tell me, you didn't even lift a finger
to help?
I…I…look… I…I climbed Mount Olympus.
I…I rescued you from Zeus.
What do you want from me?
Did you ever think to ask if I wanted to be rescued?
Open up! It's me, Zeus!
Where… where are you?
Down here!
Zeus, what happened to you?
Hera.
Hey, lady!
Lemme in!
Ares?
Just watchit. Don't make me ma-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-d.
Uh, I think I'm allergic to rabbit fur.
Mo-o-o-o-o-ove!
Uh, this is so gross.
I don't even eat red meat
and now I am red meat.
What are you laughing at?!
This is all your fault!
Yeah, why didn't you pitch in up there?
Now the Titans rule the universe. Who knows
what misery they'll cause.
They couldn't do much worse than you have, now,
could they?
Is this really how people live down here?
Uh, pathetic.
Mother, would you wait?!
Oh, Iolaus! I knew you'd make it!
Yeah, huh.
What?
What? I couldn't stay. I had to get my mom.
I…Xena, I…
Forget it!
Oh, and say hello to Gabrielle.
Gabrielle?
Oh, maybe you didn't recognize her…
…thanks to your family.
Hey meet the former gods of Olympus.
Which one of you animals is Artemis?
Uh, that would be me.
Why, Mother? Why would you go with Zeus, after
the way he's treated us all these years?
I mean,
he's never been there for us, not once. I mean,
what could he possibly have to offer you?
Life.
What?
I know. I know, I should've told you.
I've been ill for
quite some time.
I didn't realize how ill until a
recent visit to the Oracle.
I didn't know what to do.
Then, one day, Zeus appeared.
He knew.
And he made me an offer which would
make up for all his years of neglect.
He would take me to Mount Olympus, where I
would become an immortal.
It was the hardest
decision I ever had to make.
To lose my life, or
risk losing you from my life.
Why didn't you tell me?
I knew you'd try to stop me.
You've always hated
your father so.
As long as you're happy.
What?
What do you mean, you can't change her back?
If I could change her, do you think I'd stay
a bunny rabbit?
Not that I don't, uh, sympathize, believe me, but,
hey, these things happen
Ooh, what do birds your
size eat, anyway?
Oh, I was afraid of that.
It's the Chronos stone.
As long as the Titans
control Mount Olympus, they have the stone, and
we have no powers.
Yeah, we're stuck down here…
…while Hera lives it up on Mount
Olympus with the Titans.
We're the Titans,
we're the best.
We're bigger and we're smarter than the rest.
And after all the years we were repressed,
We're the Titans, we're the best.
We romped on them, we stomped on them,
We blew them to their knees.
Can we boast?
We drowned them and we pounded them,
And squashed them all like fleas.
Now they're toast.
We're the Titans, we are strong.
We knew that we could beat them all along.
They thought that they could win,
but they were wrong, wrong, wrong.
We're the Titans, we are strong.
Oh, yeah.
We're the Titans, we're the worst.
We're meaner and we're so much more perversed.
Zeus had all the luck, but now is cursed,
'Cause we're the Titans, we're the worst
We trounced them and we bounced them,
And we pushed them off the edge into the void.
What's a void?
And once the Chronos stone is truly mine…
It's mine.
The world will be destroyed.
I'm getting annoyed.
We're the Titans, we rule the day.
We'll make the gods and little humans pay.
We'll bury them beneath our feet of clay.
We're the Titans, we're okay.
Quiet!
I can't even hear myself gloat.
Just look at
this place! It's a disaster!
I had forgotten just how
stupid you Titans were.
You belong down in Tartarus!
Sorry.
To think I have an eternity of this to look forward to.
Is that old hag going to boss us around forever?
No, not forever. In fact, not much longer.
Gabrielle,…
…this is terrible. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
This is a fine mess we're in.
I went and let the bad guys win.
Look what they did to you.
I thought I was a warrior.
Still, I failed somehow.
So tell me, what do I do now?
I thought if I did my best,
I'd never make mistakes.
I'd always win the battle,
no matter what it takes.
I'd keep my friends from danger.
That's my sacred vow.
So tell me, what do I do now?
Hear me, silver sister moon, shinin' in the blue,
Had I wings to fly away, I would fly to you.
But that's not what warriors do.
Maybe there's more to bein' human,
than actin' brave and strong.
Maybe it's list'ning' to your heart,
and knowin' when you're wrong.
It's keepin' the faith and trustin'
you'll come through, somehow.
And maybe, that's what I'll do now.
I believe we'll come through, me and you.
That's what we'll do… now.
Oh, hi.
So, you're, talking to me, now?
I had no right to blame you for what's happened
to Gabrielle. If I hadn't been so…
We've both made some mistakes, lately.
The
question is,…
what're we gonna do about it, now?
This is all Hercules' fault.
My Dear, you know as well as I, that Hera would
never have revived the Titans if you hadn't brought
me to Mount Olympus.
Well, uh…
And if we had been frank with our son,
he might
have been there at your side when you needed him.
She's right, you know? He's always been there
for me, before.
Yeah, for me, too.
So, in other words, I'm to blame.
No, not really,
but it was good of you to say it.
Hey, why is everyone looking so gloomy?
You think
we're gonna take this lying down?
I would, if I could figure out how to get back up.
Xena and I were talking.
The thought of my mother
spending the rest of her life,
surrounded by a
bunch of whining farm animals who think they
should be ruling the universe…
And Gabrielle staying the way she is.
These aren't situations we're prepared just
to sit back and accept.
So, we've decided…
…to attack Mount Olympus.
Why not? The Titans took it from you. We'll just
go up there and take it back from them.
You've forgotten one thing.
The Chronos stone. As long as Hera and the
Titans control it, we have no powers.
Well, I don't mean to be insulting, but,
you didn't do so hot when you had powers, did you?
Son, I mean it. If you go back to Mount Olympus,
there's a good chance you won't come down alive.
It's a chance I'm willing to take…father.
Disgusting!
And you want to rule over all creation? Hah.
Well,
coming back to play, are we? Let's make
things a bit more interesting this time…
and teach
these buffoons a lesson.
Hey! I feel pain!
I tingle! Strange! Hold it! Stop it!
No!
Now, Hercules and his little friends won't stand
a chance.
Give me… the stone!
Get away, you lummox!
Go defend your new empire!
We have the power, now!
What are you doing?!
Is it just me, or have these guys gotten even uglier?
Well, one thing's for sure, they
haven't gotten any nicer.
You know? This could go on forever.
Got any bright ideas?
Now that you mention it, I do have a thought.
Keep them busy!
Throw them over the side!
It's no good. He draws his power from the earth,
and every time he goes down, he gets stronger.
Yeah. What can we do?
I've got an idea. Come on.
You should've quit when you were ahead, little man.
Grab him!
I… never… quit!
Now! Drop him!
Hercules!
Climb, Gabrielle, climb! Back to Olympus! Hurry!
Hey, nice job with that monster.
You didn't do so badly yourself.
Gabrielle, can you ever forgive me?
There's nothin' to forgive. I knew you'd come
through for me.
I sort of enjoyed the flying part.
It was fun while it lasted.
He's…he's here.
I will miss you every day.
Just remember,…
…I'll be watching over you.
Son,…
…you know you're always welcome at
my, uh…
Yeah, I know.
She'll be okay.
He does care for her.
So, where are you headed?
Corinth. I still have a bag of gold to return.
Maybe, we could walk along with you for a while.
Sure.
That'd be great.
And along the way, you can teach me that great
kick you did up there against Porphyrion.
Sure, if you'll teach me how to flip a Titan.
I would love to, but it's a family secret.
GSsub
http://xena4gabrielle.livejournal.com/