You're sure about this?
(WHISPERING)
Why are you guys in my school?
Are we supposed to
have Scouts now?
Mikey, we just
need to chat, okay?
Usually, we'd talk to you like
men should talk to a little boy,
but, today, we're gonna
talk like we're all men.
Let's all make
a scouting promise.
No matter what
we talk about in here,
nobody's gonna cry,
okay? Agree?
Why would we cry?
Sometimes you don't see a thing
coming until it hits ya.
It goes in your ears,
it goes into your heart and
you can feel it hurting
all the way down.
Mikey, you can feel it
hurting all the way down to
your little butt crack,
you feel it,
it's like a punch
to your insides, man.
And you're not expecting this.
It's like a sucker punch.
(YELLS)
Mikey, you know, we all have
people that we can depend on.
Ivan's got me,
and Eddie's got Ivan and,
hey, all three of us,
well, we've got you.
And I've got my dad.
RANDY: Oh, boy.
Look, okay, you know, my dad's
been sick for a long time,
and he's not gonna be around
forever, I know this.
And maybe you haven't had time
to think about this, but,
you know, our dads...
Your dad loves you, man.
No matter what.
And no matter
where he might be.
RANDY: Even
if he goes away.
Goes away forever.
Forever?
Is he okay?
What? Wait...
Is he dead?
This is the sucker punch
that I was talking about.
Mikey... I'm not gonna
cry, Mr. Stevens.
Um...
Do you want a cigarette?
No.
(EXHALING)
RANDY: You made the right
choice by becoming a Boy Scout.
Even without a dad, we're always
going to be here for you.
That is in our blood.
It's part of our history.
Look at the great men who
came before us. It's FDR.
What's up, Neil Armstrong?
Hey, look, Hank Aaron.
Bill Gates, David Bowie,
Donald Rumsfeld...
This brave and honorable
group of men,
none of them are losers, and
all of them started as Scouts.
My father founded one of the greatest
scouting troops in the country.
He raised my brother and me
by the pages of
the Boy Scout Handbook,
and I followed in every one
of my dad's footsteps.
But my brother hated the woods
and mocked our uniforms
and camping trips.
He quit, and the other boys
were quick to follow,
deserting our troop.
The Scouts
became a joke to them.
Like right now,
I'm losing my dad, too.
And when he's gone, it'll be
up to me to step forward,
become the leader of the
next generation of Scouts
and guide our troop down
those paths to greatness.
And two...
We're gonna do eight more.
We're gonna go all the way.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNORING)
(IVAN GROANING)
It's fine.
Just come and put
your hand like this,
and push it hard.
No.
Look. The blood
that's going to his feet
is coming from here,
that's where you gotta stop
the blood flow, man.
Yeah. Tibbits, go. It's just
his femoral artery. Do it.
Come on, Tibbits.
(GROANS)
Go ahead, Tibbits.
I don't want to. It's
sweaty and gross in there.
So, Tibbits, you're gonna
let him bleed to death?
No, Tibbits.
Don't let me die.
RANDY: With the amount
of blood he has lost,
he's looking at
an amputation or death,
unless you jump to the job
and save his life.
(LAUGHING)
I wouldn't touch that.
That's how you get diarrhea.
Elevate the leg, all right?
And you tie
the tourniquet here.
You can save a leg and a life.
(GIGGLING)
Hey, I know this looks
creepy and weird, okay?
And a lot of people die because
somebody else doesn't want to
look creepy and weird, right?
You gotta get past that.
All right.
Look, Tibbits,
we're gonna work on this
this weekend.
Any questions?
(GRUNTING)
We've been installing these ATMs
all over the freaking place.
And the secret's pretty simple.
Just get people
to want to use 'em.
Like this guy right here.
One of our first jobs.
Simple enough.
Use this ATM, get a gumball.
Kids come by, want gum,
mom needs money,
and boo-yah!
We get a $4.75 fee.
Wait, that's genius.
$4.75?
Yeah, and we've been
installing them everywhere,
daycare centers, hospitals...
I just made a deal with
a funeral home in Tulsa.
Man, I'm interested.
Whoa! Whoa!
Dwande.
I said no dogs in the house.
(CHUCKLING)
We're gonna get you
real-deal friends. Humans.
Right, Janine?
Oh, is this your wife?
Janine, this is Drew Pritchard.
We are talking to him about
putting some ATM machines
in his dentist office in...
And who is this little guy?
JANINE: This is Dwande,
our son.
Oh, are you having
a birthday party?
It's not my birthday.
It's an adoption day party.
He's one.
One what?
One year in the U-S of A.
Well, he's 10, actually.
DREW: (LAUGHING) Okay.
He's from Africa, man!
Whoa, that's the real deal.
Africa?
Janine was in the...
What's that called, honey?
Peace Corps.
KIRK: She was all "Save
the whales" in college.
I'm sitting there,
adoption papers in hand,
I'm flying to a city with no
vowels, and I'm thinking...
What you're thinking is,
"If he can play basketball,
"this is golden."
(MEN LAUGHING)
(CLEARING THROAT)
But, seriously,
first time I saw
this little guy
was a pretty special moment.
As a special surprise
for tonight's meeting
and for the campout
this weekend,
yours truly managed to
procure the founder
and Scoutmaster of
this very troop,
my father,
Scoutmaster Stuart Stevens!
(APPLAUSE)
Where's your uniform, Kent?
Mommy says I don't have to
wear that bullshit outfit
if I don't want to.
Okay. First off,
it's not bullshit,
and secondly,
you have to wear it if you're
gonna go camping this weekend.
Screw camping!
Especially in that crap-ass
church parking lot.
Why are you a Scout, Kent?
For my resume.
You got a resume?
Yes. Do you?
I can't go this weekend either.
What? Tibbits, no.
This is for your
Lifesaving badge advancement.
My mom said I should
go to a sleepover instead.
Sorry, Randy.
I'm not going either.
Gary!
Prior obligations.
Dude, you're eight years old!
What kind of obligations
you got?
Slumber party.
Guys, camping is
a slumber party!
Are you still gonna do
magic tricks tonight?
No. No. Dismissed.
TIBBITS: Wait. We can
go home early?
Yes! Go! All right?
Troop dismissed!
(SLAMMING)
All right, Randy,
take a breath.
This is ridiculous.
I know that camping in the
parking lot is lame, okay,
I know that,
but these moms! It's...
They won't let the kids more
than five miles from the house.
Gary's mom insists he has
at least three bars of
cell phone service
and access to a flush toilet.
You know, when Stuart started
this troop, he had 90 Scouts.
What about the little
African immigrant?
Yeah, what about your nephew?
Why doesn't he come?
My brother's not into it.
Have you showed them
the recruitment video?
I don't want to
show them that video.
Randy, first
you sell the kids on this,
then you get the kids to sell the dads.
It's called up-selling.
Double teaming.
EDDIE: You gotta think
like a CEO, man.
We shouldn't have to
show them this video.
They should wanna do it!
Hey, they're kids, man.
You gotta sell them on stuff.
That's how it works. You gotta do
the yickety-yickety-yickety, man.
Or otherwise, I'm gonna
tell you something, Randy,
we might as well just go ahead
and do something else. Okay?
We are taking
my father camping.
Randy. Randy, chill,
all right?
Just take a break, right?
Re-evaluate, man.
We're going camping.
We are not abandoning you.
We're going if it's just us
and him in the parking lot!
Right. Right. Right.
So you tell me,
without the boys,
how is that scouting, man?
(TV BLARING)
KIRK: Ah, you've gotta be
kidding me, man!
Those effects are so cheap.
GENTRY: Cheap!
So obviously fake.
Totally fake.
KIRK: Every time you see a
guy on fire in one of these,
he's got his arms out like that...
(LAUGHING)
Totally fake! No one would do that!
It looks real to me.
Please, Janine,
shut your hole, all right?
You weren't even invited.
What do you mean?
(DOORBELL RINGING)
That was my bedroom before...
Would you get the door, Janine?
JANINE: Pretending
you're not here.
I would be rolling around on the
ground trying to save my ass.
You know what I'm saying?
I know exactly
what you're saying.
But maybe this was before
computer effects were invented.
Hey, Moses,
you need to knock that
computer crap off, all right?
We're not
talking about computers!
We're talking about a real
man with real fire here.
God, focus up already!
Oh!
Oh, no! Fuck me, I missed it.
What happened?
I missed it!
It's outta here.
Oh, shit!
Fuckin' Moses fucked me up!
HARTNETT: I brought a few more of 'em.
I hope you don't mind.
JANINE:
Oh, no, great.
They were all supposed to
go camping this weekend,
I talked their mothers
into this.
It's a much safer choice.
And such a good cause.
Uh, good cause?
Well, finding, you know, friends
for your new little boy.
Real American friends.
Hey, Leonard,
say hello to Ruanday.
Dwande.
Dwande!
Oh, for heaven's sake,
Leonard, shake his hand.
You don't even know
anybody from Africa!
Hey, what's going on
in here, young warriors?
You ready to have some fun?
BOYS: Yeah!
Let me take these TVs.
Everybody in there.
Take the TVs in there.
All right.
Come on, Dwande.
(LAUGHING)
This is a really big
step for Leonard.
He's never done
anything like this.
Oh, he's never been
to a sleepover?
No. Honestly,
I can't imagine
having my eyes off him
even for one night,
it just makes me nervous.
Oh! Please remember
to have him
use his inhaler before bed.
Got it.
Yeah. I just want him
to be tougher, you know?
I don't know why he's not latching
on to all those guy stuff.
Hmm. Well, listen,
they're perfectly safe here.
That gentleman is
Kirk's chief of security,
so, really, there's
nothing to worry about.
(SHOUTING) Fuck yeah!
Smackdown is on, shitheads!
(CHEERING)
All right, listen up, kids.
Tonight, very special night,
we've done it all for you.
Four hours to hook up
a dozen TVs to watch.
KIRK: That's right.
"HD" stands for high-def.
We also upgraded to
the triple diamond package.
That means we have
over 2,500 channels.
Yeah!
And we got $800 worth
of firepower here
going up
after the game tomorrow!
What? No way!
That's amazing!
By the way, guys,
illegal gunpowder.
KIRK: Straight from China.
Oh, check it out! Check it out!
Big game. All right,
I got, like, $2,000 on this.
What?
What the hell is this?
Dwande!
Dwande, buddy, no.
This is live TV, man.
Ah, Dwande! Do something!
Change it, man!
(MOANING)
(SHRIEKING)
(BOYS CHEERING)
Yes!
(LAUGHS)
MOSES: Naked lady!
Look at those bazongas!
Oh! What?
Come on, man!
No, no, no, no! Look here, kids.
It's a hit!
Put it back!
Okay! All right.
Cheer, fellows!
God. Did you
see that girl?
She was getting
fucking plowed... What?
(CROWD CHEERING ON TV)
Hey, Dwande!
Listen, I'm hanging on
by my fingernails here,
so let's go tell your dad about
this camping trip we're going on.
He's gonna love it. He might freak
out, but let's go tell him.
Okay, this is for you,
and now let's take a look.
Not a lot of places left
around here to go camping.
Everything here's paved over,
and the point is to be away from all
this, so there's no much choice,
unless we wanna go
all the way out here.
This place is restricted.
You know why?
'Cause it's awesome.
That's where my dad used to
take us when we were kids.
That is where we are gonna go.
ALL: Shakes! Shakes!
Shakes! Shakes!
Hey, Janine,
this party's awesome.
Thanks.
And your house
is just beautiful.
Janine! These kids need
some chocolate lubrication!
Kirk's the luckiest man
in the world.
(WHIRRING)
(POWER SURGE)
GENTRY: God damn it!
Come on, Janine,
you put the blender on the same
line as our TVs, for Christ's sake.
Nobody panic!
(BOYS SCREAMING)
(BOYS PANTING IN RELIEF)
This is the sleepover?
Really?
This is what you gave up
the camping trip for?
They got shakes,
Mr. Stevens.
Randy, out.
And, Dwande,
get out of that stupid costume.
Hey, you know,
hey, these are my Scouts.
And that is not your son.
All right, now. Come on,
Randy, that's enough.
Come on, Dwande. Why don't you
hang out with Kent in the kitchen?
GENTRY: Randy, Randy, Randy.
Why don't you and I take a little
walk outside together, huh?
Why don't we all
go outside together
on the camping trip
that we all agreed to?
These kids are not gonna
give up skybox seats to go
prancing through the woods
with you.
(WHISPERING) We got skyboxes?
You're treating them like a bunch
of bankers at a country club.
Fucking A right we are!
I will treat my son
how I wanna treat him.
But he's not gonna
go build fires
and tie knots with you
in the woods!
He is from Africa, brah!
Yeah. He's had enough
of that shit.
Oh, well, take a bow,
because you've set Dwande
down the path of
"Turn him into
a douche bag like you!"
BOYS: Oh!
(CHANTING)
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Can we please not do this
in front of the boys?
Shh! Men are talking.
I will bare-hand
neuter you!
GENTRY: Yeah!
Let's neuter him, Kirk.
(GROANING)
Kirk, be careful, your angina!
Oh. Hey... Kirk... What's an angina?
(BOYS LAUGHING)
Kirk! Kirk, what the hell?
You need some help?
BOYS: (CHANTING) Angina!
We can all take 'em
camping together.
Randy, keep your hands
where I can see 'em!
Keep your hands
You want me to take him out
or take him down?
Talk to me, Goose.
What do you want me to do?
I don't understand.
Fuck it, it's my call.
I'm taking him out.
Fuck you!
BOYS: Take him out!
Take him out!
(PHONE RINGING)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPING)
ON MACHINE: Randy Stevens. Regional
President Chuck Schwatzer here
from the Boy Scout
office downtown.
Hey, I'm gonna need those
camping trip permission slips
from your boys ASAP, or you're
not gonna be able to go.
I mean, what,
you got three kids
and you can't get me
some slips?
What happened? Did they all quit?
(CHUCKLES)
I'd love to give you the
go ahead on this weekend,
'cause I know you've been
looking forward to this one,
but you know the rules.
No slipsies, no tripsies.
Right on, brother man. Gimme a call
at the office and let me know.
RANDY: I'm out of ideas.
(SIGHS)
# If you're sitting around
with nothing to do
# Adventure is waiting for you
# Fighting dragons
with all of your might
# And in the morning,
we can go for a hike
# Boy Scouts! #
It's not like that.
Randy makes us
sleep in the park
next to a hobo toilet.
This is bullshit.
Tibbits.
Not this time, man.
No hobo toilets.
No parking lots.
I'm talking the deep woods, the
real outdoors, like Scouts.
Okay?
Without your moms around
treating you
like little babies,
and your dads
bringing you milkshakes.
Outside?
Yes, Leonard, outside.
But what about our skyboxes?
Kent, who cares about
the skyboxes?
Those are always
gonna be there.
The stuff
I'm taking you to see,
the boulders
the size of houses,
and the waterfalls,
and the wildlife,
I mean, that stuff might not
actually be here forever.
And at night there's gonna be a
bonfire, huge bonfire party.
Camping is for ugly women.
It's stupid.
Gary, take this,
pass it around, let everyone see it, okay?
(EXCLAIMS)
Wow!
Look, guys, this is Dwande's
weekend, all right?
What would you
rather do? Huh?
Yeah.
EDDIE: Hey, I'm not smokin' in the house.
I'm talking to you.
You said no smoking
in the house,
I'm not smokin' in the house.
Jesus Christ! Randy.
Guys, why aren't you
in your uniforms, man?
Randy, no, no, no,
right here, right now,
get the fuck off my property.
All right?
We are staying home.
What?
Let me tell you somethin', motherfucker.
We got in a fight
with our wives,
all right? Period.
No, no, no, no. Camping with you
ain't worth getting yelled at.
Randy, with all due
respect, man.
I know we said
we's goin' with you,
but if it's cool with you, man,
and even if it's fuckin' not,
just get the fuck outta here, we
call this whole thing off, man.
Eddie, I wanna
show you something.
I wanna show you something.
(BOYS SINGING)
(HONKING)
# I was walking down the street
# And I saw a bunch of girls
# I asked them for their numbers and
they gave me their numbers... #
Damn!
The video, it worked?
We got a troop again.
(BOYS CONTINUE SINGING)
What's up, Pops?
(HONKING)
Oh, but wait a minute.
You guys want to stay here
and get yelled at
by your wives, so...
Fuck that. We go. We are in!
Welcome aboard, guys.
Good morning, Janine.
Did you get
a good night's sleep?
Hi.
Where are the other boys?
Oh. They all went camping.
Hey, Kirk!
Hey. You wanna
do some Pilates?
Kirk!
(ALL YELLING)
Hey, shut the fuck up!
Everybody, dig in this box,
put yourselves together
a uniform, put it together.
We don't have much,
but make it work!
Second, anything that is
electronic goes in here,
not into the woods. Come on, give
it up, give it up, give it up.
I know you guys got cell phones.
Let's go, let's go.
Fast, fast, move your ass.
Now, who has been
camping before?
I have.
Great.
Okay. Pretty good. How many
of you can peel a potato?
Nobody can peel
a potato. Okay.
Who here can start a fire?
Hey! Dwande! Nice.
All right, tell me what? Who knows
how to kill and skin a deer?
(BOYS EXCLAIMING IN SURPRISE)
Really?
Randy, let's get to the woods, we
got Daniel Boone up front there.
Let's go get
the camping started!
(ALL YELLING)
Randy!
You son of a bitch!
Where are you,
you son of a bitch!
KIRK: He's not here!
Look, you're not helping us
by destroying everything.
Fuck you, Randy!
All right, maybe
we're overreacting?
The kid said he took them, right?
What's your name?
BOTH: Kent.
Kent said that
he took all of 'em!
Oh, yes, he did.
Ahhh! I'm gonna
murder him dead.
Let's murder the bastard!
What am I gonna
tell their parents?
Whoa! You're not gonna
tell them dick!
What about the police?
Maybe we could...
Hey, hold on! Don't say anything
to the police, all right?
Do not ruin this
like you ruined prom!
They're gonna be
on us for this.
It happened in our house.
It was our fault.
I am going to find them, but
nobody else needs to be involved.
Jesus Christ, Kirk,
we lost their children.
Will you calm down!
Yeah, calm down, Janine!
KENT: Calm down, Janine!
I'm gonna find him, I promise, but
just help me find some clues.
(LOUD CRASHING)
Gentry, anything?
Nothin' but a fish tank!
I'll be right up.
Now, clues are easy to find
if an idiot is leaving them,
so see what you can dig up.
GENTRY: Kirk,
help me out up here!
Tear his toilet off the wall!
He doesn't even have cable.
Randy, I don't think they
want us to camp in there.
Oh, yeah?
Well, today
it's not up to them.
Mr. Stevens,
can we pee out here?
Yeah. Guys! Nature is
your house, okay?
Nature is your toilet.
Pee anywhere you want.
Everybody, pee anywhere.
EDDIE: All right, let me get this straight, man.
So, we're gonna trespass?
That's the plan?
Did you see his face?
Do you know how long it's
been since I've had this?
Eddie. It's the cops! It's the
nature police! Hey, guys.
I cannot get busted, okay?
What is the matter with you?
Jesus Christ, dude! This is
way beyond Scout protocol.
Good morning!
Are you cleaning that up?
Clean what up?
If I came to your house
with 10 boys and
pissed on your carpet,
you'd want me to clean up,
wouldn't you?
Well, what do you expect us to do?
Have 'em whiz in a bucket?
There's restrooms
a half mile up.
You couldn't wait though,
could you?
Well, peeing in the woods,
that's not the...
Nobody pees here!
Do you understand me?
This is State property.
If you wanna be here,
you be in a public area.
We have restrooms, showers.
We have pools...
You know what? No, thank you.
We're Scouts,
so we will take
our business elsewhere.
Business?
Is that what that is?
Is that a business?
Hey! This park is not your
goddamned toilet bowl.
If it don't look like a
urinal, don't piss on it!
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
Let's be
a little bit civilized.
(RINGING)
ON MACHINE: Randy,
Chuck Schwatzer again.
I pray to Christ that you are
not on an unauthorized campout.
Randy, that would be
kidnapping.
That is some serious trouble
with the national org there.
Call me.
GENTRY: Kirk, let's check
the kitchen, too, man.
Let's see if there are some snacks.
KIRK: Janine!
What'd you get?
Find anything?
What, you think I couldn't
find you cocksuckers?
Who the fuck are you?
Get the fuck outta here!
Hey, Mikey!
We're unarmed!
Mikey! Which one of these
assholes is your Scoutmaster?
Which one told you I was dead?
Which one is it, Mikey?
I'm sorry, man. I hope
you can forgive me,
but yesterday I'm at the
hospital
gettin' a motherfucking
(WHISPERS) colonoscopy.
I don't know if you ever
had one, but it ain't fun.
So I'm tryin' to come home
and forget about this assault.
You know, relax
with my kids, chill out.
So I'm expecting my kids to
meet me at the door,
we'd have a little dinner, but
instead of kisses and hugs,
I get shot in the face
with a fucking BB gun!
(KIDS SCREAMING)
In my groin, my knee caps.
By my own son!
I don't know
what the fuck is goin' on.
Turns out that Mikey gets a visit
from his Scoutmasters at school,
they are armed
with a newspaper.
And these dipshits
read my cousin's obituary
and tell Mikey
I'm fuckin' dead!
Mikey goes home,
tells his sisters the news,
they go nuts, boom!
They deduce that their daddy
must be a goddamn ghost.
(SCREAMING)
What are you kids doing?
Try backpedaling your way out of
that with a five and a six-year-old.
You'd be up all night.
I was.
And they still don't get it.
(SCREAMING)
Sounds like we got
the same ass-kicking agenda.
You know what? They sound like
some real shitty fuckers, man.
That is our hunch,
shitty fuckers!
That's not a hunch,
that's the truth.
And we're gonna hunt 'em down.
We just need to know
where to start.
What about this, Kirk?
(CHUCKLES)
Please. Janine...
Good eye, Janine.
This might be what we need.
I think it's exactly
what you need.
Yeah, but do you know
where they're at?
Yeah, how do you know?
Well, do you see
the green spot?
With the big circle around it?
KIRK: Oh, yeah.
GENTRY: No!
Yeah. That's probably
where he took 'em.
That's out in the woods.
He said it was
a real-deal adventure.
Jesus!
Hey, you wanna come with us?
You fuckin' right,
I wanna come with you,
but I got a problem. I need
somebody to watch my kids.
That's not a problem.
That's what Janine's for.
It takes a village, Janine.
Oh, yeah. Sure. Why not?
And you don't have to worry.
They have a black son, too.
EDDIE: Who brought a garden hose?
Randy, what...
Hey! Look what I found!
A raccoon!
Should we bless him?
Smash its head!
(KIDS YELLING)
SHANE:
Slay the demon beast!
Hey, hey, guys!
Come on! Cut it out!
RANDY: Hey, hey, guys.
That's not a demon!
(YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Whoa!
Bring it down.
EDDIE:
Let's bury this fucker.
Poor little raccoon.
Gary, don't touch it.
All right, guys,
scouting is a complex
woman, all right?
There's many sides to her,
and is it our job to
control, conquer, and slay her?
Now, sometimes, you know,
she's a rapacious witch.
Other times, a tireless lover.
(HONKING)
(KIDS LAUGH)
So, okay.
Thank you, Dad.
Does anyone know where
the word "Scout" comes from?
It's a French word and
it means "to listen."
In America, that means
"Shut the fuck up," okay?
Thank you, Eddie, thank you.
So, we are each
gonna take this horn,
we're each gonna
give it a blast,
and we're gonna pass it around
and we are going to
apologize to this raccoon,
and to nature, and we're
gonna pledge it our respect.
Go ahead, Leachman,
give it a honk.
Squeeze that sucker!
(HONKS)
Nice. Pass it over.
This is the sound
and the pledge of respect.
(HONKS) Nice.
Responsibility.
Readiness.
(HONKS)
Wow! Nice.
Gratitude.
(HONKS) Whoa!
And finally, Dwande,
compassion.
(HONKS)
Very good.
Now, from this point on,
all of you are dead.
You're all dead little boys. And
when you return from this trip,
you'll return resuscitated
and resurrected as men.
And this man is gonna be the one
that breathes new life into you,
and is gonna kiss goodbye the little
corpses that you leave behind,
and he's gonna be proud
to shake the hands of the
men who hike in your stead.
Jump to the job.
Everyone, say it!
BOYS: Jump to the job!
Nice. All right. Now, are
we gonna camp here tonight?
No.
What?
We've still got five miles
until we get to the...
Five miles?
We're not... We're
not even in the woods yet.
What the fuck is this?
All right?
Eddie. Gary!
Yes, sir?
You wanna say a few words?
Yes.
Please bow your heads.
And hold hands.
Bless us, O Lord,
and these thy gifts...
Gary, that's
a food prayer, okay?
Eddie...
...which we are about to
receive from Jesus Christ,
- (ENGINE RUMBLING)
- Who watches us from heaven above,
and with pure love,
from our hearts
to yours, through Christ.
Amen.
Naked lady!
(BOYS EXCLAIMING)
(HORN HONKING)
Dwande, come on!
She's got titties!
BOY: Whoa!
SHANE: See those?
Randy, did you see that?
BOY: Guys, come on!
Hey, slow it down a little bit!
BOY: Come on, let's go!
But enjoy!
(LAUGHING)
Hey, Randy, there's
a naked lady, man!
Yo, Randy, there's
a naked lady over here,
and you're mourning
a fucking raccoon, dude.
GENTRY: You don't make
as much money as we make.
And don't get to kill people.
The cold steel in my hand,
(LAUGHS)
blood, uh, just
pumping in my veins.
(GENTRY GRUNTS)
This is some bullshit!
I'm not gonna scare
anybody with this!
Oh, please. Ninety-nine percent
of police work is intimidation.
This is a starter pistol, for Christ's sake.
It shoots blanks.
It's basically just
a noisemaker.
Randy's gonna shit yellow
when he sees you two.
I'm gonna kick
a crack in his ass
like the Liberty Bell,
ring him for recess!
(LAUGHS)
Ring-a-ding-ding.
My boys are gonna have a sweet
ass to kick when we get there.
(HORN HONKING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
I love the ATM business, but
this is what I really live for.
Child kidnapping's no joke.
When we catch Randy, I'm gonna tear
one arm off and shove it up his ass,
I'm gonna tear the other arm off
and shove it down his throat,
so he can shake hands
in his stomach.
Now, you are the two motherfuckers
that got the ATMs everywhere, right?
Yeah.
KIRK: Yeah.
I like that. I just got
a couple at my church.
Oh. Amen.
GENTRY: No offense.
Fuck church.
Randy's goin' to hell.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
That's some unnecessary
shit you just said.
BOYS: Tits! Buns!
Tits! Buns! Tits! Buns!
Tits! Buns!
TIBBITS: Did you think
she was a virgin?
LEONARD: Hey, guys,
what's a virgin exactly?
Gary's a virgin.
GARY: Bullcrap I am!
MOSES: Would your uncle ever
leave us out here on our own?
Shh. Shh.
Wait, guys.
Isn't this where we started?
LEACHMAN: Did you hear that?
Oh, my God!
LEONARD: Who is that?
Who is that?
Stuart?
TIBBITS: Oh, my God.
I don't think he's moving.
What are you doing?
Dwande, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
GARY: Leave the dead in peace.
TIBBITS: Dwande, don't be
messin' with dead stuff.
Is he really dead?
TIBBITS: Dude, come back!
Are you crazy?
(GRUNTING)
(BOYS SCREAMING)
Dwande, no!
BOY: Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
Get back into formation!
Give me that.
EDDIE: This is an exercise.
BOY: What?
Tibbits, jump to the job!
What?
There's a guy dying in the
woods, now what do we do?
There's a guy bleeding to
death on the forest floor.
What do you do?
Stop the blood?
Stop the bleeding.
Yeah, okay. Now, think, think.
What else?
Is he in shock?
Is he breathing?
There. Yeah.
Okay. Perfect.
You didn't do
any of that stuff!
Why didn't you do any of that?
EDDIE: You okay, Stuart?
I thought he was dead.
I thought he was dead, too.
You thought he was dead? Well, he's gonna
be dead if you guys just sit around
talking, not doing anything.
But it's scary!
But what part
of lifesaving isn't scary?
I didn't think
it was lifesaving.
I thought it was murder.
Murder? Eddie?
Yeah?
Eddie, help me out.
Yeah, but, Randy,
the kids are right, man.
I mean, he looked
like he was dead.
Like he was dead...
(SIGHS) Okay.
Look, all right, Tibbits,
I'm sorry, man.
It was a simulation for
your Lifesaving badge.
It was supposed to be like a
hiking accident, you know?
Stuart can't hike.
Yeah, man, you know what? Maybe we should
have stuck with the broken leg exercise.
Oh. Okay. Yes.
All right. But, hey,
the next time this happens,
what are you gonna do?
Jump to the job.
I'm sorry. What?
- Jump to the job.
Yes! Okay, guys,
he's right!
Gonna jump to
the job, everybody.
All right.
(PHONE RINGING)
JANINE: Hello?
LINDA: Oh. Hi, Janine.
Linda! Hi!
Everybody okay?
Yes, the boys are still here.
They're having a ball!
So we'll just swing by...
Um, Dwande would love it if Leonard
could stay for one more night,
if that's...
Hold on a second.
David!
Sure.
Uh, the mom wants to know if
Leonard could stay another...
David, can you come?
Do not touch me, Kent.
Hi, Janine.
Hi.
I'll be there before 9:00.
Yes. Tomorrow morning
before 9:00 a.m. Right.
Yeah. Before church.
Before church. Got it.
Okay.
Will do.
Have fun.
Thanks so much, Linda. Bye-bye.
All right.
We need to have a discussion
about boundaries.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
KIRK: The game is on
right now, honey.
And paid to have Dwande's
name on the Jumbotron,
but nobody's gonna
see the goddamned thing.
Kirk!
These women are going to be on
our doorstep tomorrow morning,
and if their kids aren't here,
the police are going
to have to be called.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No police, Janine.
Now, we can handle this ourselves
without the cops blaming us.
Just buy me some time.
I'm trying, but I'm
running out of ideas.
I told them we're doing a
goddamned Bible study tonight.
That's perfect! Goddamn,
that's why I love you!
Kirk, just get Dwande
home safe, okay?
And please just go easy on Randy until
we make sure we have all the facts.
Go easy?
Janine, he...
(BOTTLE POPS)
What was that?
Uh, look, just do whatever
it takes, all right?
I just wish I was at home and you
were doing that thing we saw
in that rap video where you...
Okay, not now, Kirk.
You are so fucking weird.
(SNIFFING)
You smell that?
The wee-wee?
Mmm-hmm.
Loud and clear.
Seems like the logical place to
take a pee-pee break, doesn't it?
Sure does. A lot of kids
pissed around here.
The adults peed over there. You
can smell the coffee on it.
You wanna whiff?
I'm good.
Found a little poop over there.
Those little BMs?
Yeah. Little kid-sizes.
Uh-huh. I saw those.
The way I see it, the van pulled up
over here, where the tire treads are,
kids bail out over here where
the little footprints are.
Okay.
They do their little diddies,
they do number ones,
they do some number twos,
they pile back in the van,
and they off on the road.
Mmm. They all drive in, load
out, unload, load up, drive out.
Drive out?
Or drive in?
He's in there.
You think we should save
the BMs for evidence?
We don't need evidence.
We're going in there
to get him.
EDDIE: Freakin' woods.
We should be home,
making babies,
sweet dirty love to our wives...
IVAN: Yeah.
Dirty babies.
Damn!
Oh, hitting her.
Touching her, caressing her.
That soft ass.
- Fondling, kissing, caressing...
- Eddie! Eddie.
What?
I cannot hike when
you talk sexy.
RANDY: Let's not
slow down, guys!
Bullshit we are.
Randy, we've been hiking all day,
now we're supposed to climb this?
Almost there!
Randy! We need a break, okay?
All of us!
Oh, Jesus, my feet hurt.
Come on, guys! It's
just over these rocks.
MOSES: Fuck those rocks!
I thought you said
we'd be fighting dragons!
That was metaphorical, okay?
That was just on the DVD.
We've been hiking for hours,
and haven't seen crap!
Crap.
RANDY: Haven't seen...
Gary! These rocks?
These are the gateway
to scouting!
Generations of Scouts
have passed over these!
Randy, stop the bull, please!
Guys, who wants to go home, huh?
I do!
Yes!
Take me! Take me!
You see?
All of 'em want to go home.
Well, great. Anyone who wants to help me
get Stuart to the top of these rocks,
you follow me. The rest of
you guys, go right on home.
Have a big boo-hoo party
with your mommies.
They can change
your wet diapers, okay?
But how do we know
how to get back home?
If you were a Scout,
you'd have no problem.
Wadonday.
What's up there?
MOSES: Dwande!
BOY: Where is he going?
Hey, Dwande!
Hey, look at that.
Dwande's gonna do this.
I'll go if you guys go.
Yeah. What else can we do?
Guys. Wait up.
Wait!
We might as well see what's up there.
Hey!
I'm not sayin' that
I really want to.
I thought you guys
wanted to go home!
No offense, Eddie. You probably
can't find the way home.
EDDIE: I bet you
my foot'll find your ass.
GARY: Dwande, slow down!
(CLIPPING WIRE)
All right. (GRUNTS)
Okay. Let's do this.
Dang it, man.
What?
Well, these are my
new church slacks.
Yeah?
Well, you just crawled through
a pee-pee puddle there, Kirk.
CALDWELL: Yup.
I'm going back to the car and grab my dungarees.
Just wait here, all right?
Caldwell, back me up.
Grab my iPod.
For what?
It's got a mix on there,
heavy metal.
Oh, all right.
Gets me all revved up.
(GRUNTS) You know what I mean?
I love Kirk, but he doesn't understand
how much slacks cost these days.
Hey, look around in there. I think I
have another pair if you want some.
CALDWELL: Where's it at?
You see 'em?
I don't see it.
Well, they're right there.
Y'all looking to camp?
GENTRY: Um...
Yes, sir.
That'd be great.
A lot of friendly people here.
Gearing up to have fun.
(GENTRY CHUCKLES)
GENTRY: Well, sounds like
our kind of people.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh... Should we
follow you, then?
I wish you would.
You got your pants?
Yeah, I got my pants!
KIRK: Shit!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Look at the view!
Whoa!
Ho, ho, ho.
Oh, my God!
(BOYS EXCLAIMING IN AMAZEMENT)
Awesome!
This is pretty bad-ass.
Randy.
You called this one.
Eddie.
We made it!
MOSES: We're
camping up in this?
Oh, do we get badges
and crap now?
You already have your badges. Check
your arms, check your necks.
Look at those cuts,
look at those insect bites.
You guys earned those, man. Look
at the sweat under your armpits,
and, Leachman, that heat
rash, we'll fix that.
But, guys, you've earned all of this.
You are real Scouts.
So bring it all in,
real Scouts.
Bring it in, real Scouts,
right now.
Eddie, may I?
A toast, all right?
To my dad, for being lucky enough
to be here with all of you.
And to all the dads
who couldn't be here,
Mikey Caldwell's dad,
for instance,
who's death prevented him from
coming, but you know what?
He's up camping in
the sky right now,
but he's not gonna have as much fun
as you guys are about to have.
Amen.
Hey, America!
Troop 5516 is here, and we're
about to go camping in you!
(ALL CHEERING)
(HORN HONKING)
It's the outdoors,
nipple dicks!
No, no, no, we're
blending in just fine.
Yeah, as soon as these
yokels hit the hay, man,
we're gonna be
right there with you.
No one is deserting you.
I don't want you to be scared.
I'm not scared.
Just don't go anywhere.
You guys stay put, and make
sure nobody comes after me.
Stay put?
You can't break up
the team, Kirk! All right!
Caldwell and I want in on the action.
Come on!
This isn't about a team!
This is about my son!
Well, okay, Caldwell
has a son, too, you know.
Caldwell's son is at
my home with my wife,
where I should be!
Now, if I need backup, I'll call for it.
Backup?
Backup.
Backup, my ass.
I didn't come out here
to be no damn decoy
for a park ranger, motherfucker!
Motherfucker.
Run distraction.
I need you two guys
to blend in.
It's...
It's weird here, man.
It's just weird, all right?
It's like some sort of redneck
swingers' party or something, man.
Is that park ranger
still there?
Yeah, he is
staring at me right now.
It's weird.
I think he wants to fuck me.
Wait for my call. I don't
need you right now, Gentry.
Don't break up this partnership, man.
We got a good thing here.
(KIRK BREAKING UP) Kirk!
Kirk!
What the fuck
are these people doing?
Look at that asshole,
in the yellow.
What is his problem?
(OWLS HOOTING)
KIRK: You peckerwood...
What the hell is that?
(HOWLING)
(DRUMS BEATING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
EDDIE: (SHOUTING)
Let's get the party started!
(CHEERING WILDLY)
Gary, have a Root Beer.
Normally, I'd remain celibate,
but tonight I will imbibe.
Oh. Well, hala!
How you doing there, Moses?
What's up, man?
What's up?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Your troop back.
We're...
We're resuscitating it.
Okay?
This troop's not
gonna dissolve.
It's not gonna fade away.
Randy fucking Stevens!
Jesus Christ,
you got Dad out here, too?
Oh, you really went and did it.
Seven felonies
and Dad, to boot.
Abducting him
and all these kids?
That's desperate, Randy.
I'm getting you guys
out of here.
Dad, we're gonna get you
back to your room
where you need to be, okay?
Kirk, Kirk, listen.
This is our home, okay?
Right here, with the
trees over our heads,
this soil under our feet, and the...
Stop it!
No more poems. No more speeches.
You're done.
Now let's pack it up,
shut this down,
and hike everybody out of here.
This Scout troop is finished!
Dwande!
Oh, come here, buddy.
You don't have to be scared.
RANDY: Scared?
Kirk, he's not scared.
Okay?
This is a brave little kid.
Did you know that?
He helped all these
other kids get up here.
He's a big part of this!
You're calling my son
a kidnapper?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Kidnapping?
I didn't do it. I'm not a kidnapper.
He's not a kidnapper.
Well, unless you wanna go to jail...
EDDIE: No, no, no.
Look, look. I don't
want no problems here.
I can't go to fucking
prison again.
It hurts, okay? So...
Then, help me out.
You want us to tie this
motherfucker up for you?
Randy, run, motherfucker,
'cause I'm gonna kill you!
Eddie, it's not kidnapping
if you're related.
Bull fuck, Randy, we're
not brothers anymore.
If the Boy Scouts knew...
What are you doing?
You know what they would do?
They'd fuckin' kill all of us!
(HONKING)
KIRK: Oh, Dad.
I'm saving your life.
I'm paying for you
to be comfortable.
And you don't need
to be out here.
No one deserves to be out here.
We're cooperating! What do you
want us to do with this guy?
(RANDY GROANING)
Listen to me.
We are assistants.
We don't want to get involved
in none of this shit!
Then leave.
Okay, but we could help you
with the kids, all right?
Knock it off
and get out of here!
All right. Fine.
We'll leave. Yeah.
(RANDY SCREAMING)
Randy, it's a real
shithead move, you dick!
All right.
Let's pack up and go.
MOSES: Why'd you
kick him?
Moses, they kidnapped you!
These aren't real leaders.
Hanging out in the woods
with eight-year-olds,
cooking potato dinners,
writing poems...
That's not a man.
That's not a leader.
Look. You don't need badges from
these dorks to prove something.
Then what are
we supposed to do?
KIRK: I don't know.
Stay in school and
stay off drugs, uh...
And play sports, join the army.
Let's just get
out of here, okay?
We don't need to be in the
woods talking about this.
We can be back home, listening
to some Hoobastank.
BOYS: Ugh!
We could have Janine
cooking some taquitos...
Come on, fellows.
Bump me and we'll hit it.
Dwande.
Bump your daddy.
Dwande. What's wrong?
Bump me.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOYS EXCLAIMING)
GARY: (YELLING)
Knock it off!
TIBBITS: Come on,
you can do this, Randy.
BOYS: Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight!
BOY 1: Get up, Randy!
BOYS: Fight! Fight!
Get up, Randy!
BOY 2: Come on, Randy!
(GROANING)
Randy! What do we do?
Little help. Jesus!
Fellows, help!
BOYS: Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
LEACHMAN: Do you think
that's real?
I think it's another test.
(SCREAMING)
SHANE: That's gotta be fake.
This is fake!
This looks like horseshit.
GARY: He's probably
not really on fire
(HORN HONKING)
Tibbits!
Jump to the job!
KIRK: (YELLING)
Help me, guys!
TIBBITS: Randy. Is this for real?
KIRK: Jesus!
Quickly, Moses.
(HONKING)
TIBBITS: (YELLING) Guys, hurry up!
Moses, grab water!
Come on! Leonard!
Hey, Randy.
You need an air hole?
Jesus, Gary!
TIBBITS: Come on, guys!
Harder!
No!
(FIREWORKS HISSING)
Harder!
(FIREWORKS EXPLODING)
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
Are you alive,
Mr. Stevens?
(GRUNTING)
LEONARD: Guys.
Randy's okay.
BOYS: He's alive!
He's alive!
Mr. Stevens.
Tibbits, did you...
Did you do this?
I thought you were faking it.
Be brave, Randy.
You can cry.
KIRK: Hey!
Bring him over here!
(BOYS GRUNTING)
KIRK: Will you get him out
of the sleeping bag?
TIBBITS: Careful, guys.
We gotta cut it.
(BOYS GASPING)
Now get rolling on making
me a stretcher, please.
GARY: Like the one
in the Bible?
Yeah. Like the one
in the Bible.
Guys, wait.
There was a stretcher
in the Bible?
Oh, yeah!
Heck yeah!
Moses, can you bring
my dad over to me?
MOSES: Um, well,
your dad is not...
KIRK: Just bring him here.
He's...
KIRK: You guys go
pack up or help Gary.
Just give us a minute.
This is really
fucked up, Randy.
You know, the boys collected
his ashes this morning
and put him in there.
Congratulations, Randy.
Dad's dead.
Now he's in a fucking
cooking pot.
Huh!
I was burned
butt-naked.
My arms are scorched.
I can't put them down.
I was burned in places the
sun doesn't even know about.
I have a $350 Bluetooth melted
into the insides of my ear.
Dad should be in the hospital
right now, enjoying himself!
That's what I paid for!
What do you want me to say?
Say that this was
a stupid fucking idea
and that you're
a total failure.
I... I failed.
I made a mistake.
Say you failed Dad.
Say it.
I failed Dad.
Did you know I got Dad a crypt?
I got him a primo location
in the downtown cemetery.
They disinterred
a Confederate soldier
to make sure he got
a good location.
That ain't cheap.
RANDY: Jesus, Kirk!
I loved him, Randy.
You know, I've been working
with two architects
and a stone mason to ensure
that he got a good burial,
so his body could be
treated with some respect.
Is there an ATM machine
in the crypt?
Fuck you, Randy.
It's more respect
than you can afford.
He loved it out here!
TIBBITS: Randy, we have
to tell you something.
Mr. Stevenses,
your dad's not
in that cooking pot.
This my old dirty underwear.
Okay! Stretcher's ready!
Where is he?
TIBBITS: Well,
Dwande took him.
What are you talking about?
TIBBITS: He left this morning
with your dad in a backpack.
KIRK: Why wouldn't
anybody tell me?
Where'd he go?
GARY: It's a real doozy!
The Father, Son, Holy
Spirit will be with you.
Oh, Jesus, Gary!
You and Jesus
could be like bros!
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Daddy?
No. I'm a lady.
(LAUGHING) Hi.
Hey!
Is Leonard all set to go?
Uh... No. He's...
They went on a little...
Who are all these kids?
They're friend of...
They're kids...
Kids of our friends of ours.
LINDA: Where is my son, Janine?
Is there a problem here, ladies?
Oh, God, help me.
Yeah. Where is Leonard?
Leonard went camping.
No. Leonard
did not go camping.
What is he talking
about, Janine?
Read my lips, lady.
CA-MMM-PING.
Well, isn't he snippy.
Janine.
Where is Leonard?
KIRK: Dwande! It's okay!
GARY: Now you can be as
good a Jew as Jesus Christ.
RANDY: Let's not bring God or
Jesus into this, guys. Come on!
KIRK: Dwande!
We're coming for you!
Guys, could we please
be a little more careful?
BOYS: Shut up, Kirk!
MOTHER: What kind of
monkey operation is this?
JANINE: I'm sure they'll be home
soon because Kirk promised me...
SHANE'S MOTHER: I was
under the impression
they'd be within
this immediate vicinity.
What if there was an emergency?
There won't be an emergency.
None of us was told
about a camping trip.
Why didn't you mentioned this?
Because we didn't think
it was a problem.
You didn't think
it was a problem?
Where exactly are our boys?
Ladies! Ladies! You're
barking up the wrong tree!
If you have a beef,
you have a beef with the
Scoutmasters and her husband.
She's innocent!
Thanks, Kent.
You're welcome, Janine.
Look, we just have to have
a little patience, okay?
Kirk is out there,
he'll bring them all back.
- We just have to wait for...
- Janine!
You need to take us there.
Right now.
Dwande! We're over here!
Let's go! Move!
GARY: We are moving!
Well, move faster! Damn it,
my son's lost out there!
Kirk, he's not lost.
We're gonna find him.
Randy, shut your damn...
(BLUETOOTH VIBRATING)
BOY: What is that?
Someone's calling my Bluetooth.
Kirk! I got him! Hey,
Caldwell, I got him!
KIRK: I just want my son! Ahhh!
Kirk, can you hear me?
Where are you? Listen, listen.
What?
- Ahhh!
- Oh, my God!
Holy shit!
It sounds like they're
fuckin' torturing him.
This is bad news, dude.
Dwande!
All right, listen, hey, we
are dropping cover, man.
We're dropping cover
and coming to get ya!
Let's go. Let's go!
Hey, folks, sorry...
No!
Listen, the ATM is closed. I
need everybody to back away.
Hey! You all owe
camping fees!
Hey, take a hike, bitch.
And fuck your campsite.
We're on a mission to
blow butts, motherfucker.
Blow butts.
GENTRY: Let's get
those sons of bitches!
Kick some ass!
Let's roll.
These women are gonna rip me apart.
They are going to kill me.
And Kirk's gonna go to jail.
I'm gonna go to jail.
Wow! I think you're letting it
get a little tense right now.
What am I gonna do?
Maybe we should take it easy.
Enjoy the moment
that we have together.
Ha!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(KIRK GROANING)
RANDY: Hey. Hey. Hey, stop, guys, stop.
Set it down.
KIRK: We don't have
time for breaks.
Let's keep moving!
We gotta find Dwande.
Kirk. I think
we found him.
Dwande! It's me, Daddy! I'm
down here, on the stretcher!
LEACHMAN: We got crucifixed!
What's he got?
TIBBITS: I think
that's your dad.
KIRK: Dwande?
Buddy, let's be very
careful with that, okay?
We're gonna take him back
home where he'll be...
(BELLS TINKLING)
Hey. What's that sound?
It's beautiful.
(CELL PHONES RINGING)
That's our moms calling us.
I think that means we're
in deep shit, Mr. Stevens.
Thank you, Shane.
(ENGINE STALLING)
Shit! Son of a bitch.
Damn! God damn it, man!
You know what? That hotwire
shit, it don't work!
IVAN: Okay, be nice,
all right?
All I can do is get the
goddamned radio started, man!
All right. Be nice.
Then you do it.
You get it started.
You're a smart ass.
Be nice!
(ALL GRUNTING)
RANDY: Eddie.
Sweet Baby Jesus.
Don't you need these keys?
No, no, no, no, no!
We're not getting mixed
up with this, man. No!
What, you're not
gonna help these kids?
This is my answer. Step
away from the vehicle.
Roll it, man.
The back doors are open.
Jesus.
It's not starting.
Well, pop
the fucking clutch, man!
What's a poppa clutch?
A poppa clutch?
(ALL GRUNTING)
RANDY: Okay.
EDDIE: Come on, man!
Guys, come on.
Get us out of here. Come on.
That's how you poppa clutch!
Hey! No, no,
no, no, no, no!
Randy! Don't bring him
in here!
No! No!
How would Randy
get into these woods?
Janine. Right there!
Get this shit out of here! No, no, no!
Quit screaming!
Okay, Eddie, I got us moving.
It's rolling.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(SIREN WAILING)
GENTRY: That's them!
That's them!
You, shitty little cocksucks.
We got your ass!
Give it to me.
Everybody, hands up!
You are fucked!
Get out of the car!
They're making a break for it!
Everybody, freeze!
You heard the motherfucker.
He said "freeze"!
It's rolling, you idiots!
Halt!
(SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
EDDIE: Oh, it's the cops.
Randy! You tell them we got
nothing to do with this
and I'm not your friend!
Kids, move! Move!
Everybody! Back off! Get outta
here, you little shits! Move!
No more child casualties today.
They're getting away!
Huh? What? What?
GENTRY: Shoot the tires!
CALDWELL: This shit not gonna shoot the tires!
Ow!
What are you doing?
We're moving!
You broke the skin, man!
Oh, shit.
Stop! Stop!
Don't resist!
(GUN FIRING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
Oh! I think
we did that, man!
Jesus Christ came out
that windshield!
Let's get that motherfucker.
(YELLING)
Oh! A crotch rocket!
Oh, wow!
Is that the naked lady's?
Oh! Look at that!
Wait a minute. Please.
Ah, look at this.
A silk gown.
That's disgusting.
Guys! It's her! It's the lady.
Guys, come look!
(ALL CHEERING)
(YELLING)
No, no! Yo!
Stick 'em up, jerk-offs.
Stick 'em up? We were
just in a car wreck!
GENTRY: All right.
Nobody move. All right?
Unless you got to for, like, a medical
reason or some bullshit like that.
Caldwell, you got
a 20 on this scumbag?
CALDWELL: I don't know
what a 20 is.
20, a location, man.
Where the fuck
is that little bastard?
Motherfucker.
He's getting away!
Hey! Fuck you!
Freeze!
Gentry! Gentry!
Who's a dead man now,
huh, asshole?
JANINE: What's that?
Thought you could outsmart
the outsmarters, huh?
Shoot him again, Caldwell.
Hey, cut that out, Gentry.
Oh, God!
Janine! What the hell
are you doing here, huh?
Shouldn't you be at home, like,
online shopping or something?
Gimme my gun back!
Hey, kid!
What is going on here? What
happened to the kids? Where's Kirk?
Everything is under control.
No. It's not.
You stupid, stinkin'
son of a bitch!
Oh, okay.
Hello, ladies!
Where is my son?
What did you do to our boys?
The good news is that they were
nowhere near the van crash.
(ALL EXCLAIMING IN DISTRESS)
Where are our sons?
They're not here...
MOTHER: You lost our children?
There's no reason to panic
because they will soon be back
in your warm, loving bosoms.
(MOTHERS PROTESTING)
Mr. Scout Leader,
if my sweet Lord Christ
in the trees
has any ounce of mercy to place
on a cursed soul like yours,
he better damn well show me
a sign of that right now!
(GROANING)
(MOTHERS GASPING)
Everything's perfectly
fine here, ladies!
Oh, God!
Can somebody
get me off this cross?
And on a Sunday, of all days!
You should all be
ashamed of yourselves!
All right, ladies, ladies, listen up.
Name's Gentry.
Let me lay it down for you.
Here are the facts
as we know them.
And although we can't confirm
this one hundred percent,
we believe that your
children may be dead.
MOTHERS: What?
(MOTHERS CLAMORING)
Gentry, shut up. Shut up!
Janine, it's true.
Who is this guy?
RANDY: Idiot.
He's an idiot.
He's a security guard at an ATM company.
He has no authority.
Okay, yes,
I am an ATM security agent,
which means I've been
trained in firearms.
I've been trained in black ops.
And here are the facts, ladies.
Children don't live
in the woods.
They die.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
If I could have done something
about it, I would have.
I don't like to point fingers,
but this fucking guy
killed your kids.
Oh, my God! What have
you done with him?
What have you done with him?
GENTRY: Probably being devoured
by wolves as we speak.
Jesus Christ!
What happened out here?
Where's Dwande?
He's up there.
They are all up there.
RANDY: He's making that up. He's
making that up. He totally...
(ENGINE REVVING)
Oh, my God!
KIRK: That's our son.
What the fuck is going on?
Hey, this is federal
goddamned...
That's a naked woman.
Lord, well done.
Leonard!
What did they do to you?
Mom, it's okay. It's just tits.
Leonard!
Whoo!
Look at you!
Smell it. I made testosterone.
Oh, yes!
Then we saw one
of his organs coming out,
and then over there you saw
his heart pumping out.
It was still beating, it was
like bum, bum, bum, bum, bum!
And then, after that, you saw
all the blood squirting,
and then you couldn't
even see the wires
because all the blood was like...
(MIMICS BLOOD SPLASHING)
You just saw its insides, and
there was some black thing.
It was like
the game that I have.
Hey, buddy, you be
careful with that. Okay?
Can I ask you a question?
What were you thinking?
Baby, I'm so sorry. Those women look
like they could have killed you.
Yeah. I hate those women.
They scare the shit out of me.
But at least it worked
out for your father.
Where is your father?
Dwande?
This guy did something
beautiful, baby.
Dwande, you can do
whatever you want, okay?
If you wanna be a basketball
player, or a dentist,
or a nightclub singer,
I don't give a crap.
I'm just your dumb
daddy and I love you.
You can do whatever you want.
Well, we don't have to make
the decision right now.
Let's not rush into anything.
Hey, Kirk! Ow!
(ALL GROANING)
Janine, please watch it.
Oh, whoa, brother! You look
like a bag of shit, man!
You're all burnt up!
I'll be honest,
I don't even think
plastic surgery's
gonna help you.
You need medical attention.
And you probably ought to give
your family a little attention,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Hey, it's probably a bad time,
but I'm gonna go ahead and
put in my two weeks notice.
I'm sorry. I love
ATM security, I do.
You know I'm the best,
but I just feel like
I need something more.
And Caldwell,
he needs a babysitter,
so, you know,
I'm great with kids,
probably the best,
and that's a natural fit.
I hope you guys understand.
And I hope you live.
Anyway. Hey, Dwande, do me a
favor, bury that, all right?
Thank you.
Caldwell, I got shotgun, brah!
Dad.
Yeah?
We should go home.
JANINE: Yeah. Let's get out of here.
KIRK: Okay. Help Dad up.
(GROANING)
RANDY: Over the tops of these hills
and past the roads and highways,
you can see back
to the neighborhood,
where men return home
to their wives,
ready to embrace
the future ahead.
And not far away,
on the other side of town,
the parents of these boys
have grown proud of their sons.
What they've done
and who they've become.
Following the Ten Commandments,
is the way we should
live our lives every day.
Come on, guys!
RANDY: The boys
are becoming men
that aren't afraid of
seeking out new frontiers,
while others turn their lives
around and change their old ways.
It got a little burned.
Yeah, but it's a nice try.
Thanks, babe.
Thank you.
RANDY: Learning to look toward
a greater, fuller, richer life.
Sharing stories with friends
and telling them
real adventures
that they never
thought possible.
You might hear them
talking about
a Scoutmaster they once had.
A Scoutmaster
that pushed his Scouts
to become strong,
courageous, bona fide men.
Because this is scouting
and, damn it, somebody's
got to lead the way.