Nick, get up!
Nick...
Nicholas, get up.
Come on, get up.
Mom, he won't get up.
Are you okay? What happened?
I fell.
Yeah, I can see that.
But... but what,
did you cross your skies or..?
I don't know. I just fell.
He's a klutz, that's why.
Come on, let's go.
I'm cold.
Let's get up.
Ugh!
You all right?
You scared me.
Mm, not too much snow,
but there's supposed
to be a big fall tonight.
Oh, we got a point!
I saw a green ball go in.
I can't hear you. Henry?..
Don't mess with the program...
No, I'll figure it out
when I get back...
No. No, I reorganized
all this stuff, so just...
don't touch it. Okay?
I keep all the hard copies
in a file under the desk.
You'll find it there. Mm-hm.
Oh, that was such a good...
I've been sleeping
in your T-shirt...
Mm-hm...
Me too.
Oh, jeez!..
: Ah!
None of us have got a point yet.
Come on, you've gotta get one.
You're so bad!..
No, you can't do it to me now.
I'm in the lounge...
All right.
I will.
Love ya!
Bye.
One more game, guys,
and then we're going home.
Home?
Mm-hm.
Ah, how come?
Do we have to? We're supposed
to stay here till the weekend.
Yeah.
I know...
It sucks! Home?
And I think Dad's missing us
too much. Okay?
What a rip!
It's supposed to snow tonight.
My name is Nicole
I live in a hole
with lots-
And lots of trolls
: When they want to come in
I let them right in
So maybe they'll eat my twin
My name is-
: NICHOLAS
I EAT LOTS OF LICORICE
I COME FROM-
: Nick!
Are you deaf or something?
You're so out of tune,
my ears hurt!
Okay, okay. Now, Nick...
My name is Nicholas
I eat lots of licorice
I come from a palace on Mars
Mom?
You should be on TV and radio.
You're a thousand times better
than Celine Dion.
And a mmmmmmillion times--
He's right.
You and Nicole and Daddy
are my favourite audience.
I don't need anybody else.
: My name
Is Nicholas
I eat lots of licorice
I COME FROM A PALACE ON MARS
Shhh! Guys, hold it down.
'Cause we don't wanna wake
everybody else up;
we just wanna surprise Daddy.
Okay?
I gotta pee! Oh, too late.
I wet my pants.
Shhh.
Absolute...
absolute quiet, okay?
Tiptoe.
Shhh! Take her to the kitchen
and get her some milk.
Not a peep.
Huh?
Julie?
Mom...
We're going! Now!
Move it!
Mom... what are you doing?
Run! Move it!
Get in the car! Now!
... is this?
You're scaring us!
Mom! Why are we leaving
like this?
Mom! Dad's behind us.
Julie!
Please stop!
He's chasing us!
Sit down
and shut up!
Please stop. I want Dad.
Did you hear me? I want--
All right! Anybody wants
to see your dad,
you can stop and get out!
Get out!
I said get out!
Fine!
Get out!
You just don't know
what he did.
Dad!
She said"Shut up" to me.
She's never said that before.
I know, honey.
She was mad at me.
And it rubbed off on you.
She didn't mean it, she didn't mean it.
It's gonna be okay. All right,
come on, let's get undressed, okay?
There we go.
You know, it's probably not good
for twins to be separated for too long.
You're absolutely right.
You'll see Nick tomorrow
and we'll fix everything, okay?
Get those socks off. Come on.
You better get under there
right away and go to sleep,
because you can't even imagine
the danger you're in.
There's a hungry spider
crawling up the bed.
Hungry, pinching spider
who loves little girls!
Dad, please, no.
Don't blame me, blame the spider!
Mom?
No, it's not Mom.
Who's there?
It's nobody.
Come on, go to bed.
Let's get some sleep.
We got a big day tomorrow...
and everything's
gonna go back to normal.
Okay?
Don't forget to say good night
to Nurnies.
Nurnies?
I thought Nurnies ran way
to join the circus years ago.
Well, Nurnies is back.
I remember.
Nurnies sleeps on the ceiling.
Good night, Nurnies.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Good night, princess.
Good night.
Love you.
What happened?
Your curse worked.
Can we help you?
No, I'm... I'm okay.
We'll talk in the morning.
Mom...
do you still love Nicole?
Of course I do.
Whatever happened with your dad
has nothing to do with Nicole
or you. Okay?
Why don't you want
to tell me about it?
Honey, some things...
change everything.
It's hard to explain.
You could at least try.
All you need to know
is some things never change.
Like how much
I love you and Nicole.
The important things.
And Dad's not important?
How about we cuddle
all night tonight?
Okay.
And guess what?
Nurnies is back from the circus.
Really?
Mm-hm.
Open the door.
Open up!
I know you're there.
Julie?
Nicholas?
Can't you see her car
is not here?
Dad, don't give me this.
I'm not your dad.
She doesn't want to see you.
She doesn't need you.
Daddy?
Daddy!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Mom went to get some food.
Where's Nicole?
I came to get you. No use
driving her back and forth, right?
But Mom says
we're staying here.
Well, she just meant
overnight.
That's not what she meant.
I'm taking him home.
That boy wants
to fish.
Come on, Nickers. Let's go.
We plan to fish
The cod are in.
Nicole's waiting for us,
buddy boy.
Okay...
Okay, look,
why don't you stay and fish,
I'll wait for Mom
and then we'll all go home, okay?
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, it's okay.
Go ahead.
How could you be so stupid?
In your own house.
So now you pay.
You're a brick wall.
You know?
There's no sense talking to you.
Sure, Mr. Fucking Scientist!
I am not smart enough
to understand your talk.
I'll be back
to pick up Nicholas.
Dad! Dad, is it you? Dad!
Mom...
something's wrong with Belladonna.
We've gotta take her,to the vet.
Look.
Honey, she's having
her babies.
Did it look like that
when you were having us?
Kind of.
I was in such a hurry,
Daddy barely got me
to the hospital on time.
Are you mad at me
'cause I went with Daddy last night?
No. I'm proud of you.
Julie?
I have to talk to Daddy now.
But the kittens are coming.
You'll be fine. I'll be back.
Mom...
what's going on?
Dad just...
doesn't love me anymore.
Okay. One, two, three.
Julie, I'm sorry.
I made a mistake
and I'm so sorry.
I called Monica
about selling the house.
What?
We'll split the proceeds.
What proceeds?
I'm trying to tell you what happened.
We should try to get apartments
as close to each other as possible.
Make it easier for the kids.
What are you saying?
You're leaving?
We're leaving.
The twins and me.
They've never been separated
before and they shouldn't be now, so...
I'll let Nicole stay
for a few days--
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Well, this is insane.
This is completely insane.
And ridiculous to boot.
Julie, it didn't mean anything.
It wasn't important.
Do you remember when we were talking
a few months ago about this book?
Whatever the title was...
And you said it yourself...
And I was even impressed that...
that men are not monogamous
by nature.
Remember?
It was at that restaurant
on Main. And you said it yourself,
that... that sometimes,
it just doesn't really matter
because it's a physiological impulse.
Come on, Jule,
you know that's true.
You're an intelligent woman.
Don't you
fucking patronize me!
I'm not interested
in exploring your motives.
Henry, it's over.
Julie, for God's sakes,
it was the first time,
with anyone.
But I can't ever
trust you again.
You know me, Henry.
I haven't told the kids
what you've done, so...
think of something.
Julie, I love you.
And I love our family.
Please, just give me another chance.
We--
Don't fucking touch me.
I'm not selling this house!
I'm not!
All I want
is the crystal
that belonged to my mother.
I don't care
about anything else.
Are you mad at my dad, too?
I don't want anything
to do with him.
Why? 'Cause he's Jewish?
Worse...
he doesn't care about it.
He cares about nothing.
But me and Nicole
are half-Jewish.
We celebrate Hanukkah
and Christmas.
I like that,
'cause we get more presents.
You're not Jewish.
Your mother's Catholic
and so are you.
One becomes someone
after a mother, not father.
But why?
That's the way it is.
I got one!
I think I got one!
I know how to do it.
I'll do it myself.
I wanna do it.
Mom! I caught a cod! A big one!
Wow. So we have dinner
after all.
You'll scratch it.
Like this.
Nick...
clean the fish outside.
Just be careful.
Like I showed you.
At least it's good
you are not married.
You'll save on divorce.
That's a strange thing
for a Catholic man to say.
And you're a strange daughter
for the Catholic to have.
Mugs up here with saucers.
Maybe just for fun, I'll mess
with your sock drawer, heh?
Switch all the labels
on your frozen fish. Hm?
I knew it.
I just knew it--
Don't you dare
say one fucking bad word
about him!
If you can't respect the fact
that we've had children together
and that we had some good years,
then-- - How do you know they were good?
Just because you fucked around
on Mom all those years,
doesn't mean that everyone else
is like you.
Did she know?
What do you think?
God.
Since we're on the subject,
it's been three years
since Mom...
I'm expecting someone.
Who? Now?
I invited a woman from Poland.
I met her through letters, you know...
She's a widow like me,
but no children. If we...
Iike each other, I might...
marry her.
Marry her? Come on, Tata,
you don't even know her.
I need someone.
So when's your
mail-order bride arriving?
Tonight.
Tonight?!
But...
Jesus, Dad.
Big week for the family, heh?
Not that many couples
out there, you know,
have this thing
that you two had.
You worked together,
you played together.
Keep twisting the blade.
Honey, maybe what I'm trying
to do here is make you realize
what you're about to give up.
Sometimes we've got to look
at things with a more forgiving eye.
No! No, you can't.
Not at some things.
Well, you can't, Julie.
I dunno. You're angry now,
but maybe... down the road, you...
Please don't.
Okay.
So you're gonna sell
the house tomorrow, right?
Okay.
... after way too long,
look who's back.
It's Julie McCaskie!
Come on, Julie.
Come on up here and play a song
for us.
No way!
Put it together,
for the sweetest voice...
Whoo!
So let's hear it...
Thanks for all the support.
Come on, Julie.
Whoo!
Julie!
Oh, God. Okay.
Do you remember it?
Well, I remember something.
Oh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh
It's over now
I'm cold alone
I'm just a person
On my own
Nothing means a thing to me
No nothing means a thing to me
It's not hard but it's cool
I feel alive
If you don't have it
your on the other side...
You still got great lips, Terry.
Right here?
Huh?
Sorry.
I'm not there yet.
Maybe next time.
Yeah, next time.
Another 10 years!
: Ten years!
Can you wait that long?
No, no, no...
Where's Grandpa?
'Morning.
He's usually here first.
I hope she didn't hurt him.
Do you like her?
I dunno. I can't understand
what she's saying.
Sounds nice, though.
And what does Grandpa think?
He's always smiling.
And she waves a lot, too.
Hello.
'Morning.
It's not my mug.
What's the difference.
Thanks.
You go after breakfast with us?
Dad, we've been
through this before.
Do you want me to be a hypocrite
just to please you?
Look, I pray in my own way,
okay?
I don't need some priest
to tell me how.
Okay, okay, okay.
Really, Dad,
you'd make a great crusader.
Mom don't you believe in it
at all?
In what, sweetheart?
God. Heaven.
After you die.
You and Nicole are my heaven.
I won't let you to die first.
Oi!
Welcome.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
I've... Tea or coffee?
Give her a coffee with milk.
How was the trip?
She said it went fast.
How do you know she's not
just after immigration papers?
Why do you say that?
With all due respect, Dad,
you're 75 years old.
So it's my last chance
to feel young again.
I just don't want
you taken advantage of.
She always wanted to go
to America.
These lizards, very strange
creatures -- from Russia.
The females live on their own
without any husband,
give birth to she-lizards,
grow up, never search for boys,
give birth to other girl lizards
and so on and so forth.
Some just don't need men at all.
Is Mom still gonna help you
in your book?
I don't know.
Nicole, come here!
Mom! Nick! Nicholas!
... the kittens!
Quick!
One's all black!
And I caught a big fish
at Grandpa's!
Guys...
Daddy and I need to talk to you
about something.
Actually, your mother's gonna do
all the talking from now on.
Remember last year
when we talked about
selling the house
and finding a new one?
So that we can both
get our own bedroom?
Well...
we've decided to sell the house
this time
and we're gonna make
some other changes too.
And it's gonna be hard.
We're not selling the house.
And... and...
I'm not looking to make
any changes.
Are you two getting a divorce?
Is that why you're staying
at Grandpa's?
No, honey.
Mommy's just really angry
at Daddy right now. That's all.
Julie...
Would you please go and tell 'em
you've changed your mind.
I can't.
She's here with clients.
Well, you tell them
to go home.
This house is not for sale.
I'm not gonna argue with you,
Henry. I've made up my mind.
As intelligent as you are,
you already--
Dad,
are we supposed to feel happy
that we have two homes?
Yeah.
The house was restored...
How many years ago now, Julie?
Uh, six. We moved here
when the twins were two years old.
Kitchen.
You look terrible.
I can bring them back next week.
No. No, no.
Let's just do it now.
I'll be okay.
You're a mess, honey.
I'd like to get a door
between the dining room
and the patio. It's not
very convenient to go around.
That's not a problem.
You could put a fountain here too.
A fountain in the living room?
Oh, yeah! Why not?
Or a bobsled run.
You could start up in the attic
and just wind up right down here.
My husband's just joking.
Ah, don't forget,
I'm not your husband.
We never got married, actually.
We loved each other so much,
we never bothered
with the formalities.
Henry, please.
Worked out great, though, didn't it?
You see, if you never marry,
you safe a bundle on divorce.
But if we make an acceptable offer,
we can move in as soon as possible?
You want it, you got it.
Kids, we're moving out!
Pack a suitcase!
Henry!
Throw the kids in a box!
Stop it!
Okay, we're finished here.
Hey, wow, where you going?
Don't say you wanna go now.
Come on, this is when the fun starts!
Listen, you wanted to break
that wall through?
Here, let me
help you with that, okay?
After all,
ownership has its privileges
and right now,
I still own this house.
Henry!
Are you crazy?! The kids!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Shhh, come here.
It's okay.
Out!
Out of my house!
I am calling the cops.
Good. You do that.
Are you gonna be okay
with this asshole?
How could you do that
in front of the kids?
Ahh! My God!
Nicholas!
Nick!
Nicky?
Nick.
Nick, c'mon.
Is he breathing?
Yeah. Yeah, he's breathing.
Nicole, honey,
get him some water.
Nicky, c'mon, c'mon.
What's wrong with him?
You probably scared him
half to death.
Maybe he's hot. C'mon, honey.
C'mon, baby, c'mon.
Nick.
Nick?
Nick, sweetie, sweetie...
C'mon.
Nick.
: Help me.
Nick?
Here he comes, here he comes.
Nick.
It's okay.
Here he comes.
It's okay. It's okay,
sweetheart. It's okay.
Dad...
Yeah.
You were a real asshole
to those people.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Say it 10 times.
What?
"I'm ashamed
of being an asshole."
How about... I'm ashamed,
I'm ashamed,
I'm ashamed, I'm ashamed,
I'm ashamed of being an asshole.
:
I'm ashamed,
I'm ashamed, I'm ashamed,
I'm really...
I really am.
I'm ashamed.
Come here.
Here...
have a drink.
Yeah.
I'm really ashamed, too.
: Please, God,
if Nicholas is okay,
we'll make everything
the same again. Please, God...
Hi. Sorry to keep you waiting.
I wanted to make sure
I had the biopsy results first.
Yesterday, we released a boy
almost exactly your son's age.
He came in a year ago...
with a...
with a very similar diagnosis
and now he's going home.
Uh, Doctor, I'm a biologist,
my father's a professor of medicine.
Just tell us the truth, please.
Well, Nicholas
has a mediastinal tumour.
No, but the prognosis is good.
Lymphoma B or T?
B or fucking T!
For God's sake, Henry, can youstop
showing off for once in your life?
He has cancer! Understand?
Cancer!
So... so what do we do now?
Start chemotherapy tomorrow.
Now, Nicholas looks strong
and his blood work's back in.
It's all good.
You know, 10 years ago,
I would've said,
"Pray for a miracle." But today,
we're seeing many similar cases
and we're treating them
successfully.
Jesus...
Maybe I could've
caught it in time
if only I'd taken him to the doctor
right after the skiing trip.
Honey...
it was only a few days ago.
Okay,
you can keep Nurnies here
as long as you're in the hospital.
Spirits Nurnies.
And butterfly wings.
But if there's a loud knock
on the door and Fothum comes...
They can't come to a hospital.
You're right.
Do you still remember
the magic words to undo the spell?
Elenda chao
tonay.
Good.
Tonight at nine, look at the
moon. - Nurnies will remind me.
I'll look too.
Dad said it's a full moon.
It'll be easier
to turn the spell around then.
Look!
: Spirit
Nurnies.
Elenda chao tonay.
Nicole, it's time to go.
Nicole! I forgot
to show you something.
They take the chemicals
and bomb my tumour through it.
Show it to the moon.
He'll pour in the silver ray.
Who?
The full moon.
What are you looking at?
Can I try?
My dad doesn't let us
play video games.
He says it destroys
our imagination.
Your dad's a butthole.
And so are you.
You talk to girls.
It's my twin sister.
Doesn't matter. I heard you.
You talk in some stupid language.
What is it?
Some space-alien code?
It doesn't have a name.
Welcome to our planet.
We're so dumb, our language
doesn't even have a name.
How about"Buttbarf"?
"Do you speak
Buttbarf?""Yes, I'm a butthole
from planet Moron--"
You're a butthole yourself.
Here.
Try it.
There! That way!
Go!
No, push this one!
No, not yet! Go, now, kill,
shoot, shoot!
Kill him!
You missed him. Loser.
Why are you so bald?
It's chemotherapy.
You'll look the same way soon.
Why?
'Cause you got cancer.
You get cancer,
you lose your hair,
then you die.
The doctor never really
said anything about that.
They always lie.
They can't tell you the truth,
'cause it gives them the creeps.
This guy in the next room,
he died this morning.
Gone, checked out,
vaporized, entered"kill zone"
and dematerialized.
He had cancer.
Same as you and me.
I didn't want to believe in this stuff,
but my sister had it sent
from India.
Can't do any harm, right?
Hundred dollars a box.
Oh, my God.
But I've had it analyzed,
there's nothing harmful in it.
And it helps Frankie to sleep.
You should try it.
It can't hurt.
Do you mind?
No.
That'd be great.
Since he started the chemotherapy,
Nicholas just wakes up every hour.
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Oh, my God...
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mooooom! Mom!
It's all right, it's all right...
Nicholas! Nicholas, Nick...
It's okay, it's okay.
Nick, Nick...
What happened to him?
Nick, baby...
Nick...
Everybody, clear.
... clear.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Nick...
it's okay. Don't be afraid.
Mom?
Whoa, Nicholas. Hey,
want to be a little nicer to me
and try to respond to the
medication like a good kid?
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
What happened?
Well, he had a...
a really extreme reaction
to the chemo,
but we're gonna, uh...
we'll try something else.
You gave me a fright.
I'm sorry about that.
Is that my hair?
Uh...
I don't wanna be bald.
It's okay.
We'll get you some
great new hair, okay?
What about, uh...
what about long and blond?
Would you like that?
Like you?
Like me.
Or, uh, green and spiky?
What about if I tell you
you'll have better hairthan Nicole?
Come on, Dad, go!
Come on, Dad! Faster!
You can do it! I know you can!
Come on!
Go! Go get 'em, Dad!
Go!
You were supposed to win!
: I'm in bad shape.
Not enough exercise.
Too many cigarettes.
You really thought I could win?
We want Nicholas to be okay.
Nicole!
Who told you that?
Nobody's responsible
for Nicholas's disease. Nobody.
Not you, not me, not Mom.
How about God?
God?
Because Nicholas and l
aren't baptized
and we don't go to church
enough. None of us.
Let us pray
for this brave family.
Three years ago,
we prayed for Helena,
watching her long struggle
with pain and suffering.
Now her little grandson Nicholas
has to face a similar battle.
Let us pray
for his return to health.
But if the Lord
decides to have him by his side,
Iet us praythat he does not suffer
and reaches the other bank.
Stupid, insensitive
son of a bitch!
You know I don't smoke.
Today just reconfirms
why I could never get into
any of this. You don't really need
all this hypocrisy to believe.
Believe in what?
In anything.
Life, our kids...
you.
I believed in you.
Not everyone is as strong
as you, Julie.
... and the Holy Spirit,
I baptize you--
What are you doing?
You have no right!
Nicole wanted it.
She asked me to arrange it.
Hi, Mom.
I... I thought it could help.
It's okay.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Would you like
to be baptized too?
Yes.
All right.
I'm sorry, Father.
No need. I understand.
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Spirit,
I baptize you
and give you the name of Nicole.
But she's already called that.
Can I be called Gabriella?
There's always a chance.
Miracles happen. You...
you hear about them all the time.
Remember, Sam?
You've said so yourself.
I... Yes, I did.
Things are always developing.
New treatments, drugs--
Dad. Julie, what Nicholas
needs now is love and understanding.
Love and understanding?!
You should've thought of that before!
Maybe none of this would've happened!
What are you saying?
That... that I'm responsible
for Nicholas's illness?
Henry, please.
Please what? She thinks that...
she thinks Nicholas got sick
because I had an affair?
I've had enough of this mystic
crap! Masses, baptisms in hospitals!
She's ready to become a member
of a goddamn sect!
I've been living with a woman
I didn't even know for 10 years!
There's a lot more
I didn't know about you.
Oh, I should've slugged
that priest of yours.
You've sinned enough.
But the child will stand pure
before Go--
Shut up! Just shut up!
I'm sick
of your ignorance,
your anti-Semitic insults
and your superstitious bullshit!
You understand? That's it.
You think your religion is the best,
you think your church
has a monopoly
on mercy and truth? Get down
on your knees. Let's see
your church make my son better.
Henry!
This is not the time
for recriminations!
His mail-order girlfriend
thinks the Virgin Mary is Polish.
Hey, Dad, did you tell her
Jesus Christ
was Jewish?
I am not your dad!
Stop it, for God's sake,
both of you! Nicholas is dying.
I can't...
I just can't believe it.
Sorry...
Sorry... I know old mythic...
tells me... I also...
seek--
What is she talking about?
I sorry. Look.
Big tumour
and no have it.
He touches
and I no have it.
Who touches?
Olov, the Russian healer.
He's famous. In Poland,
they show him even on TV.
He's touching his hands
and making miracles.
Oh, stop this, please.
True!
Two years no tumour.
Where? Where is he?
How do we find him?
She'll call her sister
to find out.
What are you doing?
Call her. Right now. Please.
Julie...
Julie, look at me.
Now I know
how hopeless you feel. I do too.
But this is nothing
but superstition.
And desperation,
because that's what these people
feed off of.
That's what they take advantage
of. Come here. This woman
is a lunatic. Can't you see that?
You always call women crazy
when they have answers
you can't understand.
You call them witches,
lock them up,
burn them at the stake.
Well... well, what if it's true?
What... what if Bogusha's right
and you're wrong?
You're not taking him
to Poland.
Uh--
So forget it. You're not going!
He's not going!
He's not leaving!
He's allergic to the chemo!
Nothing else is working!
We have to try it!
Faith healers. Faith healers!
We might as well put ourfaith
in fortune cookies.
Why spend money on research?
Let's just go stick needles
into dolls--
Henry, please listen to me.
During the war in Europe,
people were saved by miracles.
They escaped death
only by miracles.
All because they had faith.
Mom, this has nothing to do
with the Holocaust.
Henry, I have to try it.
With your permission orwithout.
What if he dies over there?
I tell you...
he won't die.
Mom?
Yes, baby?
I'm scared.
Why are you scared?
I don't know. I'm scared.
I don't wanna--
You don't wanna what?
Nothing.
The priest baptized me
so I wouldn't go
to the abyss, right?
What abyss?
When you're good,
you go to heaven;
when you're bad, you go to hell.
But when you're in the middle,
it's purgatory.
But when you're not baptized,
you go to the abyss.
For eternity. Forever.
Is that what Grandpa told you?
Yeah.
He really believes
in this stuff.
And what do you think?
I don't know.
But it's better not to take
any chances,
Grandpa got me baptized
just in case if I die.
You're not gonna die.
Nicole got baptized too
and she's not dying.
She's perfectly fine
and you will be too.
You understand?
Mom, I just don't want
it to hurt.
Is it going to hurt me?
No.
Mom?
If Nicole's name is Gabriella,
should mine
be Gabriel?
Well, if you want
to get baptized again,
we can change it.
You can be baptized as many times
as you like, if it makes you happy.
You haven't got a headache
or anything? Nothing's hurting?
No.
That's good.
You make me happy
when you say that.
I don't want to worry about
what Grandpa says, all right?
Why?
Because you're not gonna die.
I hope not.
I promise you.
Spine.
Chest.
Eyes.
Head.
Chest.
He has nothing.
He is healthy.
This woman, with the child,
blond hair, attached.
Yeah.
Spine.
I'm sorry,
I don't speak Polish.
Come on.
Come on, follow me.
Spine.
Alexy.
Careful.
Cancer. Chest.
They don't speak Polish.
Stop.
Want some water?
Want something to drink?
Are you gonna be here more?
I'm finished.
You sure?
Yeah, finished.
My sweetest, my sweetest boy,
please don't go.
Please, please, please,
please, please.
Please, try.
Please. Keep breathing,
please. Please, please.
Oh, please.
Hello, Henry?
Can you hear me?
Christ.
Come on,
you gotta try, sweetheart,
you gotta try. Heh?
Please try.
Please, please, please try.
Nick!
Nick?
Baby.
Mom, they don't even have a clue
about baseball here.
This game does not
make sense to me. It is impossible
to understand whatsoever.
You hit a ball then chase it
toward something
called a pack.
It's base. I told you that already.
See? He doesn't even get it
at all.
Alexy wanted me to tell you
that your boy needs more sessions.
This kind of disease
demands more than one touch.
You mean right away?
Oh, no. Our next stop
is Jelenia Gora.
Here is the address and the map.
We'll spend a day over there.
Then we go to Krakow
and Bielsko.
You will have to follow us
as long as there is need.
I... How do I pay him?
I only have credit cards.
No, no, no.
Don't worry.
He doesn't take any money.
We cover all the expenses.
Any country he goes to, there is
a special committee who takes care
of everything.
Money does not interest him.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Tell him how grateful we are.
Okay.
We'll go anywhere.
Nicholas, say thank you.
Thank you.
Maybe you will teach me
this baseball
if we travel together.
See you later.
Oh, wait. Please.
Can I ask you a question?
What is he like?
I mean,
what kind of a man is he?
Man?
Even when he was a child,
his gift would pour out if him.
He's like a river of... Iife.
Moo!
Close the window, honey,
it's stinks.
No way. I'm talking to the cows.
Oh, no, no, wait.
I think that was a good decision.
A little impetuous, but it was
good. - It's my impulse.
It was good. You know--
The door looks great, you know.
Looks like it's been there
for... forever.
At least a couple...
Hey, watch out.
She's spying on us.
Clever girl.
Hello?.. Mom!..
What did you say?..
I can't hear you...
Yeah, he's right here...
No, no...
Oh, I'm fine...
Can I talk to him?
Nick!..
What did you say?
Cows? What cows?..
Nick...
Let me talk to them.
We were cut off.
What did she say about Nicholas?
He's fine.
Say it again.
He's fine, he's good,
he's not gonna die.
He said they nearly
ran into some cows.
Cows?
On a road. He said the roads there
are full of cows.
And that they understand English.
The cows understand English?
Legs.
Head.
Stomach.
Sorry, I don't speak Polish.
Oh, sorry.
I saw you in Walbrzsych.
Now I look at the child
and I can't get over it.
He was dying, wasn't he?
I'm a physician
and I used to ridicule him.
Until one of my patients
came to try this.
I had given him a death sentence
a few months earlier
and he resurrected him.
So now you believe.
I do and I don't.
Official medicine
gave up on him.
But I feel I have no right
not to try.
What's the name of your boy?
Nicholas.
Nicholas! Come on!
Nice kid.
Very nice kid.
Hey.
Just in time.
It's all right. Go on.
Come on.
You're exhausted.
Yes,
I am.
Why are you doing this?
I have to. I just have to.
Eyes.
Mom. Mom...
Uh, a cow.
It's not a cow.
It's a bird.
We should go. I promised
I'd help her with some stuff.
: I think
he has a crush on you.
Shhh.
Nicholas.
Mom, can I have
some ice cream?
Will you be cold?
No.
Okay.
Get some for him too.
But hurry. Be quick, okay?
Eyes.
Head.
Spine.
Chest.
Can I have some?
Sure.
Mmm.
You can have it if you want.
Oh. Thank you."Speciva."
"Speciva."
That was nice.
My mom's a great singer.
Ask her to sing.
No!
Yes.
No, I haven't sung in ages.
I'm not singing.
It's a lie. Nicholas told us
everything.
No.
Ask her.
Mom, come on.
Show them how good you are.
Make me proud.
All right. I'll do it for you.
Uh...
you won't know this one,
but Nicholas likes it, so...
I am a poor wayfaring stranger
Travelling through...
This world of woe
There is no trouble...
Nor toil nor danger
In that bright land...
To where I go
I'm going there...
To see my mother
No more to roam
I'm just
A-going over Jordan
I'm just a-going
Over home
Ahem.
So beautiful.
Mountains.
Yes.
Yes. Yes, they are beautiful.
But I prefer flats.
And forests. I like trees.
Touching trees.
Is it flat
where you come from?
Yeah. Only chimneys
and factories.
First time I saw mountains,
I was old as Nicholas --
maybe eight, nine.
I went on vacation in Caucasus
and I saw some peaks in clouds.
I thought I could touch the sky
too if I got there.
And did you?
Oh, no! It's not
so easy.
Where did you learn
your English?
I was in England, a few times.
And in India,
nobody speaks Russian.
Too bad.
It's such a pretty language.
Like music.
Say something else in Russian.
What does that mean?
I don't understand.
I know a little bit of Polish,
but I don't speak Russian,
so tell me
what it means.
It means you are...
very special.
Beautiful, too. Thank you.
No, no, no, no... No,
it's... it's...
you who would...
All that you've done for me,
for Nick, for all these people, it's...
me that has to thank you.
Please, no.
Please.
Why are you so..?
Who's my favourite boy?
'Morning.
I was looking for Alexy.
He just left
for Warsaw to catch a flight
to India.
India.
I... But I... I thought you said
that he was leaving later today.
I wanted to say goodbye.
He left at dawn.
He often does it. Makes up his
mind at the last moment,
packs up and off he goes.
And Nicholas did not teach me
how to...
play baseball.
No.
Uh... could you give this to him
from me?
You know he doesn't take anything.
No, no, no.
It's just a shirt, okay?
The one that he wears all the
time is about to fall apart
and I thought that--
A shirt?
No, I don't think there will be
any problem with a shirt.
: I put our address
in Canada inside, just in case.
Could you make sure
that he gets that?
Sure. We'll send it to him.
Maybe they missed the flight.
I hope not.
There... there they are!
Look! Look!
Oh, yeah! Oh!
Grandpa!
Hello.
: We missed you so much.
We missed you too.
Lots of stories to tell you.
I can't see you any bigger,
but you grew fatter.
Three and half pounds!
They lost our bags.
Hi.
Hi, Nicholas.
Hi, Nicole.
Thanks for coming, Dad.
I missed you more.
They lost our bags.
That's why we were so late.
Let's go.
You go to my place
or yours?
I guess it'll be better
if we stay together for a while.
All right, then.
I love you, Julie.
You saved our son.
It wasn't me.
It was Alexy who saved him.
Well, then, I love him too.
Dad looks terrible.
His beloved Bogusha dumped
him. Met some other Polish guy.
A bit younger, I gather.
Dad, you have to open the door
to get through it.
Honey, what are you doing?
I check myself in the mirror
every night
to make sure
I don't catch cancer.
You can't catch cancer.
It's not a contagious disease.
But we're twins.
Doesn't matter.
You're separate people.
And anyway, you can't catch something
that's gone. It doesn't exist.
Nicholas isn't sick anymore.
You understand?
Yeah.
Tonight, can you put Nicholas's
bed right next to mine
when he goes to sleep?
Okay.
Aren't you gonna say good night
to Nurnies?
She must be downstairs
with Nicholas.
Okay.
What's it gonna be? Ah!
So how was it?
It was great.
I really liked it there.
And the man?
The healer.
Alexy?
Yes, Alexy.
How many times did you see him?
Hundreds of times.
And millions of people
stand in line to wait for him.
And he chose me.
What do you mean,
he chose you?
He saw us in a big crowd,
me and Mom,
and he told us to come first.
He was so nice to me and Mom.
Really.
He made dates with her.
All the time.
Like what kind of dates?
What did they do?
He can do anything he wants.
Once, he brung this man
who weighed over 400 pounds,
and lifted him over his head
with one hand. Like this.
But what did he do to you?
His hands were hot.
And he never gave you nothing?
He never gave you any...
any, like, pills or...
herbs or... nothing?
I want to send a video on how
to play baseball to Piotr, okay?
Yeah, we can do that.
I missed you so much, Julie.
Do you know that?
Come back to me.
You're gonna have to give me
some time to get used to all this.
You smell different.
There's something different
about you. I can feel it.
It's him, isn't it?
I don't... I don't even know
how to describe it.
It's so... different.
It's... it's unreal.
I don't even know if he's...
interested in our world,
in normal feelings and women.
Probably a good thing.
I'm sure there's an awful lot
of women
that would like to show
their gratitude.
It could be a coincidence.
There are cases
of spontaneous remission.
Are you sure the Russian man
only touched him?
No tumour.
Dad!
Dad, what is going on?
I've been calling you now
for three days.
Why'd you throw it back?
I didn't like her face.
Stupid snout.
You okay?
I'm... okay.
I just drunk... too much.
You were right. This Bogusha,
she was an ordinary bitch.
But she did me good.
She...
made him stand up.
And she saved Nick.
So, you know,
everything makes sense.
Hello?
Alexy.
I know that it's you.
I can hear your breath.
Say something.
Say anything.
Where are you?
Are you still there?
Please, just...
just tell me what to do.
I'll do whatever
you want me to do.
Where are--
We can't go on like this.
I'm just gonna take the kids
and go to my sister's.
Henry...
I don't... know--
You shouldn't
say anything yet.
Just take your time
and think about it.
And I will do the same.
Ah, Julie,
I love you so much.
I know.
I've disappointed you.
I can see it in your eyes.
What do you want me to say?
No, I'm not talking
about my affair.
I feel I've disappointed you
in a...
global sense.
Say something.
We've been through
a very difficult period.
It's a generic answer, Julie.
I think I deserve
a little better than that.
You used to look at me
with some kind of, uh...
I dunno --
pride.
It's gone, though.
I'm so confused.
Why?
I think he needs me.
Is it because you feel
that... that you owe him
for...
for Nick?
No, it's not like that at all.
It's, uh...
It's more.
Well, I... I don't think
I could hear it.
I think we both need a little
time. I need a little time.
I'm just gonna go
and get the kids.
Julia!
Julie!
I'm here.
You came.
The turn is two clicks
off the main road,
and up the hill...
Is it the only house up there?
Right, right. And the key
is under the mat. I got that.
Monica, I don't know
how to thank you.
What? It's breaking up.
She's gone.
Careful!
Hey, I'm an excellent driver.
Okay?
I am sorry. Um, for me,
it is all too complicated, this car.
I don't understand it.
Nick'll explain it to you.
You should learn how to drive
anyway.
We will see. We'll see.
Don't be afraid.
I'll teach you.
I'll teach you everything.
The key under the mat.
It's easy.
Slowly. Slowly.
Okay?
Hi, Rebecca.
Hi, guys. This is Julie.
Uh, Henry, um, I'm up
at Monica's cabin for a while.
I'll probably stay here
a couple of days
and, uh, the phone... Well,
there is no phone in the cabin
and the cell phone's
not working, so...
I guess I'll just call you back.
Okay.
Bye.
See this dog?
My father had one just like her.
It was his favourite.
When I was seven,
he got an ulcer on his head.
The veterinarian
wanted to put him to sleep,
but I knew I could help him.
How did you know?
Just felt it.
This kind of urge
that I had to do it,
because I had this power.
As a matter of fact,
the dog
was my first real patient.
I took his head in my hands
and he was healed, in no time.
After I saved the dog,
my father
didn't beat me anymore.
Even though I was still
a lousy pupil at school.
The dog is still alive.
My father,
he is dead, but the dog
is still running around.
How old is he?
Forty-three years old.
You liar!
I can't believe
a word that you say.
And then, at the asylum,
the same thing happened
Iike when I was little boy.
The director
called a specialist
from a parapsychological institute
and they start to make this test
with me.
Was it terrible?
Oh, no, it was not horrible.
Just, I, uh...
Iosing time.
Then they see my gifts,
so they started to send me
to different big shots
Yeah, politicals, yes?
So I cured them and theirwives
and their mothers-in-law
and... And one of them arranged
passport for me, so I went abroad
and I started to healing people
all the time.
I travelled and healed, travelled
and healed -- all the time.
That was my life.
Do you regret?
What?
Things you had before.
Before you met me.
Oh, no.
I have nothing before you.
Nothing.
Julie?
And the children?
You know Nicholas
is already very fond of you.
They'll love you.
It's impossible not to love you.
It's that I am not sure
if you love me
because Nicholas recovered
or is it because it's me.
How can you be so stupid?
Julie.
Mm.
What kind of life
you can have with me?
We'll travel to England.
You can heal all those mad cows.
We'll make a fortune.
No, I don't want to do it more.
I want to be with you.
Always.
And me with you.
I'll wrap you up in my big coat.
Then no one can get at you.
You wanna drive?
Absolutely not.
What the hell
are you doing?!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You have to stop this!
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
Get off!
Police!
Alexy!
Police. Stop!
What's going on here, guys?
What do you think you're doing?
Where are you going, cowboy?
What are you doing?
Aren't you gonna take
the other guy?
He started it.
Stay out of this.
Let's go. Come on, up you go.
Come on.
I... I can't believe this.
Easy, easy.
Don't fight, don't fight them.
Why did you run?
Uniforms still scare me.
Stupid old fears.
I think I'm pregnant with you.
Where's he from?
Fucking planet Russia.
Oh. No kidding.
A spy.
Or an asshole terrorist.
Why are you so rude to us?
I'm a Canadian citizen,
he's my guest.
Profession?
Oh...
uh, what you do. Job.
Oh, uh, magnetizer.
What the hell is that?
I... I cure people
with my hands.
No profession.
But you resisted arrest, Magneto.
It's an indictable offence.
You could be looking at deportation.
I can't fucking believe this.
I'm gonna call someone!
I'll call the fucking news! All right?
Are you listening to me?
He didn't fucking do anything!
Where... where's the other guy?
I mean, this was just a fight!
For God's sake. Get-get-get-get
your fucking hands off me!
Hi, it's me again.
Uh, God, you guys
are really busy, heh?
Well, I hope you're all good.
Uh, I'm gonna try to make it
back before you get there, so...
Um, God, Henry, we should talk.
Well, I love you all. Bye.
Hello.
My God!
They let you out!
Yeah.
The guy didn't press charges!
No...
I guess he and the dog
made up.
I didn't know
you were such a good fighter.
Oh, ah, I had to defend myself
at the hospital!
You're very, very brave.
You are the bravest.
You were fighting inside!
No.
Very good.
Those guys were assholes!
I swear, I'd fucking kill 'em!
This is... right here,
the healer is vulnerable.
No. No...
See, where those people
come up and touch your head,
all they have to do
is come up and tickle you.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
With the twins,
I knew the next day.
Is it twins?
God, I hope... I hope not!
I want three.
I said three children, not four.
I said three. I want three.
Don't work any magic.
When I walk the streets
the people I meet
Say hello what's up
And then I say
My name is Alexy
I'm having a baby
And I am in love with you...
Nicole...
Nicole, what are you...
what are you doing here?
You don't have to be back
till Sunday.
What happened?
Then it started walking away.
Of course, Shasta followed it.
It led him right to the tombs
and out of the desert
onto the side of them.
Hey.
Mom...
Don't be mad at me.
Don't be silly.
When?
Yesterday.
He woke up
with a really high fever,
so we came in.
Had a lot of tests yesterday,
huh, buddy boy?
It came back.
Come on, open your shirt.
Okay.
Hi, Alexy.
What's he doing here?
I'll explain later.
Where's he gone?
Do you want me
to leave the room?
They're cold.
Would you try again? Please.
Please try again.
I sorry.
Mom?
Yes, baby.
I don't want
the chemo anymore.
Okay?
We'll do whatever you want.
We'll go home,
we'll stay together.
Just don't be afraid.
I'm not. Really.
And you don't be afraid either.
Okay?
All right.
Okay.
Promise?
I promise.
His snoring is so funny,
isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Mom?
Will you sing me something?
Of course
I'll sing you something.
I am a poor...
Wayfaring stranger
Travelling through...
This world of woe
There is no trouble
Toil nor danger
In that bright land
To where I go
I'm going there
To see my mother
No more to roam
I'm just a-going over Jordan
I'm just a-going over home
How's the baby?
I can feel him kicking.
You guys want more?
Nope. We're full.
Do you feel all right?
Yeah...
War.
Three.
Flip.
Hey!
You cheated. We're not supposed
to use clubs.
Don't you remember? We made a deal.
We have to play clubs.
You're absolutely right,
except it's Sunday.
So what?
The deal was we don't
play clubs on Sundays.
Those who demand clubs
will be severely punished.
You're absolutely right.
But don't forget,
anybody named Nicholas
has the right to change the rules
everyfirst Sunday of the month.
But today
is the second Sunday.
Look out the window
and you'll see it's the first one.
If the bells tinkle 14 times
before a new bird sits on a branch,
you'll win.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
I see a big one...
Those feeders you put
on the trees are not working.
All the big birds keep chasing
all the little birds away.
Well, we're just gonna have
to do something about that.
Mm-hm.
Is that all? Is that all--
No, that's not all.
...that you've done today?
Show me.
No.
You haven't done anything.
what have you been doing here?
Just been sitting in here
all morning...
daydreaming.
You smell nice.