( Bird chirps)
( beeps )
Man: And we're rolling, sir.
( Birds chirping )
Note that this time, the X0-359
had a spontaneous reaction
to the impurities released
by the cigarette smoke.
This is-- this is very good.
This is a very good sign
of progress.
( Beeping )
My God.
Carbon monoxide, zero.
Ammonia, zero.
Nitrogen dioxide, zero.
All airborne impurities
were completely eliminated
in a matter of seconds.
This is...
This is astonishing.
The plant has created pure air.
( Groans )
I don'! know, okay?
It doesn't look like
anyone's dumping today.
I thought you were committed
to catching these polluters,
Mr. Not-Gonna-Happen-On-My-Watch.
Yeah, I am.
I am.
But that was before
my leg fell asleep
and my obsessive girlfriend
deprived me of food.
Some bastard
is egregiously polluting
this mine with toxic waste.
Look, if we don't catch them
in the act, Joe,
they're gonna ruin
this whole area.
There'll be acidic seepage
in the drinking water,
and wildlife
will start dying off, and--
I know, I know.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Joe: I don't know
what I was thinking.
- ( Vehicle approaching )
- Hey, we've got company.
( Unzips bag )
Joe:
We got you now, buddy.
( Beeps )
( birds chirping )
Woman:
He looks nervous.
Here, come on.
Kyle.
It's good to see you again.
Joe: Aguy in a suit
coming out of a mine?
You gotta be kidding me.
Something's wrong
with this picture, all right.
You came alone, right?
( Scoffs )
What does it look like?
Keep focused, Kyle.
The sooner you show me the product,
the sooner we can get out of here.
- That the money?
- 'Course.
Show me.
This guy's definitely
not dumping waste.
Well, whatever's going on
doesn't look kosher.
You think it's drugs?
We'll see soon enough.
Now you show me something.
Relax.
It's a demonstration.
(grunting )
Why'd that guy cut himself?
M-maybe this is, like,
some secret cult gathering
or something.
I doubt that.
That guy in a suit
looks like a federal agent.
I'm impressed.
Do you have the seed?
Wait here.
Whoa.
- There's a sniper up there.
- Where?
Right there
on the platform.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
He spotted us.
Man on radio:
Sir, I've got eyes on two bogeys.
- Where?
- 10:00, behind the concrete block.
(grunts)
Who are your friends, Kyle?
Oh, my Revs-
You trying to set us up?
What are you talking about?
- You wearing a wire?
- No.
Let me go.
Give me the seed.
Joe:
He's not looking.
Whoa.
All right, let's get out of here.
Man on radio:
Sir, they're on the move.
Do I take them out?
KY leg
Man on radio:
Take out primary target.
( Panting )
- ( gunshot, yells)
- Was that a gunshot?
( gasps )
Oh, my God.
They shot him.
( Groans )
(ground vibrating )
What is that?
Joe: An earthquake.
What?
(grunts)
Woman:
Let's get out of here!
(yells)
Ah-- slower, please.
You might damage
the specimen.
There you are.
Aren't you remarkably
well-preserved?
Specimen 37 is bell-shaped.
Slightly charred.
With signs of extensive hydrolysis.
Preliminary analysis
leads me to believe
it's Helianthus annuus.
Another sunflower seed.
Look, I don't see anything.
Oh, my God.
That was crazy.
Joe, what the heck
was that?
I don't know. I've never seen
anything like that before.
It looked like some kind of
giant root, right?
I don't know.
But whatever just happened,
people have to know about it.
( Helicopter approaching )
Well, it looks like
someone's on it.
(ground rumbling)
You gotta be kidding me.
Joe: Watch out.
Get in the car.
Joe: Kate!
Joe:
Kate, get in the car!
Kate, get in the car.
Now!
( Birds chirping )
Sir...
Noel, I've asked you
to move slowly
when you're in the garden.
Plants are very sensitive.
Sir, you need
to see the news.
Newscaster:
You are seeing live footage
of what appear to be
gigantic roots
devastating the remote deserts
of Nevada.
I just verified one of
the seed stock is missing.
And I couldn't find Kyle.
He's not on the premises.
Damn him.
Those seeds weren't ready
to be released
into an uncontrolled
environment.
(thunder rumbling)
Woman:
Who are these guys?
Where do they think
they're going?
Woman: Hey, buddy.
No, stop!
( Researchers clamoring )
Man:
Hey, what are you doing?
Slop!
What do you think you're doing?
You just trampled over
a prehistoric refuse pit.
Isn't it an old garbage dump?
Very old.
Dr. Stein, I'm Special Agent
Jack Tompkins.
We need you to come with us.
It's a matter of national security.
National security?
Are you kidding?
- Did I do something wrong?
- Please get in the car.
We don't have
much time to waste.
Are you sure
you have the right Dr. Stein?
I study plant remains.
You may have knowledge pertaining
to a geological catastrophe
unfolding in Nevada.
Now will you please
get in the car?
Jeremy Frame
and Matthew Kyle.
When's the last time
you had contact
with either one
of these gentlemen?
Three years ago.
Dr. Frame hired Kyle
and I to work on
a seed excavation in Turkey.
What kind of seeds?
I don't understand.
What does this have to do
with a geological disaster?
We have reason to believe
this disaster could be man-made.
Well, which is it?
Geological or man-made?
Could be both.
What kind of seeds?
Seeds from the Garden of Eden.
As in...
- the Garden of Eden.
- That's right.
You seriously believe
such seeds can exist?
I wouldn't have spent my time
looking for them if I didn't.
Okay.
Frame found lost passages
in the Dead Sea Scrolls
indicating that,
after Adam and Eve
were banished
from the garden,
Adam stole seeds in an urn
to replant a new garden.
But a flood hit
and the seeds were lost.
Stein: So Frame
got funding for me to dig
in an unmapped area
below the 11,000-year-old site
of Gobekli Tepe,
the prehistoric temple believed
to be the location of Eden.
( Men speaking
in foreign language)
I think we found something.
Kyle:
An intact Neolithic vessel.
- This is amazing.
-( rattling )
Aren't you dying
to take a quick peek?
Don't even think about it, Kyle.
This can only be opened
in an airtight lab.
( Rattling continues)
Unbelievable.
(phone ringing)
Stern: One week later,
I got a call from Frame.
( Staticky voices )
Frame: Jocelyn, I'm afraid
we have some bad news.
We've lost our funding.
Why? What about the urn?
Frame: The um was empty.
There was nothing inside.
But there was.
I heard something.
It was just...
chipped pottery.
Frame:
I'm truly sorry.
Where's Frame now?
I have no idea.
He's a bit of a recluse.
I never knew
where he was based.
Do you know what Frame was planning
on doing with these seeds?
Recreate the Garden of Eden.
(thunder crashing )
Oh, man.
This isn't good.
No.
Now what?
(ground rumbling)
Joe.
You're in danger!
Go!
Get out of here now!
Get in, get in.
Hold on.
- What are you doing?
- Just hold on.
Kate:
Joe, where are you going?
This is crazy.
(tires squealing )
( people clamoring )
(yelling )
( door closes )
What agency is this?
- Welcome to SCOPE.
- SCOPE?
- Never heard of it.
- We keep a low profile.
Our mandate
is to investigate threats
that fall outside the scope
of known science.
Hence the catchy name.
( Office workers chattering )
Man: Got new data from Skynet 2
and Skynet 3.
- ( Phone beeping )
- You're gonna have to put that away.
Got real-time satellite imagery.
Tompkins: You're looking at infrared
of Pershing County, Nevada.
This is what's going on
right now?
Stein:
What is it?
Tompkins: Our recon discovered
massive root growth,
spreading at a rate
of up to 30 miles per hour,
destroying everything in its path
as we speak.
And you think Kyle and Frame
are responsible for this?
Yes, we do.
Dr. Stein,
I'm Director Wilson.
We picked up information
that Frame was conducting
what sounded like
a preposterous experiment.
Recreating the Garden of Eden
using prehistoric seeds
from the original garden
in order to sanitize the planet.
How did you
get this information?
Our intel picked up
correspondence
between Kyle
and an interested party.
Seems your buddy's
trying to sell those ancient seeds
on the black market.
Well, that's impossible.
We never found the seeds.
Unless--
Tompkins:
So Frame lied to you.
Any idea why he'd want you
off the project?
I don't know.
Where's Kyle?
We don't know where he is.
But we are pursuing leads
to his whereabouts.
And what about Frame?
Well, we haven't
found him yet.
His so-called
Garden of Eden
was being developed
in a secret location
somewhere in Nevada.
- ( Camera whirrs)
- Joe's voice: Kate, get in the car.
Oh, my God.
This...
This is surreal.
- What are those things?
- I don't know.
I don't know. I can't believe we
just saw all those people get killed.
We need to go
to the authorities and tell them
what we saw happen
at the mine.
Look.
We're not going
to the authorities, okay?
Those guys we saw at the mine,
they looked like Feds.
So what if this is some
government test gone haywire?
I mean, what happens to us
when powerful people
try to cover their tracks?
A lot of people
are getting killed.
So until we know
who's involved,
we don't know
who we can trust.
Okay.
If we do this,
we go all the way.
- Whatever it takes.
- Yep.
(sighs)
All right, the first thing
we need to do
is we need to figure out
where that van came from.
( Camera whirrs )
Kate:
I have an idea.
What do you want from me?
I'm not saying
we buy into this whole
"Garden of Eden" thing.
But if these seeds,
in fact, are prehistoric
and have something
to do with it,
we need to know.
And right now
you are our only lead.
( Workers chattering )
Incredible.
I've never seen
a root system develop
on such a massive scale before.
Yeah, well,
you're not alone.
At least the outbreak
is in a remote area.
Now, break it down for me.
Give it to me in science-ese.
Tompkins:
Talk to me like I'm five.
A scientific explanation
for what's happening.
I warned Frame
there was a danger
to awakening
a prehistoric plant
in today's toxic world.
Stein: I don't have
an explanation yet, but...
(sighs)
you can't ignore the warnings
in the Bible.
And I can't formulate
a game plan
for fighting a disaster
based on a fable.
The Bible may be a fable to you,
Agent Tompkins,
but archeologists have found
evidence that events it depicts
have actually occurred
throughout history.
Jack, there's
a new development.
You need to see this.
G-L-9-4-3-X.
- What's that?
- License plate.
- Kate: On the van.
- Yeah? Really?
Okay, well...
now we need someone
to hack into the DMV.
Both: Spit.
Wilson:
We were lucky until now,
but the growth just picked up speed
near Pyramid Lake.
In less than three hours,
this disaster's gonna hit
its first major city.
Bob, Reno needs
to be evacuated.
- That's not your call, Jack.
- Well, then call the President.
This thing is destroying
everything in its path.
The fatalities are gonna
be staggering, Bob.
Okay,
we're talking about evacuating
half a million people
in a matter of hours.
Wilson:
It can't be done.
You wanna save these people?
Stop the damn roots.
( Door slams )
I :Pit!
Pit!
- Spit, buddy. You in there?
- You there?
Hope the air in there
is breathable this time.
Yeah, don't count on it.
Spit.
HEY-
Hey, man.
What are you guys doing here?
Don't you know what's going on?
Have you seen the freakin' news?
Yeah, yeah. We know, man.
We need your help.
We need you
to track a plate for us.
Tompkins:
Listen, we're running out of time.
This thing is effectively
still just a plant, right?
So why don't we kill it
like you would a weed?
Dump a bunch
of herbicide on it?
Herbicides work too slowly.
The feeder roots
are growing too fast and we'd need
thousands of gallons immediately.
What's a feeder root?
It's the root tip,
where the growth occurs.
So if we cut the root tips
leading to this thing,
we can stop its growth.
It could cripple
the entire system.
That's what we'll do.
Sever the root tip.
We'd launch a surgical air strike,
- we knock this thing out.
- There's a catch.
If the root recovers,
you risk having it regrow...
and multiply.
We don't have a choice.
Get me the President.
( Cat meowing )
We don't have much time here, Spit.
You in yet?
Give me a minute, man.
(ground rumbles)
Oh, my God.
Kate:
Joe, you feel that, right?
Okay, come on, Spit, man.
Let's go. It's coming.
I'm offline.
I lost connection.
- Well, we gotta go now.
- No, we need that address.
Can you get back on?
( Mewing )
- Oh-- cable got knocked out.
- Yes.
Okay, we have
to leave right now.
Seconds away.
Come on.
We're running out of time.
- I'm in.
- Here.
The plate number.
( Keyboard clicking )
G-L-9-4-3-X. Come on.
Kate: Hurry, Spit.
Spit: Almost there, Katie.
Just a few seconds.
Come on, come on.
There's your registrant
and address.
- Alamut Corp Industries.
- Got it.
( Panting )
( gasps )
- Let's take my truck.
- Go.
Wait.
I've got to get my cat, man.
- No, no, no! No!
- No!
- Whoa.
- Spit!
Whoa!
Spit.
- Get in the truck.
- Kate: Okay.
This is Ace One.
We're 10 miles out
and coming in low with 3-6-0.
Joe, look.
Joe: Oh, my God.
I think they're
gonna bomb it.
We gotta get out of here.
Pilot on radio:
Approaching targets. ETA 60 seconds.
Initiating separation.
Kate:
This doesn't look good.
We're right
in their line of fire.
We have visual confirmation
on target.
Going weapons hot.
Engaging in 20 seconds.
Can't this thing go any faster?
This thing's
an old piece of crap.
Joe:
I'm flooring it already.
I have missile lock.
Pilot:
Firing in five, four,
three, two, one.
Engage.
Oh, my God.
They've fired.
- Drive faster!
- I'm trying to!
Pilot:
Command, we have a direct hit.
Waiting for debris to clear
to verify destruction of targets.
Have visual verification.
Targets destroyed.
I repeat, targets destroyed.
( Cheering )
Wilson:
Okay, that's a kill.
Good work, everyone.
- Nicely done.
- Nice work, Jack.
Poor Spit.
All right.
We're gonna get these bastards.
All right?
Joe:
Whoever caused this.
( Computer beeping )
Jack?
Look at the screen.
Patch me through
to the lead pilot.
( Man dials)
Here, sir.
- This is Director Wilson speaking.
- Pilot: Yes, sir.
I need another visual confirmation
of the target's destruction.
Roger, sir.
Give us a moment to double back.
Slow down, Joe.
There's a driveway ahead.
Joe: Is this it?
I don't see an address.
That's got to be it, Joe.
There's nothing else
around here.
All right, well,
let's go down the road.
See if we can find a way
to sneak in.
Approaching visual range.
Pilot: Target remains.
I repeat, target remains.
Sir, I've got eyes
on multiple targets now.
Pilot:
This thing is spreading.
Stein:
It's been burrowing.
It's regenerating exponentially.
Not only that.
Look at where it's headed.
Right here.
Sir, confirming new target
inbound on Carson City.
Okay, engage target.
I repeat, you blast that monstrosity
with everything you've got.
Roger, sir.
Changing vector.
Pilot: ETA one minute
to new target.
The bombing isn't working.
It's only making it worse.
Stern:
You have to stop them.
Pilot:
Going weapons hot.
45 seconds out.
Baker and Charlie,
follow my lead to picking targets.
Pilot #2: Roger.
Target confirmed.
You gotta cancel this, Bob.
- Are you questioning me?
- Nope.
But she's right.
If we bomb this thing again,
it's just gonna get bigger.
We gotta think
this thing through.
This thing is headed here.
I don't know how much time we've got
to think it through.
Pilot: Eagle flight.
Entering debris cloud.
- Pilot: Visibility near zero.
- Bob...
We've got multiple bogeys
on radar.
Command,
Eagle Baker is down!
I repeat,
Eagle One, clarify.
It's this debris cloud, sir.
Sir, the roots
are erupting all around us
and they are massive.
Command,
Eagle Charlie is down.
I repeat,
Eagle Charlie is down!
Pilot: Command, I've got too many
bogeys to complete the mission.
Okay, abort mission.
I repeat, abort mission.
Roger.
I'm getting out of here.
Oh, my God.
No!
Woman:
Eagle One, come in.
( Static )
Woman:
Eagle One, come in.
( Static continues )
Woman: Eagle One,
confirm status.
All right, we gotta get
out of harm's way.
Is there any way to predict
this thing's movement?
Growing roots usually take
the path of least resistance.
We'd be safer
at a higher elevation.
All right, let's move.
Okay, people.
Pack it up.
I'm calling a full evacuation.
Head for the transports.
We're moving out.
( Chattering )
This has to be it.
They really
don't want visitors, do they?
- Yeah. That's barbed wire.
- Here.
Here we go.
Here, I'll lift you up.
Okay, ready?
One, two, three.
(grunting )
Noel, we have trespassers
at the northwest perimeter.
Frame: At C Gate.
I'll get security on it
right away, sir.
(ground rumbling)
Oh, my God.
( gasps )
Wha-.
Joe?
God.
All right, go! Go!
Get off the fence!
Get off!
Okay.
Watch out.
(alarm blaring )
Man on P.A.:
Please evacuate the facility.
Follow the exit path.
Get down!
Kate: Joe!
(yells)
Kate:
Joe, it's coming.
(alarm continues)
Wilson: Jack!
- Joe, hurry!
- ( grunts)
Kate: Get up there!
' ( Yells )
- Joe!
Kate, get out of here.
Go! Kate, go!
I'm not leaving you.
Hang on, Joe.
Jack!
Follow Datsun and stay low.
- Datsun!
- Dr. Stein, come on!
Kate:
Joe, Joe!
You gotta get up there, now.
Joe, are you okay?
Yeah.
That's weird.
It just suddenly stopped.
Yeah.
What do you think
that means?
I don't know.
But let's not stick around
in case it starts again.
Okay.
(distant rumbling )
- What happened?
- Incredible.
The growth was diverted.
Our garden has repelled
the hostile roots.
Held them back.
- Noel: But they're still spreading.
- Frame: Yes.
They're in a hypermetabolic state.
If I can find a way to reduce
the rate of cell division,
I can slow them down,
control them.
Like the plants
in our garden.
Frame: This work must
not be disturbed,
so you must be sure
to secure the grounds.
It's only a matter of time
before others discover
this is the only safe haven
in the country.
Woman on radio: Remote base
should be up and running in 20 minutes.
Copy that.
ETA 20 minutes.
Mobile unit's waiting for us
40 miles north up the mountain.
Is that elevation
gonna be high enough?
It should be.
- Any idea what our casualties were?
- Tompkins: Substantial.
Doctor, I need to know everything
you know about these seeds.
Is there anything in the Bible,
the Dead Sea Scrolls,
anything at all that can help us
fight this disaster?
There is a warning in the Bible.
From the Book of Isaiah.
"The earth mourns
and withers,
befouled by its
inhabitants.
Hence a curse
devours the earth,
and those who live upon it."
How does that apply to us?
What does that mean exactly?
Are you starting to get
your faith back, Jack?
I don't hear our science agencies
coming up with any answers.
The seeds are from Eden,
a time when the earth was pure.
Stein:
Before pollution.
I think the Bible was warning us
to take care of Mother Earth
or face her wrath.
What are you saying?
That's why they regenerated
into something bigger
after we bombed them.
Right. The more toxins we throw at it,
the bigger it's gonna get.
To cleanse the earth.
We're not gonna beat this thing
by fighting it head-on.
We gotta find an angle.
Well, the answers
we need are in there.
You see an entrance?
Joe: Bingo.
Guard on walkie-talkie:
Copy that, Team 2.
- Come here, come here.
- What?
There's someone out there.
Guard on walkie-talkie:
Team one, check in.
- Team, go on to zone five.
- Kate: He's got a gun.
- He's coming this way.
- Really?
Yeah.
( Branch snaps )
Go, go.
Now!
- Whoa!
Go, go, go, go!
Why are they shooting at us?
I don't know.
You wanna stop and ask them?
Doctor, the chopper
will be here soon.
That'll give us a better look
than that satellite imagery.
They just confirmed, sir.
Man:
Reno's being devastated.
Jack, look.
The root growth has been destroying
everything in its path.
Except here.
Why would it skip this area?
It's the same elevation as
everything else it's destroyed, right?
Good question.
- We need to go there and find out.
- Right.
I think we've got something here.
Understood.
Doesn't matter.
We're moving on.
- Changing course.
- Changing course?
Operation Safeguard's in effect.
- Sir?
- What is Operation Safeguard?
It's the evacuation
of all Cabinet personnel
to a fallout shelter
in the Colorado mountains.
Don't you think that's a bit premature?
This crisis has just begun.
The President's science advisors
ran computer simulations.
In one week, the whole country
will be consumed.
And in 24 hours,
Cheyenne Mountain
and Colorado
will be inaccessible.
Okay, that gives us
24 hours to fight it.
That's exactly what I and the
Administration will be doing.
But from the safety
of the shelter.
We need to protect the executive branch
of government.
- You know that.
- Look.
The destruction has skipped
this entire area for some reason.
We need to get there,
find out why.
It might hold the answer
on how to stop this thing.
And what if it doesn't?
What then?
It's a waste of precious time.
Hiding in the mountains.
That's a better use of our time.
The plan is to get out of harm's way
until we can come up with a solution.
That's absurd.
On whose orders?
The President's.
We've been assigned to join the team
at Cheyenne Mountain.
Military transport
will be here in 30 minutes.
You can choose to be on it
or you can risk your life on a hunch.
Your choice.
Dr. Stein, you're
more than welcome to join us.
After all, we need
to protect great minds.
( Groans )
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Joe, what...
Whoa.
Kate: It's beautiful.
What-- what is this place?
What do you think
they're hiding?
Something they don'!
want us to find.
Not if they're shooting at us.
Maybe we should leave, Joe.
- This is getting dangerous.
- ( groans )
You're bleeding.
Oh, my God.
You're shot.
It's just a graze.
Don't worry about it.
No, that looks serious, Joe.
You need medical attention.
Yeah, well, that's not
gonna happen.
Besides, I'm not leaving until we
get proof to nail these guys.
Okay?
Okay.
Try to stop the bleeding
with this.
- Okay.
- You're no good to me if you're dead.
( Chuckles )
- ( branches snapping )
- ( voices overlapping )
Okay, we gotta lose these guys.
Let's go.
( Groans )
You want to explain to me
what's going on, Bob?
As far as I know, our responsibility
is to protect this country,
regardless of the risks.
We were trying
to protect this country.
What are you talking about?
- We screwed up today, Jack.
- What do you mean "we"?
SCOPE had a covert team
in the field
when this thing went haywire.
What were they doing out there?
Securing the seeds from Kyle.
You're kidding me.
Those seeds
are a security threat.
Once we had credible evidence
of their existence,
we had no choice
but to pursue possession of them.
Why wasn't I told about this?
I couldn't talk about it.
It was top secret.
Top secret?
Screw top secret.
You hid a vital piece of intel
when millions of people's lives
were at stake.
( Sighs )
Bob.
That's how the game's played, Jack.
You know that.
It's not a game.
There's real people out here
losing their lives.
Transport will be here
in 10 minutes.
You can still join us.
Give the President my regards.
- Where are you going?
- To clean up the mess you made.
(walkie-talkie chattering )
There's an answer here.
We just have to
find out what it is.
Couldn't agree more.
Where exactly are we going?
You're not coming.
This could be a one-way ticket.
I want you to stay here
and wait for the transport, okay?
- All right.
- You take care of your family, Datsun.
Thank you.
Good luck, Jack.
- Doctor.
- Be safe.
Tompkins:
Keep your head down.
This is where we're going.
Put your headset on.
Pilot: Stand by for lift off.
Tompkins: Copy that.
( Panting )
( groans )
Joe!
Hey, look.
We need to get you help.
Yeah, from who?
From those
trigger-happy lunatics?
Okay, maybe we can find
a first-aid kit somewhere.
Kate...
What's happening to me?
You're healing.
This doesn't make any sense.
How?
It's the leaf.
Something in the leaf
healed you.
- I can't believe it.
- Would you stop that?
Sorry. It hurts?