[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Cell Phone Beeps ]
Hi. It's me. Um--
I know you're in Arizona
for the wedding,
but I really need--
I just wanna talk to you.
Okay? So can you please
call me back?
[ Beeps ]
[ Crickets Chirping ]
[ Man ]
Here in my arms
All my dreams come true
And we could watch
[ Man On P.A. ]
Okay, everybody.
Let's get on the dance floor
for that Minnesota
bride and groom,
Mr. and Mrs. Scott Thomas.
Hold tight
all night through
[ Chattering ]
[ Man #2 ]
What do you think?
Oh, my sweet baby
This is my best day ever.
No. Best day?
Mm-hmm.
It's pretty good.
Yeah. How about you?
Is it my best day ever?
Yeah.
Excluding the bachelor party,
right?
Well--
[ Chuckles ]
Of course it was.
I gotta be honest though.
I'm pretty open-minded about
talking about the honeymoon.
Really?
Yeah, I am.
You and me
and a bottle of red.
Deserted beach in Cabo.
I like the sound of that.
Me too.
Let's say good-bye
to our closest 75 friends
and family.
Who wants a shot, baby?
[ Laughs ]
Come on. Little tequila
for the bride and groom?
I'm still good
with champagne, Lumpy.
Yeah, maybe when this dance
is over. Okay?
[ Drums: Rock Intro ]
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
It's over.
[ Laughs ]
It sure is.
Come on. Come on.
You gotta celebrate, right?
Come on.
You only get married once.
You know, until you turn 40
and you trade in...
for the newer, sleeker,
better-looking models.
- I'm kidding.
- He's kidding.
- Okay, one time.
- All right!
- Oh!
- Oh, shit.
I thought you had--
My dress.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
Kristin, I'm really sorry.
I didn't--
I thought she was--
[ Man Rapping ]
Kristin insisted on
this destination wedding.
I would have loved
a Christmas wedding
in Minneapolis.
That would have
been lovely too.
But, you know,
I told her...
that it was gonna cost
everybody a fortune...
to fly down to Phoenix.
Honestly,
you can't even tell.
Will you button
the little buttons on the back?
Be careful.
You don't wanna rip
a $2,000 dress.
It was 3,000.
Does Scott know that?
Mm-mmm.
Man, I really, really hope
I didn't ruin her dress.
Oh, my God.
Would you stop it?
And even if you did,
when is she gonna
wear the thing again?
I like the way you think.
That is good.
[ Laughs ]
Oh.
Hey, man.
Thanks again for that loan.
Yeah. Sure, sure.
No, I-- I mean it.
That was too much.
Well, consider it
a wedding gift, okay?
Oh, what are you
talking about?
No. I'm paying you
back for that.
It was way too much.
No, I'm serious.
I didn't get you a wedding gift.
[ Chuckles ]
Take the cash.
I can't.
Take it.
Well--
Did you just kiss your tie?
No, I'm--
I've got drool.
Oh, that's charming.
Thank you.
You know the thing is--
[ Stammers ]
I need it.
I'll be honest with you.
It's embarrassing,
but I had no idea...
the honeymoon
was gonna cost so much,
and Rick screwed me so hard
on that commission.
Scotty, Scotty, Scotty.
Just stop.
I love you, man.
Oh, boy.
I do.
Okay.
Yeah, I do.
I wanna touch you.
Oh, come on.
I wanna get
my hands on you.
[ Laughing ]
Okay.
Is it too much?
That is too much.
All right.
I got carried away.
Just man up and drink,
would you?
What is this?
I'm not even sure
what it is.
Oh, my God.
You know,
I didn't say anything...
when Lumpy gargled champagne
during his toast...
or he decided to helicopter
a six-month-old
during the groom's dinner.
He kept referring to himself
as "The Baby Whisperer."
No. It's not funny.
The kid vomited mashed peas
all over the lobby.
We have to pay for that.
[ Pop Rock ]
Barkeep, another one.
[ Mutters ]
[ Man ]
Here she come now
Say Mony, Mony
Shoot 'em down, turn around
Come on, Mony
[ Laughs ]
Hey, she gimme love
and I feel all right now
[ Shouts ]
We gotta toss and turn
and feel all right
-   And I feel all right
I say yeah
-  [ Chorus ]  Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
'Cause you make me feel
Work it, Mony
So good
Work it,
Mony
So good
Work it, Mony
Work it,
Mony
So fine
Work it, Mony
Work it,
Mony
It's all right
Work it, Mony
Well, I feel all right
I said yeah
Yeah
[ Grunts ]
-   Yeah
Yeah, yeah
All right, I'm up.
All right. All right.
Yeah. Yeah.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
I love you, Mony, mo, mo, mo
Yes, I do
Say I do
Hey. Come on.
I-I'm all right.
I love you, Mony, mo, mo, mo
Say I do
Set 'em up!
Let's go.
Said I do
I love you, Mony,
mo, mo, mo
Lumpy, man.
Hey.
All right. All right.
Yeah.
Hey, buddy, I--
Why don't you
call it a night, man?
Hmm. What? What?
Time to pack it in.
What?
Yeah.
You're cutting off--
Dude.
You're cutting off
the best man?
Dude, come on.
You threw up
in the women's bathroom.
No, I didn't.
Did I?
You did.
One more drink.
No, no, no. Please.
Come on.
Aw! You're so lame.
You're just--
You're just lame.
No, all right.
Y-Y-You're lame.
You're lame-o.
All right. I know.
You're the lamest--
Ooh. Oh!
[ Groans ]
You okay?
Yes! Yeah!
I'm good. Yep.
Okay. Okay.
[ Sighs ]
Thanks a lot,
Captain Lame.
Captain Lame-o.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's great now.
Tomorrow morning it's...
gonna be another story.
[ Lumpy ]
Livin' in a lamish community,
churnin' up that lame butter.
Sorry.
[ Lumpy ]
Look out, everybody!
[ Singing With TV ]
I knew right
from the beginning
That you would
end up winning
I knew right
from the start
[ Pounding ]
[ Man ]
Shut up in there!
You shut up!
You put an arrow
through my heart
Through my heart
-   Round and round
- Oh, God!
[ Groans ]
With love we'll find a way
Just give it time
[ Alarm Bell Ringing ]
[ Fades ]
Round and round
[ Ringing Continues ]
[ Ringing Fades ]
[ Ragged Breathing ]
[ Glass Shatters ]
[ Groans ]
[ Water Running ]
Hmm.
[ Groaning ]
[ Door Shuts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Birds Twittering ]
[ Knocking ]
[ Woman ]
Come on. Get up.
- [ Knocking ]
- Ramsey, I'm not kidding.
You can't be late again.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Blinds Opening ]
[ Hoarse Voice ]
Get up.
I'm up.
What is your problem?
Give me one second.
And don't hassle
your mother.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I'm going to bed.
I don't know a Dave.
[ Footsteps ]
David? No.
[ Sighs ]
Danny?
My boss's name is Danny.
He might be a Gemini.
What kind of danger?
Hey, um,
you're gonna have to
try harder with Winston.
Where is he?
He went back to bed.
[ Scoffs ]
Oh.
I should go too.
Okay.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Bye.
[ Beep ]
[ Chuckles ]
Ms. Shirley?
She says that Dan's
in danger.
You know,
Dan from work.
I'm gonna tell him.
You should call her sometime.
[ Sighs ]
By the way,
you never told me
where you slept
the other night.
Why don't you ask
Ms. Shirley?
God, if you were
with some guy--
I was at a friend's house.
What friend?
Hey! Aren't you gonna
eat something?
I'm not hungry.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
That's it?
Sorry. I have to
get my day started.
Yeah, me too.
What?
I drove all the way up here
to see you.
Couldn't we at least
have breakfast?
Hang out a little?
It's a small town.
Hey.
Maybe I can arrange
a day off next week.
You know what?
Forget it.
[ Door Opens,
Closes ]
Jesus!
Hot date?
What are you doing here?
You know
I like to watch.
I hate it when
you pull the blinds, Dad.
[ Sighs ]
I'm not your dad.
Dad, father, father, dad--
Whatever.
I need 50 bucks.
I don't have 50 bucks.
This is really
your best option?
Blackmailing a priest?
Think of it
as community welfare.
Isn't there a doctor or a lawyer
you can hustle?
If you want me to go back
to taking it out
of the offering tray,
I will.
[ Sighs ]
[ Kristin ]
They just found him lying there?
Yeah. I don't know
what he was doing.
How--
I don't know.
A security camera caught him
going out the back door
at, like, 1:30.
There's blood
all over his room.
I- I don't know.
Hi, honey.
Everyone
is just devastated.
Is there anything
that Roger and I
could do for you?
No, I don't think so, Gail.
Thanks though.
Well, I don't mean
to upset you,
but this might be...
a liability here.
Mom, I don't think
that this is a good time.
You know, sweetheart,
you cannot be too careful.
The hotel
should take responsibility.
We could blame
the bartenders.
Have you two
eaten anything yet?
Uh, thank you, Dad.
We're not hungry.
The resort has a complimentary
continental breakfast.
[ Sighs ]
Could you guys
go say good-bye
to some of the guests?
Yes, we could, honey.
I think that would be
really helpful.
All right.
Yeah.
[ Chattering,
Indistinct ]
I'm sorry.
Wow.
I'm sorry
I don't have a referral
to another provider.
So there's
only one company
that can ship a body?
You could keep the deceased
in Arizona,
have the services here.
No, no, no.
The funeral and the burial
have to be in Minnesota.
Um--
Then I guess you're
out of options.
Really, Mr. Huxley?
There's nothing else?
'Cause I'm in
a tight spot here.
[ Exhales ]
Oh!
Oh, God! What the hell
are you doing?
Oh. Oh, uh--
He, um--
[ Stammers ]
Jesus Christ.
Can we go, please?
Oh, my God.
There are so many questions
I have for you.
There are so many things
I'm curious about.
But you know what?
I think it would be best...
if we just never talked
about that again.
Okay? Ever.
I think that's fine.
Great.
So let's go back to the hotel.
We'll pack our stuff up
and call the airline.
See if they can get us
on a redeye back
to Minneapolis.
What--
[ Stammers ]
Minneapolis? No.
Uh, we're
going home now?
Yeah.
Why?
I assumed that
the funeral would be
after the honeymoon.
You-You wanna
postpone the funeral?
Who postpones a funeral?
This is
a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
I mean, our honeymoon--
I've been dreaming about it
since I was a little girl.
I'm supposed to be
in a caftan
under a palm tree.
What's a caftan?
You don't know
what a caftan is?
I know you never got Lumpy.
Okay? Let's just be honest.
You didn't want him
to be my best man.
I didn't say that.
What I said was,
you two didn't spend
much time together anymore.
What does that mean?
We're men.
Men don't spend
a lot of time together.
We have to go home
because I have to...
take care of my friend's
funeral arrangement, okay?
I can't believe
this happened
on our wedding night.
Hey, will you hold this?
It's Lumpy's.
Then we can make some calls,
just let people know
what happened.
There are only
six numbers stored.
Two of them
are for pizza delivery.
It's not a joke.
It's true.
- Who's Ramsey Anderson?
- No idea.
Probably a friend
from law school.
Or a restaurant maybe.
[ Sighs ]
So, after the autopsy...
they're gonna ship the body
back to Minnesota
by budget courier.
Budget courier?
Is that a normal thing?
I don't know.
I've, weirdly, never
had to ship a friend's body
anywhere before.
It's still gonna be $2,000.
We don't have it.
Not after the open bar
and the welcome baskets
for the guests.
And a $2,000 dress.
So it wasn't worth it?
Come on.
I didn't say that.
We're gonna have to use
the honeymoon money...
for the funeral though.
What choice do I have?
Kristin, he was my best man.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Alarm Chiming ]
Hi.
Aren't you supposed
to be in school?
Someone's gotta shop for food.
Yeah. Well, you don't
have a job.
Neither do you.
Why you gotta be
like that?
I'm trying
to make things work,
you know?
I thought
we had a deal here.
I don't like that deal.
I didn't ask
if you liked it.
Hey.
I'm not finished.
[ Door Shuts ]
This is your family,
Ramsey.
Whether you like it or not,
we're family.
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Up-tempo Guitar
Strumming ]
[ Man Vocalizing ]
Under the covers
A man can tell
It's my world
That I'm in
Without you near me
You know I need ya
I want you to be
Oh
[ Vocalizing ]
Under the table
Nobody there
Under the ceiling,
under the stairs
A funny feeling
My head is sleeping
I want you to be
Oh
[ Vocalizing ]
[ Alarm Blaring ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
In the morning
I'm waiting for you
To come back home
You're welcome?
[ Vocalizes ]
[ Ends ]
Can we just go?
I have to tell
your mother.
No!
I know what I promised,
but I could get
in serious trouble here.
[ Groans ]
It was just cold medicine.
You don't look
like you have a cold.
[ Coughs ]
You're lucky I was able
to talk the sheriff into
releasing you into my custody.
Yeah, really lucky.
Ramsey.
Ramsey, wait.
Look, it's seriously
decent of you to spring me
from my incarceration.
But I'm fine, okay?
I know why people
buy cold medicine.
It's to make crystal meth.
Why'd you steal it anyway?
I just gave you money.
I spent it.
On drugs?
Don't you have
candles to light,
or, like,
wine and crackers
to hand out?
That's what you think I do?
Mood lighting and catering?
I don't do drugs, okay?
You only have a couple
of more months of this.
Don't blow it!
[ Jet Engine Whining ]
[ Man On P.A. ]
Welcome aboard
Valdez flight 896,
redeye to Minneapolis,
Minnesota.
It's gonna be
a full flight tonight, folks,
so we ask you to find your seat
and stow your luggage
as quickly as possible...
for an on-time departure.
[ Sighs ]
Oh, my God.
What? What's wrong?
I think I packed the Ambien
in my suitcase.
Okay, are--
I can't believe this.
Are you sure?
Oh, my God.
Well, look--
Look in that guy.
Jesus.
Kris, it's only
a four-hour flight.
But I need to sleep.
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
I need a Xanax.
Jesus. How many pills
are you taking?
My God.
You're like
a pharmacy in there.
These ones
are the white ones,
not the orange ones.
They're like
half as strong.
And the blue ones,
those are the ones
that are for crazies.
Okay, Elvis,
when did chronic anxiety
take over your life?
Am I missing something?
Why are--
You're like announcing this
to the entire plane.
Oh, relax.
He's the one guy
that's eavesdropping.
We don't even know him.
Who cares?
Hi.
I'm Neil.
Your mom's cousin's son?
We met at the reception.
Right.
Hi, Neil.
I'm really sorry
about your friend.
Thank you, Neil.
I don't have
anxiety issues.
Oh, I wasn't even
paying attention.
He wasn't listening.
I have a slight fear
of flying.
Xanax helps take
the edge off
during takeoff.
But... don't need 'em.
Not like I'm addicted.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Whispers ]
Kris, he doesn't care.
How are you at flying?
Do you want one?
They're the white ones.
They're not the orange ones.
No. Thank you though.
I appreciate that.
Um, gosh, you know,
that is a "D"
on my ticket,
which means
I have the wrong seat.
So I'm gonna
scooch on over.
Rick going to be
at the funeral?
Oh, well, yeah, probably.
We've both known Lumpy
since junior high,
so guessing.
Such a real estate crook.
Yeah, and his dad's my boss,
so please remember that, Kris.
I thought you didn't have
to pay a referral fee
if it was within the office.
You do sometimes.
It depends.
[ Woman ]
He fails.
Ethan risks everything
to be with the woman
that he loves,
but he fails.
Why?
Why would Wharton
have Ethan and Mattie fail?
Anna? What do you think?
I didn't read it.
Did anybody read it?
No. See, that's the thing
about literature--
You have to read it.
Okay. For tomorrow--
[ School Bell Rings ]
I want everyone
to finish Ethan Frome.
Lunch?
Sure.
I was talking to her.
[ Kristin ]
All I'm saying is
that I can't think of a time...
when Lumpy wasn't either drunk
or naked or both.
Yeah, everyone lets loose
on vacation.
Clearly you've forgotten
about the hairy bead rack
incident on Bourbon St.
[ Chuckling ]
Oh, yeah.
I mean, New Orleans
was struggling through
a post-Katrina holocaust,
and Lumpy thinks he can
brighten everyone's day
by hanging beads from--
What did he call it?
His hairy button.
Hairy button.
That was hilarious.
Oh, Scott.
Okay, listen.
You know what?
I agree with you.
In the last year the drinking
got a little out of control.
But I don't know
what you want me to say, Kris.
I mean,
he was my best friend.
But... he wasn't
your best friend.
He was
your oldest friend.
There's a difference.
I don't care
what you call him.
I knew Lumpy
better than anyone.
I'm very sorry
for your loss,
but Lawrence is no longer
a law student here.
What? N-No.
That must be a mistake.
Well, he hasn't
been enrolled
for almost a year.
A year?
Did he transfer
to another school?
I don't have any record
of a transcript request.
He flunked out
of law school?
Actually, his grades
were quite strong.
He left
for personal reasons.
What does that mean?
I-I'm sorry.
I don't have
any further information.
But I'd be happy
to put his funeral announcement
on our Web site.
Uh, thank you--
Actually, could you search
for one more student for us?
It's a friend of Lumpy's.
Lumpy?
Lawrence. Sorry.
Of course.
Uh, what's the name?
Uh, Ra--
Ramsey Anderson.
[ Typing ]
I'll check.
Sorry. Lots of Andersons.
No Ramsey.
You are my lover
and I do like you
Yeah. This is it.
What's the matter?
Tell me what to do
[ Bell Jingles ]
[ Continues ]
- Hi.
Two?
No, we're actually
not here to eat.
Um, we're friends
of Lumpy's.
[ Laughs ]
Last time I saw Lumps
we were totally wasted,
and we ended up--
N-Never mind.
How old are you?
[ Stammers ]
I'm afraid we have
some really bad news.
Uh, L-Lumpy passed away...
over the weekend.
What?
It was an accident.
It was a very unfortunate
accident.
We just wanted
to tell his manager...
and let everyone know
about the funeral.
Oh, my God. He O.D.'d.
No. No, no, no.
Why would you think
he O.D.'d?
He died on a cactus.
Can you tell
your manager...
that we're here
to talk to him or her?
Uh, sure.
Lumpy hasn't worked here
in a couple of months though.
He hasn't?
No, he was--
he was fired.
What?
How could he fire Lumpy?
Is he in there?
You can't go in there!
Scott, don't do that.
I swear to God.
Bruce doesn't like
to be interrupted.
[ Rock ]
Oh, eureka.
What?
Oh. God.
Sorry.
- Um--
- You can't just barge in here.
I just wanted to talk to you,
but I-I'll wait outside.
I think he needs a minute.
He--
He was stealing?
Uh, we caught him
on camera.
No. There's no way.
Not Lumpy.
Look, bartending
is a cash business.
It happens, you know.
Sooner or later,
temptation wins out.
Well, did you
call the police?
Is there a report
that was filed
or something?
The owners wanted to,
but I never did.
Why?
I think
he was in a bad place.
What do you mean?
There was a lot of booze
and, uh,
some girl up north
in, uh, Lutsen.
Do you remember her name,
by any chance?
Oh, man. Uh--
Was it Ramsey?
It-- Maybe. Yeah.
That sounds right.
Okay. Thank you
for your time.
And sorry about
barging in again.
I'm real sorry
about your friend.
Everyone
liked Lumpy.
Yeah.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Don't touch it!
[ Coughs ]
Thank you.
[ Birds Twittering ]
Hey.
Aren't you
going to work?
I called Dan.
I told him
I wasn't feeling well.
Is he okay?
Hmm?
Wasn't he in danger?
You don't believe
in Ms. Shirley, do you?
She's from
Thief River Falls, Mom.
It is a gift.
She has a real gift.
Yeah.
For taking your money.
The first time
I talked to her,
she knew everything about me.
Names.
She knew names.
[ Door Opens ]
Have you ever heard
of caller I.D. and Google?
[ Door Closes ]
Hi, baby.
Hey.
Can I talk to you?
[ Chuckles ]
Did you get it?
Tried.
What happened?
One of the security thingies
went off and I got busted
for shoplifting.
But I told you to take
the security tags off.
I did.
Must have missed one.
It's okay. It's okay.
Did you, uh--
Did you say anything
about me?
No.
You sure? You sure?
'Cause you can tell me.
Just tell me.
I didn't.
Ramsey, we need this money.
Your mom won't ask,
but we need it.
How bad does she need it?
I told you
it ain't for us.
Look at me.
I come back from
two back-to-back tours
in Iraq last year,
and I got shit.
No job, no degree,
no money-- nothin'.
All I have is respect,
and from you
I'm gonna get respect.
- I asked you to do one thing,
one stupid little thing--
- [ Cell Phone Buzzes ]
[ Buzzing Continues ]
and you messed it up.
Uh--
What's this?
Where'd you get this?
A friend.
Nice friend?
Yeah.
I wonder what
you have to do for a friend
to get a phone like this.
[ Whispering ]
Don't mess up again.
[ Line Ringing ]
[ Woman's Voice ]
Your call has been forwarded...
to an automated
voice-messaging system.
3-3-2--
[ Beep ]
Would anyone like
some more wine?
Yeah.
I would.
Your uncle and I
are very happy...
to have a belated
Christmas dinner
with the newlyweds.
We're all glad you're here.
Too bad your brother had to fly
straight back to Wilmington
from Phoenix.
Helen, you should see
the house he bought.
Oh, John's work
is just going so well.
His company is exploiting
Chinese children into
making automotive paint.
Here we go
with all the green talk again.
We are proud of you too,
being a teacher.
Why would--
That's not what I'm--
[ Chuckles ]
[ Stammers ]
Could somebody please pass
the Mrs. Dash?
She might be hiding
with Mr. Dash.
Oh, we don't know if there
is a Mr. Dash, Dad.
Maybe things didn't go well
after their wedding
or something.
Well, maybe Mr. Dash
had some things on his mind,
and things he had
to take care of.
I just wonder
if Mr. and Mrs. Dash
didn't go on a honeymoon...
and then after that
stop communicating.
Maybe Mrs. Dash should stop
feeling sorry for herself.
I think that Mrs. Dash
is trying really hard and maybe
feels underappreciated.
Maybe Mrs. Dash should remember
she's not the only spice
in the spice rack.
I'm not saying
that Mrs. Dash
is the only spice.
Mrs. Dash has gotten
very arrogant lately.
Little one-sided.
Arrogant?
Mm-hmm.
There's paprika,
there's thyme, there's rosem--
a lot of other spices.
I think maybe it's time
to clear the table.
- I'll help you.
- No, no, Helen.
Now, you sit.
I only get to wash
the Christmas dishes
once a year.
Okay, this is it.
We couldn't believe
all those strange-looking plants
in Phoenix.
What were they called again?
Cactus, Helen.
They were cactus.
They weren't cactus.
I know what cactus look like.
They're succulents.
Too bad about your--
your friend, Scott.
[ Uncle ]
Yeah. I'm sorry.
That's too bad.
It was an unfortunate lesson
for all of us.
[ Roger ]
Boy looked like
he was a lot of fun.
He was a lot of fun, Roger.
He wasn't a boy though.
He was a man.
Of course he was a man.
No, no, no.
He was a real man.
Just because he drank
a little too much...
and quit law school
and he got fired from his job,
it doesn't make him
less of a man.
'Cause he was a man, Kris.
Okay. We understand
and we know you're upset--
You asked me to pee
sitting down!
I thought it would be
a nice compromise.
You wanted me
to carry a purse,
for Christ's sake.
- Why would he carry
a purse?
- It was a man bag!
And I was only pointing out
that some men have
found it efficient.
They are in Europe,
mostly--
We don't live in Europe.
This is what
I'm talking about.
Lumpy kept it real.
He was a man.
I'm going to help Mom
in the kitchen.
Good idea.
Come on, Terry.
This isn't even gonna
get me through New Years.
Man, Terry! Hey.
[ Groans ]
[ Tires Screech ]
What?
Nothing.
[ Cocks Gun ]
Your aunt
had to bring up Lumpy.
Mom, someone died.
People are gonna talk about it.
But that's all
they talk about.
Oh, your best man
got drunk and died
at the wedding.
Do you know that he hit
on your cousin Lindsay?
She's 14.
They were just dancing.
I think
it's inappropriate.
I don't like it.
Well, don't tell me
that you don't wish...
that didn't happen
on your wedding night.
Actually,
I just wish
that it didn't happen.
Oh. Hey.
I'm sorry.
You're not a smoker.
Should we leave
tomorrow morning
after traffic?
Leave for where?
Lutsen.
What are you talking about?
Why would we drive to Lutsen?
'Cause we have to find
Ramsey Anderson and tell her
that her boyfriend died.
Kris, that's like
five hours away.
It's near Canada.
Why don't we just
call Ramsey Anderson?
I tried.
The phone's been disconnected
or something.
I googled. I Facebooked.
There's nothing.
What about a home number?
Do you know
how many Andersons there are
in Northern Minnesota?
So we're gonna
drive to Lutsen...
and just ask around
for Ramsey Anderson?
Yeah.
Why would we do that?
Because Lumpy
was your best friend.
[ Pop Intro ]
[ Woman ]
You are my lover
and I do like you
What's the matter?
Tell me what to do
[ Continues ]
Kris, can you take
your legs down, please?
'Cause we get in an accident,
you're gonna get paralyzed.
But we've passed, like, two cars
in the last 20 minutes.
Can you just work
with me, please?
Come on.
We're newlyweds.
Thank you.
I need to pee again.
Really?
Yeah.
[ Speakers: Rock, Faint ]
[ Knocking ]
[ Man Singing ]
Mom.
There's someone at the door.
[ Knocking Continues ]
Mom!
Hey.
Hi.
Hi. Uh, I'm sorry
to bother you.
Are your parents
at home?
Yeah.
Great.
Can I talk to them?
Why?
[ Chuckles ]
Okay.
Uh, yeah, because
I normally cut through
your neighbor's property...
to get down to the lake,
but they have it plowed so--
Yeah, I think they took
their Winnebago to Florida
for the winter.
Do you think it would be okay
if I just cut through
your property really quick?
Yeah. Sure.
Really?
Rock it out.
All right. Rock it out.
[ Continues ]
You like these guys, huh?
You know these guys?
Yeah, I do.
A lot of people do.
Not in this town.
Oh, no, maybe not.
Yeah. Probably right.
Okay, I'll get
out of your hair.
Thank you.
Careful on the ice.
Global warming.
Thanks.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Volume Increases ]
[ Man Vocalizing ]
[ Mother ]
Who was that at the door?
Who was that?
Some guy.
What guy?
I don't know.
He's gone.
[ Sighs ]
Have you seen my cigarettes?
Finished the pack
at school.
Don't be a smart-ass.
So, uh,
how was school anyway?
I asked you a question.
[ Stops ]
What are you doing?
- I asked you how school was.
- How do you think it was?
It sucks.
Why?
Why do you think?
I don't know, Ramsey.
That's why I'm asking.
I hate it here.
You never
gave it a chance.
No one makes new friends
in high school.
Oh, you're so smart though.
Yeah, and everyone's
just dying to be friends...
with that freak girl
who does math two years ahead
of everybody else.
Well, if you try,
it'll get better.
You sure about that, Mom?
Is it gonna get better
like Milwaukee,
where I got beat up
every week?
Or is it gonna get better
like Rockford, where you
got beat up every week?
Stop it.
I did the best that I could.
Or is it like Brooklyn Park,
where I had to watch
my dad O.D.
- Stop it!
- So tell me, Mom,
when does it get better?
Because I wouldn't want
to miss it.
[ Door Opens ]
Ramsey.
Where are you going?
Anywhere but here.
Hey.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to scare you.
You didn't.
Good.
How's it going?
Just, uh, you know,
gettin' started.
I just wanted
to make sure
you found it.
The lake?
Yeah.
Yeah. Found it.
Right there.
[ Chuckles ]
Cool.
See ya.
Oh.
[ Water Sloshing ]
[ Reel Winding ]
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Oh-- Oh!
[ Laughs ]
Oh!
Oh, look at you!
Ohh! Oh!
[ Laughing ]
Oh.
Oh, shit.
[ Coughing, Screaming ]
Oh, God!
[ Grunting ]
Help! Help!
[ Grunting Continues ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Lumpy Groans ]
[ No Noise ]
[ Screaming Resumes ]
[ Gasping ]
Hold on!
[ Gasps ]
[ Panting, Shivering ]
[ Grunting ]
Come on!
You're almost there!
[ Gasping, Panting ]
[ Grunting ]
I told you.
Global warming.
[ Exhales ]
Holy shit.
It's a wintry mess
here--
I still think you should've
gone to the hospital.
Mm-mmm. No, no.
No, Duluth is, like,
two hours away from here.
I took a hot shower.
I'll be fine.
Well, you look purple
and bloated.
I always look bloated.
It's okay, it's okay.
I work really hard
to look this bloated.
[ Laughs ]
It's a point of pride
for me.
[ TV ]
Good evening.
I'm Michelle Lee.
Mother Nature
is once again trying
to put a damper on--
Do you mind if I shower?
- You want to
take a shower here?
- I was on the ice too.
Remember?
I do. I do.
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Knock yourself out.
[ Clears Throat ]
[ TV Continues ]
Um--
I think I should
probably take you home
after that though. Okay?
Are you sure?
Uh, what would, uh--
What would your family say
if they saw you here with me?
We're not doing
anything wrong.
I just think that
it would probably be...
the right choice.
Okay?
Like it was the right choice
for me to risk my life
saving a total stranger?
I thanked you for that,
like, a hundred times.
Didn't I? I mean--
I just, uh--
-You want me to get out of here
'cause you got what you needed.
-What?
That's real fuckin' nice.
Hey, you don't even know me.
Okay?
A-And watch your mouth,
young lady.
I know you. I know men.
You want money.
You want sex. You want drugs.
Whoa-- What?
Wh-What are you talking--
Hold on.
I was just simply saying
that I think
maybe you should--
Get the hell out of here!
I heard you.
Maybe if I get home in time,
I can still score
some pharmaceuticals...
for my mom's boyfriend...
and we can all
do some meth together
and watch cartoons.
[ Door Opens, Slams ]
[ TV Continues ]
From the direction
of Eau Claire City--
[ Sighs ]
Hey, stop! Stop!
Hey-hey-hey!
God... bless America!
Stop!
- You're gonna get pneumonia.
- I-I-I'm really sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
Okay? Genuinely.
All right, listen.
Just, uh, you know,
come back inside.
Let me at least
put some clothes on
and I will drive you home.
I can walk.
Get back into the hotel room,
or I'm gonna drop this towel!
[ Shivering ]
You'll be scarred
for life.
Good choice.
Smart choice--
Ohh!
Let me in.
Now, the state patrol,
as well as local
law enforcement agencies,
are stepping up
their--
And, uh, you know,
I was gonna be
a big-shot lawyer.
I was gonna be,
you know, rich,
have a--
[ Inhales, Exhales ]
a house on a lake,
a different car for the winter,
a different one for the summer.
But everything just...
fell apart.
Rough.
Yeah.
Anyway, uh--
[ Clears Throat ]
So, you, uh-- you guys
just moved here, yeah?
Me and my mom move around a lot.
I'm gettin' out of here though.
- You are? On your own?
- I'm filing for emancipation
this summer.
I'm gonna get
my G.E.D. and--
Whoa.
I got a 1990
on my S.A.T.'s.
No, you didn't.
They only go up to 1600.
They changed it.
Nobody ever tells me anything.
[ Clears Throat ]
So, um,
what college
you gonna go to?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
You gotta go to college.
It's sort of expensive.
Yeah.
[ Banging On Door ]
Open up.
Cook County Sheriff.
What? No. No way.
Oh, my God.
Put your shoes on.
Wait--
- Ho! Whoa!
- On the floor.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Okay.
[ Stereo: Woman ]
You wake up early
I do anything I can
[ Continues ]
We should stop and ask.
This is why we should have
gotten a G.P.S.
Take you right there.
Hey.
"Lutsen, 25 miles."
All right.
[ Knocking ]
Yeah?
Hi.
Ms. Anderson?
Maybe.
I'm Scott Thomas
This is my wife Kristin.
We're friends of Lumpy's.
[ Kristin ]
Hi.
W-We have bad news,
I'm afraid.
Who's Lumpy?
Aren't you Ramsey Anderson?
No, that's my daughter.
Your daughter?
Is she home?
How old is your daughter?
Um, look, I don't know
who you people are, but--
You're friends
of Lumpy's?
[ Mother ]
Who is Lumpy?
Mom, it's cool.
You know
these people?
Sort of, yeah.
Fine.
I gotta go to work.
I'm sorry about that.
She's... tired.
- You guys can come in.
- Thanks.
Um,
I'm afraid we have
some bad news, Ramsey.
Lumpy passed away
this week.
[ Scott ]
There was an accident
at our wedding, and it was--
it was very sudden
for everyone.
So we wanted
to tell you.
What happened?
Well, he, uh--
he fell in the desert
and he hit his head.
And he-- he died.
We don't know what,
exactly,
your relationship was
with Lumpy.
It's none of
our business, so--
No, but we want you to know
that you can talk to us.
[ Coins Clinking ]
I should probably
get going actually,
if that's cool.
Oh.
Sorry.
Okay.
Well, would you
like the details
for the funeral service?
'Cause it's gonna be Monday
in Minneapolis and--
That's okay.
Okay.
[ Clears Throat ]
Um--
Sorry you guys had to
drive all the way up here.
I'm... just glad
we were able
to tell you.
Nice to meet you.
[ Door Closes ]
What was that?
I don't know.
She acted like
she didn't even know him.
[ Footsteps ]
They're gone?
Yeah. It was just
a misunderstanding.
[ Sighs ]
Danny gets
all bent out of shape
if I'm five minutes late.
If you see Winston,
tell him I'll be
off at 1:00.
Is everything
all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Smile.
Hmm?
You never smile.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
[ Crying ]
[ Kristin ]
Can't we just
drive back tonight?
Oh, come on.
Please, no.
It's so cold.
I'm tired.
Let's just order a pizza
and crash here.
It just seems like
a waste of money.
[ Sighs ]
Waste of money?
[ Chuckles ]
It's, like,
39 bucks a night.
Think we can still
swing that.
Mmm.
[ Exhales ]
What are you doing?
I'm gonna check
for bedbugs.
Um--
[ Exhales ]
I quit my job.
- What?
- Yeah.
Quit. Done.
Quit my job.
Rick wouldn't give me
the commission yet again,
so I finally called his dad--
Please tell me
that you're joking.
Nope.
And, uh, Rick Senior tells me
that I'm not a team player.
You quit your job now?
Why are you saying it like that?
I mean, you're the one
that said they were crooks.
Yeah, they are, but I didn't
say "quit your job."
We have a wedding to pay for!
Well, you're the one
that bought a $2,000 dress.
It was 3,000.
Oh, Jesus, Kris.
Oh, my God.
You have to get
your job back.
I  can'tget my job back!
I don't want
to get my job back!
Keep shafting you
on commissions,
and I'm done.
That's what Lumpy
would have done.
Oh, well, by all means
let's follow Lumpy's example.
What has he done?
He dropped out of law school.
He got fired for embezzlement.
Now I think he's committed
statutory rape!
Stop it! Please don't.
Just don't.
You know how we could
afford Mexico?
Lumpy
gave me the money.
He got us a honeymoon,
and I can't even
get his funeral right.
You never told me that.
He asked me
not to tell you.
Wh-Where are you going?
I'm gonna find us
some food.
[ Glass Breaks, Faint ]
[ Voices, Faint ]
[ Man, Woman Laughing ]
[ Woman ]
Get away!
[ Man Laughing ]
[ Woman Laughing ]
Stop!
[ Kissing Sounds ]
[ Man Moans ]
Ow. Ow!
My hand's burning.
[ Laughing ]
Ow!
[ Winston ]
What'd you do? Oh!
Ramsey. No.
Not in front of her, no.
[ Winston ]
I'm-- Hey!
It's okay, baby.
Not in front of
my little girl!
Calm down.
Why-- Get out of here!
Get out!
[ Mother Whining ]
I don't want her to see.
[ Winston ]
It's all right.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Exhales ]
Where'd you get muffins
in Lutsen?
They're just
Hostess cupcakes.
Well, it's still
a pretty good effort.
I'm sorry. I am so sorry
about the honeymoon and the job.
No. No.
I should be
apologizing to you.
You did
the right thing.
I promise you
we're gonna have a honeymoon.
We're gonna have
a-- a great honeymoon.
I know.
I need a ride.
To the funeral.
Can I go with you guys?
Uh, sure.
Yeah, we can drive you
to Minneapolis. But how
you gonna get back home?
I don't know. I'd...
take the bus or something?
I think we should
figure that out before--
I'm pregnant.
It's Lumpy's.
I knew it.
I have to go to the funeral.
Lumpy would have wanted me--
I mean, us...
to be there.
Why can't we just leave?
Because that
would be kidnapping.
So we're gonna
ask your mom.
Remember our deal.
I won't say anything about
the pregnancy to your mom.
And I won't mention it
at the funeral.
Perfect.
[ Door Closes ]
Mom.
Hi again.
They shouldn't
be here.
Mom, it's okay.
We just came to ask
if we could take Ramsey
to Minneapolis.
What's he
talking about?
It's for the funeral.
No one is taking
my daughter anywhere.
It's for Lumpy.
I don't care what it's for.
I don't even know you.
We're friends of--
Friends of
a mutual friend, Lumpy.
Yeah? Lumpy?
You were going, uh--
going out
with some Lumpy guy?
Where did you
find those?
Doesn't matter.
- You went trough my room
and dug through my stuff.
- I'm your mother!
I can go through what the--
the hell I want to!
Who'd you bring
in this house?
This about last night?
[ Scott ]
No, listen,
everything's totally cool.
We just came to ask if
we could take Ramsey to
a funeral for our friend Lumpy.
Who?
Let's just--
We should go.
No.
- I'm coming with you.
- Yeah, listen.
I'm just trying to respect
the wishes of a friend
who passed away.
- I don't care. You'd better
get the hell out of here.
- Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
We gotta go.
Baby,
what are you doing?
Social Services.
Is that what this is?
- No! Oh, no, no, no.
- He's in real estate.
I'm a third grade teacher.
Yeah.
Wh-Where did you
get that?
I promise you,
there's no reason for that.
Okay? E-Everything's fine.
We just--
We have a mutual friend
who passed away.
We're just going to a funeral.
That's it.
- I told you to leave!
- Okay.
[ Scott ]
Okay. We'll go.
Baby, it's okay.
Maybe they're right.
Maybe Ramsey should be
at the funeral.
- Ms. Shirley said
that it was okay.
- Ms. Shirley?
Yeah. She said that
maybe it's a good time
for you to start traveling.
You know, seeing other pl--
Hold on.
- How long you gonna be gone?
- I don't know.
Um, the funeral
is tomorrow,
so we can put her
on a bus by Monday night,
Tuesday morning.
Here.
I want you to have it.
I want you to know
we're gonna take
really good care of her.
It's only for a couple days.
We'll have her back.
Yeah, we will.
We should go.
Okay. I'm sorry again
about all the confusion
and, um--
I-I-I didn't
catch your name.
Um, you know what?
I-I'm just gonna leave you
a business card there.
That's me and my cell number,
if you need to get in touch,
check in.
Okay.
I love you.
[ Crying ]
[ Door Closes ]
[ Winston ]
Jesus.
It's only gonna be
two days.
[ Door Slams ]
[ Guitar ]
[ Continues ]
[ Man ]
Brianna, can you hear me?
[ Continues ]
S-So, how often would Lumpy
come and visit you, Ramsey?
Almost every weekend.
Really?
And, um, your mom
never met him?
We hung out
at the motel mostly.
Huh.
So, you guys
just got married
four days ago?
Mmm.
Yeah.
Aren't you supposed to
be on your honeymoon
or something?
Yeah, supposed to be--
[ Sighs ]
lying under a palm tree
in a caftan, sipping a mojito.
What's a caftan?
Never mind.
So--
[ Sighs ]
no honeymoon.
Nope.
Hmm.
Waste of
a perfectly good
boob job.
You got a boob job?
No, I did not,
Ramsey.
I was just kidding.
I didn't think so.
I need a Xanax.
Again?
What do you mean?
"Again"?
What do you mean,
"again"?
You took one earlier.
Yeah.
Did I?
You did.
My mom says
taking drugs for fun
is okay,
but taking them
for problems is not.
'Cause once the drugs wear off,
you still have the problem.
Yeah.
Why'd you quit your job?
Wh-- Huh?
Why'd I qui--
Oh.
It's a long story,
Ramsey.
Hmm.
We got two hours
till Minneapolis.
Yeah.
[ Kristin ]
Pop'll kill you.
We have green tea.
Ever had
goji berries?
[ Spits ]
Oh.
Well, they're filled
with antioxidants.
Well, I'm 15.
I don't need antioxidants.
That's Lumpy's
ultimate fighting phase.
Lumpy fought?
Mmm.
Only with Jim Beam.
Hey, is this picture
from the Wisconsin Dells truck?
Yeah.
How'd you know that?
He talked about you guys
all the time.
[ Beep ]
What's wrong?
That was the coroner.
Uh, apparently Lumpy
didn't bleed to death.
He had
a heart failure.
What?
Yeah. It had nothing
to do with the cactus.
He had
a heart attack?
He had a heart attack.
The coroner said
it was like, um,
you know, when young athletes
just collapse on the field.
Did you know that Lumpy
had a heart condition?
I don't think Lumpy knew
he had a heart condition.
He knew.
He knew about his heart.
He had I.H.S.S.
How do you know?
He told me.
What's I.H.S.S.?
Uh, idiopathic hyper...
something-something.
It's pretty rare,
probably genetic.
So Lumpy told you
he had a heart defect?
I just said that.
What else
did he tell you?
- Lots of things.
- Yeah? Like what?
- Like, why do you care?
- I-I-I'll tell you why.
Because I don't know what
he's doing, where he's working,
who he's dating.
-I don't really know anything
about the guy, as it turns out.
-Neither do I.
Oh, n--
I think you knew him
pretty well, actually.
Did Lumpy know
about the baby?
Scott--
No, no, no.
Did he?
Did Lumpy know
about the baby?
I don't know!
You don't know
if you told your own boyfriend
you were pregnant?
I mean, what the hell?
What if she got pregnant
on purpose?
She's just a girl.
What if that made
his heart thing worse?
It doesn't matter.
Of course it matters!
What are you talking about?
He's gone, Scott.
I know that.
I just--
He told a 15-year-old girl
he was dying.
He didn't tell me.
I just wish
he'd told me.
Oh, I wish
he had told me.
You told me you would never
involve her in the drugs.
You promised.
We all make
our sacrifices.
Yeah.
You know what I think?
I think she got caught
on purpose.
And I'm gonna have
a little talk with her
when she gets back.
[ Pop Ballad ]
It's so good, so easy
Girlfriend
Where you been?
No sense in lies
Tonight
And when you're wise
To where I am
We'll go together
Tonight
Toni-i-i-i-ight
[ Continues ]
Watch your angel
Big eyes and you don't
Know where they go
[ Fades ]
[ Gail ]
Scott.
Hi, Gail.
I am so sorry.
So sorry.
He was just
way too young.
He was.
Hey, Roger.
Hi, Scott.
Uh, I gotta--
Oh, don't you
look pretty.
[ Laughs ]
I like your hair like that.
Have you taken
any pills today?
What?
Well, your father and I
are very worried
about you and drugs.
Oh, my God.
Honey, we love you
very much.
Yes, we do.
My God.
This is about Neil
on the plane?
Yes, Neil did say
something to his mother,
and he's only trying to help.
This is so ridiculous.
I thank the Lord
that he did say something.
Because otherwise
I wouldn't know
that you have a problem.
- I don't have a problem!
- Honey, a-all right.
Don't get excited.
We're gonna talk
about this later.
Yeah, that's good.
That's right.
We'll talk about it later.
Please go sit down.
Sure. W-We'll talk
about it later.
- Just no drugs today.
- [ Whispers ]
Mother!
What is going on?
I-- I can't talk about it.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay.
[ Flushes ]
[ Organ ]
[ Clears Throat ]
My name
is Ramsey Anderson.
I know a lot of you
probably don't know who I am
or how I knew Lumpy.
[ Whispers ]
Oh, God.
It's sort of
a long story.
Lumpy had a minor heart attack
a year and a half ago.
The doctors told him
there was no way
to know for sure,
but they didn't think
he would live
more than a year or two.
He had I.H.S.S.
It's a heart defect.
Which means
the walls of his heart
were hard and thick.
And knowing Lumpy,
that's difficult
for me to believe.
He didn't tell anyone about
his heart because he didn't want
his friends or family to worry.
And if he only had
a little time left to live,
the last thing he wanted
to be was a lawyer.
He just wanted to fish
and have fun.
But then he met me.
What's this?
My last rites already?
We're dropping
the charges.
The girl told us
what happened.
We went out to the lake,
saw where you fell through.
You're lucky.
[ Ramsey ]
Lumpy started visiting me,
um, twice a month,
and then every week.
And he'd come up
and I'd do my homework
in his motel room,
or... we'd go fishing.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
It was fun.
It was always fun
with Lumpy.
I know this sounds weird,
but he was
the first real friend
I ever had.
But when things got worse
for me at home,
he decided
he had to do something.
So you want Ramsey
to move to Minneapolis
with you?
Yeah.
Why not?
She could start at the "U"
a year early.
- She aced her S.A.T.,
and she gets good grades.
- She's also 15 years old.
Yeah. And you know
what's going on
inside that house.
She's gotta get out.
You might be right,
but you're not her parent.
Then help us convince her mother
it's the best thing for Ramsey.
What if something
happens to you?
Nothing's
gonna happen to me.
You sure
this is what you want?
Yeah.
I want to leave.
But we never got to
that part of the plan.
There are a lot of moments
in life,
and I didn't know Lumpy
very long.
Most of you
probably had more time
with him than I did, but...
just because dying on a cactus
was Lumpy's last moment...
doesn't mean it was
his most important one.
I loved my friend
and the moments we had.
I loved Lumpy.
[ Exhales ]
That was really good,
what you said in there.
And I know Lumpy
would have liked it.
When I yelled
at you yesterday,
that wasn't about you.
But I had no right
to do that, and I'm--
I'm very sorry.
I've been yelled at
a lot worse.
That doesn't really
make me feel better.
I'm not pregnant.
Yeah, I kinda
figured that out.
Lumpy was a great guy.
He never would have--
I know. I know.
What's he doing here?
Rick?
You know Rick?
That's Rick?
Rick the Realtor?
The one that took
your commission?
Yeah. But--
Hey, what are you doing?
I'll be right back.
Hey.
Can I talk to you
about a friend of mine?
He's like
a father to me.
Jaime!
I had to wait
45 minutes out there.
Jaime?
[ Drawer Slides Open ]
I wanted to tell you
I'm really sorry
about your son.
Thank you.
I have something
for you.
When I went to
Lumpy's apartment,
I found this
with your name on it.
This is your money.
It's an advance to help
with your transition
to Minneapolis.
I put the rest
in a safe deposit box.
Why are you
doing this?
If Lumpy wanted you
to start college early,
that's what you should do.
You'll probably have to get
a part-time job, but that should
go a long way towards tuition.
I don't know
what to say.
You know,
I always felt bad...
my son never met
anyone to love,
someone
to love him back.
It's really good to know
that I was wrong.
Hon.
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
What is this?
A wedding gift?
I don't know.
Just came today.
Open it.
"Knew you always
wanted one of these.
Love, Lumpy."
It's a robe.
He knew you always
wanted a robe?
It's not a robe.
Looks like a robe.
What is it?
It's a caftan.
It's--
Is she okay?
Yeah, she's good.
[ Clears Throat ]
Uh, I guess I should
find my way home.
Is there a bus station
around here somewhere?
Uh, your mom
called this morning.
She did?
Yeah. She left Lutsen.
She's left
a lot of towns.
You know, I c--
I-I honestly think...
this is good for her.
I-I think
it's good for you too.
Anyway, I know
she wants to get help.
Where is she?
I don't know.
We're gonna
figure this out.
Where am I
supposed to go?
You stay here for now.
With you?
Yeah.
You guys just got married.
You don't want me here.
We talked about it.
Okay?
Stay here.
For how long?
For as long as it takes.
Lumpy had good taste
in friends.
Besides, I think
I owe you one. I don't know
what you said to Rick.
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
"Nothing"
got me my job back?
I just promised
I'd help him out
with something.
Oh, God. What?
You know what?
I don't want to know, do I?
[ Exhales ]
Probably not.
[ Laughs ]
Okay.
Well,
we'll table it.
[ Chuckles ]
You hungry?
Starving.
Come on.
Hello.
Hi.
[ Guitar ]
[ Continues,
Band Joins In ]
Closed-Captioned by
Captions, Inc., Burbank, CA
[ Man ]
We are waiting
For you to come back
To us
You can't keep going on
We are waiting
For you to control
Cascading
'Cross everything
important to us
You can't keep going on
I'm already able
To cut myself down
If I need to in the end
You can't keep going on
Going on like this
Hey, yeah
[ Continues ]
I'm already able
To cut myself down
If I need to in the end
We are waiting
For you to come back
To us