[radio chatter]
MARGIE VO: Upside down people.
The graveyard shift,
whatever you call us.
We're the ones working
at night while you sleep.
We look out for each other,
or I looked out for Lyman,
and he looked out
for everyone else.
But off the road, he
thought everyone else
had read the big
instruction manual.
Lyman wasn't going to talk until
he had it all figured out.
[siren blaring]
Riding that highway loop
night after night
was the only job he'd ever had,
unless you count all the
classes he took
at the community college.
Oh he learned lots of things,
just not the basics,
and they aren't in books.
MARGIE: You take care
out there, Lyman.
LYMAN: Hmm.
MARGIE VO: I just waited,
and kept him
away from the greasy foods.
I gave him a smile
and coffee in the night.
Some people talk
to say something.
Some when they have
something to say.
TOM: 0 to 60 in 4 seconds.
NEIL: Boy, I'd give my left
nut for a piece of that.
Morning Lyman...
Neil, you over-inflated the
right front tire again.
Say, his social skills are
improving. A whole sentence.
RADIO dd: If you're stuck in
rush hour traffic
on your way to work,
or still in the shower,
stick with us and
we'll bring the sunshine
into your day.
This is New Mexico's
first in news,
traffic and weather, kasa...
FIONA: Wanna come out
friday night?
Um come visit me in the library,
you never come by anymore.
I miss you.
Here you go, come
out friday night?
Hey ladies we're reclaiming the
myth of the cowboy friday night.
Come see us.
Hey guys.
Wanna come out friday night?
Talking cowboys not politicians,
obviously.
See you there.
Here you go.
Polly wan na...
PARROT: shut up!
Polly wanna crack...
shut up!
I'm an eagle!
Give some to the parrot.
[growling]
[chirping]
Sorry...
you bit me.
Shut up.
[chirping]
That won't do.
AMBER: how's Floyd today?
Pleased as a puppy
with two tails.
Shhhh...
it's his birthday next week...
what do you think?
Too...
perfect.
Is that it, Fiona?
Yep.
Come on sugar.
Than ks, Amber.
You look like
a first-timer.
Did you just geta bird?
No.
I found it...
a parrot... found me.
Do you have a...
if the bird's lost, you can fill
out a form, it will go on our
website, and on our lost and
found board for two weeks.
Hey congratulations,
you've been book-crossed.
"I'm free and
you've been caught,"
I'm traveling around the world,
"so, keep my dream alive,
read and release me!"
right. ok.
Can I just get the form?
I have a sort of bird emergency.
Third aisle in the back.
What'd you forget this time?
Floyd's eye drops.
So...
that guy...
yeah, cute.
He found a parrot,
and he took one of your books.
He speaks?
Okay he's a stu dent
at the college.
Every time I try to talk to him,
he just nods and walk away.
And then, I catch
him staring at me.
I figure he's either
very shy or very gay.
Or very married.
Well, no gay man is going to
walk around in that jumpsuit.
You need to get his attention.
Nice work.
Home sweet home.
Brrring Ma 17.
Brrring ma 17.
140, this is 190.
Send a tow truck to 599
and blue canyon way.
An abandoned car, plate
number charlie o1354...
RADIO: Roger.
[engine rewing]
Howdy, thank you for stopping.
I don't understand.
Oh, it's a thank
you for stopping.
I'm a librarian.
Ma'am, just pop
your hood please.
Hood...
nope...
oh.
[dog whimpering]
It's going to be fine.
I put some water in.
Your belts are frayed.
Get off at the next exit, there
is a service station there.
Thank you so much.
Don't wait.
You look really familiar.
Haven't I seen you...
you want to come to my
special cowboy poetry
and songs event
on friday night?
You know underneath this
skirt, my legs are
almost miraculously
transformed into my ass.
To everyone else it's obvious.
Please Lyman, if
you're gonna stare,
at least have the courtesy
to introduce yourself.
I was standing there and you...
said that thing...
how'd you know my name?
Cause it's written there
on your fetching jumpsuit,
Mr. Goodwrench.
You know the first time I saw
you, I decided to be forward.
I mean I was already forward
before I decided to be forward,
so it wasn't that much
of a leap for me.
But I thought it would
put you at ease.
It's unusual behavior
for a librarian.
Thank you.
I'm Fiona James.
What's your story?
I don't have one.
Of course you do,
everybody does.
Me, I specialize in
western literature.
I'm the interim director
of the eugene manlove
rhodes collection.
Temporary.
Yeah, it's what I do.
I do my work, and I move on.
I've lived all over
the past eight years.
I like conversation.
I think it's as good as sex.
And if you're a talker,
I'm a listener.
Are we gonna go for coffee?
I had some already.
Live on the edge.
Have another.
I have to go to work.
Ok. Well, I'm sure if you need
any help, you'll let me know.
I should have asked her
about books or cowboys,
something.
N.. not me, I don't
have a story.
Speak for yourself.
Brrrringg...
ma 17...
speak for yourself.
Rd of the air
shall carry the word.
Who made you?
Carry the word.
[d...]
Okay, see you on
your break then.
Stay safe out there.
Mmhmm.
I heard you got a parrot.
Does 1t talk?
Are you keeping it?
No.
No it doesn't talk, or
no you're not keeping it?
No, I'm not keeping it.
Then why did you buy a
cage at the pet store?
Don't you have something to do?
Yes.
I'm helping you.
I don't need any help.
You don't want any help.
But I'm very good
with pets. I'll help.
It's nota pet.
It's not a pet?
You're a librarian
for god's sake.
Can't you whisper?
When I talk like this,
people don't listen.
Okay I found a parrot,
and I'm trying to find
out about it so I can
return it to it's owner.
Okay, so what does
it look like?
It's uh...
pink...
pink?
The parrot is pink?
Uh... no it's... well
it's green... with uh,
it's more green than pink, with
a yellow patch on it's head.
Hm... what's his name?
How would I know?
Well, ask him.
Wait. That's him.
Yellow-naped amazon?
All the way from south america.
Look here, it says "a
fine ker, gentle and clever."
has he said anything yet?
Wow.
Really?
Yeah, sometimes he sounds
like a little girl,
then he sounds like a
wise old preacher.
What's bring?
More like brrrinnng
the way a telephone rings.
I think that "Ma 17"
might mean something.
Are you sure he didn't
say "I'm seventeen"?
No, it was a capital M,
capital A, then the number 17.
How do you know it was a capital
a, and not a little "a", hmm?
Maybe that's his name.
Why would anyone name
a bird Ma 17?
Maybe... he's
a secret agent.
[laughing]
Wait,
I was kidding.
I can help you.
I'd like to meet him.
You can't, I work nights.
Wow, our schedules
are so opposite.
Ok, I'll come to work with you.
I get off at 9,
then afterwards I
can meet the parrot.
You can't come.
It's dangerous.
How?
You're out in the
middle of nowhere,
you never know who's out there.
Robbers, axe murderers...
murderers still use axes?
Lyman wait.
Lyman...
I'll sit on the far
side of the truck.
I just think it would be cool
driving around at night,
helping stranded people.
What are you afraid of?
I've never been
afraid of anything.
That's a big fat one,
you're scared to death of me,
and I'm just a
girl that likes you.
Where does that come from?
You don't even know me.
I'll help you with
your parrot search.
The last thing the parrot said,
the B of the air thing,
I think I know where it's from.
[phone noise]
Oh look who's got my number.
And now I've got yours.
I have to put an ad in the
paper and go to class.
And I lied. I'm
afraid of tornadoes.
PROFESSOR PAQUET: "Comment dit
on il faut faire attention"
au conditionel?
Lyman?
"Qu'est-ce que vous en pensez?"
Lyman...
Scusi, cosa?
I mean... "pourriez vous
repeter la question,
s'il vous plait?"
Non.
Than ks.
I'll put your order right in.
How are you...
Margie?
Tonight.
Why Lyman, is that you
starting a conversation?
I'm very well.
My feet hurt.
But thank you for asking.
How are you?
I feel... fine.
Hungry I guess.
I found a parrot.
Hmm.
You really think so?
Yeah.
I think it means
give some of what you have to
the people with nothing.
It's good advice, nobody ever
went wrong with that.
About the other
things he said...
[radio chatter]
You eat.
TOM ON RADIO: Lyman, you
still at Margie's?
Sure is.
We've got a jack-knifed rig
flipped at the
eldorado turnoff.
Ambulance is stuck downtown.
Copy that Tom, I'll put his
dinner in the warmer.
Thanks Margie.
[grunting]
How you doing?
TRUCKER: Scorched my crotch
with my damn coffee.
I think my leg's broke.
Emt's are on the way.
[phone ringing]
[grunting]
That your girlfriend?
She's not my girlfriend.
Hello?
Jeez, tell her I'm working.
FIONA ON PHONE: Lyman?
He's kinda busy right now,
he's gonna have to call
you right back.
Hold on... she says
it's about the bird.
Hang up!
I was right.
That thing the bird said,
it's from the bible.
Really?
She says the thing he said,
it's from the bible.
Just hang up, man!
It's kind of mystical and
spiritual...
and I don't know I think it's
one very special bird.
Ma'am, you tell that bird
to pray for me, will ya?
I don't really know
what it means,
but I think it's important.
Lyman?
For pete's sake.
Lyman, why would that man want
the bird...
Lyman?
MOTHER ON PHONE:
Who's Lyman?
Oh it's uh...
it's no one mom,
uh, what's up?
I know it's someone
special when you
whisper, Fiona Christina.
I'm a librarian.
I whisper.
No you don't.
Fiona, remember our little talk?
No one unavailable this time?
Where do you find them?
Mom, I'm almost 30, you
can stop raising me now
you know.
Hey there.
It's from ecclesiastes, the
old testament, after the
"nothing new under the sun"
and "everything has
a season bit."
Look. "Curse not the king,
curse not the rich.
Fora bird of the air
shall carry the word,
and that which hath wings
shall tell the matter."
weird huh?
That which hath wings
shall tell the matter.
What does that mean?
Well, it's about this preacher
guy who decides that all is
vanity, and since life is so
short, we should eat, drink,
be merry and enjoy god's gifts.
Lyman!
Show some respect.
That is what bookmarks are for.
Lyman...
is that your first name
or your last name?
Last.
So what's your first name?
Don't have one.
Everybody has a first name.
You can tell me, I won't laugh,
I promise.
They don't have first and
last names in the bible.
Jesus of nazareth...
Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm...
Lyman of the highway.
[engine rewing]
140 this is 190.
Tell the troopers to watch
out for a red mustang
tell the troopers to watch
going north towards
decatur road.
Driving like he wants
to kill himself.
[phone ringing]
FRANK: I'm so hungry my stomach
thinks my throat's been cut.
Evening, frank.
The usual, darlin'?
Thanks, Margie.
You know anything about a '67
red mustang muscle ca
you seen it around?
A 427 cubic inch
390 horse engine?
No haven't seen it. Sure
would love to though.
By the way, Fiona says
to please call her.
She ran out of gas
on the 599 tonight.
Nice girl.
My, she sure can talk.
Met Lyman's girl.
She's not my girl.
That's not what she says.
You keeping secrets, Lyman?
Gotta go.
My ears are still bleeding.
Surprise!
I don't like surprises.
Of course you do.
Everybody likes surprises.
Nope, not me.
Well, I was worried about you.
How did you know where I live?
It's in the campus directory.
It's not an open invitation.
You didn't return my phone
calls, so I came over.
You'd thank me if you were
dead in the bathtub.
I don't even have a bathtub.
Why didn't you tell me you
lived in a place like this?
I've never told you
lots of things.
Man, if I lived in a
place like this,
it would be the first
thing that I'd tell.
Hey, do you ever go
anywhere in it?
It's my house.
I don't go places in it.
I come home to it.
I'll get it.
No it's okay, let me...
[dog growling]
- He's very protective.
- Jeez...
- No Floyd.
- Let go!
I wasn't attacking you
the phone's ringing...
let go, you stupid dog.
He is far from stupid.
Floyd, no.
How much do you weigh?
Hello, Mr. Lyman's
assistant speaking...
ELEANOR ON PHONE: I'm calling
about the lost parrot.
70?
'Scuse me...
sorry.
- Do you have my bird?
- Jeez, stop!
Can you describe
your bird for me?
He's green with a spot of yellow
on the back of his head...
every parrot's green.
Hello?...
let go!
Does your bird say
anything special?
He says, "speak for self"
and "shut up."
sometimes "prepare
to meet your maker."
I guess breakfast's
gonna have to wait.
Why do we have to
have the heat on?
It's gotta be like 100 degrees.
Non-t!
Parrots are very
susceptible to drafts.
You trying to get me to
take my top off?
Yes!
I just love it when the losts
match up with the founds.
It feels so right.
I don't know what I'd do
if I ever lost Floyd.
Are you sure you
want to do this?
[dog barking]
ELEANOR: Shut up!
Hi.
Yeah, that's him.
Bring him on in.
Thank you for
bringing him back,
have a seat.
You can put him right there.
He's trouble is all he is.
I brought his things,
his toys and...
I never offered no reward.
No it's okay, I didn't
expect anything.
I'm just happy he's...
shut up...
shut up!
Jeez, I forgot how awful he is.
I was wondering, why did you
teach him the things he says?
Honey, I've had him for eight
years and the only thing he
learned in this house
is "shut up".
Between that dog and this
bird, I'm like to lose my mind.
Then why did you answer the ad?
He's worth a fortune.
People will pay seven or
eight hundred bucks
for a talking bird.
I'll give you a thousand
dollars for him.
Well I'm not selling it now.
He keeps the dog company.
We'll take the dog, too.
Dog's not for sale.
But okay you got me, I'll take
two thousand for the bird.
Two thousand?
Are you kidding?
No.
What are you doing?
You write that check for a penny
more than eight hundred dollars,
and I will divorce
you on the spot.
Fiona will you wait outside?
Please?
I mean it.
Don't push me.
I will take the kids to mom's.
You better have
a good attorney.
All right all right... 900.
Ahem...
ok, 800.
Ma'am, can I ask you where
you got the bird from?
Murray's retirement home.
They gave me the bird for free.
Where are you going?
Congratulations,
you own a parrot.
Were you actually going to pay
that woman two thousand dollars?
Are you one of those secret
lottery millionaires
who lives in a trailer?
I don't gamble.
Why does that not surprise me?
I need to find the real owner.
The wise man that taught
him what to say.
It's not random.
It's no joke.
MRS. BLAIR: Oh yes, that looks
like shelton all right.
One of the lucky ones who got
out of here alive.
Shelton?
He was ruby Ballard's bird.
She died 12, 13 years back.
The family left him
to the center.
We kept him in the lobby
for a couple years.
Until his mouth got
him kicked out.
Pre to meet your maker?
Not what our residents want to
hear over their morning oatmeal.
I can imagine.
Anyway, it has been a real
pleasure, Mrs. Blair.
And if you would be so kind as
to e-mail me your records on
Mrs. Ballard's family.
Certainly, I'd be glad to.
I'm sure that the
inheritance you spoke of
will be a welcome surprise.
Here you go.
It says you work in a library.
Oh that's a cover,
mrs. Blair.
In our line of work,
we can't be too careful.
Thank you so much for
your cooperation.
You're welcome.
Inheritance?
MARGIE VO: The parrot brought up
a lot of questions for Lyman
but those only created
more questions.
He kept rolling ecclesiastes
over and over in his head.
Race is not to the swift,
nor the battle to the strong,
nor yet riches to men
of understanding.
But time and chance
happen to them all.
Wasn't that what he
saw every night?
Didn't it prove?
Prove what?
Anybody home?
I brought a
cage-warming present.
Hello there.
Polly want a...
shut up.
I'm an eagle.
Wow.
He actually said it.
How come his lips don't
move when he talks?
Only when he reads.
[whistling]
Why thank you.
So, does he whistle much?
First time.
Speak for yourself.
Lyman, don't forget,
read and release.
When I'm finished, I'll
release it back into the wild.
Where'd you get all this stuff?
It's like living
on an intersection.
People lose things,
I pick them up.
What?
I collect them.
You collect other
people's trophies?
I buy them,
at garage sales
and flea markets.
You're flawed...
people collect all
kinds of things.
Shows you can
accomplish something.
Well, they obviously
didn't mean very much
to the people that won them.
Ok houdini,
let's see you get out of that.
Hey, how come you have don't
have any photos around?
I don't take photos.
What about your family?
Do you have any
brothers or sisters?
No.
What about your folks?
Why are you asking me all this?
I just asked about your parents.
Why does everything have to be
such a big deal secret with you?
It's not a big deal secret.
I was found by the side of
the road when I was four.
What?
Well, at least that's what they
told me in all the foster homes.
You're an orphan?
Jeez, I'm not an
orphan anymore.
I'm own man.
You don't have anybody?
Just me.
What's wrong?
It's just normal for me.
I can't miss
something I never had.
I just...
I don't know what I would
do if I didn't have
a family that was always
ready for me to come home.
I have to go.
Hey, I'm the orphan,
I'm not crying.
I have to go.
Sounds like you got
a loose rod...
Fiona, you need to
get someone to look...
what?
Stay tuned.
Could you be more specific?
A bird of the air
shall carry the word.
You're serious?
He has no family at all?
You sure he just doesn't
want you to meet them?
How much do you know about him?
Anything?
No, but it's not like that.
He works for the
highway department,
that's nearly like the police.
Amber, don't give me that look.
Conditioner.
He's just socially challenged.
Although he has a strange birth
date on his license,
and he does talk about
axe murderers.
Give some to the parrot.
Mmm...
mmm mmm, good.
Campbell's commercial?
Stay tuned.
Shelton?
Shelly?
Tim?
Calvin?
Grace?
Walter?
Joe?
Hen ry?
Billy?
[siren blaring]
LOUDSPEAKER VOICE:
Campus security!
You, under the car!
Come out. Now!
SECURITY GUARD: Up.
Spread your legs and put
your hands against the car.
This isn't what it looks like.
Whoa, hold on a minute.
Face forward please.
Lower your left hand, sir.
Is this your car?
No, it's not.
That's my truck over there.
I work for the
courtesy patrol, and... ow!
Just answer the question, sir.
It belongs to someone I know...
she's a librarian here...
she's my..
My... girlfriend.
You're going to steal
your girlfriend's car?
No.
You think I'd steal
this piece of shit?
All I know is what I saw...
what's going on here?
Do you know this man?
He says he's your boyfriend.
Depends, what was he doing?
He was prowling around,
acting really suspicious.
Is this your car?
Yes, sir.
Isn't she a beauty?
I was just waiting
for you honey,
you didn't leave me the key.
You know how you always forget?
Oh... yes.
You're right, they're
both still here on the ring.
Silly me.
I'm so sorry,
honey.
Would you drive, honey?
It makes me feel so safe.
Thank you officer
for being so vigilant.
There's no telling what
kind of idiot pervert
could be lurking out
here in the night.
From what I hear, there
are axe murderers everywhere.
It's unlocked.
So I'm your girlfriend now?
I just said it to
get rid of him.
Because I'm not
your girlfriend.
Your car is a deathtrap.
You mean Sacajawea?
Yeah.
Yeah, names are important.
After the indian scout.
She's a heroine of mine.
Why did you say I'm flawed?
Intuition.
I'm flawed.
Everybody's flawed.
I'm sorry I said it.
I don't want to
frighten anybody.
I was disappointed.
And then you were mean
to Floyd, and I love Floyd.
And he could be your friend too
if you didn't hate dogs so much.
Your intuition is
just terrible.
I don't hate dogs.
Has mrs. Blair called
you about the parrot?
I called and they
said she was fired.
I've put ads in the
paper and gone online,
I don't know.
Just don't bail on me, Fiona.
And I do like dogs,
I just haven't spent a lot of
time around them lately.
I did some research on Ma 17.
I think it's a phone number from
way back, like the 1930's.
But that would make
the parrot 80 years old.
Parrots are like the giant
tortoises of the bird world.
Whose number is it?
I don't know.
All the old records are
kept in the state library,
archive stuff,
for reference only.
Archive stuff,
JOHN: Hey, are you lost?
[dog barking]
Who is it, Floyd?
You didn't even check
to see who was there.
I could have been...
...an axe murderer?
Yeah, I know.
Come on in.
Just for a second,
after the library
I need to go home and sleep.
Lots of books.
Yeah, I buy them at yard sales.
Sometimes they're
even in the "free" box.
I mend them and I pass them on.
Exciting hobby.
Well, it's not collecting other
people's trophies but...
those trophies would've
been thrown away.
So would those books.
So, we gonna take Sacajawea?
I wouldn't get in your car even
if it was named mother teresa.
Fine, we'll take yours,
Wigglebutt.
Where's your leash?
He's not coming with us, is he?
He's at home for nine
hours while I'm at work.
He comes.
A seeing eye dog?
He's so short he
couldn't see over a curb.
This is embarrassing as hell.
It's the only way
they'll let him in.
'cause he hates to miss out.
Stop that.
I took up Shelton's mystery,
the least you could
do is participate.
He doesn't answer to shelton.
He's yours now,
you can name him.
He's not mine to name.
He's just the messenger.
So were just gonna keep
calling him the parrot?
I'll bet every time he sees
you, he's thinking.
"Oh, there's the human."
come on, "the canine."
he's calling security.
I'm going to be
handcuffed again.
PAUL: Sit.
Good boy.
Hi Fiona, back again?
Hi paul, just those
old phone books and
census records this time.
Funny.
You are so gullible.
I didn't know you could...
mmhmm.
What did you say to make
him look like that?
I told him your
nipples were orange.
They are not!
It's not 1930.
It's not 1931 either.
Keep working forward.
Did he just bite you?
No, I was just holding his
ear and I felt a pulse.
Of course he has a pulse.
You are so weird, Lyman.
Do you have any sections
on the bible?
LIBRARIAN:
The "bible" bible?
Yep.
Sure. Follow me.
Ma 17.
I found it.
It was in the 1932 book.
It belonged to A.J. Campbell.
Than ks.
So we uh... just need to check
the uh... current phonebooks
for relatives.
I'm way ahead of
you, dr. Watson.
There are two pages of
campbells and a whole column
of j's, fifty at least.
That's ok.
I'll call them all.
No, that's ok.
Let me, you sleep all day.
Can you check these out?
I don't have a
library card here.
You're all alike.
What?
Why are you acting so hostile
towards me, out of nowhere?
[screaming] Can I get some
service over here, please?
You're always looking
for something new,
something different,
something other than
what's right in front of you.
Can I get a tiny
hint of servility?
[banging]
Tough to handle these
wild mood swings, huh?
Here she comes.
Act like it never happened.
Here.
Be sure to return them.
Don't rip them, don't
dog ear them,
don't tear them, don't
spill anything on them.
They're in my name.
I'm sorry, it's just
a release, screaming
in other peoples libraries.
Come on, Floyd.
Come on.
You love me...
next time bring a pillow.
[engine rewing]
BEARDED MAN: Ahhh! I hate you,
I hate you, I hate you!
You worthless piece of shit!
You sorry ass piece of
stinkin' garbage.
I hate you, you son of a bitch!
Go ahead, shoot!
You'd be doing me a favor.
I don't want to shoot you, sir.
Not me, you idiot.
Shoot the goddamn car!
[sobbing]
This... this damn car
is killing me.
Shoot the car, please!
Please!
[gunshot]
Yes! Oh yes,
Yes!
Thank you.
Again!
[gunshot]
Yes.
Beautiful.
Now me.
No no, it's my gun.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Yes!
140, this is 190.
I've got a wreck
at mile marker 92.
Send an ambulance.
TOM ON RADIO: Copy 190.
WHISPERS: Hey buddy, come on.
Come on.
[crying]
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
I've been looking
all over for you.
I've got a deadline.
I need to keep my head down.
Well, here.
Ms. blair from
the home emailed.
It's charles Ballard's
phone number.
Ruby's son.
Thanks.
You're amazing.
Were you hiding from me?
No of course not, it's just
quieter back here, that's all.
Well, somebody in this
town knows you.
Hello, is this
Mr. Charles ballard?
Mr. Ballard?
CHARLES BALLARD: You the
parrot fella?
Prepare to meet your maker.
Momma believed since you never
knew when you're really
gonna go, it was best
to keep a clear conscience.
That led to some pretty
awkward conversations,
I tell ya.
Some things a son
should never know.
When did you buy the
bird, Mr. Ballard?
We bought it for momma for
company after daddy died in '79.
That's when she had the
stroke and that's...
when she and the bird went
into Murray's home.
Do you remember who
you bought it from?
Yep, sure do.
He was being transferred
out of state,
so he couldn't take
the bird with him.
I've got some information
on him if you'd like.
I'll get it for you.
I think I found him here.
That's him.
Stowalski, Eli Stowalski.
Seen him ata screaming eagles
reunion about four years ago.
Nice to see him
after all those years?
Naw, he was always
a total asshole.
LYMAN ON PHONE:
Hello, Mr. Stowalski?
This may seem strange, but I'm
calling about a bird.
It's the parrot you owned Mr.
Stowalski, back in the 60's.
STOWALSKI: What?
What are you talking about?
That thing should have
been dead years ago.
No, sir, it's him all right.
Mr. Ballard confirmed it.
Ballard? That asshole?
What would he know?
Did you teach him anything in
particular, Mr. Stowalski?
Who, ballard?
No sir, the parrot.
I sure did.
I painted his head white
with shoe polish, I was an
instructor with the
101st airborne, "screaming
eagles" you know?
So, I taught him to say:
"I'm an eagle."
the boys in the flight ready
room would rub his cage
before flying,
for luck.
Gave them some confidence, a
feeling of self-worth you know.
Like we were all
in it together.
Do you remember where
you bought him from?
From the paper.
Damn thing cost me 50 bucks,
back when that was real money.
You recall when that was?
Let me see.
I was just transferred...
must've been early... june 1968.
That's all I know.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Asshole.
"Screaming eagles", huh?
I'm an eagle!
[answering machine]
No one is home.
Please leave a message.
Hi.
I'm not sure if this
is the right number,
but I'm calling about
a parrot you sold.
In the 60's.
Anyway, I own it now and...
I'd appreciate it if you
could call me back.
Eh... 555-0115.
My name is Lyman. L-Y-M-A-N.
Thank you.
[chirping]
Prepare to meet your maker.
DR. REYNOSA: Parrots
thrive on contact,
feather plucking is often
associated with loneliness.
Have you thought about
getting him a mate?
No, this guy's pretty ancient.
Sex would probably pop
his heart like a balloon.
Well I don't know about you,
but I'd say it's a better way to
go than dying bald and alone.
Why do you do that?
You didn't look
through the peep hole.
It's none of your business
how I open my door.
It's just not safe, that's all.
Just because I'm not afraid of
my shadow is no reason for...
hey, is everything okay here?
Yeah thanks john,
everything's fine.
What, Sacajawea
break down again?
Cause I can give you a ride...
oh no she's great,
but I would love a ride in
your new car some time.
Yeah, sure thing babe.
I can give you a ride
any time you want.
[alarm beeps]
That's avery unsafe color.
You're a very
unacceptable person.
He just got a promotion,
and he bought
a car he's wanted for years.
Did you see that tie, puking out
of the collar of his shirt?
Oh who made you
the fashion police?
I came to apologize.
I should have told
you I was there.
I'd just been given all this
homework I'd missed and...
I brought a present.
I hate all that flowers
of forgiveness crap.
It's for your dog.
It's got... it's got these
reflective stu ds on it.
Just like you.
His name is Floyd, and just
because he accepts your gift,
doesn't mean that I forgive you.
In that case, would
you go out with me?
How about you?
I can't.
Remember?
Our schedules are so opposite.
It would either have
to be early in the morning,
or really late at night.
Then come to work with me.
Tonight?
I'll pick you up.
But Floyd can't come.
He sleeps a lot anyway.
Are you serious?
I can come?
God, that is so cool!
Floyd, get your butt in here.
[clears throat]
Change into this,
I'll be back at 9.
Roger that.
And don't bend the
visor on the cap,
I like it the way it is.
Howdy.
Deputy courtesy patrol officer
James reporting for duty.
Do I have to wear
this sleeping bag?
It is so not my color.
Ok.
From now on, you do exactly
what I tell you,
or the free ride is over.
- Got it?
- Got it.
You don't get out of the truck,
roll down the window,
or touch anything unless I say?
Sir yes, sir.
And if I tell you
to do something,
you do it immediately.
You don't ask why.
You just do it.
It's for your own safety.
Understood?
Understood.
Ok.
Now scoot across the
seat and kiss me.
[knock on window]
Oh, my god, it's you again.
Sorry.
It might help if you
turned off your light bar
while you make out.
[laughing]
You're supposed to wear
clothes under the jumpsuit.
I've got clothes on.
What clothes?
My underwear.
What kind of underwear?
Just wondering...
well continue wondering.
Did you know you have more
college credits than I do?
I looked you up.
You've taken every
utilitarian course
offered over the
past ten years.
Every fix-it, lifesaving,
plumbing, woodworking,
italian, chinese,
self-defense,
and yet no degree?
I take courses to learn stuff.
Well if you'd taken some
literature or philosophy
courses, you'd understand
the parrot.
I don't need a formal education
to understand the obvious.
Oh, really?
Tell me what's so obvious...
"shut up."
No, you shut up!
No, "shut up."
It's the first thing the
bird said, which means
en and stop talking long
enough to understand the rest.
[car screeching]
You okay?
You've gotta be careful,
that truck must have been
going at least ninety.
Okay, "stay tuned"...
be alert in case of danger.
Ak for yourself...
make up your own mind.
Be an independent thinker.
Next,
I'm an eagle.
That just feel good to say it.
Yeah, feels good.
I like to say "I'm a
Tyrannosaurus Rex."
come on, try it with me.
Uh-oh, work.
Stay here.
What seems to be the problem?
[speaking spanish]
I couldn't fix
my car if I had to.
The internal combustion engine
is all cause and effect.
Anyone can understand
it, then fix it.
As opposed to people?
Well, they're
not so easy to fix.
What is that supposed to mean?
Relationships... they don't last,
they all break in the end.
That's fairly pessimistic.
I'm being honest.
Take you, for instance.
You've lived in what, a half a
dozen cities since you left
school, with a whole string
of temporary friendships.
Then you move on.
I have friends and family
all over the country.
What about you?
Have you ever crossed
the state line?
It's not like I've
got family to visit.
Ok. I was engaged once,
but he wouldn't set a date.
Then I found out he
was already married.
No one else ever came close.
Maybe they don't all last
Lyman, but like they say,
doesn't mean the fall
wasn't worth the ride.
You know, you could pick
your own first name.
I never found a name
that seemed right.
I guess my mom wasn't one for
sewing on name-tags.
But what about your birthday?
When do you have your party?
It's not important.
FIONA: take this exit.
Make a right.
I want to show you something.
Your parents checked in here.
No previous address.
And then in a moment, they were
taken, and you continued.
After the accident, they
couldn't be traced.
No next-of-kin, and you
couldn't remember anything.
Missing persons
turned up nothing.
I chased every lead,
blood types,
car registration,
every receipt.
I just kept thinking that there
must have been somebody
out there who would
have missed them.
Code of the west, rule number
one, "don't inquire into a man's"
"past." don't you read those
books you pass around?
Rule number two,
"take the measure of a man
for what he is today."
you're right. I'm sorry.
Do you hate my guts now?
Yeah I do hate your guts, but I
sure like the bag they come in.
Come on, lets eat.
I understand about Ma 17
and some of the rest, but then
there is the bible stuff.
The "prepare to meet
your maker",
you never know when
your number is up.
Don't have regrets.
The ecclesiastes
thing makes sense...
yep, eat drink and be merry.
I'm all for that.
It's very optimistic.
It is not.
I'm prepared, and you just
keep your fingers crossed.
You think the parrot
makes sense,
but there are some things you
are never going to learn.
You don't understand life
like I don't understand
how to fix a car.
It's all just one big
tangle under the hood.
I think some women
believe that a man is born
the moment they meet him.
Now what'll you you have?
Why thank you, Lyman.
"T builder of men."
well, I do my best.
Margie, this is Fiona.
I heard about you.
Is my Lyman sweet
on you, honey?
I think it's the
way that I dress.
Thank you Lyman,
for bringing her by.
I approve.
MARGIE VO: They were
talking so hard,
like there was a
fire somewhere and
only their words
could put it out.
I could tell just by the sound,
seemed like Lyman was finally
getting closer to an answer.
I left them alone.
I decided dinner
was on me that night.
How many campbells
have you called?
I'm still trying.
I have dozens left.
Some of these people just talk
and talk and talk, and
I can't get them off the phone.
What?
Cheese stuck on your teeth.
Toast crumbs at the
corners of your mouth.
Butter on your lips.
Want to go fishing?
Oh Lyman, you say
the sweetest things.
It takes a few seconds to reach
bottom, but it comes up quick.
I've found hubcaps, cans, tools.
Once I found a set of
braces, with a tooth in it.
Wow Lyman, that's the mother
load. Now we can retire,
and live happily ever after.
Maybe one day I'll solve
a great mystery.
The crime of the century.
Until then I just
fish for clues.
Fiona?
Happy birthday... Mr. Lyman.
What?
I couldn't bear the thought of
you never having birthdays.
But I don't know
what the date is.
So I figured someone
better pick a date,
and I say it's today.
Unless you can prove me wrong.
I declare this the
thirty something
birthday of baby boy Lyman.
It's around now that
you blow out the candle
before I'm horribly
disfigured by molten wax?
There. You're no longer a
birthday cake virgin.
If you're looking for
something french and lacy,
you uh... you
got the wrong girl.
I uh... I don't think
I'll be talking anymore
from here on out.
[d...]
You're perfect...
Sshhhhhh...
[car screeching]
[dog squealing]
What was that?
They hit a goddamn dog.
Stay here.
[whimpering]
Is it going to be okay?
Lyman?
What are you doing?
Oh god, please no.
Just stay in the truck, Fiona!
Lyman, we can take
it to the vet.
Lyman, please listen to me!
Lyman, please!
Lyman, no!
[gunshot]
[crying]
Fiona, there was no saving it.
How can you bear to do this?
I've never had to
share it with anyone.
I don't want to share that.
[chirping]
Give some to the parrot.
Just you and me now, buddy.
From now on,
thou shalt be called...
"zane".
[chirping]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
MRS. WEBER: Hello?
Can I speak to Mr.
Lyman please?
Speaking.
This is mrs. Weber.
I'm returning your
call about the parrot.
Come on in,
one more won't make
a difference.
WEBER: Jesus Christ,
it's him.
I don't believe it,
he's still alive.
Yep.
That awful bird.
Mr. Lyman, this is
my husband duncan.
[chirping]
Oh, he's a sight for sore eyes.
Kids, this is old tonto.
My dear friend from back
in the olden days
when I was your age, henry.
BILLIE: I'm Billie.
Dad always talked about his
parrot like he was human.
SUSIE: Sue.
We didn't know what to believe.
Tonto was my best friend.
We used to listen to the lone
ranger on the radio every week.
He could mimic all
of the theme music.
[sings theme]
Does he still say
"Hi-ho silver away?"
No.
Oh.
I thought he was the smartest,
funniest thing in the world.
That was before
he met me, of course.
I was an only child.
This bird got me a lot of
friends at school.
He could do tricks, he was
like a one man circus.
Why did you sell
him, Mr. Weber?
Because I didn't want
him around the children.
I thought they
carried diseases.
That's not why you
wanted him out, ella.
It was the green-eyed
monster, jealousy.
She loves me more
than life itself.
She couldn't bare to
share me with anyone.
Well if you can find anyone
who'll take you now,
they're welcome to you.
He must have been pretty
rare back then,
did he come from a pet store?
Oh no, from a
neighbor, mrs. Hall.
She had a son michael, back
then we called retarded.
Dad I told you,
you can't say that.
...challenged,
yes. Challenged.
The kid learned to
speak by mimicking the bird.
Do you know where
the halls got him?
Oh sorry no,
I never asked, and
they're long dead now.
[chirping]
Ma 17!
It must have been hard
giving him up, Mr. Weber.
Yeah, but look what I got in
exchange. A world of family.
The bird got me
through my childhood,
ella got me through
the rest of it.
Thanks for bringing
him by, son.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
[siren blaring]
[dog howling]
[dog whimpering]
[air horn blaring]
[automatic operator] The number
you dialed has been changed,
disconnected or is no
longer in service.
If you feel you have
reached this...
prepare to meet your maker!
190 here.
Mile marker 83.
Driver's out of his car.
He looks drunk.
Send the troopers.
RADIO: 190, roger.
Why'd he want you
to shoot his car?
He was tired of it.
Gee, I'm tired of my boss...
why do you work
the night shift?
Because my husband does too.
It's the only way we can be
together, have a life.
Aren't the people who
are out at night strange?
Don't you get tired of it?
I like my job.
I like the people
who come in at night.
My regulars.
You thinking of qu1tl'ing
the courtesy patrol?
12 years.
You've been at it for so long.
Cars don't break down as often,
but, people need
me as much as ever.
I don't know, 1t just doesn't
seem to mean much anymore.
You'll find it again,
like your parrot.
Being lost is only temporary.
Hi.
Well Floyd can come in too.
He's fine where he is.
This is for you.
And I need the library
books, they're overdue.
Sorry, I forgot.
I'll pay the fines.
Than ks.
I call him zane now.
I named him.
That's good, Lyman.
I'm happy for you.
Well I called you,
your number was disconnected
and I came by...
yeah, I've been really busy,
getting ready to leave.
I found another
library that needs me.
So...
you're leaving?
I thought I'd spend some
time with my family.
Fiona, you know there
wasn't anything else
I could do for that dog.
She was suffering...
I know that, Lyman.
I know that.
It was all just a bit
too stark for me.
I felt like that dog was a
part of me or something.
But I can't think
of you out there,
every night with all of that...
so umm...
I have something for you.
A going away present.
Ivy campbell, daughter of jack
campbell from the 1930 census.
There's no phone number
but there's an address.
If you'd just stay we...
I've never been able to stay.
Maybe I don't want to
believe what you believe.
know what you know.
I have to leave.
I knew you couldn't take it.
So you were trying
to sabotage us?
Is that why you let
me go with you?
Oh, I'm not the one
running away.
You'll never get anywhere
in this piece of tin.
You've got romance novels
for auto sense.
Your right back-up light is out,
your tire treads are shot, you
need an engine overhaul.
God only knows what condition
your brakes are in.
If you head out onto the highway
without knowing where the jack
is, you'll end up stranded in
the middle of the desert
or on top of some mountain or...
yes Lyman, but people like you,
and they are few and far
between, they always
seem to show up.
Good-bye.
Excuse me, I'm sorry
to drop by like this.
Does ivy campbell live here?
IVY: I don't want
any insurance.
I'm going to die
whether I've got it or not.
I'm here about this parrot.
I believe your
father owned him?
Mr. Roosevelt?
But how could that be?
I gave him away in the 50's to a
woman named emma cowen.
She'd lost a baby, so I
gave her Mr. Roosevelt
to keep her spirits up.
She had him until
she had her next child,
then she gave him
to a slow fella.
Mike hall.
Yes.
And I lost track from there.
He still says your phone
number from when you
lived on summit drive.
Ma17?
That was our phone number?
He's got a better
memory than I do.
Who's bird was he?
My father's.
He was killed in the war.
Was he a religious man?
I don't think so.
Mother gave him a
bible before he left.
Father said he might not read
it, but he would keep it in his
breast pocket to protect him
from a well-aimed bullet.
What he worshipped
was this country.
Then who taught him
the bible verse...
'a bird of the air
shall carry the word?'
why, he came to us saying that.
Do you know where
your father got him?
Mother said that he
bought Mr. Roosevelt
from a band of gypsies that
were passing through.
What does it
matter Mr. Lyman?
I've gone as far as I can go.
I don't know where to go next.
You go forward, Mr. Lyman.
Forward.
We met at the beginning and
the end of long lives.
Goodbye Mr. Roosevelt.
Ooh...
I woke up and the
heat had gone down.
I forgot to refill
the propane tank.
It's all my fault.
He's a tropical bird.
He couldn't stand the freeze.
Just be prepared, Lyman.
He's an old bird.
This might be his time.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
TOM ON RADIO: Lyman, I know
you're taking some time off,
but there's been a black ice
pile-up on the
west street bridge.
Fiona was one of
the people involved.
[horn blaring]
Move!
Get out of the way!
No! Floyd!
No Floyd!
Floyd!
Nooo!
DR. DOUGHERTY:
And next of kin?
No.
None.
I need your accident report.
Hi daddy.
It sucks.
Mom, I need to come home again.
Right there.
And I thought he
couldn't stand Floyd.
No, he just couldn't let
himself get too close
to a live dog, that's all.
Stay tuned!
You are one lucky parrot.
[chirping]
Tornado!
[grunting]
What?
Zane?
FIONA VO: Lyman, I'm
taking you with me.
I want to give you my family.
You can't work a while
anyway and I have a few weeks
until my next job,
so I thought we could
look out for each other.
And you can finally see some
of the rest of the planet.
You were out cold for a week.
Then you started telling
me about gypsies.
Me and half the hospital staff.
They finally let me
take you this morning.
I'll stop, if you
want to turn around.
Call me on channel 9.
In this state, it is
against the law
to haul a trailer with
someone in it.
Unless, you've got a
special license.
Frank and Neil and Tom helped,
and don't worry,
it all passed inspection.
Why didn't you ask me?
Well you've been
on pain killers.
Plus I didn't trust
you to make the break.
You're unreliable when it
comes to your own interests.
I still get confused.
Tell me again...
oh well, when you threw
him to me I caught him,
but then I stuck my
finger in his eye.
He'll get better too.
Fiona, I've never
been outside the county line.
Not in my whole life.
Just wait till you see
the atlantic ocean.
Fiona...
and you know what else?
I got a tool belt to snap onto
your wheelchair, just in case.
We're prepared.
What the heck...
let's go.
Surprise me.
[d...]