Jan Svankmajer is a Czech filmmaker,
krown for his animation.
THE SVANKMAJERS' lMAGlNlNGS
Jan Svankmajer's work
goes beyond filmmaking.
For more than 30 years
he has worked with his wife Eva,
and their work
is inseparable from their life.
Engraving, painting, collage,
ceramics, invention of objects
and animals, puppets,
poetry and so on.
They work in many different media,
but always as a response to surrealism.
As secret members of the surrealist group
in communist Prague,
since the Velvet Revolution
they have beer working tirelessly.
Last winter they interrupted work
on their new film  Little Otik,
to organise an exhibition
showing their body of work.
HUMAN ANATOMY
NATURAL HlSTORY
And over there are the collages.
Yes, those are the collages.
Some of them are new,
some are of disjointed anatomy.
- But those are new things?
- Yes, also.
l found inexpensive, second-hand
anatomical atlases.
l couldn't resist cutting them up.
Although it's a bit...
Some objects travel
from one film to another
or from another art form to a film
or conversely from a film to another art form.
l think there is only one sort of poetry
and that the form of expression
of that poetry is not that important,
whether it's film, painting,
engraving, collage or ceramics.
lt's professional laziness
to only use one form of expression.
ln that respect l consider myself
to be a militant surrealist.
The Felaceus Oedipus or 'false Oedipus'
is an extremely rare species found
on the edge of the Australian bush.
Its neck extends
from a giant elastic pouch,
A bony thorax rises
from the upperpart of the neck.
The Australian Aborigenes
call the bird 'Maca Samambo',
which means 'giver of sons'.
They believe that
if a pregnant woman eats one of its eggs,,
she will give birth to a son.
And the Felaceus Oedipus' eggs
hatch into male chicks,
which are born penis first.
There was once a man and a woman
who didn't have any children,
which made them very urhappy.
One day the man went into the forest
and there he found a root
in the shape of a little boy.
He took it back to his wife
and they called it Otesánek
We are cutting various shapes
of Otesánek's body
for different stages of the animation.
We need the legs
to have different positions,
the branches as legs
in different positions
so we can make them move
as Otesánek moves.
And what's that for?
That's to animate the facial expressions.
We choose different shapes
with different orifices
because afterwards they become eyes or teeth,
orifices where light disappears.
We want to make Otesánek's expressions
out of real pieces of wood.
There are still lots of Otesáneks
to be made here.
For example,
this piece of wood has a lovely penis.
We have chosen to create the movement
in different stages.
There are some with their legs apart,
others with one leg
or with both legs together.
And we're going to film all that
in sequences of two images
to create movement.
We made this one sitting down
so the mother can hold it in her arms.
For the animation,
they will be done differently,
clothed and made of lead wire.
Fingers and hands will be animated,
the legs and head will move.
This stage is between that one -
its legs are closer together which is good -
- and this stage.
l think we should have enough stages.
lf we add the two completed Otesáneks
we have over there,
l think that should be enough.
l'll chop it into pieces!
You've gone mad!
You've gone mad. l won't let you.
Martin, there's one there on that side.
There on that side.
A feature of these pine roots
is that they look like little fingers.
We're going to use them
to make Otesánek's fingers and toes.
So we've come here
to look for fingers and toes.
The roots can go up and then disappear.
We can start.
The shoulder!
ls it going?
Otesánek!
We're using classical techniques
to animate Little Otik
We're going to combine animation
in close-up shots
with techniques
using puppets on nylon strings.
And we're going
to combine that with shots
where someone is inside Otesánek
with gloves made like little roots.
He moves his hands,
his fingers, the roots.
So we combine
those classical techniques.
That's the best way because...
because before the spectator can grasp
how each picture is made
the technique changes again.
So he's been tricked
and can't work out how we did it.
lf you move something
when animating the roots,
you'll have to work with it...
ls it more difficult to animate
real wood than latex?
ln some ways
it's a bit more complicated
but on the other hand,
the material implies its own movement
so, in a sense, the material cooperates.
lt's not the stylisation of an object.
So it's more difficult.
But l prefer it
because it's kind of natural.
Animating Otesánek
is physically demanding!
Leave that
Don't do that
Why don't you listen to me?
Don't tear it.
What did l tell you?
What do you think
of computer animation?
l haven't used it so far.
What l've seen up to now seems
to be very cold,
very technical, very distant.
All that l've needed
to do up until now
l have done using classical,
manual techniques,
including the film Food
where the characters...
are devouring the tables and chairs
and we see their heads change.
All that was done with modelling clay.
lt's not that l am a lover
of the days gone by
but l don't like these techniques
because there's something missing.
lt's too perfect.
The technique is too garish.
Whereas with manual animation,
it's less precise.
There are lots of little
imperfections and mistakes
and for me mistakes are very important
because they make the film subjective.
Like the ancient Hermeticists,
l believe that objects
have a life of their own.
And because
they have witnessed certain events,
or rather because
they've been handled by people
who were in a certain frame of mind,
who were tense or anxious,
and these objects have absorbed all that
and in certain situations objects
can convey what they have absorbed.
So based on what l feel they contain,
l collect these objects
and introduce them into my films.
THE CELLAR
Places haunt me as much as themes.
One of the most haunting themes
is the cellar.
l really suffered as a child
when l had to go down there.
The cellar in Alice
and of course in Little Otik  too,
is the cellar from my childhood.
There was a cellar like that
in our block of flats in Vrsovice.
My mother sent me down to the cellar
to fetch coal when l was older
and before that to fetch potatoes.
lt was, of course...
a terrifying experience.
lt was awful.
When my mother asked me
to go down to the cellar for potatoes,
l almost felt like
running away from home.
But at the same time,
it fed my imagination.
Why did you choose to use a little girl
to represent your fear?
lt didn't feel right to use
a little boy in that role
because l thought
that my anxiety was linked
to the feminine side that exists in a man.
So l decided to replace myself
with a sort of childlike
incarnation of my spirit.
These objects are from the film Alice
There you have croissants with nails
and these are eggs with skulls.
lt's marinated in something.
Some eggs are probably bad
and if we were to uncork the bottle,
it would stink.
Look, it's rotten there.
That's from the film Alice
This is classic putrefaction.
These are the shoes worn
by the cameraman on Alice
They've been in here since 1986.
lt's hermetically sealed
and they're slowly rotting inside.
We're going to put this one here
and the other one against the wall.
Here are the king and queen.
Eva has depicted herself
as the wicked queen.
Off with their heads!'
ordered the Queen.
This is the March Hare
and this is the Mad Hatter.
They're the characters in Alice
Eva made the hare and l made this one.
CREATlVE DlALOGUE
Can it be washed?
lt can't. l can scrub it
but water won't clean it.
All along l carry an idea about the film.
l also have an idea
and of where l come in,
what l will do.
l try my hardest
to understand what Jan wants.
I don't know how to copy.
l have my own personal expression.
l've had it for years...
Of course, l give Eva free reign.
What l want from her is
within the framework
of her own thinking, her own creativity.
She fits in
without forcing herself.
l can't say to her,
'l want that redder,' or 'bigger'.
Eva did a lot of work as a painter
on The Pendulum, the Pit and Hope.
She made the moving wall,
the panels which represent hell
and push the condemned into the abyss.
To sum up the collaborative process,
Eva has her own creative programme.
She is a painter,
she writes prose and poetry.
We work independently of each other.
We are linked by surrealism
but that's another matter.
Once l broke one
because people was watching me.
I needed them to go away,
so that l did not have to see
them seeing me.
Leave me alone.
l can see you're very good at group sex!
Oh, no!
Once someone l knew
invited me to an orgy
and l got such a shock
that he never suggested it again.
They are placed around the outside.
- That's impossible.
- Leave it.
l'll position that one.
lf you numbered them they must...
You'll break it.
That's not the way.
That's number five. lt can't go there.
But this one belongs here.
OK, OK.
This one fits in here.
You'll break it.
That's number two. lt goes there.
l put them wrong yesterday.
Right...
Wait!
You're messing it up.
Again. Take them all off.
We'll have to start again.
That one should be in front.
Eva.
Shouldn't they be the other way round?
What?
That one should be in front
and that one behind.
That one has to be in front.
l prefer not to see it.
Well, put some cloth over it.
We're always trying
to say something to each other.
We're always curious
of what the other's attitude will be...
how they will react.
lt broadens the perspective.
There we go. At last.
Why do you sign your ceramics E and J?
The initials E and J
distinguish between things
made by Jan and by me.
We work with the same materials,
we share the same life
but we express ourselves differently,
not in terms of ideas...
nor in terms of our interpretation of life,
but the art we create is different.
Our work is not interchangeable.
How did you work together on Little Otik?
Eva really liked
the story of 'Otesánek'.
She wanted to make it
into an animated film
and she wrote a script.
l tried to dissuade her
but Eva was already working on it,
and because of the transfer
of thought processes
that passes between two people
who live together...
l was very sceptical to start with
about the idea of making a film of a fairytale.
Then suddenly l found myself
thinking also about the subject.
lt started taking shape in my head.
And l said to myself,
'Christ, l can't steal this idea from Eva.'
But l had delved so deeply
into the subject
that l couldn't stop developing it further.
l was presented with a dilemma
and l didn't know what to do.
So l admitted to her
that l wanted to work on 'Otesánek' too.
She got a bit angry.
Then we realised
that there was no conflict of interests
and that we could incorporate
her film in mine.
One morning the man dug up
a little tree stump in the forest.
It looked like a little child.
He just had to cut the roots
into hands and legs.
These are the preliminary sketches
for the animation of Little Otik
Here's Otesánek in the house.
And that's the old woman
who cuts his stomach open.
But the ohd womar was quick
She took her hoe
and with one blow
split Otesánek's stomach open
These are the different stages
for the father
when he sees the mother
being wolfed down.
That's what it look s like.
Then l put it on a lit table...
l light it so l can copy
the different stages of the image,
with the agreement of the film's director.
But the director is unavailable at the moment
because he's looking after the actors.
These are our children's things.
The little hat, the panties. All of it.
- And look, this one has little buttocks.
- Look at the little bottom!
He has all he needs.
We've come here
to look for the film's protagonist.
l know what l need to look for.
Good.
l have a photograph of Eva at that age.
We're looking for a girl like her for the film.
l don't know if we'll find her.
lt's Jan who's looking for that.
l don't know how he knows
what l looked like as a child
because l'm different now.
Perhaps he has seen photos?
But it's him who's looking for that.
When the photos are ready,
Jan's going to take them.
Then he's going
to sit in a chair and complain.
You're going to say to him,
'You've wet yourself again.
Can't you warn me?'
You have to warn me
You mustn't do that
She's very expressive.
Yes, she's perfect. She's the best.
She doesn't look older there.
She's a big girl. She could be...
You should be ashamed of yourself
Who's going to wash that?
Bed-wetter
He's going to hurl himself at you
and you must be waving your arms about.
He will be fighting with him, won't he?
He is crawling like this into the bed.
This way so that you can stretch them.
How?
Against him.
Like that. Against him. Yes.
THE PERFECT PALACE
Tuesday 17 July
My cameraman and his wife Anna
came to our house in Stankov.
Having done a tour of the castle,
Anna made the following observation:
'You're transforming Stankov
into a puppet theatre'. She had a point.
I think what we had done with Stankov
was an amazing feat in its own way.
I hope we will have the courage
to see it through.
We need to build something
somewhere between Kuks Castle
and the postman Cheval's Perfect Palace -
a kind of surrealist home for sages.
It's going to need ever more concertration
and more intersive work.
We should draw up a plan
for the finished project.
Ever at the stage it's at row,
I think it could be a project
that will take your breath away.
But I don't know what to do.
lt's terribly neglected.
Why do you surround yourself with statues?
That's a stupid question.
How can you live without statues?
Without trees, without water?
Perhaps because life
without sculptures is meaningless.
Perhaps because sculptures,
like trees and things that last,
are essential to life.
l can't say why l put statues somewhere.
l can't.
Why is Jan fascinated by Arcimboldo?
l can't answer that.
You'll have to ask him.
Today I spent all day in the studio
making a new Arcimboldo.
It's terrible but I find this activity
as exciting as ever,
and I'll probably never understand why.
SURREALlSM
AGAlNST THE TlDE
At the end of the '60s,
especially with the Prague Spring,
we were able to organise one or two exhibitions
and publish a few things.
Then with the Soviet occupation
the group went back underground.
Here there was a big table
and we would sit here with the group.
The whole house was given over
to our surrealist activities.
The whole house almost all the time.
There was always someone sleeping there.
We had meetings every week.
We did that for years,
until the revolution.
Before, when we met in a cafe,
we could be sure that at the third meeting,
not the second but the third,
that at the next table
there would be a man in an raincoat
drinking beer slowly,
without looking at us.
So we said, 'We can't talk here.
We'll meet at the house.'
To a certain extent,
we were against Stalinism
as well as against other dissidents.
We were involved,
we communicated
with Havel, for example,
and with dissidents
who now hold political posts.
For 20 years
we illegally created
the real Czech culture.
When the totalitarian system
came to an end,
everyone dispersed.
Dissidents dispersed,
the underground movement broke up,
but the surrealist group stayed together.
ln the '50s
l had a manual and on the back page
there was a portrait of Gottwald,
who was the President
of Czechoslovakia,
as well as a portrait of Stalin.
For me these two men
were personal enemies
because they endangered
my family and my future.
l come from a rich family
and my only prospect was
to become a chimney sweep...
or a miner
and something else like that.
l can't remember.
Equally ghastly.
l'm a hard worker,
l don't mind crawling into a chimney
or digging coal. That's OK by me.
But what l objected to was the terrible...
deculturisation of society
and l felt despair at the idea
that one day someone might wrestle
my pencil or pen out of my hand.
l left school at 14 and said to myself
that no-one would ever snatch my pen off me.
lt was hard, but no-one ever did.
The regime has changed
and for ten years people have been
encouraged to be interested only in money.
lt's the same thing.
Whenever l say l'm a surrealist
l get pitying looks...
People think, 'Those poor people
who lived under communist rule,
they don't know that surrealism
is no longer fashionable.'
They tolerate my declaration
but as soon as we start discussing it,
especially with young people,
they start getting interested
because they understand there's more to it
than Salvador Dalí's paintings.
Young people
are interested in my films.
They realise
that there's more to surrealism
than they've learnt at school
and been told about.
They say to themselves,
'lf that's what surrealism is,
then it's not dead,
because l'm interested in it.'
FOOD
l was a very thin child
who needed to be fed constantly.
l was forced to eat,
l was sent to camps to be fed.
The only aim of these camps
was to force-feed kids.
lt was terrible.
lf a child put on a kilo in a week,
they got a sweet.
So each week
before we were weighed,
we drank loads of water
so as to put on a kilo.
Of course this was in collaboration
with the political regime
which was there to help everyone,
including skinny children.
lt was terrible.
We were kids separated from our families
and we spent two months there
at the hands of women
who force-fed us constantly.
They even refused to put me
in the top class
because l was too thin.
l even ended up in a wheelchair
because l couldn't walk any more.
lt was a traumatic experience
and of course l used it in my films.
The meal is naturally symbolic.
Food and eating are symbols of...
human aggressiveness.
And yet it was only when l had finished
writing the screenplay for Little Otik
that l realised that the whole film
was about my obsession with food.
Otik, drop that! Don't eat that!
We're going to add a bit more bark
to make it more realistic.
Then we'll do a close-up with the teeth.
But l don't have any rational control
over my obsessions.
They behave in an irrational way
and do what they want to do.
Otesánek could of course
also represent our unconscious.
We know that fairytales
start out as myths -
either cosmic myths
or social myths,
but myths all the same.
Otesánek is definitely an archetype.
And that's what interests me,
going to the root of what
Otesánek embodied for people.
He's not just a monster who scares kids.
EROTlClSM
Eva has made all these dolls.
They're the main characters
for the film Conspirators of Pleasure
Can you hold it there?
This one's a travelling lady,
like the inflatable dolls
or the dummies that
men get themselves in prisons.
Mr Pivoine, the character in the film,
got himself a doll made
in the image of his neighbour.
And she made a doll of him.
They play out their sadomasochistic
relationship through these figurines.
Erotic fantasies
are figments of the imagination
and generally they aren't played out...
at the level of what we view as sexuality.
These are purely imaginative perversions.
That's why l so meticulously,
almost in a documentary-like fashion,
record the lengthy preparation
to show what people are willing to do
to satisfy their erotic fantasies -
what they're prepared
to be subjected to.
lt's clear that for lots of people
television has become
the only contact they have with the world,
including with eroticism.
l don't know if it's the same in France,
but there are erotic films
on Czech television every Saturday night.
Television is the only contact
a lot of people have with the real world
and represents the only reality they know.
Clearly, it targets this type of civilisation,
communication of a bawdy kind.
TACTlLlSM
Tactile game
We buy four wooden rolling pins.
We cover one half of a rolling pin
with grains of uncooked rice
and the other half with the scahes
from a broken pine cone.
We get undressed
and so as to heighten the sensibility
of the skin on the stomach and thighs,
we brush it with emery paper.
lt's quite arousing.
And here...
l'm touching a kitten.
l'm putting my hand in its mouth
and it's licking me.
Touch is the first sense
to develop in humans,
even before they see or listen,
they feel the mother's body.
So it is a very important sense
which has never been
shaped in an aesthetic form.
lt hasn't been developed
in the same way as sight or hearing,
which have their own forms
of art and poetry.
Watch that she doesn't bite.
And there...
There l'm touching someone's nose.
Touch is always constrained
by utilitarian functions.
l wanted to instigate new research
with the aim of developing
new possibilities for touch.
l wrote a tactile poem
called 'Beside the Tactile Sea'
because we are merely at the edge
of this unexplored ocean.
That's how it's meant to be read.
There's a word,
then a tactile element.
Then more words,
then another tactile element, etc.
These are the tactile objects.
l call it the 'new eroticism'.
lt's for autosexuality.
This is obviously how you use it.
And this one like this.
We know that in its utilitarian function
sight is closely linked to touch.
So sight can serve
as an intermediary for touch,
through imagination,
not in the natural world.
lt opens up new opportunities.
That's what l used
in Conspirators of Pleasure
when they use tactile rolling pins.
l think many people
through their eyes
sensed the rolling pins as if they were
being used on their own bodies,
thanks to the imagination.
l see this as the future for tactile films,
rather than handing out
objects to be touched.
For me tactilism is something
very sexual, terribly private...
Jan has opened up a secret chamber
and l have never fully come
to terms with it.
Every time...
it still shocks me.
l wrote the text before making the object.
First l expressed my feelings in words,
the tactile impressions
l would have had
when l put my hand inside Eva.
In the bottom corner
there will be pieces of broker glass,
which mean that you heave
Eva's portrait feelling wounded.
Have you touched your tactile portrait?
l read the notes. That was enough.
lmagine if there had been
a mouse in there.
No, thank you.
Eva and Jan have just finished making Little Otík.
Already in the preparation
an international exhibition
with the various surrealist groups,
a film about the life
of the Marquis de Sade,
several cartoons inspired
by popular Czech fairytales,
a fantasy crockery set,
and busts and portraits of their friends,
a series of new tactile collages,
the publication of a monograph
and a collection of poems,
an anthology of subversive literature,
the conversion of an old barn
into a gothic castle.
We'd like to thank everyone,
particularly Eva Svankmajerová
and Jan Svankmajer
for their availability, kindness and patience
throughout this project.