What are you doing?
Nothing.
Tell me what you're doing.
Setting up these speakers
my friend Mike gave me.
- Can I help?
- No.
- C'mon please?
- No!
- Why not?
- Because.
- Just fuck off and leave me alone!
- Mom!
What?
What are you doing?
- Can I please help you?
- Quit fucking hitting me!
- Please?
- No!
- Mom!
- Alright, fine.
- What do you need me to do?
- Help me lift the TV up.
Why do we need to move the TV?
Because I have to get in there
and drill a hole in the back.
It's heavy!
What do we do now?
Help me lift this.
Alright, now pass me the drill.
- No I want to drill.
- Give me the fucking drill.
- I want to drill.
- Give me the drill, alright?
- No
- Quit fucking around, give me the drill!
No!
- Gimme...
- Mom!
Alright.
- In the middle, right here.
- Okay.
It's not working...
Oh my god.
Are you sure you're
doing it right?
- Just push it through!
- I'm trying!
- Give me the fucking drill.
- Okay.
Just give it to me,
stop screwing around.
Fuck, it's in reverse.
Ow, my eye!
I didn't mean to!
Are you ok?
I didn't mean to, it's okay.
- What hap- Marc! Jesus!
- I was setting up these
speakers and drilling a hole
- and he was right there...
- Okay, lets go, lets go!
I don't know
what you were thinking.
It wasn't even my fault,
I don't understand why you blame
- everything on me.
- Then whose fault is it?
- It wasn't mine! I was
setting up these speakers-
You don't give
an eleven year-old a power tool!
I was setting up these speakers
that I got, and he wanted to help,
- and he kept bothering me-
- Thanks for the speakers by the
way, great thinking-
- You're welcome! I mean the place is
a fucking shit hole and I was just trying to-
- Do not call our place a shit hole!
- It's a fucking shit hole!
Don't smile!
I'm working my ass off!
Well work harder.
Oh, this is funny?
You need to grow up.
Hello, Stephen.
- Hello.
- Hi.
You are very lucky.
His eye was scratched
pretty good.
He's got a lacerated cornea.
Luckily, the drill
barely touched his eye.
Now, the scar will be there
forever,
but it's nothing that
won't hear it on it's own. Ok?
- So... are we going to be
seeing a lot of you?
Well, yes.
Are we going to have all these
repeat treatments for this, cornea, or...
He'll have to come in a
few times for check-ups, and
even after the patch comes off
we'll want to monitor the
scar, just to make sure
things are healing properly.
It's quite normal.
Stephen, can you go
outside for a bit?
Okay.
I was... I just...
I'm wondering, if you have any idea
how much this is going to cost me?
Yeah I got this scheme
to get the girls...
I go where they all,
ya know, flock together...
and then I break out my violin
and I play something real romantic
Really?
If you don't got someone
to fuck you got to go looking
- for one, ya know?
- Mm-hm.
Ever been to one of
those those uh-
"Social Nights" over at the
community center, have you?
Uh no, I don't know
about those.
Well, maybe you're a little
too young for that.
It's mostly older girls, like
divorcees and widows and shit...
Mhmm.
- Yeah it's a total trip.
- I bet.
When I was your age,
I had a girl.
What was her name?
Her name was Crystal.
She'd fuck me any way I wanted.
Whenever I wanted.
Yeah.
How's your eye feel?
Fine.
Can you see alright?
Yeah.
What do you have
going on at school?
It's summer school, no
one cares. It's stupid.
Well I have to work every day,
and Marc's working all summer,
so you're not staying here
watching TV every day.
Everyone's going to
laugh at my eye patch.
You want me
to call them?
- I don't want you to call.
I can deal with it.
What's your teachers name?
Ms. Moss.
Number three?
They can
propose laws.
Right, they can propose laws.
So not only do they have
the right to do away with a law,
they also have
the right to suggest a law.
Okay.
Who can give me three
responsibilities of the Judicial Branch?
Yes.
They have control
over the Supreme Court?
That's right.
Control over Supreme
Court. Anyone else?
- Stephen, how about you
-Huh?
What did I just say?
Stephen, can you
come to the front please?
Thank you, now, I want you to do
me and your classmates a favor-
I want you to tell everyone
what happened to your eye,
so they can stop wondering
and start paying attention.
I was helping my brother
and I hurt it.
Ok, and how did you hurt it?
A drill.
I'm sorry?
A drill went into my eye.
Thank you. Have a seat.
Okay.
Hey Sheryl,
how's it going?
Hi, I'm just
about done, sorry.
No worries,
take your time.
We actually thought we
were going to be here earlier
but we're a little late.
Sorry about that.
- That's alright.
- Cheque for you?
That'd be great.
How was your day today?
It was good, thanks.
Alright well, there
you go, thanks very much.
- It looks great.
- Thanks, I appreciate it.
Sure.
I smoke.
Dude some of my friends
smoke weed and I want to try it soon
My friend- my
friends mom and dad,
both of them did it.
They were smoking,
They caught the couch on fire!
Have you ever looked
at one of these before?
No.
Here.
So damn hot out here, man.
Why are you guys
in summer school?
Didn't read the books.
My- my- my mom just
put me in here-
Shut the fuck up.
Hey!
You cannot be on this roof!
Get over here!
The rest of you have until the
count of three to get over here.
Stephen!
You could get
in a lot of trouble for this!
I know.
I'm sorry.
Nice eye patch.
Thanks.
You look like a pirate,
kind of.
Thanks, I know.
What's it like?
What do you mean?
Well, do you only see
half of everything?
I pretty much see everything.
So what do you
think of this place?
It's really cool.
Yeah it's pretty neat.
So, you got a boyfriend?
No.
Why not?
Don't want one.
Well, you think maybe
I could be your boyfriend?
No.
Why not?
I don't know...
I've never had
a boyfriend before.
Well I've had a few girlfriends.
What did you guys do together?
You know, just hung out at
school, went to the movies,
nothing too big.
Will everyone know?
Well, I guess.
Is that bad?
No, but,
my parents wouldn't like it.
Well we could just keep it
a secret for now.
So you want me to be
your girlfriend?
Yeah.
Okay.
Cop hold? Huh?
Oh fuck!
One! Two! Three!
Hi, how are you doing?
Doing alright, how are you?
I'm fine, good.
I'm just getting
ready to leave, actually-
Oh, damn, I'm sorry to hear that.
Thanks.
You have a good night.
Thanks, maybe I'll see you
again next time.
You fuckin' her yet?
Uh, no not yet, but I
mean, we're moving pretty fast.
No you haven't,
I can tell.
You want her to put out, you
gotta give her something nice.
Like jewelry or some shit.
Why do you say that?
Girls are suckers
for that.
You give her some jewelry,
she'll put out, trust me.
Am I doing it right?
Yeah, yeah,
you're fine.
Is something wrong?
No.
I can tell
that something's wrong.
Nothing's wrong.
Do you want to do
something else?
No, you're fine.
Do you want me to do
something else?
Well
I mean, just, ya know, an idea-
Yeah, go ahead-
Could you use your mouth?
I've never-
It's just an idea,
you don't have to.
Do you want me to? Do you really
want me to do that?
Yeah of course.
Would it feel good for you?
Yeah, definitely.
Okay well, you have to
tell me when.
Because I don't want
to taste it.
Of course.
Do you promise me?
Yeah I promise,
of course.
Do you pinky-promise me?
Pinky-promise.
Okay.
Look at that car!
That's a piece of shit!
I bet that's your car, Stephen!
That was the weakest throw
I've ever seen.
Nice!
Yeah!
Come on guys!
We can do
better than this!
That close up,
you can't do nothin'!
You can't
do any better!
Nice throw,
you weakling!
Come on guys, watch this!
What the fuck you doing?
Whatcha gonna do about it?
What should I write?
What should he write?
"Fag"
Write "fag", Stephen!
Yeah!
I bet he can't
even spell "fag"!
That's what he is!
He can't spell his name!
Hey, you know what
a blow-job is?
It's when a girl
puts it in her mouth.
What does it feel like?
Pretty good. My girlfriend does
it whenever I want.
You have a girlfriend?
Don't tell Mom.
Why not?
Don't fucking tell her!
I think I love you.
You love me?
Yeah.
Are you in love with me?
Yeah, is that bad?
I'm just not ready yet.
What do you mean
you're not ready?
I can't.
Well, when are you
going to be ready?
If you love me then
there's no rush.
People who love
each other have sex.
That's what happens.
I'm just not ready.
Well when are you
going to be ready?
I'm getting tired of waiting.
I just want you so bad,
is that wrong?
No.
Well then I don't see
what the problem is.
I heard it hurts.
It doesn't hurt.
For girls it does.
No it doesn't, it feels great!
How would you know?
I just do.
Will you just please tell me
when you're going to be ready?
I don't know.
Mom?
Yeah?
Can I have some money?
What do you need money for?
I don't know,
I could just really use some.
Well, you have a job, you
could use that money.
Yeah, well I could have enough
if I waited all summer but, I need it now.
Well, you should know,
as an adult if you...
spend money you don't have,
it puts you in a bad situation.
Please can I just have the money
and I'll pay you back as soon as I
get it from my work?
How much do you need?
Maybe, two hundred?
What the hell do you
need two hundred dollars for?
I want to get something
for my girlfriend.
Well I don't have
two hundred dollars.
So I can't give you
anything I don't have...
You can save the money,
then buy whatever it is this
thing you want with your own
money.
Mom?
Yeah?
Can I have
some money too?
No one's getting any money!
But I need some...
Okay, shut up! Eat your food.
Okay, seven basic
principles of the Constitution,
can anyone name one?
- Yes.
- Freedom of speech?
Freedom of speech, yes, but what
principle does that fall under?
Individual rights?
That's right,
individual rights.
Can someone
name another one?
There's one in particular that
I'm looking for- yes?
Separation of power?
There you go,
separation of power.
The reason I was looking for
this one
is because we just
covered this the other day.
Who can give me
a third basic principle?
Stephen, can you stay
for a minute, please?
Can you come over here?
Everyone else, don't forget
your homework for tomorrow.
Okay, first of all,
you're not in trouble.
But I just wanted to talk to you
for a second,
because I've noticed that
you've been drifting in class
and you seem
a little distracted,
is there something on your mind?
No.
Is everything ok?
Yeah.
You're sure...
Okay,
well how are things at home?
Fine.
That's good, what about your mom
and dad, do you guys get along-
I don't have a dad.
Well what about your brother?
You mentioned you had
a brother... how old is he?
He's turning sixteen soon.
Oh okay, is he your best friend?
No.
How's your eye?
Feels better.
That's good.
Look, Stephen,
I just want you to know that if
you ever have any questions
or you feel like you need to talk to
someone, you can come to me, okay?
Okay.
Yeah?
What are you doing?
Using the bathroom.
Well,
I'm going to go pick up dinner.
Okay.
That bitch is
pissing me off.
She's always yelling at me about
slacking off and everything-
Wait, Stephen, didn't she like,
make you stay after school?
Yeah, why?
Why, dude?
Got some nice pictures
in here.
We should get her back
somehow... some shit.
Maybe we could break into
her house when she's not there-
Nah man, shit on her car-
Pee in her garden!
You guys really
shouldn't get back at her,
you guys are gonna get caught...
Because we're the only ones
in the class that hate her-
Shut up, Stephen!
- Everybody hates her!
- If we plan it right we won't!
What, are you sticking up for her?
Nah I ain't sticking up for her-
Then why don't you
wanna go with it?
You guys think I can
shoot this behind my back?
Who gives a shit?
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Nothing
- So what are you doing today?
- Working.
Oh, well, you think
you could come over?
Now?
Yeah, just take a lunch break
or something.
I already took it.
Oh.
-Well, I got something for you.
-What is it?
Just something.
Tell me what it is.
I gotta tell you in person,
you gotta come over to get it.
Okay.
Okay, alright.
I'll see you soon, alright?
- Okay.
- Alright, bye.
- Are you ready?
- Mm-hm.
- Are your eyes closed?
- Yeah.
Alright.
Is it a promise ring?
Well, if you want
it to be.
Do you want it to be?
Yeah.
It's so pretty.
Where did you get it?
It's a family heirloom.
And you're giving it to me?
Yeah, I love you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Do you really love me?
Yeah.
I love you too.
Doggy, doggy, doggy!
Doggy, doggy!
Come here!
Come here, dog!
Doggy, doggy, doggy!
You ready?
Come on, Stephen! Come on!
We gotta do this quick!
Stephen, I want you
to look out, alright?
Okay.
Don't be a pussy.
- Keep a close eye out!
- We gotta do this quick!
Gotta do this quick guys!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Shut up!
Guys hurry up!
It's gonna be so sweet
when I see her face.
Guys! She's here!
Hurry up!
Fuck!
Dude, come on!
She's coming!
Come on, Stephen!
Dude, come on!
Just leave him!
Come on!
There she is!
I didn't do it.
Don't lie to me, Stephen.
I'm not lying, I didn't do it-
Who did it?
I don't know!
Leave.
I didn't do it-
Leave!
Go!
She keeps looking over
here, man! Tell him!
Look, look...
You gonna show us
how to do it, mac-daddy?
Come on, you can do it.
Get me some chips
while you're over there.
Hey...
- Hey.
You want a... want a beer?
I snuck some in.
Sure.
I'm Sheryl.
I'm Gabe.
Thanks.
This is a great table you're at.
You come all the time to this?
No, you?
No.
Do you want to dance?
Yeah that'd be great, yeah.
♪ The very thought of you ♪
♪ And I forget to do ♪
♪ Those little ordinary things ♪
♪ That everyone ought to do ♪
♪ I'm livin' in a kind of daydream ♪
♪ I'm happy as a king ♪
♪ But foolish though it may seem ♪
♪ To me that's everything ♪
♪ The mere idea ♪
♪ The longing here for you ♪
♪ You'll never know ♪
♪ How slow the moments go ♪
♪ Until I'm near you ♪
♪ I see your face in every flower ♪
♪ Your eyes in the stars above ♪
♪ It's just the thought of you ♪
♪ The very thought of you ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ I see your face in every flower ♪
♪ Your eyes in the stars above ♪
♪ It's just the thought of you ♪
♪ The very thought of you ♪
♪ My love ♪
Thanks.
God, that was boring
in there, huh?
Yeah.
You want to go for a ride?
Okay.
I have two boys.
I have an eleven
year-old and a fifteen year-old.
Stephen, the eleven year-old, has
a patch on his eye right now.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Marc got him in the eye
with a power drill.
How's that happen?
Stupid... I don't know.
I've never heard of that.
You have any kids?
No.
We could go back to my place
if you want.
We'll have to be quiet but...
It'd be nice to hang out.
Yeah.
You have to stop.
Get off of me,
you have to stop.
I can't. I can't...
You have to stop,
get off of me.
Baby I can't, just...
just hold on.
We have to try
and be quiet.
Door slams shut]
Thank you.
We're gonna have to be quiet,
they're right in there.
They're right in there, okay?
Go upstairs.
Fuck.
Good morning.
Hey.
You in a hurry?
I'm late.
Can I make you some
breakfast or something?
I'm late!
I'm sorry, it's my second time
late this week-
I just...
I just wanted you to meet
Stephen and Marc, it's okay-
Who?
Stephen and Marc...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Look, second time late this
week, I gotta run.
Hey, I had a good time.
Fuck, Gabe?
Gabe!
My car, I forgot my car.
My car is at the club.
Okay, okay, okay!
I'll be in the truck!
Hey.
Want some crackers?
No thanks,
I'm good.
How's your eye doing?
It's doing good.
I don't even know why I have to
wear this stupid eye patch anymore.
It doesn't
do anything.
You should just take
it off. Who cares?
Okay.
The fair's coming up...
I know, you going?
Yeah, I think if my
older sister takes me.
Do you kiss girls?
Yeah, why?
I don't know.
What else have you done?
- What do you mean?
- With girls, what else?
A lot of things.
With who?
Who have you kissed?
Do you want to
kiss me?
Sure.
Well not if you
don't want to cause' it's-
Yeah.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah.
You want to try again?
Sure.
Why'd you take off
your eye patch?
It wasn't doing
anything anymore.
It made me
look like a pirate.
The End
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
E N J O Y   this   SRT   SUBTITLE   R e l e a s e
http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1528309
A Little Closer (2011) English for hearing-impaired.srt
AND: A Little Closer (2011) English.srt
FPS: 23.976
With special thanks to: "superbad"
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
We want more subtitles right NOW!
1) ALL DVD's to be subtitled.
2) ALL VIDEO GAMES to be subtitled.
3) ALL videos/DVD's used in lessons at school to be subtitled.
4) More pre-recorded & live subtitles on TV.
____           __            ___   __              ___        __               __
/     /   _   /    )  _   _ (_     /  _)        _  (_      _   /  _)        _   / _   _
(     /)  (-   /(_ /  (-  ( /  /     /(_)  () (/ _)   /   () /    /(_)  () (/ _)   (__)  /  () (/  /)
- Bringing you free subtitles       /                  Online  /  Since 1993    - /
-  |Africa| |Asia| |Australia| |Europe| |North America| |South America|   -  /
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+                          A big Thank You to EVERYBODY                            +
+        involved in making [closed capture] srt files and supporting us       +
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+