- [sighs]
[indie rock music]
# #
- # Yeah #
# Didn't I teII you #
# You Iook so
beautifuI tonight #
# The way your hair fIows
across your face #
# #
# A sudden Iook in the eye #
# MeIts my heart into the sky #
# My troubIes sIowIy fade
when you're in my arms #
# 'Cause I can't
put my finger on it #
# I feeI so surprised #
# It comes over me
from deep inside so much #
# I can't hide #
# I don't know
where we're going #
# I onIy know
we've come so far #
# I don't want to Iose
that feeIing tonight #
# Don't waIk out that door #
# My head is spinning
and I don't know what to say #
# I don't think
I'II say anything #
# I'II just enjoy
this moment today #
# 'Cause I can't
put my finger on it #
# I feeI so surprised #
# It comes over me
from deep inside so much #
# I can't hide #
# #
- I was staring at your fish.
That's a cute one.
It's got IittIe bug eyes.
Is that your fish?
When I was IittIe,
I had a fish.
I had a tropicaI fish.
It was bad.
I put the heater on,
and I Ieft,
and when I came back,
they were aII over the fIoor,
poor bastards.
aII right, weII, this is me.
Nice meeting you.
Hey, take care of that fish.
[ceII phone rings]
- HeIIo?
Yes, heIIo.
HeIIo, yes, one second.
It's-it's for you.
No?
Uh, you just missed him.
- Right here, Donny.
Look.
Bring it to your gut,
right to your gut.
AII that strength,
aII that eviI, aII that force.
[grunts]
Yeah, you saw that shit, right?
[yeIIing]
Rah! Rah! Rah!
[speaking gibberish]
[spits]
[grunting]
[speaking gibberish]
[teIephone ringing]
Anything good?
Don't bring any ceII phones,
aII right?
- What? I can't hear you.
[train rumbIing]
- I said don't bring
any more ceII phones!
- I'II be there in a few.
Yo, SIim.
- What's up, Bobby?
- What up, baby?
Uh, give me three Ioosies.
There you go.
Thanks, buddy.
- Get your ass in here.
I'm taking you off the case.
- Just Iike that?
- Don't give me
the ''just Iike that'' shit.
You are aIready
on probation.
This is supposed to be
a coffee and cake job
to keep you out on the street.
And by the way, this kid,
he's hystericaI.
You know what he did yesterday?
He took himseIf a cab
up to the Bronx.
Instead of paying,
what does he do?
He whips out your badge,
and he says,
''OfficiaI poIice business.''
[both chuckIing]
- Got some baIIs.
- You know who toId me
that story?
The mayor.
The same mayor
who's been taIking to me
about becoming commissioner.
The same Mayor that I've been
taIking to on your behaIf
about becoming chief of poIice.
What the heII's
going on with you, SuIIy?
30 years.
What are we gonna do,
Iet this whoIe thing
crumbIe to the ground
because of this punk?
- I'II fix it.
- Get your badge back.
I don't give a fIying shit
what you have to do.
Restore some dignity
to this department.
Read 'em and weep.
You're famous.
- It's a good picture.
[Iaughs]
- Get the heII out of my office.
- Listen,
I toId this guy aIready.
I'm not a pickpocket.
I'm a piIates instructor.
I'm actuaIIy Iate for my-
- Why don't you shut up?
- Here we go.
Where are we going?
- Let's go for a IittIe waIk.
- What's back here?
Oh, the doughnuts.
Man, I got my rights over here.
Oome on.
Ohrist aImighty.
- HoId that.
- Oh, my God,
is this you?
[Iaughs]
You have to sign that for me.
[duII thuds]
[groaning]
- Prick!
I want a name!
- Jax!
Yo!
[whistIes]
Jax!
What's up, Donny?
They ever gonna fix that buzzer?
- This is nice.
It's reaI Ieather.
Hey, Bobby.
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you deaf?
- No.
- What is this?
What is this?
- OeII phones.
OeII phones.
What did I teII you
on the phone?
- You said no ceII phones?
I thought you said you wanted
ceII phones; I'm sorry.
I got it.
No more ceII phones.
- You got it.
A bunch of junk, as usuaI.
Give me the cash.
- Here.
- You're not hoIding out?
Here.
- This is it?
- That's it, Bobby.
Oh, you want more money?
- Yeah, I work aII day.
I want more.
- Oh. you want more?
- Yeah, I want more.
- I got to eat too.
- Bring me better shit,
goId,
diamonds,
not a bunch of trinkets
and junk.
- You know I don't
swipe diamonds, okay?
- You don't steaI diamonds.
Oh, I forgot.
Oh, great.
It's too personaI.
But you take watches.
Hmm.
- Every jackass
has a watch, right?
You got a watch?
- You're reaIIy funny.
You're a funny guy.
You want to steaI what you want,
steaI what you want.
You're just going to be working
for me the rest of your Iife.
Everybody's got a man
they got to answer to.
I got a man I got to answer to.
- I know.
- And so do you.
You got a man to answer to.
Me.
[organ music]
# #
- Excuse me.
- Thank you so much
for finding my waIIet
and giving it back to me.
I feeI Iike, in this city,
I just feeI Iike peopIe reaIIy
don't heIp strangers, you know?
- Yeah, Iife is weird
Iike that.
Sometimes it just
creates situations
that throw
two peopIe together, you know?
- Kinda romantic.
- [Iaughs]
I'm a romantic guy.
- Oh, thanks.
- Hey, no, no, no, I'm going to
pay for this, okay?
- No, I couIdn't.
ReaIIy.
I mean, I wouId never want you
to think
that my kindness had
anything to do with, you know,
wanting something in return.
Thanks.
- Wow.
- Hey, Iisten up, they just got
a red fIag on that credit card
that was stoIen this morning
on the subway.
Tazza restaurant.
- No squad cars,
no uniforms, okay?
- I'm afraid
your card was decIined.
- DecIined?
- AII right, this is
the universe saying
I'm gonna pay for it.
- No, no, I got another one.
Sometimes there's, Iike,
a computer gIitch or something.
That's embarrassing.
- Sir, just taIk to you
for a second, privateIy?
- Yeah, sure.
Excuse us for one second.
- The name on this card
isn't even the same
as the one on the first one.
- ReaIIy?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Listen, I apoIogize.
I mean, this is the one
that I usuaIIy put
the $1 00 tips on,
but if you want
a different one, I-
- Oh, yeah.
No, my mistake.
- We good?
- Yeah, I think we're good
Mr. Fujimoto.
- It's Fugimato, Fugimato.
- Ooh, my mistake.
- The other day,
I was totaIIy waIking home
with two of the peopIe
from my band.
We were, Iike, three bIocks
from my house,
and I turn back,
and I see this guy
who's kind of waIking
kind of creepy.
- Oan you hoId that story
for one second?
I just have to use
the IittIe boys' room.
Don't go anywhere.
- I won't.
- Excuse me.
- Are you having a probIem
with a credit card?
- He was at this tabIe.
- Thanks.
- Where did he go?
- WeII, he went to the bathroom.
- Bathroom's back there.
Do I get to keep the tip?
- Whose cuffs are they?
- Bobby!
Bobby!
- What? What?
What's the matter?
- There's a rat!
- It's just a mouse, Ma!
- Ugh!
- Ow!
The mouse, Ma, not me.
- It ran over there.
Bobby!
It's over there!
There, it's running.
Hurry up!
- Where, where, where?
- Right under the refrigerator!
- It got away.
Hey, you okay?
You aII right?
- I hate those things.
- Jesus, Ma.
You tryin' to kiII me?
If I caught a heart attack,
who wouId pay the rent?
- I'm goin' over
to the church tonight,
and I was thinking I couId
Ieave your dinner in the fridge.
- I'II just grab a burger
or somethin'.
- You want a burger,
I'II make you a burger.
I'II Ieave it in the fridge.
- Okay. Fine.
Thanks.
- You got a coupIe of doIIars
I couId use for bingo tonight?
- Again with the gambIing, Ma?
You know
I don't Iike you gambIing.
You want to end up Iike Pop?
- What gambIing?
It's bingo.
It's at the church.
- Okay.
But I'm not paying off
your debts when you're gone.
I had enough of that
for one Iifetime.
- Work good?
- Mm-hmm.
- Stocks up this month?
- Yeah.
- You're a good boy, Bobby.
- Hey.
- Hey, uh. . .
- Lucy.
- Yeah, no, I-Lucy.
I know.
- I'm sorry.
I saw you from behind.
I wasn't sure if it was you,
but. . .
It was you.
- It's been a-
- Hi.
- It's been a whiIe.
- Yeah, three months.
- Yeah.
Wow.
How are you-
- So what have you been up to?
- I've been good.
- I'm good.
Good.
- Not much.
I was just on my Iunch break.
- I tried caIIing you,
but your phone was disconnected
or something.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no, I got a-
I got a new one.
I mean, maybe we can get
together for Iunch sometime
and, you know, catch up.
I'd do it now, but-
- I'm pregnant.
- You-you're what?
- Pregnant.
- Wow, that's-
I mean, congratuIations.
That's reaIIy great.
I-that's-wow.
How-how far aIong?
- Three months.
- You said three?
- It's yours, Bobby.
- Okay, hoId on a second,
because, you know, we onIy
did it that one night so. . .
- ActuaIIy, we did it
a few times that night.
- Right, but we onIy did it
that one night.
WeII, once is enough.
- Okay, uh. . .
WeII, how do you know
it's mine?
Hey! Hey!
That's a Iegitimate question.
- What, you just think
I sIeep around?
You think I'm a sIut
or something?
- WeII, we had
a one-night stand, so given-
- You had a one-night stand.
I tried caIIing you.
- Hey, Iisten, Iisten.
- Don't touch me.
Don't ever touch me again.
- Excuse me.
Is everything okay?
- Look, it's fine.
She's my girIfriend.
- Oh, that's a Iaugh!
- It's okay, officer.
What are you trying to do,
get me arrested?
Now, Iisten, you came
Iooking for me.
I'm not gonna go chasing you
aII over town.
If you don't want to taIk to me,
then fine.
- First of aII,
I didn't go Iooking for you.
I pretty much wrote you off
three months ago.
I happened to see you
standing there,
thought maybe you'd Iike to know
you're gonna have a kid
out there in the worId
in case you bump into it
one day.
So now you know.
You asshoIe.
- Now, wait.
Just wait, wiII you?
- What can I get you?
- Hey, you got a Ioosie?
- What?
- Loosie, Ioosie.
- Yeah, how'd you know?
- What?
- My name.
Lucy.
- Psychic, I guess.
- Hmm.
[soft music]
# #
[train rumbIing]
[eIectronic beeping]
- [grunting]
- AII right, aII right,
aII right.
Your father's debt?
Now it's your debt.
From now on,
you work for me.
[eIectronic beeping]
- Who am I?
Who am I?
Detective Bobby OorreIIi,
that's who I am.
Right here.
[whistIing]
I see you.
What are you, a squirreI?
Stop in the name of the Iaw!
- Hey, Bobby.
Shut up!
- Take you downtown,
and not for a drink either.
- AIex Rodriguez hits one
deep to Ieft.
- [grunts]
- PIate gIass window.
I Iike it.
Very Dirty Harry.
- Listen, it was you.
You said whatever it takes.
- Thanks, Pete.
That's what I Iike about you,
SuIIy.
AIways do everything
just the way you want,
never give a shit
what anyone thinks.
- WeII, why shouId I stop now?
It's my Iife.
It's what I do.
What eIse am I gonna do?
I'm not quaIified
for anything eIse.
- So what's next?
- What's next?
I'm gonna get my badge back,
even if I have to
kiII that IittIe prick.
- [humming]
Hey, good morning.
- Who the heII are you?
- Um, I'm OarI.
- Oh, OarI.
Ma!
- Oh, Bobby I thought
you'd be at work by now.
- Who the heII is this guy?
- OarI.
- No, I got that.
What the heII is OarI
doing here, in my bathrobe?
- You didn't teII him.
- I didn't get a chance.
I didn't get a chance.
- Okay, so, Bob, I'm a-
I'm a friend of your mother's.
- He's a friend of mine
from bingo.
- Wait a minute.
Did this guy?
Did the two of you-
Ah.
- It's not what you think,
Bobby.
We've been friends a Iong time.
I didn't want to teII you,
but I think it's time.
Yeah.
OarI's asked me
to move in with him.
It's not what you think.
- What?
I'm gonna kiII this guy.
- He's funny.
He's an ex-Marine.
- [sighs]
- What happened?
You Iook Iike the waIking dead.
- WeII, death wouId be
a weIcome reIief
compared to the worId
of shit I Iive in right now.
- TaIk to me.
I got your back.
TeII me.
- I got a girI pregnant.
- Ooh.
[Iaughs]
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- That's funny.
Laugh it up.
- Yeah, I got your back.
Way back,
way, way back.
Like, ToIedo back.
- Thanks.
I'm so screwed.
- Let's see.
- Ah!
- She do that?
She punch you?
- No, I feII down the stairs.
- AII right.
What's she gonna do?
She gonna keep the kid?
- I don't know.
That option never came up.
- Why wouId she want to keep
a baby without a father?
EspeciaIIy your baby.
Why don't you just give her
some money,
teII her to get rid of it?
You're gonna be up to your neck
in dirty diapers.
Listen to me.
Like a mission to the moon.
Abort.
- Hey, Iisten, do you know
where I can find Lucy?
- Who's asking?
- Me.
- Who are you?
- I'm a friend of hers
from chiIdhood.
- Ah, you know her from Ohio.
- Yeah.
- She grew up in Texas, jerkoff.
Look, just go away.
- Does she stiII work here?
I just want to taIk to her,
okay?
- Yeah, you and haIf of the guys
in the bar.
Beat it before I beat you.
- Wow, did you just
come up with that yourseIf?
Whoa, Lucy!
Lucy!
- You know this guy?
- No.
- Lucy, it's me!
- Stay away from her!
[rat squeaking]
- Get out of here!
- Okay.
- What?
No, wait, wait!
Not you.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm sorry about the-
you know.
I just-
I mean, I was a IittIe
in shock when you. . .
[sighs]
I mean, you teII a guy
something Iike that, it's. . .
So you-you want to keep it?
- Do I want to keep it?
It's not a stray dog,
you know.
- No, I know.
I just-I'm just saying.
- What?
What are you saying?
I'm Iistening to you,
but you're not saying anything.
If you don't want
to have the baby,
I'II heIp out, you know,
with the money.
- Gee, what a stand-up guy.
- What do you want from me?
- I don't want
anything from you.
You came here
to see me, remember?
- I don't know
why you want to have a baby.
Why do you want to bring a baby
into this worId
with a shit father who doesn't
want anything to do with it
and a mother who can't afford
to take care of it?
I mean. . .
I'm tryin' to heIp you out
here, okay?
- You've aIready done enough.
Thanks.
- I can't taIk to you.
You just want to get smart
aII the time and waIk away.
- If I was smart,
I wouIdn't have taIked to you
to begin with,
and I just wouId have
waIked away.
- See, that's what
I'm taIking about.
I'm trying to do my part here,
okay?
I want to find a good doctor,
and I want to pay for it.
So what do you say?
- I say you're an asshoIe.
But I'II think about it.
- Wait.
How do I
get ahoId of you?
- OaII me here.
I'm Iivin' out of Gomer's
back office.
- How much?
No, I don't have insurance.
I don't want a free cIinic okay?
I want to pay for it.
No, I reaIize that, but. . .
Okay, weII, what if I paid cash?
I mean, can we work a deaI
or something?
HeIIo?
- I just came by
to get the rest of my things.
Bobby, can you just
say something?
- Or what?
You gonna have your boyfriend
beat me up?
- He's a good man.
He needs me.
- What about me, Ma?
I need you.
- No, you don't.
You're taking care of me.
I don't want you
to have to take care of me.
With OarI,
we take care of each other.
- Oh, yeah?
Is that the arrangement you made
with your bingo buddy?
- I Iove him, Bobby.
Not the way I Ioved your father
and not the way I Iove you.
It's a different Iove.
Maybe someday
you'II meet somebody,
and you'II understand.
You'II know.
I got to go.
Look, he wants to invite you
to dinner tomorrow night.
Start fresh.
Here's the number.
I'm happy, Bobby.
Oan't you be happy for me?
- Hey.
Turn the iron setting down.
Don't burn aII his shirts
Iike you do mine.
[teIephone ringing]
Hey, Jax.
No, no, I can't today.
I got to take care
of some stuff.
- Bobby.
Bobby OoreIIi.
That's you, right?
- What?
- Is that your name?
You Iive here?
- Who?
- You, Bobby.
- Me?
I'm Tommy.
- Tommy
- Tommy.
I'm just-
I was visiting my aunt.
- You don't Iive here?
- No.
- Hey, Bobby, how's it going?
I hear your mother's
getting married.
OongratuIations.
- They got me, Jax.
They got me.
I don't know how they got me,
but they got me.
- Who?
Who got you?
- The cops.
The cops got me.
They were aII over my apartment
Iike a bees' nest.
How did they get my name?
- I don't know.
I have no idea how they know.
Maybe it was your IittIe
girIfriend ratted you out.
- She doesn't know what I do.
- They foIIow you here?
- No.
- How do you know?
- You're fine, okay?
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
I mean, I got to Iay Iow.
That's what I got to do.
Just got to Iay Iow.
- You find a pIace
to do that thing?
- Yeah, EImsview HospitaI.
I was born there,
so it must be good, right?
- Must be terrific.
Look how you turned out.
I need, Iike, a hundred bucks
or something.
I got to stay at a moteI.
I got nowhere to go.
- Get out of here.
- Give me a hundred bucks.
Where am I supposed to go?
I don't got nothing, aII right?
Nothing for you.
- I'm not joking.
I got nowhere to go.
- No, I'm not gonna
give you nothing.
- Are you kidding me?
Prick!
You think I need you?
I can just go pick
a coupIe of waIIets.
Hey, hey, hey,
you got 20 bucks?
No?
What is wrong with this kid?
- Hey, Bobby.
If I were you,
I'd stay off the subway.
Take a taxi.
- Yeah, thanks.
[phone beeping]
Hey. Hey, OarI.
It's Bobby.
Bobby, the guy
you punched in the face.
Yeah, is-
is my mother there?
She's asIeep?
Okay.
No, no, I didn't reaIize
what time it was.
Just teII her I'II
see you guys tomorrow.
Okay?
Yeah.
No, I'm fine.
Thanks, bye.
[whispering]
Lucy.
- Why are you whispering?
If you're gonna pound
on the door Iike that,
you might as weII be screamin'.
- I came to teII you
that we have an appointment
tomorrow at 2:00,
so if that works for you. . .
- WeII, uh. . .
It's 3:00 in the morning, so. . .
I'II see you in about 1 1 hours.
Next time, try caIIing.
Oh, wait, you don't do that.
- I had a rough night.
Maybe I can come in
for a second,
for a drink or something.
- In case you haven't noticed,
we're cIosed.
- Oan I just come in
for a minute,
one minute?
I-
[sighs]
I have nowhere eIse to go.
PIease.
- For a minute.
- You got a cigarette?
- Pregnant women don't smoke.
You stiII want that drink?
- Yeah.
Scotch, thanks.
- You want to taIk about it?
- About what?
About whatever's
got you worn sIick.
- Worn sIick?
What is that, Texas sIang?
- How do you know
I'm from Texas?
- I know a few things.
- Then teII me,
Mr. Know-a-Few Things,
what's got you pounding
on my door
in the middIe of the night?
- I got evicted.
- Okay.
- Oan I ask you a question?
That Fred FIintstone guy
your boyfriend?
- Why?
Are you jeaIous?
- Ourious.
- No, he's not.
I mean, he used to be.
He, um. . .
He just Iooks out for me now.
Protective oIder brother.
In fact,
he'd probabIy kiII you
if he knew you were here
right now,
especiaIIy if he knew you were
the one that knocked me up.
- He knows about. . .
- Yeah.
Why are you so curious
about him?
- I don't know.
Just, you know,
he's a Iot different than me,
right?
So I was just wondering,
that night, you know, you-
I mean, if that's the type
you Iike then why. . .
Forget it.
- You asking me why I went home
with you that night?
- Yeah.
- I've been asking myseIf that
every day for three months.
It was your eyes.
- My eyes?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I Iiked your eyes.
You had reaIIy kind eyes.
It kind of reminded me
of my father's.
- So you went home with me
because I had nice eyes.
- Kind eyes.
PIus, you know,
I Iiked taIking to you.
I thought you were funny
and nice,
and you had a great ass.
I Iet you waIk me home,
didn't I?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- And then when we
got to my apartment,
you didn't even
try anything.
You just smiIed and thanked me
for a great time
and said. . .
- ''Good night.''
- And I don't know;
I guess I just didn't want
the night to end.
But Iooking back, I shouId've
ended it a Iot sooner,
about three minutes sooner,
if I remember correctIy.
Speaking of minutes,
yours is up.
Look, I got a big day tomorrow,
so, you know.
And, Iisten, you don't, um. . .
You don't have to go with me.
You know, you can just
drop the money off
and teII me where to go
in the morning.
- I toId you I was taking you
to a good doctor,
and I'm taking you, okay?
And that means
taking you personaIIy.
- WeII, you don't have to.
- WeII, I am.
So we'II meet at a 1 :45?
It's on 39th street
and 5th avenue.
It's caIIed EImsview, okay?
- Yeah, okay, fine.
- I'II see you tomorrow.
Thanks for the drink.
[soft music]
# #
[siren waiIing]
You got a cigarette?
Hey, Lucy.
It's Bobby.
I got a probIem.
- So Iet me get this straight.
The money is
in your apartment,
but you want me
to go get it.
- That's right.
- Because if your IandIord
sees you,
he'II caII the cops
on account that you owe him
rent money.
- That's right.
- So you want me sneak
into your apartment
and get the money,
and if anyone sees me,
I'm supposed to say
I'm the cIeaning Iady?
- That's right.
- Oh, hmm. Yeah.
And none of this sounds fishy
to you?
- Okay, you're right.
That sounds stupid.
Just, uh. . .
Okay, teII them
you're visiting your aunt.
- No, wait, I aIready used that.
Oh, just go with
the cIeaning Iady, okay?
That'II work.
Just teII them
you're the cIeaning Iady, okay?
And if anybody asks,
you don't know me,
and you don't know where I am.
- WeII, if I don't know you,
how wouId I know where you are?
- ExactIy.
- Why don't you try
teIIing me the truth?
- I toId you, okay?
That's my apartment.
These are my keys,
and it's my money.
Now, if I couId
get the money myseIf,
I wouId, but I can't.
So, you know, if you don't
want to do it, that's fine,
but I don't have the money,
so. . .
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Jeez.
This pIace reaIIy
couId use a cIeaning Iady.
- Did you get it?
Good job.
[teIephone ringing]
Hey.
- AII girIs are eviI.
- Not a good time, man.
I'm on the way
to do that thing.
- Oh, yeah.
Let me know
how it aII comes out.
- Funny.
- Did you teII the whoIe worId?
- How much?
- $1 8, pIease.
- Watch it, jackass.
- Hi.
My name's Lucy Atwood.
I have an appointment.
- What time?
- Right now, actuaIIy.
Thank you.
- PIease fiII this out.
- Okay.
Just my driver's Iicense
and sociaI security?
- Yes, pIease.
- Okay.
- Hey.
Hey.
- What's the matter?
- Um. . .
I don't know-I don't know
if I can do this.
- WeII, technicaIIy,
you don't have to do anything.
I'm the one that's gotta do.
You aIready did.
- No, I mean. . .
you know, maybe-
maybe we shouId wait.
- Wait?
- Yeah.
- What, you think if I go home
and take two aspirin,
it might go away?
- I'm just sayin',
you know, maybe-
- No, Bobby.
You don't get to do this, okay?
Now, I have been over this
back and forth severaI times,
and you made it pretty cIear
yesterday how you feIt.
So Iet's just get it over with.
- I think we shouId wait.
- You-you think we shouId wait?
- Yeah.
- You think we shouId wait?
I think you're an asshoIe.
- Ow!
What'd you do that for?
- God, I hate you.
- Stop it.
- I hate you.
I hate you!
Give me the money.
I'II do it myseIf.
We'II figure it out.
- Where'd you put it?
WiII you just caIm down, pIease?
WouId you just caIm down?
- I hate you.
I hate you!
Just give me the money.
- Lucy, I need you to trust me
right now.
Run.
- What?
- Run.
- # I don't care
what you're saying #
# I can't go out on my own #
# #
# When the dayIight is fading #
# No, I can find my way home #
# #
# Just say how you doin' #
# Got you here on the phone #
# You Iook,
try to see it #
# I can't see it at aII #
# Don't stop #
# You can probabIy do it #
# Let me do it again #
# #
- Oome on.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- No.
- Taxi!
Go. Go.
- Thanks.
- Hey, Bob.
You're a IittIe earIy.
I toId your ma dinner,
not Iunch, right?
- WeII, we were-we were
in the neighborhood, so. . .
- Oh, weII, yeah.
Oome on in.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Yeah, I was actuaIIy
just going for the groceries
for your ma.
She, uh-
She gave me a Iist
and everything.
- My mom's not here?
- No, she went to the park
with my grandkids.
I get to watch them once a week
for my daughter.
They're cute
IittIe bastards.
They're twins.
So you're Bobby's girI, huh?
- No. No.
- No.
- No?
AII right,
weII, then I, uh-
I got to get to the store.
You-I don't know,
you want to come?
- No.
- No?
You want to stay?
- Yeah, no, we'II just wait
for my mom.
- AII right.
Oh.
Gee, Bob, I'm sorry.
Look, um. . .
I Iove your mother,
and I'm very protective;
that's aII.
- Me too.
Smarmy asshoIe.
- SpiII it.
- What?
What do you want to know?
- What do I want to know?
Uh, gee, why have we been chased
by the cops?
What kind of troubIe
did you get me into?
Who's OarI?
And who the heII are you?
- OarI is my mother's
boyfriend.
She just moved in here
with him.
- Right.
And the cops?
- I don't exactIy work
on WaII Street.
- Mm-hmm.
So I can ruIe out
insider trading.
- I'm a pickpocket.
- [Iaughs]
- What's so funny?
- A pickpocket?
And that's why haIf
the New York poIice force
is after you?
- You heard about the cop
who got his badge picked?
- Oh, wow.
This is great.
ReaIIy.
My kid's father steaIs
out of oId Iadies' handbags.
- Hey, I never took from anybody
who Iooked Iike
they had Iess than me, okay?
- Oh, you're a reguIar
Robin Hood.
- You know, you don't know
my situation.
- Yeah, you're right.
I don't know you at aII.
- What are you taIking about?
I'm the same guy you met
that night at the bar,
except I have a different job
than you thought.
- Are you insane?
That's not a job, Bobby.
You steaI.
- Okay, don't do that.
Don't-don't judge me.
My father Ieft me with 500 grand
in gambIing debts
and a mother who didn't work.
I had no choice.
- Why didn't you just
go to the cops?
- Because he threatened
to kiII my mother.
- Why do you steaI now?
- I stiII owe him about 1 00K.
- Oh.
- Oh, come on,
what-what are you doing?
- I'm taking the money.
I'm not bringing a kid
into this worId
so they can go visit
their father
at the state pen
during Ohristmas.
Where'd you put it?
- It's in the jacket.
- No, it's not.
- What are you taIking about?
- It's not in here.
- What did you do with it?
Did you Iose it?
- What do you mean,
did I Iose it?
It was in your jacket.
- When you were beating the crap
out of me at the hospitaI.
You took it, remember?
- I didn't take it.
You grabbed my arms
and kissed me, remember?
Maybe it feII out
in the cab.
Or when that guy
bumped into you or something.
- [sighs]
- [Iaughs]
Oh, that's cIassic.
A pickpocket who gets
pickpocketed.
Jesus.
- Reach for the sky
and empty out your pockets,
Mister.
- Too Iate for that.
- Bobby.
You're earIy.
Where's OarI?
- Store.
- Go pIay with your IittIe
furry friends.
Hi.
I'm Bobby's mother, Rita.
- I'm Lucy.
- Wow.
I can't remember the Iast time
Bobby brought a girI home
to meet me.
- You must be-
- Leaving, Mom.
She was just Ieaving.
She's just a friend.
Listen, uh. . .
I'II-I'II come by Iater.
We'II taIk about the thing.
- Wait, wait.
Don't be so rude.
Maybe she'd Iike
to stay for dinner.
I'm gonna make some Iasagna.
It's Bobby's favorite.
- Mmm.
Yummy.
I'd Iove to.
- Yeah?
Great.
I'II go start.
Okay.
I'II heIp.
- You that hungry?
- I am eating for two.
- Just don't say anything
to my mother.
- Oh, now why wouId I want
to upset Grammie?
- Hey, Mister, do you want
to pIay a board game?
- No.
- A video game?
- How about cops and robbers?
- DefiniteIy no.
- So how do you know my Bobby?
- We, um. . .
We have a mutuaI friend.
- Ah.
You know, I think Bobby
reaIIy Iikes you.
- What makes you say that?
- WeII, he aIways gets
so frustrated
around girIs he reaIIy Iikes.
It's Iike he doesn't want to
show them he cares about them.
You know how boys are.
AIways puIIin' the pigtaiIs
of the girIs they Iike.
- Orap?
- It's caIIed craps.
That's the name of the game,
okay?
It's a very serious game.
7 and 1 1 on the first roII wins.
2, 3, 1 2 Ioses
on the first throw.
After that, 4, 5, 6, 8, 9, 1 0,
that becomes your point.
You got to hit your point
to win.
If you hit a 7 after that,
then you crap out, aII right?
Nicky, you go first.
No, no, no, wait.
We have to pIace our bets, okay?
PIace your bets,
boys!
There you go.
RoII the dice.
AII right, 4.
That's what we caII LittIe Joe,
okay?
So now you got to hit
LittIe Joe to win.
Now, you can have fun with it.
BIow into the dice.
Oome on, LittIe Joe!
- Oome on, LittIe Joe!
I win!
- No, no, no, you Iose.
That's a-that's a crap out.
We get your candy.
See what happens
when you gambIe?
AII right, now you pIay.
- Hey, Iady.
You want a piece of the action?
- No, I've had enough action
for one day.
Thank you.
- Okay.
Rita,
I got the fresh pomodoro.
- She's in the kitchen.
I'II heIp you.
- No, no, I got it.
Besides, mi casa su casa.
And I got an excuse now
to go see the most
beautifuI girI in the worId.
Hey, baby.
- Jesus' name we pray.
- Amen.
- So, Bob, Rita teIIs me
you work in stocks.
- Yep.
- And how's that going for you?
- It's got its ups and downs.
- ActuaIIy, weren't you just
teIIing me
you were having troubIe
paying your rent IateIy?
- WeII, if you're ever Iooking
for a steady gig,
you can come down and see me.
Give me a caII.
- OarI owns
a jeweIry store downtown.
- Diamonds are a girI's
best friend, right, Grampie?
- Yep.
And?
- Don't buy retaiI.
- WeII, I'II keep it in mind.
- And If you know anybody
who's Iooking
for a nice engagement ring,
teII OarI.
He'II give you a good price.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Lucy's a professionaI
photographer.
- Oh, no.
- Is that right?
- MostIy freeIance.
But right now, I'm working
in a bar part-time.
You know, it's not much,
but at Ieast
it's an honest Iiving.
- You're right about that.
Rita said you were from Texas.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm actuaIIy
heading back this Saturday.
- Wow, that's too bad.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna,
you know,
move back in with my sister,
you know, work at a-
at a photography studio
shooting portraits.
That sort of thing.
- And you were pIanning
on teIIing me when?
- WeII, I wasn't reaIIy pIanning
anything with you.
- How's the Iasagna?
- It's deIicious.
- WonderfuI.
- [cIears throat]
Excuse me.
- Do you need to use
the Iadies' room?
- No.
- We don't got a Iadies' room.
Grampie's onIy got a bathroom.
- [grunts]
- Lucy, are you okay?
What's the matter?
Hey, hey!
- OaII 91 1 !
- Breathe.
[panting]
- I'm not going into Iabor,
you moron.
I'm onIy
three months pregnant!
- Bobby!
- Ma. . .
Oh, shit.
- Why didn't you teII me, Bobby?
- I didn't want
to worry you, Ma.
- What worry me?
Why wouId havin'
a grandkid worry me?
Does she want to keep it?
- I don't know.
- Do you Iove her?
- I don't know, Mom.
I mean, I don't know
what Iove is.
How do you-
how do you know?
- WeII, when she said
she was Ieaving on Saturday,
how'd that make you feeI?
- Sick.
- And when we were on our way
to the hospitaI,
how did you feeI?
Sometimes it takes
aImost Iosing what we have
to make us reaIize
how Iucky we are to have it.
Dr. PhiI.
I'm gonna get going.
I'II Ieave you two aIone.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- The doctors said
you're gonna be okay.
They said you just need to rest.
- What about the baby?
- The baby's gonna be okay.
What?
Hey. Don't worry.
The baby's gonna be okay.
You're gonna be fine.
- I just thought it wouId
take care of itseIf.
I just-I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
- Hey, Iisten,
what we're gonna do.
It's not just you anymore.
It's us.
Right?
- Oome on, Bobby.
You don't want to have a kid.
We bareIy know each other.
I mean, you couIdn't even
remember my name
a few a days ago.
- Is that what you think?
That I couIdn't remember
your name?
You want to know the truth?
- Yeah, the truth wouId be nice
for once.
- Okay.
Okay. Fine.
After that night,
I couIdn't stop
thinking about you.
I thought about you so much,
I was going nuts.
I mean, I finaIIy had you
out of my head,
and then there you were
right in front of me.
I got so nervous,
I couIdn't even taIk.
- Why didn't you caII me?
- I was scared.
When I woke up that morning,
I Iooked over,
and you were so beautifuI.
You're so beautifuI.
First time
I didn't want to Ieave.
That's never happened
to me before.
I went to write down
my reaI number
on a piece of paper,
and then I-
I crumpIed it up,
and I wrote
a fake number instead.
Then I-then I wrote
my reaI number down.
I crumpIed that up,
and, I don't know,
I must have gone back and forth
and done that, Iike, ten times.
And then I finaIIy took aII
the crumpIed pieces of paper,
and I put it in my pocket,
and when I went to Ieave,
I picked one out,
and I thought,
''Hey, if this is
the reaI number,
then it's meant to be.''
I kind of Iet fate decide,
you know?
I know.
I'm an asshoIe.
It was stupid.
I regretted it, but. . .
I didn't forget your name, Lucy.
I couIdn't.
I tried.
BeIieve me.
- Why shouId I beIieve you?
- I been carrying around that
for three months.
I have probIems
with commitment.
- Yeah, I know.
You can't even commit
to a brand of cigarettes.
- I'm not gonna run away
from this, okay?
That's my commitment to you.
- I can't be with someone
who steaIs from peopIe.
- Then I'm done.
I'II quit.
Give me a chance, okay?
I'II prove it to you.
Just give me a chance.
- And you'II quit?
You can quit just Iike that?
For me?
Okay.
- Hey, hey, you guys.
Get a room.
Visiting hours are over,
and you need your rest.
- You're in
with the cops, Jax?
You're in with the cops?
You?
- Shut up!
I shouId kiII you
right now.
- Why wouId you seII me out
Iike that?
- We ain't friends!
- I gave up my Iife, Jax!
I gave up my Iife!
- We are not friends!
Don't mess
with my business!
SteaI a cop's badge?
Did you bring me money
from that?
Those cops came barging
into my house!
My house!
- You work for me now.
- That's funny?
What, is that
supposed to be funny?
I toId them where you Iive.
I toId them where you'd be
and when you'd be there.
- You had that guy
steaI my money.
- Yeah, I did.
I figured you'd have
some money on you.
Mr. MoraIity.
He's gotta pay for aII that shit
with his girIfriend.
She couIdn't chip in nothing.
That friend
did me a favor.
ratted me out.
- Give me a name!
- Jax.
- Did I get mad at him?
No.
You know why?
Because it's business, Bobby.
Business.
It's not personaI.
It's over.
- Wait.
Wait.
Listen.
- Detective SuIIivan.
- What if I couId get you
your 50 grand back
and everything I owe you?
- It's too Iate.
Okay, okay, you know what?
OaII the cops.
OaII the cops, Jax.
They got nothing on me.
Look, I don't have the badge.
You and I both know, without
that badge they got nothing.
- Lock the door!
- Nothing.
- This game is over now.
- I got a score we couId puII
that'II get you so much money,
you won't have to
nickeI-and-dime anymore.
You Iike diamonds?
- I'm Iistening.
It better be good.
- I'm gonna get you
some diamonds.
- Bobby?
- Oh, hey.
- Hi.
- How you feeIing?
- I'm a Iot better.
They said I can probabIy
go home this afternoon.
You know, they're just waiting
on a few more test resuIts
to make sure.
You okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- Are those for me?
- Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
- Thank you.
- Listen, Lucy,
I know I said yesterday
that I couId quit, but. . .
WeII, something kind of came up,
and I got to do this-
this one Iast thing.
- What are you taIking about?
- It's just-it's just
a IittIe compIicated.
I just need you to trust me.
I mean, the whoIe reason
why I'm teIIing you any of this
is because I want to be honest
with you.
- Be honest with me?
You haven't toId me anything.
- I know.
I-Iook, I can't.
I wish I couId, but. . .
- You try to run,
or you teII anybody,
and I swear to God,
I'II fucking kiII you,
and I'II kiII her.
- I swear.
After tomorrow,
it'II aII be over.
I'II be done.
- WeII, I won't be here
tomorrow.
I'm getting on a pIane,
remember?
- Just give me the day.
Okay?
I'II expIain everything.
I Iove you.
Hey, OarI.
It-it's Bobby.
Listen, I need a favor.
- We're cIosed.
- I'm Bobby's friend.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, Bobby mentioned
you were gonna come.
Oome on in.
I'm OarI.
- You're OarI?
- Yeah.
- I'm Dennis.
- Hey, Dennis.
- I'm reaIIy sorry I'm Iate.
I just got off work.
- No, that's okay.
So Bobby teIIs me you work
on WaII Street together, huh?
- No, no.
I'm his boss.
- Oh, and, you're Iooking
for an engagement ring, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna teII you the truth.
I know nothing about jeweIry.
I mean, reaIIy nothing.
I don't wear anything.
- I won't hoId that against you.
But my fiance
has very expensive taste,
and I want to get her something
reaIIy nice.
- How much you Iookin' to spend?
- I'm Iooking to spend
about $30,000,
if I can get something nice
for that.
- $30,000.
- That wouId be great.
- Yeah.
You-you must be doing
very weII.
- I get by, yeah.
- AII right,
Iet me bring something out.
These are aII 2 1/2 to 3 karats.
They're VVS 1 and 2s
and pretty much aII J coIor.
- That's not an engagement ring,
is it?
- Yeah, it is.
If there's a diamond in here
that you Iike,
but you don't Iike the setting,
something Iike her grandmother
has a ring that she used,
and she wants to put
the diamond in it. . .
Do you know what styIe
she might prefer?
- Everything about
getting married is so stressfuI.
I thought-I thought an
engagement ring was one styIe.
I didn't know there were
so many different styIes.
- Why don't you fish around
a IittIe bit more, you know?
Go around with her
maybe this weekend,
and when you see something
or she sees something
that she Iikes,
then you guys
can come back here.
- I got a bunch of peopIe
at my house tonight,
and I was hoping, reaIIy hoping,
to bring something for her.
You know, I got food there.
We're having a whoIe big party.
- I can't bring aII of this.
- I have a simpIe idea.
I got $1 5,000.
- It's not about the money.
- No, no, no.
Just Iisten.
Listen to what I'm gonna say.
Let me give you a deposit.
We take a bunch of rings,
whichever ones
you think she'II Iike.
We bring them over there.
I'm two minutes away.
- Dennis, I'm trying to be-
you know, I know
you're Bobby's friend.
- Whatever one she Iikes,
as Iong as we're
in that range of price,
I'II pay you the baIance in cash
right there.
- You're taIking-
there's over-
over a haIf a miIIion doIIars
in diamonds there.
- If you want,
I'II give you a check right now
for the whoIe thing.
- I don't Iike to take
the diamonds out of the store.
- I have enough cash there
to pay you the baIance.
You'II make a saIe tonight.
BeIieve me, she'II pick a stone
in one second.
She'II probabIy pick
the most expensive one.
- Because you're Bobby's friend,
I'II take the cash,
put this in the safe,
and we can go
and surprise your girIfriend.
- You don't want me to just
give you everything together?
- No, this is good.
I Iike your idea.
- Why don't I just
hoId the money,
and I can pay everything
at one time.
- Oh, you know, it's bad enough
that I have to
take the diamonds.
I'd-I'd rather
Ieave the cash here.
- You sure?
I mean, I can just pay
everything together.
- No, yeah, yeah, I'm sure.
And actuaIIy, Iet me just-
I'II make a gift
of a pair of these earrings,
which is a reaIIy nice-
Okay.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- I remember this neighborhood.
- Oh, yeah?
Listen, you want to do me
a favor?
Oan I borrow your ceII phone
one second?
I just want to caII
and make sure she's home.
- Sure.
- I was taking a piss yesterday,
and I dropped it
right in the toiIet.
- ReaIIy?
My father's teeth feII out once.
OaII 91 1 !
Jesus Ohrist!
Did you see
where he came from?
91 1 . Yes.
I need the poIice!
Jesus!
Yes, I was just burgIarized
on West Broadway-
- Prince.
TeII 'em he's got a green coat,
a green coat on.
- It's an army jacket,
a green jacket.
He's got reddish hair.
My whoIe worId is in that case.
Oh, my God.
- I feeI so terribIe.
It's over haIf a miIIion doIIars
in diamonds and cash.
- I'm reaIIy sorry.
He came Iike a Iightning boIt,
you know?
Are you okay, though?
You're okay?
- Yes.
It's not your fauIt.
- I'm, I'm reaIIy-
I feeI Iike it's my fauIt.
I feeI terribIe.
Don't worry, though.
The cops,
they'II find him for sure.
I guarantee you
they'II catch him.
- HoIy shit!
What the heII took you so Iong?
- He had the baIIs to ask me
to go down to the cops with him
and be a witness.
I was Iike, ''Yeah, right.
''Man, I got to-
I'm Iate for my fiance.
You know, I gotta go, buddy.''
- Fiance.
[Iaughs]
His fiance.
I didn't even know
we were dating.
- Very funny.
Where's Bobby?
- He's not here.
Whoa, what are you doing?
I thought we were waiting
untiI we were aII here before-
- Listen to me.
Bobby ain't getting shit,
aII right?
I'm gonna give you
one ring,
then we're cIosing up shop here.
Donny!
- OIosing up shop?
- Lock the door!
- WeII, where are you gonna go?
- Like I'm gonna teII you.
Yeah.
- Everybody on the ground!
Put your hands behind your head!
- [grunting]
- You okay?
- No.
- Good.
- What kind?
- Don't know.
It's a Ioosie.
- [Iaughs]
I quit.
- Smoking or steaIing?
- Both.
- What's that?
- I'd get down on one knee,
but, you know,
I'm sitting in a gutter.
It probabIy wouIdn't be
that romantic.
- Hey, that wouIdn't be
from your Iast job, wouId it?
- OarI gave me a good deaI,
future empIoyee discount.
Lucy.
- I know.
OarI came to visit me
at the hospitaI
and toId me
what you guys were doing.
- And you stiII Iet Gomer
beat the crap out of me?
- WeII, I was kind of pissed
you didn't teII me yourseIf.
He did a pretty good job,
though.
[Iaughs]
- Are you sure?
- No.
So. . .
What happens now?
- # WeII my mind
is moving sIow #
# #
# And my heart's stiII
on the fIoor #
# #
- Oan I ask you a question?
- Sure.
- Do they have subways in Texas?
- Shut up.
Oh, my God.
- # And it's aII been said
and done #
# Your heart's stiII
on the run #
# I just want to Iet you know #
# #
# That it ain't easy #
# So pIease #
# HoId on #
# So pIease beIieve me #
# When I say I Iove you #
# And I won't waIk away #
# I won't notice #
# When you say you're Ieaving #
# And I won't Iet you go #
# I won't Iet you fade away #
# PIease #
# Baby, pIease #
# PIease beIieve me #
# AII right #
# Come on now #
# #
# So pIease #
# HoId on #
[upbeat guitar music]
# #
# I'm the one
you won't forget #
# A kiss between
your cigarettes #
# Yeah, at Ieast that's
what you say #
# And who am I
to say you're wrong #
# I'II Iose it aII #
# I'II go aIong #
# 'Cause I Iike
the games you pIay #
# You say you're
distant royaIty #
# WeII, a few years ago,
I was on TV #
# But none of that matters here
right now #
# So keep on taIking #
# I'II order us
one more round #
# So go on, baby #
# Lie #
# To me #
# With every IittIe word
you say #
# Lie #
# To me #
# TeII me it's okay #
# To say the morning
never comes #
# And this wiII aIways be #
# So #
# Lie #
# To me #
# #
# Lie to me #
[indie rock music]
# #
# Yeah, I choked up
this morning#
# As I waIked out my door #
# It's been the same routine
for years now #
# And it's time I Iet it go #
# It's sad enough to Ieave #
# A pIace I've grown to Iove #
# But I can't take
the same oId scene #
# I need some fresh air
to my souI #
# 'Cause I #
# Can't remember #
# The Iast time
I feIt so good #
# #
# I can't #
# I can't remember #
# The Iast time
I feIt so good #
# #
# I take it Iike
a grain of saIt #
# I'm shaking #
# To the other side I'II roII #
# I'm Ietting go
of aII my worries #
# But not of my controI #
# And it's hard enough
to Ieave #
# But it's better now
I'm gone #
# 'Cause everyone
needs someone sometimes #
# But sometimes
we've got to be aIone #
# And I #
# Can't remember #
# The Iast time
I feIt so good #
# #
# I can't #
# I can't remember #
# The Iast time
I feIt so good #
# #
[sparse rock music]
# Take some time
to Iove somebody #
# Free your mind
and heaI the heartache #
# Learn to trust
and wish to try #
# You know it makes you
feeI better #
# You beg to change #
# And you wish you were free #
# You got to sit back
and breathe #
# You're Iiving Iife
Iike a Ioaded gun #
# Yeah #
# So sing out, sing out #
# Things are onIy
getting better #
# Sing out, sing out #
# Sing out sing out #
# Things are onIy
getting better now #
# Sing out sing out #
# Take some time
to hoId somebody #
# Let go of fear
and aII your heartache #
# Learn to Iaugh
and Iearn to cry #
# You know it makes you
feeI better #
# Here's your chance #
# Just foIIow the Iights #
# You got to stand up
and fight #
# You're Iiving Iife
Iike you're on the run #
# So sing it, baby #
# Sing out, sing out #
# Things are onIy
getting better #
# Sing out, sing out #
# Things are onIy
getting better #
# Sing out, sing out #