For legends in spanish: Javier AC - Thanks to @ vgfilducci Nehrox1337 for the correction.
http://facebook.com/VideoGameHighSchool
Last charger!That we move!
The stable output locked!They are counting!
Where is BrianD!?
ow about the long way home, Briand?
Do you sweaty enough for you? - Can this wait, K-Pop?
Afternoon I get a game of CLA
In this FPS from Think Geek That goes a Lei following the service!
Come on, do you want?
Like any strategy ... real time
Resources.
Our guest stable decorated BY PwnZwn As "lover Player of the Year" ...
and PetiteElite As "Adolescent player handles most of the Decade".
It is also captain of the team FPS Games School of ...
and sorry, girls. This caught.
Hang your uma males, because here comes Lei!
Here this!
Law ¿ready for this? (Pun with Law and You)
So, uh ...
Who wants to see a demonstration of Trickshot?
Oh, I love you!
She wants.
It took three weeks to get all that!
And I three seconds.
I guess it's called, uh ...
Strategy.
GG Briand. See you tomorrow. GG - Good Game.
Yes!
See you tomorrow ...
Forever!
Hi, Mom, the school went well! I love you, goodbye!
I can touch them? - Sure, you can play both!
Sorry I'm late.
I'm glad you could join, captain!
Come on! Follow me!
Have you seen that?
What folly! Guys, I ...
Thank you!
Well, you told me on the racks this is what is called a "pubstomp"?
What else happened on the racks, Bella?
Anyway, girls ...
"Pubstomping" is when a pro like me ...
enters a random server and gets the, uh ...
I hear you out there!
Long arm of Law! Long arm of Law! (Law = Law)
I love these people.
Left Flank ... Laser ¿Occam to three?
As in the Milwaukee Invitational.
Come on!
Prepare to take the point ...
Brian! Take the cat for a walk!
First, I will take the cat!
We are as always!
Cheeto ...
Cheeto!
Cheeto ... Chee-to! Cheeto .... Cheeto ...
What are you doing, guys?
-AFK. - Cheeeee-to!
Here! Kitty, kitty ... - For god. Guys ...
We need a new captain.
Yes .. We seem to have found a server ...
Why we have retrofitted?
LAW HAS COME TO THE GAME.
Well, guys ...
I have him.
I have you, oh, God.
Too much power. As always, too much power!
Run!
Chee-to ...
Come here, Cheeto!
Cheeto!
Amazing, right?
I still feel that rush.
Oh, my God ... Once I ended up with a whole family with that movement.
Cheeto!
Cheeto ...
Cheeto ... good kitty ...
Cheeto ... Ah! Ow!
Cat stupid!
Go! It seems that this guy is AFK!
Away from the keyboard.
Let's see if we can have fun along with him.
Yes ..
Mom! Where is the iodine?
Whatever it is, boy.
It ...
That has been around!
Burning ...
Burn!
Well, what do you call this movement?
You know what? That's not really a movement ...
I ... I ... I ...
killed.
You know, is a pubstomp, anything can happen ...
Who was that guy? Right?
Who was that guy?
So, uh ...
Well, I guess, uh ...
Court for ads or something?
- Law has killed, has killed Law. - Briand, are the King!
And still unaccounted for president right now ...
The nation expects ...
Hold on to your joysticks, zoners!
We bring you an alert PwnZwn urgent!
ShotBot ? What do you have?
VGHS star, The Law has been humiliated ...
live on national television
by a nameless noob ...
In a pubstomp has gone wrong!
Does my computer?
Death of the century! Attentive to repeat!
Our sources tell us that a player not rated, Briand
has already been invited to attend the prestigious and exclusive ...
Video Game High School, a school where students are ...
to make millions with the pros.
Yes, that's true, we were with Brian when the call for VGHS!
Do you want, Briand! - Yes! Brian!
Give me a break!
What makes you think that lucky brat who has what it takes?
What makes you think that lucky brat who has what it takes? - Ron ...
Ron!
I totally agree, Ron!
VGHS school is professional players in the country!
VGHS school is most important professional player in the country! - Guys, guys, guys ...
Can we agree for a second?
Can we agree for a second? - Your agreement has been recorded!
Boys, boys, boys! Please!
Just ... look at his video acceptance, right?
It will study physics.
Will study the physics engine.
It will study fine arts.
Will study the arts of war!
Learn biology ...
bathing in the blood of your enemies!
Does that sound OK?
Well, bievenido to VGHS.
You have been accepted.
This is really happening ...
Everyone says they do not get, but ...
I have to try, I mean ...
I dreamed of playing for a team since he was "PEGI +3".
I hope you understand.
Cheeto typical.
I will miss this tug of war.
Take care of mom, okay?
Brian?
We will prepare. The reporters are here.
I love you, Mom.
I put more food in the bowl.
Where are you?
I'm going to VGHS.
- Brian! Brian!
- Brian! Brian! - What do you say to your fans, Brian