Subtitle by heeji16
and shinostarr
Once again, my lovely wife is very busy preparing the meal today.
My wife has never slacked on cooking.
It's a bit extravagant, isn't it?
Why do you ask?
If you love, this is what happens.
[Shotgun Love]
It's hot, it's hot. Eat slowly.
That's right.
Slowly, yeah.
Ah~
Is it good?
How was that? Yes, how would you like to have this pork on your table for dinner tonight?
We will leave now.
We sincerely thank those of you that have been with us.
Cut! Okay.
Good work.
Good work!
Good work, good work.
You all worked hard.
Yes, you worked hard.
PD Park, good work.
Today's sales have reached 94%! It's a  huge hit.
How can you eat someone else's meat so realistically well?
-You did well in casting them.
-Ah, yes, thank you.
Your shoe is untied. Look at me.
-Good work!
-Yes.
Give me two of them.
Ah, okay. Good work.
Good job.
Let's put your shoes on.
Wow...
She's more charming by the day.
I have to get married to that kind of a woman...
That's why you should chew slowly.
Ah, I can't see...
Hey! Pierce this.
-Me?
-Yeah.
Ah. Uh..
Ahh!!
Ah really.
Let me see. Ah...
I told you to pierce her hand, but you gave her a shot. A shot!
Do you already have ulnar nerve palsy? You're so young.
If you meet a man, avoid those with ulnar nerve palsy.
He'll have paralysis before he turns 40.
I don't have ulnar nerve palsy.
Ow it hurts..
I'm just shivering because it's cold.
What am I supposed to do if you call now, all of a sudden, and say you can't come?? Huh?
Ah hello... hello?
Hyung, I'm leaving first.
Okay. I have to do one more seasoned mackerel.
Ah, right. Hey, do this mackerel before you leave.
-The other guy said he couldn't come in...
-Ah, I can't do mackerel.
I'm allergic to mackerel and my skin reacts badly.
Ah, what do I do about this? PD Park is going to bitch...
Oh Hello!
She has a killer body, doesn't she?
With that body, she ate meat before, and now she's going to do seasoned mackerel again.
It's really fascinating.
When does it start? The seasoned mackerel?
Does it start right now? I'll do the mackerel.
Didn't you say you were allergic to mackerel?
It's okay, I can endure it.
How do you endure an allergic reaction?
I can bear it!
I've held diarrhea in and turned it into constipation!
I can hold it in. It starts now, right? Where?
That's it! Hey, hey, hey...
-Yes, there is no deal like today's.
-Yes, that is true. Please do not be surprised.
If you purchase this while this show is airing,
We will give you an extra 10 packs.
Then, that means it's 40 packs. I don't know if you could eat all of this.
-It's packaged like this, so you can store them in your refrigerator.
-Yes.
These seasoned mackerel are really big and succulent, aren't they?
So big and succulent.
How plump are those? When mothers look at these,
They ask if the fish are Yankee Mackerel. These are Korean Mackerel.
Yankee Mackerel. You are so funny.
Yes, because they are so large and succulent.
-Please give us a call right away. -Yes.
Ah~
AHH!!!
What's with him? What's wrong with his face?
Change to camera number 2. Hurry!
Hey, Host! Host!
Yes, everyone! Our Ahn Dong Mackerel are so delicious
that our model has grown happy flowers on his face.
-Yes he has. That is how delicious these are.
-Yes, right, right, right..
That could happen if you get an endorphin rush.
-Please make an automatic order.
-Yes.
-Also
-Yes?
We'd like for you to call again for our second round.
-Please order~
-Yes. Please order now.
Those Ahjusshis always trying to keep the change when they come into the neighborhood.
Myung Boo~
Hey, what's wrong with your face? Do you have the measles?
Ah, don't ask me. Why are there so many annoying things happening today?
Why'd you call me?
Umm, Myung Boo...
Myung Boo~
I can't.
What can't you do?? You haven't even heard what I'm going to say.
You're asking me to lend you money again. Didn't you say you were going to pay me back as soon as you got paid?
If I don't pay you back this month, I'll cut my finger off.
Then, go cut it off first.
In the kitchen.
Ah Myung Boo, why are you acting like this? Myung Boo...
I'm begging you.
Myung Boo~
It's raining, the weather is accurate.
Go on.
Hey Sang Yeol,
Can you walk me to the bus stop?
Ah, it's only drizzling rain. You can run.
Jeez, I really can't understand you.
If I caught you, I would really...
Ah, why are you being so creepy?
Because you keep pushing me out from under the umbrella. You're only covering yourself.
When did I push you out? When did I only cover myself?
How can you say such things... Ah what is this smell??
Ahh! Really!
When was the last time you washed your hair?
Tomorrow is the day I wash it.
I heard if I wash my hair too often, it will fall out.
Hey! You trying not to have your hair fall out will make other people's noses fall off!
Why don't you think of others?
You rich bastards are all like that.
Hey, why'd you turn around?
Myung Boo, you go ahead.
There's still a long way till the bus stop...
Take the taxi.
Why are you doing this?
Ah, it's cold.
I don't have any money.
Why don't you have any money?
I lent you everything I had.
Ah dude! How could you lend me everything?
What kind of a person doesn't have $30-40 in their wallet?
Ah dude, really...
I have to use this tomorrow, so be sure to pay me back tomorrow.
Hurry, go!
Ah, right! Right, right!
I was going to get bread on the way, I almost forgot.
I should get some.
Oh? Hello!
Ah, I almost passed you by.
Why are you standing here?
Ah, you're staying out of the rain.
Ah, why is it raining all of a sudden?
Where are you headed to?
To the bus stop.
Would you like me to walk you there?
Why are you doing this to me?
What are you doing right now?
Cover yourself with the umbrella.
Ah, that...
When I share my umbrella...
I care more about the other person...
I saw you coming with your friend earlier and you only covered yourself.
Ah, that was because that friend cares more about me.
What are you doing tonight?
Aren't you hungry?
You didn't even have dinner.
Mm... I don't feel so good lately. I get indigestion whenever I eat.
It's just an eating disorder.
Because you always force yourself to eat.
Do you want a break from your work?
Are you going to take care of me?
You don't think I can?
Hello.
Miss So Yeon. Hi!
Eat this before you work.
Did someone bite your hand?
No, I...
Ah, you must have an upset stomach again. Um.. Uh...
Give her some good medicine!
Have a pleasant meal.
I'm sorry to keep making you do things.
Ah, it's nothing.
You are so kind.
Thank you.
Why?
You are really kind.
Are you like that to everyone?
When was I?
Since when were you so close with the president's daughter?
How am I close?
She's the president's daughter, so I just...
Ah, so if you're the president's daughter, you can touch another woman's man?
Okay. I was wrong.
Let's stop and eat something delicious. Huh?
I'm pregnant.
Oh, right now... here...
If you look here...
There is a problem here.
On both sides... it's a bit serious.
Is it cancer?
It isn't that...
If you undergo surgery this time...
In the future... You won't be able to have a child.
What?
Ah, this pregnancy is a miracle too.
Ah, let's do a test to find out the details.
How old are you?
I'm five years old.
Mm? What are you doing there?
Don't bother the ajhumma and come here. Come here.
Stay there.
It's okay.
How many weeks are you?
7 weeks.
Ah, then you must have heard the baby's heartbeat.
A heartbeat?
You can hear that already?
Of course.
I heard my kids' in their 6th week.
You have to listen to it. It's really fascinating.
I still cry when I think of the emotions then.
Why did you take that out? Huh?
Mommy told you to stay still! Do you want to die?
You really..
Ah, I'm so sorry.
The kids are so active.
I don't hear anything.
I haven't turned it on yet.
I can't do it.
Really, why do you keep saying that?
Am I like this for no reason?
Why are you like that really?
We're already done talking about it.
We've decided to do that.
Yeah.
But...
After hearing our baby's heartbeat...
I can't do it.
I won't do it.
Ah! So frustrating.
Ah, why are you so frustrating and stubborn?
Am I pregnant with a different person's child?
How could you say that?
That's why. Why can't you understand what I'm saying?
I don't ever want a child.
You're being so stubborn.
Huh? Is that love?
If you keep going on like this, I have no other choice than to end this.
Alright. Let's end this.
I'm really scared this child in my stomach will be selfish like you.
I don't have any feelings left for that kind of child.
I'll do what you want.
Ah, you crazy fool.
-Why doesn't it turn off?
-Ah you bastard. You rotten man.
Quit playing with yourself, you rotten fool.
It'll explode. Ah gross!
It isn't anything like that.
Hey, then what's this naked woman?
She isn't naked!
It's lingerie!
I'm just monitoring a coworker.
Ah, you bastard. Lies spew out of your mouth whenever you open it.
Aigoo, answer the the phone you imbecile.
Who is it?
-It's a woman.
-I told you not to answer my phone! Why do you keep answering it?
Then don't leave your phone lying around, you idiot.
-Woman who? Aunt? This is Aunt's number..
-Is Aunt a woman?
Lift up your leg. Look at all of this hair! Move out of the way! Look at all the hair!
-Ah be quiet!
-Are you shedding? Why is there so much hair?
-The son or his father...
-Ah, get out!
Ah, why does it smell so sour in a human's home? It smells like sour dog food.
Rub with this you bastard!
I got it! Get out, get out. Hurry.
-Ah, so gross.
-Ah shit really!
Why does it smell so sour? So sour...
It smells like rotten dog food, you rotten fool.
I'm going to leave this house, really!
Get out! Please!
Hello?
Hello.
Who are you?
It's me, Shin So Yeon.
She heard everything! AHH!
Ah shit! She heard everything! Ah, so embarrassing!!
Your mother seems to be really angry that I called..
[Pirates Of The Caribbean]
Ah no...
I'm sorry.
Oh no, it's nothing.
Ah.. but... Why did you call me today?
It doesn't seem like you are interested in me...
Yes.
Still, you are pure.
P..p..p..pure?
How am I so pure?
She's saying you are incompetent.
Why can't you understand what she's saying?
Ah, you.. What are you doing?
Ah you're doing it again, again.
Excuse me...
Let me ask you one thing.
Yes, go ahead and speak.
A certain man and a woman, in love, got a baby.
The woman wants to have the baby, but the man...
He loves the woman so much...
But he doesn't want a child.
Ah, that's a definite no.
That person is too selfish, in my opinion...
If a person you love,
gets pregnant and wants to have the child,
then you have to let her have it. That's real love.
Am I wrong?
Excuse me...
Ah, where is the women's washroom?
Oh, washroom.
That... If you go straight out of here,
There is a parking lot with cars parked. Just go behind there.
Choose any car...
Yes...
You can't do the number 2... That wouldn't be good..
Ahjusshi.
You can't tell the difference between pure and incompetent?
Aigoo...
If a woman tells you you're pure,
it means 'hey you idiot, you couldn't take it even if I gave it to you.'
That's just what you think.
Aigoo.
Ah... Forget it... Just give me another bottle of soju.
Also, in this kind of situation,
you have to drink a strong drink, like a man.
That's what makes women fall for you. Ah...
A strong drink?
That's right, for example.. Yea, this one is good, Ahn Dong Soju.
You have to drink something like this.
That's what makes women say, 'Ah, what do I do tonight?'
Give me that.
Ah, hey there!
Go home. Quit being pure.
That is enough of being pure.
I can go when she comes.
That woman isn't coming back.
Have you seen a woman that pees for 2 hours?
Aigoo, aigoo...
She left?
Ah ahjusshi, you kept telling her to pee behind the truck,
that's why she left.
If she liked you, she would pee even at the front and come back.
You don't think of how much you lack, but have such a temper...
Wait... Stop! Stop! Stop!! Ahjusshi!
Ahjusshi, stop!!
Oh! Miss So Yeon...
You said you were going to the bathroom...
But you are here.
Are you crying?
So Yeon... Why? The weather is so cold right now, and you're here by yourself...
The Han River winds are really strong...
Ah, it's really cold...
Is something wrong?
Will you...
hug me?
Why are you crying?
Would you like to get another drink?
I'll buy.
Ah, umm... I drank a lot...
But I have one condition.
Let's go somewhere with a washroom.
Hello?
Sir, it's time for you to check out.
Yes.
I don't remember a thing about last night...
Did I come into this room by myself?
You came with a woman.
Why? Is there a problem?
It's my privacy.
It hasn't been long since we met.. but already...
You did good. It's now absolute.
You bastard...
Hyung!
Oh, I'm a little busy.
Has So Yeon come yet?
She quit.
What did you say?
Yeah.
Hey, hey. There, that woman is your new wife starting today.
Doesn't she look like she could eat a lot of meat?
Her nickname is 'the hippo that drinks meat.'
Ah... Just because we slept together once, she quits her job...
I guess it would be uncomfortable to see each other.
What do you mean slept? With who?
Don't be surprised.
Hey, Miss Hippo! Why do you keep eating the props?!
You wouldn't believe me even if I told you.
[Ulnar Nerve Palsy]
Hello?
Yes, hello. Uh, it's me, Yoo Sang Yeol.
Pure man, Yoo Sang Yeol...
So?
Ah, why did you quit your job over that kind of thing?
What kind of thing?
Uh, last night... Why are you asking? I'm embarrassed...
What about last night?
You're doing this because we had sex last night.
What kind of crazy thing are you talking about right now?
Are you really going to deny it?
Che!
Hey you crazy pervert! HANG UP!
What kind of guy is this?
Who is it?
You don't need to know.
Ulnar nerve palsy?
A Chinese person?
Mind your own business.
No.. she slept with me..
And now saying that she didn't doesn't make it so it hasn't happened.
Ah, really...
My heart hurts really bad.
Why that woman did that to me...
You would know...
How cold-hearted of a person I am...
After sleeping together, I can't do anything.
My heart's beating so hard.
Stop eating, you! Stop!
Are you even listening to me?
I'm listening.
I'm ashamed of myself for bringing you along
and telling you these things.
Do you like the Bladder Moon Snail?
No, it's so gross I can't eat it.
Really? Ahjusshi, one more bladder moon snail please.
Okay, buddy~
I heard you have a tough love life.
I don't know about anything else, but if you have any questions regarding romance, ask me.
Ahjusshi, do you know anything about romance?
That's why.
You did it with her.
-But she's arguing that she didn't.
Yes!
That's a simple matter.
A simple matter?
Of course.
That just means that
you weren't very good in bed.
It isn't anything like that.
I'm telling you I'm right.
Then, ask that woman if what I said is wrong.
How could I ask her such a thing? It's humiliating.
It's okay to ask. The audacity of a man to ask those things,
can be seen as charming to women.
Women? There isn't much to them, the more you know.
If you are bold and good in bed, you are great as a man.
Ah, that's what you think.
This is really frustrating!
Would you like to bet with me?
What should we bet?
How about my eye?
Hello?
Ah, I called the wrong number. I'm sorry.
Sang Yeol.
Yes.
Why do you keep doing this?
-Please don't call.
-Ah, that...
I'm hanging up.
Ah, wait, wait.
What is it?
I'm sorry, but I...
Let me ask you one thing and I will hang up.
I won't call you again.
What is it?
Um,
was I not very good?
There's nothing you did wrong.
No, that's not it..
I'm asking if I did badly that night...
You don't have any fault.
Yes, I know, but...
That's not it...
What is it?
Was I bad at sex?
What?
-Oh my, this guy is really...
-Uh, no that's not it... Someone asked me to ask so I am asking...
Oh my, what a dirty person!
Hey! Wake up you crazy fool!
That's not it... I don't know how to ask those kinds of things... Hello?
Hello? Hello...
I'm screwed. Shit.
I'm going to pluck out his remaining eyeball.
Die!!
Hey, why does that idiot claim that you did it when you didn't?
I know. He was drunk, so I took him to the motel...
He took off his clothes as soon as he went in... and then slept.
Then, you must have seen his manhood.
Mm.
Is it big?
No.
It's small.
Shit. How small?
Quite very small.
How small is that?
Why do you ask that kind of thing?
-Ah, hey.
-I don't know.
Hey!
Like this, but.. hold on..
It's smaller than that?
About this much?
Well, it's about that size.
Oh my god, that's a shrimp cracker. Is that a human's...?
Ah, life is so pitiful.
Just neatly reject him.
Of course I did.
What about the baby, did you do it?
No.
I'm going to have it.
You're going to raise it by yourself?
Why? Can't I?
You crazy bitch.
Our country still thinks unwed mothers are criminals.
Do you want to live your life being treated like that?
Would you say that if it was the only child
you could have in your whole life?
Ah, it's so complicated.
Don't say that just because you don't have to deal with it.
I'm sorry for saying it, but...
I'm just thinking of you.
Also, do you want to live the same way your mother did?
She had a hard time raising you without a husband.
If she finds out that you are living the same life,
She'll cry tears of blood.
Ah, enough! My ear hurts.
You bitch. You don't understand what I'm saying.
Who is it?
Ulnar Nerve Palsy.
Wait a minute.
Hey. Didn't you say that idiot is arguing that you slept with him?
Mm.
Then say it's his. That would solve everything.
You crazy bitch.
You're telling me to live with a person that I don't love?
If you find that you can't live with him, just divorce him.
A divorcee is better than an unwed mother.
Are you crazy? I'm about to go crazy anyways.
Would I say this if I weren't as frustrated?
Really, why is he calling? Why?
Ah, so annoying. I'm so annoyed.
Hey. Leave it to me.
This kind of guy will continue if you are nice.
Hey. Hello!
You know why, right?
When a woman says she doesn't want to, but a man keeps bothering her.
Don't you know that's called stalking and sexual harassment?
You could go to jail for this.
If you make one more call to my So Yeon,
Then I will cut off your fingers one by one.
So you won't be able to touch your phone.
Ah, pull out his eyeball instead.
Ahjusshi, Ahjusshi! Please!
I'm sorry, but
I really had no idea that it was that bad to do that.
But, since it's turned out this way, I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Is it the caller's fault? It's my fault for making you call.
Hey, that's a good line.
So, it's settled.
In the name of repenting and forgiving,
Shall we toast?
You guys have made up. Okay?
Hold it up. Shrimp crackers.
Hey. Let me ask you one thing.
You love her, right?
You're embarrassing me. Why do you ask that?
Ah, shit. You're a man and you can't be honest.
Hey. Backbone!
-What?
-Sit straight. Your backbone...
Do you think you are a hunched shrimp cracker?
What do you think you are doing, hunching like that
in front of me?
Honestly tell me. You love her, right?
Do you love her?
A little...
You bastard. What's a little?
That's why that is small too.
Hey. Why do you point out his weakness?
Do you really like me?
Yes, I told you everything awhile ago.
Since when?
The Fall Special... 6 piece beef gift set..
Since then...
What do you like about me?
So Yeon, you may not feel the same but...
Every time you wrapped meat and fed me...
'Ah, we really are a couple.'
I thought those things.
Ah, it isn't that I thought that...
I think I fell into the illusion.
So Yeon, me,
and our daughter... a family...
It felt so happy. Those kinds of thoughts...
Those illusions...
During those times,
I told myself I had nothing more to want in this world.
It made me think like that.
It's funny, isn't it?
I'm so sorry, I shouldn't have said that...
I...
am pregnant.
Hey!
What do we do? You'll be so surprised when you hear this.
Hey, PD Park is here.
You've got quite the nerve to call him here.
I didn't call him.
You crazy bitch.
I've heard of switching kids but never heard of switching dads!
Be quiet. Someone will hear.
Hey, this was your idea.
Oh my... you are accusing an innocent person.
You're the one that did it.
Ah.
Hey, but you've got skills.
You made her pregnant in one go.
There is a really important thing for men.
You can't change it with money or power.
What's that?
Strength! Power, a strength that doesn't know how to tire.
You're joking.
You have a really small one.
Women like smaller ones.
Don't lie!
They like big ones you idiot.
When you scratch your ear,
Does it feel better when you use your thumb?
Or does it feel better with your pinkie finger?
Pinkie.
See, you fool.
Can I have all of the groom's friends come out?
We don't have much time.
We're all here.
Whiskey please.
[*Note: Koreans say Whiskey when taking pictures.]
It's mine. Give it to me.
They say kimchi stew is the best when you have morning sickness.
Ah, don't just sit there because you don't have an appetite.
Try to eat something.
Have some.
How is it?
I don't feel like eating.
Then watch me eat. People say that when they watch me eat,
it makes them want to eat too.
Here.
Did you brush your teeth before eating?
I will brush when I'm done eating. Oh hot!
You don't brush your teeth when you sleep either, right?
Don't you brush your teeth in the morning?
Do you have to make that much noise when you eat?
What noise is she talking about?
It's hot.
I'll be right back after stopping by the hospital, So Yeon.
Hello. You're peeling garlic.
Sit here for a bit.
I can't. I have to go.
Just peel 3 of these for me before you leave.
It's because my hands hurt.
I would like to do that too...
But I can't be late.
What are you doing?
I'm an actor.
[*Note: Actor in Korean = bae woo = to learn also :)]
What are you learning?
Ah, that is... I'm acting on T.V.
A talent?
[*Note: A talent in Korea is like a celebrity.]
A person with a face like yours can be a talent too?
His wife is like a flower growing on dog shit.
Wow, this really tastes the best of all the meat I've tried.
It just melts in your mouth.
Yes, we hope that you can experience this melting feeling as well.
We will leave the decision to you.
I am Shopping Host Hong Ga Young and Ha Wee Soo. Thank you.
And cut!
Good work. Good work.
Hey. Is this all you can do?
If you eat, frowning, do you think the viewers would want to eat it?
Ah, it's not that...
This woman kept wrapping the meat...
And kept shoving it into my mouth...
I'm not a meat grinder...
Ah, Yoo Sang Yeol is right about that.
That woman shoved it in very roughly.
Are you his representative?
I apologize.
Didn't I tell you not to let the actors overlap?
He ate at another show, do you think he would be able to eat again?
You're a useless bastard.
Are you okay?
Do your job right!
-Did you work another job in the morning?
-Yea.
You told me to work hard before the baby was born.
Ow! My nose!
My nose..
Ah, see! You snore so much, of course your nose hurts.
I have something I want to eat.
Really?
Ah, that's great.
What is it?
-Barbecued chicken.
-Barbecued chicken?
With lots of radish in vinegar.
Ahjusshi!
Oh, what brings you here at this hour?
You're going to have a drink?
No, do you have charcoal?
Charcoal?
I can't use that because it's too expensive.
What do I do?
My wife wants barbecued chicken.
Can't I do it on the grill?
Ahjusshi, if you grill a chicken, would that be considered a bbq chicken?
Is that how it is?
Does it become a lightning chicken?
Lightning chicken?
It's so good.
-It tastes better than barbecue.
-Isn't it?
This is totally different than barbeque.
A lighting strike has much higher wattage...
Oh, then is this grilled with lightening?
No, it isn't anything like that...
Why? Are you looking for something?
My radishes. Radishes in vinegar.
Ah, we grilled that at the street stall...
Why? Why aren't you eating it?
I don't eat radish to eat chicken.
I eat chicken to eat radish.
Just eat this for today, it's raining a lot outside.
When a pregnant mother
says that she wants to eat something,
it isn't because she wants to eat it,
it's because the baby
needs the nutrition in that food.
Ah, well... okay. I'll go.
I'll go right now and buy some.
What kind of nutrition does radish have that you want it so bad...?
Oh, it moved! It's moving.
Wow, it's fascinating.
Doctor, when will our baby be born?
There're 15 weeks left.
Didn't I tell you?
Oh I see.
It's kicking again, again! Wow.
Doctor,
is our baby a son or a daughter?
I can't tell you that.
Ah, why? I heard all of the other hospitals tell you things like that...
We go by the rules.
Oh! That looks like a weenie.
It's a boy! That long thing is a weenie, right?
It's the umbilical cord.
-How is your constipation?
-It's bad.
If you continue to be constipated, then you can take a laxative.
Okay.
Also, the baby is very good looking.
Thank you.
-Get up slowly, from your side.
-Yes.
"We go by the rules"
Will you get much business like that?
The gynecologists are going bankrupt because people aren't wanting to have babies...
They couldn't let us know even that...
She says it's a boy.
Who did?
She says it's good looking.
Hyung, do you see this long thing here?
Do you know what this is?
-The umbilical cord.
-Oh. You know at first sight.
I was so happy because I thought this was a weenie.
Hey, how could that be possible?
They say the size of a weener depends on genes too.
Ah, that's true. He shouldn't take after me on that...
Have you given him a name?
Yes, Bok Ddang. The lucky 'bok' letter and
the thank you 'ddang' word. So Bok Ddang.
[*Note: "Ddangi" in Korean is like a cutie.]
-Thank you 'ddang'?
-Yea. Look at how high his nose is.
Hey! What are you doing?
Ah, you're here?
You're not getting ready for the show?
Director. Look at this. It's Sang Yeol's baby picture. Isn't it cute?
Do you have time for this right now?
Have you passed out all of the cue sheets?
Ah, those.. PD Jang said not to pass them out.
Are you PD Jang's assistant or mine?
Ah, I'm sorry.
That's why you are still an assistant after all this time.
Hyung, isn't PD Park younger than you?
Why does he speak so informally? He's very rude.
That kid is younger than you too.
Really? Are you serious? I'm shocked.
Hyung, let's speak to him comfortably from now on too.
Ah, what can you do if you want to live.
I can't do that even if I starve. He's younger than me..
If I catch him, I'll break his leg...
-Hey! Come in!
-Yes? Yes.
Hey, hey, hey, me, me, me...
I get more nervous by the day.
It seems like Sang Yeol knows something,
and is acting like he doesn't...
What are you going to do? You're so nervous.
Also, that means that Bok Ddang is coming out in 8 months.
Even the most innocent person knows that a baby is born after 10 months.
That's true.
Ah, why didn't I think of that?
It's driving me crazy.
Hey, just tell him that Bok Ddang is premature.
There are more babies that are born in eight months than you think.
Do you think he'd believe that?
No, if it's Sang Yeol, he'll believe it.
He's not a common idiot.
Who's an idiot? He's just innocent.
Crazy bitch.
Just because he is your husband.
Ah, that feels good.
You ate a lot for lunch and you're eating that again?
The baby has to grow, so the amount that I eat would of course increase.
This belly...
By chance, is it that it isn't a baby growing...
But your poop is piling up in there?
Ah, I'm eating. Really...
But...
Can't we take that picture down?
It makes me feel like that weird guy is going to pop out.
Really?
But, that is supposed to protect your love,
And it holds your water veins steady.
So, it's a good thing...
We can take it down.
But, I'm kind of sad.
Just leave it then.
No, it's not that...
This is your home, So Yeon.
There's no need to ask permission from me.
Ahh...
Yes, So Yeon.
-Sang Yeol...
-Yes?
It's about to come out...
-The baby is about to come out?
-No...
Oh, poop is about to come out?
Hold on just a minute.
Sang Yeol!
Yes, I'm coming out.
Hurry, please.
Ah, that smell.
Why, Why?
So Yeon, what's wrong?
Again?
Is this poop or an anaconda?
Ah,
I'm going to die of suffocation.
How is it?
So Yeon, will you open the door for a minute please?
Why?
I can't breathe.
Ah, I don't want to...
I won't open the door until the water has gone down.
I'm scared...
What are you afraid of? I'm the one who's going through your poo.
Oh, I think it worked.
I'm going to flush it.
That's right, that's right.
Uh... this shouldn't happen, right?
Open the door, So Yeon!
The anaconda just popped out.
-Oh no!!
-I won't open it.
I won't ever open it.
Just one time.
Go to sleep. Please!
I'm tired.
Just sleep. I'm tired.
I told you to go to sleep.
I told you I'm tired.
What are you doing right now?
I'm asking you what you're doing right now!
Ah, So Yeon. Why aren't you sleeping?
You're not letting me sleep.
You keep doing this. How can I sleep?
We did it just once before marriage and haven't done it since.
The doctor said
to be careful. Don't you remember?
Go to sleep. Okay?
Let's sleep.
You have another worry?
If you are worried about something, tell me.
Ahjusshi, mind your own business.
Don't sit here and go. Quickly.
Aigoo.
Something's really bothering you today...
On a day that you feel down like this,
there's nothing better.
Have a drink of soju and go to your wife.
That's the best thing.
I got it.
-Eat lots.
-Yes.
You scared me.
Why'd you call me all of the sudden?
You idiot. Really..
I don't have any money today, so don't think of borrowing any.
This outfit doesn't even have any pockets.
I bought this because of you.
[Pirates of the Caribbean]
I haven't done it in so long, I think I'm going to explode.
I'm not getting married.
Marriage is a crazy thing.
It isn't that you aren't getting married. You can't.
I'm leaving.
I thought you were leaving.
Pay back all of the money you borrowed from me right now.
Why are you so heavy?
Just a little more...
Hey, Sang Yeol!
Hey...
Try to get up.
Hurry, get up!
Wake up...
He's totally drunk.
Hey!
This is revenge.
Wake up!
I told you to wake up.
Mmm...
So Yeon, what are you doing? It's too noisy.
Ah..
So Yeon, what are you doing? It's loud...
Where is this?
How long has it been since we got married
that you slept outside?
I was drunk and I had no idea...
Where did you sleep?
A motel..
What?
A motel...
What are you saying? Say it clearly!
Motel.
A Motel?
With who?
-Myung Boo.
-With Myung Boo?
Nothing happened between us.
Okay. There wouldn't be anything between you and Myung Boo.
Do I wash?
Go wash up.
Ah that rascal.
I, go to counseling lately.
I know. Ahh...
Lately,
even if a man sits next to me in the bus,
I get scared.
No matter how drunk I was,
no matter how much I haven't had sex with a woman,
How would I do you?
How could I do a man?
And honestly.
How do I trust your words?
It's not like there is any evidence.
Evidence?
Here. You see the yellow, right?
What is this?
What do you think it is?
-Hmm?
-Shit, really...
Put it away, quickly. Put away the evidence.
There's no use in denying it anymore.
I did a DNA test yesterday.
What is it that you want?
Compensation from the heart.
Hey!
[Bok Ddang's Mom]
Hello?
Where are you right now?
Sang Yeol is busy doing laundry...
Ah, Myung Boo!
But why is Sang Yeol doing the laundry?
Ask him yourself.
The sinner.
The sinner?
What are you ...
The sin of wanting me.
Myung Boo, you make the funniest jokes.
This isn't a joke.
Ah, Myung Boo. Come over to our home sometime.
Then I'll go today.
Today?
Ah, today's a little... What about next time?
-Yes. That sounds good.
-What?
No... good... That's not what I ...
Scary. It's like a red balloon.
So Yeon. Don't you worry.
I'm a hunk of collagen. I won't explode.
If you're done eating, you should go.
Hey, hey. Myung Boo.
Aish!
Don't try to trap me.
What does that mean?
What do you mean by trap?
It's nothing.
Whenever he drinks, he babbles.
Like that..
I'm going to the bathroom.
Do you want to die?
Why?
Are you scared?
Why did you do something you would be afraid of?
Let me off just once. Save me.
Please.
Hurry and go. Okay?
What are you doing here, you crazy fool?
I can't sleep on the couch because my back hurts.
I have a herniated disc in my 3rd and 4th vertebrae.
So what do you want me to do about it?
Let me sleep on the bed..
I'm going to sleep. I'll sleep quietly.
Why would you sleep here? Hurry and get out.
So Yeon, sleep well.
You crazy fool.
-Leave me alone.. I'm going to sleep here.
-Get out. Hurry.
Sleep with him here, Sang Yeol.
I'll go to the sofa.
Why would I sleep here with him?
Then, are you telling me
to sleep with Myung Boo?
I agree with her.
Ah, So Yeon, it's not that...
I'll take him out to sleep.
So Yeon, sleep well...
Hurry up and turn off the lights.
We should sleep.
You son of a bitch. Sleep, you son of a bitch.
Ah... You really hit me..
[Dad's Bok Ddang Diary]
[Dad: Yoo Sang Yeol]
[The lucky 'bok' letter and
the thank you 'ddang' word.]
[Lighting chicken]
Bok Ddang likes = Radish in vinegar..?!
Bok Ddang's family picture.
[Yoo Sang Yeol <3 Shin So Yeon's hot masterpiece]
["He's good looking = Bok Ddang is a boy"]
Did you smash your face against something?
Your whole face is bruised.
Why did you call me?
Why did I have to get caught by this kind of guy?
The underwear he wears...
Why does he always have to wear the white ones like this.
Where in the world do they sell these? Look at how long it is.
Shit. This bastard was using this to use me..
-No, I'm not..
-About what?
Oh, it's nothing.
So Yeon, why aren't you sleeping?
Just because... I'm not sleepy.
Why? Is something wrong?
Why?
The house is a little different today.
Our picture is up...
Did you see the flowers?
Flowers? Oh, that's why the house smells so nice.
You even bought flowers?
Home seems like the best thing.
So Yeon~
So Yeon! What are you doing?
You don't even feel that well.
It's okay. I want to do it today.
Ah... Why are you doing things you don't usually do? You're making me nervous.
I haven't eaten breakfast in so long
that I can't eat it anymore.
-Come out here for now. I'll do it later.
-It's okay.
Wow.
Look at the steam!
Wow! It's delicious!
It doesn't taste good, does it?
No, it's really good.
I had no idea that you could cook like this.
It's steamy. Wow!
It's not too salty?
No, it's not salty. Never salty!
It's amazing.
Food should be seasoned well like this.
Instead of using other weed-like things, it should be seasoned.
I'm not feeling good..
So I'll go and lay down for a bit.
Ah, why? You should eat a bit before you lay down.
Later. Eat.
Ah...
But this is really good!
Hello.
You said it's a son?
Yes.
When did you say the birthdate should be?
Yes. There are 8 weeks left.
8 weeks...
He's younger than me and keeps speaking informally..
Are you coming home early today?
Do you want to go to the street stall?
And eat some lighting chicken...
Why do you say that?
That Ahjusshi likes you, Sang Yeol.
Okay.
Then I'll see you later.
Get in.
Do you want all of the neighbors to know?
Why are you doing this?
You should know better.
About what?
It's my kid, isn't it?
Are you crazy?
How are you going to explain why
the child is born after only 8 months?
Th..that's because he's premature.
Your hospital told you he's premature?
They could win the Nobel Prize.
Where have you been?
Why are you out here?
You told me to come in early,
but you weren't home and your phone was off.
Oh! You bought something for Bok Ddang.
Wow. It's so pretty, this gift wrap.
-Were you out long?
-No, only about 2 hours.
Why are you so foolish?
I just went out because I wanted to.
I thought I might get some fresh air.
Your complexion doesn't look good.
Are you feeling alright?
I'm just
a bit dizzy.
Oh! Isn't that pregnancy dizziness?
I heard that pregnancy dizziness could be dangerous.
It's not.
Have you eaten?
That's not the problem... Dizziness is dangerous...
My friend, Byung Gook, his wife,
she ate this and was all better.
-She was very energetic after it.
-Oh, it looks really good.
Mixed? What? Hello.
-Hello.
What's that?
Ah, this isn't much.
His wife is a bit sick.
We heard that deer blood was really good for dizziness.
So Hyung got it for me..
Hey. Who feeds a pregnant woman this kind of thing nowadays?
Are you going to be responsible
if something happens to the baby?
No. Don't ever feed this to her.
Come see me after you're done.
Don't do it!
He's lunatic. Why is he going crazy? Is it his kid?
Do you know why I called you?
I'm sorry.
I won't do it from now on.
What won't you do?
Eating, overlapping shows...
You think I called you because of that?
It isn't?
Ah, I apologized for no reason.
I thought that was the reason..
Then what is the reason?
This is good.
Why did you call me here, PD?
How ridiculous would I feel if I were in your position?
But there's nothing you can do.
I'm the father.
If by chance it was your child,
how would the child be born in 8 months?
Sang Yeol!
What happened? I was worried.
Since when have you worried about me?
Why do you eat only that much?
I don't have an appetite.
Sang Yeol.
I have something to say.
Ah, I have something to say too.
-Umm...
-It's okay if I speak first, right?
Go ahead.
I have someone I love.
What?
But it's a man.
I'm in a relationship with Myung Boo.
How can you tell such a weird joke?
It isn't a joke.
All this time, I wanted to live like others,
so I used you, So Yeon.
I want to quit now.
Living like I love you, So Yeon, when I love someone else...
I just feel so bad. I can't do it anymore.
Let's get a divorce.
Sang Yeol.
I'm normally this kind of person.
I use other people for my benefits.
I don't even love you, So Yeon.
And on top of that, I couldn't become a good father.
Why are you doing this to me?
No matter what you say, So Yeon, I've made my decision.
Don't look for me anymore.
Find your road and live a happy life.
Why is a talent like you so down?
Here. Eat it.
It's sweet, right?
Feel better.
You haven't gotten a single call?
Yeah.
Is it really over between you and Sang Yeol?
Say something!
-Myung Sook.
-I want to mind my own business too.
So?
What are you going to do with PD Park?
Does he want to get married and have the kid now?
I need some time.
How much time do you need?
You're having your baby the day after tomorrow.
How much time do you have?
What are you going to do?
After sending you off like that,
it was really tough on me.
At the time, I was very confused.
I was too afraid of becoming a father.
So Yeon.
Forgive me.
For the sake of our baby,
Let's start again.
The person you've called is unavailable..
They said this was really good for pregnancy dizziness.
Don't misunderstand.
But that,
protects your love.
It's a good thing.
We can take it off.
It's exactly the same as before, right?
Stay here by yourself for the moment being.
Isn't this Jang Myung Boo's home?
What is that now?
What brings you here so late?
What's up with your outfit?
Ah, so refreshing.
Who's that?
Oh, are you done with your shower?
I'm asking who it is.
Oh, a friend.
A friend?
What kind of friend?
We graduated together... from middle school.
He's married.
-What is that?
-What?
That?
You're scary. So scary.
This'll be yummy.
Okay, it's all done.
Here, one scoop.
-What about me?
-Make it yourself.
Honey, do you want some more?
-This is already a lot...
-Eat more.
You should give some to Sang Yeol.
It's better than throwing it away.
Throwing it away is better.
Ah, che..
Hey, aren't you overdoing it?
You.
Who do you think you're yelling at?
Why are you protecting him?
There's something going on between you two, right?
Why are you acting like this?
What a shame.
If you take a look at him, he's a total player.
Hey, the maintenance guy asked about you.
What relationship are you in with the maintenance guy?
Ah really... You're really using your looks to your advantage.
You guys are really beautiful.
If there's trouble with anything, they all come to me.
That's how I grew so old.
I took care of all of them...
You should have stopped me.
You knew everything. Hyung, you're really bad.
I'm sorry.
You should have told me ahead of time.
Look at me now.
You liked her so much.
And they broke up.
You're life is really ruined from meeting one woman.
Do you call that comforting?
Anyways, there are too many great people surrounding me.
It sounds like
your wife is bothering you.
Feel better.
It's possible that your wife could look at other guys.
And the same goes for you too.
Are we gods? We aren't.
We can make mistakes.
Honestly, it's fine
just as long as your wife doesn't
get pregnant with another man's baby.
-Am I wrong?
-Die!!
Let go! Let go!!
No, no.
I'm at the cafeteria on the first floor.
I'm in the middle of my show.
Why?
Is something wrong?
I'll wait.
Let's talk.
It's been awhile.
Oh, hello Director.
Have you been well?
Yes.
When are you due?
Next month.
Is that so?
Then you should be free.
Come by if you have time.
Don't feel too burdened.
Yes.
Yes. Take care.
[Park Joon Ho & Han Kyung Ah]
So Yeon.
Listen to me.
So Yeon!
I was going to tell you.
It's just my outer shell that's getting married.
Get your hands off of me. It's disturbing.
Where are you going to go?
Are you going to go to that imbecile?
Hey.
Do you think you can go to that bastard?
That's not important.
Why wouldn't it be important?
Hey. You were going to use that idiot
because you thought it'd be hard to live on your own with a baby.
You can't go to him.
I told him.
That your child is mine.
That's why that retard
left you and ran away. Do you know that?
You coward!
Who are you calling a retard?
You can't even compare him to people like me or you, you garbage!
Trash?
Then what does that make you?
Ah...
Dressing up like this,
It really gives off a party atmosphere.
Honey.
How do I look?
Does it look good on me?
Don't go around like this.
Why?
It makes me nervous.
Ah, you scared me.
You scared me.
Why do you hit me? You're so cute. So cute.
But why isn't this guy coming out? This is so annoying.
I know.
So annoying.
Look at that.
Look at how he is coming out slowly on purpose.
He wants to see me die of frustration.
He's a total gift set of hateful things.
Ah.
What are you doing?
That man.
I want to erase him from my life.
Ah, honey..
I should have bought one size larger for my wig.
-Why?
-It's tight. My head hurts.
It still looks good.
Bok Ddang's Mom
Ahh.
Alright, next time we'll take more time getting ready.
Of course, you bought it for me.
[So Yeon]
Sang Yeol,
So Yeon is calling.
Don't answer.
Don't answer it?
Ah really.
Sang Yeol! What do I do?
Just leave it.
Hold on a minute. Wait.
-Huh?
-That's a man, isn't it?
It's So Yeon.
You liar.
Did you save the number under the name So Yeon?
-Give it to me.
-Why?
Let go!
Hey. Who are you?
-Ahh!
-If we don't answer you should hang up. Why do you keep calling?
Hello?
Are you a pervert? Who do you think you're moaning to?
The woman is moaning.
Give it to me.
Hello? So Yeon?
-I think she's in pain.
-So Yeon! What's wrong?
So Yeon! Where are you right now?
Sang Yeol...
Okay.
Yes, I got it.
Wait just a little bit.
-Is it that woman?
-So Yeon!
Hello? So Yeon, don't hang up.
Hello? Say something! So Yeon, say something.
It looks like a big accident.
Hurry and go!
Ah stop yelling!
You think this is a tank? Do we shove ourselves through?
-Hey, pull out your car!
-Do something. Please!
Honey. Try driving.
No, I'll do it.
Honey, where are you going? Do you have to pee?
Sir, we have a pregnant woman in that car.
Could you pull over a little?
Yes. Thank you. Have a safe trip.
Sir, I'm sorry but could you..
-Who do you think you are?
There's no need for you to know.
Just pull your car over to the side.
Who are you to tell me whether or not to pull over?
Wait, wait, wait...
You should've done that at the beginning.
Sir!
Ah, good good. Just a little more. Yeah, okay.
Sir! You too.
Thank you.
Hey!
Oh my god!
Oh my!
You have to turn here.
So Yeon! So Yeon!!
Wake up!
What do I do?
Oh my god.
Yea, hurry.
Sang Yeol, hurry.
-Careful.
-Wake up, So Yeon.
Stop! Stop!
I'm not on. Stop!
So Yeon, come to your senses! So Yeon!
So Yeon. Wake up.
Can you see me? Who am I?
So Yeon.
Sang Yeol.
Yes, Sang Yeol. It's Sang Yeol.
-So Yeon.
-Sa....
What?
Sa?
Sang Yeol...
I am Sang Yeol! Wake up!
Okay?
So Yeon wake up!
Sang Yeol...
I am Sang Yeol.
Hurry up!
Someone! Where is the doctor?
So Yeon. Wake up for just a bit.
So Yeon!
What happened?
I think it's kinda serious...
Hey, where are you going?
Coffee?
You're not going to drink coffee?
Where are you going?
[On Air]
Wow! There really are all kinds of meat here.
-Yes there are.
-Please explain each kind.
What you see here is the neck meat.
If you mean neck meat, it's here right?
Yes, and on rainy days...
I want to eat some now.
Ah!!!
You bastard!
You son of a bitch!
What is this?
Hey! Director!
Cut. Cut!
Camera 2. Show Host!
You son of a bitch.
Ah, you viewers must be really
surprised right now.
Ah, because
we couldn't call the customer,
The consumer came here in person.
Yes, orders cannot be connected here.
Please call the ARS number.
What did you do to So Yeon?
You pile of garbage!
Let go.
The door is opening.
[Emergency Surgery room.]
Doctor.
How is she?
It's a girl.
A daughter?
Not a son, a daughter?.. No no..
How is the mother?
The mother,
lost a lot of blood.
We have to watch over her tonight to monitor her condition.
Right. You should see your daughter.
Your daughter takes after you.
You're so pretty, my Bok Ddang.
Pretty.
It's nice to be out, right?
I'm sorry.
Daddy is sorry.
I was wrong.
You look so pretty.
One year later.
Oh my, our little Sarang is putting pretty clothes on.
Sarang. Why are you so shy?
Auntie. I'm Auntie.
Don't cry.
Oh my, it stopped in one go. How cute.
Auntie my ass.. You're an uncle.
A big uncle.
This is certainly a sight.
There, there.
No, no, I won't hurt you.
Are you a woman?
Not really a woman...
Your voice.. Is this a male or a female?
Omo! What are you doing?
Omo! I was invited here.
See! Good things happen when you listen to me.
Ahjusshi.
Your eye patch is on the other side.
It's on the same side.
Ay.. last time it was on the right.
I'm telling you it's right.
No it isn't.
It's on the right side.
Do you want to bet me? What do you want to bet?
Yeah, how about our eyeballs?
There's no need to bet the eyeball...
Where are you going?
I...
Even the doctors said there was no hope.
Why? Because the child was so weak in the womb.
Anyways, drink this deer blood!
A grandma can have a baby too.
Today's highlight!
Grab the Silver Spoon!
I am really curious as to what our Sarang will grab.
Ok. Shall we find out what our Sarang's dream is?
Here, Sarang.
Grab the one you want.
Ah not that. She keeps wanting to take the mic.
It looks like our Sarang has something she wants to say to you.
Oh!
It looks like she is looking for her mother.
Where is her mother?
You shouldn't do that..
Ah, I made a mistake..
I...
Honey! What's wrong?
Honey! Calm down. Calm down.
-Relax.
-Honey!
Honey! I feel like it's going to come out!
Okay, okay.
Oh, oh, okay.
It's today again?
Hey, hey!
The car, car.. car!
Honey, breathe. Breathe!
Breathe. In out.
Quit torturing your wife you rotten fool.
What was the need to rush and get her pregnant again?
Be quiet. Please!
She should have a day of rest too, you rotten fool.
It's not like that.
What's not like that? You rotten fool!
-You always watched such sexy and weird things..
-Be Quiet, Please!
You do the same thing even when you get married.
Ahhh!
-My hair! My hair!
-Pull it all out! You rotten fool.
Pull it all out!
Translation by heeji16
Timing and QCing by shinostarr
Editing by omgsun