Yo, man, come on!
Eighteen to
party, 21 to drink.
Have your IDs ready.
Eighteen to
party, 21 to drink.
Have your IDs ready, ladies.
Eighteen to party, 21 to drink.
Oh, my God.
Goddamn, I say I love my job!
Come on now, let's go!
Now where are all my sexy
Sagittarian ladies at?
Man, where your dollars?
Where your dollars at?
Man, she doin' it, y'all.
Chill, chill.
Watchu' come here for?
Oh, come on, baby,
I'm not going to bite.
Sorry, excuse me, sorry.
Come on now, let's go.
Yeah, it's your girl K-Sty.
You know you're rocking
with your girl K-Sty.
We're live at the Catnip Lounge.
Give it up for your girl Maine.
Maine's in the building.
Come on, we're late. Huh?
I gotta go. Hold on a minute.
Why you trippin'? What?
I gotta go. Why are you trippin'?
I'm gonna get in trouble.
Let me dance with shortie right
quick and then I'll be ready.
What?
Stop pulling on my clothes, yo.
Sorry.
How many numbers you get? One?
I could've gotten more, but your
moms was holdin' me up.
That's messed up.
How many you get? How many you get?
Oh. Let me see.
Tonya, Denise, Shelley...
Oh, wait, that's an old one,
I could delete that one.
So, Tonya...
Hold up. Liar.
Ain't Shelley that chick
from your math class?
Give me! Denise?
Yo, hold up, these are your damn
study group numbers, yo.
Why you frontin', huh?
I don't see you with
no list of numbers.
I'm not the one looking
for a girlfriend, man.
You the one still a virgin!
Trying to help your ass, you
know what I'm saying?
I don't know what you
waitin' on. Shit.
Still kickin' that quiet shit
from sixth grade, nigga.
I don't need to press, I gets
plenty. You feel me?
Wah-wah. Look, I get more pussy
than your daddy, nigga.
What? Okay, you got
me with that one.
You got me with that one.
Yeah, I know. I know.
You need to pop that
damn cherry, yo.
Shut up.
That's what you need to do.
Quit playing. Your stop.
Huh?
Your stop. Time to get off.
Nah, I'm gonna roll with you
a few more stops, a'ight?
Why are you gonna go all the
way up to come back down?
Make sure you get home safe.
I don't need your protection.
You ain't big, nigga,
get off. Hey, yo!
That's a'ight, man.
Yo, yo, yo. Next stop.
A'ight? Would you get off the bus?
Yo, what you pushin' me for?
Why're you beastin'?
I'm not beastin'. Just get off!
Tsk.
You got a problem. Yo, call me.
I'll call you. Bye.
You're late. Be quiet.
Where you been this late? Movies.
Movies ended at midnight.
Shut up. Don't push me.
I know what stays open
past midnight.
Good for you. Go to sleep.
Goodnight, Lee.
Lee?
Nice to know you still live here.
What are you doing home
so late, anyway?
Lost track of time.
You know what time your curfew is.
Where were you?
Movies.
The movie ended at midnight
and your curfew's at 12:30.
I lost track of time.
Well, at least you were cute.
I like that shirt. Where'd
you get that from?
Angel.
It's old.
Really compliments your figure.
You know, maybe we can go shopping.
I saw one just like it...
Goodnight, Ma.
You know what?
I don't like that young lady
that you run around with.
Yeah, okay!
Yeah, okay! And tie up your head.
It's your head.
And wash your face, too!
I don't have makeup on.
Wash your face, anyway!
Mom, I'm seventeen years
old. Can you please...
You need to watch your tone!
It's your skin.
All right, as
I promised, people,
these will be graded on a curve.
So, you're not going to get a whole
lot of help unfortunately
because the highest score
on the test was a 98.
This wasn't
even in the study guide...
Guys, I gave you all the answers
and the questions on
the review sheets.
It was on the test. I didn't
say that.
Y'all have a good lunch.
I'll see y'all tomorrow.
Study, people.
Hey, girl. Hi.
How you doing?
Talk to me.
You eat that shit?
I do. I don't know about
what you eatin'.
Tastes good. You should try it.
Yeah, listen, hummus will keep
me alive longer than that.
So, where's the new stuff?
Here you go.
Hmm.
Do you see the one in the back?
I'm gonna... I'll probably
do that in class.
Hmm.
So?
So what?
So what'd you think?
Yeah, they're okay.
Okay?
Well, they're lovely.
I mean, of course your
descriptiveness
and your use of alliteration
are beautiful and all, but
you know that.
But I don't know, is it your best?
No.
I thought it was good.
They're okay. Not great.
I think you can go deeper.
I'm not
able to take your call.
Please leave a message at
the sound of the tone.
Peace.
Hey, this is Lee, I'm not
able to take your call...
How's it coming?
It's good.
Let me know if you need me.
I don't see why we can't just
watch TV like usual.
Shut up.
You shut up! AUDREY: Girls!
I was expecting a call.
Hello?
Yeah.
It's your father's night off.
Straighten up.
So, Homecoming
got moved up this year.
It's actually going to be in September
instead of October.
Really? Yeah, which
means that I can actually
go to the Autumn Ball and
the Homecoming Dance.
Who're you going to go with?
I don't know, uh, maybe
Derek, if he asks me.
Or maybe Parrish.
But I know for Homecoming that I
definitely want to go with Craig.
And who are you going
to go with, Lee?
I'm not going.
What do you mean,
you're not going?
It's your junior year!
Leave her alone, Audrey.
If she doesn't want to go,
she doesn't have to go.
But she's a junior. She's not
going to have any memories!
I don't like all those boys
buzzing around my daughters anyway.
Nobody's buzzing around Alike.
That's right, and
it better stay that way.
Matter of fact, I'm not sure
if I'm gonna let you go.
Dad!
Shut up!
So what are your memories, Mother?
I got plenty of memories.
Like?
I'm just saying, share with us.
Did you go to prom?
Yes, I went to prom.
Who'd you go with?
Are you comfortable with this?
I'm fine. She asked you.
Did you have sex at prom?
Hey, hey, hey!
Relax.
I'm definitely
having sex at prom.
Oh, my God!
No, you're definitely
not going to prom.
You're not having sex for
10 more years, so...
Ten years?
At least.
That's like 25!
Exactly. That's early for me.
That's an inappropriate question.
Is that how old you
were when you first had sex?
That's how old you'll
be when you find out.
This isn't dinner conversation.
Guys...
Oh. Oh, my God.
That's just embarrassing, girl.
You ain't got
no range either!
Well, at least I hit
the backboard, damn.
Help! I'm getting mugged!
Girl. Come on, what's the score?
One up.
One? Yup.
Girl, I got at least three.
Definitely three, come on.
You trying to cheat me, too?
Help me!
Hey! Hey, hey.
Mind if I sit here?
Sure, go ahead. Help yourself.
Oh, thank you.
What you got there?
You been shopping?
Mmm-mmm. Just some yogurt.
Some vanilla yogurt.
No, I mean in the bag.
What do you got in the bag?
That big red thing?
Oh...
I don't know where my
mind is.
That's okay. Um...
Yeah, let me... Let
me show it to you.
Okay. Can I get your opinion?
Oh.
That's really nice.
Isn't that cute?
Yeah! Is that for your daughter?
Yeah, yeah. It's for Alike.
Oh, the youngest one.
No, the oldest one.
Oh, the other one.
Oh. Okay. Yeah.
Why, you think it's too young?
Oh, no! For some reason
the youngest one
just popped into my head
first, that's all.
Oh, but I think it'll be fine.
Oh, it's really nice.
Thank you. Yeah.
And you know what, it'll
compliment her figure.
You see, that's what
I thought. Yeah.
For some reason, Lee
just doesn't like
anything I pick out
for her anymore.
Oh, girl, please.
My oldest has banned me from
buying her any more clothes.
I just get her gift cards now.
Trust me, we're both
happier for it.
She needs to go
on a diet. Anyway...
Hey, Brenda! Hey!
Audrey, you got me a present!
No, I didn't.
What y'all in here talking about?
None of your damn business.
Let me know how it goes, okay?
Okay, I will. Hey, Bren...
This is the article I was
telling you about.
Oh, no. Is that her?
I told you! Look how
big she done got!
Oh, my gosh, that's a shame!
Isn't that crazy?
So, it was,
like, seven of us.
Me, Khalil, Misha, Tamara...
Tamara Marks?
Hell, no. Fat Tamara.
Oh, I was about to say.
Tamara Marks is a...
Uh, I can't stand her.
Anyway, it was all of
us, and oh, Laura.
You know that girl from
the restaurant?
She was there with one
of her friends.
The gay chick?
Y'all be hanging out like that?
Anyway, there's
a couple of them.
She's mad cool though, so she come
out with us every now and...
Man, y'all be doing it
big on the weekends.
Let me know!
- I told your butt to come.
- But anyway...
Yo, some of them AGs
are kinda cute.
I'm not saying I would,
but I'll holla.
I don't know
about all that.
Yo, isn't that one of
them over there?
What's her name? Amika? Alisha?
Alike.
Yeah, Alike.
She's cute, too.
I don't be looking
at them like that.
Look, I'm not gay, but if I was
gay, I might talk to her!
She's in the middle anyway.
Yeah, I know, if she was just
a little bit harder...
'Sup, ladies.
Oh, hey. Hey, what's up?
What's going on? Hey.
What's good? What's
good with that party?
What's good with this hat?
Don't play me.
Yo!
Oh, Mika, you act like
you bi or something.
I like girls. I love boys.
I can't tell!
Whatever!
So what do you think?
Watch out, it's slippery.
I already told you what I think.
But you know her.
I know of her, but I don't
"know her" know her.
Okay, you know her friend.
Can you hook us up?
Yo, put that stack over there.
Um...
Yo, pass me that rice.
Are you listening?
Yeah, I'm listening, man!
All I'm saying is that
I don't think
you should be putting yourself
out there like that.
Especially if you don't know
she like you like that.
She does.
She does?
How do you know she does?
I just know she does.
Hmm. We'll see.
What are you doing?
Thought I felt a drop of pig shit.
Shut... Shut the fuck up!
All I know is I've been
trying to get you
to talk to chicks for the
longest in the club.
I don't want to holla
at girls at the club.
Obviously.
So, why are you so pressed
about this one?
I wanted to ask you something
else, too.
What?
I need you to get something for me.
Just for my image.
What?
You trying to strap, yo?
Oh, my God, yo!
What are you going through?
By next Friday, please.
Next Friday?
Please. All right.
Okay, whatever. I mean...
Oh, my God, yo!
She better be cute for this, yo.
That's all I know, she
better be cute.
I think it looks natural.
I'm serious, I mean, it
doesn't look that bad.
I can't believe you.
What?
Laura, this looks stupid!
It doesn't look right!
Well, first of all,
it's not supposed
to be over your underwear
like that.
I'm not putting this thing
next to my skin.
It already pinches! It's supposed
to fit like that.
They didn't have brown?
I didn't have time for all of that!
And plus the brown ones are
too big for you anyway.
It's not funny!
Here, you gotta take it back.
I can't take it back.
No, here's the receipt!
Yo, I'm not going back in there.
One time was embarrassing
enough. No.
You grown! So what?
What if someone see me in there?
No, I'm not going back!
Then where's my change?
Lee, where'd you put my makeup.
Ooh, I'm telling.
Hey! Hey, get off of me!
Stop! Stop!
Get off of me with
that thing, geez!
Be quiet! Okay. Be quiet!
I'm telling you got that!
You can't tell.
I'm telling! Shut up!
Gosh, it looks nasty!
See, I told you so!
Yeah, whatever. Where's my makeup
case? I know you've got it.
I just borrowed it.
Okay, well, give it back!
Take it.
Promise you won't tell.
Just give it back!
All right! All right,
all right, all right.
All right, I won't tell. Okay?
Geez.
I'm still telling.
Telling what?
She took my makeup again!
Lee, please stop with the...
Oh, hello, Laura. I didn't see
you standing over there.
Hello, Mrs. Freeman.
How's your mother?
I haven't spoken to her in a while.
She's fine.
I hope so.
And I was glad to hear that your sister
finally got back on her feet.
Mom! Mom! She's good, she's good.
No, I don't think so.
We leave this door open.
Let a little fresh air
circulate in here.
I was just about to
leave anyway, so...
Mom?
Just try it.
Chill, you just
got to get used to it.
Stop touching it like that,
people gonna think
you got something.
The string hurts. I'm
going to take it off.
You're not going to take it off.
I'm going to take it off.
Where you gonna take it off
at? In the bathroom.
Then where are you going to put it?
You going to walk around the club
with a dick in your hand?
I mean, chill, man, you're straight
blowing me right now, yo.
Then I'm out. No, you're not!
You're about to go
through with this.
You're the one that wanted
to meet her, not me.
Okay, then come on then, let's go.
All right, man, chill.
Hey.
Where are my AGs at?
Where are my butches at?
Throw your hands in the
air. Let's get it.
You all right?
Yeah, um, I think there's a spring
in the cushion or something.
You wanna switch seats?
Nah, I'm good.
And you don't wanna dance?
Hey, yo, we gonna go dance, a'ight?
Nah, I'm not really
feeling the music.
Well, look, you don't mind, right,
if I go dance with somebody else?
Nah, do your thing.
If you change your mind, we...
Nah, it's cool.
Turn that mess off!
Sharonda!
Sharonda, stop lollygagging!
Lee! Are you ready?
Yup.
I said off.
And I thought you said
you were ready?
I am ready.
You're not going to church in that!
What's wrong with this?
Where's that blouse I bought you?
Dad!
Do what your mom says.
Are you hungry? Here, let
me heat this up for you.
That's okay. Oh, it tastes
so much better.
Dad...
Lee! Leave me out of it.
Now go get changed.
Dad, what's wrong with this outfit?
See.
I'm not going to argue with you.
Do what she says. Dad!
And put on a skirt!
Give me a beer, please.
It's Sunday morning.
It goes with the spaghetti.
Too much lip gloss.
Did you talk to her?
Sharonda's fine.
I'm talking about Lee. Alike.
And I don't see that
there's a problem.
I'm tired of this whole tomboy
thing she's been doing.
And Laura.
You said that you were
going to handle it.
Mmm-hmm.
She needs a male point of view!
I said okay, damn it.
Do you have to work tonight?
To put food on the table and
clothes on our backs, no.
To go out to restaurants and keep
designer sneakers in the closet, yes.
Are you forever gonna be mad?
Are you forever gonna be happy?
You made that decision
a long time ago.
We both made sacrifices.
You look beautiful,
baby.
Tuck your blouse in.
Tuck it in.
Leave it out.
I think it's fine out.
Are you coming with us?
Nope. Sleep.
We could do a later service.
Maybe the one o'clock.
I said no! SHARONDA: I'm ready!
Sharonda, Alike, you
look beautiful.
Everybody looks beautiful, okay?
Well, fine then.
Stop hitting me. Put
this one in then.
"God's love"? I don't
think so. Put it in.
Stop! Put in that one.
Audrey, hey! Hi!
How're you doing, girl? All right.
I'm not touching you. Stop!
I'm not touching you!
Sharonda, stop!
Ouch!
Lee, there's somebody I want you
to meet. That's just mean.
Huh? Here's somebody
I want you to meet.
Oh, hi.
Get down out of the
car and come speak!
What's wrong with you?
All right, Mom.
You'll have to excuse my daughter,
she's been feeling rude lately.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I understand how it is.
Hormones, you know.
It's just a phase.
Alike, this is Mrs. Singletary,
one of my coworkers,
and her daughter Bina.
Hi.
And that's my youngest
daughter Sharonda.
Hey. MRS. SINGLETARY: Hi,
there. Nice to meet you.
Lee, Bina goes to your school.
Cool.
Yeah, I think I've seen you around,
um, Mrs. Alvarado's class?
AP English?
Yup.
Well, now that we're all acquainted
with one another,
let's not be strangers.
Oh, no, no, we won't. Right, honey?
Bina, you know, I think you two
even go to school the same way.
Oh!
Well, you know,
there's something to be said about
safety in numbers, right?
Yup. Yeah.
Well, you know,
we need to be pushing off.
I'll call you about
the VBS workbooks.
All righty. All righty.
Take care. All right?
Great. Come on, honey. Bye!
So,
where you wanna go?
Um, I want to get those pancakes.
Oops.
You're funny.
I don't know what your problem is.
Mom, can you
put this in please?
I don't know what you think
this is going to change.
I know God doesn't make mistakes.
I know that.
Now, you may not like Bina,
but you're going to be spending
a whole lot less time
with that Laura person.
Mom, can you just put this in?
I can guarantee you that.
No, shh, be quiet, I'm not
putting anything in.
I'm going to listen to what I want
to listen to for a change.
Look, I just don't like lying
to my mother, that's all.
So then don't, she doesn't
have to know.
Yes, she does, she
asks me every day!
So, then, tell her yeah.
No! I don't want to lie
just to cover for you.
So don't!
Look, Alike, or Lee or whatever
it is you want to be called,
I'm really not trying to hang
out with you either, okay,
but I'm not about to
take an L for it.
So just stop dodging me!
Let's just go to school
together and then...
Then it's over with, we don't
have to hang out with
each other after that.
You know what, whatever!
She asks me again I'm
gonna tell her,
and then she's gonna
tell your mother,
and then it's whatever for you.
Hey! Hey, look, I'm sorry!
Look, I'm sorry!
Hello, I said I'm sorry!
Yeah, you sorry your mother's
about to bug out.
No, for real, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to be that
way, it's just...
Okay, look, I am concerned
my mom will find out,
but it's... But...
It's not like that, it's
just that she's...
Look, if you knew my mother,
you'd understand.
She's... Overprotective?
Yeah. Yeah, I know, I've seen her.
I see what she's like, but lots of
people's parents are like that.
Yeah? Yeah.
Yeah, but not like mine.
Anyway... Anyway, like I
said, let's just walk.
Thank you so much for
bringing that.
No problem.
You done studying yet?
No.
Did you start studying yet?
I'm on chapter nine. Now, stop.
Get them fucking cards out of here.
No, we gonna study these words.
I ain't studying. We can
play 'em like Tonk.
We can play Spades with
these vocabulary cards.
Get outta here, yo. I'm
about to deal you in.
I'm gonna deal you in.
So, listen, I'm gonna work some
more hours so we could...
"Listless, apathetic, having no
interest in anything." That's yours.
Listen! I have a job.
I'll work some more hours.
I don't need school.
"Clandestine, secret, hidden,
undercover." Not you.
Annoying, you annoying
me. Like, really.
"Turbulent, violently disturbed...
Come on, yo.
"...agitated, unruly."
That's yours.
Anyway, how much we
paid him last time?
Six twenty-five.
So, that's another 275 for
the rest of the month.
Electric?
Half.
Phone?
Let it ride.
Gas?
How much is it?
Eighty-five.
Half.
No, mmm-mmm.
Let it ride.
I could get some more hours.
No.
You know what you need to do.
Nah, Candy, I can't just dip
out on you like that, man.
Please, I was doing just fine before
you moved in, remember?
You working was only supposed
to be temporary.
Remember that?
I'm only gonna work
for a little bit.
Ma would've wanted you to
be done with... Who?
Who?
Yo, don't even... Just...
Just stop.
Mom would have wanted you
to be done by now.
Look, I'll get the money
orders in the morning.
I'll look into it.
The next test is coming up soon.
I said I'll look into it.
Without them and their
courageous efforts,
we wouldn't have been able
to pull this off.
Look, it's on again.
Check it out, Free.
Channel Five and Channel Two.
Look who's big time.
Oh, yeah, but my brother
looked clean though.
Yeah, you look like, you look
like, uh, that guy on TV.
Oh, yeah...
There's been more of that
since they opened up that
new club 'cross the way.
Excuse me, Miss?
Miss?
On certain Fridays they
got this, you know...
Special party going on. Miss?
Or should I say, "Sir"?
Sir? Sir?
Hello? Chill out, Sock.
Hey, my man, you hear
me talking to you?
Hey.
Mind your business. Hey!
And a pack of Kool.
Say, I've been trying to
get your attention.
Do you go by sir or miss?
Will that be all, ma'am? Yeah.
Look, I just had a simple
question I wanted to ask.
$67.05.
See, I just wanna know,
how does pussy taste?
You know, I just want to know
if you go with women
for the taste,
or is it because you too
dry, crusty, and ugly,
so don't no man want you?
I can't lie. The pussy
do taste good.
Oh, yeah?
Maybe you should try it sometime.
Or better yet, ask your wife
how much she like me.
Fuckin' bulldagger!
He-she dyke! Yeah.
Hey, ask yo' wife!
She told you.
She ain't tell me shit!
What the fuck y'all niggas
are laughing for!
Oh, shut up, man,
your big mouth got you
in trouble as usual.
Thought you was my friend, Mack.
Oh, man!
But I guess I didn't expect
you to defend me, Free.
Way your daughter's running around
here bull-dyke. Say what?
Say what? Hey! Hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come on, he don't mean nothin'.
What? He don't know what
he talking about, man.
He ain't moved outside
of a two mile radius
of where he crawled out
his mama's pussy.
He don't know shit! I
been to Poughkeepsie!
Yeah, well, get your Poughkeepsie
ass out my store!
Fuck y'all! I should
arrest your ass.
Man, fuck y'all!
Come, come on, Free.
Don't pay him no mind,
he just talking trash.
...had you all mad. ALIKE:
I wasn't mad.
Yes, you was. Yo, Candy,
I'm home yo.
Getting all crazy.
Damn, this your color, man.
So what's the deal, incog-negro?
Ma has me hemmed up.
Your phone ain't broke. You
coulda called a nigga.
My bad. She's got me hanging out
with this chick from
church. It's crazy.
Well, is she making you?
I mean, you a grown-ass
woman, bruh!
Here, put these on.
So I guess the piers is out
for this Saturday, huh?
Uh... I don't know if
that's me anymore.
That's hot, yo, you
should rock that.
I was thinking maybe we could
do something different.
Different like what?
I don't know. Like, maybe
check out an open mic or something.
Open mic? Nah, man, there's plenty
of chicks at the piers.
You just gotta be more confident.
I mean I haven't even wore
this, you could rock that.
If you want.
But I understand if you got
better things to do.
No. I'm down.
I don't want you getting all
hemmed up. No, seriously...
I'm down for whatever.
Real?
Promise.
A'ight.
I'ma take Saturday off at work,
it's going to be on and
poppin', you feel me?
It's gonna be mad tight.
We goin' get that punani,
yo. Feel me?
They look fake. AUDREY:
No, I think they're happy.
Now, that looks fake.
You should wear your hair
down more often.
Your father likes it up.
It looks nice down.
Maybe.
Give this back to Bina's mom
when you go over there
tomorrow night.
Saturday night?
We talked about this.
No, we didn't!
Lee. I had plans this weekend!
Well, you don't have
to go to Bina's.
You can stay here with
me on Saturday night.
God!
Come on.
So you like Destiny's Kids?
Mmm-mmm.
JP?
Nope.
What about Fiddy?
No, I don't like any of that
commercial bullshit.
Okay, so who do you like?
Just some underground stuff.
None of that crap they
play on the radio.
Okay, like who?
You know, people you probably
never heard of.
Conscious stuff.
Okay, like who?
Like Trees, Black Circle,
Far Front.
Far Front? Girl, I know Far Front.
Really? Yeah!
What about, um, Trade, or BRawls?
Or what about, um, Mama Dobia?
Uh-oh. What do you know
about Mama Bodia?
Let me find out.
See. You
don't even know me.
Oh, hi,
Audrey. Yes, she's here.
Yeah, yeah.
No, no, I understand.
Sure.
Not a problem.
What about rock? It's cool.
All right, I'm out. Wait,
oh, hey, wait, hey.
You gotta check this out.
Wow.
Hello!
Hey. You look nice.
Oh, um, is Lee home?
No, she's not, she's
out with a friend.
Oh, do you know what time she'll
be back? She won't be back.
She's out with a friend
the entire evening.
Oh, 'cause, we was gonna...
You take care.
Goodnight.
The love is gone
but the memory lingers...
Yo, this shit is hot.
Oh, don't you gotta go?
It's cool, I'll... I'll
cover for you.
Nah, I wanna stay.
Hey, this is Lee, I'm not
able to take your call.
Please leave a message at the
sound of the tone. Peace.
Hey, yo, where you at, Lee?
Yo, hit me up when you
get here, a'ight?
A'ight?
Come on, man, let's go,
man. A'ight, yo.
What happened? She didn't
fucking show up, man.
Well, you stressing
that shit too much.
Uh, Mrs. Alvarado's trying to get me
to check out one of these places.
Oh, hell, no. This
is for old people.
You know what, I'll write
down some places for you.
And maybe you can read
some of my stuff, too?
Definitely.
Yo, y'all remember when we used to
come out here all night?
Shit, used to.
You staying with your
sister now, huh?
Yeah.
Lucky as hell, man. Think?
My sister be home by six, so,
you gotta be out by then.
A'ight, good-looking.
Yeah, there's some lunch meat in
the fridge if you want some.
I appreciate you. Yeah.
Okay, easy, easy.
Watch the right hand side,
watch the right.
I am!
Okay. Oh, careful of the curb!
All right. Okay.
Good, good.
See.
I did it. Can I drive
back home? Please?
Uh, I don't know about
all that girl.
You're shaky. You're shaky. Please?
Here, here, get us some chips
and we'll think about it.
Come... Give me some
time to consider.
Careful.
Hey, Mack!
Hey there. Hey, Mr. Ferguson.
How you doing? I'm good,
how you doing?
I'm all right, I'm
all right. Thanks.
Yeah, I see where Alike been
running you around again, huh?
Oh, little bit, little bit,
but you know, I still
got it, though.
Yeah, I remember that crossover
you used to have.
You got to come out there with us
so I can show her what it's
like in the fifties.
Get in the car.
Wait, I'm driving! You said
I could... Get in the car.
Look, um...
You know you're daddy's
girl, right?
"A butterfly,
briefly suffocated
"on the mucus of its own change,
"imprisoned by the
membranous chaff
"of its own underdeveloped wings
"and cramped in the darkness
"of the too tight cocoon
of its own creation,
"pauses, thinking
death inevitable,
"prepares to die in the absolute
solitude of swollen husk.
"A crack appears,
"a thin, jagged light connecting
the inner to the outer world,
"a butterfly, briefly paralyzed
by the imminence of death,
"discovers life is possible."
Comments? Critiques?
Julie, tell me what you think.
I like how she described
the butterfly.
I could almost see her...
I liked your story though,
it was tight.
Yeah, which one? The
one about the...
Karma. About how things
come back to you.
That one, it was tight.
For real? Thanks. Yeah.
I wasn't gonna say anything, but...
I liked yours, too.
Why?
Why wasn't I gonna say anything,
or why did I like it? No,
why did you like it?
I don't know, it just...
It felt real.
Okay.
Didn't you have a different
shirt on earlier?
What?
Nothin'.
No, say what you're
gonna say. Nothin'.
Yeah, I had on a different shirt.
That's cool.
So how come you weren't going
to say anything about it?
About your shirt? About the poem.
'Cause you're moody. Moody?
And quiet. I'm not moody!
Yeah, right!
What? This is me.
Hey, it's not so bad when there's
a little conversation!
You wanna come up?
Who gave you this?
The bear? My dad. No, this.
Girl, my stupid ex-boyfriend
gave me that.
Oh, cute.
Not really. But I guess
it was at the time.
So this is the artist I
was telling you about.
Her stuff is like...
I don't know, dense.
Yeah, this is straight.
You burn me a copy?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good. Thanks.
I got some other stuff
for you, too.
Cool.
So who do you hang out with?
'Cause I never really
see you with anybody.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for
it to come out like that.
I was just curious 'cause
I don't really like anybody
that goes there either.
No, my, my friend Laura
used to go there.
Not now, but she's coming back.
Cool.
'Cause I was gonna say, I'm
going to this house party
and, you know, you can
come if you want to.
They play like this kind of music.
Sure.
How am I supposed to dress?
You don't gotta dress,
you just come however.
Come as you are.
Okay.
Can I see?
It's... It's mostly
old stuff, though.
Oh, this is the one that
you did earlier.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's nice.
Here you go.
Take it. You play too much!
Just take it. Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, what's so private?
Nothing. It's just my writings.
Why'd you do that for?
I'm sorry.
I thought... No, I'm sorry,
I just gotta go.
But I thought that...
I'm sorry.
We gonna get y'all on the
board, God damn it!
Okay.
Let's play, keep it rolling,
keep it rolling!
Ain't giving you
no stupid-ass hand.
You
gonna get that?
Yeah, I got it. There
you go. Cut that!
Come on, bring it out,
bring it out.
Ooh!
We went in the hole one time.
Y'all went in the
hole twice! Yo, wassup.
Yo, whaddup, Lee!
Yo, what you got, Ty?
Pick 'em up! Nasty!
Oh! We goin' to eight!
We goin' to eight!
Uh, can I talk to you for a second?
Yo, I'm busy right now,
I'm doing something.
Holdup, holdup! That was
my jack! I cut! I cut!
Laura, I really need
to talk to you.
Laura, I really need... Yo, man.
I told you I'm fucking busy! Shit!
Nah. Nah, nah. I'm busy.
Goodnight. GIRL
2: Get home safe!
Yo... I thought that was your girl.
Mind yo business! I'm her girl!
Exactly. Exactly. This will...
You go ahead. That's what
I'm talking about.
Y'all niggas don't know.
You know, boo. Get the
fuck outta here, yo!
Dad!
Come on, now, you know that's
not what I want.
That's not what I'm saying!
Lis... Listen to me. Are you
going to listen to me?
Dad?
Listen, I gotta go.
I gotta go, my daughter's...
My daughter's up!
Dad? Talk to you later, bye.
Who was that? What you doing up?
Just wanted to talk.
Dad, the plate!
Don't trash the plate.
Aren't you hungry? No.
Ate already. You ate at work?
Grabbed some takeout. Oh, where?
Why you asking me so many
goddamn questions, girl?
What's wrong with you?
You don't question me.
Sorry.
Hold up, Alike.
Come on back. Look.
I got patties.
Beef? And chicken. Come on.
Listen, um...
Your mom was worried that uh...
She's been wanting me to ask you,
that, uh...
How's school?
Straight As?
Probably.
That's right. Wanna sip?
I said a sip! A sip!
What's on your mind?
Nothin'.
What if...
What if say... Somebody liked you?
They like you? Or they
"like you" like you?
They "like you" like you.
Uh-huh.
They haven't said anything
yet but...
But what if... All right,
what if the person
is kind of like a friend,
but you know they like
you more than that?
Well, I think that's the best
way, to start as friends.
What if... What if the person is...
What if the person...
What's his name?
What grade is he in? I'm gonna
look his ass up in the system.
Wait till I tell your mama.
She'll be so goddamn happy.
Yeah.
Say, uh...
There's this new, uh, women's club
up there by the liquor store.
Do you...
Have you... You haven't heard
anything about it, right?
Called the Kitty Litter, Cat
Box, something like that?
Nah, never even heard of it.
Good.
'Cause it's a...
That's a rough neighborhood.
You know that, right? I
had a case over there.
You wanna be careful.
Stay away from that element.
In case it ever comes up.
I'll be careful.
Good.
I know you will.
Dad, when you were on
the phone earlier...
Uh-huh. It sounded like...
I mean...
I guess you're headed
back to work, huh?
Yup.
Your mama still up? Probably.
Tell her I had to work.
Love you.
Hey. Hey.
I'm real sorry about the other day.
It's cool. Things have been crazy.
But look, I'm really
sorry I bugged out.
It's just, I didn't know that you...
I wasn't expecting that.
First kiss?
It's cool.
You still comin' to the party?
Um... I don't know. I need to
try to catch up with Laura.
Oh, okay.
No, but I do wanna hang, but I
mean, maybe we could do both.
Cool.
Uh, do you want to spend the night?
You know, maybe avoid that
whole curfew thing?
Oh, you're home?
Hey.
I must have dozed off.
How long you been in? Hour.
Did you see the plate over there?
This is fine.
Why don't you come sit over
here? There's room.
You could see the TV better.
This is fine.
Thank you.
Just alike.
Say what?
You and your daughter. Did
you talk to Lee yet?
I told you she's still...
I talked to Alike.
You did?
Everything's fine, like I told you.
Matter of fact, she's
got a boyfriend.
A boyfriend? Just give
her some space.
Space?
She's never around as it is.
And you're just like her!
Creeping in all hours of the night.
Running around like you
got something to hide.
Both of you!
And acting like I'm
the big bad witch!
What about me, huh?
I'm here alone by myself
all the time.
And Sharonda's getting older and
she's starting to go out,
and pretty soon... I don't
have anything to hide.
Look, I told you, I
talked to Alike.
Everything's fine. Did you ask her?
No, because I don't have to.
Besides, I would know, okay?
I know my daughter better than anyone
else. "Your daughter."
So all of a sudden now she's
your daughter? And I'm
telling you, she's fine.
Well, I guess then I just shouldn't
say anything else about this!
That's your damn problem. You're
too much of a damn worrywart.
Well, let's hope you're
right, detective.
Will you shut the fuck up?
An hour? Really?
I'm not your damn dumb
floozy on the street
and you will not talk
to me like that!
Dammit, Audrey,
you're making a scene!
I'm not making a scene. You're
the one making a scene!
You're all paranoid and sick!
You're never here!
I know you're not scared.
I'm not.
Lee... Hmm?
I hope you know it doesn't
matter to me.
I know.
And she ran like blood
Through the corridors of your mind
Into a brand new future
One without the likes of you
You are mad fun to hang
out with, I have to say.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah!
Whatever!
I'm just playing. About...
About six months ago.
What's good? What's up?
How you doing? Good.
So what do you think?
She's cool, right?
She's hot, right? I told you!
Right? I told you! It was
so... Yo, I'm right here.
Oh, my bad!
I thought you were right beside me.
No. Anyway, I was thinking
next weekend,
the three of us, we could,
you know, go out.
I'm sorry about all the drama.
Nah, it's cool. I mean,
I should have... No.
You know. What I'm saying is,
I probably overreacted. I mean...
But then, I don't know, seeing
the two of you together...
I'm glad you're finally
happy though.
Come on, man, you know
you're my best friend.
I'm not, no one's ever... You don't
have to say anything, yo.
I just want to get this off
my chest, all right?
I'm glad she makes you happy.
I'm happy for you.
A'ight?
'Cause I love you.
Hey. Hey!
- Come on, let's get
- So...
Wait! Laura.
Come on, let's go, I
know some... Laura!
What up, boo?
Come on, let's go.
I'm not sleeping. Yes, you are.
Are there any more brownies left?
Nope.
What? Nothing.
What? Nothing!
What's wrong?
This is...
I never...
I'm sorry, I'm trippin'.
It's okay.
We don't have to.
Oh.
I thought you went
out for something.
How you been?
You know me and Candy
doing real good.
We might even get a bigger place.
She workin' at the hospital now.
You'd be real proud.
She might even get her RN.
How's... How's pops?
You look good. You look real good.
You know, we miss you
and everything.
I don't, I don't want to take
too much of your time
or anything like that. I just...
I got my... I'm getting
my stuff together, too.
You know?
So I did it.
I got my GED.
Nah, nah, I did it! I got my GED!
Good morning. Hey.
You're up already.
Actually, it's after one o'clock.
What's wrong? Nothing.
I'm just trying to clean
up, that's all.
Okay, let me help you then. No,
it's all right, I got it.
What's wrong? Nothing!
Look, um, last night was...
It was amazing, and thank you.
Last night was just playing
around, all right?
Look, we can slow things down.
People don't have to know
that we're together.
Together? Whoa.
No, uh-uh.
Look, if you don't want to
call it that, that's fine,
but don't act like
nothing happened.
I'm not like "gay"
gay, I'm just...
I'm just...
You know, I'm just doing
my thing, that's all.
I'm just, I'm not ready
for all of this, okay?
Excuse me.
Hey, Lee, Lee! Hold up.
What?
You don't have to tell
anybody, okay?
Where in the hell have you been?
You hear me talking to you?
You left Bina hours
ago! I am not Dad!
I'm not your husband, so stop
coming at me like I am!
I'm not your companion and
I'm not your friend!
You made that abundantly clear!
I'm your daughter! And I have
my own shit to deal with!
You must have lost your damn mind!
You wait till your
father gets home!
I would be something
else if it wasn't for you!
I'd be a lawyer maybe! AUDREY: Oh,
you wouldn't be shit because
I made you! I made you!
You couldn't even get a damn B...
Always thinking about yourself!
...on a test until I helped
you! We'd have more money!
We'd have a damn brownstone instead
of living in the basement of one!
You the one who's making a scene!
Doing all this paranoid shit!
You're never here!
I'm not paranoid.
I can't take this shit anymore!
Will you stop saying that!
It's the truth! Audrey, stop it!
Alike, go back to bed.
You have a slut on the side!
Nothing's going on!
I'm not paranoid! I'm not paranoid!
I can't take this shit anymore!
You are paranoid!
Alike, baby, go back to your room!
Lee, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. ALIKE: Go upstairs.
Don't leave me, please! No, No!
Go in my room and lock the door.
Keep me company, please?
Do not come out the room!
Go upstairs in my room and
lock the door. Please!
I'm not paranoid!
You are paranoid! All
you do is break!
All you do is break!
When do I see you?
When do the kids see you? I just
need to get outta here!
You don't want to face the facts!
You don't wanna face the facts!
No dammit, that's not true!
It is true! Look, would
you stop saying that?
It is true! Audrey, stop it!
Alike go back to bed.
Your daughter is turning into a
damn man right before your eyes
and you can't even see it!
No, you take that back!
Shut the fuck up about that, Audrey!
Mom, Dad, stop! Please!
Tell him!
Tell him where you hang out!
Tell him about your butch-ass
girlfriend! Laura is not my girlfriend!
What the hell are you
talking about?
Alike, please, just go back
to your room, baby.
Tell him! Tell him! Tell me what?
Tell him you're a nasty
ass dyke! No! No! No!
Alike, you tell your mama
that's not true!
Baby, tell her!
You see! You see! Will
you shut the hell up?
You tell her. Dad.
You tell your mother
that's not true.
You already know. No, I don't know.
You tell your mama it's just
a phase. It's not a phase!
See, you should
have done something!
You should have done something!
What's wrong with you?
There's nothing wrong with
me! This is your fault!
Shut the hell up! Lemme talk!
If you had been here!
Yeah. I'm gay!
You say it again. Say it again!
I'm a lesbian! Yeah, I'm
a dyke! Audrey! Audrey!
Get off! Get off!
Audrey! No, you're not!
You get off of me!
Come on! You cheater!
You get off me!
Get off of me! ARTHUR:
Come on, we gotta go!
Okay.
Would you care to say grace?
Heavenly Father,
we thank you for this food.
We pray for your continued
blessing.
We pray...
We thank... Amen.
Amen. This food should
be delicious.
I got the recipe from a magazine.
And I made your green beans
that you like so much.
Sharonda, could you pass
me the green beans?
This is yummy.
Dad, you know where she is.
Yo, Lee.
Where's Mom?
She...
Your mother couldn't make it.
You remember our old place?
Way out in Queens?
It was our first apartment.
We were so proud.
It had all those trees around it.
In October, the whole block would
be covered with leaves.
You remember?
Couldn't have been more
than two years old.
When that wind would blow,
those leaves would come rushing
down the street at us.
You thought they were alive.
You'd get so scared.
You'd cry and scream and beg
for us to pick you up.
I would try and tell you, "They're
only leaves, baby,"
and make you stay on the ground,
but your mother would
always pick you up.
She always picked you up.
Remember how we used to race
to the phone when it rang?
I've been accepted into an
early college program.
It starts in the spring.
It's in Berkeley.
It's a 10-week writing workshop.
Boot camp, then I could
start summer semester.
We can talk about that, okay?
I need you to meet with
my guidance counselor,
so you could sign the paperwork,
so I can graduate early.
I'm sorry, all right?
I'm sorry I let her hurt you.
I just need to know if you'll sign
the paperwork. Yes or no?
Can you forgive me? Yes or no?
You can always come back home.
Things are going to be different,
I promise you.
Dad...
I'm not runnin'.
I'm choosin'.
I'm not going back home.
I know.
And you could tell
Mom she was right.
God doesn't make mistakes.
You should tell her yourself.
Mom.
Lee.
Alike.
How have you been?
Fine.
Did Dad tell you?
Yeah. He told me.
How you been?
I sure hope you've been
keeping yourself safe.
I love you, Mom.
I said I love you.
I'll be praying for you.
"Heartbreak opens
onto the sunrise
"For even breaking is opening
"And I am broken
"I am open
"Broken to the new light
without pushing in
"Open to the possibilities
within pushing out
"See the love shine
in through my cracks
"See the light shine
out through me
"I am broken
"I am open
"I am broken open
Be careful.
"See the love light
shining through me
"Shining through my cracks
"Through the gaps
"My spirit takes journey
"My spirit takes flight
You just better fuckin' call, man.
"Could not have
risen otherwise
"And I am not running
"I am choosing
"Running is not a choice
from the breaking
"Breaking is freeing
"Broken is freedom
"I am not broken
"I am free"
Yeah.