I'm not gonna make excuses.
I asked for this.
All of it.
And I did it to become someone else.
I wanted more.
We belong to a generation that watched
our future get stolen out from under us.
The American dream our parents knew
has been hijacked by men
who are willing to lie, cheat and steal
to protect their wealth.
Used to be if you got good grades,
you got into the right school,
got the right job.
And after 15 years of hard work,
you get your name on the door.
But that world is gone.
People always tell you
be careful what you wish for.
I never believed them.
The lights always looked brighter
across the river.
Hey, come on!
Hey, I'm coming. Chill.
I'm paying extra for that?
Don't worry, it's covered, scout.
- Nothing's covered, dad.
- Where you going?
I'm going to the club with Kev.
- Which one?
- Why? You think you might know it?
Well, I have been known to frequent
discotheques in my heyday.
They don't call them that
anymore, but that's good.
Hey, don't let him smoke. He hides
cigars under that cushion there.
Don't smoke!
What's the matter? You jealous?
Oh, yes.
Club rise, baby.
What took you so long?
Why don't you do yourself a favor
and lift the rope?
And how is that
doing me a favor?
Consider it an investment.
Come Monday, my boy and I
will be making so much money,
you'll be begging us to come back
to this flavor of the month of yours.
Look, no hipsters
and no virgins.
Virgin?
He's not a virgin.
I just watched him get laid outside.
I watched it,
I literally saw him get laid.
- Adam, come on.
- I saw him with my own eyes.
I'm going to be back.
Are you nervous yet?
Nervous? About what?
On Monday we pitch our product
to Nicolas freaking Wyatt, that's what.
Kevin, we've been working on that pitch
for four months. It's genius.
The only thing
I'm worried about is
who Wyatt's gonna fire
for not promoting us sooner.
How great is it gonna be
to pay our bills
and eat in the same month?
Oh, get ready
'cause it's happening.
You always say it's happening,
and then I end up paying for the cab.
This time's different.
This pitch,
it's gonna change our lives.
Promise you.
But I'm still paying for the cab, right?
- Yeah.
- Got you.
It's not me.
Hello?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Sir, can you turn around? We need
to go to Saint Joe's hospital.
Adam, he's doing great.
He's up to his old tricks.
He's right through there.
We cleared out
the mucus, and he's fine.
But he must use
the oxygen more,
and he has to call us
at the onset of congestion.
- Yeah, he knows.
- Wants to do it his own way, huh?
Yeah.
- You can take him home.
- All right. Thanks.
As you can see, Mr. Cassidy,
the last two procedures
were not covered by insurance.
What do you mean?
I have extended coverage.
You did.
Wyatt corp terminated it.
They can't do that. I have it.
I need to have it.
Unfortunately, they can.
A lot of our companies
are doing it now, cutbacks.
I don't have 40 grand.
We can help with a payment plan,
or a medical loan.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah. I'll figure something out.
We did everything we could.
We work for Wyatt corp,
one of the top tech companies
on the planet.
When they hired us,
we were going to take over the world.
Six years in,
we were still just lowly cubicle drones,
watching our bosses take home
obscene bonuses...
While we were stuck
with entry-level salaries.
We'd waited long enough.
It was our turn.
Our time to shine.
You all right?
Yeah. We're gonna kill it.
Yeah, well, if things go South,
just stay cool. All right?
Yeah.
Mr. Wyatt is ready.
Stay cool.
Good morning.
We are all in the business
of connecting people.
This water's not hot enough.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wyatt.
I'll take care of it.
It should be boiling.
Uh... we're in the business
of connecting people.
You already said that.
Right. That's what our customers have
always wanted. To stay connected.
Those same customers are now texting
more than they're talking
and tweeting more
than they're meeting.
So, what's changed?
What are we missing?
We don't want to be
connected anymore.
We just want to feel connected
while we isolate.
So, what if...
A four-inch mobile had
a 60-inch screen?
Well, then it wouldn't be mobile.
With a voice-activated pairing device,
Ethion will allow users
to broadcast their mobile
across any monitor in the home.
Pick up.
Ethion 3.0 gives you the power
to bring your world to you.
Is he pitching me software?
Sir, we see a unique opportunity to take
Ethion from a run-of-the-mill phone...
This is a re-branding meeting.
Where's the disconnect?
Well, sir, I believe the disconnect is
between you and the consumers.
You didn't hire us to sit around
and watch you make tea, did you?
Tell me, why did I hire you?
Because we know
what a younger generation wants.
Which is?
A phone that doesn't just look new
a phone that is new,
a phone that changes the way we live.
You know, you're right.
I have lost touch with your generation.
What was your name again?
I'm Adam Cassidy.
How old are you?
Twenty-seven.
When I was two years younger
than you are now,
I was pioneering
digital cellular technology
while my colleagues were still pissing
around with electronic pulses.
I had vision.
But you have all the technological
advantage imaginable
and what do you bring me?
Social networking on a television.
Next! Bring in Richard McAllister.
I'm sorry, guys-
you just left us standing there
looking like idiots.
I mean, what were you thinking?
We all backed the idea.
Our idea wasn't the problem.
I railroaded him. You saw his face.
That's what happens when your team
leader goes rogue and argues with God.
Well, uh... I guess now
that we're not working together
we can start sleeping
together, right?
I seriously hope
you're not talking to me.
We'll find new jobs, right?
We weren't laid off,
Chels. We were fired.
How are you going to explain
that on your resume?
You know what? The least I can do
is buy you guys a few drinks.
Our discretionary account? Really?
Adam, no. If Wyatt ever found out
that we spent any more money...
What are they going to do? Fire us?
The money was ours to spend
as we see fit. We're going to rise.
- We can't get in there.
- Yes, we can.
- Try and stop the guy.
We're going to rise,
baby! Oh, yeah!
Dude, you realize this is
going to be so awesome.
- We're going to pop ten bottles.
- Think so?
I hate this doorman.
Adam Cassidy.
Told you I'd be back.
Your table's right this way, sir.
Yeah!
- Yeah!
- Oh!
- Shots!
- Oh my God.
Ooh!
If you guys don't get lucky tonight,
it's never going to happen.
I'm fielding offers. You want in?
See me after.
- Cheers, guys!
- Whoo!
Yeah!
Adam, maybe
we should close out the tab.
Hey, don't worry about it, man,
don't worry about it.
Hey, can we get
another bottle of Ciroc?
- Twirl me!
- No, no, no.
Come on!
Hey, buddy, where you going?
Could be love.
Wake up.
Hey, wake up.
- Hmm?
- I have to go.
So do you.
No breakfast?
Did I, uh, do something wrong?
If you had done something wrong,
you wouldn't be here, would you?
So...
So, uh, we...
Are leaving.
Wait a second,
I don't even know your name.
Are you taking the fire escape?
Ok.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey. Black, or cream and sugar?
- You stalking me now?
- I just want to know your name.
Why? So you can poke me,
friend me, ask for my number?
Or you could
just give me your number.
You're not
relationship material.
Relationship?
You're looking for a relationship?
I love relationships.
I'm great at relationships.
No. Actually, I'm just trying
to get rid of you nicely.
Didn't we have sex?
I have a thing for bridge-and-tunnel
guys when I drink.
Did you just call me
bridge-and-tunnel?
You took me out
for cheese fries.
Cheese fries!
Oh. Then what?
Then you had the night of your life.
Your words, not mine.
Oh... black.
Adam Cassidy?
My name is Miles Meachum.
Mr. Wyatt would like to speak with you.
How did you know where I was?
I mean, I don't even live around here.
Ah! Mr. Cassidy.
The man who claims he knows
my business better than I do.
Here, take a seat.
- Drop of vino?
- Uh... no.
It seems you were the beneficiary
of an accounting error we made.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
The Ethion discretionary fund.
Where's my money?
We used it on market research.
At club rise?
Sixteen grand?
It must be a very detailed report.
You think you can rip me off
and get away with it?
Credit card fraud?
No, sir, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna pay you back.
No you won't. It wasn't a loan.
Now there's two ways
we can play this.
Are you a horse or a dog?
A horse is motivated by fear.
He's running from the whip.
The whip here being felony fraud.
- He's a dog.
- A dog is motivated by hunger.
He's chasing the rabbit,
his next meal.
You were raised
in a low-income home in Brooklyn.
Your mother died
when you were seven.
Your w-2 says you
now support your father.
30?
So, it means you came
across that bridge every day
hungry to succeed.
- Everyone wants to succeed.
- Yeah, but not like us.
Your father spent 32 years
as a security guard.
- Where's the ambition in that?
- What's this about?
You want more out of life!
I grew up like you.
I mean, different streets.
Same dream,
but nobody gave it to me. No one.
And what if I told you
I could make you rich?
And give your friends their jobs back?
That was a smart pitch
you gave yesterday.
I started out at Eikon.
Jock Goddard was my mentor.
Do you know him?
Yeah, of course I know him.
I did my graduate thesis
on semi-conductor memory.
Goddard's basically the reason
cell phones aren't the size of bricks.
He founded Eikon.
And built it
into the largest publicly traded
technology company in the world.
And ever since I left,
he has spent
every waking moment
trying to destroy me.
Eikon has a new smartphone coming
that's said to be a game-changer.
They're calling it Occura.
You are going to work for Eikon.
- What?
- Get us in the door, you get 500k.
Get us what we need, you'll see
another million in stock options.
Money like that
would allow you to take care
of your father and a whole lot more.
Eikon's not just going to hire me.
They will when
we're done with you.
This is illegal.
It's stealing trade secrets.
This is the opportunity
you have been waiting for.
Now, you could have done a lot of things
with that credit card last night.
Your father's health insurance premium,
graduate school loans,
but you decided to take your mates
out on the town, living it large.
Because you want to know
how the other half lives.
We are the other half!
That's what I'm offering you.
If I say no?
You and your friends will be prosecuted
to the full extent of the law.
And you don't want to sit around
and watch me make tea, do you?
What are you, the TV police?
- You were asleep.
- My eyes were closed.
Where you going?
- I caught a break at the company.
- A break, what kind of break?
A kind of break that pays our rent
and keeps your pretty nurse around.
It's a training thing,
so I'll be gone all weekend.
It's Friday night. I thought we were
going to Benzio's for pizza and beer.
I got to work, dad. That's how you
climb the ladder in this business.
You work harder than the guy below you.
Otherwise you get stuck
doing the same job your whole life.
Look...
Here's some money.
You can order in, ok?
No, no. Thanks.
All right.
What exactly do you do
for the company, Judith?
I have a PhD
in behavioral psychology.
I can take one look at you and tell you
why you haven't succeeded.
Why don't you tell me
how you really feel?
I can give you the tools to ascend
to the highest ranks
of corporate America.
But you have to lose the attitude.
This way.
I'll show you to your room.
When we meet someone, an immediate
cognitive process takes place.
We construct our first ideas on them
based on their appearance.
So, if you want to be accepted,
you have to look the part.
You have to fit in to get in.
What happened with Wyatt and Goddard?
Jack's a brilliant businessman.
He was always able to imbue his products
with a magic of big ideas,
but Wyatt was the brains.
Without his designs,
none of it would have been possible.
Hmm. Sounds like a perfect pairing.
For Goddard, yes. Wyatt gave him
the best years of his life.
Jock lost his son Dylan
to a drug overdose.
So, if you talk
about losing your mother...
No, I won't.
Then, appeal to his void.
Say you had no father figure.
I have a father.
You don't aspire to be like him.
Which brings us to trust.
If you can convince him
that you're just like him,
that you share the same beliefs as him,
it will engender trust.
And trust is
the holy grail of espionage.
She makes it sound so easy.
But this is a man who recognized me
for who I was years before I did.
He kept me close because that's
what you do with an enemy.
When I got restless, he promised me
partnership. It was genius.
I saw the finish line
and I gave him every good idea I ha...
- Who's this?
- He's the new tailor.
I'm George Gardelo, sir.
Would you excuse us, George?
- Yes. Of course.
- Just for a second.
What's going on?
That's how it happens.
A little guy with a needle and thread
brings down an empire.
You really believe that?
Look, it doesn't matter. If you let
no one in, you get burned by no one.
You know what Picasso said?
"A good artist copies.
A great artist steals."
There's nothing original left
in the world, Adam.
We're all stealing
from someone.
You might want
to remember that.
If I lose one percent market share,
one percent, and I'm ruined.
There is the Dutch deal,
but they're offering half
of what Eikon's willing to pay you.
No, no, I don't care.
I would rather counter
the Dutch for a fraction
than sell to Goddard.
Anything's better than Eikon.
I know.
Hello?
When are you going to find
my friends jobs?
As soon as you get me what I need.
You only have one shot at this.
Mate.
Tom Lungren is
executive hiring coordinator for Eikon.
Your objective here is to connect.
Adam?
- Tom.
- Tom Lungren.
Nice to meet you.
Let me introduce Emma Jennings,
head of our marketing department.
Nice to meet you, Emma.
Please, sit down.
Well, let me start off
by saying that we're
huge fans of the work you did
on Ethion 3.0.
Well, you know,
it hasn't been released yet, so.
Is that because power management
doesn't deliver?
No, the power management is fine.
That's not what we've heard.
We're tweaking
the networking module to make
download speed
the fastest on the market.
Oh, God. I hope that's not why
we agreed to meet with him.
Can you talk specs?
The orion was an LTE advanced
with Max speeds of 44.2 mbps.
Our new platform is
a wave os 7.5...
Which probably won't solve
the biggest issues you had with 7.0.
- It outsold your model two to one.
- Yeah, the marketing was genius.
I spearheaded that campaign.
Then you know
you're good at hiding flaws.
Have you two met?
No.
I think we got off on the wrong foot.
Always do your homework.
That's what you said, isn't it?
Next time
follow your own advice.
- It wasn't tom Lungren?
- It wasn't just tom Lungren.
I told you he might bring
someone else.
Someone that I knew?
What happened?
I saved the day. Connected.
Pulled an offer, a big-ass offer.
Let's take
you to your new apartment.
- What apartment?
- You'll see.
Whoa.
Thought you'd like it.
This is mine?
Of course.
Eikon's newest executive
needs to look the part.
It's nice to see you again, Adam.
Per our agreement, we've deposited
$500,000 into an escrow account.
We're hearing Goddard could
debut aurora in the next two months,
so I've downloaded background files
on all your co-workers.
First, Emma Jennings.
Father, George Jennings, was.
Chief of surgery
at New York Presbyterian.
She grew up with four brothers,
was always on the outside
of the boys club, looking in.
Desperately wants to succeed
in a man's world,
so she's always the most prepared
person in the room.
Would have been useful
a couple of hours ago.
Don't waste your time.
She has certain standards.
Judith, maybe you're not as smart
as you think you are.
Now don't always say
what you think, darling.
Because from here on out,
you are all the way under.
We'll be communicating
through this phone only.
You will respond to my calls,
no matter the time, day or night.
You got it.
Good morning, sir.
I want a copy of his
body scan sent to my office.
Yes, sir.
- Adam.
- Mr. Lungren.
I told you. You gotta stop calling me
that, you're gonna make me feel old.
- Welcome to Eikon.
- Thank you. It's great to be here.
- We're damn glad to have you.
- Ok, good.
The lower floors are legal, hr,
middle floors are all the other
departments, including marketing.
The 38th floor is R&D,
top security projects.
And we're here on the 40th.
There's just a few tricks to being
in this building and getting around.
Your thumbprint on a keycard app
generates a bar code
that gets you anywhere
your clearance is allowed.
All right.
So any words of wisdom
on Goddard?
Be brilliant and be genuine.
He can spot a fraud a mile away.
Here's your office.
So, type x was meant
for social networking,
but it turns out that people don't
always want their friends
to know where they are so precisely.
Right. What's the system tech?
It's 3dps, which is like GPS
plus precise triangulation.
I'm familiar with it.
Problem is, it's twice as heavy
with three times the battery drain.
So, you're handing me a dead fish.
You've got 72 hours
before you present to Goddard.
Thank you.
It's a real-time tracking device
that needs a new purpose.
It's all about the presentation.
You have to impress him.
Yes, I understand what I have to do.
I'll schedule a brainstorming session
with our best R&D guys.
Why do you do this work, Judith?
I mean, is it out of loyalty,
or is it just money?
Don't you have enough
to think about?
Rowena,
I need you to put together
an R&D focus group.
I don't care, wake them up.
Call me when everything's
in place. Bye.
Soldiers.
Soldiers need to know
where each other are at all times.
- They have GPS.
- Yeah.
GPS is great for navigation,
but it doesn't work indoors.
Can't tell if you're
on the first floor or the ninth,
so it's useless in urban warfare.
But with 3dps,
if I can Trojan-horse tracking data
in an e-mail to each of them...
I could make this thing work.
- Who are you calling?
- My own R&D focus group.
Yo, Kev, it's me. I need your help.
I got recruited by one of those...
Headhunters.
Long story short,
I work for Eikon now.
I heard they weren't hiring.
I got lucky, I guess.
I guess.
Well, hey, I've been working
on what we talked about,
and the military thing is
definitely possible.
I just tweaked
the Eikon software a little.
I'm calling it the boomerang.
Just check this out.
I sent your 3dps data e-mail to you,
me and Allison.
So now our phones track each other
working in unison.
And you were right, the SDPS,
that's what makes the difference.
That was a good call, by the way.
Dude, that's awesome.
You crushed this. Good job.
Yeah, but that ain't all.
Pick up Allison.
- What can I get you?
- Another OJ.
One more OJ.
How the hell did you do that?
Who orders orange juice in a bar?
Someone who wants to keep
his edge.
- What's your name?
- Allison.
Do you know that guy?
Hey, OJ!
We're sleeping together, me and her.
Nice to meet you, Allison.
All I do is sit around here,
watching her get hit on all the time.
It's exhausting!
I need a job.
Good morning, Caroline.
Excuse me.
- Jock Goddard.
- Adam Cassidy.
Of course you are. Everything all right?
Settling in ok?
- Yeah. Thank you.
- How's your office?
- Oh, yeah, it's beautiful. Thank you.
- Good. Let's get started.
Ok.
Well, sir, I'm afraid
you've wasted a lot of money
developing type x
as a social networking device.
But the military applications
of this device are undeniable.
I sent you all an e-mail this morning
in which I encoded 3dps-like data
to identify you.
Everyone I sent an e-mail to is
in this room. Except for one.
Death by friendly fire remains
a sad reality of war.
3dps is more precise than GPS
and works on a z-axis.
While the product was deemed
too heavy for civilians,
an added 12 ounces is
nothing to a soldier.
So this is all so you can see
what floor our phones are on?
Yes. 'Cause in the heat of battle
that can be the difference
between killing the enemy or...
Killing your own.
Type x just saved her life.
Good morning.
Good morning, sorry.
Morning.
How long have you had with this?
Seventy-two hours, sir.
Let's put together a team for Adam.
Design, engineering. Let's see
if we can get some DOD funding.
Issues? No? Good.
Good.
Nice work.
I thought that went pretty well.
Beginner's luck.
- You are hard to please.
- Not that you'd remember.
Let me take you
to dinner this weekend.
I have to be
in the Hamptons this weekend.
Oh, good. I'll come with you.
It wasn't an invitation.
Ok.
Hi, Adam. I'm calling
from jock Goddard's office.
Jock is having a few people over
to his house in the Hamptons
on Saturday
and he'd like you to join him.
So now we go
for military funding.
Dude, that's great.
Congratulations, man.
Hey, so, I got a favor to ask.
I got an interview at Eikon next week.
And I know I'm gonna be
another resume in a stack
if I don't build some traction.
Right.
So, I feel awkward
even asking you this, but...
Hey, of course.
All right,
I'll speak to HR on Monday.
All right.
Thanks.
Nicest guy.
Right through the red light
and hit the back of the car.
- Very apologetic.
- Somebody looks lost.
Oh, hey!
- Hi.
- Hey.
- There he is.
- I'm glad you could make it.
- Thanks for having me, Mr. Goddard.
- Jock.
- You know tom, of course.
- Hey.
Jock tells me my stock's gone up
in value since your type x pitch.
First time up at bat and you bang it
off the scoreboard? Way to go.
And this is Emma.
She's spearheading the marketing
on our new smartphone, Occura.
Nice suit.
Watch our for her. She's one
of those Ivy Leaguers. Princeton.
Yale, actually.
Where her brothers went.
How did you know
I went to Yale?
It was on Facebook
or something.
Ah.
So much for privacy.
Privacy.
Absolute myth, no such thing.
- Tom, you want a drink?
- Yeah, absolutely.
A glass of wine, sir?
- White wine.
- Mineral water, cold.
See you later.
Kind of like a Bordeaux,
more dry.
If you're looking
for the bathroom, you missed it.
Yeah, sorry, I, uh...
I saw the radio. Does it work?
Yeah, they work.
They all work. I built them.
That's how I spent
my teens. Ham radio.
Where'd you grow up?
Town of Hamilton, 3500 people.
Where is that?
It doesn't matter.
You remind me of Wyatt.
I'm surprised he let you go.
He wasn't too happy about it.
I knew he'd be
my competition someday.
I knew it before he did.
Why'd you take him
under your wing?
It's not about him.
It's about putting products out there
to make people's lives better.
Competition fuels innovation.
Without it,
Eikon wouldn't be where it is today.
And where is that?
On the Eve of a revolution.
Is that your son?
Yeah, that's Dylan.
You have a bit of success,
you begin to think
that you've got some control
over things, but...
Shit happens to everybody.
Yeah.
I lost my mother when I was seven.
Do you remember her?
Not much.
I feel like I lose her
a little more every day.
Yeah.
Couple nights after dilly died,
I woke up in the middle of the night
in a panic.
Rummaged through the whole house,
his whole room...
Looking for anything.
Kid's drawings, schoolwork...
Old pair of tennis shoes.
Anything that would keep him alive.
The front hall, under the stairs.
Sir?
The bathroom.
Thanks.
You know,
the suit's not all that bad.
You don't have to hide way out here.
I was, uh, playing hard to get.
But you're already gotten.
So tell me,
how is it that you know
so much about me
and I know nothing about you?
It's this, uh, little row home
my grandmother owned.
Five of us sharing one bathroom.
My dad was a security guard.
Now he has emphysema,
but still smokes.
And I'm pretty sure he's putting it
to the nurse I'm paying for.
When I think of losing him...
Aah...
What about you?
I come from a family where...
The expectation is so high
that I can't really ever succeed.
It's fine,
it's just that I keep trying.
So...
I'm trying to sleep
my way to the top.
Are we covered?
Come on. Take me home?
Yeah.
Dad?
You got a visitor.
Who are you?
You might want to remove the battery
from your cellular device.
What?
You think 'cause you're not on a call,
they can't hear you?
Agent gamble.
I'm with the FBI's
criminal investigation division.
We've been looking at the Wyatt corp
for about five years now.
- I don't work for Wyatt.
- John Moore did.
He was in Wyatt's training program
in '09.
Stella Ross, migrated
from Wyatt to Eikon like you.
Two months later,
her steering column exploded.
And Richard McAllister...
Whose Ethion work you drafted off of.
I didn't draft off his work.
A month ago,
you were circling the drain at Wyatt.
Now you're some hotshot exec
over at Eikon? Don't bullshit me.
Ok, I think it's time for you to go.
You think Wyatt's gonna fill
your pockets and let you walk?
I don't know what
you're talking about, ok?
Come on, Adam.
How long do you think
you can keep this up?
All it takes is one mistake,
one slip up.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
Just don't wait till it's too late.
You wanna tell me
what's going on?
You wouldn't understand.
Yeah, I was probably too busy
putting three meals
in front of you every day
and giving you all the love
that parents had.
Come on, Adam.
We had a perfect life.
You know, if your insurance covered
even half of what morn needed...
Don't try to revise death.
What did you want me to do?
I wanted you to fight.
I wanted us to have enough
to at least give her a chance.
You gotta give that up.
These companies steal so much,
there's nothing left to earn.
Yeah, what you're doing
doesn't make it right.
No.
No one can make it right.
So, why shouldn't
I get my share? Huh?
The FBI just walked out of our house.
I don't want to end up like you.
So that's what he's up to.
That's what you wanted.
I'm done now. This isn't who I am.
This is exactly who you are.
Did you frisk him?
You hiding something?
Knock it off!
You've been a little temperamental
lately, haven't you?
Are you falling for that girl?
- He's falling for jock.
- All right, all right!
What'd he talk about?
He talked about progress,
enriching people's lives.
Yeah, he talk about his son?
Yeah. A little.
It seem rehearsed?
No.
It did the first time he told it.
That was when the world fell in love
with jock Goddard,
the grieving father.
That story of his little dead boy
saved Eikon.
I got what you asked for, ok?
We had a deal.
I just want my money.
Oh, he wants his money.
We'll keep your money for you.
You'll be doing five to ten upstate.
I got the specs. That was the deal.
Pictures are no good to me.
I need to know what it does, I need
to hold it in my hand and see it run!
Do you understand me?
Put it in my fucking hand!
Or what? I end up like Richard?
Jock builds one prototype.
It's assembled in the vault,
piece by piece, until beta trials.
It stays in the vault
on the 38th floor.
Without files, without source code,
you can't do...
No, I don't need his files.
I just need to see his vision.
No, I'm not doing this anymore. I'm out.
You're out?
You are only out, my son,
when I say you're out!
I own you right now.
You see? I can get to anyone.
Don't make this harder
than it has to be.
It's just business, Adam.
Everybody steals, everybody lies.
There's no right or wrong.
There's just winning or losing.
Now the first order of business
is lifting Emma's fingerprints.
So my parents
are having this thing
for my brother's engagement
this weekend.
You wanna go with me?
To meet your parents?
It's just dinner and drinks.
You, uh...
You sure I'm relationship material?
You know what? It's...
It's actually gonna be really boring.
- Probably better if you don't.
- Hey.
Of course I will.
Even if it is boring?
Yeah, even if it's boring.
Hey, what happened to you?
Kev! What are you doing here?
What do you think
I'm doing here?
Your interview. Right.
Uh...
- How'd it go? I spoke to hr.
- No, you didn't.
I'm sorry, man. I, uh...
I've been under a ton of pressure.
I completely forgot...
Yeah, I understand, man. Your new
apartment, new car, new girlfriend.
You have no idea
what I'm dealing with.
No, I don't.
And I don't think I ever will.
- Thanks.
- Come on, Kev. I'm sorry, man.
Kev!
Mr. Goddard wants to see you.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I understand that.
Wyatt has to consider our offer.
He has no choice.
I mean, he's tap dancing
on the Titanic.
Come on in.
Look, somebody just walked in.
I've got something
I've got to deal with.
All right. Thanks.
Don't forget, you have
a lunch reservation at the club.
Come on. Let's take a drive.
I'll buy you lunch.
Got some interesting news
this morning concerning you.
Thought I'd make sure it was true
before I talk to you about it.
- Is everything all right?
- You tell me.
The DOD has given us
preliminary funding for type x.
- We'll leave it here, Mr. Goddard.
- Thanks, bud.
- Well, what do you think?
- It's powerful.
Yeah, it is.
Consider it a loaner
for saving type x.
- Jock, I couldn't.
- Yeah, you could.
Power is the juice,
get used to drinking it.
I heard you talking
about Occura.
There's a lot of buzz about it.
Yeah, Occura's been,
uh, gestating
for... quite a few years.
We only recently were able to put
all of the elements together
to make it happen.
- I'll have coffee.
- I'll have a water.
Very good.
Imagine walking around
with nothing but your cell phone.
No wallet, no keys.
Like a digital wallet.
It'll be your driver's license,
it'll be your credit card,
it'll be more than that.
Super slim. Foldable, with a battery
that recharges itself
from any ambient electrical source.
It'll know where you've been,
who you've been with.
It'll track your priorities,
expenditures,
your health, calendar.
It will know who you are.
And it's all ours.
You think people really want
all that personal information
under one roof?
It's not the roof that matters, Adam.
It's the warm fuzzy feeling
of the home under it.
People are so distracted these days,
they don't know who they are.
But we will.
We'll know them better
than they know themselves.
Oh, my goodness.
Jock.
Nick.
How long has it been?
Not long enough.
You look like
you're holding up all right.
Oh, I'm doing fine.
What brings you here?
Lunch. Lunch brings me here.
- You remember Judith.
- Oh, of course.
- How are you, Judith?
- Good.
You remember Adam Cassidy.
He designed your Ethion.
Yes, he did.
Hello, again, Adam.
He reminds me of you.
Way back when,
before you walked out on us.
Let's not muddle the facts.
You asked me to walk
and locked the door behind me.
Besides, I was smarter than Adam here.
And I didn't spend all my time
kissing your ass.
How is Ethion? We've heard
remarkably little about it.
Mm. Ethion's fine.
How's Occura?
Right on schedule.
And it's something you're
never going to be able to duplicate.
Is that so?
Remember when we used
to share ideas, Nick?
I try not to.
When we put our heads together,
there was no problem we couldn't solve.
Nothing we couldn't make.
There was no problem I couldn't solve.
Nothing I couldn't make.
I miss your friendship.
Why don't we sit down together sometime.
Always so full of shit.
You sit here like...
Like some big shot
with boy wonder here,
blowing smoke up your ass
like it's still relevant.
The truth is, I'm gonna bury you,
and your boy here
is gonna be working for me again.
Because working for you,
means he'll be working for me.
Don't let your lunch get cold, Nick.
Nice seeing you, Judith.
He's running
search after search on Goddard.
What is he looking for?
I don't know.
I think this
boy's gone soft on us.
Were you going to ignore my call?
You should have told me
Wyatt was gonna be there.
Why do you keep pacing so much?
You look nervous.
You have something you want to tell me?
Where are you?
Now let me explain to you
how this is going to work.
We hit one of your friends first.
Or maybe the girl.
If you even touch her...
Then get us what we need.
You have two days
to break into Eikon.
This is your last warning.
Help! Help me! Somebody help me!
He said I had two days.
That was the night before last.
These people are everywhere.
Put cameras in your house.
I'm sorry. I just...
I messed up, dad.
I thought I knew what I was doing.
You have to figure a way out.
Adam.
- Adam!
- This is serious, ok?
You got to figure a way out.
It's not that easy.
Ok? I put a lot of people
I care about in danger.
Adam, I think
the FBI is the only option.
I could go to jail.
Or they could kill you.
There was a black car and it
just came out of nowhere and it hit him.
Slow down. Is he all right?
Where are you?
I've been trying to reach you all day.
Kev's at the hospital, but he's ok.
I think they're discharging us now.
Ok, were there witnesses?
Did anyone get the plates?
I don't think so. I don't know, it just
all happened so fast. I got to go.
- Ok, call me back.
- I will.
Hey!
Hey! What's the matter with you?!
Go, go, go, 90!
On your knees.
- I'll do it, I'll do it!
- Get on your knees!
You're going in tonight, and you'll need
Emma's phone to do it.
Get moving.
Can I come in?
I haven't been honest with you.
What do you mean?
There's things I want to tell you
that I haven't told you.
What is it?
Mr. Cassidy.
- Yeah?
- Working late tonight?
Burning that midnight oil.
Adam?
I've lost floors one through five.
We've got security lights
in sector two.
Hold your position.
Get our it guy on the line.
Before we move on to sector three,
let's check that server.
I want the list
of everyone in the building.
Control...
- I'm only showing one exec present.
- Who is it?
Adam Cassidy.
Oh, come on.
Hi, it's Emma. Leave a message.
Marty, go check on Adam Cassidy.
Roger, I'm en route. Come on!
Adam Cassidy is not in his office.
Shit.
All hands on, get this guy!
Use any means necessary.
Clear.
Mr. Cassidy!
We've got somebody at the vault.
What the hell?
Jock.
Mr. Cassidy.
Got caught with your hand
in the cookie jar, didn't you?
I... jock, I can explain this.
Where you gonna start?
I was beginning to think
it would never happen.
Wyatt would rather watch
his company crumble than sell it to me.
Then you came along
with your blind ambition.
We recorded it all, every conversation,
every text between you and Wyatt.
You tell Nick he'll be selling me
majority shares in his company
or evidence of your collusion goes
to the FBI.
You manipulated me.
Yes.
You'll be at the Sutton club tomorrow
at noon. You, Nick, and me.
Nobody else.
No lawyers, no handlers. Nobody.
Let him out!
Big mistake.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
You can't be here.
You used me.
I'm sorry. Ok? I'm so sorry.
You got to go,
you're not safe here.
Everything you...
Everything you said,
every... everything you did...
Was a lie.
No, that's not true.
Not everything.
I wanted to be someone else.
Now you are.
You know...
I fell for you because
you weren't like everyone else.
Emma, I'm gonna make this right.
You don't know what that is.
Well, you sure messed that up.
Hey, look, I'm trying, ok?
Yeah, well, now you're done trying.
Let's go for a ride.
Look, you don't get it, ok?
It was all a setup!
- Get in the car!
- It was all a setup!
I'm sorry, man.
What are you sorry for?
You didn't run me over, did you?
I'm the reason for all of this.
The real question is...
What are we gonna do about it?
I'm going to use what they taught me...
To destroy what they built.
So, what's the news
on the Dutch deal?
- I don't know.
- Good, we won't need them anyway.
Don't remember inviting you.
My going-away party got
this whole thing rolling.
I thought it was only fair
that I show up for yours.
What are you talking about?
Goddard orchestrated this whole thing...
To entrap you
into committing a crime.
I didn't commit a crime.
You did.
This is the death of your empire, Nick.
And you were funded
with money I never touched,
by corporations I had never heard of.
He has nothing.
He has everything.
E-mails, texts.
He got the break-in on camera.
All the dots connect back to you.
The whole thing was a setup.
What's going on?
- We had good intel on this!
- Where did you get that intel, Nick?
This is absurd.
You can't just...
Hamilton.
Jack's hometown.
Nick...
Meachum.
That's one down.
One more to go.
Whatever you have better be good.
If it works, we both walk away
with an insurance policy
no amount of money can buy.
Yeah, but if it doesn't?
Get out your phones. Sit down.
Put the batteries on the table.
It says you've got another phone.
- Oh, no, no.
- What happened?
I lost the signal.
Both phones, they're gone.
Can you get it back?
- You'll pay for this.
- Yeah, I'll pay.
I'm buying every goddamn share
of Wyatt corporation's stock you own,
and I'm paying
40 cents on the dollar.
How does that sound?
I get it or the feds do.
- You'll never get away with this.
- Shut up, Adam.
You're nothing but a convenient tool,
an empty vessel.
I filled you with piss and vinegar
and told you it was champagne
and you lapped it up.
- I'm not signing this.
- Then you'll go to jail.
With what? What have you got?!
Ah...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What?
- Sign it!
- You have taken credit for everything.
And you've created nothing!
You arrogant bastard!
I took a brick device
that everybody laughed at
and turned it into the one thing
that no one can do without.
I earned my arrogance!
Yes, and none of that happens
without me! You stood on my shoulders!
And now I'm standing on your neck!
I'm 15 moves ahead of you, Nick.
The Dutch offer, me!
I strung you along
until the only hope was... Adam.
That's impossible.
Impossible?
I built Wyatt corp.
Sell or not, your company is finished.
You've got nothing in the pipe,
and even if you did,
you've got no money to market it with.
Forty cents on the dollar is
a lot better than jail.
You make the choice.
Now get out.
He likes to eat his young.
They're mine to eat.
It's time to go back
to your sad little life.
Why go to all the trouble?
Because I wanted to see him bleed. Go.
No. There's more to it,
you wouldn't risk it all just for that.
I told you, Adam,
competition breeds innovation.
With his name on the door,
he developed his ass off.
You needed him.
You needed his mind
because he was smarter than you.
He made a great processor
and a shitty phone
and he served a purpose,
just like you did. Go.
You're nothing without him.
Occura is real.
It'll do everything I said it would.
I just needed his processor to run it.
- Who is this?
- Mr. Goddard?
Who is this?
You should really trash your e-mails
when you're done reading them.
I sent you all an e-mail
this morning
in which I encoded 3dps-like data
to identify you.
Someone is always listening, jock.
Always.
Mr. Goddard.
Mr. Goddard, you're under arrest.
I'm gonna make your life a living hell.
Please stand,
place your hands behind your back.
Yes! We got him.
You did the right thing, kid.
The charges against you
include felony fraud,
industrial espionage,
obstruction of justice, insider trading.
Augustine Goddard,
you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
the court will appoint one for you.
Do you understand these rights
as I have read them to you?
I handed the feds Wyatt and Goddard.
They won't be seeing light
for a very long time.
Judith and Meachum got
what they deserved too.
As for me, I got lucky.
The feds out me a break
for my cooperation.
No...
The things I thought I wanted
don't seem so important anymore.
I do know right from wrong, and...
I'm sorry it took me
so long to act on it.
I just want you to know that.
I never wanted to do any of this to you.
I hope one day I can make things right.
I'm sorry, Emma.
Thanks.
Go, go, go, go! Go! Go! Go!
Run, run!
What?
Did I ever tell you, you were right?
About what?
Everything.
I mean that.
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you.
How's it going with that girl?
Well, she won't talk to me.
It ain't over till it's over.
You know how long it took me
to get a date with your mother?
How long?
A long time.
And I was much better-looking then
than you are now.
- Oh, is that right?
- Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Where you going?
The subway is this way.
I got a faster ride. Come on.
I thought we were done
with this shit?
It's a rental, dad.
I got it for the day.
Oh, yeah?
Well, then, let's have some fun.
One way to remember who you are...
How do you open this thing?
Is to remember who your heroes are.
I'm doing things my way now.
Building from the ground up.
There are no shortcuts.
Oh my God, what are you doing?
- What? I messed it up.
- We have a lot of things to do.
- Come on!
- All right, Jesus!
Hi. Emma Jennings.
One second.
Adam, you have a visitor.
He'! -
hi.
Nice place you have here.
I mean, for Brooklyn.
I'm glad you came.
Kept getting e-mails about a job offer
at a brand-new startup company.
Why I didn't see that coming...
Yeah, we, uh...
We really need you here.
You couldn't afford me.
Lots of stock options.
You have to do better than that.
Ok.
I need you here.
I'll think about it.
Come on,
let me buy you a drink.
You said you had a thing
for bridge-and-tunnel.
Your words. Emma.
Can I at least thank you
for considering my offer?
Thank you.
I like being across the bridge.
Over here, it feels like home.
SubLand.info