You don't understand.
Krypton's core is collapsing.
We may only
have a matter of weeks.
I warned you,
harvesting the core was suicide.
It has accelerated
the process of implosion.
Our energy reserves were exhausted,
what would you have us do, El?
Look to the stars.
Like our ancestors did.
There are habitable worlds
within reach.
We can begin
by using the old outposts.
Are seriously suggesting that
we evacuate the entire planet?
No, everybody here
is already dead.
Give me the control of the codex,
I will ensure the survival of our race.
There is still hope,
I have held that hope in my hand.
- This council has been disbanded.
- On whose authority?
Mine.
The rest of you will be tried
and punished accordingly.
What are you doing, Zod?!
This is madness!
What I should done years ago! These
lawmakers with their endless debates
have led Krypton to ruin!
And if your forces prevail?
You be the leader of nothing.
Then join me, help me
save our race, we'll start anew.
We'll sever the degenerated
bloodlines that led us to this state.
And who will decide
which bloodline survives, Zod?
You?
Don't do this, El. The last thing
I want is for us to be enemies.
You have abandoned the principles
that bound us together,
You've taken up the sword
against your own people.
I'll honor the man you once were, Zod.
Not this monster you've become.
Take him away!
Sir, is everything all right?
- Out of the way! I said..
Get me to Lara.
Jor! Behind you!
Lara, you have to ready the launch,
I will be with you as soon as I can.
- Have you seen the codex?
- It's just beneath the central house.
But I'm compelled to warn you, reaching
the chambers is class B crime punishable
Nobody cares any more, Keelex!
The world is about to come to an end.
Jor-el, by the authority
of General Zod, surrender the codex.
Easy, Harraka.
Did you find the world?
We have.
Orbiting main sequence yellow star
just as you said.
Young star.
His cells would drink its radiation.
It has a seemingly
intelligent population.
He will be an outcast, a freak.
They'll kill him.
- How?
He'll be a god to them.
What if the ship doesn't make it?
He will die out there.
Alone.
I can't do it.
I thought I could, but...
now that it's here...
Krypton is doomed.
It's his only chance now.
It's our people's only hope.
What is it, Keelex?
Five attack ships
converging from the east.
Citadel’s defenses
are being scanned and evaluated.
I'll upload the codex.
- No, wait.
Lara...
Just... let me look at him.
I'll never get to see him walk.
Never hear him say our names.
Out there amongst the stars...
he will live.
Goodbye, my son.
I hope some dreams
travel with you.
Concentrate fire on the main door.
Lady Lara, the phantom drives
are coming on-line
Proceed to ignition.
We have identified an engine ignition
within the citadel.
A launch...
Hold this platform, Commander.
I know you stole the codex, Jor-el.
Surrender it and I'll let you live.
This is a second change
for all of Krypton,
not just the bloodlines
you deem worthy.
- What have you done?
- We've had a child, Zod.
A boy child.
Krypton's first natural
birth in centuries.
And he will be free.
Free to forge his own destiny.
Heresy!
Destroy it!
Lara, listen to me!
The Codex is Krypton's future.
Abort the launch!
Your son, Lara...
Where have you sent him?
His name is Kal.
Son of El.
And he is beyond your reach.
Bring that ship down.
Target locked.
Lay down your weapons,
your forces are surrounded.
General Zod, for the crimes
of murder and high treason,
the Council has sentenced you
and your fellow insurgents
to 300 hundred cycles
of somatic reconditioning.
Do you have any last words?
You won't kill us yourself!
You wouldn't sully your hands,
but you'll damn us
to a black hole for eternity.
Jor-El, was right
you are a pack of fools,
every last one of you!
And you...
You believe your son is safe?
I will find him.
I will reclaim what
you have taken from us.
I will find him.
I will find him, Lara.
I will find him!
Lady Lara,
shouldn't you find refuge?
There is no refuge, Kelor.
Jor-El was right,
this is the end.
Make a better world than ours, Kal.
Watch it, dumbass! Keep your eyes open
or you are gonna get squashed!
Where the hell
did they find you, greenhorn?
Gentlemen, secure the deck!
We just got a distress call
from a rig due west of us.
Secure the deck!
All civilian folk, stand clear,
the sub-sea valve's failed
and the rig is about to explode.
Roger, coast guard. What about
the men left inside, over.
- Forget them, they are dead!
- Greenhorn, fetch me my binoculars.
Greenhorn!
This is the last of the oxygen!
I don't know how much longer
we can hold out!
This is coast guard 65-10.
We're gonna make one more pass
and then we're getting out of here.
Wait, wait,
I've got some guys on the heli-pad!
Get that last guy rolling,
we have got to go!
Hey, let’s go!
What are you doing!
When Kansas became a territory...
Clark!
Are you listening, Clark?
I asked if you could tell me
who were the first settlers of Kansas?
Are you alright, Clark?
Clark!
- Clark, come out of there!
- Leave me alone.
Clark, I have called your mother.
I'm here!
Clark, honey, what's wrong?
Will you open the door?
- What's wrong with him, anyway?
- He's such a weirdo!
- Crybaby!
His parents won't even
let him play with other kids.
I know.
Sweetie! How can I help you
if you won't let me in?
The world is too big, mom.
Then make it smaller.
Just...
Focus on my voice.
Pretend it's an island.
Out in the ocean.
Can you see it?
I see it.
Then swim towards it, honey.
What's wrong with me, mom?
Clark...
Hey, asswipe! What do you think,
did you see the game?
Leave him alone, Pete.
- What are you, his girlfriend?
I want hear what he has to say.
Come on, dick splash.
My son was there, he was in the bus.
He saw what Clark did.
I know he did. I'm sure
that what he thought he saw...
Was an act of God, Jonathan!
This was providence!
Well, I think you're blowing it
a little out of proportion.
No, I'm not.
Lana saw it too and the Forny boy.
And this isn't the first time
Clark's done something like this.
- I just wanted to help.
- I know you did, but we talked about this,
Right?
Right, we talked about this,
you have...
Clark, you have keep
this side of yourself a secret.
What was I supposed to do,
just let them die?
Maybe.
There's more at stake here than just our
lives and the lives of those around us.
When the world...
When the world finds out what you can do
it's going to change everything.
Our believes, our notions.
What it means to be human, everything.
You saw how Pete's mom reacted, right?
She was scared of you, Clark.
Why?
People are afraid
of what they don't understand.
Is she right?
Did God give this to me?
Tell me.
We found you in this.
We were sure that the government
was gonna show up on our doorstep.
No one ever came.
This was in the chamber with you.
I took it
to a metallurgist at Kansas State.
He said whatever it was made from
didn't even...
It didn't even exist
on the periodic table.
It's another way of saying
that it's not from this world, Clark.
And neither are you.
You are the answer, son.
You are the answer to
are we alone in the Universe.
I don't wanna be.
And I don't blame you son.
Be huge burden for anyone to bear,
but you are not just anyone, Clark.
And I have to believe
that you were,
that you were send here for an reason.
All these changes that
you're going through, one day,
one day you're gonna think of them
as a blessing.
When that day comes,
you'll have to make a choice,
choice of whether to stand proud
in front of the human race or not..
Can't I just
keep pretending I'm your son?
You are my son.
But somewhere out there,
you have another father too.
Who gave you another name.
And he send you here
for a reason, Clark.
And even if it takes you
the rest of your life,
you owe it to yourself
to find out what that reason is.
They did find something strange in...
I know, it's crazy, right?
The Americans are there too.
Lots of them.
They are calling it anomalous object,
whatever that means.
Back off rebel, I'm serious.
Oh come on, Chrissy.
- Knock it off!
- Sit down.
- Let me go!
- Hey, leave her alone, man.
Or what, tough guy?
Or... I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
I think I'll probably just leave
when I'm good and ready.
O, there he is.
It's not worth it, sweetie.
Hey, asshole, don't forget your tip.
Thanks,
Hi.
Miss Lane, how are you doing?
- Jed Eubanks, Arctic cargo.
- How far to the station?
Camp is just over the rise,
I'll walk you over. - Great.
- Help her out.
- Careful with those, they are heavy.
I got to confess, Miss Lane,
I'm not a fan of The Daily Planet.
But those you pieces you wrote...
Well, they were pretty impressive.
Well, what can I say, I get writer's
block if I'm not wearing a flat jacket.
Miss Lane!
Hardy, US Northcom, dr. Emil Hamilton.
You are early, we were
expecting you tomorrow.
Which I why showed up today.
Look, let’s get one thing straight,
guys, okay?
The only reason I'm here
is because we are on Canadian soil,
and the appellate court overruled
your injunction to keep me away.
So, if we are done
measuring dicks,
can you have your people
show me what you found?
NASA's EOS satellites
pinged the anomaly first,
the ice shelf's plates
held the echo soundings.
But, there is definitely
something down there.
- A submarine, maybe Soviet era?
- Doubtful, that's 300 meters,
considerably larger than
anything they build back then.
But here is the spooky part.
The ice surrounding the object,
it’s nearly 20,000 years old...
Miss Lane, you are not to wander.
Temperatures drops to
- 40 at night around here.
We couldn't find your
body until after spring.
There you go.
- What if I need to tinkle?
- There's a bucket in the corner.
Where the hell are you going?
It's all right, it's all right..
You are hemorrhaging internally
and if I don't cauterize this bleed...
I can do things
that other people can’t.
Now hold my hand.
This is gonna hurt.
What Colonel Hardy and his team
surmised was a Soviet era submarine,
was actually something much more exotic.
An isotope analysis
of the surrounding ice bores,
suggests that an object
had been trapped in the glacier
for over 18,000 years.
As for my rescuer, he disappeared
during the object’s departure,
A background check revealed that his work
history and identity had been falsified.
The questions raised by my rescuer's
existence are frightening to contemplate,
but I also know what I saw.
And they've arrived
at the inescapable conclusion
that the object
and its occupant,
did not originate on Earth..
I can’t print this Lois, you might have
hallucinated half of it.
What about the civilian contractors
who corroborated my story?
The Pentagon is denying that
there was a ship.
Of course they are, that's what they
are supposed to do, it’s the Pentagon.
Harry come on, it’s me we are talking
about, I'm a Pulitzer winning reporter.
- Then act like it.
- Print it or I walk.
You can’t, you are under contract.
I'm not running a story about
aliens walking among us...
Never going to happen.
That's a Scotch
straight up for the lady.
I'm sending you the original article,
my editor won't print it
but, if it happened to leak online...
But, didn't you once
describe my site as a...
- "creeping cancer of falsehoods"?
- I stand by my words, Woodburn.
- But I want this story out there.
- Why?
Because I want my mystery man
to know I know the truth.
Recursive diagnostics complete.
Guiding process authenticated.
All systems operational.
To see you standing there,
having grown into an adult.
- If only Lara could witness this.
- Who are you?
I'm your father, Kal.
Or at least a shadow of him,
his consciousness.
My name is Jor-El.
And Kal?
It’s my name.
Kal-El, it is.
I have so many questions.
Where do I come from?
Why did you send me here?
You came from Krypton.
A world with a much harsher
environment than Earth's.
Long ago, in an era of expansion...
...our race spread out
through the stars,
seeking new worlds to settle upon.
This scout ship was one of thousands
launched into the void.
We build outposts on other planets,
using great machines to reshape
environments to our needs.
For 100,000 years,
our civilization flourished,
- accomplishing wonders.
- What happened?
Artificial population control
was established.
The outposts on space exploration
were abandoned,
we exhausted our natural
resources, as a result...
our planet's core became unstable.
Eventually our military
leader, General Zod,
attempted a coup,
but by then it was too late.
Your mother and I
foresaw the coming calamity,
and we took certain steps
to ensure your survival.
This is a genesis chamber.
All Kryptonians were conceived
in chambers such as this,
every child was designed to fulfill
a predetermined role in our society,
as a worker, a warrior,
a leader, and so on.
Your mother and I believed that
Krypton had lost something precious,
the element of choice, of chance.
What if a child dreamed
of becoming something other
than what society
had intended for him or her?
What if a child aspired
to something greater?
You were the embodiment
of that belief, Kal.
Krypton's first natural birth
in centuries.
That's why we risked
so much to save you.
Why didn't you come with me?
We couldn't, Kal.
No matter how much we wanted to,
no matter how much we loved you...
Your mother Lara and I
were a product of the failures
of our world as much Zod was,
tied to its fate.
- So, I'm alone.
- No.
You are much as a child of Earth now
as you are of Krypton.
You can embody
the best of both worlds.
A dream your mother and I
dedicated our lives to preserve.
The people of Earth are different
from us, it’s true.
But ultimately I believe
that is a good thing.
They won't necessarily make
the same mistakes we did.
Not if you guide them, Kal.
Not if you give them hope.
That is what this symbol means.
The symbol of the House of El
means "hope".
Embodied within the hope
is the fundamental belief,
the potential of every person
to be a force for good.
That's what you can bring them.
Why am I so different from them?
Earth's sun is younger and
brighter than Krypton’s was.
Your cells
have drunk in its radiation,
strengthening your muscles,
your skin, your senses.
Earth's gravity is weaker,
yet its atmosphere is more nourishing,
You've grown stronger here
than I ever could've imagined.
The only way to know how strong,
is to keep testing your limits.
You will give the people of Earth
an ideal to strive towards.
They will race behind you,
they will stumble, they will fall.
But in time...
they will join you
when the sun comes.
In time, you will help them
accomplish wonders.
How do you find someone who has
spent a lifetime covering his tracks?
You start with the urban legends
that have sprung up in his wake.
All of the friends of a friend
who claim to have seen him.
For some, he was a guardian angel.
For others a cypher,
a ghost who never quite fit in.
As you work your way back in time,
the stories begin to form a pattern.
I'm looking for a Pete Ross,
do you know him?
Yes, he works at the I-Hop.
You go down the road...
Pete Ross?
I'd like to talk to you about an accident
that occurred when you were younger,
a school bus
that went into the river?
Rusty!
Mrs. Kent, I'm Lois Lane
from The Daily Planet.
Quiet!
I'm from The Daily Planet and I'd like
to talk to you about your son.
Where are you from, what are you
doing here, let me tell your story.
- What if I don't want my story told?
- It’s going to come out eventually.
Somebody’s going to get a photograph
or figure out where you live.
Then I’ll just disappear again.
The only way you can disappear for good
is to stop helping people altogether,
and I sense
that's not option for you.
My father believed...
...that if the world found out
who I really was...
they'd reject me, out of fear.
I'm tired of safe!
I just want do something
useful with my life.
So farming, feeding people,
that's not useful?
I didn't say that.
Our family has been farming
for 5 generations, Clark.
Your family. Not mine.
I don't know even why I'm listening
to you, you are not my dad,
you are just some guy who
found me in the field.
Clark!
That's all right, Martha.
He is right, Clark has a point.
We are not your parents.
But we've been doing
the best we can,
and we've been
making it up as we go along,
so maybe... maybe our best
isn't good enough anymore.
Look...
- Dad, please...
- Hold on.
Go for the overpass.
Go for the overpass!
Take cover! Take cover!
Over there, just follow them!
She's stuck!
You guys follow me.
The dog's in the car!
I get him!
Get your mom to the overpass.
- Jonathan!
- It's okay!
- Ma, stay here.
Dad!
I let my father die,
because I trusted him.
Because he was convinced
that I had to wait.
That the world was not ready.
What do you think?
You better watch out Lois.
Hey, Perry's gunning for you.
He knows you are Woodburn’s
anonymous source and he cannot wait...
...to rip you a new one.
I told you not to run with this,
and what do you do?
You let Woodburn just shotgun it
all over the internet!
Now, the publishers want me
to sue you!
Well, if it makes a difference,
I'm dropping it.
- Whoa, just like that?
- Yeah.
- What happened to your leads?
- They didn't pan out.
The story was smoke.
Or perhaps it just didn't get
the attraction you hoped it would.
2 weeks leave, no pay -
that's your pennance.
You try something like
this again - you're done here.
No, let’s make it 3 weeks, since you
are so willing to agree with me.
No, no, don't.
I believe you saw something Lois,
but not for a moment do I believe
that your leads just went cold,
so whatever your reasons
are for dropping it...
I think you're doing
the right thing.
Why?
Can you imagine how people
on this planet would react...
If...
they knew that there was
someone like this out there?
Go get him!
Well, look at you!
A reporter came by here.
She is a friend, don't worry.
Mom.
What?
- I found them.
- Whom?
My parents.
My people.
I know where I come from now.
Wow...
That's wonderful.
I'm so happy for you.
- What?
- Its nothing.
When you were a baby,
I use to lay by your cradle.
Listen to your breath.
It was hard for you.
You struggled.
And I worried all the time.
You worried that the truth
would come out.
No, the truth about you...
...is beautiful.
We saw that, the moment
we laid eyes on you.
We knew that one day,
the whole world would see that.
I'm just…
I'm worried
they’ll take you away from me.
I'm not going anywhere, mom.
I promise.
- General Swanwick, sir.
- What am I looking at, doc?
Comet? Asteroid?
Comets don't make
course corrections, General.
I wanted you see this before
some amateur with a telescope
creates a worldwide panic.
The ship appears to have inserted
itself into a lunar synchronous orbit.
Though I have no idea why.
Have you tried...
communicating with it?
Well, they haven't
responded as of yet.
I'm just speculating,
but I think whoever is
at the helm of that thing
is looking to make
a dramatic entrance.
Does anybody know where
we keep the toner cartridges?
- What's going on?
- It’s all over the news.
You got to see this.
Clark!
Yeah, coming.
You are not alone.
Yo.. Ar.. No.. Alo...
- It’s coming in on the RSS feeds.
- You are not alone
It’s on my phone, too.
My name is General Zod.
I come from a world far from yours.
I have journeyed across an ocean
of stars to reach you.
For some time your world
has sheltered one of my citizens.
I request that you return
this individual...
...to my custody.
For reasons unknown,
he has chosen to keep his
existence a secret from you.
He will have made efforts
to blend in.
He will look like you.
But he is not one of you.
To those of you who may know
of his current location:
The fate of your planet
rests in your hands.
To Kal-El, I say this:
Surrender within 24 hours,
or watch this world
suffer the consequences.
If he truly means us no harm,
then he'll turn himself in
to his people,
and face the consequences
and if he won’t do that,
then maybe we should.
The Daily Planet's Lois Lane
knows who this guys is.
And I think she’s the one
we should be questioning.
Hold-on, you are saying
Lois Lane knows...
Are you watching this crap?
Been running all morning.
For once I actually I agree with
Woodburn. Now, have you seen him?
No, and even I did, I wouldn't say.
The entire world
is being threatened here!
This not the time for you to fall back
on your journalistic integrity!
This is serious, Lois! The FBI is here
hurling around words like treason.
I got to go.
FBI, hands up!
Drop the bag, now!
Regarding the visitors themselves,
we know very little at this point.
According to
government officials I've spoken to,
the visitors do not represent a threat,
despite the ominous tone
of their message.
Then, of course, there’s
the question on everyone's mind:
Who is this Kal-El person?
Does he actually exist? How could he
have remained hidden for so long?
Come on, Kent.
Come on, fight back!
Get up, Kent.
Is that it?
Is that all you got?
Come on, Kent!
Come on!
Did they hurt you?
They can't.
It's not what I meant,
I meant are you all right?
I wanted to hit that kid.
I wanted to hit him so bad!
I know you did, I mean...
Part of me even wanted you to,
but then what?
Would it make you feel any better?
You just have to decide what kind of man
you want to grow up to be, because...
whoever that man is -
good character or bad - he is...
He is going to change the world.
What’s on your mind?
I don't where to start.
Wherever you want.
That ship that appeared last night.
I'm the one they are looking for.
Do you know...
- why they want you?
- No.
But this General Zod,
even if I surrender, there's
no guarantee he'll keep his word.
If there's a chance I can save
Earth by turning myself in...
...shouldn't I take it?
What does your gut tell you?
Zod can’t be trusted.
The problem is... I'm not sure
the people of Earth can be either.
Sometimes you have to take
a leap of faith first,
the trust part comes later.
All right, you got our attention.
- What it is you want?
- I would like to speak to Lois Lane.
What makes you think she's here?
Don't play games with me, General,
I'll surrender.
But only if you guarantee
Lois's freedom.
Why are you surrendering to Zod?
I’m surrendering to mankind,
there is a difference.
You let them handcuff you.
Wouldn't be much of a surrender
if I resisted.
And if it makes them feel more secure,
then all the better for it.
What does the S stand for?
It’s not an a S,
on my world it means “hope”.
Well, here it’s an S.
How about...
Sir, hi.
- My name is doctor...
- Emil Hamilton, I know.
I can see your ID tag
in your breast pocket,
along with a half eaten roll
of Wint-O-Green Life Savers.
And I also see the squad
of soldiers in the next room
preparing that
tranquilizing agent of yours.
You won’t need it.
Sir, you can't expect us
to not take precautions,
you could be carrying
some kind of alien pathogen.
I’ve been here for 33 years, doctor,
haven't infected anyone yet.
That you know of.
We have legitimate
security concerns.
Now you revealed your identity
to Miss Lane over there.
Why won't you do the same with us?
Let’s put our cards
on the table here, General.
You are scared of me
because you can't control me.
You don't and you never will.
But that doesn't mean
I'm your enemy.
And who is? Zod?
- That's what I'm worried about.
- Be that as it may,
I been given orders
to hand you over to him.
Do what you have to do, General.
Thank you.
For what?
For believing in me.
Didn't make much
difference in the end.
It did to me.
They are coming.
You should leave now.
Go, Lois.
Kal-El, I'm sub-commander Faora-Ul.
On behalf of General Zod,
I extend you his greetings.
- Are you the ranking officer here?
- I am.
General Zod, would like
this woman to accompany me.
You asked for the alien.
You didn't say anything
about one of our own.
Shall I tell the general
you are unwilling to comply?
I don't care what you tell him.
It's all right.
I'll go.
The atmosphere composition in our ship
is not compatible with humans.
You will need to wear
a breather beyond this point.
Kal-El.
You have no idea how long
we've been searching for you.
- I take it you are Zod.
- General Zod, our Commander!
It's all right, Faora. You can
forgive Kal any lapses in decorum.
He is a stranger to our ways.
This should be cause for celebration.
Not conflict.
I... feel strange.
Weak...
- What's happening to him?
- He is rejecting our ships atmospherics.
You've spend a lifetime
adapting to Earth's ecology
- but you never adapted to ours.
- Help him!
I can't. Whatever's happening to him
has to run its course.
Help him!
Hello, Kal.
Or do you prefer Clark?
That's the name they gave you,
isn't it?
I was Krypton's military leader,
your father - our foremost scientist.
The only thing we agreed on
was that Krypton was dying.
In return for my efforts
to protect our civilization,
and save our planet...
...I and my fellow officers
were sentenced to the Phantom Zone.
And then,
the destruction of our world...
freed us.
We were adrift.
Destined to float among the ruins
of our planet until we starved.
How did you find your way to Earth?
We managed to retro-fit the phantom
projector into a hyper drive.
Your father made similar modification
to the craft that brought your here.
And so
the instrument of our damnation...
...became our salvage.
We sought out the old colonial
outposts, looking for signs of life.
But all we found was death.
Cut off from Krypton, these outposts
withered and died long ago.
We salvaged what we could:
armor, weapons.
Even a world-engine.
For 33 years we prepared,
until finally
we detected a distress beacon,
which you triggered when
you accessed the ancient scout ship.
You lead us here, Kal.
And now it's within your power
to save what remains of your race.
On Krypton, the genetic template
for every being yet to be born,
is encoded
in the registry of citizens.
Your father stole
the registry's codex
and stored it in the capsule
that brought you here.
For what purpose?
So that Krypton can live again...
...on Earth.
Where is the codex, Kal?
If Krypton lives again,
what happens to Earth?
A foundation
has to be built on something.
Even your father recognized that.
No, Zod.
- I can’t be a part of this.
- Then what can you be a part of?
Stop!
Your father acquitted himself
with honor Kal.
- You killed him?
- I did.
And not a day goes by
where it doesn't haunt me.
But if I had to do it again, I would.
I have a duty to my people.
And I will not allow anyone
to prevent me from carrying it out.
What's the setback, Major?
DSP pinged 2 bogeys
launching from the alien ship.
- Put it up.
- Yes, sir.
There it is.
Retask I-Com 4, give me
a closer look. - Yes, sir.
Command, word of the day is "Trident".
- We have 2 alien craft on aggressive
approach. - I-Com 4 coming online.
- Air speed? - 380 knots, they are
not responding to our hails.
You are wasting your efforts.
The strength you do have from
your exposure to the Earth's sun
has been neutralized
aboard our ship.
Here, in this environment,
you're as weak as a human.
- Where did you come from?
- The command key, Miss Lane.
Thanks to you, I'm uploading
into the ships mainframe.
- Who are you?
- I'm Kal's father.
- Can you help us?
- I designed this ship.
I can modify its atmospheric
composition to human compatibility.
We can stop them, we can send
them back to the phantom zone.
- How?
- I can teach you.
And in turn, you can teach Kal.
Will you help me?
The ship's crew are alerted.
We need to move quickly.
Retrieve the command key.
- Did you do that?
- Yes. Pick up the sidearm.
What's happening?
To your right, fire!
Behind you!
Secure yourself inside the under pod.
Safe travels, Miss Lane.
It's highly unlikely
we'll be seeing each other again.
Remember, the Phantom Drive
is essential for stopping them.
Movie your head to the left.
Is it true
what Zod said about the codex?
Strike that panel.
We wanted you to learn
what it meant to be human first.
So that one day,
when the time was right,
you could be the bridge
between two peoples.
Look.
Lois.
You can save her, Kal.
You can save all of them.
You will be safe here.
- Are you all right?
- Oh yeah.
I'm sorry. I didn't wanna tell them
anything about you,
but they did something to me,
they looked inside my mind...
It's okay, Lois.
They did the same thing to me.
Clark!
The craft he arrived in,
where is it?
Go to hell.
There.
Where has he hidden it?
I don't know.
Where is the Codex?!
You think
you can threaten my mother?!
What have you done to me?
My parents taught me
to hone my senses, Zod.
To focus...
...on just what I wanted to see.
Without your helmet,
you are getting everything.
And its hurts, doesn't it?
Get inside, it’s not safe.
All clear, this is Guardian,
I'm airborne mission commander.
I have previously encountered
and observed
the beings we are about
to engage at close proximity,
they are extremely dangerous,
we are authorized to use deadly force.
Roger, Guardian,
we're inbound to target.
- We're hot, weapons free.
- Copy One-One, weapons free.
Thunder One-One,
tally three targets.
Thunder One-One, good hit,
request immediate re-attack.
Roger, Guardian, we'll make a second
gun run ahead of you 2-1-2-3.
Thunder One-One, eject, eject!
Thunder One-One, eject!
I have a bogey incoming!
You are weak, son of El.
Unsure of yourself.
The fact that you posses
a sense of morality and we do not...
...gives us
an evolutionary advantage.
And if history has proven anything...
it is that the evolution always wins.
All Rangers,
I need you engage the targets.
Guardian, this is Battle Zero One,
what about that guy in blue?
I said, engage all targets!
Contact, contact!
Are you okay?
We're going in hard!
Brace for impact!
Brace for impact,
we're going in hard!
Fallen Angel, Fallen Angel,
Guardian is down.
I repeat, Guardian is down!
Thunder One-Two calling Guardian,
Guardian, do you read?
I want you to put down everything you got
at my position, this will be danger close.
Copy, danger close.
Good luck, sir.
A good death is its own reward.
You will not win,
for every human you save,
we will kill a million more.
We have an "All clear"?
Do we have an "All clear"?
Alfa Team, stand fast.
Alfa Team, do you copy?
This man is not our enemy.
Thank you, Colonel.
Mom?
I'm alright!
Nice suit, son.
I'm sorry.
It's only stuff, Clark.
It can always be replaced.
But you can't be.
Mom...
Zod said this Codex he's looking for
can actually bring my people back.
Isn't that a good thing?
I don't think they're interested
in sharing this world.
Clark!
I know how to stop them.
- What happened down there?
- He exposed a temporary weakness.
It is of little consequence,
because I have located the codex.
It was never in the capsule.
Jor-el took the codex,
the DNA of an billion people..
And he bonded it with
his sons individual cells,
all Krypton's heirs,
living hidden in one refugee's body.
Does Kal-el need to be alive, for us
to extract the codex from his cells?
No.
Released the world-engine.
What did just happen?
The ships just split in 2,
track 1 is heading east,
track 2 is deploying towards
the Southern Hemisphere.
- How fast is that bogey moving?
- Approaching Mach 24 and accelerating.
Looks like it’s going to impact
somewhere in the South Indian Ocean.
- The rest of the ship is descending.
- Put it on the board now.
Oh my God!
Bring the phantom drive on-line!
We are now slaved to the world engine.
Initiate.
What have they hit us with?
Looks like some kind of gravity weapon,
its working in tandem with their ship.
Somehow they are
increasing the Earth's mass,
clouding the atmosphere
with particulates.
Oh my God!
They are Terra-forming.
What's that?
Planetary engineering modifying
Earth's atmosphere and topography.
And turning Earth into Krypton.
- But what happen to us?
- Based on these readings,
there won’t be an us.
General Swanwick, sir.
I'm on with the control tower,
Colonel Hardy is on his way in
and he got Superman in tow.
Superman?
The alien, sir. That's what
they're calling him, Superman.
- We have a plan, General.
- Is that what I think it is?
It's the ship he arrived in.
This ship is run by something
called a phantom-drive.
Its bends space. Zod's ship
uses the same technology.
If we can make the two drives
collide with one another...
- A singularity could be created.
- Like a black hole.
Yes. So if you open up this doorway,
then theoretically
they should be pulled back in.
So, you want us bomb them with that?
General, if that craft
maxes at 17,000 pounds,
we can drop it from a C-17.
It’s a viable plan.
And if I don't stop that machine
over the Indian Ocean,
the gravity field
will continue to expand.
If that thing is making Earth
more like Krypton,
would you be weaker around it?
Maybe, but I'm not gonna let that
stop me from trying.
You may want
to step back a little bit.
Maybe a little bit more.
Faora! Take command.
- Yes, sir.
I need to secure
the Genesis chamber,
and pay my respects
to an old friend.
Guardian en route to Metropolis.
Package in tow.
Command key accepted
Genesis chamber coming on-line, sir.
Stop this, Zod,
while there still time.
Haven't giving up lecturing me
have you, even in death.
I will not let you use
the codex like this.
You don't have
the power to stop me.
The command key I have entered
is revoking your authority,
this ship is now under my control.
North Com, Lightning 1. Request
permission to unleash the hounds.
North Com, Lightning 1,
you are clear to engage.
Send battle damage
assessment when able, out.
Avionics are going haywire,
the gravity field is pulling our
missiles down, we got to get closer!
All right everybody, we are leaving,
we're leaving the building now!
We've lost our wingman!
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
Everybody, this way! Come on!
Everybody, go!
Keep moving, keep moving!
Our people can co-exist.
So we can suffer through years of
pain trying to adapt like your son has?
You are talking about genocide.
Yes, and I'm arguing
its merits with a ghost.
We are both ghosts, Zod,
can't you see that?
The Krypton you're clinging on to
is gone.
Ship, have you managed to quarantine
this invasive intelligence?
- I have.
- Then prepare to terminate it,
- I'm tired of this debate.
- Silencing me won't change anything.
My son...
...is twice the man you were.
And he will finish what we started.
I can promise you that.
Tell me, you have Jor-El's
memories, his conscience.
Can you experience his pain?
I will harvest the codex
from your son's corps.
And I will rebuild Krypton,
atop his bones.
Jenny, where are you!
- I'm here!
- Hold on, hold on.
I can't get free, I'm stuck.
We get you out there, all-right.
Just sit tight.
- No, no! Please don't leave me!
- I'm not gonna leave you.
Robert, get your ass
over here and help me!
Try this.
It's getting closer!
Come on, push!
North Com, this is Guardian,
are we clear to make the drop?
Negative, Guardian.
He did it.
Northcom, this is Guardian, we're passing
the phase line, we're good to go.
Godspeed, Guardian. Arm the package.
You are cleared hot.
We are lining up
for the final run.
It’s up to you and Hamilton now.
- Are you planning on getting me in?
- Load master, is the package armed?
- You know we're ready to drop.
- Negative.
There is something wrong,
it’s not supposed to do this.
- What is it supposed to do?
- It's supposed to go in all the way.
- Let me take a look.
- Co-pilot's aircraft.
Co-pilot's aircraft.
We are lined up for the drop,
what's the hold up?
We have a slight set-back.
Target that aircraft!
Target locked.
- Zod!
- If you destroy this ship...
...you destroy Krypton.
Krypton had its chance!
Are they gone?
I think so.
He saved us.
You know they say it's all
downhill after the first kiss.
I'm pretty sure it only counts
when you're kissing a human.
Look at this...
We could have built a new Krypton
in this squalor.
But you chose the humans over us.
I exist only to protect Krypton...
That is the sole purpose
for which I was born,
and every action I take,
no matter how violent,
or how cruel,
is for the greater good...
...of my people.
And now I have no people.
My soul...
that is what you have taken from me!
I'm going to make them suffer, Kal,
these humans you've adopted.
I will take them all from you,
one by one.
You are a monster, Zod.
And I'm gonna stop you.
There is only one way this ends, Kal!
Either you die, or I do!
I was bred to be a warrior, Kal.
Trained my entire life
to master my senses.
Where did you train? On a farm?!
Are you F-ing stupid?!
That's one of your
surveillance drones.
That's a 12 million $
piece of hardware. - It was.
I know you are trying to find out,
where I hang my cape, you won't.
Then I'll ask the obvious question -
how do we know you won't one day
act against America's interests?
I grew up in Kansas, General.
I'm about American as its gets.
Look, I'm here to help,
but it has to be on my own terms.
- You have to convince Washington of that.
- Even if I was willing to try...
- What makes you think they'd listen?
- I don't know, General.
Guess I'll just have to trust you.
- What are you smiling about, Captain?
- Nothing, sir.
I just think he's kinda hot.
- Get in the car, Captain.
- Yes, sir.
He always believed you were meant for
greater things, and when the day came,
your shoulders will be
able to bare the weight.
I just wish he could have been here
to see it finally happen.
He saw it Clark, believe me.
What are you going to do, when
you are not saving the world?
Have you given any thought to that?
I have, actually.
I'm going to find a job, where I can
keep my ear to the ground.
Where people won't look twice,
when I want go somewhere dangerous,
or start asking questions.
Come on Lois, when are you
going to throw me a bone?
Courtside seats to the game
tonight, what do you say?
I'd say, you should go back
to trolling the intern pool,
you'll probably have more luck.
Sorry.
- Courtside?
- Don't, don't.
Lombardi, Lane. Want you
to meet our new stringer,
want you to show him the ropes.
This is Clark Kent. Good luck, kid.
- Hey. Steve.
- Nice to meet you.
Lois Lane, welcome to The Planet.
Glad to be here, Lois.