Holy...
oh. Whoa.
I was thinking if you need money
you can use my credit card.
What?
I got it under control.
Sure you don't want to come
and stay at my place tonight?
I'd like to, but I'll be
up all night studying.
Now get out of here.
Marcus sent me
to get the money.
You cannot be showing up
to my fucking house like this.
- I need more time.
- Marcus said to get the money tonight
or he's going to pay himself
at your girlfriend's house.
Listen to me.
You leave her the fuck
out of this.
Oh, I'm just the messenger.
Get us the fucking money.
Jesus.
Cool.
No.
My husband liked
to collect awful things.
Take it to the dump
with everything else.
- You know I can sell this...
- young man,
when you take this
to the landfill
promise me
you'll watch them bury it.
Yeah okay.
Sorry, ma'am,
but one man's trash
is another man's treasure.
Cooler than I thought.
What?
Shit.
- What is it, man?
- Get your shit together. You gotta see this.
All right.
Wow.
- What the hell is it?
- I don't know.
What's that?
It's a key.
- Is that an engraving?
- Yeah.
"Von tristen, 1452."
Dude, we might have
a real antique here.
Come over here.
Check this out, dude.
I think I figured out
where the key goes.
Give me that.
That's creepy.
What happened?
Why would someone put a
music box in a coffin?
I don't know.
But I'm going to bed.
So you're thinking post-modern
philosophy... ambitious.
I like it. Right here. First few
chapters are a little slow.
Mid-way through it picks up, but
the ending... change your life.
Okay, I'll take a look.
Come over.
Skinner was asking
about you in class today,
wondering if you dropped out.
Yeah, I slept right through it.
The harder I try,
the worse I do.
- I wish I could help, man.
- Show me what you found.
Wolfgang Von tristen.
Frankfurt, 1412.
Builder of torture devices.
I saw that already.
There's no mention
of coffins...
- of any kind.
- Right this way.
"Age of darkness."
This guy was like an evil
version of Leonardo Da Vinci.
They called him
the devil's craftsman.
That's it.
"Idolon machina.
Von tristen was fascinated with
death and the worlds beyond.
The later part of his years
were spent creating
the ultimate machine...
a mechanical coffin
that allowed him to safely
experience the sensation of death.
Von tristen called this
'geist maschine'...
ghost machine."
How much you think it's worth?
Thousands?
Millions?
Collectors would kill
for something like that.
Hey... the book's not allowed
out of the archive!
You're gonna set off the alarm.
Glad to be of assistance.
Dude, what the hell
are you doing?
I just replaced a couple
of pins in the music box.
It should work fine.
Easy, man.
What's up?
Read this.
"Von tristen's ghost machine.
This coffin-like device
is said to produce
an out-of-body experience
similar to the first
moments of death.
Von tristen was accused of
sorcery and burned at the stake.
Although sketches of the coffin
were recovered from his laboratory,
- an actual prototype was never found."
- Until now.
No way.
Grab minnie.
You'd better not hurt
my goldfish, man.
- What'd you do?
- Nothing!
Wait wait wait wait.
Just give it a sec.
Minnie's dead.
Oh ho!
I can't believe it.
Hey.
Call platt.
Kyle!
Why are you beeping?
- Honk honk.
- Hey.
What's up?
So what's the surprise?
Ah, that is exactly
what I needed.
What happened to your neck?
It's a hickey from Gina.
What?
She tried to roundhouse me
in kickboxing class,
but I kicked her ass.
Ohhh, that's my girl.
# ...the night as it
cuts before #
# whatever we're going thru
just want to be with you... #
Kyle, the gas company
just called.
They're going to shut off the
gas if we don't pay the bill.
Not now, Sutton!
Sure, I'll take care
of the bill.
Just like I did last month.
When are you moving
into a new place?
I am not moving
into a new place.
I got an awesome bathroom
and Sutton pays for everything.
Hi, Julie.
Hi, Sutton.
Yeah, thanks.
Sutton, will you get the door?
Hey, platt.
Well?
Let's see this thing.
Interesting.
Wait till you see the inside.
Amazing.
- Wanna go for a ride?
- I wanna run some tests first.
You scared?
I'm careful.
- How about you, sutt?
- Yeah right.
It didn't hurt the fish.
Um, there's a big difference between
a goldfish and a human being.
All right, it's gotta be me.
Hey, do I have to remind you
this was built
by an expert
in torture machines?
- With some help from the devil.
- Wait? Huh, what?
Just kidding.
If you see spikes
shooting out of the sides,
pull me out.
October 10th,
Kyle Baker enters
the ghost machine.
Three turns should put Kyle
in a trance for about a minute.
Kyle,
- are you afraid?
- Just turn the key.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Ha ha ha. Kyle, you can
quit pretending now.
Dude,
I don't think he's joking.
He's... he's not breathing.
This is not good.
I'm not okay. This is not okay.
This is not okay.
- Huh-uh.
- Careful.
- Come on, Kyle.
- I don't know if you can touch him.
- Kyle, wake up!
- Easy, okay.
- No no, Kyle, Kyle.
- It's okay.
One minute.
Come on.
No, we need to wake
him up right now!
Just let the music end!
- Ooh ooh!
- Holy shit!
You scared the hell out of me!
One minute, five seconds.
- Tell us what happened, man.
- Man!
Dude, do you remember anything?
Come on, what the hell, man!?
- Say something.
Wow.
It was like...
Virtual reality.
You're there, but you're not.
You mean like a dream?
No, it's more like
being invisible.
I wish you could
tell me more, man.
Try it for yourself.
I shouldn't do this.
Yeah, platt,
I thought you were smart.
I'm cursed with curiosity.
You're gonna be fine.
Relax.
Bon voyage.
Ahh!
- Easy, man.
- Chill, dude. We got you.
Thank God! Get me out of this thing!
Get me out!
What the hell happened to you?
I don't think my experience
was as enjoyable as yours.
No, this isn't good. I do not
like this at all! Not one bit!
Not one bit. It's evil,
I don't like it! It's not good!
Dude, dude!
What do you think
it's doing to us?
It's an n.D.E....
a near-death experience.
We seem to be approaching
the threshold of death
without actually crossing over.
You all right?
Do you need a breather?
You want some water?
I'm next!
I was hoping you'd say that.
I really think
this is a bad idea.
It's gonna be fine, platt.
Sutton, when you go under
I need you to read
the words on this card,
so that I'll know
we're not dreaming.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
My God.
Kyle! Kyle!
Shit. Listen,
I need you
to keep an eye on him.
What's going on?
I came to show you something.
When I offered you
my credit card yesterday,
I didn't know you had already
been using it for a month!
Oh come on, I was going
to pay you back.
- Look, I can't talk about this.
- What are you thinking?
I can't talk
about this right now!
Oh my God! What the
hell is going on, Kyle?
Something big is going down.
I will call you tonight
to explain all of this.
Unbelievable.
That's platt's scooter.
Great.
Holy shit!
- What did I tell you?
- I was walking.
What was written on the card?
Sometimes, I dream
that I'm walking.
But never like that.
- What was written on the card?
- What?
- The card.
- I don't know.
Maybe we were just dreaming.
Steal your girlfriend's
credit card, huh?
That's pretty low, man.
You were out there?
Sneaky little bastard.
And you...
you might want to go look
at your scooter, dude.
Julie can really kick.
Wait, what?
This is bigger than
anything else I've ever known.
This is bigger than lasers.
This is bigger than...
this is crazy. We're on a
canyon of unknowing, guys.
Look, some art collector
finds out about this,
some criminal, the police,
it'll be gone by morning.
So it's our secret, okay?
And no more using the machine.
Not until I do
some more research.
Seems perfectly safe.
Look!
- Whoa!
- Whoa whoa whoa.
- I was standing.
- You were falling.
You saw it!
I felt my legs.
That's impossible.
The feeling is gone now.
Look, we've got
something powerful here
and we have absolutely no idea
what it's doing to our bodies.
I want to do some more research
before we use it again. Agreed?
I'm ready to go
back in right now.
- No! No, you're not. No.
- Easy!
We'll get there.
Agreed.
Sutton?
I felt my legs.
Excuse me, sir?
Come on, pooch.
Good boy.
This relationship
isn't working.
I need more than casual sex.
I want some time off.
Either we take two weeks off
from each other or...
We can end it right now.
Two weeks.
I love you, Kyle, but I really
don't like you right now.
Of course.
I thought I might have
seen you tonight.
I've got your money.
Jerrod,
get the schoolboy some tea.
Why are you messing
with all this stuff anyway?
Ain't they got beers
or cigarettes at your school?
Yeah. It was helping
me study harder.
Now it's just helping.
Let me show you something.
You know, smoking is fine...
if you want to lose your teeth.
Real pros shoot their crystal.
Maximize the effects.
Saves money.
I'm not that desperate.
There you go, buddy.
Have fun.
Wait a minute.
Ow!
What the fuck?!
Just 'cause you go to college
doesn't mean you don't follow
the same rules as
the other junkies, okay?
From now on you pay as you go.
- I'm not a fucking junkie.
- Just wait till you start losing your teeth.
- Yeah. I got some
info on the music box.
- What time is it?
- It's almost noon.
Shouldn't you be in class?
Shit.
- What did you find out?
- It relies on the diminished fifth,
also known as
diabolus en musica,
a tonal interval banned
by the medieval church
because it was considered
to be satanic.
I want to record the music
so I can study it further.
I don't understand
a word you're saying, platt.
Just don't touch anything.
I'll be there at 6:00.
This stuff goes way too quick.
A lot of religions believe
in the power of sound.
The vedics believed that the universe
was created by sonic vibrations
and will be destroyed
the same way.
Uh, how you guys feeling?
Fine.
You guys haven't had any problems
since we used the coffin last night?
Nosebleeds, headaches,
that sort of thing?
Nope.
How about your legs, sutt?
Nothing.
Must have been a nervous
reaction before.
It happens.
Have you seen anything strange?
Hallucinations,
hot flashes, nightmares?
I slept like a baby.
Me too.
I saw something horrible.
It looked just like this.
Scared me half to death.
You were really
freaked out yesterday.
This thing's gotta mess
with your head a little.
Tonight
- I'm going for maximum duration.
- Wait wait wait.
Wait just a minute. I'm here to
do the sound and nothing else.
Don't touch me.
Fine.
Listen, you guys don't tell me
what to do with my machine.
Kyle Baker enters the ghost
machine for the second time.
Tell us what you're
going to do, man.
- Why?
- For the marketing video.
That's nobody's business
but my own.
Come on, man.
Time's up.
Stop it!
You know, man?
Your girlfriend
ain't half bad.
Doesn't move much,
but you can do anything
you want with her.
Just give me my stuff.
Give them what they came for.
Thanks, jerrod. I knew you
were good for something.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
Real good.
Come on, man.
Tell us where you went.
The gates of heaven.
Come on.
You guys gonna help me out?
You guys might want
to take a look at something.
Goldfish die all the time.
- Take me to the Max.
- You guys are tweaked.
Good night, fellas.
See you in class tomorrow.
What?
- I miss him already.
- Oh.
You should just get it
over with and leave him.
He used to be different...
like really sweet.
After college we were
gonna go to Europe
to see the castles.
You're such a sucker for their
romantic bullshit, aren't you?
No.
No no no.
Don't answer it.
I'll just tell him
to stop calling me.
Okay.
Julie, please don't
hang up on me.
I meant it when I said
I needed time off, Kyle.
I know.
But I got some great news
for you.
What?
I have to tell you in person.
I got something to show you.
You're burning me out, Kyle.
Meet me tomorrow at the
cafe near your house.
It'll be worth it, promise you.
- Noon?
- Okay.
I love you, Kyle.
No!
Whoa.
How are you feeling?
I never felt better.
Where were you, man?
The audience wants to know.
I snuck into a movie theater.
Must have been a good movie.
Look, I'm sorry.
Get me out of here!
Come on!
Grab the waist.
That was strange.
Yeah.
I didn't think
he could get those.
Me neither.
Nice fugue, tristen.
Bach would have been proud.
Sound without sound.
I know that number.
I am Professor Julian cutler with
the center for acoustic studies.
The founders of the medieval church
understood the power of sound...
"For a sustained period of time
to cause trauma or death."
Organ music has been known to provoke
religious feelings and dread.
7-8 hz is the frequency of the
average brain Alpha wave.
Sustained sound
at this frequency
can cause disorientation,
unconsciousness
and even death.
Enough for a small creature...
It worked on an insect,
maybe even a small fish.
Definitely not enough
for a human body.
Hmm, there must be
something else.
I paid it all off...
everything I owe you,
plus some of your stuff too.
- How did you get the money?
- It doesn't matter.
You and I
are going to be happy from...
it's not about
the credit cards, Kyle.
What happened to the guy
that I used to date?
The one that used to smile
and make me laugh?
I look at you now and all I see
is some sort of sick person.
And, babe, I don't know why.
I don't have to tell you every
fucking detail of my life, do I?
See, that is what I'm talking
about... that right there.
Look...
I'm sorry.
Things have been
a little crazy lately.
What's up, platt?
It's in the music.
But not the way you think.
The real power comes
from ultra-low frequencies.
I'm with Julie right now.
The music requires
a transmission device...
something to focus
and channel the sound.
Then there must be something
else hidden in the coffin,
shooting the sound
directly into our heads.
- Let's talk about this later, platt.
- A needle perhaps.
That would explain
Sutton's cns reaction.
Direct stimulation
of the craniocerebral junction
could restore some form
of neuromuscular activity
- when the brain dies.
- I'm losing you, platt!
Kyle!
When you use the coffin,
you are not having an out-of-body experience.
Your brain is dead!
Do you hear what
I am saying, Kyle?
You're killing yourself
every time you use that thing!
- Yeah.
- I'll be over at your place at 7:00.
We need to figure out what we're
gonna do with this goddamn thing.
See you soon.
Hey, I'm perfectly
fucking fine!
I've never felt better
in my entire life!
Yeah.
Fuck!
It's fucking gone, man.
It's all fucking gone.
You fuck!
You let somebody follow you?
No, there was nobody fucking...
I don't fucking know!
I don't fucking know, man!
Okay, there was nobody
fucking... fuck!
Do you know how fucked we are?
Calderon is going
to cut out our throats
and yank our tongues
through the fucking holes!
That's how fucked we are!
He's officially an hour late.
Let's do it.
Ugh, you're bleeding, man.
What if we really are dying?
Then death is
a wonderful thing.
You want me to go first?
No.
I'll go in.
It's a stupid idea.
If we're gonna pay
Calderon tonight,
we need to move some shit.
This crap is all we got left.
Mixing those is fucking poison.
We fuck the junkies
or Calderon fucks us.
I'd rather fuck some junkie,
than us get shot.
Marcus ain't interested
in your bitch tonight!
I got cash.
Hey, man.
Hey, listen to me.
Hey, you don't want to do this.
Hey...
Look at me.
You don't have to do this.
Hey!
Sutton, get me the fuck
out of here!
Sutton!
- Were you careful?
- Of course I was!
Two, one!
- - Really good.
Open the heels,
drop down to the knees,
lift the feet to push up.
Aren't you gonna invite me in?
Sure.
Nice place.
No!
When did you take
these pictures?
Just tell me about Kyle.
How much do you know
about crystal meth?
Kyle's an extreme personality,
but he's not an idiot.
I didn't believe it
myself at first.
I gave him this box.
I'm sorry I had to be
the one to tell you.
I had a feeling.
I really appreciate
you helping with Kyle.
I hate what Kyle's
doing to you.
I love you, Julie.
What are you afraid of?
I'm sorry, Sutton, I just don't
feel the same way about you.
- Because of this.
- Of course not.
Do you know that I've been in
love with you since high school,
and you never even noticed me?
I never meant
to make you feel bad.
I chose Kyle to be my roommate
just so I could be
close to you.
- You did what?
- I'm a whole different person now!
Oh my God.
I'm healing!
And I'm getting
stronger every day.
- You're hurting me.
- Shhh.
No more talk.
Get out!
Get the fuck out!
Idiot!
- Kyle Baker?
- Yeah?
You're a friend
of Oscar platt, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm going to need you to come with me, sir.
What happened?
He was in a big hurry
to get out of here.
Did your friend have anybody
who would want to hurt him?
Everybody loved him.
Yeah.
It looks like he was into
some pretty creepy stuff.
We found this on the screen.
It's unfinished.
It's addressed to you.
"No one cheats death, Kyle.
We must destroy it."
Destroy what?
I have no idea.
Okay, tell you what...
If you do get an idea,
give me a call.
Thanks, fellas.
What are you doing?
Oh my God.
Platt was right.
He was.
How long you been hiding this?
Get away from my coffin.
You are not gonna
take it away from me.
- All right, Sutton.
- Put it down, Kyle.
- Okay, Sutton, all right.
- Put it down!
I don't need you
to fuck Julie for me anymore.
# You're so beautiful #
- # the night as it
cuts before... #
Oh shit.
# Whatever we're going thru
just want to be with you #
# you're so beautiful... #
What's going on?
What the hell?
Someone help me!
I'm in apartment 303.
Please, somebody.
Who are you?
Answer me.
Please stop. No.
What did you do to me?
Sutton? No.
I never meant to hurt
your feelings.
No no no.
Oh fuck!
Julie.
Kyle, I think
Sutton drugged me.
He's hiding somewhere.
You're not going
to be able to see him.
- Get out of your apartment.
- I'm too weak.
Julie, keep your eyes open.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
No no, Julie!
Julie.
Julie!
Some guys give a girl a ring
or a nice vacation.
But I'm going to give you
something priceless...
And you're going to love it.
We're gonna use
the coffin together
so that you can see
the world the same way I do.
Hurt me all you want.
I don't care about
this useless body anymore.
Julie.
Julie!
Do you really love him?
Then you just killed him!
Julie.
Guess you learned a trick
or two, huh, Sutton?
The power is
in the music, Kyle.
I just had to make it
play a little longer.
What the hell?
I can't believe you wanted
to hurt my coffin, Kyle.
It's killing you.
Right here, Kyle!
That's for all the times I had
to listen to you fucking her.
Tonight you're gonna
be the one listening
on the other side of the wall.
Leave her the fuck alone!
Do you believe in ghosts?
Scream for him.
Fuck you.
- Help me, Kyle!
- Julie, listen to me.
Hold tight. I'm coming for you.
Hold on.
Where are you, Sutton?
Hiding and spying as usual.
Not anymore.
You're a sick son of a bitch,
you know that?
No no.
No.
Please, Sutton, no.
Please no.
Please no, Sutton.
So this is it, huh?
I'm not afraid of you.
You wanna take me, take me!
Kyle's not going
to save you, Julie.
Sutton, please.
Oh God.
No fucking way.
Help me burn it, Sutton.
Aww, are you afraid to die?
'Cause I'm not.
What makes you think I'm not
gonna come back and haunt you?
Without the coffin?
Good luck.
No!
Send me a postcard from hell!
Not this time.
You cunt.
Ha ha! You're gonna have to aim
straight if you want to kill me.
Good.
You and I got something
to finish,
but first things first.
Come on, man, let's end it now.
Oh! No!
No.
No-ooo!
Are you sure about this?
It's something I have to do.
Just wait for me.
I should have destroyed it
like you said.
I should have done it
a long time ago.
You?
Now I can finally
leave this place.
Hey, how long
will I see it for?
For the rest of your life.
Death is always
walking with us...
Waiting for the time.
The only difference is
now I can see it.
# Another fight club game
just to be alive today #
# if it's a chain of pain
life's a bitch #
# another double fault crime
made a freak #
# to break up the fight now
who makes it real #
# death is a beautiful thing #
# beautiful beautiful #
# beautiful
beautiful... #