Previously, on
"The increasingly
"Poor Decisions
"of Todd Margaret"...
Todd Margaret,
he's a temp.
He has no experience
in a national market.
Brent Wilts: Bullshit.
He's perfect.
Two weeks ago,
I made the mistake
of sleeping with you.
That mistake doesn't
make me your girlfriend.
What the fuck are you
doing here!
Actually I'm here
to ask you a few questions.
You're fired!
Still!
Again!
This is your boss.
This is the chick
you wanna bang?
Hello, I'm Hudson.
I'm from Canada.
He's down for the weekend.
He's staying here.
You grew up
in Leeds?
My dad lives in Leeds.
He lived in Leeds.
He's dead.
My dad lived in Leeds.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Steve Davis: Snooker.
Snooker.
Snooker!
Not snucker.
Not sniker.
You sold
all the Thunder Muscle?
Yeah, the turkish people
from the news agency,
they came in to buy
all the Thunder Muscle
we have in stock.
For my best friend.
Cash.
I'm fairly confident
this is a forgery.
What-what?
Where Todd and Brent Misjudge
the Mood of a Solemn Day
Original Air Date on October 29, 2010
The charges include
antisocial behavior, disruption
of national solemnity,
money laundering,
lewd sexist behavior,
failure to pay
for a cranberry juice.
Order!
Silence in court!
-- sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Hello, Mr. Wilts.
I want my money,
fuckstick!
Yes, sir.
And I'm not gonna take "no"
for an answer.
I said "yes".
Right.
You listen up, douchenozzle,
you better get it right
this time.
I want that money
or I'm gonna fuck you
like Mike Tyson on E!.
Yeah, okay, uh,
I'll meet you at your hotel
as soon as I can.
No, fuck this place.
A bunch of stuck up
frigid bitches.
Meet me at that bar
down on the corner.
Todd, tell me that you nailed
that cafe vag-Jay-Jay
last night, buddy.
Oh, boy, did I.
I didn't, no.
Ah, come on, stud!
It ain't gonna happen.
I'm clearly not her type.
She goes for something, uh,
a bit more exotic,
if you catch my drift.
Listen, man, if you wanna
plug that weeping hole,
here's what you gotta do.
Whatever he type is,
be her type.
Yeah?
Yeah, dude.
You ju gotta look the part.
All right, yeah.
Look the part.
Hello?
Mr. Wilts?
Ow!
Jesus!
Hello, Dave,
it's Todd Margaret,
your ex-boss.
Um, just wanted to let you know
that I'm going to be
calling the cops
and having you arrested.
I don't know how dumb
you think I am, but, uh,
the fact that I feel compelled
to leave a telephone warning,
I think, speaks volumes.
Goodbye.
Number one, I want my money
or I will fuck you
like Mike Tyson on E!.
I can't do this.
Give me my money
or I will rip off your arm
and stuff it
down your cockhole.
Down your cockhole.
What am I doing?
Hi, Miss Plimpton.
Brent Wilts calling you
from the marketing department
over here at Dynamic Integrated
Business Solutions.
Do you mind taking
a brief survey?
We'll send you a ten dollar
coupon good for nasal spray.
Would you describe your
toilet in the following way?
A, luxurious,
B, functional yet savvy,
C, Orwellian,
D-- hello?
Hello?
Miss Plimpton?
Oh, cheese at Christmas.
Come on, Wilts,
this is pathetic!
You couldn't sell crack
to a crackwhore!
No, I know,
I fudged that up.
I'll say you fudged that up.
You fuckin' fudged that up
real good.
You better start showing me
something by the end of today
or I'm gonna
reach down your throat,
I'm gonna grab your balls,
and I'm gonna pull with vigor.
And I'm gonna take your balls
and throw them out the window.
Then I'm gonna leave
this office, get in my car,
find the ball pile,
and I'm gonna run over it
back and forth
and back and forth.
And I'm gonna get outta my car
and I'm gonna hover
over the ball pile
that's now been flattened.
I'm gonna defecate on it.
Miss Turgid,
there's a Mr. Moundford
on line one for you.
I've gotta take
a phone call.
Why don't you get back
to not selling things?
Okay?
Yes.
I'm turning it around.
Hey, dickbreath.
As you know, the Falcons
did not cover the spread.
Payment, please.
This is Turgid.
Double or nothin', right?
Come on, what do you say?
Let's do it.
Brent Wilts.
He's a temp.
He has no skills
internationally.
Bet, right?
What do you say?
Bet, man.
Okay.
Bon jour,
monsieur naked.
What was you doing last night
sneaking in
in your wet underpants?
Pam.
I got a good look
at that there,
and Pam likey what she see.
What are you doing
in my bath?
How long have you been here?
Calm down!
I told you
I couldn't use mine.
There's a spider in it.
Is that my tooth brush?
I thought it was
a bit small.
Haven't you got a loofa?
Pam, you gotta go, okay?
I've gotta go which means
you gotta go, all right,
and-and now I gotta get
a new tooth brush.
Thanks a lot.
Might need a new razor
as well.
Why?
Got it.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Oh, God!
That's okay.
Simple mistake.
You'll be all right,
won't you?
Thanks.
Oh, got it.
What the hell!
No!
Please, that was a mistake,
too!
That was a mistake!
I'm from Leeds!
Excuse me.
What's going on?
Are we at war?
No.
This is Remembrance Sunday,
the day when we remember
our fallen soldiers.
Oh, Memorial Day.
No, Remembrance Sunday.
Thank you very much.
What are these?
Oh, they're just symbolic,
just a way to show respect.
You know what, I'd like
to show some respect.
Put this in here.
I'll only take
five pounds back.
You can keep the change.
Why thank you, sir.
Um, this isn't
for charity, is it?
Yes, all the money goes
to help injured soldiers,
war heroes.
I'll tell ya what.
Thirty, sixty, ninety pounds.
God bless you, sir.
And I'll just take
a little bit back
for old time's sake, huh?
...Five.
Okay, great.
You enjoy.
Now it's time
to look the part.
Oh, hey, Alice.
I was just on my way
to play hockey in honor
of remembering day.
Do you have any maple syrup?
No.
No?
Oh, shoot.
Uh, mousse?
Any mousse?
No, Todd,
I have no mousse.
I really wanted
some maple covered mousse.
All right, well,
I'll be oot and aboot.
Oh, Canada,
to me you are the best.
Is that Todd?
Yeah.
Is he making fun of me
'cause I'm a Canadian?
I don't know.
Is he all right?
Yeah.
No.
He's just-- he's harmless.
You know.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't I invite
some friends over tonight?
You could screen your movie.
I could maybe digitize
some appetizers.
That would be very nice.
Okay.
But not Todd, right?
Oh, God, no!
No.
Oh, that is a lot sperm,
but it's all
for a good cause.
Uh, cranberry juice.
And finally,
you think your flat stinks.
Well, here's a story from
Portland, Oregon in America.
A hundred and twelve people
found themselves homeless
when their entire building
was condemned after
one tenant left over 30 cans
of tuna open in 30 degree heat
for over six days.
Now apparently
this attracted various animals
which then attacked
and killed each other.
Really?
That's amazing.
Yeah.
Apparently the smell
was visible from outer space.
Police are looking
for this man,
the tenant responsible,
for questioning.
Well, he's certainly
caused quite a stink.
And now we return
to our coverage of
the Remembrance Sunday
ceremony.
There you go, mate.
That's one pound twenty,
please.
I can't go home.
Um, is everything okay?
I, uh, oh, my Fanny.
My building's been condemned.
The police found Fanny
rotting in it.
Can you turn this
from the news?
Put it on anything else,
please.
Oh, well, this is gonna be
on every channel, I'm afraid.
It's the Remembrance Sunday
ceremony.
It's live, so.
This is live
on every channel?
Yeah.
Huh.
Hey, nutbreath.
Hey there, Mr. Wilts.
What the fuck
are you wearing?
Oh, I took your advice
about being Alice's type.
This has happened
to me before.
The girl I was seeing
in Portland had a thing
for Texans.
Why the fuck did I ask?
What the hell is going on
on your face?
Oh, um, I was in the park
and there was this little boy
and, uh, oh, man,
I saw his balls
comin' at me, and, uh,
it has been a long time,
and I don't have
the best control,
and I ended up
just splatting him
right in the face,
and his dad didn't
take too kindly to that.
Been there, done that.
No judgment here.
Do you have my wallet?
Yes, do you got that
Thunder Muscle money for me?
Not exactly.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm gonna rip
your fucking arms off
and shove 'em
up your cockhole,
you stupid fuck!
Oh, no!
I've got the money.
I've got the money
right here.
I've got 30,000 pounds
in this briefcase.
All right, close enough.
No, no, wait, wait, wait,
wait!
No, you can't-you can't
have it yet.
Fuck that.
I gotta get back to my hotel
and send this out today,
get that fucker off my back.
No, no, you can't.
Why not?
Because...
It's fake.
How's that?
It's counterfeit.
I messed up.
I got ripped off.
You stupid motherfucker!
You worthless piece of shit!
Pack your shit up and go back
to Portland right now.
No, no, no!
I can't!
I can't go home!
You give me a briefcase
full of counterfeit money,
you expect to keep your job?
Oh, no!
No, sir!
I'm sorry.
You thought the money
is fake.
I meant the briefcase
The-the, yeah, the briefcase.
I'm so sorry.
It's-it's fake leather.
It's, uh, uh, leatherine,
a counterfeit,
leather-like substance.
The fucking briefcase!
Yes, I'm so sorry.
I--
Todd, I don't give a shit
about that!
Oh, okay!
I didn't know.
I thought maybe--
so you're telling me
that there's 30,000 pounds
in here, right?
You know, minus a handful
of 30 pound notes.
That is so fucking great.
Now wait, wait, wait,
Frank.
This whole briefcase scenario
has got me thinking.
Um, we should really have
a lawyer on retainer.
Great.
Yeah.
Great idea.
Okay.
Uh, yesterday I was googling
"Young and Not Legal"
and they look quite attractive.
Well, you oughta try
"tight, willing, and fresh".
Where are they
based out of?
I don't know, Bangkok.
Listen, it's crunch time.
Sixteen thousand more crates
of Thunder Muscles
are being unloaded right now.
I know, okay!
Okay.
Sorry.
I...
Am very excited about it.
I was tryin' to say that
you're doin' a good job up
'til now, Margaret.
But you need to step it up now.
What else you got?
I think I figured out a way
to get the word out
about Thunder Muscle
to all of Britain for free.
How is that?
Uh, yes, is this
the Human Resources Department
at Dynamic Integrated
Business Solutions?
I'd like to lodge
a formal complaint
against Brent Wilts.
Wilts, w-I--
No, not the telemarketer.
He's the President
of Global National.
The company
that owns Dynamic Solutions .
W-I-l-t... s.
And, um...
Wait are you telling me
that Brent Wilts
is not the President
of Global National?
Global National.
Look it-look it up.
Keep looking!
Excuse me.
Please don't use
that tone of voice with me.
I-- you know what, um,
what's your name.
Um, I'm gonna add your name
to the complaint list also.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
Please don't speak to me
that way.
Kindness would be appreciated
right now, sir.
Excuse me.
Please.
That's-that's inappropriate.
Stop looking at me that way.
Okay, so, yeah, Andre,
you can get changed in there
if you want.
She should be here soon.
You know the basic plot,
right?
I fuck her on the desk?
Pretty much, yeah.
Okay, cool.
Good call on the outfits.
It's all about fittin' in.
Now we gotta get some
of those tomato pins.
Those show double respect.
Yeah, what the fuck
is Remembrance Day?
It's just a day that all
of us Englanders get together
and remember how awesome war
can be, and this our parade.
Are there gonna be floats?
Uh, yeah.
Are they gonna
have Spiderman?
Uh, yeah,
but the English Spiderman,
a little different.
Oh, there's some tomato pins.
I've got to get
some tomato pins.
Sorry, mate.
You know what we should do,
find one of these old fuckers
with a bunch of war medals on
and get him to drink
this shit on camera.
Hey, guy, what war did you
fight in, the war on big fat,
'cause you lost.
Kidding, relax.
He's Todd Margaret.
Uh, hi, um,
I'd like to tell you
about a great new energy drink
called Thunder Muscle.
Now's not the time.
It's always a good time
for Thunder Muscle.
Oh, piss off!
Fuck this douche.
Let's find a cripple.
Oh, this is a frickin' layup.
What are you a nurse?
Hopefully of the wet variety.
Hey, you look like you
could use a little get up
and go or-or probably just go.
This one I got
for mass bravery.
And this one I got
for bringing over 1,000 women
to a very satisfying climax.
Uh, how about a can
of Thunder Muscle?
Is it free?
Is it-is it free?
What?
No.
Not this kid.
What, he's a war hero.
He's not a war hero.
It's just some kid with aids.
I don't have aids.
Or cancer.
God!
Whatever the fuck it is,
I don't want it associated
with Thunder Muscle.
Come on, Margaret,
what the hell is it with you.
You haven't impressed me
at all today.
I-I-I'm sorry.
I'm just-- this is all
reminding of my dad.
He used to love
Remembrance Day.
He looked forward
to marching in it every year.
He's kind of like a mascot
for them
sorry about
yelling at you before.
Hey, check it out.
It's your dad's old company!
Huh?
Leeds, right?
Yeah.
Oh, great.
Hey!
Hey, Uncle Ernie!
Uncle Ere!
That's not my real Uncle.
It's just a nickname.
You gotta sell 'em
some Thunder Muscle.
I don't know
if that's really--
what are you talkin' about!
Get the fuck in there!
But I--
sell 'em the God damn
Thunder Muscle!
Come on!
Don't be a pussy, Margaret.
Right.
Hello, gents.
Don't worry.
I'm from Leeds, meself.
You must be thirsty
with all this marching, huh?
Piss off!
Well, try this great new
energy drink, Thunder Muscle.
Oh, piss off,
you American twat.
Well, it's all right.
Oh, hey!
No need to shove!
Hey!
Yes!
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes!
Yes!
And cut!
Okay, brilliant work, guys.
That's another episode
of "there's a negro in my wife"
in the can.
Uh, please, help yourself
to a complimentary case
of Thunder Muscle.
You guys have earned it.
Oh, great job, Svetlana.
Can you tell me
when this will be airing?
Um...
Tonight.
May I come to the edit.
Oh, no.
What does S.A.S stand for,
shitty and mean!
Hey, what the hell,
Margaret?
We've been here
two solid hours.
You haven't sold shit!
I think I'm beginning to see
what you're all about.
I got it figured out.
Don't worry, I'm not angry.
I'm in the same situation.
I think it's time
that we fess up.
All right, look, I mean,
you-you can't blame me.
I mean, you know,
I-I-I-I was-I was a temp.
We need to get you laid,
right?
Little boy, am I right?
No.
Two little boys?
Two little brown ones?
A little brown
and a little yellow one?
Like fuckin' a bag of M&M's.
No, no, no,
it's not boys at all.
Oh, girls.
It's that-it's that
Alice chick, right?
All right,
here's what we're gonna do.
I got a sack of rufies.
No, no, Mr. Wilts.
It's not that.
What the fuck is it then?
'Cause all of a sudden
you can't sell shit.
I brought you
all the way over here.
Do you want me to send you
back, is that it?
No, no, no, sir.
No, sir.
You get out there
and you sell this shit.
Okay.
All right?
Yup.
Sell it, and I'll have
the God damn camera on you.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, man, that killed.
Don't worry, take five.
I got it.
Hey, everybody,
I wanna introduce you
to a brand new energy drink
that you are gonna love.
It's called Thunder Muscle
and it's totally awesome!
Seriously, I just wanna try
to tell you about a-a great,
new energy drink.
Please, if I could just get--
you guys wanna take five,
please.
Uh, okay.
Thunder Muscle, oh,
it's so good and good for you.
Wait.
Just-- can I just get
two goddamn minutes
of silence, please!
Thank you.
Okay.
Like I was sayin',
Thunder Muscle,
it tastes great, chalk full
of energy and vitamins,
and science--
can we lose the bells!
Be quiet!
Show some respect!
Hey, shut the fuck up,
grandpa!
Listen to what he's saying!
Jesus Christ!
If you pussies would've had
some Thunder Muscle during
the war, we wouldn't have had
to come out and bail
your faggot asses out!
Am I right?
No?
Holy shit!
No, hey!
No, wait, wait, wait, wait!
This is a misunderstanding!
Wait, no, I'm American!
Mean, I grew up in Leeds.
Church Avenue.
But, uh,
drink Thunder Muscle!
Brent, Mr. Wilts, help!
Anyone!
This morning's Remembrance
Ceremony was interrupted
by a mentally ill American
protesting against Britain's
alleged cowardess
in all wars, ever.
Unbelievable.
Um...
Hudson, I'm just going
to pop out for a bit.
Oh, don't tell me
you're gonna leave
because of this guy.
Well, somebody's
gotta help him.
Oh, Alice.
We've only got a couple
of hours left.
Sorry, everybody,
enjoy your Vietnamese,
cafe Milan infused
torch beams.
And Rachel,
don't-don't eat the batteries.
They're not Kosher.
Alice.
Drink Thunder Muscle!
Oh, no!
Honey!
I just thought
that was terrible.
The worst film
I've ever seen.
Worst film I've ever seen.
It's a bucket of shit.
-- sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
of the season to get you
in the mood to motor...
Including classics like,
'thirty one
days of ways to save.'
'skidmarks and smokescreens?'
'kiss my resale value.'
and the timeless
'make it mine for $199.'
celebrate this
motor-tober with
a new 2011
mini Cooper
hardtop for
199$ a month.
www.tvsubtitles.net