He loves me.
He loves me not.
Once there were
three little girls.
Anushya, marushya and varushya.
Three sisters.
They had dark golden hair
and golden eyes.
Three little flowers.
They were all very beautiful.
But marushya and varushya
were the most beautiful of all.
"Where are we going, mama?"
She didn't answer me.
She knew or she didn't know,
she knew or she didn't know,
but she kept silent.
"Hurry.
Your comb, your toothbrush,
your cup and your spoon,
put them in the little bundle."
"Is that all I have left, mama?
Where are we going, mama?"
Destination unknown.
"Step up high.
It's a big step onto the train."
"Is this a train, mama?
It doesn't look like a train."
"Hold my hand tight."
"I'm holding it, mama,
as tight as I can.
There are too many people.
I can't breathe in here."
"Breathe, smell, live, dora.
Nothing else matters."
Unknown.
We didn't know
where we were going.
what was happening.
And when we got there,
we still didn't know.
And then they stood us in line
and put the numbers on our arms.
"What's that smell, mama?
That horrible smell?
That smoke,
that thick black smoke?"
She didn't answer.
"Mama.
Is that really you?"
"Dora, is that really you?"
My own mother,
and I--
I didn't even know her.
She was naked,
her head shaved.
Her beautiful hair
she used to comb
every night, gone.
"Mama...
Why did you have me?
Why did you have me, mama?
It's all your fault.
If you hadn't had me...
I wouldn't be here."
But then, always,
I was sorry.
Sing that song, mama.
The one about two Grey kittens.
Or the one about the prince
and the princess.
Sing it to me
sing it to me
so I can fall asleep.
She sang for everything
that had existed before...
Which we knew would
never exist again.
And yet, amazingly,
we still hoped.
Although we knew
there was no hope possible.
There was no hope possible.
How old were you when you went
into the concentration camp?
Just your age.
- What did you weigh at the end of the war?
- 50 pounds.
Shit.
Were you tortured?
- Did you know Anne frank?
- Did you get to meet Hitler?
- Did he ever come to the camp?
- Did you get his autograph?
Weren't you sorry you
weren't a Christian?
If you survived,
then what was so horrible?
Do you still have nightmares?
Was there anyone left
in your family besides you?
- Do you have that number on your arm?
- Yes, I do.
Can we see it?
Of course you can.
Have you ever thought
about having it removed?
What do you think?
Should I remove it?
- No, don't ever take it off.
- No.
Now, I want
to ask you a question.
Have any one of you ever
seen anyone with a number
on their arm?
Why didn't you raise your hand?
What stopped you? God, Daisy.
You don't understand. I was the
only one in the whole class who--
I know you were.
That's just why.
Everyone was staring at me.
- I could feel their eyes.
Everyone was-- - so what?
You can't keep thinking
about everyone all the time.
Who cares what they think?
You do. I know.
I wish you didn't care
so much, Daisy.
I can't help it.
You're not the only one
who's different, you know.
I know. I know, Jess.
I wish I was like you.
You're so strong.
I have to be. I'm the only girl.
You've got those five brothers.
I wish I had just one.
Instead, I only have them.
And where are those parents
of yours off to this weekend?
I don't know.
Some romantic hideaway.
They drop me off
and reappear the next day.
Hey, guess what? I know one
person that was looking at you.
- Who?
- You know.
He wasn't! He was, really?
Jess, are you sure?
Positive. I saw him.
I don't believe it.
He couldn't have been.
Jessica, you're wrong.
I mean, god,
he doesn't even know I exist.
Ah. You came early.
We left at 7:00.
They didn't even stop.
They said they were in a hurry and
they'd stop on their way back.
Well, anyway, now you're here
and we have the whole
weekend together.
They're coming in the morning.
I have a test.
Oh.
We have the whole day together.
I have to study.
I know you.
You didn't have breakfast.
What shall I make? Pancakes?
- I'm not hungry.
- When will you be?
I don't know. Maybe never.
- Look at you. You're too thin.
- don't say that.
- Once there was a little
girl-- - stop forcing me.
- Stop forcing me.
- Who's forcing?
Come on.
Give me that.
You know, I was thinking I'd
leave before they got here.
Uh-huh.
And go where?
You don't know what it's like.
You were lucky.
You weren't an only one.
- The only what?
- Child.
My friends all have millions
of brothers and sisters.
Well, at least one anyway.
I still get down on my knees, but
they'll never change their mind.
Why should they?
They have each other.
They certainly have.
How about a little
game of cards, huh?
Move.
Oh, you know something?
The first crocus is out.
A blue one.
Before anyone else's.
I don't want to go outside.
Why? What's the
matter with outside?
Just a little walk.
I don't want
to go for a little walk.
- I want to stay here.
- Why?
I thought you wanted to leave.
I'm tired, Nana. Totally tired.
Totally, hmm.
And what makes you so tired?
- School.
- Ah, school.
What's at school
to make you so tired?
- Everything.
- Everything?
Homework?
Teachers?
Friends?
Boyfriends?
Hey, girls. How's it going?
- Hey.
- Studying hard?
- Yeah.
- Math?
German.
Man, that teacher,
she's something else, huh?
Yeah, well, we all know
about you and kleiss.
It's not just me there, janebo.
What's wrong with your friend?
Can't she speak?
Or can she just read?
Daisy can talk, Tony.
Yeah? Well, you know
something, flower girl?
- Hey, knock it off, man.
- I think your friend is lying.
I don't think you
can say a single word.
Hey, she can talk.
I'm sure of it.
She just needs the right
person to talk to.
Christ. Let's get going.
Come on, let's get out of here.
And then she will,
when she wants to.
When she really wants to.
So, tell me.
What?
Something must be going on.
Nothing.
Someone told me
I have a beautiful smile.
Someone? Who's this someone?
You think that's true, Nana?
I don't know. Show me.
Oh, that's a smile?
We have a German test on Monday.
Mm. That's the famous smile?
Oh, god, I'm gonna throw up.
Oh, not before I see
that famous smile.
- I'm gonna fail. I know it.
- Again?
Well, I didn't fail
last time. I fainted.
You fainted? You were
so sure you would fail;
Instead, you just fainted.
Oh.
What's this fainting?
You never do think
you're going to pass a test.
You, who always gets as.
Not once.
Now where are you going?
Ben? Where are you?
How are you, my dear?
- Good. How are you?
- Fine.
So, mayn daisele.
Always with that head in a book.
You must be very smart.
No one I know likes to read.
They all--
Everyone thinks it's weird.
They think--
I had a friend
who read like you do.
There were no books in her
house, so I gave her mine.
We spent hours in my
grandfather's yellow bookstore.
She was my first friend.
When we went to dances together,
the boys used
to get us confused.
The boys used
She had long,
blonde hair like mine.
They thought we were sisters.
I loved that.
Only I was Jewish.
Her parents didn't like me
from the very beginning.
Once she wrote me a poem
about the yellow bookstore.
"Yellow roof. Yellow windows.
Yellow chimney to the sky.
We are standing,
forever reading,
between the yellow bookshelves.
You on one side. I on the other.
You on the right.
I on the left."
When they burned it down...
When they took
my grandfather away...
When there were no more books...
I was glad she had mine.
One day I saw her
walking down a crowded street.
So many people.
But that day, to me,
it was though
there was only her.
She was coming right toward me.
So I started walking faster.
I hadn't seen her in months.
Then I saw her eyes.
Blue.
Blue like the flowers
in the field
around my grandfather's house.
And then, Nana?
- And then?
- We have to leave.
Mr. gilman's going to town.
You always stop in the middle.
- I have to pay.
- Mr. gilman never lets you pay.
I will this time.
This time I got a surprise.
I don't care. What surprise?
- "Anna Karenina"!
- Yes.
Oh, Nana!
At last, I have it, too!
Mm. Oh.
I hear. I hear you.
I hear you, mom.
I'm not! I'm not, mom.
I'm not using a tone.
Oh, please don't put him on.
Mom, do you have to--
Hi.
Of course I heard her.
I just talked to her.
I'm not using a tone!
Why do you two always say
the exact same thing?
Books?
Not many, just a few.
About 20.
Oh, please, don't put her on.
Hi.
What?
But I still read them, mom.
I read them all the time.
I'm not too old for fairy tales.
Nana says we should never
throw our books away.
Books are stories.
Books are life.
All her books
were thrown away, mom.
I want to keep mine.
You are? Why?
What am I gonna--
Okay. Okay.
I'll do it. Okay. Bye.
- God!
- Well?
They always do that.
They're coming back tonight.
They--
I don't know.
- So?
- Mmm.
How is it?
- Good?
- It's very good.
It's great.
You want another little piece?
And they say you don't eat.
They worry.
I still give my food to the dog.
"All happy families
resemble one another,
but each unhappy family
is unhappy in its own way."
Oh, you know it by heart!
This is the way it
always should be.
No school. No homework.
No being nice to everybody.
Just read and read forever.
The way it was before you left.
Mm, daisisch.
Why did you, Nana?
Why did you leave?
Your parents and I--
Your mother--
- did you do something wrong?
- No.
But there were things
I couldn't tell, and now--
Now, Nana?
Your friend,
the one who read so much?
What happened to her?
What happened that day?
- She stopped.
- She just stood there.
I thought she's waiting for me.
She came all the way
over here, through everything,
and she's waiting for me.
I kept on walking.
Close... closer.
Another step
and I could have touched her.
When she turned
and crossed the street,
she walked slowly, deliberately.
And I watched her go.
I watched her.
Maybe she saw them
close off the wall.
And maybe she came all the
way to the ghetto to see me,
to tell me
where they were taking us,
where we were going.
Maybe they told her lies,
and maybe she believed them.
Maybe she was afraid.
Who knows, Daisy?
Close your eyes. Close them.
Don't move.
Nana, open your eyes!
Turn around!
Nana.
Look, I found it. I knew
just where to look.
Look, Nana. It's pretty. Look.
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh. Who picks the crocus? Hmm?
Ethan, even his name
is gorgeous.
God, he's so cute.
He must be the cutest
boy in the whole school.
Everyone practically faints
when he walks into assembly.
When I'm near him,
in class, in the lunchroom,
at lacrosse, even on the street
outside his house
when he's not there,
something swallows me up
or grabs me,
my throat, my chest,
my whole insides,
so that I can't think
or hear or breathe.
And I don't want to.
Let the whole world disappear
so I can think about him,
be with him in my mind.
It's like I'm blinded
to everything else.
I had to watch. I had to.
I saw him lean over her,
his hair on her cheek,
his hand on her knee.
And then I saw him
kiss her on the mouth.
I thought my heart
would split open.
Who is this boy?
He's got this blond hair
and these...
Incredible eyes.
Like the ocean, Nana.
They're blue one minute
like the ocean, Nana.
and green the next.
They're incredible.
Incredible eyes.
He's president
of the senior class.
His father's an architect, so he's
traveled around all over Europe.
He grew up in england.
And he has this
totally dreamy accent.
And Nana, he's so smart.
He gets a-pluses in everything.
He's captain
of the lacrosse team.
He's...
Nana, are you listening to me?
Of course I'm listening.
The what team?
Lacrosse. It's a game.
I was saying he's--
- He's what?
- Perfect.
There's not one thing
wrong with him.
It's like he just... shines.
"So clare bear had
to glare and swear,
'give me a square of your pear.
If we're to live in this lair
here beneath the stair,
we must learn to share,
especially pear.
But if you dare tear
your pear and not share;
Just wear that smile
with pompous style,
just wear that smile
I'll bite your head off.'"
- Whoo!
- Excellent, Ethan.
Great job. Who would've thought a
bear had so many sides to him?
It was about this bear.
This bear that ate pears.
It was really funny.
It was hysterical.
Everyone laughed.
No one laughed when I read mine.
Let's hear from Daisy. What poem
have you written for us today?
"The first time
that I went there,
there was silence all around
and your street was almost empty
and the sun beat on the ground.
And since then I keep on going.
Something pulls me, so I go,
though I don't
want you to see me.
I don't want you to know.
For I know you'll never love me.
I know you'll never care.
But still I can't help going,
for the only place
I want to be is there.
For the only place
Yes, there. Oh, there."
It was awful standing there,
like I was naked.
And the poem was naked too, every
word, like it was branding me.
After class,
no one talked to me.
They didn't even look at me.
God, I wanted to die
for having read that poem.
I want to read it. Where is it?
I threw it out.
- What?
- I thought he hated me.
Why shouldn't he like you?
Nana, he's so normal.
Normal?
Why should you be normal?
It's not
the most important thing.
Oh, yes, it is. I know it is.
You know it is. Absolutely.
- You don't need to be normal.
- But I want to be, Nana.
I have to be.
Hey, wait up! Hey!
Listen, I'd really like
to talk to you...
About that poem.
You see, you should not
have thrown it out.
How about tonight
after lacrosse?
I've seen you there.
Haven't I?
I can't tonight. I have someth--
How about tomorrow morning?
Early?
- How early?
- 6:00.
6:00 in the morning? He's crazy.
Hi.
Are you scared of everything?
It's like you're gonna
break or something if I--
That poem was
about me, wasn't it?
No.
I mean... not really.
Well, it sure sounded like me.
Who was it,
if it wasn't about me?
It wasn't about anybody.
Come here.
Sad eyes. Where'd you
get such sad eyes?
She loves me.
She loves me not.
She loves--
Hey, flower girl!
Scared I'll pull
your petals off?
I'm asking you, who is this boy?
He's right. Last year everyone
talked about running away.
Not me.
I can't even say shit or fuck
without getting scared.
- What did you say?
- I can't--
I can't even say them.
What was that? What what?
Shit. Fuck.
- I can't hear you.
- Shit! Fuck!
Oh, yes, now I hear you!
I never hear those words.
- How come? Everyone says them.
- Not around here.
Please, say them for me again.
- What?
- Come on. Say them.
Oh. Come on, Daisy. Please!
Daisy. Say them!
Say them. Say them.
Say them.
Wh--
He's never gonna come.
I know it.
He's never gonna be there.
I wrecked it.
I wrecked everything
in that coffee shop.
And he'd like you.
I know he would.
If he ever got to know you,
he'd love you.
Guess who.
I always knew you
talked to someone.
I just didn't know
he'd be a dog.
Um...
Howie, this is Ethan;
Ethan, Howard.
Well, he wants to go
for a run, don't you?
Don't you want to
run with Ethan?
Well, what are we
waiting for, man?
Come on. Let's go.
So...
We're finally here.
Together, I mean.
Isn't that what you wanted?
I mean, every morning,
the street...
The secret tree.
The one you thought I didn't
see you hiding behind.
Your face.
The way you look at me in class.
The way you always look at me
the way you always look at me
every time you see me.
Oh, maybe I was wrong.
Maybe I just imagined
all those things.
Tell me I imagined them and
we'll forget all about this.
- No, you didn't imagine anything.
- Oh.
She speaks to me.
At last.
So you do want to be here
with me?
Say it.
Yes.
I do.
More than anything.
You're not sorry you came?
I'm not sorry.
All those times on my
street, why didn't--
Why didn't you say
something? Anything?
Why didn't you just talk to me?
Girls talk to me all the time.
Oh, but I did.
You did? When? I don't remember.
In the poem.
Promise me something?
Don't be afraid of me.
Say you won't be.
I'd hate it if you were.
I won't be. I promise.
Trust me.
I won't hurt you.
I know.
I couldn't. I wouldn't know how.
Daisy.
It suits you.
You really are a flower.
Like petals.
Flowers break, you know.
You have to treat them gently.
Come on. Let's go.
Whoo-hoo!
No.
- Have some.
- Right here.
Wasn't that fun, Howard?
Didn't you have a good time?
I knew you would.
I knew you'd like Ethan.
I knew you'd love him.
Wasn't that the best day
of your whole life?
It was of mine.
It really was.
Well, there'll be more days.
Yeah, but not like this.
This was the first.
♪ I had to escape ♪
♪ the city was sticky
and cruel ♪
♪ maybe I should have
called you first ♪
♪ but I was dying
to get to you ♪
♪ I was dreaming while I drove ♪
♪ the long straight road
ahead, uh-huh ♪
♪ to taste your sweet kisses,
your arms open wide ♪
♪ this fever for you
is just burning me up inside ♪
♪ I drove all night ♪
♪ to get to you ♪
♪ is that all right? ♪
♪ I drove all night ♪
♪ crept in your room ♪
♪ woke you from your sleep ♪
♪ to make love to you ♪
♪ is that all right? ♪
♪ I drove all night ♪
♪ what in this world keeps
us from tearin' apart? ♪
♪ No matter where I go, I hear ♪
♪ no matter where I go, I hear ♪
♪ the beating of your heart ♪
♪ I think about you
when the night ♪
♪ is cold and dark ♪
♪ no one can know me
the way that you do ♪
♪ nothing erases
this feeling between-- ♪
It's them.
I bet they changed
their minds again.
I bet they're on
their way right now.
Talk to them, Nana.
Make them understand.
One more night.
Just give me one more night.
Oh, sashyenka, is that you?
Tonight?
I thought you were coming
for her in--
But why not?
It's only one more night.
Oh. Another German test.
But I can help.
Of course I can.
Believe me, it's not as if
I've forgotten my German.
Ah.
She reads too much.
I read "Anna Karenina"
when I was 12.
I know there's a suicide.
Fine, fine, fine.
We read something else.
She has another book here.
I know you'll be in a hurry.
She'll be ready.
No pancakes. No maple syrup.
She'll do her homework.
Her German. What else?
I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm not using a tone. What tone?
Oh! I didn't know she used one.
I don't know anything
about tones.
All right, all right.
Sashyenka, see you tomorrow.
Dobranoc.
♪ Daisy, Daisy ♪
♪ Give me your answer true ♪
♪ I'm half crazy
all for the love of you ♪
♪ It won't be
a stylish marriage ♪
♪ I can't afford a carriage ♪
♪ But you'll look so sweet
upon the seat ♪
♪ but you'll look so sweet
♪ of a bicycle built for two. ♪
"Deutsch mit Emil."
Lesson 12, Nana.
The overnight hike.
Family.
You say the German and
I'll give you the English.
- Fine. Die familie.
- Family.
Das butterbrot.
Sandwich.
Das schmetterlingsnetz.
Das schmetter--
Don't tell me. I'll get it.
Das schmetterlingsnetz.
- Das schmetterlingsnetz.
- Shh.
- Sunset.
- Butterfly net.
Der sonnenuntergang.
Oh, god. That's Sunset.
Das feuer.
Fire.
- Der rauch.
- Smoke.
- Der weg.
- Road.
- Finden.
- Find.
- Folgen.
- Follow.
- Fuhren.
- What?
- I can't hear you.
- Fuhren!
- Lead.
- Schnell. Schneller.
- Fast. Faster.
- Links.
- Left. Go left.
- Rechts.
- Right. To the right.
Links. Rechts.
Rechts.
- Links.
- Rechts.
Links. Rechts.
Nana?
Nana, I'm dead.
Ach so, mein engel.
Stop speaking German.
You never speak German.
Aber du wolltest.
Okay, that's enough.
Next stay, we'll do more. Maybe.
Yeah! Yeah!
No more sad eyes.
No more. No more.
- Know what?
- What?
- They're still sad.
- They are not.
- They are?
- Definitely.
They always give you away.
Why do you like me?
Why do I like you?
First of all because you're--
And 'cause you're--
And a little bit--
And sometimes you're--
But most of all--
Uh!
"All happy families
resemble one another,
but each unhappy family
is unhappy in its own--"
you know something? My
grandmother gave me this book.
- It's her favorite book in the whole world.
- Oh, yeah?
Your grandmother this.
Your grandmother that.
I never heard someone talk about
their grandmother so much.
So tell me...
When do I get to meet this
famous grandmother of yours?
Or don't you think
she'd like me?
Remember the day that woman
came and spoke to the class?
What woman?
What are you talking about?
You know, she talked about
the concentration camps
and everything?
Uh, that woman. Yeah.
- Well, my grandmother--
- Again? You're kidding me.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Your grandmother what?
She is one.
One what?
One of the people
who was in the camps.
One of those?
One of those people?
And, like, all those things
we heard about--
All those slides,
those stories--
- Yeah.
- They happened to her.
Wow. Really?
She had this friend,
this beautiful friend.
- She loved her so much.
- Yeah?
They were always together,
all the time.
But then in the end,
when she was in the ghetto
and everything,
and when they came
to take her away--
Don't you get kind of de--
Depressed talking
about concentration camps
and stuff like that?
I mean, like, we're sitting here
talking about death,
for god's sake.
Come on. Lighten up.
Let's get ice cream.
And then we'll rent
a video or something.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
I can't believe it.
I just can't believe it.
Why would someone do
something like that?
Why, Jess? I don't understand.
They're bastards, that's why.
They can't help themselves.
Why me, Jess?
Why not you?
I've gotta go back
in there and take it off.
- No, wait.
- What for?
I don't want anybody to see it.
Nobody can see it, Jess.
Please, I've gotta get it
off that locker.
I'll get it off. I don't want
you looking at it again.
No.
No, it's mine.
It was meant for me.
- "Is this a train, mama?
- It doesn't look like a train."
Another step,
I could have touched her.
- "Hold my hand tight."
- "I'm holding it, mama."
Maybe they told her lies.
There are too many people.
I can't breathe in here.
Breathe, dora.
Nothing else matters.
Unknown.
Remember when I was little
and I asked you?
Mm. You were so tiny.
We were having a bath together.
"What's that, Nana?
Why do you wear that?
What's that on your arm?"
"Are you sure you didn't
do anything wrong
to make them do that to you?"
Let me see it, Nana.
Show it to me.
"A." "A" is for Auschwitz.
Oswiecim.
A24839.
Mm.
Eins, zwei, drei, vier...
- Funf.
- Fimpf. Oh, fimpf. Fumpf.
- I can never get that "fumpf."
- Funf.
Are you sure you're warm enough?
You know I can't sleep
without them.
- Nana, don't go.
- Who's going?
One. Tell me just one.
- Oh, Daisy!
- Come on. Tell me about them.
Once...
Once there were
three little girls.
Anushya, marushya and varushya.
Three sisters.
Anushya was the oldest.
She was just my age.
And marushya and varushya,
the little ones, the twins--
They wore white sailor suits and
got into mischief all the time.
They had dark, golden hair
and golden eyes.
Three little flowers.
They were all very beautiful.
But marushya and varushya...
Were the most beautiful of all.
They lived in a house with rickety
windows and rickety doors,
and they slept
in a small, rickety bed.
And they slept
A great wall surrounded
their house,
a wall which
they could not go beyond.
Go on.
Early one morning,
their mother and father
woke anushya and said,
"quick, take the little
ones' hands and run, run,
for here, it is no longer safe.
Follow the stream
that flows past our house,
and it will take you
through a crack in the wall.
And it will take you
Run all day till the stream
turns into a river,
and the river turns
into the sea.
And there, in the dark,
a boat will be waiting
to take you to a safe place,
the place
where we all shall meet."
Yes, tell me.
Fast, faster they ran
till they saw the sea...
With a small boat waiting.
They had almost reached it.
They were almost there
when a shadow overtook them,
they were almost there
small at first
but growing larger,
till like magic
it turned into an angel
before them.
They drew back,
for surely this was the angel
of their dream.
They would've
known him anywhere.
Tall and beautiful he was,
with shining black hair
and pale white skin.
He smiled at them
and held out his hands.
And they saw he wore gloves.
White gloves.
- And boots.
- Black boots.
And he carried
a magical shining wand.
The wand.
He couldn't come and get
me, could he, Nana?
He couldn't come
inside my nightmares?
Of course not.
There's no way in the world
that he could come and get you.
I haven't done anything.
No, you haven't done anything.
Go on. You have
to finish this time.
The black boots.
The magical shining wand.
In that wand, he held all
the power in the world.
The power over life
and death itself.
Do you have enough to eat,
little children?
Do you have enough to drink?
Oh, surely, surely
they had nothing to fear.
For surely he had come
to save them.
And he looked down on them
and stroked their hair
and said...
- Do you not know me?
- "Do you not know me?"
I am I'ange de la mort,
malach hamovess--
The angel of death.
Come with me, and I will
take you to your parents.
Come with me,
and you will be safe.
And marushya and varushya,
the little ones, the twins,
looked up at him with hope.
And he laid his arm upon them,
separating them from anushya.
And as I felt them slip away,
and as I felt them slip away,
I held even more tightly
onto their thin little hands.
I let go. I let go and gazed
at their golden hair and eyes.
- And it seemed to me they
were like two-- - flowers.
Two flowers just ready
to be picked.
What happened to anushya?
Oh, anushya.
Mayn daisele.
Anushya is still here.
Two flowers.
Ready to be picked.
Nana!
Uh, just a little
something that's come up.
Nothing serious.
Custard?
Oh. Vanilla custard.
How did you think of it?
What an imagination.
- Don't tell. Please.
- I really can't go into it now.
Please, Jessica, you promised.
We're having a special assembly today.
don't worry.
Oh, my god, you told him
already, didn't you?
I don't believe it.
Why? Why, Jess?
I had to. I knew you wouldn't.
♪ Bring me my chariot of fire ♪
♪ I will not cease
from mental fight ♪
♪ Nor shall my sword
sleep in my hand ♪
♪ Till we have built Jerusalem ♪
♪ In england's green
and pleasant land. ♪
Before we go on with
our usual Friday assembly,
I wish to bring up an incident.
A series of incidents, in fact,
which, it shames me to say--
Which, it shames me to say--
It should shame us all--
Occurred recently at our school.
- What's he talking about?
- A profanation.
Because it means even here,
even at hunt,
where we think of ourselves
as sheltered, shielded,
how can such things happen?
We owe an apology
to you, the innocent ones.
You who may be different,
you who may be different,
but who must be made to feel
exactly the same
as the rest of us.
Coming here today,
I did not wish
to name the victims;
Neither to name the
perpetrators of these crimes,
for surely that is
what they are.
And I am certain
that each of you,
victim and perpetrator,
knows in your heart
exactly who you are.
But, in order for such incidents
but, in order for such incidents
never to be repeated,
such as the vilification
of one's name,
the desecration
of one's personal property,
I am convinced it is
for your own good
and the good of us all
that when I call your names,
I want you to stand
and make yourself known.
- Oh, my god, what's--
- Daisy. Daisy.
Do you have enough
to eat, little children?
Do you have enough to drink?
Daisy?
Oh, man, that fainting.
That was no act. That was real.
I mean, like, you fainted
in front of the whole school.
Takes guts.
- Why do you do it?
- I don't know. I--
I've never seen someone faint
before, not in my whole life.
Everyone I know is so normal.
Yeah, well, you can't help it.
- What? What do you mean?
- What?
You know, you're an only child.
You're so sensitive
and everything.
I wish I weren't.
How do you think she got
an "a" in gym, dude?
The girl can hardly
throw a softball.
And she never even showed up.
- She was never there.
- She's off smoking in the bathroom.
Good point.
- A book!
- A book! Can you--
We're in the middle
of central park,
and she's reading a book.
You want to tell me
what's up with that?
- Yeah, what's up with you, man?
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
- I'm the same old guy.
Yeah, maybe, but, um--
You know, we never see
too much of you anymore.
- Yeah. You're always with that "reader."
- So?
So what we're saying, eth,
is it's really not cool.
Watch out. You might
catch what she's got.
What's that?
Weirdness.
- Aw, look at that.
- Mm, look at that.
Look at 'em all, eth.
Every girl on that field wants
your jock, you know that?
You could have your pick.
Your entire pick.
Yeah, and look who he picks?
Another Anne frank.
Flower girl.
You're here.
You were waiting for me?
Always wait for me, will you?
Always.
Always. I promise.
- Come.
- Where are we going?
There. Up there to the castle.
Look, it's like a fairy tale.
Fairy tales aren't real.
They're just make-believe.
Oh, no.
- Come on.
- You're crazy.
You know that? You're
absolutely out of your mind.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
You're trembling.
Am I?
All over.
Look at you.
Those eyes again.
Say it.
What?
You know.
Say it.
I want you to say it to me.
Ethan.
Hey.
No.
Why?
Not now. Not yet.
But when?
- You just--
- No, I know.
I know. I just--
When?
Wait for me.
Please.
- You know something?
- Huh?
This is my favorite place
in the whole city.
Your favorite?
Wow.
Even when I was little,
my grandmother used to--
I mean, I used to come here
all the time by myself.
Uh-huh.
Lots of people don't
even know it's here.
This incredible, magical place
right in the middle
of New York City.
Sometimes I can't--
I can't even really
believe it exists.
Can you believe it?
No. I mean--
Not really.
No, I mean, it's really great.
Sometimes I even come and ride
with all the little kids
and everything.
And now--
Now?
Well, now I'm here
in a different way.
I mean, now I'm here with you.
And, like, I can't
really believe it.
'Cause it's, like--
I don't know.
It's sort of like a dream.
A dream. Yeah.
Yeah, so what do you guys think
about that Douglas, huh?
Useless book to read.
I haven't even started.
- Well, you got all tomorrow.
- If he sleeps off tonight.
Uh, "Tess of the doberdolls."
- I can't even get the name straight.
- It's dooberdogs.
"Tess of the dooberdogs."
D'urbervilles.
"Tess of the d'urbervilles."
- Whatever.
- Yeah, who cares?
Why do I have to read
about some stupid whore?
How can you say that?
She was abandoned, alone. Haven't
you ever felt like that?
I mean, don't you understand?
What else could she do?
- Back off there, girl.
- No doubt. Relax, Daisy.
She wasn't a whore.
She's not a whore.
Relax.
We're only kidding.
- Hey! Look who's here.
- Hey!
- How you doin'?
- Dance time?
- This is her lucky day.
You're joking, right?
I'll flip you for her.
Yeah, right.
Do you want some head
or some tail?
Tails.
Hi.
God, these are great.
They're just great.
I could eat 1,000 of them.
Well, you're getting close.
You always say I'm too thin,
but if I lived with you,
I'd get fat.
Totally fat. Don't you think so?
Don't you think so, Nana?
You know what I think?
I think it's time
for a nice game of cards.
Go fish.
- I love this game.
- Me, too.
Do you have any fives?
Hey.
I go again, right?
But why? What did I do wrong?
Nothing. You never
do anything wrong.
You're perfect.
Do you have any queens?
If you had them before,
why didn't you ask me before?
You knew I wanted queens.
But I don't understand.
What's wrong with me?
Nothing. You're-- nothing.
Do you have any nines?
I hate this game.
I don't wanna play.
Fine. I'll go and make
myself a nice cup of tea.
No! Pick. Go ahead.
- What?
- You're just so--
You're too intense.
It's embarrassing sometimes.
Go on. Ask me.
- Do you have any--
- Any what?
If you win, I'll kill you.
Maybe we could just be friends.
Gotta go.
I'll be late otherwise.
Any kings?
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you!
I hate it here! I hate it!
You'll see. You'll all see.
What will we see?
You know.
Don't you see there's
nothing I can do right?
Nothing, nothing, nothing!
Don't touch me.
Get away from me!
Everyone says
I don't really look it.
What?
You know. Like I am one.
One Jew.
Like I'm Jewish.
Jew, Jew, animal,
vegetable, mineral, Jew.
How can they tell?
Can they smell one?
But not you, Daisy.
We'll always love you!
Except for the eyes.
The sadness in the eyes.
That's the one thing
that gives it away.
I don't want to be chosen, Nana,
like marushya and varushya!
I don't want to be taken away!
Oh, Nana,
talk to me.
Say something.
Once there was a Nana
and a Daisy.
Oh, Nana.
Please, won't you say anything?
Daisy!
I don't know what
makes me do those things,
makes me say those things.
But I only do them with you,
Nana, only with you.
I feel so ugly, Nana.
What are you talking about?
You're a beautiful girl.
- I know what I look like.
- Silly Daisy.
Don't call me that.
I hate that name.
It's a beautiful name
and a beautiful flower,
a flower that grows in the wild.
He loves me. He loves me not.
He loves me.
He loves me not, Nana.
He loves me not.
And all that's left is that horrible
little thing in the middle.
It's ugly.
A Daisy with
all its petals gone.
It's a survivor, a yellow
sun, a yellow star.
Do you know what people say?
They say it's a difficult age.
- Mine, you mean?
- The moods.
That's what they talk about.
The ups and downs.
I wonder if it's true.
I'm tired.
Really tired.
- You are?
- Totally.
Maybe we should
take a little walk?
You mean, go out?
I don't want to go out.
I don't want to move.
- I'm fatigued.
- You're what?
I'm fatigued, fatigued.
I'm making pancakes,
thousands of them.
I can't eat. Don't force me.
Probably I'll never eat again.
- And you know something?
- What?
- I'm thinking of running away.
- Somewhere I know?
Where, Nana? Where would you go?
Oh, daisele, a little town
with winding streets
and winding hills.
Everywhere green except for
the deep blue of the sky,
everywhere green except for
the lakes,
the wallpaper in my room.
And the singing,
the singing everywhere.
All that singing stopped.
And the bookshop was yellow,
bright yellow,
like the heart of a Daisy.
And before anyone came
in the morning,
there was just my grandfather.
My grandfather and me.
- Mmm.
♪ Daisy, Daisy,
give me your answer true ♪
♪ I'm half crazy
all for the love of you ♪
♪ It won't be
a stylish marriage ♪
♪ I can't afford a carriage ♪
♪ But you'll look sweet
upon the seat ♪
♪ Of a bicycle built for two. ♪
Don't be afraid
of kissing someone,
of loving someone,
afraid of life, even of death.
Afraid of saying those words.
- What words?
- You know.
Nana.
Oh, Nana.
Keep me with you. Keep me.
I can't. You know I can't.
Please, Nana. Please!
Nothing will happen, will it,
before I come back?
Everything will
happen to you, Daisy.
Everything.
And then you'll come back.
You can always come back.
Nana.
It's all right, my Daisy.
It's all right, mayn daisele.
Go, go!
I'll be here.