Live from the Opry studios
in Nashville, Tennessee,
make welcome David King.
♪ I cannot hear
I have no sight ♪
♪ Dark is near
And your blinding light ♪
♪ Can you hear me
When I cry? ♪
♪ Catch me when I fall ♪
♪ But I can't hold on ♪
Take it away, boys.
The words of the Teacher,
son of David.
Killer job, man.
Killer job.
Great show, baby.
This teaching is a light.
Yeah, man, now you're talking.
Good show.
Correction and instruction
are the way to life,
keeping you away
from your neighbor's wife.
Go.
Do not go near her door.
Where you going, boy?
Keep to a path far from her.
Do not lust in your heart
after her beauty
or be captivated by her eyes.
Can a man scoop fire
into his lap
without his clothes
being burned?
Can a man stand on hot coals
without his feet being scorched?
Another man's wife preys
on your very life.
Hey, baby, you okay in there?
No one who touches her
will go unpunished.
I looked and saw all the evil
that was taking place
under the sun.
I declared that the dead
are happier than the living.
But better than both is the one
who has never been born,
who has not seen the evil
that is done under the sun.
Hello.
Jealousy arouses
a husband's fury.
He will not accept
any compensation,
however great it is.
- No! No! No!
- Daddy.
Don't leave!
A man who commits adultery
has no sense.
His shame will never
be wiped away.
But
And do you, David,
take Bethany...
the one who confesses
and renounces sin finds mercy.
...to love and to cherish
for better or for worse
from this day forward?
I do.
As you do not know the path
of the wind
or how the body is formed
in a mother's womb,
you cannot understand
the work of God,
Watch his head.
The maker of all things.
Hi, Jed.
Who knows what is good
for a person
during the few meaningless days
that they pass through
like a shadow?
Give me a hammer, Jed.
Who can tell them
what will happen under the sun
after they are gone?
Hold on a second. Right there.
Move that finger up there.
I've been doing that every time.
No one knows
when their hour will come.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Generations come...
generations go...
but the earth remains forever.
What has been will be again
and what has been done
will be done again.
There is nothing new
under the sun.
I have seen all things done
All of them are meaningless,
a chasing after wind.
♪ I was born the son of a king ♪
♪ Princes die
Over petty things ♪
♪ Yeah, our families
They're about war ♪
♪ You'd think that we could
Settle the score ♪
♪ But the consequences stay ♪
♪ Yeah, the consequences stay ♪
♪ Yeah, I was born
The son of a king ♪
♪ You don't know what that means
Do you? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Yeah, you might say
It's living a dream ♪
♪ Somehow dreams have a way
Of coming true ♪
♪ Like you don't want them to ♪
♪ And to the God in heaven ♪
♪ Give me the wisdom
To see this through ♪
♪ Love is a choice
We're making ♪
♪ But even if it's not
What we choose ♪
♪ I'm still the son of a king ♪
♪ You can say it was love ♪
♪ I don't know
What I think of that ♪
Stan, we will sell more albums
if you get me
playing bigger venues.
This place sells out
at like 18 people.
People come
to see you for one reason.
They loved your dad, okay?
Now, until you find heart
or inspiration
or something to sing about,
you're just gonna
be David King's kid.
A little parting gift
from old Stanager, okay?
There's a vineyard
over in Sharon, all right?
They do a festival every fall.
They need a musician.
Pays pretty well. It's only
30 minutes away from here.
You don't have to pay me.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, I'm serious.
I'm a bridge.
I'm on fire.
You are brilliant.
- Appreciate that.
- Just go, Stan.
I'm happy to leave.
In his heart,
a man plans his course,
but the Lord directs his steps.
♪ It comes right out
Of the mountains ♪
♪ Down to the valley below ♪
♪ Sweeps out across
The bluegrass ♪
♪ It gets down in your soul ♪
♪ It might come as a whisper ♪
♪ That cuts right through
The north ♪
Jed?
Are you Jed King?
- Yes.
- I'm Rose Jordan.
Um, we spoke on the phone.
Right, right. Yeah.
- It's nice to meet you.
- This is your place then?
My dad's.
It's beautiful.
Well, he'll wanna know
you're here, so...
- Come on. There we go.
- Old piece of junk.
- Daddy?
- Yeah.
- Jed King is here.
- Who?
The singer.
I'm sorry to interrupt. I'm Jed.
Sheppard Jordan.
- It's great to meet you.
- This is a beautiful place.
- You David King's kid?
- Yes, sir.
Uh-huh. Hon, show him
to the stage.
I got work to do.
Nice to meet you.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Good to meet you.
- Uh-huh.
Dad's really sweet.
He's just a little stressed.
No, it's fine.
Who did he say your father was?
David King.
So he's a singer too?
You don't know who he is?
Oh, I'm sorry, I don't know
anything about music.
Please, don't apologize.
It's a good thing, believe me.
Hey, Rosie.
Eddie.
- What are you doing here?
- Tasting wine.
It's free wine tasting, right?
It's what the paper said.
- Right.
- This is Kristen.
Yeah, I remember.
How are you?
The wine is really good.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
Who'd have thunk? I mean,
Kentucky? Heh. Right? Heh.
So are you two...?
- No, we... This is, uh...
- Yes. Don't be shy. Don't be shy.
- Jed King.
- Jed King, as in David King?
See? Yes.
You're hotter than your dad.
- Thank you.
- Well, there you go.
Better than your dad
at something.
How's your dad?
I don't know.
Why don't you go ask him?
He looks busy.
No, no, I'm sure
he'd love to talk to you.
No, maybe later.
Excuse me.
It was nice meeting you again.
- Sorry. It's this way.
- He's a winner.
Here you are.
Just make yourself at home.
Thanks.
And sorry about Eddie.
He's a jerk.
You deserve better.
Better than a guy who'll dump me
for not sleeping with him.
I just don't know
if "better" exists anymore.
Wow.
- I just said that, didn't I?
- No, it's okay.
When I get done playing,
and you get done
with whatever you have to do,
you wanna hang out?
Look, you seem like
a really nice guy.
- A nice... Ow. That hurts.
- Heh.
Look, it's only that
I just met you.
Right.
I don't even like him,
but it still kind of kills
to see him with her.
Well, I'd hate to see you die.
Sorry.
- Uh, good luck, Jed.
- Thank you.
"I'd hate to see you die"?
Thank you, everyone.
You're in for
a real treat tonight.
Give a warm round of applause
for Louisville's Jed King.
Nice banjo, Jed.
Kentucky.
Ha, ha. Right?
♪ Let me cut right
To the chase ♪
♪ Rose
When I see your beautiful face ♪
♪ I can't help but ask myself ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ And if I didn't need
This gig ♪
♪ I swear I'd flip my lid ♪
♪ And already Eddie
Would be nursing a black eye ♪
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Oh, yeah?
- ♪ It seems like such a waste ♪
♪ To let him in the way ♪
♪ Of what you and I might have ♪
- ♪ One day ♪
- Ha-ha-ha.
♪ I don't want to quit you
Baby ♪
♪ I ain't gonna split you
Whoo!
♪ I'd rather give you up
Than watch you die ♪
♪ I don't want to ♪
♪ Yeah, I know loss hurts
More than a little ♪
♪ But he splits you down
The middle ♪
♪ It's time to give good love
A try ♪
Hey!
♪ Yeah, it would be such a pity
Just to split you fifty-fifty ♪
♪ Especially some guy
Who makes fun of my banjo ♪
♪ Shows up at a thing
With another girl ♪
♪ When he knows
You're gonna be here ♪
♪ Is scared of your dad
And breaks up ♪
♪ With the most beautiful girl ♪
♪ For the dumbest reason
In the world kind of guy ♪
♪ Hey, Rose
You and I will bloom ♪
♪ In no time ♪
- Thank you for coming.
- Thanks.
That was an awesome show.
Thanks, appreciate it.
God bless.
Hi.
Wow.
That's really nice actually.
Here, I have something
for you too.
Oh. Yeah, this is great.
Thanks.
Really?
I think so.
But like I said,
I don't know
anything about music.
Everybody knows something
about music.
Very little, in my case.
What's your favorite
Beatles song?
Everybody has a favorite.
"Strawberry Fields Forever,"
"Hey Jude."
Well, I've always really liked
"Turn! Turn! Turn!"
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
- What? I love that song.
- I love that song too.
It's just not the Beatles.
- Yeah, it is.
- No, it's the Byrds.
- You're thinking of the Byrds.
- No.
- Agree to disagree.
- No, you'd still be wrong.
The lyrics are in the Bible.
Can we agree
that God wrote them?
Absolutely.
Too bad my song
isn't on here. Heh.
Never had my own song before.
You're probably gonna ask me
out again then, huh?
You know what? I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked
you out like that.
No, that's all right.
Not without talking
to your dad first.
- What?
- He seems like the kind of guy
that would appreciate
being asked.
For my hand in marriage maybe,
but one date?
We're gonna have more
than one date.
How do you know?
I know.
He's busy with clean-up.
Monday?
- Monday.
- Good.
You're gonna need a day
to prepare.
Mr. King,
I don't know you.
That's true, sir.
And you can call me Jed,
if you like.
So, what makes you think I
should let you date my daughter?
At the very least,
Mr. Jordan,
you know that I'm the kind of
guy that's willing
to ask a very intimidating man
if I could date his daughter.
No, that says more about me
than it does you.
I just want you to know
that I respect you
and that I respect Rose.
You sing about God in
your songs, don't you?
I sing about things
that I'm passionate about.
- Like Rose?
- You heard that, I guess.
I love Rose a lot.
And I have always
tried to protect her
from certain
kinds of men out there.
Just to be honest,
men like your daddy.
He sang about God too,
didn't he?
I know he made mistakes,
Mr. Jordan,
but he learned from them.
So did I.
I won't repeat them.
So I'm not gonna lie,
your dad freaked me out
just a little bit.
Well, you're gonna have
to tell me all about it,
because I wasn't listening.
- Oh, no?
- Nope.
Okay. Uh...
Well, since you
weren't listening,
I'll give you the highlights.
He loves you a lot,
and he has quite the collection
going on in that room.
Ha, ha. Yeah.
- It wasn't great.
- Heh, heh.
So, yeah, I was basically raised
by my father and two brothers.
But they weren't cut out
for wine making, so they bailed.
You think you'll ever bail?
No.
No, I love it.
Yours skipped like 10 times.
- Well...
- How do you do that?
My dad, he was legendary
at slinging these things.
Lethal, some would say.
I don't know. I mean,
I guess I can find a career to
help me pay for all the stuff
I'll eventually throw away,
or leave to someone else,
but family's forever.
Right?
Agree to disagree.
And side-arm it, right?
And flick your wrist at the end.
Whoo! Ha-ha-ha!
There you go.
I did it.
You did it.
You have stolen my heart.
You have stolen my heart
with one glance of your eyes.
Oh, my goodness.
I don't think ice cream was such
a good idea. I'm freezing.
You done?
- Here, I got it.
- Brr!
- Okay.
- Wait right there.
♪ You made me love you
And I did not wanna do it ♪
- Come here.
- What?
- Let's dance.
- Oh. Ha-ha-ha.
Come on.
Come on, it'll warm you up.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
You are such a schemer. Heh.
♪ Give me, give me
What I cry for ♪
♪ You got the kind of kisses
I would die for ♪
Show me your face.
Let me hear your voice.
For your voice is sweet,
and your face is lovely.
Ice cream was a good idea.
♪ You made me love you ♪
How delightful is your love?
How much more pleasing
is your love than wine?
Remember when we broke
the windows in this old house?
This is what I wished for.
This one's my favorite.
I've always loved it.
♪ I love you truly ♪
♪ Truly, dear ♪
You know,
I don't normally do this,
but here's one you might know.
♪ I cannot hear ♪
♪ I have no sight ♪
♪ Dark is near
Blinding light ♪
♪ Can you hear me
When I crawl? ♪
♪ Catch me when I fall ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't hold on ♪
You were really great tonight.
I'm glad you think so.
- Everyone thought so.
- Well...
That last song, well,
people really liked that one.
- Oh, yeah.
- What?
That was my dad's song.
Oh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't be, it's fine.
It's a good song.
You know, sometimes...
I think about
letting it go. Music.
I look at you...
tonight...
under the stars.
I mean, look.
I see God here.
If you could ask God
for anything,
and you know he'd say yes...
I'd want to be wise.
That way I can live right...
and really live.
And if I did sing,
it'd only be because
I had something to say.
You should just ask for that.
I won't listen. Go ahead.
God, I wanna be wise.
Please.
You feel any different?
You think your dad would let me
build a chapel here
at the vineyard?
Like the one in your book
with the sticky note thing.
Why would you want to?
So I could marry you.
I'll ask your dad.
Build the chapel.
Marry me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah!
Let me do this.
Let me build you a chapel.
How long will it take?
- A year.
- Oh. Uh-uh.
I can't wait that long.
♪ I love you truly ♪
♪ Truly, dear ♪
♪ Life with its sorrows ♪
Like a lily among thorns
is my darling
among the young women.
♪ Fades into dreams ♪
♪ When I feel you near ♪
I am my beloved's.
♪ Oh, I love you truly ♪
And my beloved is mine.
♪ Truly, dear ♪
How beautiful you are, my love.
How beautiful.
Your eyes are doves.
You are altogether beautiful,
my darling.
There is no flaw in you.
You're so beautiful.
I want you to know that.
♪ Oh, I love you truly ♪
♪ Truly, dear ♪
♪ I've been waiting on you
To come along ♪
♪ Seeing notes on a page ♪
♪ But not the song
Had a hole in my... ♪
- Hey.
You're up early.
I had a dream.
- A dream?
- Yeah.
About what?
Your new song.
- My new song?
- Mm-hm.
- Mm.
- It's good.
- You wanna hear it?
- Mm...
- I feel you should hear it.
- Maybe later.
Did you have something
else in mind?
Mm-hm. Yeah.
Something.
Me too.
You know what?
"Something"
is gonna be incredible
after you hear this song.
Trust me,
it'll take two seconds.
All right.
Sit down.
♪ I've been waiting on you
To come along ♪
♪ Seeing notes on a page
But not the song ♪
♪ Had a hole in my heart
A pain so strong ♪
♪ Only a woman like you
Could take me on ♪
♪ There's a plan for us
A hand divine ♪
♪ The waiting was worth it
Now you're my wife ♪
♪ We've been taking our time
Doing this right ♪
♪ Tonight I'm not gonna
Just kiss you good night ♪
Play the rest.
♪ You, the song my heart sings ♪
♪ Awake, love ♪
♪ I want you to know
We're making love ♪
♪ Deeper than our bodies ♪
♪ You are written on my soul ♪
♪ Your eyes like the dawn
You are beauty ♪
♪ The touch of your skin
Consumes me ♪
♪ You shine like the sun ♪
♪ Pure and lovely ♪
One, two, three!
♪ Set me as a seal
Upon your heart ♪
♪ Our love stronger than death ♪
Come on.
♪ Flashes of fire
With purest desire ♪
♪ The waters will never quench ♪
♪ Awaken love, awaken love ♪
♪ No riches or power appeal ♪
♪ All will find
You are truly alive ♪
♪ In love as it was
Meant to be ♪
♪ This is love as it was
Come on, sing it out!
One, two, three, four!
♪ Oh ♪
Come on.
♪ Love is the power that heals ♪
♪ Oh ♪
You know it.
♪ Love is the power that heals ♪
- Hey, Daddy.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hey.
- How did it go?
It was great.
- Welcome home, Jed.
- Sir.
- Good to see you.
- Thank you. Yes, sir.
- How'd he do?
- Oh, he's fine. He's fine.
He's up there asleep.
We had a blast.
Oh, good.
I'm gonna go.
Hey, Jed, don't wake him up.
I won't.
- Thank you again.
- Yeah. Yes, sir.
Anytime. All right,
I better be going.
All right.
Good night, Ray.
I wish my dad could be here
to see all this.
He'd be proud of you.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
So now what?
Jed.
Enjoy it.
All this I tested by wisdom,
and I said,
"I am determined to be wise."
Shut the door.
But this was beyond me.
What more can the
king's successor do
than what has already been done?
Okay, I'm gonna do it.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
All right.
Hey.
Can I help you?
Well, you actually
already have, Jed. I just, uh...
I don't smoke.
And I definitely don't sleep
with groupies, so just...
Actually, I heard you were
really religious, and so...
- I take it you're not.
- I'm spiritual.
Isn't everybody?
You just have no idea, do you?
About what?
You know, normally,
I would be really,
really offended,
but you are just so cute.
And now I get to have a secret,
and that's always fun, isn't it?
Okay. It's good to meet you,
whatever your name is.
This whole thing is great.
No, I know. I just
thought I'd introduce...
Come on!
Whoo!
♪ Take your words and overtures
Your jokes, so green, those ♪
♪ Let them sink into your drink
Tonight I want to close ♪
♪ Underneath my overcoat
Yes, underneath my chest ♪
♪ A hurricane is shaking ♪
♪ And I'm faking
To get undressed ♪
♪ Take me, shake me
And break me into two ♪
♪ A million little pieces
I'll spread all over you ♪
♪ I wanna fly up to the roof
And come down when I'm ready ♪
♪ I want my head down to my toes
To feel like confetti ♪
Whoo!
Have you heard of Shelby Bale?
I've heard of her
but never seen her.
Well, you're gonna be doing
a lot more of both.
She's your new opener.
♪ She'll make your worries
Run away ♪
♪ They're going up in flames ♪
♪ Let yourself do what you want
Without an ounce of shame ♪
♪ 'Cause when the morning
Sun comes ♪
♪ You'll have to say goodbye ♪
♪ So come and claim your throne
Be king tonight ♪
♪ Take me, shake me
And break me into two ♪
♪ A million little pieces ♪
I find more bitter than death
the woman who is a snare.
You're welcome.
Whose heart is a trap,
whose hands are chains.
♪ To feel like confetti, yeah ♪
♪ I'm just out of control
Whoo ♪
- Hey.
- Hey. Hey, buddy.
- Oh. How are you?
- Good.
- This is a nice surprise.
- Did the show get canceled?
- I wish.
I fly out tomorrow
morning actually.
I just had to come home,
you know?
- Do you wanna be in my band?
- That's what I wanna do.
That's why I came home.
Go upstairs and get
that ready, all right?
Thank you.
Yeah, I just wanted to be
with my wife, you know?
Don't start
what you can't finish.
Nap time?
No, I'm afraid
we've outgrown nap time.
I miss it.
I'm exhausted.
- Tonight, I promise.
- Tonight.
I'm gonna hold you to that.
Couldn't hold out
for another couple weeks, huh?
- How long this time?
- Three months.
Stan added Shelby Bale
to the tour.
- Who?
- She's just this singer
with a cult following, and I get
her fans, she gets my fans,
and we book a lot more shows
and make more money.
Do you need more money, or fans?
- It's not just that, Rose.
- Then what?
I'm helping people.
I know it sounds stupid,
but in my own way, I am.
Look, I get e-mails
and people coming up to me
saying that they...
I'm helping their life
make sense.
They were about to give up
and they heard my songs.
People are looking for stuff,
Rose. Meaning, hope, God.
I don't tell them,
they're not gonna hear.
Jed.
Your biggest fan is upstairs
and he needs you more
than God does.
Bring him and come with me.
So he can sleep
on buses and jets?
Getting dragged
from hotel to hotel?
What kind of life is that?
It's not a life, Rose.
I'm talking about three months.
Which will become a year.
You won't have a reason
to tell Stan no.
You'll have me to play groupie.
What is that supposed to mean?
Feels like you don't
come home for me anymore.
It's like you come home for...
Let me fix that.
Please, I'm trying to fix that.
If you come with me,
I'll see you every day.
I'll see Ray.
We'll spend time together.
- Please.
- It's not just Ray, Jed.
What?
Your dad has a dead bear
in his living room.
I'm sure he's gonna be fine.
- Please.
- No, no.
He's not doing well, Jed.
Daddy, do you wanna be
in my band now?
Sorry.
Yeah, buddy.
Yeah, come on.
All right, let's go.
Drum solo!
I got blisters on my fingers.
All right, Ringo.
It sounds good.
Rose.
Ray's asleep.
I fell asleep.
Yeah, you did.
Okay.
Rose.
When are you gonna stop
being so rude?
I'm Shelby.
I know.
You know now.
Why didn't you just tell me
who you were?
Kindness.
I was being nice.
How is that being nice?
For a moment,
you felt wanted and...
It's a good feeling, isn't it?
Okay, unless turning me down
was unpleasant.
If it was, I'm really sorry.
You can let me know
how to make it up to you.
Hello, you've reached Rose.
Please leave me a message.
Hey, babe, it's me.
I just wanted to call
and say that I love you,
and that I miss you
and I'm thinking about you.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
♪ And all I wanna be
Is with you ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ There is nothing that's new
Under the sun ♪
♪ I ain't doing nothing
That hasn't been done ♪
♪ All the lies be truth to me ♪
♪ When all I want to be
Is with you ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ I want your love
I want your touch ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ I miss you more
With every mile ♪
♪ I go to bed just to dream
Of your smile ♪
♪ You're a garden bloom
In a thousand hues ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ And with every goodbye
It gets harder to try ♪
♪ When all hope seems lost
The heart just dies ♪
♪ But there's life
If we see this through ♪
♪ And all I want to be
Is with you ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ I want your love
I want your touch ♪
♪ Yeah, all I wanna be
Is with you ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ I want your love
I want your touch ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
♪ See the fire in your eyes
Light in your smile ♪
♪ All I wanna be is with you ♪
Good job.
- That was awesome. So good.
- Oh, thank you.
I knew you were good
but that was ridiculous.
- Thank you.
- Guys, that was magic.
- That's what I was telling her.
- That was wizardry.
I need three more months
of that. Okay?
- You got it. You can do it.
- All right. All right.
Perfect. Perfect.
Do you know any more
of my songs?
Okay, I always thought this song
needed a little ladies' touch.
How about y'all?
That may be true, but I don't
see a lady up here right now.
Ooh...
Jed, you just try to
sing the song,
and I'll see what I can do.
♪ I've been waiting for you
To come along ♪
♪ Seeing notes on a page
But not the song ♪
♪ Had a hole in my heart
A pain so strong ♪
♪ Only a woman like you
Could take me on ♪
♪ There's a plan for us
A hand divine ♪
♪ The waiting was worth it
Now you're my wife ♪
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Where's Ray?
He's asleep.
Good.
Hi.
I'm really tired, Jed.
Me too.
I'm exhausted.
I've been gone a long time.
How long are you home this time?
The tour was great, Rose.
Thanks for asking.
Had a great time.
I know how the tour was.
I have the Internet.
It's how I get to know
my husband.
You have the money too, right?
You think that's what
I care about?
I think you care about
your dad and I can feel it
every time I'm laying
in bed by myself.
Thinking about
all you care about.
Rose, if that was all I
cared about, I could get it.
I wouldn't have to come home.
Can we at least talk first?
"Hi, honey, how was your day?
How was your year?"
Don't exaggerate. Don't act
like I haven't seen you
and we haven't had the
same fight every two weeks.
I was trying to get you
to do something romantic.
I was trying to do
something romantic.
Ask you to do something
besides just grab me.
How awful for you.
To feel desired by your spouse.
- It's a terrible thing.
- Leave me alone, Jed.
Forgive my insensitivity,
but I don't have a lot
of experience in that.
Maybe you can tell me
what that's like.
Leave me alone!
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
- Hey, come here.
- Hey. Hey, buddy.
- What's wrong, Mom?
- Hey. Oh, nothing, baby.
Everything's fine.
It's okay.
I just miss your daddy.
That's all.
Let's go to bed.
Come, my beloved.
Let us go to the countryside.
You old buzzard. Oh!
What a big boy. Ha-ha-ha.
- Unh! Let Pop-Pop put you down.
- Ha, ha. Hey, Daddy.
Let us go early to the vineyards
to see if the vines have budded.
- Hey.
- Shep.
How you doing? Welcome.
Ha, ha. Hey,
you little rascal.
What are you doing, buddy?
Come back here.
- Daddy? You all right?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm all right.
That little rascal.
I'm gonna go over here
and work this other row, hon.
All right.
Oh, come on, buddy.
Come on.
Oh! Oh, you got me.
You got me.
I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead.
You got me. I'm done.
You gonna help me?
All right.
- Jed.
- It's all right.
I found this.
- Oh, okay. All right.
- What are you doing, buddy?
- I'm making them grow faster.
- Ha, ha. No.
You're making them
grow faster, huh?
Oh, buddy
that's not how it works.
If you force them,
you'll get bad grapes.
- You want bad grapes?
- Yes.
No.
No, you don't want bad grapes.
- Yes, I do.
- Ha, ha.
- Treat them right.
- Okay.
- Give them time.
And when they're ready,
they'll let you know.
Okay.
I undertook great projects.
I built houses
and planted vineyards.
In all this,
my wisdom stayed with me.
Have fun with your grandpa,
okay?
We'll be back in a couple hours,
hon.
All right, Daddy. Bye.
Come to Europe with me.
Please.
I'm hoping
we can come visit soon.
No, Rose, not visit.
Come with me.
I can't, Jed.
You've seen him lately.
I can't leave him.
Not now.
Okay.
I understand.
And when I surveyed
all my hands had done,
what I had toiled to achieve,
everything was meaningless.
A chasing after the wind.
Nothing was gained
under the sun.
There was a man all alone.
There was no end to his toil.
Yet his eyes were not
content with his wealth.
Hey, you're growing, buddy.
"For who am I toiling?"
he asked.
"And why am I depriving
myself of enjoyment?"
Whoever loves money
never has enough.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Love is the power
That heals ♪
Thank you, Glasgow!
Thank you, Dublin!
Thank you, London!
- I love you! I love you!
- Ha-ha-ha.
This too is meaningless.
Ow! Ha-ha-ha.
Okay, all right.
All right, shut up, people.
Uh, Mr. King, your turn.
Uh-oh.
- I'm good. I'm good.
- Oh, yeah.
So I think he's adding drinking
to the list of things
he's only done with his wife.
Ooh...
You guys, he has got a vineyard
back home. A vineyard.
Because he knows,
as soon as he gets home
and walks through
his big front door,
he can have all the wine
he wants.
Am I right?
No.
Heh, are you serious?
Okay. I'm sorry,
I didn't know. I just...
I hate seeing you like this
and I wanted you
to have a good time.
Enjoy it.
Are there not shots on the bar?
I think there's shots
on the bar. Right?
Jed! Jed! Jed!
All I'm saying is,
you've earned it.
Jed! Jed! Jed!
- Come on, man!
- Let's do this!
Whoo!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I think we all owe it to
Miss Shelby Bale.
Give it up.
This one's for my boys,
ladies and gentlemen.
Ah!
- He can't even walk.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- That's your band. Ha-ha-ha.
- I know.
- It's your room.
- Oh.
Okay.
So did you have a good time?
I really did. Thank you.
Thank you.
Now I get to scratch "Visit
England" off my to-do list.
Was that right after
"Get a whole lot of tattoos"?
I've been noticing.
You have one or two.
Uh, yeah, no. Uh-uh.
It was after
"Meet Jed King."
- Oh.
- Mm.
Seriously.
What's the story
with these? Hm?
Just my way of preserving
memories, I guess.
- You should try scrap-booking.
- Scrap-booking.
Heh. Ha-ha-ha.
It's just...
It seems more prudent.
Yeah, it kills memories.
- It kills memories?
- It's a fact.
I don't know.
It's just that a photo replaces
a memory in your mind.
Mm.
I see these and the memories
just come flooding back,
you know?
So you don't regret any of them?
Feeling regret and guilt is like
punching yourself in the face.
Sure, it hurts, but it's
self-inflicted, so don't do it.
That's how I feel about tattoos.
Well, all I'm saying
is do what you want...
and don't feel guilty about it.
Good night, Jed.
I said to myself, "Come now,
I will test you with pleasure
to find out what is good."
But that also proved
to be meaningless.
♪ Deep, dark sky
So black, so bright ♪
♪ All curtains back tonight ♪
♪ I'm obsessed,
I must confess ♪
♪ I don't care
If it's wrong or right ♪
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
- Good morning. Um...
- What time is it?
It is 1:15.
You okay?
- Yeah, you?
- Mm-hm.
- You can take that if you want.
- Uh, what?
The phone.
Actually, it's you.
I'm sorry. I, uh...
I grabbed it for you
because you left it at the bar
and obviously forgot to give it
back to you, so, yeah.
Whoa.
Jed, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- I feel terrible.
It's not your fault.
I should call her back though.
Yeah.
- See you later, okay?
- Mm.
- Jed.
- Hey.
Where were you? I've been trying
to get a hold of you all night.
There's a time for everything,
and a season for every purpose
under heaven.
The wise have eyes
in their heads
while the fool walks
in darkness.
But I came to realize that the
same fate overtakes them both.
So then I said to myself,
"Like the fool,
the wise too must die."
What then do
I gain by being wise?
No, no. I'm sorry, sir.
No!
- Hello?
- Oh, buddy, man, I woke you up.
- What time is it over there?
- It's 6 a.m.
Wow, man. Do you want me
to call you back?
No, it's fine.
Listen, are you anxious
to get back out here?
- Yeah.
- Because we are certainly anxious
and excited about
having you back out here.
Friday is Amsterdam.
Everything is a go.
Stan, listen.
Brother, we have lost six shows.
Now, I know
that was an emergency.
But we have an emergency
here, okay?
We are hemorrhaging money.
Hemorrhaging money, man.
- People are getting upset.
- Stan, this is my life.
This is my life.
And this is how you pay
for your life.
If you were a nobody,
still just David King's kid,
I wouldn't care what you did.
No one would.
But I don't think that's
who you wanna be, or is it?
Because you can always
just walk away.
I have to go back.
- Please.
- I don't have a choice.
- Yes, you do. Please just stay.
If I stay, we're gonna owe
a lot of money.
Take me with you then.
I can't...
I can't do that, Rose.
Why?
All the reasons you said.
I can't do that to Ray.
I should've gone with you then.
I'm so sorry, Jed.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's all right.
I should've gone with you.
You have a lot to do.
You have a lot to do here. Okay?
Help me get through
these next eight weeks.
Then I have a show in Cinci,
and then I have a break.
How long?
We'll start with a year.
Okay?
Okay.
Amsterdam!
Can I just tell you
what a great time
we've had in your city tonight?
Ha, ha.
Well, there's more fun
to be had.
- Hey, Jed.
- Aah.
What is it? What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
- Slow down.
- He's having a panic attack.
Listen to me.
- I can't feel my hands.
- You're not gonna die.
Jed. To help you relax, okay?
I'm just trying to help you.
- I can't sing that song, Shel.
- Yes, you can, Jedediah.
It's her song.
No, it's your song.
Do you ever feel like you
don't write your own songs? Hm?
- Like they were given to you?
- By who?
God?
- What if he takes them away?
- Why?
Because he doesn't like
what you're doing?
Look at the world.
You like what he's doing?
The first time
I heard your music,
I thought, "This is it.
This guy really gets it.
This is what I need."
But I also thought, you know,
"If only he weren't so...
Married.
...narrow.
But think of the music he could
write if he just let go
and lived without
all of these rules."
And then I realized,
"I can help him let go.
He needs me to."
I thought I was going to die
out there.
I don't ever wanna feel
like that again.
You won't.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
I tried cheering myself with
wine and embracing folly.
Laughter is madness.
And what does pleasure
accomplish?
This is what's happening now.
The heart of fools
is in the house of pleasure.
The heart of the wise
is in the house of mourning
because a sad face
is good for the heart.
What do you think?
You're the expert.
Well done.
♪ Under this moon ♪
I denied myself nothing
my eyes desired.
I refused my heart no pleasure.
♪ Under this moon ♪
♪ We are falling ♪
♪ You belong ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ Under this moon ♪
♪ We are falling ♪
♪ Like stars ♪
Everything was meaningless.
Chasing after the wind.
- Daddy!
- Hey, buddy.
- Unh. Did you have fun?
- Uh-huh.
Look at Mom's belly.
Wow.
- Hi.
Oh...
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to tell you in person.
Hi, Shelby.
I'll be right there.
Yup.
- Shelby.
- Yeah.
This is my wife, Rose.
Yeah. It's really
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Great show tonight.
You're very talented.
Thank you.
- This is my son, Ray.
- Ray.
You are so handsome.
I've heard so much about you.
I feel like I know you guys.
But I did not know
that you were expecting.
- Neither did he.
- Oh.
No?
I'm gonna go drink
with the guys.
We were headed out.
- So I'll just catch you tomorrow?
- Yes.
Okay. It was nice to meet you.
You too.
Ready to go?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I missed you.
When did you get this?
Amsterdam.
Why?
I don't know.
It seemed like a good idea
at the time.
Oh.
Everything okay?
Yeah, just...
Just give me a second.
Jed, please don't do this to me.
Please.
Let's just go back out there.
No, no, no.
I'll sing it myself.
No, no, no,
you won't sing that, no.
You will never sing that song.
You will never sing that song!
Play it.
Just play the song.
♪ I've been waiting for you
To... ♪
Stop it! No!
You think you're better than me?
You think she's better than me?
- What was that?
- You broke it! You broke it!
- Shelby! Get off.
- You think you're better?
- Get off me!
- Stop! Stop!
No! I'm gonna tell her!
Let me go!
I'm gonna tell her!
I'm gonna...
- Are you threatening me?
- Jed!
You don't threaten me!
I love you.
Yeah, Stan, this is Matt.
I'm over at will call.
I'm gonna call you back.
Thank you.
Don't hang up.
Look, I don't care what you do.
I don't care who you do it with.
When you bring
your problems on stage,
they become my problems.
My very expensive problems.
Now, if you can't keep your
baggage off stage, I will.
Shelby, you are done. Done!
I was hoping to bring Ray
to your Nashville show also.
That be all right?
Jed?
Yes. That would be fine.
Why is Shelby off the tour?
I read that
she was off the tour.
She punched Stan in the face.
Good for her.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Look, I don't wanna talk
about work right now.
Rose. What?
Do you not want me here?
You're not here.
We have to say your name five
times before you even answer.
- Something is wrong.
- I'm just tired.
Why aren't you singing my song?
Do you...?
- Do you not love me anymore?
- Rose, of course I do.
- Why would you ask me that?
- Sing it.
I want you to sing it right now.
Rose, that song
is special to me.
All right,
it holds a special place,
and I'm just tired of
being demanded
to sing it like some sort of
performance monkey.
What is that?
- What?
- Shh.
Try it.
High five.
You still didn't get it.
You spit, but you didn't get it.
- But you can try...
- Shelby?
Hey, Jed.
Hey, babe, come here.
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you answer
your phone?
I'm having dinner with my
family. What do you want?
Okay, can you just tell Stan
to bring me back?
Shelby, don't come to
my house...
What? Are you done with me,
is that it?
Please.
- Ray, go inside, please.
- Okay.
Because of me?
Honey, he's the druggie.
- He's the one that takes all my...
- Get out.
Seriously, dinner on the porch,
how cute.
Okay. Got it.
You too.
Get out.
- Rose.
- Get out!
- Get out of the car.
- That wine was terrible.
Get out of the car.
- Jed, stop.
- Stop talking!
Ray, where's your mom?
Rose.
You were with her!
While I was here
carrying our child.
- You think this is what I wanted?
- Yes!
It's what you did.
This was your choice!
I wanted you!
But you made me beg.
Girls are begging me
and I had to beg my wife.
Don't blame this on me, Jed.
You did this.
Don't blame this on me!
I did this,
and I'm glad I did this.
I'm glad I didn't have to jump
through 15,000 hoops
or build a chapel,
Rose, to do it.
She wants me.
Me!
Because she doesn't
know you, Jed.
- She does.
- No, she doesn't!
- She does!
- She thinks she does.
She thinks she matters.
I used to think that.
You used to think
you mattered so much
you could treat me
however you wanted.
How dare I ask to be treated
like an actual human being
before I give it up?
How cruel, right?
You'd tell me over and over
you didn't want me.
- I never said that. I never...
- You did!
And now that somebody
actually wants me,
now you wanna act like a wife.
- It's a little late.
- You didn't want a wife.
- I did!
- You didn't. You wanted a whore.
- That's not true!
- Someone who would lay there.
It is true.
It clearly is 'cause that's what
showed up at our house today!
You don't even know her!
Right.
Because she's the wife
you always wanted.
She's gonna raise your children?
She's gonna grow old with you?
And then, with her sleazy
saggy tattoos,
that skank will always
be in the mood, right?
You're a fool, Jed.
You are such a fool!
You're right!
I am a fool!
I'm a fool
because I married you.
But I'm done.
So I hated life,
because the work
that is done under the sun
was grievous to me.
What do people get for all
the toil and anxious striving
with which
they labor under the sun?
All their days,
their work is grief and pain.
Even at night,
their minds do not rest.
This too is meaningless.
Jed. Stop, stop, stop.
What are you doing? Stop.
- I want it off.
- Stop it.
- Stop!
- I want it off.
Did you flush them?
No, no, no.
Please say something.
Jed. Jed.
Jed, please. Jed, please.
Jed. Please, come on.
Please. Please wake up.
Please wake up. Wake up.
Please. Please.
Will you please talk to me?
- Please say something.
- Rose.
Jed! Jed!
- No! No! No!
- Jed! Jed. Stop running.
What would have happened
if you would've died, Jed?
You would've been better off.
You would've had everything.
Jed, what did we have
when we first got married?
I had everything I needed.
But you didn't.
You still don't.
I made mistakes.
With us, there's things that
I wish I could do over.
But I can't give you whatever
it is you're looking for.
No one can.
When Dad died, I realized
there's nothing in this world
that won't go away
eventually.
My only hope
is that there's something
bigger than this world.
What if that's a fool's hope?
Then I'll take it.
I'll take it.
If I'm gonna raise a son
and a daughter on my own,
I need to believe
there's a point.
A girl?
Found out I'm having a girl.
You wanna raise them
on your own?
That wasn't my plan, Jed.
I want a man who believes in
something bigger than all this.
Someone greater than himself.
And that's not you anymore.
That man died a long time ago.
Goodbye, Jed.
♪ There's a valley of sorrow
In my soul ♪
♪ Where every night I hear
The thunder roll ♪
♪ And the shadows
Filling up this land ♪
♪ Are the ones I built
With my own hand ♪
Here you are,
Mr. King.
♪ In this valley of sorrow
In my soul ♪
♪ And the rock of ages
I have known ♪
♪ Is a weariness
Down in the bone ♪
♪ I used to ride it
Like a rolling stone ♪
♪ Now I just carry it alone ♪
Hello?
Hey, buddy.
What are you up to?
Working. The grapes
will be ready soon.
I take it
you're working with your mom.
Is she there?
Can I talk to her?
She's busy right now.
That's fine.
I just wanted to call
and see how you guys
were doing, okay?
Do you wanna come home?
- Are you coming to the festival?
- When is it?
When is it?
- October 12th.
All right, count me in.
Hey, listen. I'm gonna let you
get back to work, okay?
- I love you.
- I love you too. Bye.
Bye, buddy.
♪ Why should we be ♪
♪ If no one's there to see ♪
♪ All of our deeds ♪
That's good.
New song?
Hey, hey.
What's happening, brother?
Very nice.
Beautiful place.
I'm serious.
What do you want, Stan?
Maybe I wanna come see you.
See how you're doing.
Do you?
Okay. I do wanna show
you something.
Here, just look at this.
Why would you show that to me?
Not the video.
Don't look at the video.
Look at the view counts.
I don't care about
the view count.
There's something here.
There's something here
we can build on.
It's a story of redemption.
This isn't redemption,
this is exploitation.
Just listen.
American Roots Music Awards.
You and Shelby,
if you can put your junk aside
for just one second,
let the world see your healthy,
redeemed, rehabbed faces on TV,
ready for a comeback.
- When?
- October 12th.
I can't do it.
Can't do it.
I have plans. I promised Ray.
- Ray? Who is Ray?
- Stan.
Ray is your son, of course.
Come on, man,
you know I love Ray.
Hey, you know what? Ray wants
to go to college one day.
Ray wants his dad to shave
and sing, be a rock star.
Do you understand
that this is a second chance?
This is a chance for you
to put everything behind you.
Rehab, Rose, your dad.
Are you in?
♪ I thought that I was strong ♪
♪ I thought things
Would be different this time ♪
♪ I guess that I was wrong ♪
♪ As wrong ♪
♪ As you ♪
♪ You call me beautiful ♪
You ready to do this?
I guess we'll see.
♪ It wasn't me ♪
You look really good.
Thank you. You too.
- You look healthy.
- Thank you.
♪ How ugly I can be ♪
Jed, um...
I knew you were
eaten up with guilt,
and I just thought
if she knew...
then it would be over and you
and I could be together
without all this guilt...
and you'd be at peace.
♪ You call me beautiful ♪
♪ But you
Must've seen the light ♪
We have a chance to start over.
For things to be the way
they should be, you know?
♪ Don't call me beautiful ♪
♪ You don't know how ugly ♪
♪ I can be ♪
- Here we go.
- Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome
Jed King and Shelby Bale.
♪ Why have everything? ♪
♪ You're leaving here
With nothing ♪
♪ Can't take anything
'Cause you have to move on ♪
♪ You were the wise one ♪
♪ Putting your disguise on ♪
♪ Lying to protect
You're chasing after wind ♪
♪ Why should you be ♪
♪ If no one's there to see? ♪
♪ All of your deeds
Are raindrops in the sea ♪
♪ What do we mean ♪
♪ If nothing has meaning? ♪
♪ If in the end ♪
♪ We're chasing after wind ♪
♪ I had everything ♪
♪ That don't leave me anything ♪
♪ I had my plans ♪
♪ Crumble in the sand ♪
♪ Now I understand ♪
♪ I was born a natural man ♪
♪ Racing through the end ♪
♪ And chasing after wind ♪
♪ Why should I be
If nothing has made me? ♪
♪ All that I've done ♪
♪ Will flame out with the sun ♪
♪ Why should I sing ♪
♪ If nothing has meaning? ♪
You know, when you're
always under bright lights...
you can't see the stars.
You forget things.
You forget that somebody
put the stars there...
and that they love you
enough to die for you.
And it's that kind of love
that makes songs worth singing
and life worth living.
I had that love.
I threw it away.
Because I am a fool.
I'm sorry.
You're right. We have a
chance to do things right.
You really think
she'll take you back?
Either way, this is goodbye.
Jed, stop!
You can't do this.
I can.
You're watching it happen.
You realize what you
are walking away from?
- Nothing that matters.
- Let me tell you something.
You walk out that door,
I will sue you for every
show you canceled.
I know. Go ahead.
It's only money, Stan.
I've lost much worse.
- Ray.
- Dad.
Hey. Unh!
- I missed you.
- You're late.
I know. I'm sorry
I'm a little late,
- but I'm here, right?
- Uh-huh.
Where's your mom?
She's over there
by the wine people.
Heh. By the wine people?
Okay.
I'm gonna go talk
to her, all right?
- Okay.
- I love you.
- You know that? Ow.
I'll see you in
a little bit, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
I'm glad you could make it.
Excuse me.
Rose.
What are you doing here?
I thought you had a show.
I love you.
- I love you.
- Jed, stop. Just stop.
I did it. I quit it.
Everything. Tonight.
I was on stage
and I just walked away,
because it's not what I want.
I want you.
- You had your chance, Jed.
- Rose.
- It's really good, Rose.
- Oh, good, good. Thank you.
That's our Syrah.
It's from '95.
'95 was one
of our best years, so...
Is that who I think it is?
Jed, get off the stage.
Rose, I wanna play you a song.
All right? I've wanted
to play it so much.
I never can.
It makes me think of you.
I've heard it.
Everyone has.
Not like this. Please.
No.
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time to every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time to be born
A time to die ♪
♪ A time to plant
A time to reap ♪
♪ A time to kill
A time to heal ♪
♪ A time to laugh
A time to weep ♪
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time for every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time to build up
A time to break down ♪
♪ A time to dance
A time to mourn ♪
♪ A time to cast away stones ♪
♪ A time to gather
Stones together ♪
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time for every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time to gain
A time to lose ♪
♪ A time to rend
A time to sew ♪
♪ A time to love
A time to hate ♪
♪ A time of peace
Rose, know it's not too late ♪
I'm so sorry.
Marrying you is the only
smart thing I ever did.
You're enough.
You're a gift from God.
All I want
is to be your husband.
I wanna raise our children.
I will never leave you again.
I'll never sing another note
if you're not there to hear it.
Please forgive me.
It'll take a really long time.
I just cleared my schedule
for forever.
And if it takes forever,
I'll be here forever.
Remember your creator
in the days of your youth.
Before the pitcher is shattered
at the spring
and the dust returns
to the ground it came from,
and the spirit returns
to the God who gave it.
You who are young,
be happy while you are young
and let your heart give you joy
in the days of your youth.
Goodbye, Dad.
I love you.
Enjoy life with your wife,
whom you love,
all the days
of this meaningless life
that God
has given you under the sun.
For in the realm of the dead
where you are going,
there is neither working,
nor planning,
nor knowledge, nor wisdom.
Now all has been heard,
here is the end of the matter:
Fear God
and keep his commandments,
for this is the duty
of all mankind,
for God will bring every deed
into judgment,
including every hidden thing,
whether it is good or evil.
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time to every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time to be born
A time to die ♪
♪ A time to plant
A time to reap ♪
♪ A time to kill
A time to heal ♪
♪ A time to laugh
A time to weep ♪
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time to every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time to build up
A time to break down ♪
♪ A time to dance
A time to mourn ♪
♪ A time to cast away stones ♪
♪ A time to gather
Stones together ♪
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time to every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time of love
A time of hate ♪
♪ A time of war
A time of peace ♪
♪ A time you may embrace ♪
♪ A time to refrain
From embracing ♪
♪ To everything
Turn, turn, turn ♪
♪ There is a season
♪ And a time to every purpose
Under heaven ♪
♪ A time to gain
A time to lose ♪
♪ A time to rend
A time to sew ♪
♪ A time for love
A time for hate ♪
♪ A time for peace
I swear it's not too late ♪
One, two.
I think you'll know this one.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's a beautiful voice
That made it.
♪ Your arrows have pierced me ♪
♪ I'm bleeding
I'm shaking ♪
♪ You have overwhelmed me ♪
♪ And made my heart grow ♪
♪ I cried all these tears ♪
♪ With fears I was forsaken ♪
♪ After I've begged you
To leave me alone ♪
♪ I cannot hear
I have no sight ♪
♪ Dark is near
And your blinding light ♪
♪ Can you hear me when I cry? ♪
♪ Catch me when I fall ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't hold on ♪
Take it away, boys.
Ha, ha.
Oh, I love that.
♪ Now here is the end
Of the matter ♪
♪ Why you should live
A good life ♪
♪ Days dawn in the shadow
Of the darkness ♪
♪ He's gonna bring
To the light ♪
♪ So cherish the gifts
Of your maker ♪
♪ Delight in the wife
Of your youth ♪
♪ Remember God's your creator ♪
♪ Whose help leads
To the truth ♪
♪ So here is the end
Of the matter ♪
♪ While you're searching for
The truth my friend ♪
♪ He carved his mark
In our hearts ♪
♪ But we're never gonna
Comprehend ♪
♪ Just how he caused
The beginning ♪
♪ How he's gonna bring it
All to an end ♪
♪ The only hope that we have ♪
♪ Is the only son
That he did send ♪
♪ So at the end of the matter ♪
♪ His will be done, not mine ♪
♪ He breaks the seals
Fulfills the signs ♪
♪ And makes everything
So beautiful ♪
♪ It's all gonna be
♪ In his ♪
♪ Time ♪
Hi, guys.
Hi. Come to see me?
How are you so big?
Let's go.