Heeyah!
Hyah!
Whoa.
Hey.
Her mother is dead.
You are her aunt.
I don't know what to do with her.
I'll send more each month.
Before you can even start to miss me,
I'm going to sail right up that river,
take you back to Africa.
Girls in Africa may not wear shoes...
but French girls do.
Quietly, Therese.
Your father isn't coming back,
Therese.
He'll come back.
My brother has never
done a single thing
he said he was going to do.
Therese, your cousin
needs his medicine.
God gives and he takes away.
He took away Camille's health,
but gave him you.
You're his guardian angel.
Boo!
Should you be out?
I escaped.
Kiss me, Camille.
All right.
No, not like that.
Like this?
No.
Well, how?
Never mind.
A letter came...
for you, from Africa.
Your father went down
off the coast of Algeria.
What's going
to happen to me now?
Well, there's the small pension
your father left you, perhaps.
Perhaps we could use that
to help find our way.
Oh, my son.
Oh, my God!
What was I thinking?
You should be inside.
It's damp out here.
I'm fine.
You're overreacting.
Camille has an announcement
to make.
We're moving to Paris.
Paris?
Such a filthy city.
Yes.
Through an old friend of mother's,
Inspector Michaud, I've found a job.
In an office.
A lowly clerk in a big company,
be with my own little desk.
It sounds wonderful.
Makes no sense to me
whatsoever.
I mean, how are Therese and I
supposed to look after you
if you're gone all day?
The doctor did say
I should exert myself more
and you do spoil me, mother.
He said so.
Oh, he's a country doctor
with one dead eye.
I hardly believe
that he knows what's--
I've let you coddle me all my life.
The least you can do is allow me
a will of my own, mother.
It's time I take control
of our little family.
Well...
I've often dreamed of having
a small shop again.
Ha, see? A silver lining.
You know, a few special lace pieces
in the window and...
Well, you let me take care
of everything, you naughty boy.
I wouldn't dream of having it
any other way, mother.
We can leave right after the wedding.
Whose wedding are we going to?
Well, yours, dear.
Well, but who am I going to marry?
Why, Camille, of course.
Therese...
We don't even know
who your mother was.
Illegitimates have been dealt
an unlucky hand.
We should consider ourselves lucky
that you have Camille.
And he is so excited.
Oh, and you will be Madame Raquin,
just like me.
In the name of
the Father and the Son
and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Clear the way, lad.
Children.
This way.
Set it there.
"I found the most wonderful shop,"
you said.
I saw it in the daylight.
"An enthralling arcade"?
Well, it was enthralling.
Therese, let the young man pass.
He has work to do.
It's smaller than you said, mother.
I adore this house.
It's our new home.
It's dark.
Oh, well, be fair. It's late.
When the sun streams in,
- it's lovely.
- It's mean.
Oh, don't be silly.
Well, I will be cooped up all day,
content in my new job at the office,
while you two girls will have each other
to thin the gloom.
Customers bustling in and out.
Oh, yes. Won't it be exciting?
And even I will admit, my dear,
that it needs a few touches.
Well, there were financial
limitations, of course.
I mean, but I think we can do wonders
with the place. Really.
Hmm.
Just get some flowers
on the windowsills,
and wallpaper.
Curtains, of course.
Let me show you the upstairs.
Yes.
- We have a generous storeroom.
- Right.
This one.
Thank you.
What do you do all day?
You know what I do.
I don't. Go to the office.
And then I come home.
Are you happy?
Not at the office.
Where?
At the zoo.
The zoo?
By the end of another meaningless
column of figures,
my mind is blank.
Feels nice.
I let my feet decide the destination
and the rest of me
just sort of follows along.
Your feet decide
to go to the zoo?
Oh, yes. I don't know why,
but four days out of five
I find myself outside a cage
and I watch the bears.
I see.
I get to feel the ground
shuddering under my feet
as they move about.
Where's my book?
Oh, I must have left it downstairs.
I'm too tired to read tonight.
Hey.
I might be a bear.
But you're not.
You're my little Therese.
- Candied grapefruit peel?
- No.
Camille is never this late.
Mother!
Finally.
I'll return in a moment.
And no cheating.
Therese.
Camille! Where have you been?
You've--
Ta-da! I brought you a present.
Imported from your
long-lost past in Vernon.
Oh.
You don't remember him.
- Do I?
- It's Laurent.
You must remember Laurent!
His father owned the dairy
beyond the church.
Oh, my! Yes!
Oh, my!
Little Laurent.
Yes!
Oh!
This is before you came
to live with us.
Oh, so long ago.
When I was a girl,
a summer day was just...
Now, mother, let's not get started
on summer days
or we'll die of hunger.
Can you feed this great ox?
Well, yes, of course I can.
Oh, little Laurent.
You can stay, can't you?
I would love to stay, thank you.
He works for the company, too,
and we never even knew.
Oh, my.
So I thought why not?
I'll bring him along to Dominoes Night.
Oh, well, that's perfect.
Thursday evenings here
are always so exciting.
- Yes.
- I mean, the banter,
especially Inspector Michaud.
And his son Olivier.
He's fantastic.
Come, come, come, come!
You must meet everyone.
Oh, I will.
Therese, put the lights out, dear.
Good evening.
Welcome, Laurent.
- Mr. Olivier.
- Good evening.
This is my wife Suzanne.
Here you go, my friend.
Ah, Inspector.
Very good to meet you.
Ah!
- Very nice.
- Well done.
Would you open a window, Therese?
I keep smelling an odor,
like gas.
It's probably me.
Oh, no, certainly not.
Yes. Owing to an investigation,
which I'm not at liberty to discuss,
I had to go to the morgue today.
It was, uh, rather warm.
The aroma clings.
I seem to be having
the slightest attack of the vapors.
Excuse me.
Therese.
Don't bother. She won't be long.
Grapefruit peel?
Oh, yes, thank you.
When I was a young police officer
like my son here,
I wouldn't go down
to the morgue at all.
I had to draw a line.
Send me into the nearest
den of thieves, unarmed.
I've been to the morgue myself,
a number of times.
What for? On a bet?
No, no, no, not at all.
With my artist friends.
You didn't paint, did you?
I'm afraid I did.
While my father paid my way
in the hugely mistaken assumption
that I was grooming myself
for the law.
Were you good?
No, not at all.
But I liked the life.
By "life" you must mean--
He said life, he meant the life.
Let's leave it at that.
But why the morgue?
Well, we'd stand at the public rail
with pad in hand and sketch the bodies.
Wasn't there a supply of,
uh, warmer models?
Obviously not.
So why did you
hang up your brush?
Well, my--my father came
to my garret one day
and my model opened the door
as she was and my father
was so shocked that
he took a step backwards
and fell down
three flights of steps.
Was he hurt?
Oh not a bit, but I was.
By the time he hit bottom,
he'd cut me off completely
without a sou.
Hmm.
I haven't spoken
to the old skinflint since.
You weren't prepared to starve
for your art?
Do I look like a man
who would starve for his art?
I couldn't say you do.
No.
- Therese.
- I have to open a window.
- Why? What's wrong?
- Nothing. The air is close.
Won't you come
and join us at the table?
No. My head is splitting.
Laurent will think you don't like him.
I don't.
Might have a think about that.
He smells like an animal.
I can smell him from here.
Don't be ridiculous.
Oh, Grivet, you've won again!
I've tried, but I just can't imagine it.
What?
Standing there with palette
and brush in hand
while a woman takes off her clothes.
Can't you?
Therese!
I wouldn't know where to look.
There are dozens of places.
My hand would shake.
- Therese!
- Should you not see
- what she wants?
- Don't move.
Sorry.
A customer probably wandered
into the shop by mistake.
I'd be hypnotized.
The model is hypnotized, too.
Do you look at her face?
Mm-hmm.
And I look at her body.
I listen and try to hear
what the body is saying.
"I have to go wee"?
Yeah, maybe.
The body says other things.
"Love me," I suppose.
The first model I ever had
was this beautiful redhead.
Natural red,
as I quickly discovered.
With the only hitch being
that this wonderful creature
was deaf as a brick.
Hmm.
Couldn't call out if I wanted
adjustments. I had to...
mold her like a sculptor,
Part by part.
One afternoon,
I wanted her legs to be a bit wider.
So I went to move her knees apart
with my hands,
but my touch was clumsy.
And then, on a hunch,
I touched the inside of her thigh
with the tip of my brush...
where the skin is soft as cream,
and warm.
Lightest touch of camel's hair.
Did she make the small move
you were after?
She did.
And what was her body
saying to you?
"Brush me again."
Did Madame call?
Yes. Five minutes ago.
Is it done?
It's a painting, Madame,
not a roast.
Great art takes time, mother.
Just one small peek.
Ah! Can't be done.
Oh, but I could be called away
to heaven before it's completed.
No, I doubt it, Madame.
My guess is you'll see us
all snug in our graves.
What a horrible thought.
Mother, I'm posing.
Oh, so handsome.
Therese. Now.
Don't move.
I've painted your shadow
into the picture.
Therese, I need
my hot water bottle.
My feet are freezing.
Therese, honestly,
I wonder your head is.
You're not even listening.
Could you come up here, please?
Hmm.
I look--
is "distinguished" the word?
It's a word.
Thank you.
But it barely resembles you.
It's so blue.
And so...gray.
It resembles my soul, mother.
Oh.
Is that what you were after,
his soul?
I paint what I see, Madame.
It does grow on one.
So does mange.
Oh, no, don't belittle yourself.
You've given us a glimpse
of something...
eternal.
Oh, no, not a customer now.
Let me go out and get a bottle
of champagne to celebrate.
- Yes.
- No, no, no!
- Two bottles.
- Yes!
And then we can come back here
and marvel at Laurent's masterpiece.
- But hurry.
- Of course.
Marvelous.
It really is an extraordinary thing.
Thank you, dear friend.
Do you like it?
You said you couldn't paint.
Unbutton your blouse.
We don't have time.
Am I hurting you?
Yes.
Don't moan.
Don't make a sound.
Keep quiet.
Well, you're busy as a little bee
this morning.
I slept very well last night.
- Buzz, buzz, buzz.
There?
Show me where.
Ah. There. Right there?
Tomorrow. Don't be late.
Yes.
Therese? I need you.
Well, um, I'll save them
both for you,
and you can stop in once
you've given it some thought.
Oh, that's what I'll do.
Thank you.
Boo!
Jesus, Camille,
you scared the hell out of me.
Will you join me for some lunch?
- Um, uh...
- It's not a difficult question.
I'm sorry. The head clerk needs me
to run an errand for him.
Oh. Will I see you tonight?
- Tonight?
- It's Thursday.
Oh, yes. Yes, of course.
I'll see you tonight.
I'm sorry, I'm late, Camille.
Come over whenever you want.
You're family now.
Your marriage bed?
Madame could come up here
at any minute.
Oh, she wouldn't dream
of leaving the shop.
Besides, I have a terrible headache
and need to rest.
You're afraid.
I can't believe that you're
the same lifeless girl
who always sat in a corner.
You have no idea how much
they've stolen from me.
I almost ran away twice.
But she always told me
I couldn't survive without them.
And I believed her.
There is nothing left of me
but a bit of burnt wick
and a wisp of smoke.
And look at you now.
So don't be afraid.
Danger passes by those
who look it right in the eye.
He still had her blood
under his fingernails
when we found him.
Oh--
Excuse me.
Therese.
She won't be long.
Thou shalt not.
Is it the sixth or the seventh?
- The seventh.
- The sixth
and the seventh.
There is nothing but murder
and lust.
To be stuffed into her own oven.
Hacked to bloody pieces
and baked in a pie.
Therese.
It's your move.
Oh.
Oh, now.
I had no idea you were such
a skillful player, Therese.
It's always the quiet ones
in the corner
that you have to keep an eye on.
I can't stand not being with you.
Therese?
Oh, for God's sake.
Therese, are you ill?
I have a terrible migraine,
Madame.
Well, would you like a cup of tea?
Maybe later. I need to rest.
Hmm.
You like to lie.
I do.
And I'm good at it.
They made me better.
Thank you for locking me up
in a sickroom.
Shh.
And thank you
for burying me alive.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Therese, is the cat
coughing up furballs again?
What's wrong?
You dug me up too late.
No.
No. Just in time.
Just in time.
Save me.
Please save me.
- Shh.
- I was sinking.
I was sinking into
something cold and deep.
I couldn't breathe.
You were dreaming.
What are you doing?
Listening to the river.
That's just a brick wall, Therese.
Hmm.
Do you often sit up alone at night?
Sometimes.
You have secrets from me.
I didn't know.
Sometimes at night
I sit up at the window.
That's all.
Well, come back to bed.
I want to hold you.
I never dream when I hold you.
I hated you.
You hated me?
Before you ever touched me.
I used to walk into a room,
and I'd see you there
and you'd barely look up.
I'd find myself moving around
and around your chair,
hoping that a small part of my dress
or my hand might touch you.
Do you still hate me?
Yes.
Why?
Because you can leave me.
But I won't.
I promise.
Camille! What are we doing?
Come to see my bear.
Why?
Last week there was a young boy
here with a crust of bread
that he'd spread with honey.
He threw it
but his aim was bad.
The bread hit the bear on the back
and it stuck there.
Poor thing could smell the honey,
but he couldn't quite reach it.
The bear went crazy.
The poor thing mauled itself.
Why dwell on it?
It's sad.
Come on, let's go.
I don't know how
to make Therese happy.
Isn't she happy?
I don't even know
how to tell anymore.
Just love her, Camille.
It just seemed so much easier
back in Vernon.
Just love her.
See if she comes around.
Come on, let's go.
I want to fall asleep in your arms.
I wish that could happen.
I want to touch your body
while you sleep.
I want to wake up
with your tongue inside me.
Therese.
Therese, I made you
some chamomile tea.
Go. Get under my skirts.
Therese?
Open your legs.
- No.
- I can't breathe.
I don't care.
Were you dozing, dear?
I thought I heard you muttering.
Maybe I was.
I don't remember.
- Tea?
- Yes, please.
How's your head?
Still agonizing?
It comes and goes.
Perhaps I should rub your neck.
Oh, you know,
I don't think that's--
Oh, it always helped
when you were small.
You know, you've had
so many headaches lately.
Perhaps we should
talk to the doctor.
I need you by my side, dear,
down in the shop.
My brother was an officer
He went away to sea
He met someone,
somewhere, somehow
And brought you home to me
- Is that better?
- Oh, yes.
Thank you.
You should start getting packing
material from Fragnet's shop.
What for?
We're moving back to Vernon.
What?
Paris is so bad for my health.
All the filth and soot.
But your job, the shop?
Both easily replaced in Vernon.
Camille, Camille.
When were you going
to discuss this with me?
I like Paris.
Well, Mother says you've been getting
terrible migraines every afternoon,
so it's better for you, too.
The air is much cleaner in Vernon.
God, what's gotten into you?
I'm the husband.
I make the decisions.
Yeah, but we have friends here
and our business.
Therese!
I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you.
We will live out our lives together
away from this filthy city
and all will be fine.
Therese, it's time for bed.
Therese?
Yes?
What are you doing?
Uh...
Uh, checking that the door is locked.
Go to bed this instant.
It's late.
Good evening,
Monsieur Jeanneau.
Oh, I can't live without you
any longer.
If only he'd go away.
Well, people don't just go away.
Sometimes they do.
But it's...
it's dangerous for...
people they leave behind.
Not if the going away
is an accident.
People have accidents
every day and...
sometimes they
just don't come back.
That's all.
I have to go.
Therese.
Do I own you?
Completely.
Yes. Yes.
For you.
They're supposed to go
into water, Therese.
Oh, and don't tell mother.
She'll be jealous.
Feels like summer's nearly over.
The leaves will be falling
before we know it.
Why does that happen?
Listen.
What?
I hear water.
Ah. Maybe it's the leaves
drifting down.
It's the river,
beyond those trees over there.
Oh, why don't we rent a boat
and row out into the sunset?
Just-just let me
sit down for a moment.
Are you tired?
Oh, I'm exhausted.
I couldn't have trudged
another step.
Just let me catch up
with a couple of winks.
Therese.
Notice this, Laurent.
If you get married, you'll find yourself
with a portable pillow.
Don't flaunt your good fortune,
my friend.
Oh, we must have
walked 20 miles.
Maybe two.
I'm getting old.
What an odd thought.
Are you warm enough?
Camille?
Shh.
Don't.
I have to touch you.
Oh, my God.
I know.
No, you don't know.
There, clomping through the leaves.
Isn't that Therese?
Oh, look.
It's Laurent and Therese.
- Hello.
- Laurent!
One, one boat.
Shh.
Oh. Sorry.
Is he sick?
Oh, no.
He's napping.
- Oh.
- On the damp ground?
His mother would have a heart attack.
I won't tell if you won't.
What happened to your foot?
Oh. A blister.
I got one, too.
I told you this walk was too far.
Well, we're leaving now,
aren't we, darling?
Without doing the single thing
we came to do.
If you want to rent a boat, Suzanne,
and row out into the fading light,
be my guest.
I'm going home.
Good afternoon.
Can I tell you something, Therese?
All men are pigs.
Why can't you two
be civil to one another?
She wants to go on a boat.
Wait! Olivier, please!
Wait for me!
Will you control your temper?
Have a good afternoon.
I was ready to go
in the boat this Sunday,
but somebody had taken their time
choosing the right dress.
Let's have a lovely walk
by the river.
We should go.
- Where?
- Back.
To what?
I'd never make a sailor.
Go easy.
Want to know why?
I'm terrified of water.
Don't be such a baby.
If God had intended us
to conquer the waves,
he'd have fitted us with pontoons
instead of feet.
Look, just sit down.
Don't stand in the boat.
Sit.
When we were little,
remember, Therese,
you'd make me play that game.
Remember?
We'd sit in our room
and the sun would go down,
and you'd say,
"Don't light a candle yet."
The light would fade.
But we could still just
make out things in the room--
the table, the rug, the vase.
Then they lost their color.
Then their edges.
Therese?
When it was completely dark...
Get in the boat.
It'd feel like there was almost
someone else with us there in the room.
I wanted to strike a match,
but you called me a baby.
- Remember?
- I love you.
Well, at least I'm not afraid of boats,
like some babies I could mention.
Is there anything as depressingly calm
as a Sunday afternoon?
Camille!
Man over!
Camille! I have to go back in!
- Laurent!
- Camille?
Laurent.
Oh, my goodness!
My dear! What's wrong?
I have to save him!
Camille!
Therese, shh.
Therese, shh. Therese.
I told him to stop dancing round
in the boat.
I told him.
And then the boat tipped over.
You did all
that was humanly possible.
She's got a fever.
He kept shouting,
"Save my Therese."
You die just like that,
in the twinkle of an eye.
Horrible, just horrible.
A report will have to be filed.
Certainly someone saw something.
And they will find the body.
No, wait here.
You've been through enough
today, dear boy.
I'll take over now.
I should go to Madame.
We have a long way to go.
You can never leave me now.
Be strong.
I think you should come in now.
No, no, no, no, no!
- Shh, shh.
- Oh, no, no!
Therese,
Madame needs you now.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
I miss my boy!
No, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
My boy!
- Shh, shh, shh.
- I miss my boy!
Oh, no!
Anima eius et animae omnius
fidelium defunctorum
per misericordiam def
requiescant in pace.
Amen.
I'm so sorry, Madame.
I'm so sorry.
I'd do it all again if I had to.
I love you.
Therese, please, let me do it.
No, I want to keep busy.
I see him sometimes
breaking the surface.
Have some tea, Madame.
Swelling and...
bursting apart.
Madame, I beg you.
And other times...
Other times,
I see the boat tipping
and I see him falling.
And then I see him
swimming away.
Flopping up onto a bank,
exhausted but happy.
And I wonder,
why couldn't it be that way?
Tea, Madame.
Have my son bring it to me.
Therese.
Madame, you should come inside.
Shh.
You did this.
No. I don't know what you mean.
You, you took your eyes off of him.
You weren't watching.
You were supposed to be
his guardian angel!
Madame, accidents
happen every day.
When the boat tipped over,
how did you survive?
How did you survive
while my child sank down
into the blackness?
What were you doing?
Tell me, tell me.
Oh, God, tell me!
What were you doing?
Madame, I tried.
No, you didn't.
You let him die.
How did you manage to live
and not him?
How?
He should be standing
right here beside me.
Not you, not you, not you!
Not you!
Madame. Shh.
Shh.
Therese. Oh, my..
Oh, my baby girl.
I didn't mean those things I said.
I didn't mean...
Something has reached inside...
and destroyed my heart
and my mind.
Oh, my sweet girl.
Is she sleeping?
Yes.
Perhaps we should leave.
Please stay.
We, uh, we weren't sure
whether to come here
even after you invited us.
But it's been so long
and we've missed your at-homes.
Well, she's missed them, too.
Please, stay.
I had to be near you.
Near whom, Therese?
Did you say something?
No, mother.
You must have been dreaming.
How long...
does it take to drown?
To sink down into the murk,
how long?
It's very late.
We've worn you down.
Oh, no, no.
No.
I'm thankful for that.
- And please do come again soon.
- Madame.
You must try not to imagine
Camille in bits and pieces.
How should I imagine him?
Gone, just gone.
Gone?
We'll see ourselves out.
Just gone.
If I make grief an inconvenience.
Perhaps it pains them
to see you suffer.
You have a kind heart
Oh, it's nothing, Madame.
No.
No, it's not nothing.
It's comfort, Laurent,
and you give it gladly.
Lock up the shop as you leave.
Of course.
Therese, I need you.
Don't...Don't ever do that
to me again.
Therese. I can't sleep.
I haven't slept in months.
Let me come to your room tonight.
No. No, we have to wait.
Why did We kill him?
- To be together.
- Exactly.
I can't sleep. I keep having
nightmares about it.
Darling, as soon as we're married
and sleep in the same bed together,
all of the nightmares will stop.
Let's just leave.
We'll leave tonight.
- I don't care where we go.
- Therese. Stop.
If we left right now,
we'd go straight to the guillotine.
Soon. We'll have each other
and the shop.
Oh, I don't care about the shop.
Well, you should care about
the shop. It's yours now.
I don't know, Laurent.
Everything is in her name.
Nothing was in his name,
not even a bank account.
What?
Yes. Nothing.
Can you grieve a little more?
Therese, have you
made any tea?
Therese, what is that sound?
Therese?
Oh!
- Suzanne.
- My, you scared me!
Just making sure all the doors
were locked up tight.
I never realized the shop
had a side door.
Hmm. Both doors are secure.
It's heartbreaking.
Just heartbreaking.
Mmm. Perhaps we should
just let them be.
I should help.
It's a beautiful evening.
Let me walk you home.
Um...
We'll take the long way.
Yes.
How sick is Therese?
I beg your pardon?
She's as white as
a slab of marble, Madame.
Her eyes are empty,
her skin is dull,
and either she's sick
as a dog or...
Or what?
Or she's sick of lying alone
in an empty bed.
Father!
Well, wouldn't you be?
I only wonder if anyone
even remembers.
Remembers what, Madame?
That I had a son who died
just eight months ago.
But shouldn't Therese move on?
Well, of course she should.
I don't..I don't know.
It's as if she's fading away.
Madame, I've seen
many things in my life,
and I can tell you
with absolute certainty
that that woman is dying
of a broken heart.
From a bleeding wound
that never heals.
Marriage is the cure.
Marriage?
No. Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's not possible, no.
- Who would she marry?
- Who else but Laurent?
Oh.
More respectful
to Camille's memory
than were she to marry
a stranger.
A stranger?
Oh, no. No.
No, not--not a stranger.
Not at this late chapter in my life.
A stranger?
They're watching us.
Do you miss me?
Yes.
That's not very convincing.
Well, sometimes at night
when I'm afraid, I miss you then.
Only sometimes?
Well, sometimes...
I lie in my great big bed
completely alone
for the first time in my life and...
I feel like a little girl again.
Once we're married
it'll be like it used to be.
Have you taken a mistress?
No.
I can smell her from here.
What does she look like?
She looks like you.
- But it's over.
- Really? Why?
Because I couldn't
remember her name.
I'd be dreaming and I'd whisper
your name in her ear.
Does she have red hair?
Therese.
With the love and support
of our dear friends,
I'm ready to discuss
your marriage.
Marriage, mother?
But to..to whom?
But I love Laurent as a brother.
I happily accept, Madame,
if Therese will have me.
Camille slipped from these hands.
I will never let that happen to you.
Ever.
Amen.
Since Therese is the last
of our family,
I have decided to change my will
and put it in both of your names.
Upon my passing,
you will receive the shop
and 20,000 francs.
That's hardly a fortune,
but it will be yours.
Bound by a tie more powerful
than love money.
Shall we go celebrate?
Madame's really outdone herself
with our room.
New sheets, fresh flowers.
Therese.
Oh. Madame has..
- Take it down.
- It's only a painting.
If it's only a painting,
why are we whispering?
That scar on your neck.
It was bright red today
at the church.
Was it?
Mmm. How did you...
Don't.
We've dreamt of this moment
for so long
and now the dream's come true.
Remember you said that you wanted
to fall asleep in my arms?
And then wake up with me
warm beside you?
Did I?
Yes.
And now we can.
Now that Camille is gone...
Oh, no!
Why did you say his name?
What?
You say it.
Oh, I can't.
Therese, say it!
Camille.
See? What happened?
Nothing.
Why?
Because he's gone.
He's dead.
Camille? Camille?
How badly did he die?
You didn't see?
I closed my eyes.
When?
Stop it!
You're tickling me!
No!
I was gentle, Therese.
I lowered him into the water
like it was a bath.
Show me how.
He didn't fight?
No he was quiet
like it was bath time.
Show me.
Don't lie to me.
He didn't go gently, did he?
I closed my eyes.
I couldn't close my ears.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- I heard him call my name.
Therese!
- Therese!
- Shh! Stop it!
Stop it.
Do you know what tonight is?
I'd almost forgotten.
It's our wedding night.
We were married the moment
I stepped into that boat.
Madame.
Hmm?
Oh, perhaps Therese
might like a ginger biscuit.
Every afternoon since the wedding.
I'm not much for napping myself.
Do you like the chicken?
Yes. Thank you
for bringing me lunch.
Lunchtime used to mean something...
very different for us.
We're settling in.
I have to get back to work.
Mother.
When I was a girl,
a summer's day...
Oh, there she goes again.
Tell us about a summer's day.
Oh. I babble on and on and on.
As I drift away.
How long will it take?
I think I shall turn...
and see someone I knew.
Someone I loved.
A summer's day, spun out like...
sugar...
spun white.
What?
What spun? What? Oh.
You--you said a day.
We thought the cowpats
were stepping-stones
and my sister Amalie
stepped on one
and screamed again,
and I laughed so hard, I thought...
Mother.
Oh!
Shh.
Madame? Laurent!
- Madame?
- Mother?
Try to get her to move unassisted
as often as possible.
The smallest movement will help.
Certainly.
And encourage her to talk,
even moan a little.
The slightest sound may help her
regain her speech.
So how can she be able to...
You know, she's very lucky
to have the two of you
to watch over her.
Good night.
Good night, doctor.
We're all alone now.
Carry her down to the shop
before you leave.
All right.
Ready, mother?
You need both of our signatures
to get the money.
Good morning!
We'll be right down.
Laurent, time to go home.
Yeah. Just finishing up.
You should learn how to cook.
You should learn how to eat.
If only I was more like Camille.
Hmm?
Well, it's getting late, isn't it?
You should be in bed.
I don't know who you are
sometimes.
Till death do us part, dear.
Therese!
What?
Stop the ticking.
The ticking is the only thing
that drowns you out.
I'm not saying a word.
You are. I can hear you.
What am I saying?
Exactly what I'm saying.
You're not saying anything.
The boat.
The afternoon.
- The sun going down.
- Shh.
- The fog.
- Come here, come here!
The shore is gone,
the boat is drifting.
We're all alone.
He sees my face.
He starts to shout.
I grab his throat.
"Therese!"
I lift him up and he bites my neck.
- He screams your name.
- "Therese!"
- I heave him in!
And then he's gone.
That's right, he's gone.
You killed him?
You liar! You liar!
Liar!
You wanted him dead!
You begged me to kill him.
We killed him!
Then why does he only haunt you?
Are you out of your mind?
You know he comes to you
every night.
He slithers into your dreams
and you wake up screaming.
I scream because you hold on
too tight
and your nails bite into my skin!
Oh.
Oh, God.
Go ahead, say something.
Spit in my face.
Tell me to go to hell.
Where do you think
you are now?
Therese!
Therese! Where do you think
you're going? Get over here.
- Let go of me.
- What are you doing?
Tea, Madame?
Six or the two?
Oh, I see. Voilà.
She sparkles at the six
and won't look at the two, so six.
Simple.
My mind over her dead matter.
Then what is she writing?
Beg pardon?
While you were going on,
her fingers were tracing letters.
- Watch.
- Hmm?
Uh, start over again, Madame.
What's that look like?
It's a T.
- It's a T, isn't it?
- Isn't that a T?
H.
E, the...
The something.
The...
- Let me see.
- Darling, you're just on my leg.
R-
- E.
There but for the grace...
- Shut up, Grivet.
- Shh!
What's the next one?
- S.
- Is that an S?
- It's an S.
- That is an S.
- E. Therese?
- E. Therese.
Thank you, professor.
Therese.
She's written "Therese."
Oh.
Therese...
- Therese and...
- Therese and Laurent!
That's what she's written--
"Therese and Laurent."
Aw.
Therese and Laurent.
- A.
R-
- E.
- E!
Therese and Laurent are--
What, Madame?
- Oh.
- She's tired herself.
No need for her to finish.
Just look in her eyes.
Therese and Laurent are...
wonderful children
who treat me very well.
Am I right?
Why is she crying?
Gratitude.
No, mother.
We are the ones
that are grateful to you. Shh.
Ohh.
- To a perfect couple.
- Yes.
Perfect couple.
This is a happy home.
Good people live here.
Are those headaches back?
I can't take it.
The two of you can't fool me
for another moment.
I predict an addition
to this little family
- in eight months.
- Oh, no. No, Suzanne,
- I'm...
- Hmm?
No, I'm certain.
That's not it.
Thank you.
I'm going to go lie down.
My head is throbbing.
I'll listen for the bell.
I forgot my buttons.
I've changed my mind.
I have to get out of here.
Go ahead. Hmm?
Bore a hole right through me.
Right here.
Who sold me into marriage,
hmm?
Who would do anything
to keep from being alone?
You.
Drink up. It's time to go.
The bar closed half an hour ago.
- Sorry, darling.
- No, don't leave.
Well, we can't stay here.
Don't..don't leave.
Don't leave. Please stay.
Sorry, darling.
No, please stay.
You must stay.
Could I buy you a drink?
I have one.
Can I buy you?
I'm free.
Hmm.
Get up on this table.
Come on. Lift your skirt.
For what?
Come on. You'll see.
This will make it all better.
Hang on.
Go on. Yeah.
One second. Hold on.
I don't want you.
Prussic acid.
Quick as lightning.
Tiniest drop you'll never
see those rats again.
Have a good morning.
Laurent?
Laurent, come and get her.
Hello?
Madame?
Oh.
We'll be right down, Suzanne.
- Oh, no!
- Careful!
Suzanne?
I loved your son.
Please.
And if you could forgive me,
I'd kill myself and end in peace.
Please, do you forgive me?
Do you forgive...
Do you forgive me?
Get off the floor.
- Forgive me, please.
- Oh, get off the floor!
- Please.
- Yes, she forgives you!
Look! She forgives you!
She wishes that she had
a dozen children
so you could kill them all
as well!
- They've come for us, Therese.
- I'm sorry.
Go see who it is.
I want this over.
Therese, go see who it is.
Go! Go!
May I help you, sir'?
Olivier.
Ah, I, uh I didn't hear
you come down.
Is Suzanne with you?
No. No, I was just passing by.
We haven't seen any of you
in so long.
I know.
Madame has been very ill.
May I say hello to her?
She's sound asleep.
I'll tell her you stopped in.
Yes, let her know
that we send our best.
Mmm.
Well, hopefully we'll start
our Thursday evenings very soon.
She misses them so much.
As do we.
Olivier.
Your hat.
Oh.
Have a good morning.
It's all gone.
The shop is completely empty.
It's been abandoned.
- This way?
- The river.
They're headed this way?
Did you ever love me?
Yes.
When he was alive.
I loved you.
After I killed him.
We killed him.
Do you want some wine?
Yes.
I want to kiss you.
From your neck to your thigh.
- Put my tongue inside--
- We did all that.
Do it.
No. You.
This way, this way.
Down there.
Therese!