Yeah, we'll see about that.
I wanna be traded.
Here's Tommy. Tommy, Tommy, Tommy.
Happy Halloween!
I thought we were all
dressing as babies.
Sorry. Sorry.
Hey, baby, you're behind me.
I just wanna tell you I love you!
- No biking in the video.
- Here.
- Doesn't make sense.
- Oh, gosh. All right.
- Enough.
- Dan, why are you so flexible?
Let's get out of this...
Did you see that?
There it is!
It's really cold!
No, you don't.
- I think I'm filming.
- Are you filming? Thanks.
So, Jack, anything you wanna say to Dan?
'Cause this is it, buddy.
Tommy?
Don't you think if you're shooting the
wedding you should wear some pants?
Hi, how are you?
Dan, today is your day, my friend,
and we are happy to be here.
Tommy even wore his lucky boxers.
We're here for you, brother,
and we love you.
Lauren is late.
She's gotta be freaking
out that I'm late.
Any pre-wedding advice for Dan and Skylar?
Put the other person's needs first.
Maybe that's why I'm still single.
Quit chasing after
the wrong girls, buddy.
How you feeling, buddy?
Do not film me while I'm peeing.
That's not gonna make the video.
Oh, it is, it is.
I left my car running
outside if you wanna bolt.
Your car wouldn't make it
out of the parking lot.
- It's a piece.
- What? Just put some new tires on it.
Could always hijack the limo.
You need to find yourself
a girl like Skylar.
Groom wisdom. Nice.
I'm serious. There's nothing better than
being in an honest, committed relationship.
Coming from the guy who
just joined the church
because his fiancée wouldn't
have married him otherwise.
Hey, the girl gets what she wants, bro.
Gentlemen.
- Mr. Chapman.
Congrats. Hey, nice wedding.
Okay, if this is as compelling content
as you're getting, we're gonna be in trouble.
- I got great stuff with Dan. Wait till you see it.
- I'm sure.
Get out of the way.
Just trying to capture the good,
the bad and the ugly.
Did you just use the word "ugly"
at Skylar's wedding?
I did.
- You know, you could help.
- I am. I got you in focus.
You gonna catch the bouquet?
Yeah, she is.
All right, let's do this.
Do you, Dan, take Skylar to
be your lawfully wedded wife,
and, forsaking all others,
keep thee only unto her,
so long as you both shall live?
I do.
And do you, Skylar, take Dan to
be your lawfully wedded husband?
- I do.
- The rings?
I give you this ring as a
sign of my promise to you.
With all that I have and
all that I am, I honor you.
I give you this ring as a
sign of my promise to you.
And with all that I have and
all that I am, I will honor you.
And now, by the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss your bride.
Dan! Come here!
- Hi.
- Hey.
Are you the videographer or something?
Documentaries.
I'm doing it as a favor for Dan.
I was his wingman throughout LSU.
Sorry, my name... I'm Tommy.
Ashton. Nice to meet you.
Nice meeting you. I'll facebook you.
She's taken, Tommy.
Story of my life.
Father, we come here today
to thank you for Skylar and Dan
and the gift they are to all of us here.
We ask that you keep them close
and keep them in your
heart and bless them.
- Amen.
What?
It's on me.
I will never forget when
Dan called me and said,
"I'm gonna ask Skylar to marry me."
Dan said to me, "When you find the one,
"whether you believe in God,
whether you believe in fate or whatever,
"you act on it."
And you did, and I tip my hat
to you for doing just that.
So let's give a warm round of
applause for the bride and the groom.
Cake for the girl at table one.
Is it diet?
Come on, you gotta be done
starving yourself. The wedding's over.
Good point.
Look at that.
So cute.
I've seen you in action at
weddings before, all right,
and currently you're not dancing
on a table or breaking glasses.
Come on. It's me.
I'm at my best friend's wedding and
I'm upset because my boyfriend
just gave a speech on
how important it is
to act on it when you cross
paths with the right person.
It was a pretty good speech.
I crossed paths with
Jack seven years ago.
No, no, I get it. I get it. I get it.
I'm so lame. I'm sorry.
No, you're not lame. Okay?
You are a catch.
Yeah. Most amazing girl I've ever met.
What?
- Top 100 for sure.
- Good. Funny.
But probably number one.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
It's time for the bouquet toss.
Come on, ladies.
One!
- Two!
- Throw it over here, Skylar.
Three!
Let's get Jack here!
Jack, get up here!
Hey, baby. You okay?
- I gotta go.
- Why?
- What happened?
- Don't worry about it.
Is everything okay?
I love you, and I show it.
So I don't get it.
Either you don't love me, or you have a
really crappy way of letting me know it.
Am I missing something?
Seriously, I don't know what...
You rolled your eyes. It was a joke.
- Honey, I'm sorry.
- I can't do this anymore.
Wait. Hold on.
Please don't leave. Please.
I love you. I'm sorry. We...
Tommy. Really? Come on, man.
- Tommy, please?
- What's going on?
Come on, man. I know you got
a camera, but... Ally! Ally!
What's going on?
We'll just talk after.
We'll give her some time to cool down.
Let's go back and party. Come on.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Come on. Let's go.
Thanks for heading up to our room
to get the presents, Tommy.
Yeah, no problem.
Now that I have you guys trapped,
let me ask you this.
What is the secret to staying
married so many years?
I'm always right.
That's actually correct.
Skylar, if you're watching this now,
your wedding was absolutely perfect.
Would she have it any other way?
It should have been at the church.
It was her choice,
even if it's not what we wanted.
And Skylar always gets what she wants?
Like mother, like...
- Did you feel that?
- It just got so cold.
Mr. Chapman... Mrs. Chapman,
what's wrong? You okay?
You okay, Mr. Chapman?
Somebody help me! Help me!
Somebody help me!
What's happening?
She's not breathing.
Does anyone know CPR?
Tommy! Tommy!
Jack, I'm coming.
Stay there. I'm coming.
Sky!
I can't find her!
She's dead. She's not waking up.
Have you seen my parents?
- My mom? Please?
- Hey, Jack.
Jack. Jack.
Jack.
I was with Skylar's parents in the
elevator, and they just fell dead.
- What?
- They fell over. They just fell dead.
What?
Skylar, your parents were in
the elevator, and they just...
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- Allison. Allison.
Sounded like a missile.
Come outside. Come on.
So close!
Look out! Get back!
Did you see that? Jack, Jack, come on!
Earthquake! Watch out! Watch out!
Run!
Tommy, look out!
Run! Come on, Sky!
Stay with me, Sky!
Get away from the window!
What is that?
Okay?
- I need to find Ally.
- We don't know where she is.
My phone doesn't have any service.
Does yours?
- Check my phone.
- It says she's at 45 North.
- When did she text you that?
- About a half hour ago. We gotta go.
Tommy!
So what do you think
killed all those people?
Why are we still alive?
The fact that there was an earthquake
and the lightning like that.
- I've never seen anything like that.
- Did you see their eyes?
- Maybe it's aliens!
- Yeah, Dan, it's aliens!
Look, guys, over here.
Over here, over here!
I'll stay right here with you, ma'am.
- Keep your head up.
- You okay, Sky?
Does that hurt you?
I heard my parents talk
about this for years.
What?
- It's the biblical end of the world.
- Don't be ridiculous.
It's not ridiculous.
All the good people are gone and
all the bad people are left here.
Whatever's happening is rooted
with science, all right, not fantasy.
- No. You're wrong.
- Am I? You go to church, right?
You're a good person,
you're still alive,
so it's obviously not the
biblical end of the world.
Guys, enough with the religious BS, okay?
It's happened, it's done,
and we all survived.
It's not the end of the world.
We have to get to safety,
'cause things are gonna get really bad.
What do you call this?
It's hail.
Go, go, go!
Don't let go of my hand!
Here! Come on! Get in the library!
Keep going!
Skylar! No!
- Where's Skylar?
- What?
- What do you mean?
Sky!
Get back. Skylar?
Skylar?
You go that way. You go that way.
- Skylar?
Where are you?
Skylar?
He's dead. He won't bite.
Sam.
Yeah, I was kind of looking for...
Skylar?
Skylar? Skylar? Skylar? Sky!
- What's going on?
- There's got to be a Bible in here somewhere.
I'm gonna prove to you
guys what's going on.
Five rows over.
Sky, what are you doing?
Storm's passed. We need to find Ally.
Skylar, seriously?
Is this what you wanted?
See this?
- Is that a Bible?
- Yes, it's a Bible, Jack.
- It's not in here.
- What?
Rapture. It's not in here.
- Rapture?
- Hail.
- She's looking for Rapture.
- Hail. Hail.
Bro, come on. We gotta get Ally.
Hail.
"When the first one blew his trumpet,
there came hail and fire mixed with blood."
Sky, that's not helping.
That's not helping us.
I shouldn't be here. I went to church.
I did everything right.
You'll be okay. We're gonna be okay.
Stop.
It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
Let's get out of here.
- You guys, please! We can't leave!
- We're going to 45 North.
We're not going. No!
You don't understand.
- We can't go out there.
- She might be at the church on Camp Street.
She texted you 45 North.
You're right. You're right.
But I know she likes to go to that
church when she's upset and I'm...
When does Ally go to church, Tommy?
Every time you guys get in
a fight, she ends up there.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm her best friend.
- It's a new thing for her.
- We're going to 45 North.
The church is closer, all right?
And it's on the way.
- I think we should maybe check it out.
- What are you guys talking about?
- We have to stay here where it's safe.
- Fine. We're gonna go to the church.
We're staying.
Sky, this place isn't safe, all right?
What if there's another earthquake?
There's no food. There's no supplies.
- We gotta get going, we gotta stay together.
- No, I'm not going.
There's safety in numbers.
He's right. We should go.
Wait, "we"?
Yeah, we.
All right, well,
we gotta get moving. Let's go.
- This is a bad idea.
- We have to stay together.
Come on.
The church is on the
other side of First...
What is going on?
What could have brought
down these planes?
Do you believe me now?
Stay together. Stay together, guys.
- Is the church up ahead?
- Come on. Keep moving, guys.
Okay, where is everybody?
Where are the people? What's that?
It's the carriage to our...
I don't understand.
Dear God, please help me.
I don't understand what's going on.
What are you doing?
- Sky, praying isn't gonna help us.
- I'm sorry for not believing in...
- Can you hold up?
- We gotta keep moving, Dan.
- Come on.
- It's gonna be okay. All right?
- Please.
- Keep moving.
- Just don't let go of me, okay?
- I won't.
Did you hear that?
No.
Exactly. It just got quiet.
- What was that sound?
- I don't know. Let's keep moving.
Something's wrong.
Something just flew by. Feel that?
God, please be with us.
Keep going.
Lord, we really need you right now.
Something's in the tree.
What is that?
I didn't let go. I didn't let go!
She was right here.
She was right here! I didn't let go!
I didn't let go!
What are you talking about?
Where did she go?
Dan!
Sky?
Skylar! Skylar!
The church is right there!
Let's get inside! Go, go, go!
Help! Help!
Hey!
Help!
Get in. Get in.
Is she all right?
Do you know what did this to her?
Do you know what's happening?
You dropped this.
All the words are missing.
Let's get her into the sanctuary.
Help them, Doug. Sanctuary, please.
Inside. Inside.
- Put me down. Put me down.
- Are we gonna be safe in here?
Yes. I think so.
I'm Pastor Shay. And you are?
- Tommy. This is Jack.
- Tommy. Jack.
- Sam.
- Sam, Skylar, Dan.
Let's get some help for your friend.
I'll find Nurse Rachel.
Rachel! Nurse Rachel! We need help!
- Ally?
- Jack!
Jack! Tommy!
Sky! Is she hurt?
She's okay. Are you okay?
You came looking for me.
I tried to call. Everything was dead.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- How did you know I was here?
Tommy.
Where's Lauren? Where's everyone else?
They're dead, honey. They're all dead.
I'm sorry, honey.
What happened?
What did this to her?
We need to clean out that wound.
Looks like a stab wound.
It's okay. It's okay.
Remember when you
walked into Jack's party?
My jaw literally dropped. Yeah.
I never saw anybody so
beautiful in my whole life.
I love you, Ms. Gardner.
I'm gonna have to lift
the arm to reset it.
Mrs. Gardner.
Ready?
Good. Now the left side.
- Can we maybe give her a minute?
- No. Just do it.
Okay, hey, hey, hey.
You remember when we went
to go get our marriage license
and the office was over that crazy deli?
We had to wait for a copy
looking at pig's feet.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
Do you have any idea
what's going on out there?
The Rapture.
Right out of the New
Testament of the Bible.
Come on.
You mean the thingy where Jesus
teleports the good to heaven...
The believers.
- ...and leaves us heathens...
- The nonbelievers.
We are all presented
with the same evidence.
I guess it's
what conclusion you
wish to draw from it.
I don't draw anything from it.
What do you think attacked your friend?
Aliens, maybe. I don't know.
I can't really explain it.
Aliens?
We'll find out soon enough.
There's more survivors coming in.
- Bring them inside.
- One of them's pregnant.
- Wet some towels.
- It's all right. Just breathe.
Remember, breathe. Breathe.
There we go. Breathe.
- One more.
- Hold my hand.
Yes!
One last one. One last one.
It's a boy.
Can I hold him? Please?
Why isn't he crying?
Follow me.
You...
You knew the baby was
gonna be a stillborn.
I knew.
He was an innocent.
Why would God kill all these
people and an innocent baby?
He didn't.
He left their mortal bodies
behind and he took their souls.
That baby, he didn't get death.
He got eternal life. Bliss.
I was at home with my family
when they all were taken.
Then I heard the first trumpet.
- First trumpet?
- You didn't hear it?
I froze.
Knew instantly.
And all I could think
to do was come here.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Wasn't my loss. It was their gain.
Why weren't you taken?
Why wasn't I taken?
You know, just because you
have a church and a title
doesn't mean that you have real faith.
I had no relationship.
I just had comfort.
And that is how I failed.
All right, guys, come on, come on.
Circle up. Circle up.
All right, all of us. Come on.
- So how's Skylar?
- She's all right.
Ally and Dan are back there with her.
So what do you want to do?
Hole up here.
Hole up here? Hole up here until what?
We don't know what's going on out there.
So at least in here it
seems like we're safe.
So you just wanna sit in
here and see what happens?
Until we figure out a
better plan, Tommy.
Maybe we should move,
find another place.
To where?
Can't exactly move Skylar, can we?
Let me in! Let me in!
Help me! Help me!
My name's Tommy Covington.
If you are watching this,
then I'm probably dead.
It's been 10 hours since everything started,
and we made it to a church, found help.
If anything happens, Ally,
there's something I wanna...
I wanna say.
What are you doing?
I don't like people filming me.
Says the guy filming everyone.
So, what's so important
you need to tell Ally?
- It's complicated.
- Complicated.
Don't you think fire and ice falling
from the sky should uncomplicate things?
Yeah. Probably.
Then tell her what you wanted to say.
I'll show it to her
if something happens.
Allison, I...
When I met you seven years ago,
we just clicked.
Truth is,
I've loved you every day since.
And if it's not me,
I just want you to be happy.
Feel better?
Video footage has been streaming
in on a worldwide mysterious illness
that strikes without warning
and has caused millions of
fatalities in the past hour.
Oh, my God. Geez.
People are...
- Help!
- Say something.
This isn't right.
This isn't happening. What in...
Leading experts from around the globe
have been unable to determine
the cause of what is being labeled
"instant death syndrome."
The syndrome strikes without warning
and has universally caused death
in children and infants worldwide
as well as random segments
of the adult population.
- Are you okay?
- The car's on fire.
Get the extinguisher!
- What's going on?
- We need help over here!
Give me a hand! She's hurt!
- Are you okay?
- She's not breathing.
Go get it, Max. Yeah.
Talk to me. Are you guys okay?
We will continue to upload
videos as the story progresses
and we'll bring you breaking updates
as soon as we have them.
I'm so sorry about how
I left the reception.
It's okay.
It seems pretty stupid now.
I'm sorry that I was
the reason you left.
You came looking for me.
That's all that matters.
So how long you been
going to this church?
About six months.
I don't know, it's not like an
every Sunday thing or anything.
How come you never told me?
I knew you'd laugh. Or roll your eyes.
Yeah, I probably would've.
Then.
Not anymore.
Surprise!
- Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday, Mom!
We got you.
Happy birthday!
I love you all so much,
and you're so wonderful.
So where are your parents?
Killed.
Taken. Whatever they're calling it.
Sorry.
I hope you don't mind crunchy.
You wanna add anaphylactic
shock to our day?
I'm allergic.
Note to self. Note to self.
So, why are you here?
You're obviously a good person.
I am a good person.
Just not a churchy good person.
- You never went?
- I'm not really a "sit in a pew" kind of girl.
Guess I blew that one.
Yeah, yeah, I guess I did, too.
Are you this comforting all the time?
No, no, just...
Just when the world's ending.
We have received several eyewitness
accounts of unusual weather patterns.
Reports and images from around the world
are both troubling and foreboding.
The National Weather Service
has issued storm warnings
and travel advisories
from coast to coast
in the wake of this
unprecedented devastation.
Federal, state and local officials
are asking all individuals
to stay indoors.
Stay in your homes for the time being.
Safety is of utmost importance
at this very unpredictable time.
We're safe, okay? We're almost...
I don't know what I was waiting for.
I think I was waiting for a sign,
some "eureka" moment to happen.
And all you gotta do is make a choice.
I love you.
And I know
that I wanna marry you.
Guys. You gotta see this.
I was filming and I caught it on tape.
I didn't let go. I didn't let go!
She was right here!
- May I see what you're looking at?
- Yeah.
Revelations 9.
I didn't let go!
And the fifth angel sounded his
trumpet and opened the abyss.
The sun and sky were darkened
and locusts fell upon the earth.
Their hair was like women's hair,
their teeth were like lion's teeth,
and their wings made the sound
like the thundering of many
horses rushing into battle.
Look, you can see it when
I go frame to frame.
They were given stingers like that
of scorpions to torment people.
What is this thing?
One of the fallen.
And what do they want?
To torture. To destroy.
Can we fight them?
No.
This is the first season
of bad things to come.
What, the first?
It's only gonna get worse.
- It's not right.
- What's not right, baby?
How do you feel?
I've given you the last dose of Vicodin,
so your pain should come down
just a little bit. Okay, sweetie?
No. Don't touch that.
- Let me look. Just let me look.
- No, stop. It's burning.
- No, it's okay.
- Please, no, it's burning.
I gotta get up. Stop! I wanna get...
Get out of here.
- I gotta get out of here!
- Calm down. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Listen to me.
It's already getting infected, and I don't
have any antibiotics in here to help her.
Where do I get her the
medicine she needs?
My car. I have some sample
packets of amoxicillin,
but it's just too dangerous
to go out there.
- Give me the keys.
- It's not safe to go out there.
I'm going with you.
I'll go too.
We got this.
Let's go.
It's a green Chrysler minivan
blocked in on the Sixth Street side.
Just out of the parking lot.
- There's an SUV there, I think.
- Wait. You think?
I'm sorry. I got blocked in.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We'll find it. It's okay.
Keys?
Thanks.
Listen. The sample packets of amoxicillin
are in a duffel bag at the back of my van.
Hey, you sure you don't want me to go?
No, we're good.
- You sure about this?
- Yeah.
You hear that?
You should get in the
church where it's safe.
- Here's the SUV.
- Here it is!
- Unlock it.
- Why isn't it opening?
Unlock it!
I have an idea.
Tommy, lights!
I know what's going on!
Don't believe what the
government is feeding you.
There was no viral outbreak.
- Turn that off!
- No terrorist attack.
There are millions of
dead all around us.
All the children are dead.
This was the Rapture.
You need to understand that
there is only one way to God.
Only one way to eternal life.
You listen to me.
- Stop what you're doing, get down on your...
- I got it, I got it!
Something hit the front.
You don't act for God.
The power of Christ compels you!
Run! Go!
Run, Tommy! Come on, Tommy, come on!
They're coming.
Run, Tommy! Run!
Run! Run! Run!
Open the door!
Tommy!
You made it. Oh, good.
You got it. You got it.
What do you want to say to camera?
I don't know. Like a confession?
Sure. Yeah.
Get something off your chest.
I don't have anything to confess.
What do you want to say, Jack?
Tommy, why are you still filming?
'Cause if we don't make it out of this,
- somebody needs to know what happened.
- Don't say that.
We're gonna make it out of this, okay?
My name is Jack Turner.
I don't know why this is happening.
Don't know why.
But it's not gonna beat me.
I'm not ready to call it quits.
I don't know why you're filming.
Tommy, come on!
Do you love Allison?
Of course.
And it's taken you seven
years to figure that out?
- What?
- I just want to know how you feel.
Tommy, what are you doing?
I almost lost her today.
How do you think that feels, Tommy?
So it takes losing her
to feel something?
That's not love, Jack. She deserves
somebody who loves her, all right?
- She's a great girl. Seven years?
- What?
- Seven years?
- Stop it.
Do you know what I think it is, Tommy?
I think you got a confession
you need to make, Tommy.
- Guys! Guys!
- So go on. Say it.
- I don't have one.
- Come on. Say it.
- Say what?
- Say it!
- Don't!
- Say what?
You hang out with her all day.
- Guys, stop. Stop. Stop.
- You don't date.
- So say it, Tommy!
- Say what?
It's not so fun now that
I got the camera, is it?
Say it.
- Say it, Tommy.
- Stop it.
Fine.
I love you, Allison.
- I knew it.
- What?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Jack, stop it! Guys, stop it!
Stop! Now! Stop!
- Katie Murphy.
- What?
It was after the LSU-Alabama game.
I drove Katie home.
And it was just a moment.
We just got caught up in it.
We both did, and it happened.
I tried to tell her
before we got married.
She deserves to know the truth, right?
Dan, it doesn't matter now.
Everything matters now.
Don't you see that?
I'm sorry.
So, Tommy, confession time
was a good idea.
What'd we learn from that?
You're an idiot.
This is an emergency notification alert.
During this emergency,
please seek shelter immediately.
Do not leave your home,
and avoid going out at night.
If you are unable to survive
under your current conditions,
search for a place of refuge set up
by civil and military authorities.
Civil and military authorities
are establishing relief centers
in major metropolitan areas.
- You okay?
- All broadcast and cable systems
shall transmit this
emergency alert message...
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's see how she's doing.
There's nothing I can do for her.
- The antibiotics aren't working.
- What do you mean?
The infection, it's spreading.
It's acting like a venom.
You said she needed antibiotics,
and now you're saying you're not sure.
I've never seen anything
like this before.
She needs an antivenom like
Anascorp or a doctor who can help.
I'm sorry.
- I'm going to the hospital.
- No, wait, wait.
It's on the other side of
the freeway, all right?
On the other side of the freeway?
We almost didn't make it 30 feet.
I know it's not a good plan, all right,
but we got to save Sky.
- It's a couple hours till dawn.
- What does that have to do with anything?
Listen, those things, okay, whatever they are,
they've only attacked at night.
Maybe they're nocturnal.
Does she even have a couple hours?
She's a fighter.
She's fought it this long.
I'd wait until morning.
Pastor Shay wants to talk
to everyone in the sanctuary.
We leave for the hospital the
second the sun comes up.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, guys.
Come in.
You know, that was the first
real prayer I ever said.
Do you have any idea
how powerful it feels?
Can't say that I do.
It's not too late for us to believe, Tommy.
God still loves us all.
And if I do make it...
If we make it out of this mess,
we'll be raptured?
No. The Rapture is over.
- We missed that boat.
- Well, that's no good.
But we have hope in the path to the
Father and his gift of eternal life.
You have to make a choice, Tommy.
And what are you going to do?
I'm going to be a pastor
for the first time in my life.
For those of you whom I
haven't met, I am Pastor Shay.
And I have been a fraud.
It's true.
I walk through this sanctuary
with my soul asleep.
In Matthew, Jesus said
there will be those who use his name
in fancy speeches and sermons,
and Jesus said unto them,
"I never knew you."
Forgive me, Jesus. I never knew you.
I was a charlatan.
I was a traveling salesman passing
through life hocking his wares.
Like you and you.
I needed something miraculous
to open my eyes to the truth.
To see clearly.
I hold myself responsible
not only for my failed faith,
but everyone yet still
stands here today.
This is our wake-up call.
The path before us will not be easy.
It will not go unchallenged.
And this path will lead to pain
and suffering, even death.
But real life, eternal life,
is where the path leads.
But this is our opportunity.
I can now show you the way.
We can share this journey together.
Everyone, get to the basement!
Come on! Keep running! Keep running!
Keep running! Keep up with me!
- Where's Rachel?
- Has anyone seen Nurse Rachel?
Is Rachel in here? Rachel?
It's right above us.
Tommy? Tommy, what is it?
Everyone be quiet.
Sam.
Rachel!
- Help me! Help me!
- Rachel! Rachel!
Rachel!
Rachel! Rachel! Rachel!
Forgive me.
There's only one way out.
They're here for me.
Shay, don't go out there. No, Shay!
Please. Please.
I don't hear anything.
I'm gonna open the door.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Come on, Sky.
The sun's up. Let's get to the hospital.
Baby, do you smell that?
Look at me. Hey. All right?
Don't look. Come on.
I think it's okay. Come on.
This is crazy.
Hey, there's nothing that way.
It's gone.
Come on, let's just get
to the relief center.
Where are these people going?
Let's find you a room.
There's got to be a doctor here.
Help her.
- Please. Please help her.
- We're getting out of here.
There's a relief center
at the Riverfront Bridge.
There's nothing. Nothing.
- You got her?
- Yeah.
The place has been ransacked,
cleaned out.
There's nothing in that pharmacy.
Guys, there's nothing left.
Hey. I'm gonna go upstairs
and find her a doctor, okay?
Someone who can help.
There has got to be a doctor here.
I'm gonna go with him.
Sam, Sam, you stay here, okay?
Tommy.
Be careful.
Jack!
Jack, wait up.
Jack.
Jack!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Look, I need this.
I can handle this on my own, Tommy.
Yeah, I know.
I read somewhere that the
light you see before you die
is just your brain releasing massive amounts
of endorphins to ease the pain of death.
Some people believe that.
There are others that believe the
light is a sign of God's existence.
Do you believe that?
I do.
Son of a...
Why do you have to get to a point where
something's going to be taken from you
for you to realize how important it is?
No need to explain. I know you love her.
Yeah.
Did you hear that?
Did you hear that? What was that?
One,
two,
three.
Let's keep going.
Hi, sweetie.
Hey.
I'm right here.
Are you still hurting?
I don't really feel anything.
I forgive you for everything.
- How did you...
- I heard you.
I love you.
Dan...
Where I grew up
if you didn't go to church,
people looked at you funny.
So that's what I did.
I never really believed.
And that's okay.
I get it now.
I love you.
Do you see that?
It's so bright.
It's beautiful.
No, please.
Stay with me, Sky. Please stay with me.
Hey. Hey.
Don't leave me.
Somebody help her, please!
Dan, there's no one here to help her.
How can you sit there
and pray to a god that would
let this happen to her?
She was your friend.
Dan!
Will you do something for me?
I was wrong, and I realize that now.
I spent my whole life telling
myself that I was spiritual
and that was enough.
Obviously, that didn't work out too well.
I hate you!
- I hate you!
- What's Dan doing?
I hate you, you hear me?
Come on! Give it to me! I'm right here!
- Dan!
- Dan, stop!
- I hate you!
- Dan, no!
- Give it to me, God!
- Dan, stop!
God, are you even listening to me?
Please.
No, Dan!
We don't have much
time left on this earth.
We have to make a decision.
Ally?
Oh, no.
Listen, maybe they're looking for us.
This way.
Ally?
No, please.
Go! Sam, run! Run! Run! Don't look back!
Don't look back! Just go!
Just go!
She's not here! Ally's not there.
Tommy, what do you see? What's wrong?
Oh, God, no.
No, no.
I was hiding.
They didn't get me. I was so scared!
You're okay. You're okay.
Let's go.
Listen, we got to go.
We need to get to the relief center.
I'm not leaving her.
You can go.
No, you were my best friends
and I will not leave you.
- I'm not leaving her! You can go!
- No.
No, I won't.
- Just go.
- No.
Jack, she's gone.
I mean it. Go.
She's...
Shut up!
Stop! Stop!
- Get off of him!
- There's nothing out there that I want.
Do you understand that?
Do you understand?
Then I'm staying, too.
So take all the time you need.
We'll stay as long as it takes.
Do you think we'll be safe there?
The military must be at
the Riverfront Bridge.
They'll have food, supplies.
They'll know what to do.
There it is.
The governor has issued an edict
asking all nonmilitary personnel
to check in at the main gate.
Food, shelter, donated clothing
and medical supplies
are available to all those in need.
For those with more serious
medical conditions,
please report to the triage area
outside our hospital tent,
where you can be evaluated
and treated in a timely manner.
If you have any further questions,
please ask any uniformed military
personnel stationed throughout the area.
You think that's where they're
setting up the church?
I heard they're bringing in a chaplain.
It's the group from the church.
You made it. Welcome.
Come and get warm.
Warm yourself here, huh?
It's good to see you.
Now what?
Get in line right over there.
Please get this to the chapel.
I need to show you guys something.
I was wrong, and I realize that now.
I spent my whole life telling
myself that I was spiritual
and that that was enough.
Obviously, that didn't
work out too well.
But now,
I found real faith.
These demons are here to
remove the Word of God.
Don't you see?
It has to be the truth.
Even they recognize it.
We all have to make a choice.
We can choose to accept and believe
and get life like we've never known it,
or continue to live selfishly,
ignoring God,
and end up dying anyway.
We all have to make a choice.
We don't have much
time left on this earth.
You have to make a decision.
I choose God.
Go! Go! Sam, run! Run! Run!
- Is he going to be okay?
- Give him some time.
Faith.
What'd you say?
They're drawn to faith.
We got to find Jack.
Wait! Tommy!
Turn off the music!
Turn it off! Turn it off!
Where's the PA? Where's the PA?
Turn off the music.
Turn the music off!
Baptism is an outward sign
of an inward commitment.
Jack!
It's also like taking the witness stand
to declare the truth of the Gospel
to all who are present.
They're coming!
Jack!
Sam!
Sam, I got you. I got you.
There's only one way, Tommy.
We have to make a choice.
Jack did. Allison did.
And I think they made the right one.
The choice is ours, Tommy.
It always has been.
Listen, don't go.
I choose God, Tommy. You should, too.