-Hey, boy. Hey. Hey, look.
-Look what?
Hey.
Hey, you better chill.
Hey, hey. Shit, nigger.
Stop putting your hands up.
This is a bridge.
Hold on. Hold on.
Shit.
Tommy?
Tommy, come on, man. Wake up, bro.
Tommy, we hit somebody. Damn.
Come on. We gotta get the fuck out of here.
Every once in a proverbial blue moon
we stumble across an author
who may verily change our lives.
Someone from we know not from where,
perhaps even Dante's own paradise,
who assembles the words
that we must read and hear.
None of your scribbler of syntax,
but a heavenly scribe of powerful ideas.
An absolute and true author.
Ladies and gentleman,
I present to you Thomas Carter.
We can do better than that for Thomas.
You're welcome.
May I ask you about
your near death experience?
Did you see a white light?
No. Nothing like that.
What did happen?
Well, that's for the next book.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Could you make this out
to Angel, please?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
You've read this a lot.
Yeah.
"It's better to light a candle
than to curse the darkness."
Why did you write that quote?
Well, it harkens back to a wise proverb.
"Self-doubt can be a demon."
I try to warn people to be mindful
of the difference between
what's harmful and what's reflective.
Do you do one-on-one sessions?
No. Sorry, not anymore.
But I can refer you elsewhere.
If you change your mind,
I could pay your fee.
Thank you, Mr. Sanchez.
What issue exactly did the book
help you overcome?
The death of my mom.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
I keep seeing her.
What do you mean by that?
I see her in all these different places.
I know that's not possible.
I know it's not true.
But I keep seeing her
in these different places.
Was she a good mother?
She was heaven.
Then she will be reborn.
And she's at peace.
It's her karma.
Thank you. Thank you.
...showers and thunderstorms expected
to continue into tomorrow morning.
Rain tapering off tomorrow afternoon,
followed by partial clearing and a high of...
What exactly is a praline?
It's good.
Your editor called.
I told him we can't do the on the road part
of the tour until after Memorial Day.
It's just weird, you know?
I mean what am I supposed to do?
Sign my signature and take pictures?
Don't do that.
People love meeting authors.
You're like a literary rock star.
Maybe you'll have some cute groupies.
I already have a cute groupie.
Yes, you do.
I'll throw my panties at you.
You left the window open.
It's okay, baby, it's just getting a breeze.
-I think I heard something.
-What?
You just heard the wind. It's okay.
-What's up, little brother?
-What the fuck!
-Jesus Christ!
-What up, punk!
What the fuck are you doing?
Man! What's up, man?
Just rode in on the bike, man.
Just come home from the county, baby.
You know I had to come and see you.
Getting that money now, baby.
You scared the hell out of me.
Don't I always?
What?
Where have you been?
Mom and Dad haven't talked to you
in almost a year.
They ain't exactly talking to me right now,
man, since I come home from the county.
You couldn't call nobody?
It's the middle of the night.
I got to call you? You're my brother.
Yeah.
Y'all are looking at me
like I’m a ghost or something.
It's me, baby.
You got a beer or something in there?
In the fridge.
Really?
I’m sorry.
He can't stay here.
I know. Just, all right...
-He can't stay here.
-Look. All right.
Let me talk to him.
Now meditation is very calming
if you stay quiet within yourself.
Close your eyes and breathe in through
your nose and out through your mouth.
Look, she can't do it.
This is weird. Why do people do this?
Think about it like looking into a mirror.
Okay? Now close your eyes.
Take a deep breath in through your nose
and out through your mouth.
Do you see your reflection?
Do you see your hair? See your smile?
And if you look really, really close,
you can see much more.
Excellent metaphor.
All right, guys.
That was a great class. Thank you.
Good job!
Now who thinks she is
the bestest teacher in the world?
Raise your hands.
Who thinks our guest today
is a bit on the lame side?
Keep your hands up
if you still think she's beautiful.
Do you and Miss Carter kiss?
Hey!
Everyone say a big thank you to Mr. Carter
for speaking to us today.
Thank you.
And thank you guys for coming.
Give yourselves a round of applause.
Good job.
See you all next week.
Hey, you did a good job today.
What's your name?
Francesca Sanchez.
I’m eight.
Who is coming to pick you up,
your mom or your dad?
My mother and father
aren't together anymore.
I’m sorry.
Guess what I do for a living?
I’m a life coach.
That means I help adults
with their problems.
And a big part of my job is keeping secrets.
So if there is something you want to say,
I won't tell anybody.
Really?
Cross my heart and promise.
Francesca.
Let's go.
Hey, Dad.
-Hey. Did you have fun?
-Yeah.
What are you looking for?
Where's the coins
Granddaddy left for both of us?
Why?
Where's the fucking coins?
What happened?
I got beat the fuck up.
What it look like happened?
By who?
Just, where's the fucking coins at, man?
How much?
I need 12G's.
$12,000!
I got jumped on, man.
I was hanging out with Crystal
and some niggers from the Ninth Ward
jumped on me.
I’m gonna kill them bitches.
They some dead motherfuckers, man.
People were after you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I’m a grown-ass man, man.
They got a bounty on my head for 12K, bro.
I’ve been sleeping on park benches.
I’ve been sleeping in the trunks of cars.
I’ve been trying to survive, man.
'Cause they gonna kill a nigger, man.
I don't got $12,000.
You got a book deal.
That was an advance. That was nothing.
You owe me, man.
-What is that supposed to mean?
-You fucking owe me.
I read about your memoirs.
I read about your near death experiences.
And you left out one thing, Tommy baby.
I was there with you.
I was with you.
That story was meant to illuminate
a changing point in my life.
That's bullshit, man. You lying.
You lying.
And the truth ain't in you.
But you ain't got to worry.
'Cause I ain't gonna tell your secret.
I’m gonna die with it, bro.
Got us a bottle of Barolo.
It's some fancy stuff.
Have a good night with your wife, man.
What was that?
Nothing.
What?
Don't worry about it. Hey.
-Hello, Meyer.
-Hello.
Mr. Meyer, hi.  It's Thomas Carter.
I was wondering...
I was wondering
if I could get some more money?
I could add a couple more stops
on your book tour,
but you would have to leave this Friday.
Okay. All right. Okay. All right.
-How about Chicago?
-Book it.
Consider it done. See you Friday.
Thank you, Mr. Meyer.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Looks like you hit a sewer pipe.
Me and my wife, my ex-wife,
we bought this place together.
But I just haven't been able
to bring myself to finish it up.
It's big.
You think about ever selling it?
I gotta finish it up
before I can put it on the market.
I figure you're too busy
for a simple guy like me.
You say you don't do any
private sessions anymore, right?
It seems like you were in need,
so I figured I’d reach out to you.
How much lithium you taking?
Side effects are debilitating.
The ataxia must be affecting your work.
Blurred vision.
Lack of sleep.
Look, I saw my fair share
when I was a therapist.
Are you bipolar as well?
Don't worry about me.
I believe in confidentiality. I’m like a vault.
It's a struggle.
I’m not gonna lie, it's a struggle.
May I speak frankly with you?
I don't think renovations are keeping you
from selling this house.
You want your family home.
Your center.
You keep it dark on purpose. Right?
Your denial is so deep.
And you don't know why.
Can you help me?
Well, my rate's $300.  an hour.
And we can start today.
I’m gonna wash my hands up
and I’ll be back out.
All right.
You're self-conscious.
You're a man who does not like
to admit his faults.
But I want you to be pure with me, Angel.
Tell me your deepest, darkest thoughts.
Breathe.
Breathe. Take a deep breath.
Gautama Buddha,
in the mist of his meditation,
was assailed with doubt.
Christ on the cross said, "Father,
"why has thou forsaken me." Doubt.
Breathe and release your doubt
and feel the pulse of the trees.
It's good.
Listen to the earth, Angel.
Feel the pulse of the trees.
Good.
What was that?
You didn't see anything?
No. I’m sorry. Angel, now where were we?
We're done.
-Wait. What? Wait.
-You don't get it.
My thoughts are running
through my mind so fast,
it's like channels that just keep switching.
I can't just stop them
'cause you want them to relax.
It doesn't just go away
because you tell them to.
What happened to your mother?
What's that got to do with anything?
Angel, how did she die?
I can't do this with you.
-No, I can't do this.
-Angel.
Wait, no. Look, I have an idea.
Drugs don't cure pain, they just mask it.
I have an idea, but I need your mind
to be clear for it to work.
I can't do it.
Please.
Angel, please.
Thank you.
I trust you.
-Hello?
-Hey, honey.
Just wondering where you're at.
Yeah, I just had a business thing
I had to take care of.
I've been trying to call you
and your phone kept going to voicemail.
I don't...
Look, sweetie,
I took a wrong turn off the interstate
into the wetlands somewhere, so...
Well, your dinner is cold,
but it's here when you get here.
Okay. All right, okay.
-Love your face.
-Love you, too.
Bye.
What's wrong?
Who were you with?
I was with a new patient.
You working with clients again?
It's Angel Sanchez, Francesca's father.
I know you think it's a bad idea,
but it's something I have to do.
Don't ask. I just got to do it, okay?
Trust me.
I want Ben out the house.
Okay.
Okay. He's been on the couch for too long.
-I just want him out.
-Okay.
I’ll talk to him tomorrow.
What are you scared of, Angel?
I just don't see the point of being out here.
We must face your fears head on, Angel.
I’m not afraid of the water.
I’m not. I’m afraid of the river.
When was the last time you smiled?
I don't know.
Did I scare you?
Tell me, Angel.
Be honest, Angel.
Be verbal. Come on.
You don't want to know what I’m thinking.
Look, as ridiculous as it might seem,
just be honest!
It's a boat, Angel. Smile! Try smiling!
Look, I know the distress you feel.
Don't hold it in. Release it.
Toss it out, Angel.
Breathe, Angel. Yeah.
Breathe, Angel.
Breathe.
Are you mocking me?
What are we doing?
They took my mom before her time.
I’m all fucked up.
I’m empty inside.
I didn't pay you to bring me out here.
I didn't pay you for no boat rides.
I paid you to get rid of my pain.
All right, Angel.
All right.
Which one is hers?
This one at the end. This one.
How do you feel, Angel?
You have to speak to your mother.
Talk to her. Open up.
Breathe, Angel.
Then what? These memories
are not just gonna go away just 'cause...
Repeat after me.
Talk to her.
Mom, I miss you.
I love you so much.
I can't figure out a way to let you go.
And that is selfish of me.
Breathe, Angel.
I can't.
And that is selfish of me.
Angel, could you lead everyone in please?
We're here to invite AngeI’s mother in
one last time,
for one last visit,
then she will be free to move on.
Angel, sit there.
Those were her favorite.
Where do you want it?
-There is fine.
-Okay.
We've prepared this meal for nourishment,
for AngeI’s mother, for her journey home.
Daddy, I’m scared.
It's  okay,  Franny. I’m not gonna let
anything happen to you, okay?
Nothing is gonna happen, Francesca.
We're just here to help your daddy, okay?
-You know what? Jessica.
-Yes?
Can you take Francesca
into the kitchen with you?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
I don't know about all this.
The boy is just sad 'cause his mama passed.
This isn't as much a ritual
as it is a way to help Angel
let go of his mother.
I’m glad you said that
'cause this is a Christian house.
For the purposes we're here,
you can think of this as a therapy session.
I wanted AngeI’s relatives here because
you share the same blood as him.
There's not too much
you can't accomplish as a family.
And together you can pray
to your ancestors to guide AngeI’s mother.
And then we can rejoice
in her transformation.
For your ancestors.
I give them fresh water to clear their path.
Angel, can you give me names of relatives
who have passed away?
My dad.
Fred Sanchez.
Uncle Charles.
My Aunt Jane.
-Maurice.
-My cousin. My cousin Edward.
Let's ask them
to meet your mother
and help her on her path
to heaven.
Shall we pray?
Do you have your wishes?
-Yeah.
-Put them in the fire.
Okay?
Come with me.
Sit here.
Angel, let's pray that your mother
moves into the next life.
With all your family here,
let's ask her to move on.
Let's pray
that she will go into the afterlife.
She leaves you
with nothing but her love.
You won't hold her here any longer.
All the sorrow is being washed away.
She's gone, Angel.
She's gone to continue her journey.
She's free.
That leaves you with nothing but her love.
Open your eyes.
Mama.
She's here.
She's still here.
You mean, you feel her presence?
No, no. She's standing.
She's standing right there.
Something's wrong with him.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I’m not sick. I’m not crazy.
She's here.
She's gone into the next life.
She's gone.
Get out! Go!
Go! Get out of the house!
Go!
Angel, I don't think you understand.
You gotta go.
-You gotta go.
-Okay.
You gotta go.
Get out.
Hey, here.
Fuck that. I’m cool.
It's cash. It'll get you out of it. Take it.
You think that little shit
you doing is something?
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
I rearranged my entire life for this.
I just came home from the pen, bro.
Working for 35 cents a day.
And I’ll go work for $5 an hour, man.
Fuck your money, bro.
What the hell are you talking about?
You said you were in trouble
and they were gonna hurt you.
I bought three weeks with them dudes, man.
Your money don't mean shit to me, bro.
You got a problem with me?
Yeah, you can't buy me.
I been knowing her. I introduced you to her.
She wasn't nothing
but a little old bartender.
You had the college degree,
you had the money.
You chose her.
And she chose you, over me, bro.
Now you acting all high and mighty
and fancy and all that.
'Cause you some kind of little therapist
and some shit like that.
And people think you're pure.
But, nigger, I know you.
You ain't shit, nigger.
Go look in the fucking mirror.
Oh, yeah, here's your cut
of Granddaddy's coin collection.
You were giving him money?
Is Ben the reason
you started taking clients again?
The father of that girl
in my yoga class, for him?
My brother's gone. I hope you're happy.
I got to go pack for my trip.
Tommy?
Are you serious?
You came.
I made us some dinner.
What do you think of the place?
-Nice.
-It's nice, right?
Yeah. It's nice.
It's been so energized ever since your visit.
I was cleaning.
I’ve been cleaning all day long.
I feel so good.
Listen, Angel,
I’m afraid I can't continue our sessions.
But I paid you already.
Full refund.
I don't understand.
I wanted to tell you in person.
I’m leaving town.
-For how long?
-A few weeks.
That's fine. A couple weeks is nothing.
But I think you still
should speak with someone.
Just to help you keep that balance.
You know?
So I wrote down some of my colleagues'
names and numbers for you.
For you to contact.
You don't understand.
See, my little girl is coming over
and my wife, Sophie, she's coming with her.
I was thinking that you could meet her
and you would be able to tell her
that I’m getting better
and that you've worked it out.
That we've worked it out,
that you've fixed things.
Angel.
Fixed.
Another time.
How about you just stay for a drink?
Just a drink?
I can't. Thank you.
I understand.
You got important places to be.
I don't mean to bother you.
Thanks for coming in the first place.
One last hug?
Well, I hope that your journey
brings you to where you need to go.
You, too.
She says you can't leave.
What is this?
Angel?
Where am I?
Angel!
Angel.
Answer me.
You hear me?
What are you doing?
Angel. No. No.
Angel!
Franny, stay up there.
What are you doing down there?
Stay up there. All right?
I had a bad dream.
Okay. I’ll come up, all right?
I’ll be right there.
Close that door for me, all right?
Angel, look, why am I...
Why am I here? What are you doing?
Where am I?
All right. Listen carefully, okay?
I’ve been gone a whole night, all right?
Sooner or later my wife is gonna
figure out something is wrong. Right?
You know what she's gonna do?
She's gonna call the police.
And you know what that means? Cops.
They're gonna come here,
they're gonna see what you're doing to me,
and they are gonna arrest you.
Angel, everybody,
your whole family, your wife,
everybody's gonna be heartbroken.
You're never gonna see
your daughter again.
Is that what you want, Angel?
-Is that what you want?
-Have some cleanser.
Keep your mouth closed.
Cleanse away your soul.
How long do you think
you can keep me here?
You made this up, not me.
Help!
Can anybody hear me?
You know, the people
who designed this house,
they're quacks.
It's a bomb shelter.
You remember when people used to be,
like, afraid of the Russians?
It sounds crazy now,
but remember, Russians?
Is anybody out there? Help!
Can you hear me?
Maybe you should yell to Mr. Yang.
Mr. Yang!
That's my neighbors.
They live right next door.
They're not here right now, though.
They had to go to their son's graduation.
I sent them... I sent them a card.
Angel,
let me go.
I can't.
Want to tell me what you're feeling?
Why?
Because this lack of reason
is not you, Angel.
It comes from a place of confusion inside.
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah.
This state of mind is strong.
It's toxic.
Makes you feel like you've split.
One side is making the other side
question your basic humanity.
Right? But look, don't blame yourself.
Don't blame yourself. It's not you. Okay?
Look at me.
I’m not crazy!
Then why am I tied up, Angel?
To tell the truth.
It's that simple.
You can trust me. I value privacy.
I’m like a vault.
Tell me all your secrets
and I’ll let you go.
Who taught you that?
I got to see this through.
You got to see what through?
Look, our decisions make our paths.
Don't make bad decisions.
Angel, look,
think about what this will mean
in your next life.
You are so smooth.
Do you know that? You are so smooth.
Do you even believe the things
that you say? Do you believe them?
You didn't want to be alone. I get that.
But this isn't the correct way
to handle this, Angel.
You think this is because I’m lonely?
Is that what you think?
You'd rather believe that
there's something wrong with me.
You think that I’m losing my mind,
that I can't think straight.
I was mistaken. I’m sorry.
I was wrong. I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
I’m not gonna let you infect my ideas.
I’m not gonna let you get inside of my mind.
Wake up!
Wake up, Tommy!
Are you ready?
No, Angel. Angel, don't.
Whatever you're thinking, don't do it, Angel.
I was just trying to help, Angel.
I was just trying to help.
I’m sorry!
Bring forth that which is within you.
That which is within you, will save you.
Hello?
Maggie, it's Meyer. Where's Tommy?
Isn't he with you?
No, no, no, he flew off alone.
I’m supposed to meet him later.
He missed his book signing.
-What?
-Yes.
Are you sure he has his dates right?
Have you heard from him?
-I got a text from him, he said he was okay.
-Well, just sit tight. We'll track him down.
Have him call me
when he gets to Chicago. Good?
Yeah, I will.
I have a confession.
This house used to be happy.
Once.
Water.
I need water.
You know, I read this, you know.
It opened something in me
that I thought was lost.
How to channel optimism.
I can't feel anything.
To be optimistic.
It says here,
"If we aren't positive,
it will show and we will flounder."
"Flounder." That's a great word.
Why are you keeping me here, huh?
Are you ready to embrace your words?
What do you want?
Are you ready to go
on a journey of healing with me?
There's stages. There's stages.
There's steps in your book.
Let's start at the beginning.
Down the road of virtue.
You know, a person can't be at peace
if they have negative attitudes.
Optimism. That's what I want from you.
I want you to turn that frown upside down.
Sometimes I failed, it couldn't always work.
But I’m telling you, if you just smile,
just smile, doesn't mean you feel it,
something will change.
Smile!
Just smile! You know what?
I don't need this.
I don't have time for this shit!
When you're ready, I’ll be back.
I’ll be back in a few hours.
Maybe you'll think about it then.
No. Angel. No.
You're serious.
I’m waiting.
Smile.
Watch me.
Do a little Snoopy dance.
Smile.
You're faking it!
It's very strong.
Hydromorphone.
lt works.
You didn't even wake up
when I pushed that through your leg.
-Angel.
-You don't even feel any pain.
You will feel pain.
Please, look, I need a hospital.
This book right here, your book, it says,
you are committed
to help individuals find their path.
Individuals.
What do I look like to you?
You just abandoned me!
What are you... Look, I wrote the book
to help people find a better life.
That's what I do!
I know what I’m talking about. All right?
Call Dillard and ask them
what my two graduate degrees are in.
Clinical Studies.
And the second is in Theology.
It's better for my patients if I know both.
You're making this very hard on yourself.
Only the truth
will set you free.
No. Angel.
I need a hospital.
Angel! No!
It's Tommy. Leave a message.
Hey, it's me.
I need to talk to you.
Call me back please.
What?
Angel, please. Give me a shot.
I want you, when I uncover your eyes,
to see the world anew.
The good, the bad, skillful deeds.
See it in the mind.
Only then,
can you see who you really are.
These are your words.
Is that the lesson?
You wrote, "The first truth
shows the presence
"of suffering.
"The second truth seeks
to determine the source
"of suffering."
No. No.
Oh, my God, Angel. No, please.
God, no! Okay.
Okay, I killed a cat.
I killed a cat. I killed a cat.
Go on.
I killed my mom's cat in third grade.
I wanted to see if it was true
if a cat had nine lives or not.
So I took my mom's cat in the garage
and I choked it.
It took a long time for it to die
and it scratched the shit out of me.
My mom found the cat in the trash
and she was crushed.
My dad wanted to beat me,
but my big brother Ben stepped in
and took the blame.
He's been a bad guy
and I’ve been a good guy ever since.
I see.
Worst thing that you've ever done?
Yes.
I swear to God.
Why did you work with me?
I mean, you said before that
you weren't taking any new clients,
but you sought me out,
you were looking for me.
Money. My brother needed the money.
Were you just using me?
Yes. Now could you please
let me out of here? Please?
You could die right here in this place
in a peaceful way or a painful way.
If you keep lying,
you're gonna live to regret it.
It's your phone.
Hey. It's your wife.
Don't you talk to her.
Don't.
Don't talk to her.
That's for the cat.
Hey.
You want me to read you
a spooky ghost story?
Not tonight.
Hey, there's something
talking to me from down there.
-That was you.
-It was not me.
I’m telling you.
He's down there talking to me.
There's monsters in the basement.
No!
For real. There are really scary monsters...
I’m gonna take Leonard with me.
We're gonna go downstairs.
We're gonna take care
of those nasty monsters.
Love you.
Don't die.
Good job, Cathy.
Try a little tighter. A little tighter.
Good girl.
Excuse me. Is this Karma Kids Yoga?
-Yeah.
-Hi.
I’m here to pick up my daughter Francesca.
-She didn't make it today.
-What?
Her father was supposed
to bring her to class.
Well, schedules can sneak up on you.
It happens all the time.
No. Her father always sticks to the schedule.
You want to use my cell?
No. You know what? He lives right nearby.
I can just stop over there.
My husband, Tommy Carter,
he's been working with Angel.
Is he in construction, too?
No, he's a life coach.
-They were in sessions last week.
-Oh, no.
I doubt that.
Angel doesn't really open up to people.
I really gotta go find her.
Thank you!
Fuck.
You were in her room.
The next stage
is acceptance.
Acceptance of who we are.
Acceptance of our situation.
Acceptance of what we become.
Rules!
You come clean and it will stop.
Okay. All right.
Okay.
My brother was in love with a girl
who worked at Chantilly Lane, a bar.
A bar uptown.
He used to make me go with him
just so he could see her smile.
He said her smile used to melt him.
I talked to her
and made her go out on a date with him.
But the two of them didn't work out.
-When he got arrested...
-Yeah.
...I went back to that bar
and her smile melted me, too.
I never visited him in prison
because I felt so bad.
I felt wrong.
Yeah.
Angel,
why are you keeping me here?
Don't.
Angel?
Help!
-Don't make a sound.
-Help me!
-Help! Somebody help me!
-Shut up!
Angel, open up. It's me.
Okay, she was supposed to be at yoga.
You cannot just switch up the plans
on me without telling me.
She didn't want to go.
I didn't want to make her.
It's because she doesn't want to take yoga.
She wants to take ballet.
You're the one who pushed her to take yoga.
-Sophie.
-Where is she?
She's fine. Okay.
She's fine. She's upstairs,
she's doing her homework. I got this.
What's all this? Is this blood?
Wow. Yeah. I guess so. I...
I’ve been working so hard, I probably
nicked myself, I didn't even realize it.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
Okay, you need to start
being honest with me.
Look, I cannot risk leaving her here if you...
Hey, Mom.
Hi, baby.
-Sweetie, you okay?
-Yes.
Daddy, can you please help me
clean Leonard's bowl?
Sophie, please don't make her think
there's something wrong with me.
I can't take that.
Don't do it. Don't. Don't.
Don't let her think that.
Daddy, you coming?
Daddy, will be right in, baby.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Take your pills.
Let me walk you to your car, all right?
Hey, what did you do with all that
horrible plastic you had everywhere?
I... Let me move this.
I took it down
and I wrapped up some garbage
and threw it in the basement.
You know, you should fix this place up.
Try to sell it. Get a fresh start, you know.
I mean, there's just too much stuff that
needs to be fixed up right now. I mean...
Hey. Hey. Hey.
-Sorry.
-Close your eyes.
-Okay.
-Close your eyes. Okay?
Yeah.
Now remember your mama taught me this.
She said,
"Wipe the trouble away.
"Let the beauty in.
"Let the beauty in."
Angel, don't go back to that dark place.
You hear me?
I...
I’ve been having sessions
with this guy and...
-Really?
-Yeah, I’ve been working on
getting past my issues.
He's been helping me channel all that.
-Really?
-Yeah, it's working.
I never would have thought you...
That's great.
Just say you'll come home.
I can't.
Soon, right?
I...
I’m done with the living room.
And I’ve been trying to finish those cabinets
in the kitchen that you always wanted.
Trying to make it really, really special.
Beautiful.
Perfect for you.
I know you are.
Why don't you try to make it
beautiful for you?
I can't make it beautiful for me
if you're not there.
Please, I can't...
-I can't make it perfect unless you're there.
-Angel. Angel. Angel.
It doesn't work like that. I need you.
-Angel.
-I need you.
I’ll call you later, okay?
I love you.
Hello?
Hey, if you can hear me, call the police.
Hello!
Hey. What are you doing?
Daddy! Listen, listen,
there's monsters in the drain.
You ready to go?
Come on.
Thank you. Let's go.
If you can hear me, call the police.
Your mama was an amazing woman.
I’m so sorry.
You know, Sophie, I’m sorry.
I just need a little space, okay?
I just need a little space. I’m sorry.
You need to take your pills, baby.
Take your pills.
Some space.
So, this is where you work?
Yeah. Beats living in the streets.
What's happening?
Have you talked to Tommy?
No, I ain't talked to him.
I haven't heard from him.
I’ve been calling him.
This isn't like him.
His editor doesn't even know where he is.
You know, Tommy made his own bed, sis.
He got to lay in it.
Why do you hate him?
What, you thought it was gonna be roses?
You thought I was gonna be happy
'cause you and him was together?
Look, Maggie, you see me in here
working these little odd jobs.
I’m trying to do the right thing.
I’m trying to show you
that I can play in the same lane.
Why? I love Tommy. I love him.
And when I find him,
I’m gonna tell him I love him.
Why don't you just kill me?
Certain actions bring upon oneself
certain inevitable reactions.
You're not misinterpreting my book.
You're just bat shit crazy.
You ever heard of
a man named António Egas Moniz?
He won the Nobel prize.
Over. For a procedure that cured the brain.
Lobotomy.
Angel, you can't do this.
Sophie, everybody's gonna be heartbroken.
You'll never ever see your daughter again.
Is that what you want?
You know.
"It's better to light a candle
than curse the darkness."
than to curse the darkness."
Why did you write that quote?
A psychic quoted to you a line I said
and because of that it's my fault?
I’ve never even seen your mother.
You're lying.
I’m telling the truth.
My near death experience
was a car accident.
I swear. Ask my brother. He was there.
No!
It can't be true. It's not true.
I don't even know what the bayou looks like.
-You're lying.
-Look at me.
-I’m not lying to you.
-No.
I know the pain you must be feeling,
but no matter how much you torture me,
it won't bring her back.
Her death is the effect and you are cause.
It has to be.
Let me help you.
Untie me. You got the wrong guy.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Stay calm. Stay calm. Stay calm.
"Don't look back."
What's that supposed to mean?
Do you do one-on-one sessions?
If you change your mind,
I could pay your fee.
No! The signs all pointed to you!
You're seeing connection
where there is only coincidence.
There is no such thing as coincidence.
That's in your book.
You wrote it in your book.
Angel, you don't believe that.
In my heart, I believe that you're guilty.
You're guilty.
That weight, it just rots you to the bone.
It's a cancer.
And that is why I’m being haunted.
I’m sorry for what I’m about to do.
You gave me no choice.
Angel. Angel.
Wait.
Thank you. I’ll see you next week.
-Okay. Bye.
-Bye.
Olly olly oxen free, you can't find me.
Franny.
Franny, I don't have time for this.
I can't play with you right now. Okay?
Olly olly oxen free, you can't find me.
Franny.
I need you to come out. Come out right now.
Franny. Franny. Come out right now.
I don't have time for this.
Franny!
You can't find me.
Gotcha!
You know what? I almost didn't find you.
You're getting too good for me.
I was gonna hide in the basement,
but it was locked.
Well, you know, you promised that
you'd stay up there till I came to get you.
-You remember that, right?
-I did. I just came down to surprise you.
Yeah, you surprised me.
All right, Franny.
Stay in here and get some rest, okay.
Maggie's here.
She's upstairs.
Ben's here.
It's Tommy. Leave a message.
Yo, bro, I’m here at this place
you told me to come to.
They got boards
all over the fucking windows.
Call me back.
I’m going to stick around for a few.
Help me.
Help.
Maggie?
Baby.
Are you okay?
What did he do to you?
Don't worry. Almost done.
You still got some fight in you huh?
I wanted to bring Tommy's family here
because you share the same blood as him.
And as you know there is not too much
a family can't accomplish together.
Even telling the truth.
Right now, what are you thinking?
This is about me, right?
I’m not talking to you, Tommy.
I’m talking to her.
Do you love him?
Yes, very much.
Do you believe in the things he says?
Things that he teaches?
Is he an honest man? That's the question.
Yes. He's a very honest man.
You know, here's the thing.
You are all about to die.
That's a fact. That's going to happen.
The question is
do you want to die with regrets?
Ben, is there something you want to share
with the group before you die?
You don't know what the fuck
I’ve done for you.
You fucked my life up, man.
I’m always covering for your ass.
I’m always looking out for Tommy's ass
ever since we was kids.
We was both tanked that night.
We was both drunk as fuck.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop putting your hands up.
Wait. Wait. Look here.
This is a bridge.
God damn.
What the fuck, man.
Damn.
Man.
Come on, man. Wake up, bro.
Tommy, we hit somebody.
Damn. Come on.
Tommy.
Shit.
Come on, man.
Just stay right there, bro.
My mother died in agony.
That's what you're telling me?
Angel, I am so sorry.
No, you're not. You're still holding back.
-That's right.
-You're holding back.
There's more to that story.
I heard her voice.
I was so scared.
Help me.
Ben.
Where are you going?
The weeks went by
and they never found her.
And it was history.
Tommy?
Tommy, baby, tell me that's not true.
Tell me.
I knew...
Knew I was right.
I’m so sorry.
One sound, you die.
Daddy?
I’m almost done in there.
Okay?
Come on.
Let's go.
How'd you get out?
I opened the door, silly.
Yeah, but I locked the door.
Come on, tell me,
how'd you get out of there?
Grandma.
What do you mean?
Grandma unlocked the door.
She says, "Wipe the trouble out
"and let the beauty in."
She says if I did this to you,
you'll calm down, Daddy.
And then she said goodbye.
She did?
Yes.
I love you so much.
Why don't you practice
your piano for me. Okay?
Only one hour, then I’ll be back.
All right?
Okay.
You're letting us go?
He's free now.
Tommy?
We're already dead.
What the fuck, bro?
We're spiritually dead.
Tommy?
What you doing, man?
Don't do anything crazy, bro.