- Is that your son?
- Uh, yes, sir.
Big fan of the Justice League?
(LAUGHING) Yeah.
He used to play with
a toy submarine I gave him,
but not anymore.
His dad can't compete with
heroes like Superman around.
(CHUCKLING) Well, not
all heroes wear capes.
- Yes, sir.
- Take us,
investigating an SOS beacon
in the middle of the Atlantic.
- That's pretty heroic.
- (LOUD WHIRRING)
What is it? What's wrong?
Sonar has inbound, sir.
Impossible! It's open
ocean for miles.
Computer has 15,
no, 22 separate inbound.
Evasive maneuvers, now!
Captain, the inbound,
they've changed course.
(RAPID BEEPING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Sir, 37, now 55,
inbound still on target.
We have to return fire!
At what? We don't know
what's chasing us.
Coming in hot.
Impact in T-minus 15.
- They look like...
- Like what?
- T-minus 10.
- Like people.
Brace for impact!
(ALL GRUNTING)
We've lost propulsion.
- Engine room, report.
- Taking water, Captain.
(MEN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
- (GASPING)
- (METAL SWISHING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Engine room. Engine room!
(LOUD FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(ALL GASPING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
SOS, this is the
SS California with
an emergency SOS.
We're under attack.
I only hope somebody's...
(SCREAMING)
This is Colonel Trevor,
Government Liaison
to the Justice League.
No, we changed it last week.
Justice League tested better.
- (CRANKING)
- Oh, crap!
GIRL: (GIGGLING) Victor,
wait up!
(GIGGLES)
(GASPS)
VICTOR: No, not now.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
It's time, Victor.
Time to wake up.
No, please.
Just a little longer.
Please.
(GASPING)
Dr. Charles.
Please, Vic, it's Sarah.
Right. Sarah, I forgot.
I came by to see how you were
doing after the operation.
Fine. The environmental
upgrades you and my
dad made to my systems
will make me
more useful in the field.
And you're okay with us
replacing your remaining
human lung?
At this point I'm more
machine than man anyway.
As long as I have
my brain and heart intact,
I'll be all right.
Uh, okay. Well, I guess
I'll check you later?
Yeah, do that.
(DOOR OPENING)
Way to go, Stone.
COMPUTER VOICE:
Incoming call
from Silas Stone.
Ignore.
Figured I'd find you here.
You're always here.
Naval sub went dark
and sank to the ocean floor,
mid-Pacific.
Pulling it up now.
(MEN SCREAMING)
Sounds like
they're being slaughtered.
The Navy wants their missiles
back and I want to know
what happened.
I'll boom down there
and check it out myself.
- You want help?
- If it was done manually
I won't be able to track
anything besides
the point of access.
Maybe security cameras
could give me a visual.
-I meant you could
call the League.
-I know what you meant.
Until we have answers,
no need to escalate
this any higher.
Have it your way.
Let me know what you find.
Sir, the others?
They don't really
come in, at all.
Despite what you would
like the world to think,
Colonel Trevor,
there is no Justice League.
It's a beautiful view,
isn't it?
It is. I forget
to enjoy it sometimes.
WONDER WOMAN: This must have
been what the view
from Olympus was like.
We're not like the gods,
but we're not
like them either.
We're not like anyone.
- Do you ever feel alone?
- Diana, of course I do.
But I've learned
a way to deal with it.
I can show you.
ARTHUR: You know,
buddy, life sucks.
Never believed it before,
but I believe it now.
I buried my dad this week.
I'm all alone.
Hey, listen,
he's talking to himself.
He's staring at the aquarium.
Hey! Another one over here.
BARTENDER: Okay,
but I'm cutting you off
after this one, Arthur.
ARTHUR: Now, where were we?
Yo, leave him alone!
We're talking!
Arthur, I know you
miss your dad but...
(GRUNTING)
I was gonna eat that!
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
Then you're gonna have
to go through me first.
Works for me, tough guy.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(COUGHING) Wait! Whoa!
Hold on, hold on!
(GROANING) Okay, let's go.
(SCREAMING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
After all these years,
I've found him.
He's exactly what we've
been looking for, David.
We must confront him. Tonight.
Maybe we shouldn't out
him here just yet, Doctor.
We can approach him
in the morning.
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN GROANING)
Thanks, guys. I needed
to blow off some steam.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(SCOFFING) I always
kind of wondered about that.
What the hell are you?
(SCREAMING)
(SPUTTERING)
I wish I knew, pal.
I wish I knew.
Here you go, buddy.
I got to thank Sarah
for those upgrades.
No way I'm doing this
if hadn't replaced that lung.
-(BEEPING)
-AUTOMATED VOICE:
Reminder sent.
- Scan for discrepancies.
- AUTOMATED VOICE:  Scanning.
-Structure compromised.
-Yeah, I can see that,
but by what?
- Magnify.
- (BEEPING)
- Is that a handprint?
- Affirmative.
Hmm.
Accessing security footage.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Error. Files corrupted.
Damn. Locate missiles.
- Scanning. Not found.
- That's not good.
What the hell?
(GRUNTING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Servos damaged,
suggest retreat.
Hostiles in pursuit.
Boom us outta here.
Hey, Dad, I'm home.
Oh, right.
SHAZAM:
You contacted everyone?
Yeah, Billy, you came.
Sure, I prefer ditching
school for the day.
This chair
is nicer than my bed.
(LOUD WHIZZING)
Hey guys, sorry
I'm... Not late?
Where is everybody?
The human internet router's
having trouble getting
the word out.
Let's do it
the old-fashioned way.
I'll bet you like Cuban food.
I know this
sick place, in Cuba.
I'm going to
disembowel you, Barry.
Took you long enough.
Yeah, yeah, what's the what?
I was just about
to seal the deal.
Cyborg's got something.
All hands on deck.
- Race you to headquarters?
- We have a headquarters?
- Clark.
- Yeah?
- This actually works.
- I know it.
To hide in plain sight
as one of them.
Not hide as much as
be one of them.
The difference eludes me.
We can just
blend in, together.
Smallville, is that you?
Oh, Lois, hi.
(LOIS CLEARING THROAT)
(NERVOUSLY) I'm sorry, sorry.
This is, uh...
- Lois Lane.
- Diana Prince.
Ooh! That's some grip.
I work with Clark, closely.
We share a by-line sometimes.
Diana is a diplomat.
Oh, so this is an interview.
No, it's a date.
Oh, right.
Nice manners, farm boy.
Girl like this you
take somewhere posh.
It's a wonder women
go out with you at all.
And Diana,
love your glasses.
Thanks, they're new.
SHAZAM: Dude,
are they on a date?
WOMAN: Look, it's Cyborg.
- What are they doing here?
- I love you, Shazam!
Nice to meet you. Got to go.
- We'll need this to go.
- WOMAN: Shazam!
What, the Bat's
too good for us now?
It's Batman,
he doesn't answer hails.
Yeah, if I have to be here,
so does he.
Hal, don't do anything...
Stupid.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Scarecrow don't pay me
enough to deal with this shit.
You got that right.
There he is!
(GUNS FIRING)
Hiya, Spooky.
You don't write,
you don't call.
I'm busy.
(GUNS FIRING)
Well, clear your schedule,
because you and I...
I hate that guy.
- The League needs you.
- This is about the missiles?
Lucky guess.
Relax, I got this.
Hey there, henchdudes,
I'll be handling
your arrest today.
Get us out of here!
(GROANING)
(SIREN WAILING)
Ready? Because
we're done here.
Are we?
Who's the supplier
for the aerosol component
of the fear toxin?
(STAMMERS)
Who, who's the what now?
Who is the Scarecrow
targeting in City Hall?
No, what about
something simple.
Like where's the Scarecrow?
Bro, I caught them
for you. You're welcome.
- I didn't know...
- I didn't need them caught.
I needed them scared.
I needed information.
Next time you want to help,
do me a favor, don't.
No energy signatures.
- This was all done by hand.
- Who could do that,
besides us?
I count four dozen unique
handprints moving in sync.
Four squadrons. This was
a choreographed onslaught.
You think Darkseid's
army has returned?
No, doesn't fit.
Walk us through your assault.
Kinda cool, like watching
a 3-D movie, with no glasses.
- (GRUNTING)
- Freeze. Observations?
They avoided his gaze,
kept to the shadows,
used their element.
- These were warriors.
- Agreed. Resume.
(LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
That looked like
it hurt all over again.
Who has the force to knock
a quarter ton of metal
to the ground under water?
Freeze. That's a barrel roll.
These guys are skilled
in 360-degree combat.
Agreed. Note
the sound sensitivity.
Makes sense.
Sound travels 4.3 times
faster under water.
(COUGHING) Kiss ass!
Whatever, Mr. Barrel Roll.
Resume.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Freeze.
So that's what you look like.
Magnify.
Gills? As in... mermaids?
As in Atlantis.
Where is this?
These carvings,
I recognize them
from the  Tales of Atlantis
I read as a girl.
It sunk into the ocean,
but its people
were saved by the magic
of the King's trident
which turned them irreversibly
into creatures of the sea.
That's a fairy tale.
I believe you.
Well, of course
he does. (KISSING)
So, where is it?
The location
has been lost to time.
What does a mythical,
mystical undersea world
need with missiles?
And I so dare you
to say that five times fast.
Obviously they
plan to attack us.
Any way you look at this,
it's bad.
Uh, terrible idea,
I saw an Atlantis show
on the whatsit channel,
with this professor.
Maybe he can help us.
We're at S.T.A.R. Labs,
the greatest minds
on the planet
are right next door.
Jeez, I said, "terrible idea."
Maybe it's not.
Dr. Steven Shin,
I'm scrubbing
through his research.
He's got some pretty
out-there theories about
the existence of Atlantis.
Superman and I will
go question Dr. Shin.
When did we vote
him team leader?
What should the rest of us do?
Find Atlantis.
Now that the plans have been
set in motion, Manta,
there is no turning back.
You were right to strike
first and strike
quickly, My Liege.
My mother will not
see it as such.
She has yet to grasp
the dangers of the surfaces
you have, Prince Orm.
Soon she'll have no choice.
She's been waiting for you.
Someday, Mera,
I will be on throne
and you will guard my body.
Let's hope I fall in battle
before that day arrives.
Perhaps you will.
(KISSES) Mother.
Your transparent aggression
towards the surface world has
left Atlantis exposed, Orm.
-Do you deny it?
-That ship would have
discovered us.
Nonsense! Our magic
continues to protect us.
We are myth.
They doubt our very existence.
So we hide?
Mother, every day
the surface dwellers
grow stronger.
They have guardians with
powers that walk among them.
Guardians directly
responsible for the death
of my father!
Your king!
The volcano that killed
your father was not
the fault of the surfacers,
but the one who attacked them.
Death by collateral damage
in a surface war
does not comfort me.
They kill our race.
They poison our oceans.
They will destroy this
planet and take
Atlantis with it.
We must protect our
people and attack!
As long as I am Queen,
you will preserve
the peace, at all costs.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, Mother.
- Damn her!
- Patience, My Liege.
He has always been a problem
child, coddled by his father,
unsuitable for the throne.
Our only hope for peaceful
existence with
the surface dwellers
is with the one
who is of both worlds.
What of my other son?
Have you seen Arthur?
- Yes, my Queen.
- And?
My Queen, he is not yet
ready for the weight
of the crown.
He will learn
at my side, Mera.
Bring him to me at once.
YOUNG ARTHUR: Dad,
watch, I can get to the top.
(GIGGLING)
Not too far, Arthur.
Don't fall in.
I can do it.
I'm a better swimmer
than you are.
Arthur, no!
(GASPING)
- I told you to be careful.
- I saw her, Dad.
I saw my mother.
She was watching me
in the water.
-She kissed me.
-It was just the sea playing
tricks on you, son.
No, it was her. I saw her.
She left, Arthur,
and she's not coming back.
It's just you and me now, son.
And I'm not going anywhere.
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
(SIGHING)
These photos of Arthur Curry
are proof positive
of everything I've been
working towards.
BLACK MANTA:  I'm very pleased
for you, Doctor.
The world will have
to believe me now.
They'll know what I know.
-Call me after you've
made contact.
-I will.
Congratulations, David.
I could not have
found him without you.
Thank you, sir.
Manta to Drift 1, report.
-Payload ready, sir.
-Excellent, I will
handle the rest.
Take your men to Mercy Reef.
Give Dr. Shin
and the half-breed
my warmest regards.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
DR. SHIN:
Hello, Mr. Curry, hello?
(GROANING)
You have to go away.
(SIGHING) Go away or kill me.
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
-I must talk
to you, Mr. Curry.
Come back later.
I'm really hungry now
and not in a good way.
I've information
you need to know.
It's about your father.
(GASPING)
Thank you
for seeing me, Arthur.
I have answers for you.
I know what you seek.
All right, slow down,
slow down. I had
a rough night.
- Who are you?
- I am Dr. Steven Shin,
theoretical marine biologist.
Your father, Thomas,
contacted me.
My father's dead.
I know. He was looking
for answers and I have them.
You, my boy, are the key
to all of my research.
Okay, I'm gonna let
you in because I just can't
talk through a door anymore.
(GRUNTING)
What the hell?
- Look out!
- (ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Stand down while you can,
Arthur Curry is under
my protection by
order of Queen Atlanna.
- Relinquish him to us, Mera.
- Or what?
Or we'll take him
over your smoldering corpse.
You are welcome to try.
Fire!
(SHRIEKING)
(GROANING)
(MOANING)
Follow my lead.
I am an investigative
reporter, you know.
BATMAN: Journalism's dead.
Someone got here first.
-Looks like
it's been ransacked.
-That's not all.
Someone destroyed
Shin's life's work.
- Then where's Shin?
- Probably dead.
How do you figure?
You don't destroy someone's
work and then let them live
to recreate it.
- Good point.
- Don't touch anything!
Hmm. Who is this?
BATMAN: Whoever he is,
he's got gills, too.
Cyborg, run your facial
recognition program
off this picture.
CYBORG:  Roger that.
Name's Arthur Curry.
I got a water-logged letter
from a Thomas Curry,
but it's illegible.
Cyborg, can you
extrapolate this text?
You got it.
Coming at you now.
Thomas Curry begging
Dr. Shin for help
with his son, Arthur.
Why Shin?
Shin suspects Curry's son
is half Atlantean.
QUEEN ATLANNA: Invoke
the emergency protocols.
We must tend to
our wounded first.
Do you see? Do you see
what the surface dwellers
are capable of?
This is terrorism.
No, this is an act of war!
(ALL AGREEING)
Our people swim
in a cloud of fear
of the surfacers.
This attack tells us
what we already know.
The surface world
wants us dead.
My father distrusted
the humans.
He saw them as inferior to us.
He made plans
to cleanse the surface.
And I say we break the seal
on the Atlantean war plans.
- ALL: Yes!
- No!
War would cause senseless
ruin on both sides.
However, I hear the fear
behind my son's words.
Perhaps it is time
for our worlds to
come together.
-Heresy!
-But, my Queen,
our traditions.
Have Manta arrange
a meeting between myself
and this Justice League.
I will broker a peace
with them in person.
As you wish, Mother.
Take heart, my people.
This violence was an
isolated incident.
It is addressed.
Our magical safeguards
remain intact.
Do not fear. All is well.
(GRUNTING)
Good, you're awake.
What's this? Who are you?
I'm Mera, sent by your mother,
Queen Atlanna, to bring
you back to Atlantis.
Lady, the only
so-called mother I know
ditched me and my dad
when I was just a baby.
It's far more complicated
than that, Arthur Curry.
When she was very young,
your mother met and fell
in love with your father.
That union resulted
in your birth.
Our Queen's firstborn.
But she was royalty
and promised to our king.
She could neither wed
your father nor raise
a halfling child.
Heartbroken, she returned
to lead her people.
But she never stopped
loving you or your father.
Now she needs your help.
She believes
you are our future
and can forestall war
and bridge the two worlds.
I, I never knew any of this.
Follow me.
MERA: Your mother
kept this hidden
in these ancient ruins.
ARTHUR: What is it?
This was
our king's royal garb.
Now it is yours.
You find it yet?
Not yet.
It's a little harder
than it looks.
Well, I hope so.
It doesn't look that hard.
I'm digitally
cross-referencing every
existing mention of Atlantis.
Dude, you've gone
full workaholic on me!
I mean, you're just like
your old man!
Don't ever say that, Billy.
Hey, thanks for
that field data.
I'm still working on a patch
to quiet the servos.
Sarah, I can't talk right now.
Justice League business.
Whoo! I felt
the electricity over here.
Ask her out!
I don't think so.
Seriously, you're bionic,
not dead!
Zoom in here.
I'll tell you, Flash, man,
I've seen my share
of weirdo crapola in this job.
But Atlantis? Come on.
Are you good
with the intergalactic cops,
aliens and
the cybernetic human?
Expand that.
What can I say?
-Magic gives me
the heebie-jeebies.
-(BEEPING)
Dispatch a team
to a lighthouse in Mercy Reef.
Coordinates attached.
Find Arthur Curry, fast.
On it!
Beats looking for fairyland.
You look perfect.
She'll love you.
(STUTTERING) All right,
this is nuts.
All my life I've felt like
there was something
wrong with me.
And now, some mermaid
comes out of the sea
and tells me
my mother is alive,
and I'm the future
of some fairyland
I've never seen?
I've been lost for so long,
but now... I need some air.
(SIGHING)
MERA: Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Everything suddenly
makes sense now.
Thank you, Mera.
- But I'm no king.
- (BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(GASPING)
(EARTH RUMBLING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
- Arthur!
- (WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
Arghh!
FLASH: Found him.
Arthur Curry, I'm the Flash.
(GROWLING)
We've been looking for you.
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Retreat.
- (ALL GASPING)
- (SWORDS CLANKING)
(GROANING)
You're injured.
Hey, I've had worse.
I could bandage it.
Sure. I mean,
only if you want to.
Those guys were Atlanteans?
MERA: Trenchers,
predatory creatures
that scavenged the ocean floor
before Atlantis sunk,
sent here to kill Arthur.
We're done here. Come with me.
Why can't things just
go back to normal?
Yeah, I don't see
that happening.
Atlantis thirsts
for a new perspective.
Someone who understands
the surface world
and will lead us
into the next century.
MERA: The Queen needs
a beacon, Arthur.
Maybe it's you.
I'm the sole survivor
of my planet.
If I had the chance
to save my world
and meet one of my own race,
even for a moment,
that would be enough.
ORM: Is it done?
BLACK MANTA: No,
your half-brother lives.
Even now he heads towards
Atlantis under protection.
(GROWLING IN FRUSTRATION)
The pact with the trenchers
was your idea.
They will return hungry
for meat.
This is all falling apart!
(DOOR OPENING)
QUEEN ATLANNA: Manta,
what of my meeting
with the surface guardians?
They're on their way,
My Liege.
Excellent.
ORM: It is a mistake.
It flies in the face
of everything
my father ever wanted.
What would
you have me do, Orm,
sound the drums of war
solely to honor
your father's memory?
Don't bother.
You didn't honor him
when he was alive.
Both cruel and untrue.
I am not the only one
with your royal blood
in my veins.
Then you know.
Of your betrayal?
Or of the illegitimate heir
to the throne?
I deny nothing, Orm.
Your brother, Arthur,
can bridge the peace
between Atlantis
and the surface.
We can flourish
together in peace.
Your judgment is compromised.
You refuse
to attack the surface
because you have a son there!
A bastard elder son!
You speak to me of betrayal?
You, who spilled
Atlantean blood
and blamed it
on the surface world?
I have eyes everywhere, Orm,
and you will pay
for your treachery!
BLACK MANTA: I'm afraid
after that revelation,
my Queen,
I can't allow you to leave.
(BLACK MANTA GROANING)
Get out of my way!
This coup is over.
I am Queen and war
is not in my plans.
- (SWORD SWISHING)
- (GROANING)
But it is in mine.
BATMAN:  Shazam, Flash and I
will keep an eye out topside.
Cyborg, stay in communication.
So tell me, what's she like?
It's time you found out
for yourself, Arthur.
MERA: Welcome to Atlantis.
From now on,
your life is here.
By the gods!
That's one for the books.
It's beautiful.
This is your
birthright, Arthur.
(WHIRRING)
Batman, we're here.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Error. Unknown interference.
I can't get a signal,
in or out of this place.
Where is everyone?
Something's wrong.
(WOMAN GASPING)
Tell me, why is
the royal city deserted?
Our brave men
and women have gone
to prepare for war.
Not possible. The Queen
would never allow this.
Our Queen is dead.
Dead?
Killed by a surface dweller.
ARTHUR: Mother.
I've failed you, my Queen.
Whoever did this will pay.
Welcome, bastard.
Is Atlantis everything
you dreamed of, brother?
Or in your dream,
were you on the throne?
You killed her!
I did.
I ran the sword
through her myself
as she mewled for peace.
You can count yourself
fortunate, bastard.
At least our mother
won't be the impediment
to your life
that she was to mine.
I'll tear you apart!
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Attack!
(ALL GROANING)
Stop!
Feel my power,
surface dweller.
(GROANING)
Only royalty can wield
the magic of the trident.
Offer them to the horrors
of the dark trench!
(GROWLING)
ORM: This is war!
We will cleanse the surface!
Soon they shall know
that our time has come!
I will bring our world
rushing down upon theirs!
(BEEPING)
Uh, Batman,
still nothing from Cyborg.
But you should see this.
What's wrong? What's going on?
I know. Get it onscreen.
FLASH: The mother
of all tidal waves is heading
for the Eastern Seaboard.
Is that Metropolis?
- Secondary confirmation.
- (TYPING)
SHAZAM: Holy freaking moley!
ETA to impact.
Twenty minutes.
How are the three of us
gonna evacuate entire cities?
We can't.
People are gonna die.
(GROWLING)
Huh?
ORM:  Only royalty can wield
the magic of the trident.
ARTHUR:  Come on.
(CRACKING)
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(SQUEALING)
I'll take it
from here, Arthur.
(GRUNTING)
(WHALE SINGING)
(GROANING)
(EARTH RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
MERA: Arthur, you're alive.
We both are.
Oh, and, uh, funny story,
I talk to fish now
and they actually listen.
So I'm gonna stop
my evil half-brother
from destroying
the surface world.
Do you, um, do you wanna come?
It would be my honor.
I'm still foggy
on how you escaped.
Orm said only royalty
could control the magic
of the trident.
Guess I qualify.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Re-establishing contact.
Batman, this is Cyborg,
do you read me?
(SUPERMAN GROANING)
Are you okay?
Fine, but I'm going to shove
that magic shrimp fork
down Orm's throat.
We need to get up top.
The tidal wave
is about to hit Metropolis.
(SIREN WAILING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Atlanteans,
this is General Sam Lane
of the United States Army.
I order you to stand down.
I am King Orm
of Atlantis, General,
and you are in no position
to issue orders.
Kill the humans for Atlantis!
ATLANTEANS: For Atlantis!
For Atlantis!
- Fire!
- ATLANTEANS: For Atlantis!
ATLANTEANS: For Atlantis!
(BULLETS RICOCHETING)
My turn!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(ATLANTEANS GRUNTING)
(WHIRRING)
(ATLANTEANS GROANING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (ATLANTEANS GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
-BLACK MANTA:
Half-breed trash.
-(WHIRRING)
I won't let you ruin my plans.
(ARTHUR GRUNTING)
(ATLANTEANS GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(MAN GROANING)
John, Henry, run!
(YELLING)
(GASPING)
Well, I'll be damned.
(ATLANTEANS SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (GROANING)
(GROANING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Run, Jimmy!
(BOTH PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
Your skills
do you honor, Atlanteans,
but you face an Amazon.
(GRUNTING)
(ATLANTEANS GROANING)
I would not want
to be on her bad side.
(GRUNTING)
BLACK MANTA: All this
was my doing.
With Orm's mommy issues
and sense of entitlement,
coaxing him into war
was child's play.
Frankly, he irks
the shit out of me.
-Once we've sunk
the surface world,
-(WHIRRING)
I'll slit his throat and claim
the treasures of Atlantis...
(SCREAMING)
Outrageous.
Stop this madness, Orm!
King Orm, traitor!
This is genocide.
Billions will die. For what?
So that Atlantis
can feel safe again?
Victory is the only way
to ensure our safety.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Seize her.
Make her watch my triumph!
(GROANING)
SHAZAM: Hey, fish-head!
It seems we both
call down the lightning.
Let us see
whose magic is stronger!
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
These are
your guardians? Children?
(LAUGHING) This will be easier
than I ever dreamed!
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
I admire your determination,
but the trident is mine
to command, wench.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ORM GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
BATMAN: Lantern,
I need information.
BATMAN: We're not going to win
by hitting him
as hard as we can.
Bro, do not turn this
into a learning moment.
Anything.
Um, he killed his own mother.
Does that help?
Face me, Orm!
- (GRUNTING)
- (GROANING)
Cyborg.
-(BEEPING)
-AUTOMATED VOICE:  Error.
Error. Insufficient energy...
(POWERING DOWN)
Come on, Victor.
- Error. Error. Error.
- (WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
I'm here.
Lantern said Orm confessed
to killing his mother.
Yeah, to us.
He lied to his people.
But you saw it,
and you know what that means.
(ARTHUR GROANING)
MERA:  You killed her!
ORM:  I did.
I ran the sword
through her myself
as she mewled for peace.
You can count yourself
fortunate, bastard.
At least our mother
won't be the impediment
to your life
that she was to mine.
MERA:  You killed her!
- ORM:  I did.
- What is this?
I ran the sword
through her myself
as she mewled for peace.
You can count yourself
fortunate, bastard.
ATLANTEAN: Orm killed
our queen? We are betrayed!
ORM: No, wait. This deception
is their surface magic!
Liar!
I was there when Orm boasted
of the murder of our queen.
- MERA: It was as you see.
- (MURMURING)
I am your king!
I did this for you!
(GROANING)
Is this the king
you want, Atlanteans?
A coward who lies to you.
You need a light
to guide you in the darkness,
people of Atlantis.
My people.
What are you doing?
Becoming a beacon.
I was born of two worlds!
Atlantean by birth,
human by instinct.
Join me and we will bridge
those worlds in peace!
How's that?
Let me check.
Run system diagnostic.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
All systems operational.
Seems okay.
I mean, how does it feel?
Feels good.
Vic, we gotta go!
Whoa, am I interrupting?
Yeah, you are.
But we can pick it up
tonight. Over dinner?
I'd like that.
That's what I'm talking about!
Victor-y! Victor-y!
CYBORG: Not cool, man.
Not cool.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(CHEERING)
He looks happy.
He has found his place.
Are you free later?
If I can find my glasses.
We're standing
in the middle of Atlantis!
I'm totally geeking out.
Man, we have a weird job.
(CROWD CHEERING)
We need to consider
solidifying this team.
Like weekly meetings?
Yay! We're a book club now.
Batman's right. New threats
are springing up daily.
Agreed. Someone should
be watching.
It's funny you say that.
I have been working
on plans for a watchtower.
You can count on me. Hal?
Yeah, all right.
I don't want to
miss whatever weird
crapola comes next.
We should invite Arthur.
I'm in.
He needs a code name.
Yeah? Well, online
they're calling him "Aquaman."
I hate that.
Aquaman, it is.
You won't be too busy as King?
I have seen
the pressures of the crown.
I'll make it work.
I should keep a foothold
in both worlds.
Besides, it'll help
repair relations
if I'm seen helping out.
Well said.
You are
a gifted leader indeed.
My Liege,
trenchers have been spotted
at the edge of the city.
Finally. I've been
itching all day
for some action.
Hey, let me know
when the next meeting is!
I got to do some "King
of the Sea" stuff.
Perhaps, you should
stay behind me.
I'm the one with the trident.
Perhaps, you should
stay behind me.
(GROWLING)
(WHIRRING)
(WHALES SINGING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
You cannot keep me here!
(FLIES BUZZING)
I am of royal blood!
You will let me speak
to my brother!
I am Lex Luther.
I have a proposition for you.