( alarm clock buzzing )
( music playing )
¶ In my head
I may not know ¶
¶ What I feel
down in my soul ¶
¶ With my eyes
I may not see ¶
¶ The fire that burns
inside of me ¶
¶ Just stand strong
and hold on to hope ¶
¶ Just grab on
and don't ever let it go ¶
¶ When your back's
against the wall ¶
¶ You're not alone ¶
¶ You know
I have been set free ¶
¶ Fear has got
no grip on me ¶
¶ You know I can
see the light ¶
¶ A dead man coming
back to life ¶
¶ Just stand strong
and hold on to hope... ¶
¶ His love shines
over evil things ¶
¶ I'll be
right beside you... ¶
Right beside you!
¶ In this life
I'll be the knight ¶
¶ I'll be
right beside you... ¶
So I was thinking
maybe you'd come down
to the dealership,
sign a few balls
or something this Saturday.
Nobody wants
my autograph, Milt.
You never know, man.
Come on, seriously.
Last time worked out.
Could be a win-win
for both of us.
( groans )
Oh, there she is.
Shots.
I got this.
Don't reach
for your wallet.
All right, man.
- No, don't reach
for your wallet.
- Thank you.
- ( crowd cheering )
- Here you go, sunshine.
Next round's on me,
I guess.
- ( crowd cheering )
- Man: Thank you!
- Oh!
- Ladies and gentlemen,
I think there's
somebody here tonight
who deserves just a little bit
of recognition, all right?
- Uh-oh, here it is.
- Oh, no.
Now, it's not because
he's a regular here
at Stevie Ray's...
- ( crowd cheers )
- Hmm? Is he talking
about me?
...or because
he was an All-American
at Stevenson High School...
- ( crowd cheers )
- True story, true story.
...or even because
he was a Detroit Tiger.
Milt:
That's right!
Oh, yeah!
- ( Milt laughs )
- ( crowd cheers )
Simply because
it's his birthday.
Give it up for
Calvin Campbell.
- ( crowd cheers )
- ¶ He's a jolly
good fellow ¶
¶ He's a jolly
All:
good fellow... ¶
- Oh, a cake!
- ¶ Which nobody can deny. ¶
( music playing
on radio )
( phone chiming )
Ah, dang it.
Dang it.
Hey, Katie bear.
Hi.
You said you'd be home
by 9:30, Dad.
( sighs )
I know. I'm sorry.
Dang it, I'm sorry.
Milt and Frankie,
they wanted to celebrate
my birthday,
so they took me out
for some, uh, dinner
and we just got
a little, uh...
- You're drunk.
- No.
( chuckles )
Yeah.
Yeah, not too much
that I can't drive,
though,
if that's what
you're thinking,
'cause I'm good.
Um, sweetheart,
we're gonna celebrate
when I get home, okay?
Hello?
( music playing
on radio )
( snickers )
Oh, God.
This guy's drunk.
Look at this.
He's a mess!
( door opens )
Uh, where do you think
you're going, hmm?
- It's 11:15.
- Out with Colt.
No, no. I told you
that I didn't want you
to see that boy anymore.
Yeah?
Well, at least
somebody loves me.
You are 16 years old.
I'm 17, Dad.
What happened to us
spending my birthday together?
What happened?
I don't know.
( car door closes )
( car engine starts )
( chattering )
( kids laughs )
( TV playing )
( sizzling )
What time did you
get home?
Late.
- You making some
for me?
- Yes.
I know late.
What time?
I don't know.
Colt won his
sprint car heat.
We went out
to celebrate.
At least I got to celebrate
something with somebody.
I like my eggs
over easy.
Yeah, I want to say
something about Colt.
He's like a--
he's like a fastball
from Nolan Ryan
when he was
in the prime
of his game.
- What does that even mean?
- It means he's too much
for you to handle.
Dad, can't we just have
a normal conversation
with breakfast?
Yeah, that's fine.
( sighs )
What are you
gonna do today?
- Mall and movie.
- Hmm.
- I need the car.
- I'm using the car.
Don't you think it's about time
you got a real job again, Dad?
So we can afford things?
Like, say, two cars?
- ( skillet clangs )
- You know what?
I'm the dad
and you're the kid.
So you don't talk to me
about getting a job
or getting
a second car.
Do you understand me?
The other thing about Colt,
young lady, is that he is
too old for you.
And I know
what old kids want.
- I know what
they're after.
- Okay.
Are you guys having--
are you having sex?
Really?
Really, Dad?
( laughs )
You are such
a freaking hypocrite.
I can have
all the sex I want.
You were obviously
doing it in high school.
Yeah.
( sips )
Yeah, exactly,
and I don't want you to make
the same mistakes
that I was making.
So, I'm a mistake?
That's not
what I said, Katie.
- Wow, Dad.
- Katie...
- that's not what I said.
- Well, you did.
( sighs )
You know what?
Maybe you don't like Colt
because you're just jealous
he's an athlete on the way up
and you're... you.
- ¶ My heart holds a question
between every beat... ¶
- Dexter, how are you?
¶ Got every answer
beneath my feet ¶
¶ Fallin' apart,
but I never know why ¶
¶ Walked every road
but the one that's right ¶
¶ Been chasin' my tail
instead of my dream ¶
¶ Life's just a game,
but you play it for keeps ¶
( vocalizing )
( Calvin sighs )
- ( screeches )
- Ooh. Whoops.
( groans )
Hey, Produce,
uh...
sorry, pal,
I think I just trampled
on one of your vegetables.
A tomato is a fruit.
What'd you say?
So are avocados,
cucumbers, and olives.
- All fruits.
- Huh.
Well...
that's pretty good
information.
- Thanks.
- You're pretty smart.
- You think I'm smart?
- Uh... sure.
Do you want to see
how smart that I am?
( sighs )
You know what?
Maybe another day.
I'm just-- I'm not
really in the mood
for it today, man.
- Sorry about that.
- Okay.
Have a magnificent day.
( chuckles )
All right.
Hey, Miss Amy,
how you doing?
Hey, Produce. I'm great.
How are you doing?
- Produce: Incredible.
- Amy: Nice to see you.
Produce:
Nice to see you.
Amy:
Look what I'm getting.
Mr. Campbell,
you over there
messing with Produce?
- Excuse me.
- Oh, sorry.
Just having
a conversation
with him, Colt.
I'm sure it was
compelling.
You know?
All right, see ya.
But also putting
strawberries on the top
of waffles.
- Amy: Look at you.
- Produce: Okay.
- What else is fresh today?
- Tomatoes are fresh.
( gasps )
They look good.
Hey, Produce,
uh, thank you for
that information
over there
about the fruits
and vegetables and...
You're welcome.
My mama said
- those are not
good for you.
- This?
( chuckles )
Well, your mama sounds
like a smart person, too.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Could be good advice.
Could be good advice
if I followed it.
Hey, he's a s--
uh, you know?
- The hugging.
- He's a hugger.
What's that about?
It's just his way
of being friendly.
Yeah.
I'm Calvin.
Amy.
It's nice
to meet you, Amy.
Nice to meet you.
Would you like
to have somebody
to help you shop more?
Please help me shop.
¶ And I found the beauty
that I couldn't see ¶
¶ And it's everything
I want ¶
¶ And so much more ¶
¶ You ¶
¶ It was always you. ¶
Yeah!
Thanks, man.
That was beautiful.
Thank you.
It still needs
a lot of work,
but I appreciate it.
Look... there's no one
here, Frank.
I could really use
an extra hand cleaning up
in the back.
Laura,
I'm not the janitor.
I know, but...
Hey, buddy,
it was a beautiful song.
It got me.
They're lucky to have
you here, Frankie.
What's this?
She forget her broomstick?
She left that
for me.
Got work to do.
I'll see you later, man.
You didn't leave me
any coffee.
You know how to work
the coffeemaker, Katie.
No, you drank
it all, Dad.
There's none in the bag.
That's what I'm saying.
Well, I will--
I will run to the store
and get some more
when I'm finished
with my paper.
Hey, Dad?
How about
we go see a movie
or something later?
I'd love to, Katie,
but I think I have to meet
Milt and Frank later.
Sorry, kiddo.
Produce:
Hi, Mr. Campbell.
How you doing this afternoon?
I'm fine.
How are you?
I'm doing good.
Even when I'm doing bad,
( chuckles )
Sounds pretty deep.
- ( clicks tongue )
- Have a magnificent day.
You know what?
Um...
I wasn't being honest
with you, Produce.
I'm not fine.
Well, are you sick?
- I don't think so.
- Maybe you just need
to smile.
"A cheerful heart
is good medicine."
Where'd you get that?
A bumper sticker?
You told me
that I was smart.
- Remember?
- Yeah.
You wanna see
how smart I am?
Uh...
( coughs )
Well, I'll tell
you what.
Maybe not today,
because I gotta...
( clicks tongue )
I gotta...
- Pick up that melon.
- All right.
They label all of these
fruits and vegetables
with some numbers
on them.
But I know
the number on the top
of that melon.
- Okay, go.
- 4329.
Yeah, 4329.
That's correct.
That's impressive, Produce.
Good job.
Pear. Anjou.
4422.
Yep. Correct.
Banana.
That's the easy one.
Everybody likes bananas.
4011.
Gala apple. 4135.
Orange. 9669.
Tangerine. 3144.
Granny Smith apple.
4017.
Yeah.
There we go.
( clears throat )
I'm really impressed.
I mean, you're kinda like
"Rain Man" or something.
Like Superman or Batman!
Oh!
Ow.
You're proud of me
'cause I'm smart.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Campbell.
- No, that's all right.
He didn't realize
he was bugging you.
What did I tell you
about hugging the customers?
Now you get back
to work, young man.
You have a nice day,
Mr. Campbell.
- You, too, Dexter.
- I'm sorry about the hug.
Nah, like I said.
Hey, Produce.
I'm impressed.
- Frank?
- Hi, Susan.
Is Milt here?
Is everything okay?
( sighs )
Yeah, yeah,
it's good.
I just need
to talk to him.
Yeah, come in.
- You doing all right?
- Yeah, nice to see you.
- You, too.
- Milt.
- Hey, buddy, what's up?
- What's up, man?
- What's up?
- You doing all right?
Yeah.
What's going on?
Okay, um...
there's no easy way
to ask you this, so...
- Okay.
- I need to borrow
some money for a hotel room.
It's not long.
I'll pay you back.
- What happened?
- I got evicted.
- Hadn't paid in a while,
so kinda had it comin'.
- ( exhales sharply )
Well, you're not getting
in any hotel, all right?
You stay here, all right?
We got plenty of room.
- You're like family.
- Man, I--
No, no, no, no. Stay here.
We got plenty of room.
( clears throat )
So I got some towels
if you want to take a shower
and help yourself
to anything in the kitchen.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
( music playing
on radio )
No. Colt, hang on.
What?
What's going on?
Just slow down.
The hell are you doing?
I'm cold.
Come on, take
that jacket off,
get back in bed.
You know how many girls
wanna get with me right now?
But here I am.
I'm trying to be
faithful to you.
I just want it
to be special
for my first time.
Wait, you-- so you're--
you're a virgin?
- Yeah.
- But you said
that you've been--
I know.
I-- I lied.
I just wanted you
to like me, so I said it.
( sighs, laughs )
This is awesome,
you know that?
Listen, I got some wine
out in my Jeep, okay?
It's in a box,
so we don't need
an opener or anything.
- That's special, right?
- You don't get it.
No, you don't get it,
Katie.
You can't just tease
a guy like this.
I said just lay
back down.
( door opens )
- Calvin: Katie?
- ( door closes )
Hey, Katie?
( slurring )
Hey, Katie bear,
I just--
I just wanted
to come say good night.
( laughs )
Wha-- hey.
What are you doing
with your jacket on
in your bed, huh?
Hey, what's wrong?
( clatters )
Is there something
I can do to help?
Please get out.
Okay.
( door closes )
Hey, Mr. Campbell.
How you doing?
- ( laughs )
- Where's the shopping cart?
I don't know.
I'm not here to shop.
( clears throat )
I guess I just, uh...
I guess I just
came to talk.
- To me?
- ( laughs )
Yeah, to you.
I guess I could use
some of that magical happiness
that you always
seem to have.
- So, what's your secret?
- It's no secret, Mr. Campbell.
Well, you're doing
something right.
You're doing
a heck of a lot better
than I'm doing.
Do you think that
I'm smart enough
to do anything?
Anything in the whole
wide world?
- Well, come on.
- Uh, where are we going?
( sighs )
All right.
Where--
where are we going,
buddy?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look it.
I'm not authorized personnel.
I can't go back there.
Please, Mr. Campbell?
Come-- please?
- Come on.
- ( sighs ) All right.
- What are we doing?
What? What is this?
I'm not smart enough to be
the Employee of the Month.
Oh, shoot.
Yeah, you are.
- Really?
- Let me ask you a question.
Do you think that Colt
can name every
fruit number
on every piece of fruit
in the store?
But I can name
all the vegetables, too.
( laughs )
Yeah, exactly.
That's my point.
He can't do that.
Hey, Produce.
Sometimes...
well, sometimes life
is not fair.
You know?
And sometimes we don't
get what we want.
What do you do for work?
( laughs )
Well, uh...
I've done--
I don't know,
I've done
a few things
here and there.
I used to play
baseball.
Wow!
Will you show me how?
Well, you know,
I haven't-- whoa,
I haven't played baseball
in a long, long time, Produce.
I've always wanted
to play baseball.
You really want to learn
how to play?
Yeah!
Okay.
This is what
I want you to do.
I want you to stand
over this box.
That's the home plate.
And then you're just going
to swing this broomstick
like it's a baseball bat.
Hey, Produce?
Not on the box.
Over the box.
There you go.
Just stand like that,
okay?
All right, Produce,
I just want you to keep
your eye on the ball.
- Produce: It's an orange.
- That's very perceptive.
Just swing when it comes
near you, all right?
All righty then.
I'm going to hit
a home run!
Well, not if
I strike you out
first, kid.
You ready?
Here comes the heater.
- ( thuds )
- Oh!
- It's all right.
- Strike one.
It's all right.
Here's what I want
you to do.
I want you to keep
your shoulders in, okay?
Keep your eye
on the orange.
And I always want you
to look for the rotation
of the pitch
at its highest
point, okay?
That's when
it's leaving my--
never mind,
just...
- just swing away
and have fun.
- Okay.
Oh, yeah, Produce!
Highest point,
all right?
- ( thuds )
- Oh! Close.
All right.
There we go.
There it is!
( clapping )
- There it is.
- ( laughs )
Here comes a tomato.
Keep your eye on the ball.
- Ooh.
- All right, here we go.
Boom!
There it is!
( imitates ball whooshing )
Nice!
( laughs )
Oh! All right,
there we go.
( laughs, claps )
- Oh, no!
- Grapefruit.
Yeah!
( door opens )
Produce!
Where the heck
have you been?
Get a new apron
and get back to work!
Hey, Produce,
how's it going, man?
- Incredible, man.
- That's great.
That's great.
Listen, if you tell anyone
what you just saw,
there's gonna be
some problems for you.
But you took the bottle.
- It's not yours.
- I know.
The thing is,
I'd pay for it
if I was 21,
but I'm not,
so I can't.
- Understand?
- Understand.
- All right.
- Man: Hey, speed demon.
- Mr. Jenkins,
how are you, sir?
- Great, great.
Hey, I caught your race
last Saturday night.
- Oh, thank you.
- So when are they
gonna go ahead
and just let you race
in the 500?
( both laugh )
Oh, thank you, sir.
You're too kind.
Well, keep up
the good work, son.
You're making us all
proud around here.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, not a word,
you understand me?
- Yeah.
- All right, great.
- Hey, Produce.
- Hey, what are you
doing out here?
I was wondering if you wanted
to go somewhere with me.
Where do we
want to go?
Come on.
It'll be a surprise.
( music playing )
¶ Don't need to worry
'bout me ¶
¶ I've got everything
I need ¶
¶ To be free from
all ya other ballers ¶
¶ And when I bust out
this groove ¶
¶ You'll see the room
start to move ¶
¶ So let me
hear you holler... ¶
- Dang it!
- Calvin: It's all right.
You just need
to concentrate.
You need to keep
your eye on the ball.
And I want you to put
your elbows in.
Okay, transfer
your weight back.
The swing
is all in your wrist.
- ( pitching machine
clanking )
- Let's see.
( sighs )
I'm never gonna
hit a baseball!
You're gonna
hit a baseball
and be positive!
If you keep telling yourself
that you're never gonna hit
a baseball, guess what.
- I won't hit it.
- That's right, exactly.
Baseball is 75% mental.
Trust me.
I remember you hitting
that two-run double
off of Clemens
back in the 2000 ALCS?
Do I know you?
Steve.
Bookerson.
I was out
of the league
by 2000.
Oh.
Right, it was, uh...
'99.
Hey, Produce,
try to swing level.
Do you ever think about
getting back into the game?
Nope.
Well, that's a shame
because I'm the assistant GM
of the Louisville Bats.
We're looking to fill
our manager's position and
I'd like it to be a local boy.
You know what?
I got a kid at home
that I can't handle.
I don't think I want to be
in charge of 30 more.
Look, you were one
of the smartest players
I had ever seen back in--
Hey, don't you
get it, Steve?
I wasn't as good as you
or everyone like you
thought I was.
I couldn't hack it
when it counted and
I don't want to relive that.
Okay?
So thank you,
but no, thank you.
I just wanted to offer
you the opportunity
if you wanted it.
It's a good-paying gig.
But if you got
other stuff going on...
Not really.
Look, why don't you
stop by the stadium
Sunday evening 6:00 PM.
Sunday at 6:00?
The GM, he'd be excited
to meet you and if you
don't like it...
- Okay.
- ...you can
always walk away.
Yeah, I'll--
I'll be there.
Great.
I'll count on it.
Hey, you ready?
Hmm.
( music playing )
I had a good day
today.
I took this--
this kid who, uh...
I don't know, he's--
he's, like, slow
or whatever.
- You know?
- Slow or whatever?
Like slow like what?
- Like can't win a race?
Or slow like retarded?
- ( Frankie laughs )
Yeah, no, he's got
Down Syndrome.
I don't know.
It was a good day.
He's a happy kid.
He's a good, happy kid.
- Yeah, great.
- That's good, man.
You know what would
make me happy?
- If you buy--
- ( laughter )
How about you buy
a round of beer?
That'd make me happy.
How about that?
Katie:
Colt. Colt!
( car horn honks )
( Produce grunts )
- What are you doing?
- Stay out of this, Katie.
- Boy: You need my help, bro?
- No, man, I think I got it.
Hey!
Hey, where do you think
you're going, huh?
Katie:
What are you doing, Colt?
Stay out of this, Katie.
It's got nothing to do
with you.
Listen, man, I told you
to keep your mouth shut.
I got fired today
'cause of you.
- You did something bad.
- What?
What exactly
did I do to you?
Huh? Nothing!
I did absolutely
nothing to you.
I came to give
Mr. Campbell a melon.
( scoffs )
This melon?
You came to give
Mr. Campbell this melon?
Produce:
Yes. Don't break
Mr. Campbell's melon!
Katie: Colt!
Leave him alone, Colt!
Can't you see
he's different?!
All right, man,
you know what?
Take your melon.
Come on, guys,
let's get out of here.
( car engine starts )
Produce.
( car door closes )
What are you
doing here?
Where's Katie?
She left.
I brought you a melon.
I see that.
Um... that was
nice of you.
Does your mama know
where you are?
You don't like
my melon?
Aw...
( sighs )
That's not it
at all, Produce.
- Thank you for the melon.
- You're welcome.
So... why are you
all dirty?
Did you fall
off your bike?
- Yes.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well...
um...
do you want
a ride home?
- You smell funny.
- Yeah, it's, uh...
that's what the French
call eau de Bourbon.
( laughs )
Not funny?
( chuckles )
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna
go, uh, to sleep
'cause it's
real, real late
and, um, I'll see ya
tomorrow or whenever.
- Good-bye.
- Hey, Produce?
Hey.
Thank you
for my melon.
You're welcome.
And away he goes.
Oh, he-- Produ--
( clears throat )
Produce, you forgot
your--
hey--
( birds chirping )
( footsteps approaching )
Hey, Katie bear?
Which, uh--
which tie do you
think I should wear?
This one
or this one?
- ( chuckles ) Neither.
- No?
No, you're not much
of a tie guy.
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
Why are you
so dressed up?
Ah, I got that
meeting tonight.
( sighs )
The owners of the Bats,
you remember?
- Oh, yeah,
that's right.
- Yeah.
- That's awesome, Dad.
- Thanks.
So just call me after
and we can grab dinner
to celebrate.
Yeah, okay.
- I'd like that.
- Me, too.
- Well, all right, then,
it's a date.
- Okay.
All right.
( Produce, muffled )
Mr. Campbell!
You should tell your
mentally challenged friend
not to come
around here anymore.
Produce?
Why?
- Colt says
he's a troublemaker.
- ( laughs )
He's not a troublemaker.
Colt on the other hand...
- ( knock on door )
- Can you open the door
for him, please?
Dad, Colt is gonna
be here any minute.
Yeah, I don't care
about Colt.
Okay, well,
just make it quick.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Is that for me?
- Yes, it is.
Oh.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
I got them from
the flowers department
and they've got
plants there, too.
Oh, I'm gonna go
put them in water.
- Okay.
Yeah, he's a real
troublemaker.
- Hey, big guy.
- Hey, Mr. Campbell.
- How you doing?
- Incredible.
- That's good.
- I left my book
here last night.
- And I really need it.
- Yes, you did.
It's exactly
where you left it.
- Here you go, big guy.
- Thank you.
Hey, you look sharp.
Where you going?
Thanks.
I'm going to church.
It practically starts
in 17 minutes.
- Practically, huh?
- Look at my watch.
My mama told me
it has all the whistles
and all the bells.
Yeah, well, I think
your mama's right.
It looks like it does.
- It's a beautiful
timepiece, Produce.
- Thank you.
Uh, do you want to come
to church with me?
No.
( car pulls up,
horn honks )
It's been a long time
since someone got
me flowers.
- So, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey, Produce,
let me ask you
a question.
What do you think
of that boy?
Produce:
Well, I think
he's arrogant
and I would love
to give him a karate chop.
( laughs )
Me, too, boy.
Me, too.
All right,
have a good Sunday.
Uh, well, I don't
want to be late.
If I ride my bike,
I'll be late.
Can you please
give me a ride?
- Please?
- But I've got to go
play golf with my friend.
And then afterwards
I got a real big meeting.
- So...
- I know-- I know that.
I do understand that,
but I need a ride, please.
Give me a ride,
please.
( sighs )
All right, what time--
how-- how--
all right, just...
Calvin:
Now I'm gonna drop you off,
but I'm not going inside.
Your daughter
is extremely sweet.
Yes.
I just wish she came
with an instruction manual.
Produce:
Why would she come
with an instruction manual?
- ( siren chirps )
- ( Calvin laughs )
( police siren wailing )
Oh, crap.
- Ah, man.
- What's the matter,
Mr. Campbell?
Uh, nothing.
I had some drinks
this morning.
Damn it!
( sighs )
Do you have any--
Hey, Mr. Officer.
- Hi, Calvin.
- Hey, Mitch, how you doing?
Good, good.
What's, uh--
Wha-- what's going
on here?
Uh, well...
( clears throat )
I'm just, uh--
I'm just teaching
the boy how to drive.
- Uh-huh.
- You know?
And he's doing
pretty great.
He's just-- he's going
a little fast.
( whispers )
He doesn't know
any better.
Yeah, right,
I-- right.
( clears throat )
Well, uh...
( sighs )
Encouragement helps.
All right, uh,
you're-- you're doing
a great job here, son.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Just slow it down.
Speed kills, remember that.
Okay. Speed kills.
I'll remember that.
Speed kills.
( clears throat )
All right.
- You boys have a nice day.
- Calvin: All right.
- Produce: Thanks.
- Be careful.
Thank you, Officer.
( both sigh )
Calvin:
Good job.
Good, good.
- I think you better drive.
- ( sighs )
Well...
you're about
to drive a car.
( music playing )
Go.
Calvin:
Real slow.
Keep your eyes
on the road.
I've never driven
a car before.
- I only have a bicycle.
- Well, you're doing good.
This is incredible!
Hey, uh...
so I'm gonna be
a little late.
Yeah, something came up.
I gotta take
somebody to church
and it's taking
a little longer
than I thought.
Yeah, I'll see ya.
- ( horn honks )
- All right, all right.
( chattering )
You can't get past me.
You can't get--
( laughs )
Oh, spoiled!
Nice!
( grunts )
All right, all the way.
I got him.
- Woman: Kick it.
Do it. Ah!
- ( laughter )
You're coming inside,
Mr. Campbell?
Uh... next time.
- Promise?
- I can't promise.
Hey, is this
your secret, Produce?
It's no secret,
Mr. Campbell.
Huh.
Well, good luck at your
baseball meeting tonight.
- Thanks, bud.
- You're welcome.
- Have fun at church.
- Thanks.
Huh.
Milt:
All right, so who is she?
Who?
This friend you've been
spending all this time with.
The market, church.
Who is she
and can I please
see a picture?
Oh, it's not a lady.
I've been hanging out
with that kid, Produce.
- The retarded kid?
- Hey, easy.
It's called
Down Syndrome.
I'll tell you something,
you spend a second
with this kid
and you realize
he's just like
you and me.
Milt:
You're a genius.
What's guaranteed
to make people spend money?
The mentally handicapped--
challenged, whatever
you call it.
That's what I need
for my new dealership
commercial.
Calvin:
Like you're
gonna give money
to the Special Olympics
or something every time
you sell a car?
- What are you talking about?
- No, you tool bag.
I want him to star
in my commercial.
It's perfect.
Come on, Milt.
Okay, maybe not him,
maybe one of his special
buddies will do it.
- Hey, conversation's over.
- Cal.
Come on, man,
sales are down.
Do your old buddy Milt
a solid and call the kid.
He won't know
the difference.
Maybe he'll do it for free.
You know, he's retarded.
Hey!
I said
it's Down Syndrome.
( laughs )
Okay, what are you--
you feeling sorry
for him?
No, Milt,
I feel sorry for you.
B.S., man,
you feel sorry
for yourself.
You've been feeling sorry
for yourself since Detroit
kicked you off the team.
- What'd you just say to me?
- You heard every word
I said.
I'm not gonna sit here
and debate some loser
who can't get over the fact
that he was an embarrassment
in the majors.
What, are you
gonna freeze?
Is your whole life
just gonna freeze?
Just like you did
at home plate?
( brakes squeak )
Produce:
Mr. Campbell!
Where are you?
Produce:
Hey!
- What are you
doing up there?!
- ( Calvin groans )
( Calvin laughs )
Produce,
you scared me.
Come on.
( Calvin groans )
Hey, watch your step,
Produce.
There's all sorts of...
There's just stuff.
Did you drink
that whole bottle?
Not yet.
- Now I did.
- ( glass shatters )
( sighs )
Are you sure
that you are okay,
Mr. Campbell?
I'm okay.
Now that you're
here, I'm great.
I got my drinking buddy.
Uh, maybe we can go
to the batting cages
and be baseball buddies,
not drinking buddies?
You wanna be
my baseball buddy?
- Yeah, I do.
- Uh, okay.
Here.
First lesson...
( exhales sharply )
...when you make it
to the majors--
'cause you will--
and you're standing
at the home plate
and there's
40,000 people...
cheering for you,
expecting anything...
don't forget
to swing the bat.
I know that,
Mr. Campbell.
Gah, you knew that.
You know everything, huh?
You're a smart guy.
- ( inhales )
- ( train whistle blowing )
Okay, answer me this--
who hit the ball
400 feet on to the roof
of Stevenson High School
when he was a junior?
Was it you,
Mr. Campbell?
Uh, well,
it wasn't you,
was it?
- No, it wasn't me.
- No, it wasn't you.
Yeah, it was me.
It was me.
I was supposed
to be great.
Well, to me,
I think you're great.
Well, of course you do!
Of course you do.
You think melons are great.
- I don't like it
when you drink.
- You know what?
I don't like it
when you drink
and I don't want to be
your drinking buddy
and I don't want
to be your baseball buddy.
Do you understand me?
I don't want to be
your buddy anymore.
I'm sorry.
I have a meeting
I gotta go to
at 6:00 tonight.
( sighs )
It's, like,
a really big meeting...
with really big--
big, important people.
- ( laughing )
- ( keys clink )
Hey.
Toss 'em up.
I don't think that
you should drive.
God, toss up
the keys, Produce.
I'll call Miss Katie
to pick you up.
( sighs )
- Produce...
- I'll call Miss Katie
to pick you up.
I'm gonna come
down there, Produce.
- No!
- Co-- come here!
Come here!
( Calvin grunts )
Ah, man, Produce.
Produce. Hey!
Hey!
Produce!
Hey.
If I'm late--
I'm walking and if I'm late,
it's your fault.
It's your fault!
( groans )
Hello?
It's Calvin Campbell.
I'm here for my interview!
I'm late!
Oh, come on!
Open the door!
Hey. Hey!
Come on!
( grunts )
( sighs )
( thunder rumbling )
( bell dings )
( door closes )
( thunder crashes )
( dog barking )
( thunder crashing )
( thunder rumbling )
( coughs )
( grunts )
( crowd cheering echoes )
( crowd cheering,
whistling echoing )
( panting )
( music playing faintly )
( phone chiming )
You were supposed to call me
right after the meeting, Dad.
Katie,
it's Officer Minniear.
- Is everything okay?
- Everything's fine.
- It's, uh, just--
- What happened?
We found him passed out
in the visitors' dugout
at South,
so I need you to come
down here and pick him up.
( sighs )
Here, drink this.
- Cal, come on.
- Hmm?
Drink this.
- Thanks, Mitch.
- How you feeling?
I don't feel good.
Katie.
( groans )
- ( Calvin exhales sharply )
- No, don't touch me, Calvin!
( groans )
I'm sorry.
This is the single
most embarrassing moment
of my life.
Do you have any idea
what it's like
picking up the man
who calls himself
your father
at the police station
drunk as hell?
- I'm sorry.
- No, you're not.
You're not sorry.
You're just
a pathetic little man.
You're a pathetic
little man who lives
a pathetic little life.
- Calvin: Don't say that.
- Because it's not true?
Because
you know it is.
I'm sorry.
This isn't
how I wanted things
to turn out, Katie.
I just want to make sure
you know that I've
given up on you.
Ah, Katie, come on.
Your old man's had
a rough night.
( slurred )
Don't say that to me, Katie,
'cause you're my little girl.
- I'm sorry.
- Get in the car.
( sighs )
( door opens )
( groaning )
( door closes )
Mitch, Mitch...
Mitch,
I'm sorry.
( clanging )
It's okay.
You can--
you can yell at me,
you can scream
if you want to.
I deserve it.
Why would I do that?
I already told you
I've given up on you.
What can I do
to make this better?
You tell me
what to do, Katie.
What can I do?
Nothing.
Katie.
( door closes )
- ( water running )
- ( dishes clinking )
Produce.
Hi, Mr. Campbell.
Hey, kid.
Did you make it
to your meeting?
Uh... no.
No, I didn't.
Yeah, it's probably better
that you did not go.
You-- you're
probably right.
So, are you
still mad at me
for taking your keys?
No.
So, are you here
to shop for groceries?
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Group:
God grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change,
the courage to change
the things I can,
and the wisdom
to know the difference.
Come on in.
Uh... sorry.
Hi, I'm Amy,
and I'm an alcoholic.
Group:
Hi, Amy.
Tonight's meeting
is a closed meeting.
Anyone who has a desire
to stop drinking is
welcome to stay.
Any newcomers?
Uh...
Please stand up
and introduce yourself.
We'd like to welcome you.
Um...
( clearing throat )
( sniffles )
Hi, uh...
My name
is Calvin Campbell.
And, uh...
I live here,
St. Matthews.
And, um...
I have a daughter.
She's 17.
Uh...
who I--
I love her more
than anything.
And, um...
Yeah, that's about it.
- Amy: Hi, Calvin.
- Group: Hi, Calvin.
Hi.
Amy:
Thank you.
Um, just for future,
first name only is fine.
That's kind of
the anonymous part.
And, um...
it's customary to state
that you're an alcoholic.
That part is...
self-explanatory.
All right,
tonight I'll be
reading from step three.
"Made a decision
to turn our will and lives
over to the care of God
as we understood Him."
( sighs )
( glass shattering )
( screams )
( music playing
on radio )
What?
( phone chimes )
Do you love me,
Colt?
You don't love me.
Why would you
even say that?
If you loved me,
we'd be in the backseat
right now
and I'd be hitting it.
- ( phone chimes )
- ( Katie sighs )
Prick.
( scoffs )
What did you
just say to me?
- Nothing.
- All right, get out
of my car, Katie.
What?
I'm not doing
this baby stuff
with you anymore.
I'm over it,
all right?
Get out.
- You know what?
You are a prick.
- Yeah, and you know what?
You're not hot enough
for me to be trying
this hard anymore.
Get out.
( car engine starts )
( phone line ringing )
- Hello?
- Katie: Hey.
- Hey, you okay?
- Uh, will you come
pick me up?
- Yeah.
- I-I would have called
someone else, but...
- I'm behind the Valumarket.
- What are you doing there?
Well, Colt wanted
to go somewhere that
we could be alone.
I-- just please
come get me?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm coming
to get you right now.
I'll be right there.
( shivers )
- Hey, Miss Katie.
- Hi, Produce.
I probably look silly
just standing out here
all by myself in the dark.
Are you cold?
Yeah, but won't
you be cold?
No.
( chuckles )
Thank you.
I think you
look beautiful.
- Well, you're very sweet.
- You're welcome.
Produce, listen to me.
I need you to go back
inside, okay?
Produce,
go back inside.
- What are you doing here?
- No, leave him alone.
He didn't do anything.
Listen, I don't
care about the 'tard,
I'm talking to you.
I came back
to apologize, Katie.
I'm sorry for
what I said earlier.
Damn, you drunk again,
Mr. Campbell?
- You touch
either one of them...
- Oh, you'll what?
Huh?
Go home.
- Katie: We're over, Colt.
- ( scoffs )
Colt:
Okay. Fine.
Have it your way.
- ( car door opens )
- Hey.
- ( car door closes )
- Thanks for coming.
Calvin:
I'm trying, Katie.
- I'm trying.
- I know.
- Thanks, Dad.
- And you...
( chuckles )
thank you
for protecting
my daughter.
You're welcome.
I wish there was
something we could
do to repay you.
- ¶ Oh, oh, oh, I'm so glad ¶
- ¶ That troubles don't ¶
¶ Troubles don't last
always ¶
- ¶ I'm so glad ¶
- ¶ Troubles don't ¶
- ¶ Troubles don't
last always ¶
- ¶ O Lord, what should I do? ¶
¶ I said that I--
I'm certain that... ¶
We're gonna leave
in a couple of minutes.
So what did you guys
think of the service?
Well, I mean,
she liked it.
She was smiles
and, uh, I liked it.
Think you guys
will make it back?
I don't know.
You know?
It's been a long time
since I've darkened
the doorway of a, uh...
- ( clicks tongue )
- Of a church?
Yeah, of a church.
( chuckles )
I just-- you know.
I haven't had much faith
in anything in a long time.
I hear you.
- Yeah.
- How's everything
else been going?
Um...
One day at a time.
That's right.
Hey, um, can we--
can I take you
to get some coffee or...
- Um...
- Yeah. ( chuckles )
- ( laughs )
- Yeah, you got coffee.
- Hey, Katie.
- You ready to go?
I am.
Uh, Katie,
this is Miss Amy.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- It's really nice
to meet you.
I've heard
a lot about you.
Oh, well,
hopefully all good.
- Sometimes.
- ( scoffs ) Thanks.
- Definitely all good.
- Thank you.
Okay.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Bye. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Come on, Dad.
- Come back.
- We will.
- I'll see you later.
You swing with
your club face open.
What do you know?
You swing a club worse
than you swing a bat.
Did you just come here
to mock my golf game?
I came here
to apologize.
Cal, the things
I said to you, man,
everything I said--
Hey, what you said
was true and I needed
to hear it.
( Calvin growls )
- Milt: Missed you, buddy.
- I'm sorry.
- You should be sorry.
- It was a cheap shot.
( laughs )
Let's get out of here.
Let's get a beer.
How about we make it
a coffee?
- A coffee?
- AA.
You're not
an alcoholic, Cal.
I am.
I'm an alcoholic.
Okay, happy hour.
Two for one.
- Two for me, none for you.
- ( Calvin laughs )
- Hey, Dexter.
- Hey, what's up, Calvin?
How you doing?
So today is the day
that you announce
the Employee
of the Month, right?
- Yeah, why?
- Well, um, have you
considered Produce?
- He's a hard worker.
- Now, Cal, I have a soft spot
- in my heart
for that young man.
- Yeah, I know.
That's why I hired him
the first time.
He's a good boy.
He's a good guy.
Now-- now, look, Cal.
Now, Produce ain't got
the sense God gave a cucumber.
- ( inhales sharply )
- Now, I gotta give that award
to employee that represent
what this supermarket
is about.
This ain't no YMCA
where everybody
gets a trophy.
Okay, and with
all due respect,
I think that Produce is
probably the hardest-working
employee that you have.
I mean he knows
the name and the SKU number,
the code or whatever
to every piece of fruit
and vegetable over in your...
- Now, Cal.
- ...section over there.
Just because the boy's
a retard, he don't get
no special treatment.
- You know better
than that, man.
- You know what?
We don't use the "R" word
just like we don't
use the "N" word.
- You know?
- ( sighs )
We should be clear
on our word choice, Dexter.
( Calvin sighs )
Let's get out of here.
Hey.
Wanna go have
some fun?
Hmm?
Let's go.
Well, do you guys wanna
hit the go-karts?
- Go-karts? Do we?
- Yeah! I'll do the go-karts.
We were made to hit
the go-karts, Produce.
Made.
Born to ride!
( music playing )
¶ Good morning, sunshine ¶
¶ It's nice to see you up ¶
¶ Once in a while ¶
¶ It's 12:00 already ¶
¶ The city bus is gone,
you're late again ¶
¶ But I'll give you
a ride ¶
¶ I know you don't like it
when I tell you how to live ¶
¶ But something's
gotta give ¶
¶ Life, love, and pain ¶
¶ Life, love, and pain. ¶
There you go.
( groans )
You're making this
hard on me, Milt.
Come on,
don't be soft.
( sighs )
They call that enabling.
It's called testing.
Good job, you passed.
These are actually
both for me.
- Where's your family at?
- Franklin's dropping them off.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
- We're playing house.
- Hmm.
All right,
give me a sip.
- Really?
- Yeah, just a sip, a taste,
to knock off the edge.
Are you sure
about this?
One sip.
I've been
real, real good.
- ( beer splashes )
- Ah, come on.
I may have lost
my drinking buddy,
but I still gotta look out
for my best friend.
Besides,
the beer was terrible.
Tasted stale.
- Did it?
- No.
I just remembered
I had this.
( scoffs )
I don't want
a sip of that.
( clears throat )
Produce:
Yeah.
Look who we found,
Mr. Campbell.
Produce wanted me
to come have pizza
with him.
Um...
- Amy.
- Hi, I'm Milt Malcolm.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- How are you? Nice to meet you.
- ( whispers ) Nice work.
- ( laughs )
Oh, cavalry has arrived.
Excuse me, folks.
See ya, buddy.
All right, come on,
let's go.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
( chatter )
I'll be right there.
Thank you so much.
It means a lot.
I-- I'm sorry.
Milt.
Milt!
( car beeps )
Listen, that--
that wasn't anything--
I'm not listening to you!
- You're killing me.
You're killing me!
- ( car engine starts )
Katie: Hey, Produce,
you want to go play
some games?
- Yeah!
- Yeah?
- Bye.
- See ya later.
- Amy: Wait...
- Ha.
- Wait...
- We just got ditched.
( chuckles )
Yeah, I think
your daughter just
stole him from me.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
Ah.
I'm good, yeah.
- ( sighs )
- Nice.
Come on,
go get a pizza.
- ( gasps ) Pizza.
- Talking your language?
That's unique.
( laughs )
I know how to do this.
I love laser tag.
- ( girl chuckles )
- Thanks.
Hey! We're on
the same team, remember?
Hey, Katie.
( gun shoots )
Come on.
- I wanna play.
- No, we can play later.
Colt: Come on, guys,
it's the last game
of the night.
Then we can
come back tomorrow.
We're on the same team,
remember?
I'll protect you.
( screams sarcastically )
Oh, my gosh,
you got me, man.
( laughs )
Come on, guys.
It's just a silly game
of laser tag.
- Come on, Katie,
let's beat 'em!
- Let's go.
- ( lasers zapping )
- ( music playing )
( children chattering )
( chuckles )
- What?
- What do you need to be
so rude for, Katie, huh?
- What does that mean?
- Remember? Remember you
used to say you loved me?
- No, Colt.
What are you doing?
- Once upon a time.
- I just wanna talk, that's all.
- Okay, well, I don't
wanna talk.
- Yeah, you don't need to talk.
- No, you need to put
your hands off me.
No, no, listen, I just
want you to lay back down
right now.
- That's it.
- You're disgusting.
- Disgusting?
- No, my dad was
right about you.
- Oh, my God.
- Stop!
- Stop! Get off!
- Shh!
- ( muffled screaming )
- This would be easier
if you just...
( continues indistinctly )
- Hey, I shot you guys!
- Boy: Get out of here,
Produce.
- ( muffled screaming )
- No! Is that Miss Katie?
- Get out of here!
- Colt: Shut up, Katie!
- No!
- Now!
( muffled screaming )
- ( muffled screaming )
- Shut up!
- Will you shut up?
- ( muffled screaming )
- Shut up.
Ah, come on, shut up!
- ( Produce growls )
- Dad!
- Yeah?
Dad, please come help.
Hurry!
What's wrong, baby?
What's wrong?
Produce hit Colt
and it's really bad.
Amy:
What?
Oh, no.
Hey, should you
call 911?
- Amy: Yeah.
- ( Calvin groans )
What did you do,
Produce?
- You're not proud of me?
- No, I'm not proud of you!
You cannot hit somebody
with a fire extinguisher!
I mean, are you--
are you crazy?!
I thought we'd be
like brothers!
You go call your mom
right now!
And you bring her here,
Produce.
- Ah...
- Dad, it wasn't his fault.
He was just trying
to protect me
from Colt.
- Wh-- what do you mean?
- I don't know what would
have happened if he didn't--
- ( crying )
- Oh, baby.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- ( sobbing )
I'm sorry.
Calvin:
Now is he gonna
be all right?
Once he gets treated,
we'll take him in
and interview him,
find out a little bit
more about what happened.
- Okay.
- Where's the kid?
Obviously, we'll need
to talk to him.
We don't know.
Um, he just took off.
Okay, I'll send
some officers to--
to go look for him.
Is he gonna
be in trouble?
Produce?
I don't foresee that.
I think it's, uh--
we just need to ask him
some questions.
Find out a little bit more
about-- about what went on.
All right,
well, it's my fault,
so I'm gonna get in the car
and I'm just gonna go
look for him.
All right,
I'm gonna stay here and see
if I can get ahold of him.
- Okay.
- Okay, I'll go with you.
- Thank you, Officer.
- Certainly.
- Let us know if you
find out anything.
- Absolutely.
We can't just be
driving around blindly
looking for him all night.
- We have no choice.
- Yeah, we do.
I think I'm gonna
take you home.
Maybe just wait
for him there.
Maybe he'll show up
at the house.
No, he's not gonna
show up at the house, Dad.
And I'd rather be
with you right now.
( music playing
on radio )
( phone chiming )
What does Milt want?
Hey, buddy boy,
what do you need?
Let's meet up, man.
Let's meet up.
No, I can't right now.
Katie and I are looking
for Produce.
- We're just driving around.
- I talked with him.
- Can't do that right now.
- Frank, he said he wasn't
sleeping with her.
- ( tires screeching )
- She wanted to.
I believe him, man.
Oh, jeez!
( tires screech )
( crashing through phone )
Hey! Milt?
Hey, answer me!
Milt!
Hey. Hey, Amy.
Hey, is Produce okay?
( sighs )
No, not good.
- Are you his father?
- Uh, no. Uh-uh.
Dr. Jones wants to speak
to his next of kin
to discuss what's going
to be happening today.
All right,
we'll call his mother.
No, she died
over a year ago.
What?
He talks about her
all the time.
I know.
I'm-- I'm so sorry.
I thought you knew.
Ho-- ho--
hold on a second.
So you're telling me
that he lives all on his own?
Even-- even with his--
with-- with his condition?
Yeah.
Does that
really surprise you?
The patient with DS is--
really wants a book
or his book...
You know what?
Let me talk to him.
I'll talk to him.
I'm sorry.
I'm only allowed to have
family back there.
- Amy: Please.
- Ma'am, we are the only
family that he has.
- Okay? Amy, do you mind
sticking with Katie?
- Amy: Yeah.
- I got it. Thank you.
- Calvin: Where is he?
Thank you very much.
Hey. Hey.
Oh...
( sighs )
( voice cracks )
Hey, buddy.
How you doing,
Produce?
Hey, Produce,
how you doing?
- Hurts so bad.
- Yeah.
I bet you do.
Hey, I just wanted
to say that I'm sorry.
Okay?
Back at that
laser tag place,
I-- I realize you were
just trying to protect Katie.
I just wanted
to say thank you.
You're welcome,
Mr. Campbell.
Milt:
I'm sorry, Cal.
- I want to have my book.
- You want your book?
Yes.
- Yes.
Oh, you want your book!
I'm gonna go get your book.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
Your wife's on her way.
- Hey, darling.
- Hey, Dad.
Hey, sweetheart,
will you run to the car
real quick
and grab Produce's Bible
for me?
- Hi. How are you doing?
- I'm fine. Fine.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
I just saw Milt.
He looks good.
He's gonna be all right.
Wanna go back and see him?
Actually, um, I'm not sure
he wants to see me.
Okay.
I mean, I think--
I think that he would
wanna see you.
You sure?
You know, I don't wanna
get him all worked up.
- Okay.
- So...
Okay. Okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
( crying )
Hey, here's the book I got
that you asked for.
Produce:
It's not for me.
What are you--
what are you talking about?
It's for him.
We're looking at blunt trauma
to the left upper abdomen,
ruptured spleen,
severe internal bleeding,
and hypertension.
Should I order
an exploratory
laparotomy?
No time.
Make sure we're prepped
for a splenectomy, stat.
I don't wanna lose
this kid.
Okay.
Mr. Campbell.
Calvin:
You're gonna be
all right, kid, I promise.
Please don't leave me here.
Hey, I'm right here,
Milt.
I'm right here, pal.
Look what the kid
gave you.
( chuckles )
- He's a good kid.
- Yeah.
- I'm scared, Cal.
- Hey, hey.
You're gonna be
all right.
( Milt sniffles )
My mom used to do that
back when I was a kid--
read me the Bible.
I used to like Matthew.
I can't remember why.
Hey, Sue?
Come on.
( monitors beeping )
All right.
Huh? Pick up.
( reading prayer )
"...who are weary
and burdened.
and I will give you rest.
Take my yoke upon you
and learn from me.
- For I am gentle
and humble in heart..."
- Nurse: We need to get him
- into surgery now.
- "...and you will
find rest..."
Give me another set
of retractors.
I see some bleeding
in the left kidney.
( monitors beeping rapidly )
Get two units
of blood, stat!
- More suction!
- ( slurping )
- ( saw buzzing )
- There you go.
Bring that in closer.
( heart monitor
beeping rapidly )
( phone ringing )
Hey, thanks.
What did you say?
- When?
- When you prayed.
( chuckles )
I don't know.
I said a prayer, too.
That was the first time
I've actually prayed.
Yeah?
Me, too.
I-I asked that
Milt and Produce
will be okay.
- Do you think
it'll happen?
- I hope so.
I hope so.
But I don't know
if that's the way
it works, sweetheart.
Well, then, what good is it
to pray if you don't get
what you ask for?
Okay.
Growing up, did I get you
everything that you
ever asked for?
- Of course not.
- No.
But I love you
so much
and I want you
to have everything
that you want,
but sometimes it's not
in your best interest
or it's just, uh--
it's just a hard decision.
It's not fair.
I'm saying that God...
is probably not a genie...
you know, that's granting
every wish or...
I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
I hope that you get
what you asked for tonight.
Thanks, Dad.
- ( monitors beeping rapidly )
- He's crashing! Come on!
Doctor, get that
off of the paper.
( bone saw buzzing )
Get two units of blood!
( slurping )
Probing.
Where's the CO2?
( monitor flat-lines )
Man:
You know,
it's in moments like these
I'm reminded
of one profound truth.
Life is short.
And it's meant to be lived
with courage
and not laden with fear.
And you have to decide
are your dreams bigger
than your memories?
Or will you stay
stuck in the past?
Life is meant to be lived.
Lived abundantly.
You know, you look around
this cemetery, you see
there are--
there are two dates
on every tombstone.
There's a birthdate
and there is a date of death.
Every human being
is guaranteed
those two dates,
but that little dash
that lies in between
those two numbers,
that's what defines
our life.
So make your dash count.
Live.
Really live.
( birds chirping )
( crowd cheering )
Announcer:
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's welcome
our new
Louisville Bats manager,
Calvin Campbell,
who will now take the mound
to throw out the first pitch.
( crowd cheering )
Wow.
I want to dedicate
this first pitch
to someone
very important to me,
uh, who's not able to be here
with us tonight because...
well...
his life ended
way too soon.
Produce...
can I have a ball,
please?
( crowd cheering )
Yeah! Ha-ha!
That's my boy!
Ha-ha!
- Knock 'em down, man.
- Thanks.
This one's for Milt.
( cheering )
( cheering louder )
( crowd chanting )
Produce! Produce!
( music playing )
Dexter:
Produce, where the heck
have you been?
( music playing )
I don't know.
( laughs )
( laughter )
¶ Good morning, sunshine ¶
¶ It's nice to see you up ¶
¶ Once in a while ¶
¶ It's 12:00 already ¶
¶ The city bus is gone,
you're late again ¶
¶ But I'll give you
a ride ¶
¶ I know you don't like it
when I tell you how to live ¶
¶ But something's
gotta give ¶
¶ So let it out,
you gotta move on ¶
¶ Before you lose
all you love ¶
¶ And have to
start over again ¶
¶ Maybe that's how
you'll learn about ¶
¶ Life, love, and pain ¶
¶ You say you're dry now ¶
¶ But to me
it looks like rain ¶
¶ And I don't want
to see you ¶
¶ Get soaked
all over again... ¶
( crowd cheering )
¶ Dead man walking ¶
¶ You're stumbling
down the street ¶
¶ At half past 3:00 ¶
¶ Sooner or later
you'll find the police ¶
¶ And they'll find me ¶
¶ Now I can understand ¶
¶ If you don't know
who you are ¶
¶ And where you wanna go ¶
¶ My impatience
is starting to show ¶
¶ So pick it up,
pack it all on ¶
¶ You better start soon
or I'll be gone ¶
¶ I'm not gonna wait ¶
¶ Maybe that's how
you'll learn about ¶
¶ Life, love, and pain ¶
¶ You say you're dry now ¶
¶ But to me
it looks like rain ¶
¶ And I don't want
to see you ¶
¶ Get soaked
all over again ¶
¶ Life, love, and pain ¶
¶ Life, love, and pain. ¶
( music playing )
¶ My heart holds a question
between every beat ¶
¶ Got every answer
beneath my feet ¶
¶ Fallin' apart,
but I never know why ¶
¶ I've walked every road
but the one that's right ¶
¶ Been chasin' my tail
instead of my dream ¶
¶ Life's just a game,
but you play it for keeps ¶
¶ The world is kind,
the world is cruel ¶
¶ The world you find
depends on you ¶
( vocalizing )
¶ When did I stop
believin'? ¶
¶ Wake me
from this sleep ¶
¶ Wake me from this sleep ¶
¶ Save me
from these dreams ¶
¶ When did I stop
believin'? ¶
¶ I guess I'm alive,
but I tend to forget ¶
¶ I remember the taste
and this isn't it ¶
¶ My heart holds a question,
I don't have a clue ¶
¶ It's strange we forget
everything we knew. ¶
( vocalizing )