Captioning made possible by
trimark pictures
man: Can't wait.
Background music:
¶ you won't believe ¶
¶ the things I've seen ¶
¶ far beyond
your wildest dream... ¶
bawk bawk!
Ha ha ha!
What are you waiting on, Tony?
Handle your business.
I've got $100 in this pocket
that says he don't do it.
You got a bet.
Here you go, Tony.
Don't let me down, man.
I'm betting on you.
Tony, voice-over:
Now, a lot of you guys
might be surprised
at what I'm about to say.
And you'll want to know,
who is this guy
that talks so sly,
and where did he learn to play?
Well, I'm about to tell you
the way that I failed...
And the dirty trick
that fate played on me.
These are swinging sounds
I'm running down
so you will dig my history.
Man: Come on, Manny.
Show them what you got, baby.
Manny: Yeah, I told you.
Oh, yeah, chino.
Be jamming it! Be jamming it!
Oh, look at that!
Sammy sosa!
Oye, Hector.
No trick-or-treat on pope.
Cool deal.
Oh! Oh, you...
Look at that shit.
Oh, yeah, Freddie.
Come on, papa. Get off
my fucking car, man.
What's that look like to you?
Fucking lunch cart?
Get off the fucking car.
Shit, man.
Get this motherfucker
off my car, man.
Get him off my fucking car.
Hector: Hey, yo, asshole!
Yo, what are you doing
to my Uncle's car?
Manny: Bring this
motherfucker over here.
Aah! Aah! Aah! I'm sorry!
What did I tell you, huh?
Get off my car.
Get off my fucking car,
didn't I?
I'm sorry, Manny.
Running your life, Freddie.
Dar me. Dar me. Dar me. Dar me.
Here you go, bro.
This better not
be short, either.
No way, papi.
I sold that shit
lock, stock, and barrel.
Believe that!
This ain't funny, man.
Stop fucking around.
You should've
seen them, too, man.
They were sweating me.
They were all, like,
"yo, please, Freddie.
Hook me up, man.
I'm sick."
But I was hard,
just like you told me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Listen. I'm putting
Hector on a run.
I want you to go with him.
Damn it, Manny.
What?
You said you would hook me up
with my own franchise, man.
Why do I got to
deliver with Hector?
Because he's my nephew
and I don't want anything
to happen to him, ok?
Now I want you go with him,
make sure the shit
gets delivered,
then maybe... Hey.
Maybe we'll talk
about a franchise.
Yeah. How many keys?
Cuatro.
Ok.
Make sure they get there.
Yeah. No problem.
Get the fuck out of here.
Oye, gato.
You fuck up on this one,
that's another life you lose.
Woman: Aah!
Fuck me.
Oh, yeah, taxi, taxi, taxi!
Come on.
Over here. Over here.
I'm going to Livingston street.
Where's that? In tribecka?
No, no, no. Downtown Brooklyn.
Oh, no, no. I'm sorry, no.
I cannot take you to Brooklyn.
What do you mean
you can't take me?
It's quitting time
in one half hour.
I cannot take you to Brooklyn.
I must go to queens.
You must take me
to my destination.
I'm going to Brooklyn.
Let's go.
No, no. I must ask you
to leave my cab now, please.
You either take me to Brooklyn,
or you take me
to the police station.
I cannot go.
Either you take me to Brooklyn,
or take my ass
to the police station.
Otherwise, I'm not
getting out of your cab.
Can we move this along
with a little alacrity?
I got to take a fucking piss.
What's this jackoff's name?
Michael Williams.
Want to write it
in fucking braille?
Oh, excuse me. Gentlemen,
could you please
escort Mr. Williams
to the holding tank?
Woman: Gentlemen! Gentlemen!
Gentlemen, please!
What seems to be
the problem here?
Officer, I would like
to fill out a complaint.
Oh, would you now?
That's right.
This pendejo picked me up...
refused to take me
to my destination.
Cab driver: No.
My off-duty light was on.
This guy got in
while I'm stopped
at a red light.
Liar. The man is lying.
All right. Shut up! Shut up!
Before I fucking smack you.
You want to fill out
a complaint?
I need your name.
Michael Williams.
What's the problem, officer?
No problem at all.
I just have to ask you
a few questions.
That's all.
What kind of questions?
Just some routine
questions, sir,
starting with your name.
I told you before.
Michael Williams.
Michael Williams Leon?
No, no. Lay-on.
What about my complaint?
We'll get to that in a minute.
Date of birth,
October 31, 1967?
What's this about?
This is about you, nitwit.
Michael Williams Leon?
You got a list of prior arrests
dating back 10 years,
but who's counting?
I didn't do nothing.
Not today, but you
did a bullet on riker's
a couple of years ago,
and that's the good news.
You want to hear the bad news?
You ain't been to see
your p.O. In two months.
Now you know what
that means, don't you?
He misses me?
Woman: Move it.
All you got to do
is call on him.
I was going to see him.
Look, don't I at least
get a phone call?
I got something better.
Williams! Come here!
I got someone here
I want you to meet.
Daddy?
What?
Billy, stay here, all right?
Just going to stay in the car?
All right. Stay here.
Jackie. Jackie! Hey!
Come on, Jackie.
Hey. Hey, come on.
Man: There. Hey, Mikey.
Give your daddy a kiss.
Come over here. Come on.
Excuse me, but you haven't seen
this kid but twice
since he's been born.
Now all of a sudden,
you want to come around here
and play daddy?
Jesus, he's my kid, too,
for Christ's sakes. Come on.
That's not what you said to me
when I told you
that I was pregnant.
Fuck you, Billy.
Whoa! Why you got
to talk to me like that
in front of the kid?
Why? Because you are just
such a fucking asshole.
Don't you come
stepping into my life
and telling me that
you care about my son.
Hey, "our" son.
Tony, voice-over:
Dig. Like last new year's night,
when the whole scene
shown bright
and all the goons
was stalking their prey.
The cold was pure crime
on them neon lights
and all the tricks
were doomed to pay.
Crime suddenly begun
soon as daughters made sons.
Some of them's
only 5 years old.
You know, there's been
many, many a night
I had to settle for
a bite off of some old...
Moldy roll.
Seen your father lately?
He's dead.
He's dead? You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Positive?
Absolutely.
Absolutely positive.
A fucking deadbeat.
A fucking prick is what he was.
Are you hungry? You want to go
get a slice of pizza
or something?
Come on. Take a walk with me.
I'll buy you a slice,
all right?
That's all right. I'm good.
Like you got something
better to do?
Come on. Take a walk
with me, bro.
Ok. But don't call me that.
What can I do you fellas?
Let me get two slices
and a coke.
What you want to drink, bro?
Dr. Pepper.
Dr. Pepper? You need something
with vitamin c, yo.
Hey, let me get
an orange drink with that.
Man: 10 minutes on the pizza.
Yeah. No problem.
What?
Look at you.
Wipe your nose.
Thanks.
You know you got to eat, bro.
Feed a cold, starve a fever.
That's what they say.
I fucking told you
not to call me that.
Now, see, look what you did.
Are you stupid or what?
Why the fuck you got
to talk to me like that?
You put me back
another 10 minutes.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, sorry.
It does nothing for me.
"You're sorry."
You know what? Get out.
What? We just want
some pizza, man.
Oh, get a fucking haircut.
Two of you are knuckleheads.
Aah! What the fuck!
Fuck, man!
Torch: Say it
to my fucking face.
Who's stupid now, motherfucker?
Wait a minute. We got to go.
We got to go.
The cops are coming.
What are you talking about?
What cops?
The ones behind me, yo.
Holy shit.
Officers: Hold it!
Hold it! Police!
Stop right there!
Police officer! Stop!
Get the fuck out of the way!
Torch: Wait up, man. Wait up.
How did you know
those cops were coming?
I got eyes in the back
of my head.
20/20 Mike. That's me.
What's the matter with you?
What? Are you fucking crazy?
You're trying to
get us busted again?
We just got out, man.
Yeah, well, I may be crazy,
but I ain't stupid.
What do you mean
"we" just got out?
We ain't together.
Come on. Don't be
like that, bro.
Don't fucking call me that.
Just because my old man
was fucking your mother
don't make us brothers.
Oh, wait a minute.
Why you got to talk
about my mother, huh?
about my mom?
Ha ha ha!
Fucking asshole.
You fucking put
your hands up to me again,
I'll throw you
a fucking beating
you'll never forget.
I'm sorry, all right?
Look. You're pretty good
with the smitties, right?
Maybe we could make
some money together.
Doing what?
This and that. A little flim,
a little flam, you know.
I don't know.
What? Like you got
something better
to do, Mr. Williams?
Cut me a break with
that Mr. Williams shit.
Ok. Whatever the
fuck your name is.
Billy.
Billy?
Yeah. Billy.
You want to make
some money or not?
Ok.
What you want from me, Max?
You know what I want?
I want you to do what
you fucking promised.
It's not that
fucking complicated.
You say you're going
to do something,
you do it.
It's not my fault.
Whose fault is it? Mine?
No.
And I bet you won't tell her
you won't take her
trick-or-treating.
Maxine!
Maxine what?
I knew this shit
was going to happen.
It's the same fucking shit
that happened last year.
Look. I got business
to take care of.
You're going to have to
take her this year.
You know what?
She doesn't
want me to take her.
She wants her father
to take her.
All right? She's a little girl.
Halloween is important to her.
I know that.
Think I don't know that?
Why don't you
fucking act like it?
She's not going to
be little forever.
Where you going?
Going to pick her up
from school.
This is bullshit!
Now just stop it, all right?
Max... You know the game.
I'll be back.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Just do what you got to do.
Come here. Don't be scared.
It'll be ok.
You go get precious.
Tell her daddy's sorry.
Will you do that for me?
Yeah.
I'll do that for you.
I'll tell her you're sorry.
Maxine: I don't know why
I'm with your sorry ass anyway.
Tony, voice-over:
Wayward daughters
for dollars and quarters
would sell
their youthful selves,
and in the morning they awoke
to find their hearts
near broke,
crying themselves to death.
While junkies prowl
with a tiger's growl
in search of their
much needed blow,
and winos cringe
on their canned heat bins
to find their graves
in the snow.
Where belles of vice
sell love for a price
and even the law gets corrupt,
man, you keep on trying.
But nevertheless crime,
like gin... what a bitter cup.
The jungle creed says,
"the strongest feed
off of any prey at hand,"
and I was branded "beast"
at every feast,
before I ever became a man.
They're here.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure. Positive?
Absolutely.
Absolutely positive.
Go upstairs. Wait for my call.
Man on TV: Hey, all right!
I'm here. You're here.
We're all here together.
Do you have any idea
what we're doing here?
Hey, Michael. You know?
All right! That's what
we're going to do!
Hi, Catherine. Hi, bill.
Bill: How are you today?
Are you hungry?
Happy Halloween, fellas.
Trick or treat.
Hey, come on, man!
You think I'm
fucking stupid, b?
Fuck. This is the kid
from the elevator.
Yo, where the fuck is Freddie?
He's downstairs.
He's on lookout.
Hey, man, I ain't
packing nothing.
I ain't packing nothing, ok?
How you doing?
Good. Yeah.
Listen. You guys
want to show me
the product or what?
Hector: No doubt.
Esta bien.
Oh, so it's money time
though, right?
It's money time. So why
don't you call your boy
and we get this money
and we do this?
Yeah?
It's that time. You ready, bro?
Don't fucking call me that.
Well, come on up.
We're waiting.
Keep your fucking
shirt on, Mikey.
I'm coming, all right?
Hurry up. These guys want
their fucking money, all right?
Yeah. Heard you
twice the first time.
Damn!
Mike: So, fellas,
today's your lucky day.
You're under arrest.
Man: Give me the fucking...
Oh, shit!
Watch where the fuck
you're going, man.
I'm sorry, yo.
What are you
doing here, Freddie?
Nothing.
I didn't recognize you.
How you doing?
Manny send you?
Yeah. No. I mean no.
I was just... what?
Ow! Aah!
Easy, man.
Why you bugging, dude?
Aah! What the fuck?
You're coming with me,
motherfucker.
What the fuck, man?
What's your
fucking problem, man?
Hey, yo!
Bill on TV: Ooh, boy.
Hey, Michael, can you
smell the aromas?
Boy, these guys know how
to play along real well...
You sure this is where
we're supposed to meet them?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You positive?
Absolutely.
Absolutely positive.
Yeah. We can't wait
here all night.
Yeah. Tell me about it.
Who you calling?
A friend of mine.
Hello.
Mike: Trick or treat.
Precious, how you doing?
Hello. Go put your costume on.
Hey.
Who's this?
Hey, Max. It's Mike.
Oh, shit.
Aw, damn, she got so big.
What do you want, Michael?
How you doing, Max?
Oh, I'm fine. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
What do you want?
Let me talk to Tony.
Well, Tony's not here.
Listen, can you tell him
to meet me later tonight?
Maxine: Well, Tony's
taking care of business,
and I don't know
where to reach him.
Max, please, Max.
I'm in trouble now, all right?
That's the fucking problem.
You always in trouble.
That's the only time
we ever hear from you.
I know, Max,
and I'm sorry. I just...
you just what?
You in jail again?
No. No, it's just...
It's my sister.
Debbie?
Yeah. She's shooting
dope again,
and listen, can you
tell Tony to meet me
at the old spot tonight?
Help me look for her maybe?
Please.
Yeah, all right.
I'll tell him you called.
Thanks, Max.
Yeah. Give precious
a big hug for me, all right?
Operator: If you need help,
hang up and then dial...
what's up? Who was that?
Never mind.
Come on. Let's get
the fuck out of here.
¶ Take me, help me ¶
¶ I wish I was a child again ¶
¶ pack lunch before my boots ¶
¶ so colorful ¶
¶ kaleidoscope images ¶
¶ 1975 films
and starsky and hutch ¶
¶ God, do I ask for too much? ¶
¶ too much? ¶
¶ yeah, yeah, yeah ¶
¶ yeah, yeah ¶
¶ all I want to see
is the rising sun ¶
¶ the rising sun ¶
¶ all I want to see
is the rising sun ¶
¶ oh, no, no ¶
¶ the rising sun ¶
¶ oh, no, no, no ¶
¶ all I want to be
is the rising sun ¶
¶ the rising sun,
the rising sun... ¶
Mike: Ok, ok.
Ok, ok, ok. You made it, Mikey.
You made it.
Ha ha! Ha ha ha!
Hey, we made it.
All you got to do
is calm the fuck down.
Think, baby.
You just got to think.
Yo, Billy, where the fuck
are you? Hurry up.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Keep your shirt on, Mike.
It's fucking dark up here.
You almost there.
You can make it, bro.
I told you not to call me that.
You sure we're
going to be safe up here?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Torch: Huh? Oh, shit.
This is it?
This is your fucking hideout?
Yeah, yeah, this is it.
Go ahead. Make
yourself at home.
You sure Manny won't
come looking for us here?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You positive?
I'm telling you, absolutely.
Absolutely positive.
Let me tell you something.
It looks like
quite a few people found
your little
fucking hideaway here.
Will you just go ahead
and sit down?
Yeah, yeah. I'll do that.
Let me tell you something else.
I sure as shit ain't taking
my shoes off in this joint.
God forbid, I get fucking aids.
What are you so fucking
worried about, huh?
I don't know.
What if Manny
and his boys find us?
What about that, huh?
Mierda, look it, I told you.
This place is like
fucking fort knox.
Nobody comes in our out
unless they know the way.
All right? Me and my man Tony,
we used to hide out
here all the time.
What you keep saying.
Are you sure nobody saw us?
Yeah. Yeah.
Jesus Christ. Damn
place is a mess.
No shit.
I don't know if I like this.
I think we should blow.
I think we should get
the fuck out of here.
And do what? What,
you want to ride
the fucking subway
till somebody spots us?
No. We take our chances
on the street.
We're better off.
I'm telling you.
No. Forget about it.
We got half the dealers
in the city looking
for us probably,
not to mention the cops.
We got to do some
fucking thing.
At least get out of New York.
To Jersey, Philly, maybe Miami.
I hear the weather's nice.
Miami?
Miami? What are
you, fucking crazy?
Manny's got connections
up the ass
on the east coast.
We got to go out west.
California, Seattle, maybe.
Maybe this guy Tony,
the friend you called,
maybe we could sell
the shit to him.
No way. No way.
Tony's out of the life now.
Let me tell you something.
Once you got a taste
of the life, that's it.
Once in the life,
always in the life, Mikey.
Not my man Tony, man. He's out.
Lucky motherfucker.
Oh, we used to come
up here all the time
back in the day.
Me, him, fucking Freddie.
Fucking Freddie nine lives.
A piece of work, he is.
Catch that motherfucker,
throw him off a roof.
Freddie: Aah!
I don't know nothing.
I swear I don't know anything.
I swear to God, please!
Come on, Freddie, who was it?
Come on.
Freddie: I don't know
nothing, man. I swear to God.
You don't tell me,
I'm going to throw you
off this fucking roof. Tell me.
Please, Manny, please.
I don't know anything.
Oh, God, no!
Hey, Buddha, don't cats
usually land on their feet?
Yeah, but at this
height, I don't know.
No, Manny, please.
Don't drop me, Manny.
Don't kill me. Not like
this, Manny, please.
Drop him.
No! No! No!
It was Mike!
It was Mike, 20/20 Mike!
Come on, Freddie,
stop fucking around.
Come on. The other guy, huh?
It was some crazy white boy
with long hair,
a dope fiend.
I swear that's all
I know, Manny.
Oh, my God, don't...
20/20. Ain't that Tony's boy?
Yo, Manny. I ain't seen
this cat in, like, years,
you know what I'm saying?
Freddie: I swear.
Don't drop me.
I swear to God! Please.
It's ok, Tony.
Really, it's ok.
Freddie: Oh, my God,
don't kill me, Manny.
Please, not like this!
Ruffhouse, Buddha,
why don't you take
Freddie downstairs
and hang out, huh?
Me and Tony got to talk.
I can't believe he fucking
left us hanging, man.
Cocksucker said the job
would be a cinch.
Said it would be easy.
Now look at us
sitting here
in a fucking firetrap.
It would have been a cinch
if you'd have chilled
the fuck out.
Don't fucking start with me.
I can't believe you
fucking shot those guys.
How many fucking times
are you going to say it?
You fucking shot two kids, man.
I can't believe that.
Forget about it, will you?
What's done is done.
Yeah.
You came to me
about a year ago.
You asked
for your own franchise.
I gave it to you,
and what happens?
Is this how you show
your fucking appreciation?
Manny, you got to believe...
shut the fuck up!
Just keep on talking.
Keep on talking.
Freddie: Don't hit me... ohh!
Now, I know this motherfucker
set me up.
Now, I know he's
responsible for Hector.
All I want to know is
when, where, why, what, who.
Come on.
I got to the hotel, all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
No.
Look, Max, I'm kind of
tied up right now, ok?
How's your hand, bro?
Stop calling me that.
I ain't your brother.
So it's like that now?
You bet your ass it is.
You're a sick man,
Mr. Williams.
I told you not to call me that.
Yep. You're a very sick man.
I'm not sick.
Just got a cold,
and my fucking
hand's killing me.
Come on, Tony.
Where the fuck are you?
I think I know where
they are, Manny.
That's good, Tony.
Now we're going to talk about
how you should handle it.
Me?
Yeah, you.
I can't do that, man.
Why is that?
I ain't never killed
nobody before, man.
Well, guess what, Tony.
There's a first time
for everything.
What?
It's your product
we're talking about here.
It's your responsibility.
You wanted to be
your own boss, right?
Guess what.
You got to pay the cost
if you want to be the boss.
You take that with you.
Fuck this sitting around
waiting for your friend
to show up.
God forbid, Manny
and his boys find us.
Forget it. They'll fucking
have us for breakfast.
Hold up. Hold up.
What the fuck is that?
What?
Listen.
What the fuck is that?
I don't know.
Maybe it's your friend.
No. That's something else.
I know I've heard
that sound before.
So what are you asking me for?
I don't know...
shh! Shh! Wait.
Oh, shit!
Fuck!
That's a fucking rat, man.
Don't do that shit, man!
I'm telling you,
that's a fucking rat, man.
I hate rats.
I can't stand them shits.
I remember I was
dating this girl.
She lived down by mill basin...
candy brown.
Bitch was fine, bro.
Told you not to call me...
I mean, fine.
This chick was so fine,
I spent all the bread
I could get my hands on
trying to get into her panties.
Took her to coney island,
the aquarium, the movies.
Any place in Brooklyn
I thought she might give it up,
that's where I
would take her, right?
So after we had gone out
a few times...
I don't know to this date
how I knew,
but I could tell
she had finally decided
to give me some, right?
So, we had gone to the movies
over on church Avenue,
and when the flick was over,
she asked me to walk her home,
so I go like a bat.
So, we start walking, talking,
shooting the breeze, you know.
And bing bing!
My 20/20 start going off
like crazy.
It was like I could feel
all the fellas around her way,
they were checking
me out, you know,
like, "who's this chump?
What's she doing
with him," right?
So, we finally get
to her building,
and it's all run-down and shit.
I'm like, "what the fuck
is a chick this fine
doing living in a place
like this?"
Mierda, she was fine as wine.
I'm telling you,
dress her up in garbage bags,
put fucking TV dinners
on her head,
you could not hide
this kind of beauty,
and after I'd taken
her out all them times?
Said I was going to
get these panties.
I mean, I was very serious
about this pussy, ok?
Is there a point to this story?
Oh, yeah, check it out,
I forgot.
We had stopped to get some
bacardi on the way, right?
When we get to her apartment
on the fourth floor,
that shit was hooked up.
Top to bottom,
all exotic and whatnot.
The bitch got beads hanging
over the bedroom door,
different colored
light bulbs in the ceiling,
and pillows on the floor...
that type of shit.
Yeah, she lit up a joint,
some incense,
asked me to make some drinks
while she goes
and gets comfortable.
I made it. I made it
to mill basin alive.
I'm going to fuck
the finest girl
I ever seen in my life, right?
So, I make the drinks.
One for me, right?
One for her.
I'm sitting on the floor.
I'm sipping my drink.
I'm taking it all in, right?
The lights, the reefer,
the incense...
bling bing bing!
My 20/20 goes off again, right?
It's like I could feel
something in the room.
So, I go to put
my drink down, right?
The shit spills over.
Fucking floor was slanted, bro.
No lie, the shit was like this.
So, now I'm trying
to clean up my mess,
and I hear
this scratching sound
on the floor behind me.
I turn around.
I see this rat.
Go on, yo, a fucking rat
this fucking big.
Swear to God, it was
as big as your fucking head.
Ahh, I can't stand them shits.
I'm telling you, man,
that shit blew my mind.
I mean, I couldn't
concentrate on nothing else
for the whole rest
of the night.
See, what happened was,
when I was little,
my sister Debbie,
she got bit by a rat.
She was only, what,
2 or 3 years old at the time.
I didn't know it then,
but I kept that shit locked up
in the back of my mind.
Like, in my subconscience,
you know?
So when the chick
came out of the bathroom...
I mean, all ready to go, man,
looking finer than
a motherfucker...
pussy? Furthest thing
from my mind.
About time, yo. Here he comes.
We got to get out
of here, Mike.
Shut up. I'm trying
to think of something.
While you're doing that,
I'm bleeding
like a stuck pig. I got
to take a piss...
ow, ow, ow!
You fuck!
Tony: Yo, Mike.
Yo, Mikey!
Fuck.
Yo, Mike.
Ok. I'm going to go
up on the roof.
I'm coming with you.
No way you're
leaving me by myself.
No. You move around too much,
you'll only make
yourself bleed more.
Are you stupid?
Don't call me stupid
one more fucking time!
Ok, I'm sorry, ok?
Tony: Yo, Mike.
Yo, Mike, you there?
Where you at, baby?
I don't know, Mike.
I don't know this guy.
How many times
I got to tell you?
He's a friend of mine.
You keep saying that. Big deal.
He ain't no
fucking friend of mine.
Ok.
Ha ha ha!
You playing, right?
Ok. Keep it out, all right?
Now, don't let him leave,
and whatever you do,
don't fucking shoot him.
Ok?
I'm going to go up on the roof.
Mike.
Goddamn, this place
is fucked up.
Trick or treat, motherfucker.
Yo! No problem, baby,
all right?
Shut up!
Step in the middle
of the floor, slick.
Nice and easy.
Right here ok, chief?
That's fine. Just fine.
Ok.
Hey, hey, fucker!
Use your head.
Empty out your pockets
on the table there
and be very, very careful.
Careful is my middle name, man.
Just don't shoot
a brother is all I'm saying.
Just so long as the brother
keeps his hands
where I can see them.
It's all I got, chief.
I hate carrying this thing.
Keeps the old lady
off my case, you know
what I'm saying?
Hey, I ain't interested
in your life story, pal.
You sit down over there
nice and easy,
and keep your fucking hands up.
You got it.
Yo, my man.
What the fuck do you want?
Is Mike here?
How the fuck should I know?
Didn't I hear
two people up here?
Who gives a fuck
what you heard?
Look, I'm just
trying to make sure
I'm in the right place.
That's all I'm saying.
Now, he called my old lady,
said he was trying to
find his sister Debbie.
I just want to see if I
can help a brother out.
Oh, great. Another one
with the brother shit.
So, you're a friend
of his, huh?
Look, man, that's
my motherfucking man.
Go back like car seats, baby.
There's too much crime
and too much time.
See what I'm saying?
Oh, Christ almighty.
You all right, man?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I got to take a piss.
Go ahead, man, take a break.
I ain't gonna give you no...
you, just be quiet
till Mike gets back.
Oh, so he's here?
Yeah, he's up at the roof.
He said you was to wait
for him till he comes down.
Said to keep you here.
Yo, my man.
What?
Can I put my hands down now?
Yeah.
Don't think I won't cap you one
just because you're
a friend of Mike's.
No problem, man.
Yo, what's your name?
What? Are we fucking friends?
What's your name, man?
Torch.
I'm Tony t. Nice to meet you.
Whatever.
I seen you somewhere
before, right?
Never.
You sure I ain't
never met you before?
Hey, let me tell you something.
I never seen you before.
You never seen me before.
I don't know you.
I don't want to know you.
I'd just as soon shoot you
as look at you. You got it?
I got it, man.
No problem, all right?
Put your fucking hands
behind your head.
Mikey?
Mikey, man.
I got to take a leak, man.
You better get down here fast,
or I'm going to fucking
put one in your friend here.
Hey, yo, take it
easy, all right?
You, shut the fuck up.
Oh, shit.
Ohh!
Ohh... Ohh, shit!
Shit, no.
Mike: Oh, yeah, Billy.
Motherfucker!
Oh, shit! Fuck, man, whoa!
Take it easy, torch.
Give me the gun.
Don't shoot, ok?
What's the matter? You ok, bro?
Don't fucking call me that.
What's the matter?
Tony, what happened?
I think your boy had
a little accident.
I pissed my fucking pants, man.
Oh... Shit, uh...
I'm sorry, bro.
Hold up. Hold up.
Come here. Come on.
Now, you sit
over here, all right?
There you go.
20/20 Mike.
Tony t., what's up, huh? Ha ha!
So, what happened, Mike?
Fellas, can I get
a hand over here?
Hey, yo, chill.
We'll get you cleaned up
in a second, ok?
Tony: What up, Mike?
Well, it's a long story.
Hey, you ain't seen nobody
following you, did you?
No. Two dudes on the corner
using the pay phone.
Word?
Word. Suave, Mike.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Suave. We cool.
You bet. Torch, ok?
Fuck you.
Torch: Fuck the both
of you cocksuckers.
I'm bleeding.
My fucking hand's killing me.
I'm soaked to the gills
in my own piss,
for Christ's sakes.
Torch, just take it easy, ok?
It's all right.
I got some old sweats
in my ride downstairs.
I'll go get them,
bring them up,
get you out
of them pissy pants,
get you cleaned up, all right?
Well, hurry up. What the fuck
are waiting on?
I'm dying over here.
Damn, Mike. Where you find
this evil motherfucker?
It's a long story.
Can you get us
something to eat,
and maybe something
to drink, too?
No problem.
Yeah, some cigarettes
and something sweet.
And maybe some stuff
to clean up his hand?
You know, it's
pretty fucked up.
Yeah. No problem, man.
What happened, man?
What did y'all do?
We tried to beat somebody
and we ran
into a little problem.
Tried to beat somebody? Who?
Yeah, well, you
don't want to know.
Manny Rivera, that's who.
Torch: Ok? You can
fucking go now.
Wait a minute. Wait
the fuck a minute here.
You beat Manny Rivera?
For how many keys?
3. Supposed to be 4.
Torch: We lost one.
What a fucking waste.
You got a lot of nerve
talking that shit
after what you did.
You going to start that
fucking shit with me again?
You're so fucking stupid.
The next time you
call me fucking stupid...
there won't be no next time,
Manny Rivera find
you two motherfuckers.
I'm not feeling too good, Mike.
You got to stop moving
around so much.
Look, Tony will be back
in a minute, all right?
Let me see your hand.
I can't feel my fingers.
I think I'm going to pass out.
Jesus, man, you all
fucking sweaty and shit.
That's this fucking cold
I'm trying to catch.
I'll be fine as soon as
we get out of here.
All right, all right.
Let me see that hand.
No, just leave it alone.
It will be fine.
Come on. You keep it
in your pocket,
it's only going to get
infected. Let me see.
No. Ow!
Let me see.
No, man, stop.
Let go of my fucking arm,
for Christ's sakes, will you?
Yeah, ok, go ahead.
Keep in your pocket.
Bleed to death, stupid.
Hey, next fucking time
you call me stupid,
I'll throw you a beating
you'll never forget.
Oh, right. With one
fucking hand, right?
You know, that shit gets
infected bad enough,
you get gangrene.
Cut the fucking thing
off of you.
The fuck they will.
Besides, it ain't that bad.
Oh, that's what you think?
Well, then, hey.
See if I give a marvelous fuck
when it falls off.
It ain't gonna fall off.
It ain't that bad.
I'm telling you.
Just a scratch.
Ok.
Yo, house, where's Manny?
I got to talk to him.
Manny went to see his mother.
You take care of your boy?
I'm working on him.
Buddha: Hmm.
Ruffy, you owe me $100.
Nah, nah. Give him
a chance. He's a virgin.
What you going to do now?
Buddha: I don't know
what happened,
but something's
got to be a deal.
We'll give you another
couple of hours
to take care of your business.
Or your business
becomes our business.
Ahh-ahh!
Make me some money, baby.
Look, I didn't want
to say nothing,
but I think I seen him before.
Who?
Your friend there.
Frosted flakes.
Tony?
Yeah. You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You positive?
I don't know.
I can't remember where.
How could you forget
somebody like Tony?
I don't know,
but it will come to me.
I'll tell you
one fucking thing for sure,
I don't like him.
Yeah, well, you didn't like me
when you met me either,
Mr. Williams.
Cut me a break with that
Mr. Williams shit.
Sorry, bro.
Stop calling me bro.
Jesus. I've known you
two weeks.
Already the biggest
pain in the ass
I've ever had in my
whole fucking life.
Well, that's only natural
seeing as how me and you
got the same fucking father.
You and me is
different, period.
What you and me got in common,
I don't want to talk about.
What I want to know about
is your friend there...
fucking Tony the frosted flake.
Mike: Come on, man.
Fucking Tony the tiger.
Torch: What's the difference?
We're talking about
the same guy, right?
So, what about him?
How you know we can trust him?
You see what I'm saying?
How do you know
he won't rat us out?
No way!
Look, man. Me and Tony did
too much time together for that.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Positive?
Absolutely.
Absolutely positive.
Ok.
Hey, Mike.
What?
You think they'll
really cut my hand off?
Tony, voice-over:
I was young, impressive,
hot with my fancy.
I was known as
the adequate male.
Oh, but how I cursed the day
I made my play
for that sidewalk jezebel.
Manny: Precious.
Hey, come here.
She was a brown-skinned moll
like a China doll
walking the path of sin.
Up and down she trod
with a wink and a nod,
and this bitch I had to win.
What's up, Manny?
No, it was not by chance
I caught her glance
because I meant
to steal this thing,
and when she looked at me,
I jumped a league.
Said it's time
for old slim again.
Freddie, did you miss us?
Boo hoo hoo. Trying
to say something?
What?
Huh?
What's the matter?
You got problems with language?
Come on, fellas.
Give me a break, man.
Why you got to treat
a brother like this?
A brother?
What are you, a comedian now?
You a funny man?
No, man, I'm just trying to add
a little levity
to the situation, you know.
Levity?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Here's levity.
Seriously, fellas,
life's too short.
You shouldn't take
everything so serious.
Oh, philosophy now, huh?
Make me laugh.
He's right.
Make... make Buddha laugh.
You make him laugh,
you get to live
a little longer.
Yeah. Ok. Yeah. All right.
Show your best.
Ok. All right,
here's a good one.
There's a... there's a white guy,
a Chinese guy, and a black guy,
all in the fifth grade.
Who's got the biggest dick?
I don't know.
The black guy, of course.
He's 18.
Ha ha ha!
18...
You motherfuck...
ow!
Looks like you lost
a lot of blood, Billy.
Yeah. You should have
seen the other guy.
Yeah. Very funny, very funny.
Now don't move.
All right, but it's fucking...
I told you
it fucking hurts... ow!
Hey. Quit moving, then.
You know, we're lucky
to be alive.
Come on. Quit
fucking moving, Billy.
You keep fucking
poking, and I told you
it hurts me,
for Christ's sakes.
You know, I swear to God
if I get any more
of your blood on me,
I'm gonna...
you think you're gonna
fucking catch something?
Don't worry, I've been
tested more times
than I can count.
Yeah. Yeah. Me, too.
Great. Makes us one
happy fucking family.
Ha ha ha!
You fucking asshole.
What are you talking about?
Look at you, man.
What?
You're all fucking
pissy and shit.
I'm sorry.
Look, we got to get you
out of the jacket.
Ok.
All right?
Yeah. Take it easy because
it fucking hurts, all right?
Don't fuck around.
Ok.
On 3...
let me help you.
All right. Ready?
1, 2, 3, go.
Aah! Fucking shit.
Attaboy. Attaboy.
Motherfucking son of a bitch.
There you go, Billy.
You did it, huh?
You did it, all right?
Fuck, yeah.
Good. Good.
Ok. Ok? All right.
Hey, Mike, wait.
What? What?
You ain't gonna tell anybody
I pissed my pants, are you?
No, I'm not gonna tell anybody
you pissed your pants.
You swear?
I swear to my mother. Ok?
Ok.
Come on, come on.
All right.
A guy's going to buy
a brain, right?
There's a white guy's brain,
a Chinese guy's brain,
and a black guy's brain.
White guy's brain is $200,
Chinese guy's brain is $300,
the black guy's brain
is $5,000.
This guy goes, "hey, how come
the black guy's brain
is so expensive?"
The guy goes, "it's
never been used."
Ha ha ha!
Never been used, you dumb...
go ahead. Lay down.
I like two pillows.
Mmm.
So what's up with
you and him, huh?
What's all this too much crime,
too much time shit all about?
Like I say, man,
too much time, too much crime.
I mean, it's funny
we even ended up being friends.
We were supposed to have
this big fucking fight
when we met.
The two of youse was
supposed to fight?
I'd pay good money
to see you get your ass kicked.
Ain't that much
kung foolishness
in the world, all right?
I'd have paid.
Yeah. You and the guy
that started it.
Fucking garnett...
little guy
with a big mouth, right?
Said he was Tony's cousin,
but he wasn't, right?
See, what happened was,
we was in the eighth grade.
It was just before school
was getting out for summer.
I remember it was hot that day.
Me and some of my boys
were in the bathroom
smoking cigarettes
after lunch period.
So, fucking garnett
comes in with his boys.
You know. He's wearing, like,
a brand-new leather jacket,
talking shit about how
he robbed it off somebody,
about how he did this,
that, the other thing
to the guy.
Anyway, I said
to garnett, I said,
"what's the big
fucking deal, man?
It's only
a fucking jacket, right?"
The next thing I know,
the punk jumps up in my face.
You know, talking about
he was gonna kick my ass
if I didn't mind my business.
So, I picked him up,
I threw him headfirst
right into the fucking
toilet bowl.
Motherfucker did not know
whether to shit
or go blind, but that
ain't stopping him
from running his mouth.
No. Mm-mmm.
He's all like, uh,
"my cousin Tony's gonna
make you sorry
you ever messed with me,"
right?
The next thing I know,
everybody around my way,
they're telling me
about some big dude
who's looking for me,
he's into that fucking
kung fu, karate-type shit.
So now, I'm bugging
the fuck out, right?
I mean, I got my switchblade,
I'm all up and down the Avenue
looking for this guy.
I'm standing across the street
from Danny's candy
store... ping ping.
Ping ping.
So I turn around,
and I could see it was him.
He says to me, "you're Mike?"
I'm like, "yeah, you're Tony?"
He's like, "yeah,"
so now I got my hand
on the switchblade,
and I'm hoping I get it
out of my pocket, you know,
before he commences
to kung foo-ing my ass.
Next thing I know,
he says to me,
"you want to go
for a walk?" "Yeah."
I'm telling you, bro, it was,
it was like we were
strangers to each other,
but we wasn't.
And we've been like this
ever since, man.
Went to erasmus hall together,
drank, smoke, got high...
Ate at each other's house
all the time.
You saw him, you saw me
and vice versa, yo.
My mom's practically
adopted him,
and my sister, Debbie,
forget about it, man.
She loved her some Tony.
Senior year, we...
we got tired
of doing school, you know...
dropped out, started
doing crime instead.
Got busted. They done
put us on riker's island.
I spent a whole 18 months
locked up with this dude.
I don't even know how
I would have
done my time without him,
you know?
He used to recite this...
this poem all the time.
This crazy, jailhouse
poetry-type shit,
know what I'm saying?
Tony: And under them neon
lights, her eyes shone bright,
and from them, a teardrop fell.
When I asked her why,
she began to cry
and tell me this bitter tale,
all about some guy
that blacks her eye
and takes all the bread
she gets.
When she lands in jail,
he won't go for bail,
and he defies her
to call it quits.
Well, I said, darling,
dry them tears.
Have no fear,
because the tender,
kind lover is here,
and I'm staking a claim
on all parts of your game.
I'm vowing to have no peer.
Well, she looked at me
like a slave set free
and said, "I'll be your woman."
And when I left with her,
her man did not stir.
Yeah. I knew I had me one.
That shit really
got me through, bro.
Helped me hang
in there, you know,
and do my time.
Mike: And then when we got out,
and he had Maxine pregnant
with precious,
he asked me
to be the godfather.
Me... nobody but me.
Nah, man. Fuck that noise, man.
Ain't no way that
he would rat us out.
That's my motherfucking man.
Mike: Too much time,
too much crime.
You know what I'm saying?
Mike: Torch, you ok?
Billy.
Come on. Wake up, bro.
Yo, Mike.
I got something sweet, man.
¶ And the itsy bitsy spider ¶
¶ climbed up the spout again ¶
somebody's not singing here.
Who's not singing here?
Mommy.
What's the matter,
mommy? Sing with us.
Yeah, mommy.
What time does a Chinese guy
go to the dentist?
Look out now.
2:30.
Ok.
"Tooth hurty,"
you fucking... aah!
Oh, no. It's tooth hurty.
Aah.
Come on, come on.
Why do white people
go to black people's
garage sales?
I don't know. Why?
To get their stuff back.
Ha ha ha!
Why did the black guy
hit the white guy?
Because he wasn't funny.
Pace yourself now,
ruffy, come on.
Don't give yourself
a heart attack.
Be in control of your emotions.
Knock, knock.
No one's home.
Just one more time,
break it down for me, man.
Make me understand.
Ok?
Ok.
Like I say, we got to
the stuyvesant
hotel around 3:00,
cased the joint,
like me and you
used to do back in the day
when we flim-flammed all
them wall street types.
Tony: I hear you.
Now, we were supposed to meet,
like around 4:00.
Around about 3:30,
these 3 chulitos
show up I never
seen before, man...
real young cats.
Really young... couldn't
have been no more
than what, 19, 20
years old at the most?
Yeah. Had on them
baggy clothes,
fucking cornbred hair...
they were straight up
stickup kids.
Mike: They was babies, man.
Tony, I mean, they were riding
in an elevator
with 4 kilos of heroin
and looked like they was still
on their mama's titty,
ni me pregunte.
So, we get to the eighth floor.
I break left. They break right.
I can feel them
clocking me, right,
but I never look back.
No, no, no. I just keep walking
like I'm going towards my room,
and what happened?
Ping ping.
My 20/20 goes off, right?
Tells me exactly what room
they go to, right?
Fucking guy got eyes
in the back of his head, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Ping ping.
So check it:
I just ease down the hall.
I couldn't believe
that Manny would send
such young, dumb motherfuckers
to deal with all this weight,
but I figure, ok,
it makes the job easier, right?
I knock on the door.
They let me in.
They frisk me.
They ask me who I got with me,
that type of shit.
I see they're getting
a little nervous.
So what do I do?
Try to chill them out
a little bit.
You know, try to make
a little light conversation.
Chill them out,
tell them how
professional they are.
You know, how Manny's
a stand-up guy,
he's always bringing
up new talent,
it's always a pleasure
doing business
with him and his people,
blahsy, blahsy, blahsy,
blip, blip, blip,
bullshit, bullshit, bullshit.
Carlito? Chill, papi.
Mike: They seemed
to chill out after that.
So, torch knocks on the door.
The kid lets him in
because he thinks
that we've got Manny's money.
Money talks. Bullshit walks.
Here endeth the lesson.
That's why the shit
went wrong, bro.
You came in sweaty
with your jaws all tight.
You wasn't cool.
Fucking guy was reaching
for his piece.
He never would have fired on us
if you'd have just chilled.
Get the fuck out of here.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
Let me tell you why.
Because I done it.
Me and Tony, man.
We were in the same game
with a lot of people, man.
And you got busted,
though, Mr. Pro.
Anyway...
Yeah, anyway...
So you started shooting.
Then what?
You should have seen it, man.
Fucking bullets are flying...
Fucking blood was everywhere.
Man, I must have
fucking shot these kids
5, 6 fucking times.
Lit their asses up, man.
Fucking the whole joint
smelled like gunpowder.
I didn't even know
I was shot at first.
It felt more like
something burned me.
Yeah, yeah.
And then we lost
one of the 4 kilos
because you started shooting.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I tried to pick up
what was left.
The shit was everywhere.
It was mixed up
with the shooter's blood
and whatnot.
Tasted like some very
high-quality shit, though.
Yeah. Thank you
very fucking much.
So you picked up
the rest of the shit.
You got the fuck out of dodge.
Tony: So afterwards,
where did you go?
Went to Brooklyn.
Brooklyn?
Yeah. Let me
tell you something.
We could've got busted
waiting for that
fucking asshole.
Who?
Freddie: So what's up, fellas?
Are we going to
do this or what?
He's all fucking
worried over here.
Are we going to move the shit?
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, yeah. I got
this guy in sales
says he can
move the shit no problem.
So where and when?
The stuyvesant hotel...
get this...
on Halloween.
Tony: What the fuck
made you think
you could trust that
motherfucker, Mike?
Come on, man.
We used to get all
our flimflam victims
from him, right?
Yeah, but didn't you
never stop to think, Mike?
It might have been him
that set us up
to get busted, man.
Yeah, yeah, but...
But nothing.
The fucking guy has been
working for Manny for years.
Word?
Word.
Right over here
in the fucking park.
Yo. Remember when nine lives
got shot in the head?
Yeah, when Manny...
I remember that.
That's how he got his name.
Mm-hmm.
Well, ever since then,
Manny has been real
superstitious
about nine lives.
I mean, he keeps
that motherfucker around
like a fucking rabbit's foot.
They ain't even invented
the type of shit
that can kill nine lives.
Where did you hear all this?
What do you mean,
where did I hear all this?
I heard it around.
What do you mean,
you heard it around?
Around, man. You know, around.
No, I don't know.
Around the corner?
Around the block?
Around the fucking world? What?
Mike: Come on, torch,
lighten up, all right?
What the fuck
is your problem, man?
No problem, Mike.
I just want to know where
you heard about nine lives.
You said he's
out of the life, remember?
So how the fuck does he know?
Yeah. Where did you
hear all this, Tony?
Tony: Mike,
I come to the city sometimes
with my old lady, all right?
Now, you know Maxine.
She likes the restaurants,
the shops over here,
and whatnot.
I run into people
from back in the day.
I hear things.
Hears things.
Fucking hears things.
Hear that, Mr. Williams?
Mike: What?
Fucking rat is...
where?
Right here, bro. Your friend...
Tony the frosted flake.
What's the matter, Mike?
Your fucking ping-ping
ain't working?
I told you I seen
this guy before.
All I got
is the white girl, baby.
If you're looking
to score dope,
you have to take your
business elsewhere.
See what I'm saying?
Mike: You sure?
Torch: Yeah, I'm sure.
You positive?
Absolutely, absolutely
positive.
Torch: Freddie,
I got to get well.
Ok.
Freddie, what the fuck
you doing?
What?
Manny find out
you selling dope,
he going to crucify your ass.
Fuck Manny, all right?
But you wasn't shopping
with your old lady,
was you, my man?
You know who I was with, punk.
Ohh, fuck!
¡Ay, Tony, coño!
Not the balls, man!
Oh, shit! Ow!
Hey, hey, Tony.
Be careful, man.
What the fuck are you doing?
You ok, Billy?
Hey, what the fuck
is wrong, fellas?
He's wrong, Mike.
They're wrong... him
and nine lives.
I seen them dealing
in the park together.
They's both working for Manny.
Who's stupid now, motherfucker?
Mike. Mike, I can explain.
Please, Mike. Mike,
you got to listen to me.
Fucking listen to me, man!
I'll fuck you up!
Tony: Listen to me, Mike.
Mike! Put the gun away, Mike.
Put the fucking gun away!
Ok, ok. I put it away.
All right.
Ok. Ok, now I'm
kind of confused, Tony,
because I don't remember you
telling me nothing
like that, right?
Let me explain.
I remember coming to Jersey
when precious got baptized.
You told me you was
out of the life, right?
You and Maxine,
you opened up a laundromat
or some shit, right?
Ok. So what happened to that?
I don't understand.
You understand how I could
be a little confused
when you tell me
you out of the life?
Now you tell me you
working for Manny, right?
Mike, I'm sorry, all right?
Tony, I love you.
I love you like you
was my own blood.
Te amo como mi sangre,
but if you're lying to me,
I swear to God,
I will fucking kill you.
Fuck him. Let's waste him,
take his car, get
the fuck out of dodge
while we can, man.
Come on!
Hold up.
What are you waiting for?
Fucking waste him.
Hold up a minute, all right?
Go get the phone.
Torch...
Check the pay phone.
Mike: You see anybody there?
Bet your ass, Mr. Williams.
Answer it.
Yeah.
No.
No. Uh-uh.
Not yet.
Listen up, you motherfucker.
Michael, it's Max.
Max? Hey, hey, Maxine.
How you doing, girl?
You know, how come you
always got to drag us
into your bullshit, Mikey?
We ain't even heard from
you for 2 or 3 years.
Yeah, I know, Max,
but what can I do?
Debbie's my sister,
you know. I love her.
I got to find her.
All right. I don't want to hear
about your fucking sister.
Just put Tony on the phone.
Come on, Maxine.
Don't be like that.
Just put Tony on the phone!
Yeah, ok.
Yeah, baby.
I'm sorry, baby.
Yeah, me, too. You all right?
Maxine, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm all right.
How's my little girl?
She's sleeping.
Manny is singing to her.
You got to get us
out of here, baby.
You got to get us now.
He's singing to my baby.
You got to come and
get us right now.
Maxine, I'll do that
on my way home, ok?
I'm scared.
I-I'm scared.
I'll be there soon as I can.
I just got to help
Mike out, that's all.
Maxine: Do it.
Just do it, ok?
Just do what you got
to do, you hear me?
Just do what you got to do.
Yeah, I hear you.
I love you.
Love you, too, baby.
Maxine sounds good, bro.
Sounds the same.
She's the same old Max.
So what? His old lady called?
That don't prove shit.
Still don't mean he ain't
working for Manny.
I know, but we got
to be cool, right?
I'm through being cool.
I say we fucking waste him now.
You just got to calm down, ok?
Yeah. Calm down, torch.
You already got two murder
beats hanging over your head.
I ain't interested
in being the third.
The night is young,
motherfucker.
Where are you going, Tony?
Where are you going?
Ooh!
How your balls
feel there, fucko?
Ok, maricón.
Tell me something, t.
Come on. Talk to me.
Dime.
All right. All right.
All right.
I started working for Manny
after we got out of riker's.
Me and nine lives were slinging
jobs over in seward park.
Now, I never liked
being around him,
but business is business.
We only worked together
for about a year.
He could never stop
running his mouth
about how much money
he was going to be making,
how Manny was going
to hook him up
with a franchise
of his own now.
You know what I mean, Mike?
I kept my mouth shut
and went about my business,
but Manny heard.
Man, all the wolf tickets
that nine lives was selling
decided to cash in on him.
One day, I look up,
walks up to nine lives
in seward park,
shot him in the head.
Then I come into thinking, man,
about getting
out of the life, you know?
About getting my shit together.
Max was pregnant with
precious at the time, man.
I wanted to be around
to see my firstborn,
so I went to Manny.
I told him how I was feeling
about my situation,
and he was cool, man,
so I took my little bit
of chump change that I made
from slinging them rocks,
and I stepped the fuck off,
moved to Jersey.
I got my little storefront...
some washing machines,
a couple of dryers,
and that's when I went
into business for myself.
So I swear to you, Mike,
on my little girl, man,
I ain't had no further
conversations with Manny
or fucking Freddie nine lives
or anybody else in the life
except for you.
The only reason
I didn't tell you
was I didn't want
to let you down.
Word is bond, man?
My word is bond.
Now she caught on kind of fast
as the months rolled past.
Are we game
till the bitter end?
A better ho I have yet to know,
and they claim a dog
is a man's best friend.
She ran with the best,
from the east to the west.
I liked when her
boosting hand came down.
Many, many a chump
got left in the dumps
as we stole from them
in all of them towns.
Yeah, I laid, and I played
off the bread this bitch made
from the coast to old Broadway.
My habits were small,
and the money was tall.
I really made
this business pay.
Torch: What a fucking
fairy tale.
Don't believe him.
He's only trying
to save his ass.
We're going to have
to trust him.
Why?
Because I say so.
Look. Fuck that.
Give me the piece.
You don't want to do him?
I'll do him.
How many fucking times
I got to tell you "no"?
We ain't going
to do it your way.
Why the fuck not?
Look. If I was
working for Manny,
you'd be dead already.
Ah, yeah. Maybe.
Ain't no maybe about it
because the longer
you sit here,
it's only a matter of time
before he finds you.
Come on. Think
for a minute, man.
Use your head. Maybe
he's telling the truth.
Yeah, maybe, but...
come on. I want you
to trust me on this,
all right?
I've known this guy
over half my life.
If he says he quit
Manny, I believe him.
Ok. We let him live for now.
I still don't
like you, motherfucker.
Check the pay phone.
See if our friend
is still there.
Mike.
Why heroin, man?
Thought you'd stay
away from that shit.
Debbie being
a dope fiend, and all.
I told you before, Tony.
My sister ain't got
nothing to do with this.
You understand me?
Debbie's clean. She's clean.
Oh, she's clean?
I didn't know that, man.
That's really beautiful.
How's she doing anyway?
Where she at?
Arizona.
They got some kind of
rehab program out there.
Yeah? What's it like
in Arizona?
How the fuck should I know?
Thought maybe your
sister might call you
or write you or something.
Jeez, it's a normal question.
People have families,
they try to stick close,
that's all.
Oh, so now you want to
talk about family, right?
Forget it!
Yeah. Thought so.
If it wasn't your idea,
whose was it? Nine lives?
No, it was mine.
That fucking figures.
Fuck is that supposed to mean?
How's your cold, my man?
Fuck you.
Don't fuck with me.
How's your cold, junkie?
Hey, Tony, what the fuck
you talking about?
I'm talking
about your boy there.
Can't you see he's jonesing?
Don't listen to this guy, Mike.
He's full of shit.
He doesn't know
what the fuck
he's talking about.
He ain't no junkie, Tony.
He's just got a cold.
That's all.
Wake the fuck up, bro.
Boy's got the chills.
His nose is running like
a fucking v-8 engine.
Got no tracks, motherfucker.
See, Mike? No tracks.
What about your feet?
What about them?
I peeked them after you
had your little accident,
stupid-ass junkie.
Should have killed you
when I had the chance,
you motherfucker.
Aah!
Mother, sit your
fucking ass down.
Come on, man.
Check his feet, Mike.
If you don't believe me,
check out his fucking feet.
Get off me, man! Ow!
I swear to God, Mike. No lie.
Check out his fucking feet.
Ow! Get the fu... ow! Fuck! Ow!
It ain't what
it looks like, Mike.
I swear to God,
it ain't that bad.
Man, I'm just chipping,
that's all.
Ow. Fuck! Let me up, man.
Everybody in my family
got to be hooked on dope.
You related to this asshole?
He's my brother, man.
Half brother,
you fucking prick.
Shut the fuck up!
Ow! Ow! Fuck! Ow!
What's the matter,
junkie? You sick?
Say "please," dope fiend.
Say "please"!
Leave him alone.
Ow!
Oh, Mike. That
fucking hurt, Mike.
Oh, man, you got to
fucking help me, man.
Ok. Ok. I got you.
I got you, all right?
We're brothers, right?
Somos hermanos ¿verdad?
We got to look after
each other, right?
Damn, Mike.
I ain't even know
you had a brother,
let alone one who was...
Well, you know it.
I'm sorry, all right?
Tony: I'm sorry, man.
So you all never
met before, right?
You never knew anything
about each other
or nothing?
Damn.
Your pops was a player.
Yeah. I'd like to kill him
for what he did
to me and my mother.
He didn't break
your mother's heart
by knocking up some poor
bitch from the projects.
Hey, listen. You can
talk about your father
any way you want to, ok?
But when you talk
about my mother,
you better show her
some fucking respect.
¿Oiste? You heard what I said?
Yeah, yeah. I heard you
twice the first time.
Let me tell you something
about your old man, Mike.
When I was in high school,
I was a complete
fucking ignoramus
when it came to reading,
writing, arithmetic,
but I always got
good grades in math.
You know why?
Because the old man was
fucking my math teacher.
Miss delvecchio.
Never paid attention
to what we were
supposed to be learning,
so she calls my parents
to have a meeting
about my grades.
So the old man comes
down to the school,
off we go
to the guidance
counselor's office.
So after about 5, 10
minutes of conversation
about my grades, my attitude,
my attention span, whatever,
she goes to me and Mr. D.,
"would you gentlemen
step outside
so I can talk to
Mr. Murphy in private?"
So I'm sitting in class
just after she came in.
I remember thinking,
"there's something
different about her."
She was always kind of
an uptight broad,
wore her hair
pinned up in a bun.
She comes back from
talking to the old man.
All of a sudden
she's wearing it
down around her shoulders.
You know, like out of nowhere,
she's all relaxed.
She's got that
well-fucked look,
you know?
She never said
another word to me
for the rest of the year,
not a fucking word except,
"thank you, Mr. Murphy,"
when I handed in my test,
and that was the reason
I suddenly became
a mathematical genius.
Broke my mother's heart.
Because I knew about it,
I could never look her
in her eyes again.
Now I ain't going
to sit here and tell you
that he didn't give you
and your poor mother
a hard way to go,
but me and my mother
put up with more
of his bullshit
on a day-to-day basis
than you could ever
imagine, Mike.
So believe me when I tell you
I know how you feel, bro.
Believe me, man, I do.
Damn.
That's fucked up, yo.
Tony: Now, you know
how some bitches cry
about the wind being high,
cops being on their trail,
about the snow and the sleet
being asshole-deep
and all the pimps
can go to hell.
Sitting in greasy spoons,
jukebox saloons,
killing a lot of time,
sucking on beers,
crying hard-luck tears
while the pimps
ain't got a dime.
Both: Just sitting
and bullshitting,
sucking them party friends.
Nodding so tough...
they're out messing with stuff...
that they miss
all the righteous tricks.
Why, you could lap their lid
for the lowest bid,
set that young ass on fire...
the cheapest young girl
you could buy.
Digging that cunt
for a solid month
while it's dope that's been
doing all the pimping.
But not this triple-a
broad of mine.
She was a sex machine
that could walk between
raindrops come typhoon,
blizzard, or Gale.
Standing on the hot brick,
she'd turn a trick.
Man, she'd trick
with creeps and freaks,
toenail creeps,
breeds I can't even name,
eskimo, negroes, Jews,
apache, sioux.
To her, it was all the same.
Any way she would follow
that righteous dollar
to hell if she had to go.
And be down there just waiting
that trick with Satan.
She was really
a money-making ho.
Why, for a lick or a lap
of that mental trap,
the tricks defied her due.
Of course, her longest bread
was made by head,
and, Jim, how that bitch
could chew.
Now all my troubles began,
and I quit snorting
and commenced the hit.
Now, you know how that go.
I shot up more dope
than any one bitch could get.
I sold my shack, my Cadillac,
the rug from up off my floor.
I stole from ma and pa,
and I shot up all that dough.
My woman cried
and damn near died
when I ran up with her mink,
but I stayed in my role,
and I stole, and I sold
everything but the kitchen sink.
Down I fell
to the depths of hell.
I had put myself in a cross.
My habits got tall,
my money got small,
but the deadliest blow of all
came when this bitch
took ill on short notice
and could no longer gin.
Her head was dead,
her ass was red,
the lips on her cunt was cold.
I figured, what the hell,
since the bitch ain't well,
I'll get me a wife-in-law.
Now there's this redhead bitch
with a whorehouse itch
over in Bernie Willis' stable.
I call her big mabel,
do my best while you convalesce,
get back on your feet again.
"Like hell," she cried.
"I'll see you dead
before I see you go.
"May the black coach of sorrow
pick your ass up tomorrow
"if you walk beyond that door.
"Now, I ruined my health
and a bid for wealth
"so that you
could have your bed.
"But you done went dopehead...
"shot up all of that bread.
"Now, you talking
that stable shit?
"But you see,
I'm wise to the lines
"that you pimps
drop on the frails
"and the games you try to play,
"and if this shit
don't cease like motherfucker,
"I'm calling the po-lice.
Have them carry your ass away."
Well, I just kept on
fixing my shit
because I was aiming to split.
This is what I said.
Mike: What did you say?
"Bitch, you ain't no lady.
"You know the game,
but they call it cop and blow.
"You done had your run,
and now you're done.
"I'm going to find me
another ho.
"Now, wouldn't I look silly
with a broke-down filly
on a track that
was way too fast?"
Mike: Mm-hmm.
"Besides, a bitch ain't shit
without a good man's wit,
"and your thoroughbred
days are past.
"No, I'll put you in charge
of my whorehouse at large,
"give some girls the rule.
"But you sound like hell
"talking about
putting me in jail,
"you must be
a goddamn fool, bitch.
"Step aside. Let me slide.
Hurry up. Get off my back."
"I'm going to find me
another young woman
who can run
the real fast track."
Now I lean on my back
in another ho's shack
running down my pedigree.
We heard a tremendous thunder
that shook the door under,
and I'm wondering
who in the fuck that could be.
Just then a policeman walked in
with a great big grin
fixed in a deadly expression.
Wants to know,
"your name rock?"
"Pimping rock."
"Hurry up.
Sign this confession."
"That's him," she cried,
swinging her arms
in the deepest of glee.
"That's the dirty son of a bitch
with the con man pitch
that made a stinking ho
out of me."
Just then, a deadly blow
knocked me to the floor,
and I fell into a black repose.
When I awoke, my jaw was broke.
Blood was all over my clothes.
And that's the tale that I tell
from my prison cell,
sitting here on my bed.
Murder one, possession of a gun,
and, yeah, I shot that
stinking bitch dead.
Torch: I'm really sick, Mike.
You got to help me.
Mike, I'm really
fucking sick, man.
You got to just let me
have a little taste.
No way, man.
No way I can let you
have any of that shit.
I just need a little bit, man.
That's all.
I just need a little bit.
Sorry. You got to
excuse me, bro,
but I can't let you
do that. All right?
I'm going to be sick.
Hey. Come on. Billy?
Billy.
You ok? Huh? You ok, bro?
You all right?
Oh, shit.
Shh.
Motherfucker, let me
have a little bit, man.
I just need a little bit.
Come on, man.
I need a little bit.
Come on.
I don't fix soon,
I'm going to fucking die.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Don't say that.
You ain't going to die.
He's going to wish he was dead
if he don't get straight.
It still don't make no sense
in putting that shit
in his veins, Tony.
He ain't going to get better
no time soon without it.
Torch, when's the last
time you fixed?
Yesterday.
Come on, Mike.
I'm fucking sick, man.
Come on.
Man, why I got to have
a dopesick junkie
for a brother?
Huh?
You don't want him to be sick?
Let him fix.
Ok.
Ok. Go ahead. Comé mierda.
Put that fucking
poison in your body.
Why the fuck should I care?
Come on.
Sit over here.
Thanks, bro.
Don't call me that.
Sh...
I'm sorry, bro.
Hey, don't call me that.
Aah! Mike!
You heard what I said?
Don't you ever call me that
as long as you live.
Aah!
Mike!
First my sister.
Now this fucking shit?
Put your head
out the window, man.
You need to chill.
You're only
my half brother anyway.
I don't even know why
I thought that shit
meant anything to me.
Get the fuck out.
Fuck.
You got your works, baby?
Yeah, in my jacket.
All right.
Fuck.
You guys got to help me, man.
My hand don't work no more.
I can't do this one by myself.
Don't you even
fucking look at me.
I hope that shit kills you.
Don't say that.
I got it, baby.
What you need?
I just need you
to hook it up for me.
Ok.
Like this?
Yeah, that's good.
Hey, Tony, man...
Thanks.
No problem.
I'm sorry about
throwing up on you.
It's just when I get
sick like this,
I can't help myself.
And you, too, Mike.
I'm sorry about
pissing my pants
in front of your
friend here, man.
Hope I didn't embarrass you.
It's just when I get sick,
I can't help...
Torch: Come on, man.
Don't look at me like that.
I hate it when people
look at me like that.
Don't fucking look
at me like that.
What you do that
shit for anyway, man?
I don't know.
Because it's all I got.
That's bullshit.
No, it's not bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
You are bullshit, man.
You're bullshit.
Oh, no, I almost forgot,
you're my long lost
half brother, right?
You tell me, what
else have I got?
I got no real family.
Got no job.
Ain't been able to keep one
the past 5 years.
Last job I had, I missed
so many workdays
from being sick,
I said "fuck it."
Started stealing full-time
to support my habit.
It's part of the reason
I started hitting
myself in the feet.
This way, I don't
got to walk around
wearing long sleeves
all the time.
Sure, you know, it gets messy...
walking around,
blood dripping
out of your shoe.
It's easy to hide.
You want to know why, Mike?
You really want to know why
I shoot dope?
Because I have to.
The colds, they come.
I don't, I get sick.
You ever been sick?
So fucking sick your
whole body aches,
your guts feel like
it's on fire,
your blood's boiling?
There's not a fucking thing
in the whole wide world
you can do about it.
It's not a good feeling, bro.
Stop looking at me like that.
20/20 my ass.
Yeah, you got eyes
in the back of your head.
You got any idea what it's like
to want to quit and
know that you can't?
Like you really,
really want to quit,
but you just can't?
Like in the past 5 years alone,
I tried to kick
3 different times.
Cold Turkey the first time.
Next two times,
tried a 10-day
methadone program
they got over in Brooklyn.
I had 7 out of 10 days clean
on my first go-around.
Big fucking deal, right?
Next time, two years later,
on the 11th day,
my girlfriend pattie
came to pick me up.
Off we went to cup.
I had 11 days clean,
$60 in my pocket.
Bought 5 bags of dope,
a pack of cigarettes.
Shot them up just like...
I remember the high
I got from that shit
like it was yesterday.
Felt like superman.
Invincible, you know?
Here I come, man...
Looking at you with those eyes.
Only it wasn't your face
I'd be looking at.
It was my own.
I'd be staring in the mirror,
begging and crying
for him to let me stop,
but he wouldn't.
Just kept staring back at me
with this look on his face
that's saying,
"who's that crazy
strung-out junkie
"looking at me?
"Can't be who I think it is.
"I don't look like that, do I?
"This guy looks dangerous.
"Too dangerous to be
on the street.
Too dangerous to be me."
But it is you.
It's you exactly
the way you are,
sure as shit.
What scares you the most is,
that's what people see
when they look at you
the way you look at me.
Whoa.
Mike?
I'm not feeling too good, man.
Mike: Billy, stop
fucking around, man.
Billy?
Ok, um...
Ok.
I got to pick
you up. All right?
We're going to walk,
Billy. Come on.
Going to walk with me, bro?
That's it, huh? Come on.
What's the difference
between the police
and the po-lice?
No idea.
Well, obviously you've never
been chased by them.
Come on, Billy.
Come on.
Come on, Mike. Look at you.
What you look like, man?
Tony, you're supposed
to be helping me, man.
Oh, I'm supposed
to be helping you?
Ain't that a bitch?
Don't move, Billy.
You stay right there.
I'm going to fix you up, ok?
We're going to fix you up.
Ok.
Come on. Don't be dead.
Don't be dead, ok?
Billy, Billy,
don't be dead, ok?
Come on.
It's supposed to be my dope.
Yeah.
The dope you stole?
Mine.
But you said...
you said you
was out of the life.
Oh, come on, Mike.
Once in the life,
always in the life.
You know the game.
Hey, Tony. Look, uh,
I need you to help me now.
Ok?
I want to, Mike.
I really do.
Besides killing you myself...
I can't do nothing
for you, baby.
You going to kill me, man?
I don't know, man.
You don't know?
Come on, man.
You just now said
you was going to kill me.
Me... godfather
to your firstborn.
You remember me?
Too much crime,
too much time like this, yo.
Now you standing
there telling me
that all that shit don't count?
Like it don't mean nothing?
Like, what, all of a sudden
I'm... I'm... I'm
a fucking stranger?
I don't mean shit
to you no more?
I can't believe that, man.
I mean, I know a lot of shit
can happen in 2 or 3 years.
You know, people change.
But, Tony, yo,
what the fuck happened to you?
The fucking world
happened to me, Mike.
I got a criminal record, Mike.
The world don't want
no parts of me.
It don't give a fuck about me.
It don't owe me shit.
Not a goddamn thing.
So I did what
I had to do, Mike.
Now I don't owe nobody nothing.
Yeah, nobody but Manny.
You owe him.
The motherfucker owns you.
No, motherfucker. Oh?
You own me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
about the dope, man.
I didn't know it
was yours, you know?
Talk to Manny. Maybe...
Manny ain't interested
in no conversations
about nothing.
Take a look
out the window, Mike.
Go ahead. Take a look
out the window.
This ain't no flimflam.
This ain't no
riker's fucking island.
This is the life, Mike.
What do you think
they're going to do
to me when I don't
come through?
What do you think
they're going to do
to Maxine, my little girl?
They got Max?
They got precious?
I'm sorry, Tony, man.
I didn't mean to put
you in no shit.
You are so fucking
full of shit, Mike.
I just thought that I could...
you thought?
You thought what?
That you could be Manny?
That you could
trust nine lives?
You see, that's your problem
right there, Mike.
You don't think.
You never fucking did.
20/20 Mike.
You walk around like
a fucking blind man, man.
I ain't ready
to die today, Tony.
Brother, I ain't ready
to die for you.
Ok.
Ok, I'll make a deal
with you then.
Fuck a deal.
Come on, man.
Look, I'm going
to go downstairs
like you said. I just...
ok, I'm going to go
downstairs. I'm...
shut the fuck up, Mike.
I ain't trying to hear you.
I need you to stall
them for me.
I ain't trying
to hear you, Mike.
Listen to me.
I'm going to go downstairs
like you said, but
I'm going to try...
fuck that, Mike.
Get your fucking ass in here.
I'm going to try
and make it. I just...
I'm going to make it.
I'm going to...
get that fucking hand down.
Tony, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you, man.
Please don't kill me, all right?
Tony, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you, please.
Please don't kill me, Tony.
Tony. Tony, don't kill me.
No me mates, man. No me mates.
Tony.
Get up.
Huh?
Get the fuck up, Mike.
I don't even know
why I'm doing this,
but...
Because I'm your boy.
Too much crime,
too much time. Too much time.
Mike...
What the fuck
am I going to say to Manny?
Hey, hey. Come on. Come on.
Come on, Tony.
You'll think of something.
You'll think of something, man.
You're smart.
Are we going
to do this? Mm-hmm?
We're going to do
this right now, Mike.
Ok. Ok. Do-or-die time, right?
Right. Ok.
Do-or-die time.
In all these years
I've known you,
you ain't never
laughed at my shit,
and my shit is funny.
According to you.
That... that police, po-lice...
That's funny shit.
Then why didn't I laugh?
You know, there's
funny, and there's...
You.
Oh, man.
Yo, Mike.
Take care of yourself, man.
Hell, yeah.
Listen, Tony, you give precious
a big hug from Uncle Mikey, ok?
Yeah.
He was not funny. I'm funny.
Are... are we being
a little sensitive?
No.
Come on, now.
Did he hurt your
feelings, ruffy?
You hurt my feelings.
I'm funny.
You got a... please.
That shit was funny,
what I said.
Come on, motherfucker.
Answer the phone.
All right.
Mike: Oh, shit!
Mike?
Yeah?
You all right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm ok.
What happened?
I thought I saw
a fucking rat, man.
All aboard for the night train.
Mike, it's do-or-die time, man.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to try to go out
a back window on another floor.
Hold up a minute, Mike.
You almost forgot
your piece, man.
Tony.
Thanks a lot, bro.
Goddamn, man.
Tony.
Take that with you, baby.
Knock knock.
Oh, isn't that precious?
First degree, baby.
First degree.
Tony on cell phone: Manny.
Tony. You got it?
Yeah. I got it.
All of it?
I said it's done.
Very nice, Tony.
Tony, voice-over:
And that's the tale that I tell
from my prison cell,
sitting here on my bed.
Murder one,
possession of a gun,
and, yeah, I shot
that stinking bitch dead.
Captioning made possible by
trimark pictures
captioned by the national
captioning institute
www.Ncicap.Org...
¶ Home is where we go ¶
¶ to pick up the pieces ¶
¶ once again ¶
¶ home is where we go ¶
¶ to pick up the pieces ¶
¶ once again ¶
¶ my eyes, softly they weep ¶
¶ they have seen but one
too many days ¶
¶ my heart is ever so weary ¶
¶ though it would not
know love anyway ¶
¶ anyway ¶
¶ home is where we go ¶
¶ to pick up the pieces ¶