August 3rd. July 12th. May 13th.
July 12th. May 13th. Dates,
ladies and gentlemen...
may 13th. Dates, ladies
and gentlemen... dates.
Dates, ladies and gentlemen... dates.
What are these numbers that
dates. What are these numbers
that shape our history?
What are these numbers that shape our
history? Who are the players, and what is
shape our history? Who are the
players, and what is the sport?
Who are the players, and what is the sport?
Among the toiling masses, few
the sport? Among the toiling masses,
few will rise, and among them, even
among the toiling masses, few will rise, and among
them, even fewer will secure a place in the
will rise, and among them, even fewer will
secure a place in the annals of history.
Fewer will secure a place in the annals of
history. What are these immortals whose
annals of history. What are these immortals
whose great minds live on centuries
what are these immortals whose great minds
live on centuries after their dying day?
Great minds live on centuries after their
dying day? Let us look now into the life of
after their dying day? Let us look
now into the life of one such man.
Let us look now into the life of one
such man. Ladies and gentlemen, the
one such man. Ladies and gentlemen,
the extraordinary life and times of
ladies and gentlemen, the extraordinary
life and times of k. Roth binew.
Extraordinary life and times of k. Roth
binew. Where is glory born, you ask?
K. Roth binew. Where is
glory born, you ask? Here.
Where is glory born, you ask? Here.
K. Roth binew fought his way
here. K. Roth binew fought his
way into the world with his
k. Roth binew fought his way into the world
with his perceptions fully intact and
into the world with his perceptions
fully intact and thought on birth the
perceptions fully intact and
thought on birth the following...
Thought on birth the following...
"My mother's cry rang out with
following... "My mother's cry rang out
with my own... a chorus of sorrow and"
"my mother's cry rang out with my own...
a chorus of sorrow and pain."
My own... a chorus of sorrow and pain.
If birth is violent, what will
"pain. If birth is violent,
what will be the rest?"
"If birth is violent, what will be the
rest?" Alma binew, while completely
"be the rest?" Alma binew, while completely
overbearing and sometimes cruel,
Alma binew, while completely overbearing and
sometimes cruel, proved to be his harshest
overbearing and sometimes cruel, proved to
be his harshest critic... except for his
proved to be his harshest critic... except
for his brother, Karl, of course, who
critic... except for his brother, Karl, of
course, who was harsh both critically and
brother, Karl, of course, who was
harsh both critically and physically.
Was harsh both critically and physically.
But it only made him stronger,
physically. But it only made him
stronger, and if he ever tries it again,
but it only made him stronger, and if he ever
tries it again, Karl will be very, very sorry.
And if he ever tries it again, Karl will be very,
very sorry. Lampert binew, a brilliant and
Karl will be very, very sorry. Lampert binew,
a brilliant and grossly misunderstood genius,
lampert binew, a brilliant and grossly misunderstood
genius, would provide k. Roth with the
grossly misunderstood genius, would provide k.
Roth with the necessary foundations for what
would provide k. Roth with the necessary
foundations for what would one day be his brain.
Necessary foundations for what would one day
be his brain. >> Father, what is the key to a
would one day be his brain. >> Father,
what is the key to a good life?
Well, k. Roth, don't you worry your little
head. Someday I'll explain it all to
worry your little head. Someday I'll explain
it all to you in a brief but powerful
someday I'll explain it all to you
in a brief but powerful monologue.
You in a brief but powerful monologue.
Now, how about we go and find
monologue. Now, how about we go and
find you a piece of wire, huh?
Now, how about we go and find you a piece
of wire, huh? >> When lampert binew did not
you a piece of wire, huh? >> When lampert
binew did not return home one fateful day,
when lampert binew did not return home one
fateful day, k. Roth was left to find the
return home one fateful day, k. Roth was left
to find the brief but powerful monologue on
k. Roth was left to find the brief
but powerful monologue on his own.
Brief but powerful monologue on his own.
Abandoned by the one person who
his own. Abandoned by the one person
who understood him, k. Roth retreats
abandoned by the one person who understood
him, k. Roth retreats into a deep sadness...
Understood him, k. Roth retreats into a deep
sadness... Only to be revived by the good
into a deep sadness... Only to be revived
by the good graces of young love.
Only to be revived by the good graces of
young love. Though distant in years, k. Roth
graces of young love. Though distant in
years, k. Roth and his nanny, Marla, shared a
though distant in years, k. Roth and his nanny,
Marla, shared a love unrivaled in the history of
and his nanny, Marla, shared a love unrivaled in
the history of man... truly the greatest love
love unrivaled in the history of man... truly the
greatest love affair never to be consummated.
Man... truly the greatest love affair never to
be consummated. But even love took a back seat
affair never to be consummated. But even love
took a back seat to his new friend, alcohol.
But even love took a back seat to his new
friend, alcohol. It was at this point that he
to his new friend, alcohol. It was at this
point that he stopped making friends and
it was at this point that he stopped making
friends and decided to focus on his artistic
stopped making friends and decided to focus on
his artistic endeavors... 22 novels, ladies
decided to focus on his artistic endeavors...
22 novels, ladies and gentlemen, 16 thought
endeavors... 22 novels, ladies and
gentlemen, 16 thought pieces, and over 2,000
and gentlemen, 16 thought pieces, and
over 2,000 unclassified art happenings.
Pieces, and over 2,000 unclassified art
happenings. While the arts controlled and
unclassified art happenings. While the arts
controlled and shaped his life, there were
while the arts controlled and shaped his life,
there were times when they did not pay the
shaped his life, there were times
when they did not pay the bills.
Times when they did not pay the bills.
He was employed as a bellboy,
bills. He was employed as a
bellboy, longshoreman, benevolent
he was employed as a bellboy, longshoreman,
benevolent dictator of an art farm, and
longshoreman, benevolent dictator
of an art farm, and mental patient.
Dictator of an art farm, and mental
patient. By a twist that can only be
mental patient. By a twist that can
only be ascribed to fate, he finds
by a twist that can only be ascribed to
fate, he finds himself writing math word
ascribed to fate, he finds himself writing
math word problems for a major textbook
himself writing math word problems
for a major textbook company.
Problems for a major textbook company.
Turning the industry on its
company. Turning the industry on
its head, binew was the first to
turning the industry on its head, binew was
the first to attribute personalities to
head, binew was the first to attribute
personalities to numbers, something that was
attribute personalities to numbers, something
that was thought to be stupid only years
numbers, something that was thought
to be stupid only years earlier.
Thought to be stupid only years earlier.
But even a great man is not free
earlier. But even a great man is not
free from the invisible pathogens
but even a great man is not free from the
invisible pathogens that attack the body like a
from the invisible pathogens that attack the
body like a brigade of bloodthirsty rebels,
that attack the body like a brigade of bloodthirsty
rebels, and one thing all great men can
brigade of bloodthirsty rebels, and one thing
all great men can count on is that someday they
and one thing all great men can count on is that
someday they will get bad news from a doctor.
Count on is that someday they will get bad news
from a doctor. >> K. Roth binew is dying of a
will get bad news from a doctor. >> K. Roth binew
is dying of a yet-to-be-named, grave, vague
k. Roth binew is dying of a
yet-to-be-named, grave, vague disease.
Yet-to-be-named, grave, vague disease.
It is almost as grave in its
disease. It is almost as grave in
its vagueness as it is vague in its
it is almost as grave in its vagueness
as it is vague in its graveness.
Vagueness as it is vague in its graveness.
What we do know for sure is that
graveness. What we do know for sure
is that the disease is punctual and
what we do know for sure is that the
disease is punctual and deadly.
The disease is punctual and deadly.
Which brings us to today,
deadly. >> Which brings us to
today, ladies and gentlemen.
Which brings us to today, ladies and
gentlemen. Alas, as the sun sets on
ladies and gentlemen. Alas, as the sun
sets on k. Roth binew, we ask ourselves,
alas, as the sun sets on k. Roth binew, we ask
ourselves, will our hero go into the void
k. Roth binew, we ask ourselves, will our hero
go into the void without finding the brief but
will our hero go into the void without
finding the brief but powerful monologue?
Without finding the brief but powerful
monologue? Will his greatness be
powerful monologue? Will his
greatness be recognized?
No. No. Ah.
No. Ah. Gabriel, where
is that father of
ah. Gabriel, where is
that father of yours?
Gabriel, where is that father of yours?
I have an invitation for him.
Yours? I have an invitation for him.
Get away from my kid, binew.
I have an invitation for him. >> Get away
from my kid, binew. Gabe, get inside.
Get away from my kid, binew. Gabe, get
inside. >> Reginald, I am leaving the
Gabe, get inside. >> Reginald, I am leaving
the world today, and I would like to
Reginald, I am leaving the world today, and
I would like to invite you to my going-away
world today, and I would like to
invite you to my going-away party.
Invite you to my going-away party.
If only that were true,
party. >> If only that were true,
binew, this neighborhood would
if only that were true, binew, this
neighborhood would be livable again.
Binew, this neighborhood would be livable
again. >> Oh, Reginald, let us put
be livable again. >> Oh, Reginald,
let us put aside our petty quarrels.
Oh, Reginald, let us put aside our petty
quarrels. Today my mind leans towards the
aside our petty quarrels. Today my
mind leans towards the perpetual.
Today my mind leans towards the perpetual.
So, with this invitation and
perpetual. So, with this invitation
and this handshake, I offer you my
so, with this invitation and this
handshake, I offer you my friendship.
This handshake, I offer you my friendship.
Not in a million years,
friendship. >> Not in a
million years, binew!
Not in a million years, binew!
I've endured your nonsense for
binew! I've endured your
nonsense for far too long!
I've endured your nonsense for far too
long! Today is your day of reckoning!
Far too long! Today is your day of
reckoning! >> Ah, that's the stuff, Reggie.
Today is your day of reckoning! >> Ah, that's the
stuff, Reggie. First thing in the morning, I
ah, that's the stuff, Reggie. First thing in the
morning, I like to get empty threats from a
first thing in the morning, I like to
get empty threats from a shallow man.
Like to get empty threats from a
shallow man. It gets my blood going.
Shallow man. It gets my blood going.
You're mine, binew.
It gets my blood going. >> You're mine,
binew. >> Just remember to show up at
you're mine, binew. >> Just remember
to show up at the wake, Reginald.
Just remember to show up at the wake,
Reginald. There'll be a surprise waiting
the wake, Reginald. There'll
be a surprise waiting for you.
There'll be a surprise
waiting for you. >> Sir.
For you. >> Sir. >> Ah! My ride.
Sir. >> Ah! My ride. >> You...
Ah! My ride. >> You...
You make me nervous.
You... You make me nervous.
Farewell, Reggie.
Aw, mills, it... it seems just like yesterday
that I found you cowering in that broom closet.
Like yesterday that I found you cowering
in that broom closet. Poor child.
Cowering in that broom closet. Poor child.
You couldn't speak, let alone
poor child. You couldn't
speak, let alone write.
You couldn't speak, let alone write.
And you gave me soup, sir, a
write. >> And you gave me soup, sir,
a warm blanket, and a dictionary.
And you gave me soup, sir, a warm blanket, and
a dictionary. >> And I haven't been able to
warm blanket, and a dictionary. >> And I
haven't been able to shake you since.
And I haven't been able to shake you since.
Look at you now... my best
shake you since. Look at you now... my
best friend, on-the-rise biographer,
look at you now... my best friend, on-the-rise
biographer, and poet extraordinaire.
Friend, on-the-rise biographer, and
poet extraordinaire. >> Yes, sir.
And poet extraordinaire. >> Yes, sir.
In fact, I've often thought
yes, sir. In fact, I've often thought
that if it wasn't for you...
in fact, I've often thought that if it wasn't
for you... >> the road, man! The road!
Mills! A quote from my father. "I drink to bring
myself down to the level of the common man."
"I drink to bring myself down to the level of
the common man. But remember, the common man"
the level of the common man. But remember, the
common man drinks, so I must drink twice as
but remember, the common man drinks,
so I must drink twice as much.
Drinks, so I must drink twice as much.
I am a big advocate of an even
"much. I am a big advocate
of an even playing field."
Oh, your instincts are incorrect,
liquorsmith. But, being a sporting man, I
incorrect, liquorsmith. But, being a sporting
man, I will give you one more chance to
but, being a sporting man, I will give you one
more chance to guess what I'll be purchasing.
Will give you one more chance to guess what I'll
be purchasing. >> Well, what are we betting
guess what I'll be purchasing. >>
Well, what are we betting today?
This vest.
Today? >> This vest. >>
I don't like the vest.
This vest. >> I don't like the vest.
How about that tie?
I don't like the vest. How about that tie?
All right.
How about that tie? >> All right.
My tie for... Your glasses.
All right. My tie for... Your glasses.
You're on.
Oh. Wrong again, liquorsmith.
Mills, collect the spoils.
Liquorsmith. Mills, collect the spoils.
Glasses, please.
Mills, collect the spoils. >>
Glasses, please. >> Really?
Yes.
Really? >> Yes. >> I can't
see very well without
yes. >> I can't see very well without
them, and they're my only pair.
I can't see very well without them, and they're
my only pair. >> Well, it seems you have found
them, and they're my only pair. >> Well, it seems
you have found yourself in quite a predicament,
well, it seems you have found yourself
in quite a predicament, liquorsmith.
Yourself in quite a predicament,
liquorsmith. And here I am with this
liquorsmith. And here I am with
this perfectly useless pair of
and here I am with this perfectly
useless pair of glasses.
Perfectly useless pair of glasses.
Yeah, you just won them in
glasses. >> Yeah, you
just won them in the bet.
Yeah, you just won them in the bet.
Yes.
The bet. >> Yes. >> As
a-a neutral third party,
yes. >> As a-a neutral third party,
it seems that you each have what
as a-a neutral third party, it seems that
you each have what the other desires.
It seems that you each have what the other
desires. So, gentlemen, may I suggest a-a
the other desires. So, gentlemen,
may I suggest a-a barter?
So, gentlemen, may I suggest a-a barter?
Excellent idea.
Barter? >> Excellent idea. >>
Uh, I might be interested in
excellent idea. >> Uh, I might
be interested in a barter.
Uh, I might be interested in a barter.
Tell you what, liquorsmith...
a barter. >> Tell you what, liquorsmith...
I will give you these glasses
tell you what, liquorsmith... I will give
you these glasses for your finest bottle of
I will give you these glasses for your
finest bottle of stubborn grouse bourbon.
For your finest bottle of stubborn
grouse bourbon. >> Grouse?
Stubborn grouse bourbon. >> Grouse?
Yes, the stubborn grouse.
Grouse? >> Yes, the stubborn grouse.
Come on, k. Roth.
Yes, the stubborn grouse. >> Come on, k.
Roth. >> Well, these do look quite
come on, k. Roth. >> Well, these do
look quite charming on me, don't they,
well, these do look quite charming
on me, don't they, mills?
Charming on me, don't they, mills?
Perfect fit, sir.
Mills? >> Perfect fit, sir.
Grouse.
Perfect fit, sir. >> Grouse.
Glasses.
Grouse. >> Glasses.
Thank you.
Glasses. >> Thank you.
Mind if I have a sip?
Thank you. >> Mind if I have a sip?
No.
- Mind if I have a sip?
- >> No.
- No.
- >> Here's an invitation to his.
Here's an invitation to his
wake tonight.
Here's an invitation to his wake tonight.
I hope you can make it.
Wake tonight. I hope you can make it.
I know it's short notice, but
I hope you can make it. I know it's short
notice, but the doctor only told him a few
I know it's short notice, but the doctor only
told him a few days ago, and he hadn't accepted
the doctor only told him a few days ago, and he
hadn't accepted the whole affair until late last
days ago, and he hadn't accepted the
whole affair until late last night.
The whole affair until late last night.
There'll be drinks, hors
night. >> There'll be drinks, hors
d'oeuvres, and maybe a little
there'll be drinks, hors d'oeuvres, and
maybe a little dancing after I kick off.
D'oeuvres, and maybe a little dancing
after I kick off. Who knows?
Dancing after I kick off. Who knows?
I thought it was very funny,
who knows? >> I thought
it was very funny, sir.
I thought it was very funny, sir.
Well, sir, where next?
Sir. Well, sir, where next?
To the recreation park,
well, sir, where next? >> To
the recreation park, mills.
To the recreation park, mills.
I've had some bourbon, with more
mills. I've had some bourbon,
with more on the way.
I've had some bourbon, with more on
the way. I'm feeling sprightly now.
On the way. I'm feeling sprightly now.
They will think me the fool,
I'm feeling sprightly now. They will think
me the fool, mills, in my final moments with
they will think me the fool, mills, in my final
moments with a fatal disease exercising.
Mills, in my final moments with a fatal
disease exercising. >> Who are "they," sir?
A fatal disease exercising. >> Who are
"they," sir? There you go. Upper-tupper.
Who are "they," sir? There you go.
Upper-tupper. >> One...
There you go. Upper-tupper. >> One...
They will call it futile, mills.
One... They will call it futile, mills.
They will say I am mad.
They will call it futile, mills. They
will say I am mad. And mad I might be.
They will say I am mad. And mad I might be.
Ah, your stamina is
and mad I might be. >> Ah, your
stamina is inspiring, sir.
Ah, your stamina is inspiring, sir.
Thank you, mills.
Inspiring, sir. >> Thank you, mills.
Though my hours are dwindling
thank you, mills. Though my hours are
dwindling and I am desperate for the
though my hours are dwindling and I am desperate
for the answer, I refuse to shirk the
and I am desperate for the answer, I refuse
to shirk the responsibility I have to my
answer, I refuse to shirk the
responsibility I have to my human body.
Hello!
I've got business for you!
How may I help you? >> Ah, yes.
We were wondering what kind of
ah, yes. We were wondering what kind
of body-disposal options you carry.
We were wondering what kind of body-disposal
options you carry. >> Let me say first I'm sorry
body-disposal options you carry. >> Let
me say first I'm sorry about your loss.
Let me say first I'm sorry
about your loss.
About your loss.
Haven't lost anything yet.
I'm dying tonight.
Haven't lost anything yet. I'm
dying tonight. >> You're the body?
I'm dying tonight. >> You're the body?
Yes.
You're the body? >> Yes.
Well, I admit that I
yes. Well, I admit that I
procrastinated a little.
Well, I admit that I procrastinated a
little. >> Usually the family takes care
procrastinated a little. >> Usually the
family takes care of that after the death.
Usually the family takes care of that after
the death. >> Oh! So, I am early and we
of that after the death. >> Oh! So, I
am early and we will get a discount!
Oh! So, I am early and we will get a
discount! >> Uh, well, uh, perhaps we
will get a discount! >> Uh, well, uh,
perhaps we could work s-something...
uh, well, uh, perhaps we could work
s-something... >> are you all right, friend?
Could work s-something... >> are you all
right, friend? You seem to have transcended
are you all right, friend? You
seem to have transcended pale.
You seem to have transcended pale.
Well, I-I must admit I've
pale. >> Well, I-I must admit I've
never dealt with the body before
well, I-I must admit I've never
dealt with the body before he died.
Never dealt with the body before he died.
And this whole situation is
he died. And this whole situation
is making me... A bit uneasy.
And this whole situation is
making me... A bit uneasy.
Making me... A bit uneasy.
Well, what is life if it is not.
Well, what is life if it is not
uneasy?
Well, what is life if it is not uneasy?
So, what are the various fire
uneasy? So, what are the
various fire options?
So, what are the various fire options?
I'm sure you have standard
options? I'm sure you have standard
cremation, but we were thinking
I'm sure you have standard cremation, but we
were thinking something more along the lines
cremation, but we were thinking something more
along the lines of a funeral pyre in the town
something more along the lines of a
funeral pyre in the town square.
Of a funeral pyre in the town
square.
Square.
Unfortunately, our only options.
Unfortunately, our only options
are cremation and burial.
Unfortunately, our only options are cremation
and burial. >> Or a viking ceremony.
Are cremation and burial. >> Or a viking
ceremony. Mills, tell him about the viking
or a viking ceremony. Mills, tell
him about the viking ceremony.
Mills, tell him about the viking ceremony.
Oh, yes, the vikings used to
ceremony. >> Oh, yes, the vikings
used to put the carcass on a boat and
oh, yes, the vikings used to put the carcass
on a boat and light it ablaze as it was cast
put the carcass on a boat and light
it ablaze as it was cast out to sea.
Light it ablaze as it was cast out to sea.
That's exactly what I
out to sea. >> That's exactly what
I wanted... something dramatic!
That's exactly what I wanted... something
dramatic! >> We tend to specialize in the
wanted... something dramatic! >> We tend
to specialize in the more traditional...
we tend to specialize in the more
traditional... >> oh, and who will be doing my
more traditional... >> oh, and
who will be doing my makeup?
Oh, and who will be doing my makeup?
My son does all the
makeup? >> My son does
all the preparation.
My son does all the preparation.
Tell him to go easy on the
preparation. >> Tell him
to go easy on the Rouge.
Tell him to go easy on the Rouge.
I tend to look a bit queally
Rouge. I tend to look a bit
queally with too much Rouge.
I tend to look a bit queally with too much
Rouge. >> No offense to you, sir, but
with too much Rouge. >> No offense
to you, sir, but we here at
no offense to you, sir, but we here
at mossman's family mortuary think
we here at mossman's family mortuary
think that death and dying are not
mossman's family mortuary think that death
and dying are not even remotely in the
that death and dying are not even remotely
in the neighborhood of things to be
even remotely in the neighborhood
of things to be taken lightly.
Neighborhood of things to be
taken lightly.
- Taken lightly.
- >> That song...
That song...
Um...
That song... >> Um... May I
suggest to you, sir, that
um... May I suggest to you, sir, that
you take your business to one of
may I suggest to you, sir, that you take your
business to one of our competitors, who, because
you take your business to one of our competitors,
who, because they lack a strong moral base,
our competitors, who, because they lack a strong
moral base, will oblige your every request?
They lack a strong moral base, will oblige your
every request? Death is a serious business and
will oblige your every request? Death is a serious
business and will be treated as such until it
death is a serious business and will be treated
as such until it stops happening, which will be
will be treated as such until it stops
happening, which will be never.
Stops happening, which will be never.
Father's coat.
Never. >> Father's coat.
Excuse me?
Father's coat. >> Excuse me? What...
what are you talking
excuse me? What... what
are you talking about?
What... what are you talking about?
Father?
About? >> Father? >> Sir?
Father? >> Sir? >> I
must investigate.
Sir? >> I must investigate.
You can't go in there!
I must investigate. >> You
can't go in there! >> Shh!
You can't go in there!
Shh! Careful.
Shh! Careful. >> Father?
- Careful.
- >> Father?
Father?
Well, I'm sure that he was a.
Well, I'm sure that he was a
lovely man.
Well, I'm sure that he was a lovely man.
Woman.
Lovely man. >> Woman. >> Woman.
Woman. >> Woman. And being
someone that is dying
woman. And being someone that is dying
soon, I look forward to meeting
and being someone that is dying soon, I look
forward to meeting her in the afterlife, which
soon, I look forward to meeting her in
the afterlife, which might not exist.
Her in the afterlife, which might not
exist. Sorry for the interruption.
Might not exist. Sorry for
the interruption. Father!
Collect all the stamps you can.
If you have all the postage, how
can. If you have all the postage,
how can they send you threatening
if you have all the postage, how can
they send you threatening letters?
Can they send you threatening letters?
For two days I controlled all
letters? For two days I
controlled all the postage.
For two days I controlled all the postage.
It might have gone unnoticed by
the postage. It might have gone unnoticed
by many, but you have no idea how
it might have gone unnoticed by many, but you
have no idea how it feels to be the reason
many, but you have no idea how it feels to be
the reason someone's not sending something.
It feels to be the reason someone's not sending
something. That power... very sexual in a
someone's not sending something.
That power... very sexual in a way.
Father, nobody loves your
way. >> Father, nobody loves your
brilliant wisdom more than I do,
father, nobody loves your brilliant wisdom
more than I do, but something still eludes me.
Brilliant wisdom more than I do, but something
still eludes me. Please, tell me the brief but
but something still eludes me. Please,
tell me the brief but powerful monologue.
Please, tell me the brief but powerful
monologue. >> Okay, son. I will.
Powerful monologue.
Okay, son. I will.
I do not understand you,
father.
I do not understand you, father.
Generally, I carry my
father. Generally, I carry my
nonsense-to-English dictionary
generally, I carry my nonsense-to-English
dictionary in my dream world, but I seem to
nonsense-to-English dictionary in my dream world,
but I seem to have left it at my dream house.
In my dream world, but I seem to have left it
at my dream house. Please, father, translate.
Have left it at my dream house. Please,
father, translate. Please, translate.
Please, father, translate. Please,
translate. Please, father, translate!
Please, translate. Please,
father, translate! Please!
Please, father, translate! Please!
Please, father, translate!
Please! Please, father, translate!
Translate!
Please, father, translate!
Translate! Please.
Translate! Please. Translate!
Please. Translate! >> Sir!
Translate! >> Sir! >> Mills,
I was so close to the
sir! >> Mills, I was so
close to the answer.
Mills, I was so close to the answer.
I could hear the words, but I
answer. I could hear the words, but
I could not make sense of them.
I could hear the words, but I could
not make sense of them. My God!
Could not make sense of them. My God!
They were beautiful.
My God! They were beautiful.
Oh, sir, you look crazed.
They were beautiful. >> Oh, sir,
you look crazed. Wipe your brow.
Oh, sir, you look crazed. Wipe your brow.
Oh, yeah.
Wipe your brow. >> Oh, yeah.
Time is moving.
Oh, yeah. >> Time is moving. If
we are to complete our goal,
time is moving. If we are to complete
our goal, we must not chase phantoms.
If we are to complete our goal, we must
not chase phantoms. >> Mills, you are so
we must not chase phantoms. >>
Mills, you are so cool-headed.
I would be lost without you.
Sir, your ride.
Mills, stop the rickshaw. >> What is it,
sir? >> I think you took a wrong turn
what is it, sir? >> I think you
took a wrong turn back there.
I think you took a wrong
turn back there. >> Did I?
Back there. >> Did I? >> Yes.
Did I? >> Yes. You
know the drill.
All right.
You know what to do, mills.
Sir.
Who are you?
I'm a very wealthy
who are you? >> I'm a very wealthy
businessman from a-a very rich
I'm a very wealthy businessman from
a-a very rich part of the country.
Businessman from a-a very rich part
of the country. >> What do you want?
Part of the country. >> What do you want?
I would like to spend a large
what do you want? >> I would like to spend
a large portion of my disposable income
I would like to spend a large portion
of my disposable income on chickens.
Portion of my disposable income
on chickens. >> Sounds crazy!
On chickens. >> Sounds crazy! >>
Yes, well, I am an eccentric.
Sounds crazy! >> Yes, well, I am an
eccentric. >> You're an eccentric?
Yes, well, I am an eccentric.
You're an eccentric? >> Yes.
You're an eccentric?
Yes. >> Oh.
I'm an eccentric, too. I keep
roast beef in my pockets. See?
I keep roast beef in my pockets.
See? >> Yes.
See? >> Yes. >> Now,
let me show you them
yes. >> Now, let me
show you them chickens.
If you look close, you'll notice
there's a duck amongst them chickens.
There's a duck amongst them
chickens.
Chickens.
I like to laugh at that duck.
Watch.
- I like to laugh at that duck.
- Watch.
- Now you try.
Now you try.
Me?
Now you try. >> Me? >> Yeah.
Go ahead!
Me? >> Yeah. Go ahead! Come on!
Yeah. Go ahead!
Come on!
Oh, yes.
You're a fine specimen, yes.
Oh, yes. You're a fine specimen, yes.
Come here. Come here.
You're a fine specimen, yes.
That's good.
Okay. Good.
That's good. >> Okay.
Good. >> Good job.
Okay. Good. >> Good job.
What's that man doing?
Good job. >> What's that man doing?
Looks like he's... he's got
what's that man doing? >> Looks
like he's... he's got your goat.
Looks like he's... he's got your goat.
Uh, well, another eccentric.
- Your goat.
- Uh, well, another eccentric.
Uh, well, another eccentric.
Thank you.
"A pre-picnic prayer poem" by
thank you. >> "A pre-picnic
prayer poem" by mills joquin.
"A pre-picnic prayer poem" by mills joquin.
O, majestic goat, die quietly
mills joquin. >> O, majestic goat, die
quietly on your stake and trust that
o, majestic goat, die quietly on your stake
and trust that your throat will bleat on our
on your stake and trust that your
throat will bleat on our plate.
Your throat will bleat on our plate.
O, majestic goat, have faith
plate. O, majestic goat, have faith
your surrender will sate our
o, majestic goat, have faith your surrender
will sate our tummy boat, will feed our
your surrender will sate our tummy
boat, will feed our luncheon splendor.
Tummy boat, will feed our luncheon
splendor. O, majestic goat.
Most beautiful ceremony, mills.
Well, the goat has been
mills. Well, the goat has been
dispatched, and the gods on
well, the goat has been dispatched, and
the gods on Olympus will be pleased.
Dispatched, and the gods on Olympus
will be pleased. >> Ah, the sun, sir.
Olympus will be pleased. >> Ah,
the sun, sir. It's at its height.
Ah, the sun, sir. It's at its height.
Isn't it always, mills?
It's at its height. >> Isn't it always,
mills? >> No, it's at its apogee,
isn't it always, mills? >> No, it's at
its apogee, sir... the highest point.
No, it's at its apogee, sir...
the highest point. It's noon.
Sir... the highest point. It's noon.
My last apogee.
It's noon. >> My last apogee.
Put that in your eulogy.
My last apogee. Put that in your eulogy.
Oh, I've already written it,
put that in your eulogy. >> Oh, I've already
written it, sir, and it wouldn't fit.
Oh, I've already written it, sir, and it
wouldn't fit. >> But I like how it sounds.
Sir, and it wouldn't fit. >> But I like
how it sounds. >> Well, I can't, sir.
But I like how it sounds. >> Well,
I can't, sir. It just won't fit.
Well, I can't, sir. It just won't fit.
Then why mention it, mills?
It just won't fit. >> Then why mention
it, mills? Why confuse a dying man?
Then why mention it, mills? Why confuse
a dying man? >> You're being irritable.
Why confuse a dying man? >> You're being
irritable. You're probably just hungry.
You're being irritable. You're probably
just hungry. >> Don't tell me who's hungry!
You're probably just hungry. >> Don't tell me
who's hungry! Just drive, you fool! Drive!
I'm sorry about that, mills. It was the
smell of the goat and the anticipation.
It was the smell of the goat and the
anticipation. >> I try my best, sir.
The anticipation. >> I try my best, sir.
I know you do.
I try my best, sir. >> I know you do.
I do try my very best.
I know you do. >> I do try my very best.
I know you do.
I do try my very best. >> I know you do.
It's just that my true love
I know you do. It's just that my true
love might have the knowledge that I
it's just that my true love might have the
knowledge that I seek, and I don't even know if
might have the knowledge that I seek, and
I don't even know if she got my letter.
Seek, and I don't even know if she got my
letter. It might be that love itself is
she got my letter. It might be
that love itself is the answer.
It might be that love itself is the answer.
Love is generally brief.
The answer. Love is generally brief.
Love is powerful.
Love is generally brief. Love is powerful.
While it is not a monologue...
Love is powerful.
My heavens, mills.
She has come!
My heavens, mills. She has come!
Isn't she beautiful?
She has come! Isn't she beautiful?
Finish setting up.
Isn't she beautiful? Finish setting up.
I must greet her.
Oh, ma. I am very flattered that
you've accepted my last-minute
I am very flattered that you've
accepted my last-minute invitation.
Accepted my last-minute invitation.
I see you've brought your
invitation. I see you've
brought your husband.
I see you've brought your husband.
Luckily, this is one of 10
husband. Luckily, this is one of
10 scenarios for which I have a
luckily, this is one of 10 scenarios
for which I have a prepared speech.
Scenarios for which I have a prepared
speech. "Your wife, sir, is my initial"
prepared speech. "Your wife,
sir, is my initial true love."
"Your wife, sir, is my initial true love.
She is someone that I have"
true love. She is someone that I
have fascinated, masturbated, and
she is someone that I have fascinated,
masturbated, and concentrated on for most of my
fascinated, masturbated, and concentrated
on for most of my waking hours.
Concentrated on for most of my waking
hours. So, on my deathbed, will you not
"waking hours. So, on my deathbed, will
you not allow us some time together?"
"So, on my deathbed, will you not
allow us some time together?" >> No.
"Allow us some time together?" >> No.
No?
No. >> No? Well, my
whole life's been
no? Well, my whole
life's been awkward.
Well, my whole life's been awkward.
Why should it stop now?
Awkward. Why should it stop now?
So, it's been a long time.
Why should it stop now? So, it's been
a long time. >> Yes, it has been.
So, it's been a long time. >> Yes, it
has been. >> When did you get married?
Yes, it has been. >> When did you
get married? >> Oh, decades ago.
When did you get married? >>
Oh, decades ago. >> Any kids?
Two.
Any kids? >> Two. >> Well,
they must be at least
two. >> Well, they must be
at least half-beautiful.
Well, they must be at least half-beautiful.
He doesn't look like he comes
half-beautiful. He doesn't look
like he comes from very good stock.
He doesn't look like he comes from very
good stock. >> I'm Franco-prussian!
From very good stock. >> I'm
Franco-prussian! Well, then, you're poorly
I'm Franco-prussian! >> Well,
then, you're poorly made!
Well, then, you're poorly made!
Do you remember when your bosom
made! Do you remember when your
bosom would burn and I would rub a
do you remember when your bosom would burn
and I would rub a soothing salve upon it?
Would burn and I would rub a soothing
salve upon it? >> Ooh. That would sting.
Soothing salve upon it? >> Ooh. That would
sting. >> Yes, gently massaging it in,
ooh. That would sting. >> Yes, gently massaging
it in, nursing your rickety skin back
yes, gently massaging it in, nursing your rickety
skin back to even a semblance of health.
Nursing your rickety skin back to even a
semblance of health. >> Well, I did have rickets
to even a semblance of health. >>
Well, I did have rickets then.
And never have rickets been
then. >> And never have
rickets been more erotic.
And never have rickets been more erotic.
Ah. Here we are.
More erotic. Ah. Here we are. >> Ah.
Mr. binew, welcome back.
Ah. Here we are. >> Ah. Mr. binew,
welcome back. Our favorite customer.
Ah. Mr. binew, welcome back. Our favorite
customer. How are you today, sir?
Our favorite customer. How are
you today, sir? >> Doing well.
How are you today, sir? >> Doing well.
And you, maître d'?
Doing well. And you, maître d'?
Fine, fine.
And you, maître d'? >> Fine, fine.
How many in your party today,
fine, fine. How many in
your party today, sir?
How many in your party today, sir?
Is it gonna be two or three,
sir? >> Is it gonna be
two or three, old man?
Is it gonna be two or three, old man?
Three it is, maître d'.
Old man? Three it is, maître d'.
Three?
Three it is, maître d'.
Three? Huh.
Three? Huh. I believe
that would be a
huh. I believe that would
be a 20-minute wait, sir.
I believe that would be a
20-minute wait, sir. >> Really?
20-minute wait, sir.
Really? >> Yes.
Really? >> Yes. >> Well,
maybe this $2 bill will
yes. >> Well, maybe this $2
bill will change your tune.
Well, maybe this $2 bill will change your
tune. >> Ah. Well, I'll certainly see
change your tune. >> Ah. Well, I'll
certainly see what I can do, sir.
Ah. Well, I'll certainly see what I can
do, sir. >> I'm in pretty good with the
what I can do, sir. >> I'm in pretty
good with the management, so...
I'm in pretty good with the management,
so... >> Hello. It's Mr. binew.
Management, so... >> Hello. It's Mr.
Binew. Uh, now a party of three.
Hello. It's Mr. binew. Uh, now a party
of three. Well, yes, he is our favorite
uh, now a party of three. Well, yes,
he is our favorite customer, so...
Well, yes, he is our favorite
customer, so... I don't care!
Customer, so... I don't care!
Move the mayor!
I don't care! Move the mayor!
Terribly sorry, sir.
Move the mayor! Terribly sorry, sir.
Your table is now ready.
Terribly sorry, sir. Your table
is now ready. >> Marla, please.
Thank you.
Ah. Except for a light snack
later, this will be my last meal.
Except for a light snack later, this will be
my last meal. Mmm. This goat is delectable.
This will be my last meal. Mmm.
This goat is delectable. >> Oh!
Mmm. This goat is delectable.
Oh!
Mr. binew.
Thank you.
Mr. binew. >> Thank you.
Cheers, my love.
Thank you. >> Cheers, my love.
And for you, sir.
Cheers, my love. >> And for you, sir.
To us.
Did you know, old man, that if your beautiful
wife had not saved me those many moons ago
your beautiful wife had not saved me those
many moons ago that I would not be here today?
Saved me those many moons ago that I would not
be here today? For good or for ill, those are
that I would not be here today? For
good or for ill, those are the facts.
For good or for ill, those are the facts.
For, you see, tonight will not
the facts. For, you see, tonight will
not be the first time I will have
for, you see, tonight will not be
the first time I will have died.
Be the first time I will have died.
You're deader than me, you
died. >> You're deader than
me, you drunk sack of shit.
You're deader than me, you drunk sack
of shit. >> No, the first time was long
drunk sack of shit. >> No, the
first time was long ago, old man.
No, the first time was long ago, old man.
I was 9 years old, and she...
ago, old man. I was 9 years old, and she...
well, she was timeless.
I was 9 years old, and she... well, she was
timeless. I was riding my tricycle around
well, she was timeless. I was riding
my tricycle around our backyard.
I was riding my tricycle around our
backyard. We were very wealthy.
Our backyard. We were very wealthy.
We had a linoleum backyard.
We were very wealthy. We had a linoleum
backyard. In the excitement of a turn, I
we had a linoleum backyard. In the
excitement of a turn, I got confused.
In the excitement of a turn, I got
confused. The pool was still.
Got confused. The pool was still.
It looked like a continuation of
the pool was still. It looked like
a continuation of the linoleum.
It looked like a continuation of the
linoleum. Mills, finish the story.
The linoleum. Mills, finish the story.
Yes, sir.
Mills, finish the story.
I plunged in headlong and
floated to the bottom...
I plunged in headlong and floated to the
bottom... In the deep end, old man...
floated to the bottom... In the deep
end, old man... the... the deep end.
In the deep end, old man... the... the
deep end. And I looked to the top, and...
the... the deep end. And I looked to
the top, and... and there was the sun.
And I looked to the top, and... and there was
the sun. I did not move, for I decided if
and there was the sun. I did not move, for I
decided if the sun could witness the death
I did not move, for I decided if the sun could
witness the death of a child and not intervene,
the sun could witness the death of a child
and not intervene, then what was the point?
Of a child and not intervene, then what was
the point? Old man, as you probably know,
then what was the point? Old man, as you
probably know, the sun stayed in the sky that
old man, as you probably know, the
sun stayed in the sky that day.
The sun stayed in the sky that day.
It did not alter its perpetual
day. It did not alter
its perpetual course.
It did not alter its perpetual course.
And I died at the bottom of that
course. And I died at the
bottom of that pool.
And I died at the bottom of that pool.
For 14 minutes, I was clinically
pool. For 14 minutes, I was clinically
absent as your devoted wife
for 14 minutes, I was clinically absent
as your devoted wife tried to revive me.
Absent as your devoted wife tried to
revive me. >> At first I thought it was
tried to revive me. >> At first I thought
it was simply gratitude, Marla...
at first I thought it was simply gratitude,
Marla... gratitude for being saved.
Simply gratitude, Marla... gratitude for being
saved. But as time went on and the fire
gratitude for being saved. But as time went
on and the fire in my loins burned like a
but as time went on and the fire in my loins
burned like a thousand Roman candles, I knew
in my loins burned like a thousand Roman
candles, I knew that this feeling was something
thousand Roman candles, I knew that this
feeling was something greater, something pure.
That this feeling was something greater,
something pure. It was love, Marla.
Greater, something pure. It was
love, Marla. >> Oh, k. Roth...
It was love, Marla. >> Oh, k. Roth...
It was the only time in my
oh, k. Roth... >> It was the only time
in my life that I've ever been in
it was the only time in my life
that I've ever been in love.
Life that I've ever been in love.
Sure, I love mills, tacos, and
love. Sure, I love mills, tacos, and
some of the more popular actors,
sure, I love mills, tacos, and some of the more
popular actors, but my singular true love has
some of the more popular actors, but my
singular true love has always been you.
But my singular true love has always
been you. >> And you mine, k. Roth.
Always been you. >> And you mine, k. Roth.
It was only when she pressed
and you mine, k. Roth. >> It was only
when she pressed her lips to mine...
It was only when she pressed her lips
to mine... It was only when she... she
her lips to mine... It was only when she...
she shared her breath and there were
it was only when she... she shared her breath
and there were two mouths met that I was jarred
shared her breath and there were two mouths
met that I was jarred back into existence.
Two mouths met that I was jarred back into
existence. And it is that single breath and
back into existence. And it is that single
breath and it is that single kiss that has
and it is that single breath and it is that
single kiss that has kept me alive until today.
It is that single kiss that has
kept me alive until today.
Kept me alive until today.
Huh?
Oh, Marla, you could make a
huh? >> Oh, Marla, you could
make a man forget his quest.
Oh, Marla, you could make a man forget his
quest. Now, this might be the schnapps
man forget his quest. Now, this might be
the schnapps barking, but I think that the
now, this might be the schnapps barking, but I
think that the answer rests on your soft lips,
barking, but I think that the answer rests on
your soft lips, and I long to know the answer.
Answer rests on your soft lips, and I long
to know the answer. >> Oh, kiss me, k. Roth.
Well, it seemed to go well.
I don't know if she got
well, it seemed to go well. >> I don't know
if she got anything out of it, but my goal
I don't know if she got anything out
of it, but my goal is complete.
Anything out of it, but my goal is
complete. Mills, I wonder if Hannibal felt
is complete. Mills, I wonder if
Hannibal felt this empty after taking
mills, I wonder if Hannibal felt
this empty after taking carthage.
This empty after taking carthage.
Although it was pleasant to
carthage. Although it was pleasant
to tongue-kiss my former nanny.
Although it was pleasant to tongue-kiss
my former nanny. Ah. Let's see.
Tongue-kiss my former nanny. Ah.
Let's see. Where to next?
Ah. Let's see. Where to next? Yes!
Mills, make haste to the
where to next? Yes! Mills,
make haste to the prostitute.
Yes! Mills, make haste to the prostitute.
My erection is strong, and I
prostitute. My erection is strong, and
I wish to celebrate my manhood two
my erection is strong, and I wish to celebrate
my manhood two or three final times.
Wish to celebrate my manhood two
or three final times.
Or three final times.
Oh, my darling.
You have done a dying man good.
Oh, my darling. You have done a dying
man good. Mills, get her an invitation.
You have done a dying man good. Mills, get her
an invitation. Now, don't forget to stop by
mills, get her an invitation. Now, don't
forget to stop by later for the wake.
Now, don't forget to stop by later
for the wake. It should be a riot.
Later for the wake. It should be a riot.
Hey, maybe in the next life, you
it should be a riot. Hey, maybe in the
next life, you and I could be husband and
hey, maybe in the next life, you and I could be
husband and wife... you know, take the money
and I could be husband and wife... you
know, take the money out of the equation.
Wife... you know, take the money out of
the equation. >> It's $50 extra for your
out of the equation. >> It's
$50 extra for your friend.
It's $50 extra for your friend.
What, mills?
Friend. >> What, mills? >>
It's $50 extra if somebody
what, mills? >> It's $50
extra if somebody watches.
It's $50 extra if somebody watches.
Okay.
Watches. >> Okay. I think
you've misunderstood the.
Okay. I think you've misunderstood
the situation, my love.
I think you've misunderstood the
situation, my love. Uh, this is mills.
Situation, my love. Uh, this is mills.
He is my man, my chauffeur, my
uh, this is mills. He is my man,
my chauffeur, my biographer.
He is my man, my chauffeur, my biographer.
He was not here to watch as much
biographer. He was not here to watch
as much as he was here to record what
he was not here to watch as much as
he was here to record what happened.
As he was here to record
what happened. See?
Happened. See? >> I
don't think you need
see? >> I don't think you
need another problem in here.
I don't think you need another problem in
here. >> Now you're escalating it to a
another problem in here. >> Now you're
escalating it to a hilltop it need not reach.
Now you're escalating it to a hilltop it
need not reach. >> Just give me my 50 bucks.
Hilltop it need not reach. >> Just
give me my 50 bucks. >> I will not.
Just give me my 50 bucks. >> I will not.
Besides, mills abhors sex!
I will not. Besides, mills abhors sex!
He would rather watch
besides, mills abhors sex! He would rather
watch "Lawrence Welk" than you and I
he would rather watch "Lawrence
Welk" than you and I going at it.
"Lawrence Welk" than you and I going at it.
It would be like paying $50 for
going at it. It would be like paying
$50 for having him not watch.
It would be like paying $50 for having him
not watch. >> Call it whatever you want...
Having him not watch. >> Call it whatever
you want... After you give me the $50.
Call it whatever you want... After you
give me the $50. Or I'll call my pimp!
After you give me the $50. Or I'll
call my pimp! >> All right, all right.
Or I'll call my pimp! >> All right, all
right. I only have the appropriate
all right, all right. I only have the
appropriate amount for the hour on my
I only have the appropriate
amount for the hour on my person.
Amount for the hour on my person.
Luckily, I do have my checkbook
person. Luckily, I do have my
checkbook down in the rickshaw.
Luckily, I do have my checkbook down in
the rickshaw. If you'll just excuse me...
Would you like to see my baby bird?
Look.
- Bird?
- Look.
Halfway through the day, mills.
Feeling good.
Mills. Feeling good. If
things keep going as well as
feeling good. If things keep going as
well as they have been, I should be able
if things keep going as well as they have been, I
should be able to secure the brief but powerful
they have been, I should be able to secure the
brief but powerful monologue with a few hours to
to secure the brief but powerful
monologue with a few hours to spare.
Monologue with a few hours to
spare.
Hello, binew! >> Reginald.
Prepare for battle!
Reginald. >> Prepare for battle!
Not now, Reginald.
Prepare for battle! >> Not now, Reginald.
I'm very busy.
Not now, Reginald. I'm very busy.
There is no convenient time
I'm very busy. >> There is
no convenient time for war!
There is no convenient time for war!
Prepare first wave!
For war! Prepare first wave!
What does he mean by that?
Prepare first wave! >> What does
he mean by that? >> Smokescreen!
What does he mean by that? >> Smokescreen!
The smoke is a metaphor for your
smokescreen! The smoke is a metaphor
for your inability to clearly see
the smoke is a metaphor for your
inability to clearly see reality!
Inability to clearly see reality!
Smokescreen, mills!
Reality! >> Smokescreen, mills!
Maintain your course!
Smokescreen, mills! Maintain your course!
It will pass.
Maintain your course! It will pass.
Prepare second wave!
It will pass. >> Prepare second wave!
Rusty nails!
Prepare second wave! Rusty nails!
Your ideas, binew, are like
rusty nails! Your ideas,
binew, are like rusty nails...
Your ideas, binew, are like rusty nails...
Rusty nails, mills.
Rusty nails... >> Rusty nails, mills.
...Spreading disease through
rusty nails, mills. >> ...Spreading
disease through the foot of the world!
Spreading disease through the foot of
the world! >> You know what to do.
The foot of the world! >> You
know what to do. >> Third wave!
You know what to do. >> Third wave!
This is because it's just
third wave! This is because it's
just disgusting to throw ham steaks
this is because it's just disgusting to
throw ham steaks at another human being!
Disgusting to throw ham steaks at
another human being! Ham steaks!
At another human being! Ham steaks!
Oh, no.
Ham steaks! >> Oh, no. >> What?
Oh, no. >> What? >> Ham steaks.
What? >> Ham steaks.
Take evasive action!
Ham steaks. Take evasive action!
Ha!
Take evasive action! >> Ha!
Oh, my God! Oh!
Ha! >> Oh, my God! Oh! >> Aah!
Oh, my God! Oh! >> Aah!
This is disgusting!
Aah! >> This is disgusting!
I've won this one, binew.
This is disgusting! >> I've won this
one, binew. >> Stay on the road, mills.
I've won this one, binew. >> Stay on the
road, mills. Watch out for the ditch!
- Stay on the road, mills.
- Watch out for the ditch!
- He knows all of my weaknesses,
He knows all of my weaknesses,
mills, but he is going to pay
he knows all of my weaknesses, mills, but he is
going to pay for this... In the strangest of
mills, but he is going to pay for this...
In the strangest of ways.
Librarian, we only have time for a brief
ceremony, so please smile continuously.
A brief ceremony, so please smile
continuously. It is my sincere honor to be
smile continuously. It is my
sincere honor to be here at the...
it is my sincere honor to
be here at the... >> shh!
Here at the... >> shh! >> The...
Shh! >> The... >>
The public library.
The... >> The public library.
The public library to donate
the public library. >> The public
library to donate my complete works.
The public library to donate my complete
works. Let us go through the canon.
My complete works. Let us go through
the canon. We start where I did, with
let us go through the canon. We start where I
did, with "why could it not have been me?"
We start where I did, with "why could it not
have been me?" Which has been hailed as the
"why could it not have been me?" Which has
been hailed as the most comprehensive list of
which has been hailed as the most comprehensive
list of losing lottery numbers ever
most comprehensive list of losing
lottery numbers ever compiled.
Losing lottery numbers ever compiled.
No, no, sir...
compiled. >> No, no, sir... >> ah!
"What's your problem?"...
- No, no, sir...
- >> ah! "What's your problem?"...
- Ah! "What's your problem?"...
- >> Aah!
Aah!
...The definitive collection
aah! >> ...The definitive collection
of word problems that I wrote
the definitive collection of word problems
that I wrote during my illustrious career in
of word problems that I wrote during my
illustrious career in that industry.
During my illustrious career in that
industry. "Remembrance of dawn."
- That industry.
- "Remembrance of dawn."
"Remembrance of dawn."
"Too fat to be a jockey."
And "Jack's pants."
I donate all of these to this
hallowed institution, asking
I donate all of these to this hallowed institution,
asking only that once a year, somebody
hallowed institution, asking only that once a
year, somebody visits them with a duster...
only that once a year, somebody visits them
with a duster... unless they're being read, of
visits them with a duster... unless
they're being read, of course.
Unless they're being read, of course.
In that case, let them be.
Course. In that case, let them be.
I am sorry, sir, but there is
in that case, let them be. >> I am sorry, sir,
but there is a protocol for donating books.
I am sorry, sir, but there is a protocol for
donating books. We don't just slap a number on
a protocol for donating books. We don't just
slap a number on them and shove them on the
we don't just slap a number on them
and shove them on the shelves.
Them and shove them on the shelves.
Well, then, let's put these
shelves. >> Well, then, let's put
these books through the old protocol.
Well, then, let's put these books through the
old protocol. Quickly, though... quickly.
Books through the old protocol. Quickly, though...
quickly. >> The problem with the general
quickly, though... quickly. >> The problem
with the general public, sir, is that they
the problem with the general public, sir,
is that they completely underestimate the
public, sir, is that they completely
underestimate the difficulty and scope of a
completely underestimate the difficulty
and scope of a librarian's job.
Difficulty and scope of a
librarian's job.
- Librarian's job.
- >> The one thing that does not.
The one thing that does not
fall under my jurisdiction is
the one thing that does not fall under my
jurisdiction is the choosing of books.
Fall under my jurisdiction is the choosing
of books. That's done by the board, and
the choosing of books. That's done by the
board, and the process takes months.
That's done by the board, and the
process takes months. >> Months?
The process takes months. >> Months?
This is a public library,
months? >> This is a
public library, sir.
This is a public library, sir.
Are you going to leave it to the
sir. Are you going to leave it to
the public to choose what they're
are you going to leave it to the public
to choose what they're going to read?
Public to choose what they're
going to read?
Going to read?
This place would be brimming.
This place would be brimming
with pornography and gun
this place would be brimming with
pornography and gun magazines.
With pornography and gun magazines.
The board chooses everything.
Magazines. The board chooses everything.
Oh, you are right, librarian.
The board chooses everything. >> Oh, you are
right, librarian. I was a fool to think I could
oh, you are right, librarian. I was a fool
to think I could simply saunter in here and
I was a fool to think I could simply
saunter in here and donate my books.
Simply saunter in here and
donate my books.
- Donate my books.
- I'm sorry to waste your
I'm sorry to waste your
important librarian time.
I'm sorry to waste your important
librarian time. Good day, madame.
Important librarian time.
Good day, madame. >> Yes.
Good day, madame. >> Yes. Um...
Yes. Um... Do you have
any information on.
Um... Do you have any information
on the Pennsylvania Dutch?
Do you have any information on the Pennsylvania
Dutch? >> Let me check the catalog.
The Pennsylvania Dutch? >> Let me
check the catalog. >> No, no, no.
Let me check the catalog. >> No, no, no.
I mean... I mean you.
No, no, no. I mean... I mean you.
Do you... you personally have
I mean... I mean you. Do you... you
personally have any information on the
do you... you personally have any
information on the Pennsylvania Dutch?
Any information on the Pennsylvania Dutch?
Uh, well, I believe they are
Pennsylvania Dutch? >> Uh, well, I believe
they are known for their fine furniture
uh, well, I believe they are known for their
fine furniture and their, uh, homemade
known for their fine furniture and
their, uh, homemade biscuits.
And their, uh, homemade biscuits.
Yes, yes.
Biscuits. >> Yes, yes.
That's pretty good.
Yes, yes. That's pretty good.
You'd think with all these
that's pretty good. You'd think with all
these reference materials everywhere,
you'd think with all these reference materials
everywhere, you wouldn't go through the
reference materials everywhere, you wouldn't
go through the trouble of keeping anything in
you wouldn't go through the trouble
of keeping anything in your brain.
Trouble of keeping anything in your brain.
Ah, well...
Your brain. >> Ah, well...
Where do you keep the
ah, well... >> Where do
you keep the microfiche?
Where do you keep the microfiche?
In the basement.
Microfiche? >> In the basement.
I wish you kept it at the
in the basement. >> I wish
you kept it at the dump.
I wish you kept it at the dump.
I hate microfiche.
Dump. I hate microfiche.
"B," "b," "b"...
I hate microfiche. >> "B," "b," "b"...
"b-I," "b-I, "b-I"...
"B," "b," "b"... "b-I," "b-I, "b-I"...
"Binew."
"B-I," "b-I, "b-I"...
"Binew." Ah.
"Binew." Ah. >> I just
hate anything that has
ah. >> I just hate anything
that has been miniaturized.
I just hate anything that has been
miniaturized. That's really the main problem I
been miniaturized. That's really the
main problem I have with fiche.
That's really the main problem
I have with fiche. >> Hmm.
Have with fiche. >> Hmm. >>
Your bathroom is clean and
hmm. >> Your bathroom is
clean and comfortable.
Your bathroom is clean and comfortable.
Give my regards to the library
comfortable. Give my regards
to the library maid.
Give my regards to the library maid.
Mills?
- Maid.
- Mills?
Mills?
Sir, get a picture?
Please!
- Sir, get a picture?
- >> Please!
Please!
Yes, and another.
Look proud.
- Yes, and another.
- Look proud.
- >> Yeah, we got it.
Yeah, we got it
in there.
Yeah, we got it in there. We
got them in there, mills.
In there. We got them in there, mills.
We got them in...
- we got them in there, mills.
- We got them in...
- I told you that we cannot accept
I told you that we cannot accept
books that have not been read
I told you that we cannot accept books that
have not been read and approved by the board.
Books that have not been read and approved by
the board. >> Who are these people that get
and approved by the board. >> Who are these
people that get to choose what people read?
Who are these people that get to choose what
people read? >> I don't make the rules, sir.
To choose what people read? >> I don't make the
rules, sir. >> Are they the cousins of the
I don't make the rules, sir. >> Are they the
cousins of the man who gets to choose what's
are they the cousins of the man who gets to
choose what's going to be on the top 40?
Man who gets to choose what's going to
be on the top 40? >> I'm sorry, sir.
Going to be on the top 40? >> I'm sorry,
sir. >> Are they the godchildren of
I'm sorry, sir. >> Are they the godchildren
of the person in charge of choosing
are they the godchildren of the person in
charge of choosing what colors we wear every
the person in charge of choosing
what colors we wear every season?
What colors we wear every season?
You don't make a single
season? >> You don't make a single
goddamn decision in this life if
you don't make a single goddamn decision in
this life if the options are always given to
goddamn decision in this life if the options
are always given to you by somebody else.
The options are always given to you by
somebody else. Don't you see, librarian?
You by somebody else. Don't you see,
librarian? You have the power in your hands
don't you see, librarian? You have the power
in your hands to give the people something
you have the power in your hands to give the
people something real, something that has not
to give the people something real, something
that has not been presorted or processed or
real, something that has not been presorted
or processed or edited beyond recognition!
Been presorted or processed or edited
beyond recognition! >> Sir, you have got to
edited beyond recognition! >> Sir,
you have got to understand...
sir, you have got to understand...
maybe the books are a little
understand... >> maybe the books are a
little rough, but maybe that's what the
maybe the books are a little rough, but maybe
that's what the people need to stir them.
Rough, but maybe that's what the
people need to stir them. Come on.
People need to stir them. Come on.
Flex your muscle and abuse your
come on. Flex your muscle
and abuse your power!
Flex your muscle and abuse your power!
I can't
power! >> I can't
take the books, sir.
I can't take the books, sir.
Fine, librarian. You win.
Take the books, sir. >> Fine, librarian.
You win. I will take my books away from
fine, librarian. You win. I will take my books
away from here, towards some dark future,
I will take my books away from here, towards
some dark future, where they will kick around on
here, towards some dark future, where they will
kick around on the thrift-store circuit and
where they will kick around on the thrift-store
circuit and finally end up in the garbage.
The thrift-store circuit and finally end up
in the garbage. >> Well, I am sorry, sir, but
finally end up in the garbage. >> Well, I
am sorry, sir, but the rules are the rules.
No, no. No, no, no. You must
not listen to her, sir.
No, no, no. You must not listen
to her, sir. She knows nothing.
You must not listen to her, sir. She knows
nothing. Read to me from one... one of
she knows nothing. Read to me from one...
one of your children's stories, in...
read to me from one... one of your children's
stories, in... in your biggest voice.
Your children's stories, in... in your
biggest voice. When you were making your
in your biggest voice. When you were making
your schedule, it was something I was
when you were making your schedule, it was
something I was going to request, but I didn't
schedule, it was something I was going
to request, but I didn't want to impose.
Going to request, but I didn't want to
impose. >> Well, I suppose better for
want to impose. >> Well, I suppose
better for one than for none.
Well, I suppose better for one
than for none. All right.
One than for none. All right.
"Jack's pants."
All right. "Jack's pants."
Wait a minute.
"Jack's pants." >> Wait a minute.
I am going to get my blanket.
Perfect.
Okay. Now, ready? >> Yes.
"Jack's pants."
Yes. >> "Jack's pants." >> By k.
Roth binew.
"Jack's pants." >> By k. Roth binew.
Right. By k. Roth binew.
"Once there was a little orphan boy who was
very, very sad. We will call him Jack."
Boy who was very, very sad. We
will call him Jack." >> "Jack."
We will call him Jack." >> "Jack."
"And Jack was utterly and.
"Jack." >> "And Jack was
utterly and completely alone.
"And Jack was utterly and completely alone.
One day, while searching for"
completely alone. One day, while searching
for food and friends in a nearby
one day, while searching for food and friends
in a nearby dumpster, he came across a
food and friends in a nearby dumpster, he came
across a brand-new, perfect pair of plum,
"dumpster, he came across a brand-new,
perfect pair of plum, corduroy pants."
Brand-new, perfect pair of plum, corduroy
pants." >> "Of plum, corduroy pants."
Corduroy pants." >> "Of plum, corduroy
pants." >> "These pants and this boy
"of plum, corduroy pants." >> "These pants
and this boy were quick to become friends.
"These pants and this boy were quick to become
friends. They would go everywhere, the"
were quick to become friends. They would
go everywhere, the pants and Jack.
They would go everywhere, the pants and
Jack. And Jack vowed to always wear
pants and Jack. And Jack vowed to always
wear the pants, and the pants vowed
and Jack vowed to always wear the pants, and
the pants vowed to always be pants for Jack.
The pants, and the pants vowed to always be pants
for Jack. But Jack grew up, as little boys
to always be pants for Jack. But Jack grew up,
as little boys do, and the pants did not keep
but Jack grew up, as little boys do, and the
pants did not keep their promise, for as Jack's
do, and the pants did not keep their promise,
for as Jack's legs grew long, the pants grew
their promise, for as Jack's legs grew long,
the pants grew short, until his perfect, plum,
legs grew long, the pants grew short, until his
perfect, plum, corduroy companion burst at the
short, until his perfect, plum,
corduroy companion burst at the seams.
Corduroy companion burst at the seams.
Not only had Jack been betrayed
seams. Not only had Jack been betrayed
by his best and only friend, but
not only had Jack been betrayed by his best and
only friend, but as the last stitch came undone,
by his best and only friend, but as the last stitch
came undone, Jack found himself naked in the
as the last stitch came undone, Jack
found himself naked in the town square.
Jack found himself naked in the town
square. He was quickly picked up for
town square. He was quickly picked
up for public indecency and was
he was quickly picked up for public indecency
and was sentenced to three years of hard
public indecency and was sentenced
to three years of hard time.
Sentenced to three years of hard time.
But prison life did not agree
time. But prison life did not agree
with Jack, and so one night, he
but prison life did not agree with Jack, and
so one night, he hanged himself with his new
"with Jack, and so one night, he hanged himself
with his new friend, prison-issue sock."
That was wonderful, sir. Wonderful.
I-I don't know.
Wonderful. >> I-I don't know.
You really have to pick your.
I-I don't know. You really
have to pick your genre.
You really have to pick your genre.
It... it starts out as a-an
genre. It... it starts out as
a-an intriguing and playful
it... it starts out as a-an intriguing
and playful children's story but then
intriguing and playful children's story
but then quickly descends into a highly
children's story but then quickly descends
into a highly critical exposé on our current
quickly descends into a highly critical
exposé on our current penal system.
Critical exposé on our current penal
system. It'll scare the children and
penal system. It'll scare the
children and upset the adults.
It'll scare the children and upset the
adults. As a member of the board that
upset the adults. As a member of the
board that chooses the books for this
as a member of the board that chooses the
books for this library, I disapprove.
Well that is that.
It has been made brazenly clear.
It has been made brazenly clear
I am a failure!
It has been made brazenly clear I am a
failure! >> No, no, no, there is still
I am a failure! >> No, no, no,
there is still hope, sir.
No, no, no, there is still hope, sir.
One other person heard your
hope, sir. One other
person heard your story.
One other person heard your story.
Miss, what did you think?
Story.
Why did she beat me so?
If you didn't bite her, I don't
why did she beat me so? If you didn't bite
her, I don't think I would have gotten out of
if you didn't bite her, I don't think I
would have gotten out of there alive.
Think I would have gotten out of there
alive. >> She tasted quite good, sir.
There alive. >> She tasted quite good, sir.
Oh, I have suffered two blows
she tasted quite good, sir. >> Oh, I have
suffered two blows today, one literary and one
oh, I have suffered two blows today,
one literary and one physical.
Today, one literary and one physical.
I don't know which one hurts
physical. I don't know
which one hurts more.
I don't know which one hurts more.
Ow. Ow!
More. Ow. Ow! Oh, and
it's too much for me to
ow. Ow! Oh, and it's too much for
me to bear, going into the void
oh, and it's too much for me to bear, going
into the void without the answer and unsure of
bear, going into the void without the
answer and unsure of my literary standing.
Without the answer and unsure of my literary
standing. >> No, sir, dying can only help
my literary standing. >> No, sir,
dying can only help your cause.
No, sir, dying can only help your cause.
Think of... of kafka, van gogh,
your cause. Think of... of kafka,
van gogh, Emily Dickinson.
Think of... of kafka, van gogh, Emily
Dickinson. >> Your reassurances are not
Emily Dickinson. >> Your
reassurances are not enough.
Your reassurances are not enough.
I must know before I die.
What do they say? What could the future
possibly hold for this poor, old sod?
What could the future possibly hold for this
poor, old sod? Who, if any, will remember him?
Hold for this poor, old sod? Who, if any, will
remember him? Will he, before the sun sets,
who, if any, will remember him? Will he, before
the sun sets, secure the answer that has
will he, before the sun sets, secure
the answer that has eluded him so?
Secure the answer that has eluded him so?
You will experience a great
eluded him so? >> You will
experience a great loss soon.
You will experience a great loss soon.
My body.
Loss soon. >> My body. >>
Fear not, for this will pass.
My body. >> Fear not, for this will pass.
I always thought it would be
fear not, for this will pass. >> I always
thought it would be more of a permanent thing.
I always thought it would be more of a permanent
thing. >> When this time of darkness is
more of a permanent thing. >> When this time
of darkness is through, your soul will soar to
when this time of darkness is through, your
soul will soar to new heights, as if a great
through, your soul will soar to new heights,
as if a great weight has been lifted.
New heights, as if a great weight has been
lifted. And it was that weight that has
weight has been lifted. And it was
that weight that has stifled you so.
And it was that weight that has stifled
you so. >> With my body no longer, I
stifled you so. >> With my body no
longer, I will be judged by word alone.
With my body no longer, I will be judged by
word alone. Mills, my place in history is
will be judged by word alone. Mills,
my place in history is secure.
Mills, my place in history is secure.
Hush!
Secure. >> Hush! >> I'm
sorry, but your speak is
hush! >> I'm sorry, but your speak
is so cryptic, I must interpret it
I'm sorry, but your speak is so
cryptic, I must interpret it aloud.
So cryptic, I must interpret it aloud.
Please, go on.
Aloud. Please, go on. >>
You will be remembered by
please, go on. >> You will be remembered
by many for your kindness, your
you will be remembered by many for your
kindness, your loyalty, and your patience.
Many for your kindness, your loyalty, and your
patience. >> That doesn't sound like you,
loyalty, and your patience. >>
That doesn't sound like you, sir.
Not at all.
Sir. >> Not at all. >>
For your work with the
not at all. >> For your work with
the elderly, you will be generously
for your work with the elderly,
you will be generously rewarded.
Elderly, you will be generously rewarded.
The elderly, sir?
Rewarded. >> The elderly, sir?
I will not listen to this
the elderly, sir? >> I will
not listen to this drivel!
I will not listen to this drivel!
Tell me now, psychic!
Drivel! Tell me now, psychic!
What is the brief but powerful
tell me now, psychic! What is the
brief but powerful monologue?
What is the brief but powerful monologue?
I am doing his cards!
Monologue? >> I am doing his cards!
Really?
I am doing his cards!
Really? >> Yes.
Really? >> Yes. As a
matter of fact, you're
yes. As a matter of fact, you're
going to do quite well for
as a matter of fact, you're going
to do quite well for yourself.
Going to do quite well for yourself.
What about my cards?
Yourself. >> What about my cards?
Your cards?
What about my cards? >> Your cards?
Are you sure you want me to
your cards? Are you sure you
want me to read your cards?
Are you sure you want me to read your
cards? >> Why do you think I've come
read your cards? >> Why do you
think I've come here, psychic?
Why do you think I've come here, psychic?
Fine, then.
Here, psychic? >> Fine, then.
You're next.
Flip that card again.
That organ means I'm doomed,
huh?
That organ means I'm doomed, huh?
The card means you're doomed.
Huh? >> The card means you're doomed.
The organ's for effect.
The card means you're doomed. The
organ's for effect. >> That was a bust.
The organ's for effect. >> That was a bust.
12 bucks, and she tells me what
that was a bust. 12 bucks, and she
tells me what I already know.
12 bucks, and she tells me what I
already know. I have been hosed, mills.
I already know. I have been hosed, mills.
No, not really, sir.
I have been hosed, mills. >> No, not
really, sir. You also get the story of the
no, not really, sir. You also
get the story of the thing.
You also get the story of the thing.
Why do you think I paid $100 for
thing. Why do you think I paid $100
for a watch that always breaks?
Why do you think I paid $100 for a watch that
always breaks? >> I really don't know, mills.
A watch that always breaks? >> I really don't
know, mills. >> Because it was being sold to
I really don't know, mills. >> Because it
was being sold to me by a legless man named
because it was being sold to me by
a legless man named grimelhausen.
Me by a legless man named grimelhausen.
What are you talking about?!
Grimelhausen. >> What are you talking
about?! Ridiculosity will not be
what are you talking about?!
Ridiculosity will not be tolerated.
No, I paid $5 for the watch
tolerated. >> No, I paid $5 for the
watch and $95 for the story of buying
no, I paid $5 for the watch and $95 for the
story of buying the watch from a legless man
and $95 for the story of buying the watch
from a legless man named grimelhausen.
The watch from a legless man named
grimelhausen. >> That's an awful lot to pay
named grimelhausen. >> That's an awful
lot to pay for an idiotic story.
That's an awful lot to pay for an
idiotic story. >> Oh, not really, sir.
For an idiotic story. >> Oh, not
really, sir. It kills at parties.
Oh, not really, sir. It kills at parties.
Not going so well at this
it kills at parties. >> Not
going so well at this one.
Not going so well at this one.
Are you sure?
One. >> Are you sure?
You'll be dead soon.
Are you sure? You'll be dead soon.
Biographer, kill yourself in
you'll be dead soon. >> Biographer, kill
yourself in childhood, the victim of a
biographer, kill yourself in childhood, the
victim of a mining accident, at least until
childhood, the victim of a mining accident,
at least until you apologize for that joke.
Mining accident, at least until you apologize
for that joke. When you do, have yourself
you apologize for that joke. When you do,
have yourself killed two years later by
when you do, have yourself killed
two years later by sharks.
Killed two years later by sharks.
Did you just say that your watch
sharks. Did you just say that
your watch always breaks?
Did you just say that your watch
always breaks? >> Constantly.
Always breaks? >> Constantly.
Is it broken now?
Constantly. >> Is it broken now?
Why, yes, it is.
A snail is more swift, mills! Faster!
Faster! >> I'm trying, sir.
Faster! Faster!
I'm trying, sir.
Come on, man!
But this is no small setback,
come on, man! But this is
no small setback, mills.
But this is no small setback, mills.
How am I supposed to get
mills. How am I supposed
to get everything done?
How am I supposed to get everything done?
This has no hands.
Everything done? This has no hands.
And this has no gears.
This has no hands. And this has no gears.
Oh, mills...
And this has no gears. Oh, mills...
What?
Oh, mills...
It is 9:30. I...
I've been dead two hours.
It is 9:30. I... I've been dead two hours.
No, no, no, no, sir.
I've been dead two hours. >> No,
no, no, no, sir. It is 1:30.
No, no, no, no, sir. It is 1:30.
We're hours ahead of schedule.
It is 1:30. We're hours ahead of schedule.
They're all different!
We're hours ahead of schedule. >> They're
all different! Which one is right?!
They're all different! Which one is right?!
Perhaps we should trust this
which one is right?! >> Perhaps
we should trust this one, sir.
Perhaps we should trust this one, sir.
It is gold.
One, sir. It is gold. >> But
that is madness, mills!
It is gold. >> But that is madness, mills!
You, man... what time is it?
But that is madness, mills! You, man... what
time is it? >> You have to buy a watch to
you, man... what time is it? >> You
have to buy a watch to get the time.
You have to buy a watch to get the time.
I refuse.
Get the time. >> I refuse. If
I'm forced to live within the
I refuse. If I'm forced to live within
the confines of time, the least you
if I'm forced to live within the confines of time,
the least you could do is give me the hour and
confines of time, the least you could do is give
me the hour and minute we are in free of charge!
Could do is give me the hour and minute we are in
free of charge! >> Time is my business, and time
minute we are in free of charge! >> Time is my
business, and time being my business, I must charge
time is my business, and time being
my business, I must charge for time.
Being my business, I must charge for time.
Oh, you are an impudent
for time. >> Oh, you are
an impudent clockmaker.
Oh, you are an impudent clockmaker.
But I concede to your idiocy.
Clockmaker. But I concede to your idiocy.
Mills, pay the man.
But I concede to your idiocy. Mills,
pay the man. What watch will that buy?
Mills, pay the man. What watch will
that buy? >> That's not enough for a
what watch will that buy? >> That's
not enough for a proper watch.
That's not enough for a proper watch.
But for that price, I will sell
proper watch. But for that
price, I will sell you the time.
But for that price, I will sell you
the time. >> Well, let's complete the
you the time. >> Well, let's
complete the transaction, man.
Well, let's complete the transaction, man.
With the amount you gave me,
transaction, man. >> With the amount you
gave me, I can only give you the time
with the amount you gave me, I
can only give you the time once.
I can only give you the time once.
For the love of all that is
once. >> For the love of all that
is sacred, give me the watch!
For the love of all that is sacred,
give me the watch! Oh, mills...
Sacred, give me the watch!
Oh, mills... >> What?
It is 3:30.
What? >> It is 3:30.
Four hours left.
It is 3:30. Four hours left.
I-I hoped I had more time.
Four hours left. I-I hoped I had more time.
Here I am, so far from the.
I-I hoped I had more time. Here
I am, so far from the answer.
Here I am, so far from the answer.
Give me the watch!
Answer. >> Give me the watch!
So much time, but so little
give me the watch! >> So much
time, but so little time.
So much time, but so little time.
Sir...
time. >> Sir... >> the
irony is too thick to
sir... >> the irony is
too thick to ignore.
The irony is too thick to ignore.
Stop that, sir!
Ignore. >> Stop that, sir!
Your list!
Stop that, sir! Your list! >>
There's no point in having a
your list! >> There's no point in
having a list if there is no time to
there's no point in having a list
if there is no time to complete it.
List if there is no time to complete it.
It is a wonder that people get
complete it. It is a wonder that
people get anything done at all.
It is a wonder that people get anything
done at all. Besides, I-I'm feeling a bit
anything done at all. Besides, I-I'm
feeling a bit woozy and would like some...
Besides, I-I'm feeling a bit woozy and would
like some... >> What's the matter with your
woozy and would like some... >>
What's the matter with your friend?
...More time!
Father, I have fallen slightly behind.
Please, please, I have not done
behind. Please, please, I have
not done much cardio lately.
Please, please, I have not done
much cardio lately. I am weak.
Much cardio lately. I am weak. I
cannot keep up with your brisk
I am weak. I cannot keep
up with your brisk pace.
I cannot keep up with your brisk pace.
Father...
Pace. Father... Whoa.
Father... Whoa. Demon.
Whoa. Demon. Must be
the road to Hades.
Demon. Must be the road to Hades.
Oh. Oh, the bullies from my
must be the road to Hades. Oh. Oh,
the bullies from my life, together.
Oh. Oh, the bullies from my life, together.
This must be the end.
Life, together. This must be the end.
All of the women I've had sex
this must be the end. All of
the women I've had sex with.
All of the women I've had sex with.
Mother, what are you doing here?
With. Mother, what are you doing here?
And Roy?!
Mother, what are you doing here? And Roy?!
It's a good thing there's a
and Roy?! It's a good thing
there's a recap at the end.
It's a good thing there's a recap at the
end. I barely remember any of this.
Recap at the end.
I barely remember any of this.
Oh! Thank God, mills.
Mills, I desperately need a
oh! Thank God, mills. Mills,
I desperately need a ride.
Mills, I desperately need a ride.
Mills, just up to the finish
ride. Mills, just up
to the finish line.
Mills, just up to the finish line.
That's not my finish line.
Line. >> That's not my finish line.
That's your finish line.
That's not my finish line. That's your finish
line. >> I've won this one, binew, for
that's your finish line. >> I've won
this one, binew, for all of eternity.
I've won this one, binew, for
all of eternity.
All of eternity.
All those sinners repent. All ye who seek
salvation, cometh unto the lord, for the
all ye who seek salvation, cometh unto
the lord, for the lord is your savior.
Cometh unto the lord, for the lord
is your savior. So spoke Christ.
- Lord is your savior.
- So spoke Christ.
- >> The light...
The light...
So bright...
the light... So bright...
much brighter than before.
So bright... much brighter than before.
That's it.
Much brighter than before.
That's it. I'm... Dead?
Well, that wasn't so bad.
I'm... Dead? Well, that
wasn't so bad. Mills!
Well, that wasn't so bad.
Mills! >> Yes?
Mills! >> Yes? >>
How did you die?
Yes? >> How did you die?
I didn't.
How did you die? >> I didn't.
But I'm dead.
I didn't. >> But I'm dead.
No, you're not, sir.
But I'm dead. >> No, you're not, sir.
Well, then, what was that
no, you're not, sir. >> Well, then,
what was that heavenly voice?
Well, then, what was that heavenly voice?
Over there, sir.
Heavenly voice? >> Over there, sir.
They're making some sort of
over there, sir. They're making
some sort of presentation.
"Come unto me, all ye who"
labour and are heavy laden, and
I will give you rest, for my
yoke is easy and my burden
"light."
So spoke Christ! >> So, I'm alive?
Yes.
- So, I'm alive?
- >> Yes.
- Yes.
- I am still alive!
I am still alive!
- You are alive.
You are alive.
I am alive.
You are alive. I am alive.
We are all alive!
I am alive.
Yes, my brother!
By the grace of God, we are all
yes, my brother! By the grace
of God, we are all alive!
By the grace of God, we are all alive!
Do you really think it's
alive! >> Do you really
think it's God's fault?
Do you really think it's God's fault?
He is infinitely charitable.
God's fault? >> He is infinitely
charitable. >> To everyone?
He is infinitely charitable. >> To
everyone? >> God embraces us all as his
to everyone? >> God embraces
us all as his children.
God embraces us all as his children.
Oh, yes, but some would say
children. >> Oh, yes, but some would
say that I've been a bad man.
Oh, yes, but some would say that I've been
a bad man. >> You only need to accept God
that I've been a bad man. >> You only need
to accept God into your heart, and he will
you only need to accept God into your heart,
and he will forgive you of whatever mistakes
into your heart, and he will forgive you of
whatever mistakes you have made in this life.
Forgive you of whatever mistakes you have
made in this life. >> Come on. All of them?
You have made in this life. >> Come on.
All of them? >> All of them.
Come on. All of them? >> All of them.
Well, he seems very powerful.
All of them. >> Well, he seems very
powerful. What are the rules again?
Well, he seems very powerful. What are
the rules again? Love thy brother!
What are the rules again? Love thy brother!
But I hate my brother, and he.
Love thy brother! >> But I hate
my brother, and he hates me.
But I hate my brother, and he hates me.
Forgive him, as God does.
Hates me. >> Forgive him, as God does.
Go now.
Forgive him, as God does. >> Go now.
Stand before your brother, for
go now. Stand before your brother,
for with God's love, all quarrels
stand before your brother, for with God's
love, all quarrels may be resolved.
With God's love, all quarrels
may be resolved. >> Hmm.
My father was a fool, mills, for raising
me on the religion of the ancient greeks.
Raising me on the religion of the ancient
greeks. I feel terrible about that goat.
The ancient greeks. I feel terrible about
that goat. What did you name that goat,
I feel terrible about that goat.
What did you name that goat, mills?
Zazimo, sir.
Mills? >> Zazimo, sir. >> I
feel terrible about zazimo.
Zazimo, sir. >> I feel terrible about
zazimo. But God forgives, and God knows
I feel terrible about zazimo. But God
forgives, and God knows I have a job to do.
But God forgives, and God knows I have a
job to do. Jesus Christ, this is a long
I have a job to do. Jesus Christ,
this is a long driveway.
Jesus Christ, this is a long driveway.
God damn it!
Driveway. God damn it!
Just broke a rule.
God damn it! Just broke a rule.
Aw, shit!
Just broke a rule. Aw, shit!
Mills, go ahead and flog me.
So, you see, they have this
book called "the Bible."
So, you see, they have this book called
"the Bible." It tells the story of a man
book called "the Bible." It tells the
story of a man named Jesus... a Mexican
it tells the story of a man named Jesus...
a Mexican gentleman, I presume.
Named Jesus... a Mexican gentleman, I
presume. I haven't read it yet, but they
gentleman, I presume. I haven't read it
yet, but they say it's very popular.
I haven't read it yet, but they say it's
very popular. >> Don't be a jackass.
Say it's very popular. >> Don't be a
jackass. Mother raised us both in the
don't be a jackass. Mother
raised us both in the church.
Mother raised us both in the church.
You were baptized.
Church. You were baptized. >>
Are you talking about that
you were baptized. >> Are you talking
about that robed man that tried to drown
are you talking about that robed
man that tried to drown me?
Robed man that tried to drown me?
What a fond repressed memory.
Me? What a fond repressed memory.
Anyhow, these christians... they
what a fond repressed memory. Anyhow, these
christians... they thought it would be a good idea
anyhow, these christians... they thought it would
be a good idea if I came by and made amends.
Thought it would be a good idea if I came by and
made amends. I also wanted to tell you that
if I came by and made amends. I also wanted to
tell you that I'll be dying in three hours.
I also wanted to tell you that I'll be
dying in three hours. >> Did you come here
I'll be dying in three hours. >> Did you
come here specifically to upset mother?
Did you come here specifically
to upset mother? >> Karl...
specifically to upset mother? >> Karl...
don't "Karl" me, Klaus.
Karl... >> don't "Karl" me, Klaus.
Don't "Klaus" me.
Don't "Karl" me, Klaus. >> Don't
"Klaus" me. It's "k. Roth."
Don't "Klaus" me. It's "k. Roth."
It has been so nice not
it's "k. Roth." >> It has been
so nice not having you here.
It has been so nice not having you here.
We haven't missed you at all.
Having you here. We haven't missed you
at all. >> No more animosity, Karl.
We haven't missed you at all. >> No more
animosity, Karl. It's all bourbon under the
no more animosity, Karl. It's all bourbon
under the bridge as far as I'm concerned.
It's all bourbon under the bridge as
far as I'm concerned. Hug me, Karl.
Bridge as far as I'm concerned. Hug me,
Karl. I won't be around much longer.
Hug me, Karl. I won't be around much
longer. >> You smell like shit.
I won't be around much longer. >> You smell
like shit. Is that blood on your neck?
You smell like shit. Is that
blood on your neck? >> Ah, yes.
Is that blood on your neck? >> Ah, yes.
I was beaten earlier.
Ah, yes. I was beaten earlier.
I passed out twice.
I was beaten earlier. I passed out twice.
Mills flogged me in the
I passed out twice. Mills
flogged me in the driveway.
Mills flogged me in the driveway.
The blood could be from any of
driveway. The blood could
be from any of those.
The blood could be from any of those.
But that is of no consequence.
Those. But that is of no consequence.
I simply wanted to come by to
but that is of no consequence. I simply
wanted to come by to say farewell.
I simply wanted to come by to say farewell.
I'm sorry that we didn't get
say farewell. I'm sorry that
we didn't get along better.
I'm sorry that we didn't get along better.
You're not dying.
Along better. >> You're not dying.
It's another one of your goddamn
you're not dying. It's another
one of your goddamn schemes.
It's another one of your goddamn schemes.
I am, Karl, and I wanted to
schemes. >> I am, Karl, and I wanted
to invite you and mother to the
I am, Karl, and I wanted to invite
you and mother to the wake.
Invite you and mother to the wake.
Mills?
Wake. Mills? >>
You're just like your
mills? >> You're just
like your father...
You're just like your father...
Thank you.
Father... >> Thank you.
...But crazier.
Thank you. >>...But crazier.
Mother...
but crazier. >> Mother... >>
you have embarrassed this
mother... >> you have
embarrassed this family.
You have embarrassed this family.
You are the town drunk and the
family. You are the town
drunk and the village idiot.
You are the town drunk and the village
idiot. You ride around with your mute
village idiot. You ride around with your
mute friend on that rickshaw, and you
you ride around with your mute friend on that
rickshaw, and you live in a men's hotel.
Friend on that rickshaw, and you live in a
men's hotel. When you were younger, I thought
live in a men's hotel. When you were younger,
I thought there was a possibility that
when you were younger, I thought there was
a possibility that you'd be all right.
There was a possibility that you'd be all
right. But what kind of life have you
you'd be all right. But what kind
of life have you made for yourself?
But what kind of life have you made for
yourself? I have worried too long about
made for yourself? I have worried too long
about you, Klaus, and I am tired now.
I have worried too long about you, Klaus,
and I am tired now. I'm very tired.
You, Klaus, and I am tired now. I'm
very tired. >> We're both very tired.
I'm very tired. >> We're both very tired.
Just thought I would try to
we're both very tired. >> Just thought I
would try to connect with you before I die.
Just thought I would try to connect with
you before I die. >> Stop saying that!
Connect with you before I die. >> Stop
saying that! >> You're not dying, just like
stop saying that! >> You're not dying,
just like you're not an artist and you're
you're not dying, just like you're not
an artist and you're not a writer.
You're not an artist and you're not
a writer. This is all in your head.
Not a writer. This is all in your head.
Well, there's no point in
this is all in your head. >> Well, there's
no point in trying to connect with you two.
Well, there's no point in trying to connect
with you two. You've had it out for me since
trying to connect with you two. You've had it
out for me since the beginning, and I can't
you've had it out for me since the
beginning, and I can't figure out why.
The beginning, and I can't figure out why.
If only father were here.
Figure out why. If only father were here.
He understood me.
If only father were here. He understood me.
You drove him away!
He understood me. >> You drove him away!
Why do you think he left you on
you drove him away! Why do you think
he left you on your birthday?
Why do you think he left you on your
birthday? He couldn't stand another year
your birthday? He couldn't
stand another year of you.
He couldn't stand another year of you.
You have five seconds to take
of you. >> You have five seconds to
take that back before I walk out of
you have five seconds to take that back
before I walk out of here in silence.
I see. Mills? >> You're
not dying, you know.
Mills? >> You're not dying, you know.
You're not dying!
You're not dying, you know. You're not
dying! It's... it's all right, mother.
You're not dying! It's... it's all right,
mother. He just needs to go away for a
it's... it's all right, mother. He
just needs to go away for a while.
He just needs to go away for a while.
I'll... I'll call
while. I'll... I'll call Dr.
Schoenberg.
I'll... I'll call Dr. schoenberg.
I shouldn't have listened to.
Dr. schoenberg. >> I shouldn't have
listened to those christians, mills.
I shouldn't have listened to those
christians, mills. My family is horrible.
Those christians, mills. My family is
horrible. >> Well, it was nice that you
my family is horrible. >> Well,
it was nice that you tried, sir.
Well, it was nice that you tried, sir.
What is "nice"?!
Tried, sir. >> What is "nice"?!
I don't know, sir.
What is "nice"?! >> I don't know, sir.
I have searched for the
I don't know, sir. >> I have
searched for the answer in love.
I have searched for the answer in love.
It was not there.
Answer in love. It was not there.
I know it wasn't present when I
it was not there. I know it wasn't present
when I searched for it in family, nor
I know it wasn't present when I searched for it
in family, nor did I find it in the arms of a
searched for it in family, nor did
I find it in the arms of a woman.
Did I find it in the arms of a woman.
So, I ask you, have I wasted my
woman. So, I ask you, have I wasted
my final day searching in vain?
So, I ask you, have I wasted my final
day searching in vain? Mills, time?
Final day searching in vain?
Mills, time? >> 5:00, sir.
Mills, time? >> 5:00, sir. >> Oh.
You got your watch fixed.
5:00, sir. >> Oh. You got your watch fixed.
Yes, while you were passed
oh. You got your watch fixed. >>
Yes, while you were passed out.
How did I get out of there
out. >> How did I get
out of there anyhow?
How did I get out of there anyhow?
I carried you.
Anyhow? >> I carried you.
Like a fireman?
I carried you. >> Like a fireman?
Yes.
Like a fireman? >> Yes. >>
Oh, I would have liked to
yes. >> Oh, I would have
liked to have seen that.
Oh, I would have liked to have seen that.
Yes, it was something else.
Have seen that. >> Yes, it was
something else. Well, sir, where next?
Yes, it was something else. Well, sir,
where next? >> All hope is lost, mills.
Well, sir, where next? >> All hope
is lost, mills. To the shifty Mick.
How many hours in bars, doing what?
Walking around with a cup,
what? Walking around with a cup,
posing in various stances with a
walking around with a cup, posing
in various stances with a cup...
Posing in various stances with a cup...
Refilling the cup and moving to
cup... Refilling the cup and moving
to another part of the room,
refilling the cup and moving to another part
of the room, perhaps the corner, so you can
another part of the room, perhaps the corner,
so you can see the whole roomful of people
perhaps the corner, so you can see the
whole roomful of people with their cups.
See the whole roomful of people with their
cups. "They sure are out tonight," you
with their cups. "They sure are out
tonight," you say to the man that pours.
"They sure are out tonight," you say to the man
that pours. "That they are, that they are,"
say to the man that pours. "That they are, that
they are," he says, too busy for more small
"that they are, that they are," he
says, too busy for more small talk.
He says, too busy for more small talk.
Cups to fill.
Talk. Cups to fill.
Cups to fill. Cups to fill.
Well, that's depressing.
Cups to fill. >> Well, that's depressing.
Usually you're more jovial.
Well, that's depressing. >> Usually you're
more jovial. >> I'm dying unfulfilled, boys.
Usually you're more jovial. >> I'm
dying unfulfilled, boys. Humor me.
I'm dying unfulfilled, boys. Humor me.
Perhaps it's not how you
humor me. >> Perhaps it's not
how you lived but how you die.
Perhaps it's not how you lived but how
you die. >> If you die happy, you stay
lived but how you die. >> If
you die happy, you stay happy.
If you die happy, you stay happy.
If you die in sadness, you
happy. If you die in sadness,
you remain in sadness.
If you die in sadness, you remain in
sadness. >> How are you dying, k. Roth?
Remain in sadness. >> How are you dying, k.
Roth? >> Quite well, thank you.
How are you dying, k. Roth? >> Quite well,
thank you. >> How are you really dying?
Quite well, thank you. >> How are you
really dying? >> How am I dying?
How are you really dying?
How am I dying? >> Yes.
How am I dying?!
Yes. >> How am I dying?! >>
That's what we're asking.
How am I dying?! >> That's what we're
asking. >> I am dying as you were
that's what we're asking. >> I am dying
as you were born... prematurely.
I am dying as you were born... prematurely.
I am dying as the owner
born... prematurely. I am dying as the
owner decorated this bar... foolishly.
I am dying as the owner decorated this bar...
foolishly. Finally, I am dying like my
decorated this bar... foolishly. Finally,
I am dying like my disease... nameless.
Finally, I am dying like my disease...
nameless. >> What about k. Roth binew as a
disease... nameless. >> What about k.
Roth binew as a name?
What about k. Roth binew as a name?
It already is my name.
Name? >> It already is my name.
Sounds like a disease if you
it already is my name. >> Sounds like
a disease if you say it fast enough.
Sounds like a disease if you say
it fast enough. Krothbinew.
Say it fast enough. Krothbinew.
You try it! Say it, k. Roth!
Krothbinew. You try it! Say it, k.
Roth! Say you got krothbinew.
You try it! Say it, k. Roth! Say you got
krothbinew. >> That would be ridiculous.
Say you got krothbinew. >> That
would be ridiculous. >> Come on!
That would be ridiculous. >> Come on!
It'll be fun!
Come on! >> It'll be fun!
All right.
It'll be fun! >> All right.
Ready?
All right. Ready? >> Yes.
Ready? >> Yes. >> You'd
better not come too
yes. >> You'd better
not come too close.
You'd better not come too close.
I've got krothbinew, and it's
close. I've got krothbinew,
and it's awfully contagious.
I've got krothbinew, and it's
awfully contagious. >> Contagious?!
Awfully contagious. >> Contagious?!
Oh, my God!
Contagious?! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Get me out of here!
- Oh, my God!
- Get me out of here!
- >> Well, I've always known how.
Well, I've always known how
to drive the women away.
Sir, your ride. >> Thanks for waiting.
Just think, you'll never have to
thanks for waiting. Just think, you'll
never have to wait out here again.
Just think, you'll never have to wait out
here again. >> It's quite all right, sir.
Wait out here again. >> It's quite
all right, sir. It's getting late.
It's quite all right, sir. It's getting
late. We should get you to the wake.
It's getting late. We should get you to
the wake. >> Look at the sky, mills.
We should get you to the wake. >> Look
at the sky, mills. It will be dark soon.
Look at the sky, mills. It will be
dark soon. >> Yes, sir. It will.
It will be dark soon. >> Yes, sir. It will.
Mills, if you don't mind, I
yes, sir. It will. >> Mills, if you don't
mind, I would like some time alone.
Mills, if you don't mind, I would like some
time alone. >> You don't have much, sir.
Would like some time alone. >>
You don't have much, sir. Hurry.
You don't have much, sir.
Hurry. >> Don't worry.
Hurry. >> Don't worry. One
cannot miss one's own living
don't worry. One cannot miss one's own
living wake... not for the world.
¶ I've never had a Swiss whore or a prosthetic
leg ¶ ¶ I've never heard someone beg
or a prosthetic leg ¶ ¶ I've never
heard someone beg for more ¶
¶ I've never heard someone beg for more
¶ ¶ I've barely heard people beg ¶
¶ I've never had a beach house or a meal
in a pill ¶ ¶ and it bothers me still that
or a meal in a pill ¶ ¶ and it bothers
me still that I've never been to Guam ¶
¶ and it bothers me still that I've never
been to Guam ¶ ¶ and now I never will ¶
¶ I thought I'd live to see the
future ¶ ¶ or at least a little bit
future ¶ ¶ or at least a
little bit of it now ¶
¶ or at least a little bit of
it now ¶ ¶ my life is over ¶
of it now ¶ ¶ my life is over ¶
¶ my brain and body have gone
¶ my life is over ¶ ¶ my brain
and body have gone to shit ¶
¶ my brain and body have gone to
shit ¶ ¶ and now the life is leaking
to shit ¶ ¶ and now the life is
leaking from my body like the water
¶ and now the life is leaking from my
body like the water through a sieve ¶
from my body like the water through a
sieve ¶ ¶ there was nothing that I gave
through a sieve ¶ ¶ there was
nothing that I gave this world ¶
¶ there was nothing that I gave this
world ¶ ¶ so it's like I never lived ¶
this world ¶ ¶ so it's like I never
lived ¶ ¶ so it's like I never lived ¶
¶ so it's like I never lived ¶ ¶ so it's like I
never lived ¶ ¶ so it's like I never lived ¶
¶ so it's like I never lived ¶ ¶ so it's like
I never lived ¶ ¶ so it's like I never...
¶ So it's like I never lived ¶ ¶ so
it's like I never... Lived at all ¶
let us begin. Let us begin our journey
toward the void... the journey toward
let us begin our journey toward the void...
the journey toward the void.
The void... the journey toward the void.
Let us begin our journey toward
the void. Let us begin our
journey toward the void.
All of you, for better or for worse, are the
human beings that have populated k. Roth binew's
worse, are the human beings that
have populated k. Roth binew's life.
Have populated k. Roth binew's life.
It is for this reason that he
life. It is for this reason that he
feels it is appropriate that you
it is for this reason that he feels it is
appropriate that you witness his death.
Feels it is appropriate that you witness
his death. So, let us begin our journey
witness his death. So, let us begin
our journey towards the void with
so, let us begin our journey towards the
void with k. Roth binew's living wake.
Towards the void with
k. Roth binew's living wake.
- K. Roth binew's living wake.
- Ladies and gentlemen...
Ladies and gentlemen...
The Irish body play.
Oh!
Look! A butterfly!
Oh.
Thank you!
Yes.
Thank you! Yes. Yeah!
There you go!
Yes. Yeah! There you go!
Thank you!
Yeah! There you go! Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Oh, look, ladies and gentlemen!
Thank you very much! Oh, look, ladies
and gentlemen! It's mills joquin!
Oh, look, ladies and gentlemen!
It's mills joquin! >> Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you. >> Ladies and
gentlemen, "if I was real"...
Ladies and gentlemen, "if I was real"...
By k. Roth binew.
¶ If I was real, I'd go to the bakery to
garner some pastries for my morning meal ¶
bakery to garner some pastries for my
morning meal ¶ ¶ and if I was real, I'd
for my morning meal ¶ ¶ and if I was
real, I'd probably have babies ¶
¶ and if I was real, I'd probably have
babies ¶ ¶ most likely a lady to have
probably have babies ¶ ¶ most
likely a lady to have babies with ¶
¶ most likely a lady to have babies
with ¶ >> they love me out there.
Babies with ¶ >> they love me out there.
I've got them right where I want
they love me out there. I've got
them right where I want them.
I've got them right where I want them.
¶ If I was real, I'd have
them. >> ¶ If I was real,
I'd have more insurance ¶
¶ if I was real, I'd have more insurance
¶ ¶ and if I was real, I'd be a
more insurance ¶ ¶ and if I was
real, I'd be a lot less nervous ¶
¶ and if I was real, I'd be a lot less
nervous ¶ ¶ I'm not real, I'm just bones ¶
lot less nervous ¶ ¶ I'm not real, I'm just
bones ¶ ¶ if I was real, I'd have me a.
¶ I'm not real, I'm just bones ¶ ¶ if I was real,
I'd have me a party, invite the most bawdy
¶ if I was real, I'd have me a party,
invite the most bawdy women I know ¶
party, invite the most bawdy women I
know ¶ ¶ and I'd have them hold me
women I know ¶ ¶ and I'd have them
hold me forever and make me as real as
¶ and I'd have them hold me forever
and make me as real as I'm not ¶
forever and make me as real as
I'm not ¶
Perhaps k. Roth's greatest.
Perhaps k. Roth's greatest
regret was that he never
perhaps k. Roth's greatest regret was that
he never produced the one work he adapted
regret was that he never produced the one work
he adapted for the stage, the story of an
produced the one work he adapted for the stage,
the story of an antebellum Southern woman and
for the stage, the story of an antebellum
Southern woman and all of her trials and
antebellum Southern woman and all
of her trials and tribulations.
All of her trials and tribulations.
Ladies and gentlemen, for the
tribulations. Ladies and gentlemen, for
the first time ever, k. Roth binew's
ladies and gentlemen, for the first time
ever, k. Roth binew's one-woman show,
first time ever, k. Roth binew's
one-woman show, "remembrance of dawn."
One-woman show,
"remembrance of dawn."
I do remember my youth, beauregard.
I do.
Remember my youth, beauregard. I do.
Well, I don't remember it like
I do. Well, I don't remember
it like most, with joy.
Well, I don't remember it like most, with
joy. No, I remember it with sadness.
Most, with joy. No, I remember it
with sadness. So much hope that was
no, I remember it with sadness.
So much hope that was squandered.
So many things that were left
squandered. So many things
that were left undone.
So many things that were left undone.
Oh, how I remember.
Undone. Oh, how I remember.
Oh, how I remember...
Oh, how I remember. Oh, how
I remember... Swimming.
Oh, how I remember... Swimming.
We would go down to the quarry.
Swimming. We would go down to the quarry.
There was always such good
we would go down to the quarry. There was
always such good swimming in the quarry.
There was always such good swimming in
the quarry. Mother and father and sister
swimming in the quarry. Mother and
father and sister were there.
Mother and father and sister were there.
And father would wear one of
were there. And father would wear one
of those full-body bathing suits
and father would wear one of those full-body
bathing suits that went out in the '20s.
Those full-body bathing suits that went out
in the '20s. Oh, he would look like such a
that went out in the '20s. Oh, he would
look like such a fool in that bathing suit.
Oh, he would look like such a fool in that
bathing suit. But it was all right, for he had
fool in that bathing suit. But it was
all right, for he had nice thighs.
But it was all right, for he had nice
thighs. And sometimes... well, sometimes
nice thighs. And sometimes... well,
sometimes Billy would be at the quarry.
And sometimes... well, sometimes Billy would
be at the quarry. Billy always smelled like
Billy would be at the quarry. Billy
always smelled like apple pie.
Billy always smelled like apple pie.
We weren't quite sure why.
Apple pie. We weren't quite sure why.
We thought it was maybe a
we weren't quite sure why. We thought
it was maybe a glandular disorder.
We thought it was maybe a glandular
disorder. But it was all right, because he
glandular disorder. But it was all right,
because he was sweet on me, and sister was
but it was all right, because he was
sweet on me, and sister was jealous!
Was sweet on me, and sister was
jealous!
Jealous!
And we would walk home through a.
And we would walk home through a
green field with the smells of
and we would walk home through a green field with
the smells of summer everywhere, the cicadas
green field with the smells of summer everywhere,
the cicadas singing their lovely summer
summer everywhere, the cicadas
singing their lovely summer opera.
Singing their lovely summer
opera.
Opera.
It was all so fresh, so full of.
It was all so fresh, so full of
hope, so untainted.
It was all so fresh, so full of hope, so
untainted. And then I met you, beauregard,
hope, so untainted. And then I met you,
beauregard, and all that was pure became
and then I met you, beauregard, and all that
was pure became polluted, and all that was
and all that was pure became polluted, and
all that was innocent became jaded, and all
polluted, and all that was innocent became
jaded, and all those summers turned to
innocent became jaded, and all those summers
turned to winters... cold, hateful, bitter
those summers turned to winters... cold,
hateful, bitter winters with no spring in sight!
Winters... cold, hateful, bitter winters with
no spring in sight! You have taken my youth,
winters with no spring in sight! You have
taken my youth, beauregard, which I got over.
You have taken my youth, beauregard, which
I got over. But I will not let you take my
beauregard, which I got over. But I will not
let you take my three beautiful children!
But I will not let you take my
three beautiful children! Oh!
Three beautiful children! Oh!
He needs an ambulance!
Oh! >> He needs an ambulance!
He's dead!
He needs an ambulance! >> He's dead!
No! No!
He's dead! >> No! No! >> Oh, no.
No! No! >> Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no!
No, dawn was falling.
Oh, no, no, no! No, dawn was falling.
Dawn fell.
No, dawn was falling. Dawn fell.
She used my body.
Dawn fell. She used my body.
I'm all right.
She used my body. I'm all right.
I'm all right. I'm all right.
Ladies and gentlemen, my two
I'm all right. Ladies and gentlemen, my
two friends from the bar whose names
ladies and gentlemen, my two friends from
the bar whose names completely escape me.
Friends from the bar whose names completely
escape me. Now, if you'll just excuse me
completely escape me. Now, if you'll just
excuse me for a brief moment, there will
now, if you'll just excuse me for a brief
moment, there will be a quick change.
For a brief moment, there will be a quick
change. I would like to reintroduce to
be a quick change. I would like to
reintroduce to you the master of ceremonies,
I would like to reintroduce to you the
master of ceremonies, mills joquin.
You the master of ceremonies,
mills joquin.
Mills joquin.
Thank you.
Um, so, these are onions.
- Thank you.
- Um, so, these are onions.
Um, so, these are onions.
So exciting to be at the.
So exciting to be at the
beginning of a thing.
So exciting to be at the beginning of a
thing. A different kind of excitement
beginning of a thing. A different kind of
excitement than the end... more hope, less
a different kind of excitement than
the end... more hope, less dread.
Than the end... more hope, less dread.
So exciting to be at the
dread. So exciting to be at
the beginning of a thing.
So exciting to be at the beginning of a
thing. >> And none of it as exciting as
beginning of a thing. >> And none of
it as exciting as what comes next.
You went away, and you stayed away.
And now you're here, and what do
away. And now you're here,
and what do you want?
And now you're here, and what do you want?
You wouldn't understand.
You want? >> You wouldn't understand.
It's too much to take in.
You wouldn't understand. It's too much to
take in. >> Oh, I understand perfectly.
It's too much to take in. >> Oh, I understand
perfectly. You left me alone in the world
oh, I understand perfectly. You left me alone
in the world with a family that hates me.
You left me alone in the world with a family
that hates me. You ruined fathers and men for
with a family that hates me. You
ruined fathers and men for me.
You ruined fathers and men for me.
And now, on my deathbed, you
me. And now, on my deathbed,
you wish to make amends.
And now, on my deathbed, you wish to
make amends. Well, let me say this, you
wish to make amends. Well, let me
say this, you small, selfish man...
well, let me say this, you small,
selfish man... >> k. Roth, please.
Small, selfish man... >> k. Roth, please.
Let me say this, you small,
k. Roth, please. >> Let me say
this, you small, selfish man!
Let me say this, you small, selfish man!
You are not my father.
Selfish man! You are not my father.
You are... An anti-father.
You are not my father. You are... An
anti-father. You are everything a father is
you are... An anti-father. You
are everything a father is not.
You are everything a father is not.
You lack father-ness.
Not. You lack father-ness. >>
I knew you would respond like
you lack father-ness. >> I knew
you would respond like this.
I knew you would respond like this.
You can take your brief but
this. >> You can take your brief but
powerful monologue and choke on
you can take your brief but
powerful monologue and choke on it.
Powerful monologue and choke on it.
I wouldn't have enough time to
it. I wouldn't have enough
time to use it anyhow.
I wouldn't have enough time to use it
anyhow. So if you'll just be on your
use it anyhow. So if you'll just be on
your way, the ending won't make any
so if you'll just be on your way, the ending
won't make any sense if you missed the middle.
Way, the ending won't make any sense
if you missed the middle. >> Klaus...
Sense if you missed the middle. >> Klaus...
Please, step off the stage and
Klaus... Please, step off the stage
and come back here to talk to me.
Please, step off the stage and come back here
to talk to me. >> I don't have time for your
come back here to talk to me. >> I don't have
time for your torturous babble right now,
I don't have time for your torturous
babble right now, Dr. schoenberg.
Torturous babble right now, Dr. schoenberg.
Very tight schedule.
Dr. schoenberg. Very tight schedule.
Klaus, you are having an
very tight schedule. >> Klaus, you are
having an episode, just like your previous
Klaus, you are having an episode,
just like your previous episodes.
Episode, just like your previous episodes.
Please, Klaus, go with your
episodes. >> Please, Klaus,
go with your doctor now.
Please, Klaus, go with your doctor now.
You just need some rest.
Doctor now. You just need some rest.
He's not my doctor.
You just need some rest. >> He's
not my doctor. That's my doctor.
He's not my doctor. That's my doctor.
K. Roth binew is dying of a
that's my doctor. >> K. Roth binew is
dying of a yet-to-be-named, grave, vague
k. Roth binew is dying of a
yet-to-be-named, grave, vague disease.
Yet-to-be-named, grave, vague disease.
Thank you, doctor.
Disease. >> Thank you, doctor.
10 minutes.
Thank you, doctor. >> 10 minutes.
Time waits for no man.
10 minutes. >> Time waits for no man.
I'm sure that some of you had a
time waits for no man. I'm sure that some
of you had a problem with the way I walked
I'm sure that some of you had a problem with
the way I walked through the world, so at the
problem with the way I walked through the world,
so at the end, there will be a two-minute
through the world, so at the end, there will
be a two-minute rebuttal, though I'm sure it
end, there will be a two-minute rebuttal, though
I'm sure it will be vicious, so let's cut it
rebuttal, though I'm sure it will be
vicious, so let's cut it out altogether.
Will be vicious, so let's cut it
out altogether. >> God damn it!
Out altogether. >> God damn it!
Old man, you can talk about.
God damn it! >> Old man, you can talk
about me all you want after I'm gone.
Old man, you can talk about me all you want
after I'm gone. In fact, I encourage it.
Me all you want after I'm gone. In fact, I
encourage it. Collect yourselves in small
in fact, I encourage it. Collect yourselves
in small groups every Thursday evening to
collect yourselves in small groups every
Thursday evening to discuss me and my ideas.
Groups every Thursday evening to discuss me and
my ideas. But don't forget to recruit from
discuss me and my ideas. But don't forget
to recruit from the local high schools.
But don't forget to recruit from the local
high schools. Perhaps my world view will be
the local high schools. Perhaps my world
view will be more in tune with the younger
perhaps my world view will be more
in tune with the younger generation.
More in tune with the younger generation.
Oh, registered on the scale of
generation. Oh, registered on the scale
of humanity, to register not as one
oh, registered on the scale of humanity, to
register not as one of billions who passively
humanity, to register not as one of billions
who passively consumed but as one who
of billions who passively consumed but
as one who produces, one who produced
consumed but as one who produces, one who
produced something people can turn to for
produces, one who produced something people can
turn to for the wisdom of the ages, just to
something people can turn to for the wisdom of the
ages, just to see a hand from the future reach
the wisdom of the ages, just to see a hand from
the future reach for my book on a shelf...
See a hand from the future reach for my book
on a shelf... Simple, unrealized fantasies are
for my book on a shelf... Simple, unrealized
fantasies are now too overwhelming to ponder.
Simple, unrealized fantasies are now too
overwhelming to ponder. >> Nine minutes.
Now too overwhelming to ponder. >> Nine
minutes. >> I should warn you, dear
nine minutes. >> I should warn you,
dear friends, that somewhere in this
I should warn you, dear friends, that somewhere
in this audience tonight, lurking, is
friends, that somewhere in this audience
tonight, lurking, is my enemy, the bane of my
audience tonight, lurking, is my enemy, the
bane of my soon-to-be-over existence, and
my enemy, the bane of my soon-to-be-over
existence, and he is not to be trusted.
Soon-to-be-over existence, and he is not
to be trusted. I know you're out there,
he is not to be trusted. I know
you're out there, Reginald!
I know you're out there, Reginald!
I'm right here, binew!
Reginald! >> I'm right here, binew!
Good.
I'm right here, binew! >> Good. I
would like to tell you how our
good. I would like to tell
you how our rivalry ends.
I would like to tell you how our rivalry
ends. I'm sure you think you have won
rivalry ends. I'm sure you think
you have won because I am dying.
I'm sure you think you have won
because I am dying. >> A little bit.
Because I am dying. >> A little bit.
Well, you are wrong, dear
a little bit. >> Well, you
are wrong, dear friend.
Well, you are wrong, dear friend.
I have won, because when you
friend. I have won, because when
you return home tonight, you will.
I have won, because when you return home tonight,
you will find that I have shit in all of
return home tonight, you will find
that I have shit in all of your pants.
Find that I have shit in all
of your pants. >> What?!
- Your pants.
- >> What?!
- What?!
- >> I have shit in all of your.
I have shit in all of your
pants.
I have shit in all of your pants.
Even the gaberdines?!
Pants. >> Even the gaberdines?!
Yes, Reginald.
Even the gaberdines?! >> Yes, Reginald.
And that feeling you have when
yes, Reginald. And that feeling you
have when you realize that I am not
and that feeling you have when you realize
that I am not joking... why, that is exactly
you realize that I am not joking... why, that
is exactly how awful it has been to live
joking... why, that is exactly how awful it has
been to live near you on the planet earth for
how awful it has been to live near you on
the planet earth for these past few years.
Near you on the planet earth for these past
few years. So, Reginald, it seems that our
these past few years. So, Reginald, it
seems that our case is well rested.
So, Reginald, it seems that our
case is well rested.
Case is well rested.
Because he has decided to.
Because he has decided to
maintain his unwelcome presence,
because he has decided to maintain his unwelcome
presence, I see no reason why I should not
maintain his unwelcome presence, I see no
reason why I should not introduce him.
I see no reason why I should not introduce
him. He is, after all, responsible
introduce him. He is, after all,
responsible for most of my personality
he is, after all, responsible for
most of my personality problems.
For most of my personality problems.
Ladies and gentlemen, the father
problems. Ladies and gentlemen,
the father that abandoned me,
ladies and gentlemen, the father
that abandoned me, lampert binew.
That abandoned me, lampert binew.
I did not abandon you.
Lampert binew. >> I did not abandon you.
Maybe they changed the
I did not abandon you. >> Maybe they
changed the definition of "abandon."
Maybe they changed the definition of
"abandon." Uh, perhaps "forsake" or
definition of "abandon." Uh,
perhaps "forsake" or "desert."
Uh, perhaps "forsake" or
"desert." >> Eight minutes.
"Desert." >> Eight minutes.
Father, come back in eight
eight minutes. >> Father,
come back in eight minutes.
Father, come back in eight minutes.
I'm busy right now.
Minutes. I'm busy right now.
Before I forget, if anybody
I'm busy right now. Before I forget,
if anybody wants two blankets, half a
before I forget, if anybody wants two blankets,
half a bottle of gin, a typewriter, and
wants two blankets, half a bottle of gin, a
typewriter, and a hot plate, they'll be in room
bottle of gin, a typewriter, and a hot plate,
they'll be in room number 8 at my boarding house.
A hot plate, they'll be in room number
8 at my boarding house. Be careful.
Number 8 at my boarding house. Be careful.
The typewriter is cursed.
Be careful. The typewriter is cursed.
It only types out trash...
the typewriter is cursed. It only types
out trash... unpublishable trash.
It only types out trash... unpublishable
trash. You can get the key off of my
unpublishable trash. You can get the key
off of my body after the wake, left-hand
you can get the key off of my body
after the wake, left-hand pocket.
Body after the wake, left-hand pocket.
There is also a crisp $50 bill
pocket. There is also a crisp $50
bill taped to my testicles for
there is also a crisp $50 bill taped to
my testicles for whoever is interested.
Taped to my testicles for whoever is
interested. It is well taped, so I imagine
whoever is interested. It is well taped,
so I imagine it will require some work.
It is well taped, so I imagine it will
require some work. Not for the squeamish.
It will require some work. Not for the
squeamish. Mills, what are you doing?
Not for the squeamish. Mills, what
are you doing? This is my show.
Mills, what are you doing? This is my show.
I've written something for
this is my show. >> I've
written something for you.
I've written something for you.
Well, I'm not finished, and I
you. >> Well, I'm not finished,
and I don't have much time.
Well, I'm not finished, and I don't have
much time. Don't you think you could do it
don't have much time. Don't you think
you could do it when I'm gone?
Don't you think you could
do it when I'm gone? >> No.
When I'm gone? >> No.
It will only
no. It will only take
a moment, please.
It will only take a moment, please.
All right.
"K. Roth binew, my king, my light,
your day the last has come."
Light, your day the last has come.
And as your breath doth seek its
come. And as your breath doth seek
its death upon the setting sun, I
and as your breath doth seek its death upon the
setting sun, I cast my sights to fancy flights,
death upon the setting sun, I cast my sights
to fancy flights, when you and I were young.
Cast my sights to fancy flights, when you and
I were young. K. Roth binew, my king, my
when you and I were young. K. Roth binew,
my king, my light, we will not meet again.
"K. Roth binew, so falls the night...
When falls my only friend."
Thank you, mills.
I see now why the wake is traditionally
held after death. Much quieter.
Traditionally held after death.
Much quieter. Less painful.
You can fabricate the
less painful. You can fabricate
the disposition of the dead.
You can fabricate the disposition of
the dead. You cannot hear them howling
disposition of the dead. You cannot hear
them howling their last breath in defiance.
You cannot hear them howling their
last breath in defiance. Howl!
Their last breath in defiance.
Howl! Like that.
Howl! Like that. Howl!
Like that. Howl! That
is my interpretation of
howl! That is my
interpretation of defiance.
That is my interpretation of defiance.
I died that day at the zoo.
Defiance. >> I died that day at the zoo.
Really, father, this constant
I died that day at the zoo. >> Really, father,
this constant interruption is inexcusable.
Really, father, this constant interruption is
inexcusable. >> I'd gotten you a small panda.
Interruption is inexcusable. >> I'd gotten you
a small panda. A stuffed animal, of course.
I'd gotten you a small panda. A stuffed animal,
of course. While leaving the zoo, someone
a stuffed animal, of course. While leaving the
zoo, someone bumped me, and the panda fell
while leaving the zoo, someone bumped
me, and the panda fell into a cage.
Bumped me, and the panda fell into a cage.
I was in a hurry, so without
into a cage. I was in a hurry, so
without thinking, I climbed the fence.
I was in a hurry, so without thinking, I climbed
the fence. As I bent down to get the panda,
thinking, I climbed the fence. As I bent down to
get the panda, I realized I was surrounded by
as I bent down to get the panda, I
realized I was surrounded by badgers.
I realized I was surrounded by badgers.
"Why a cage full of badgers?"
Badgers. "Why a cage full
of badgers?" I thought.
"Why a cage full of badgers?" I thought.
"Who wants to look at a badger?"
I thought. "Who wants to look at a
badger?" First they tore through my
"who wants to look at a badger?" First they
tore through my clothes, then my skin, then the
first they tore through my clothes, then
my skin, then the sinew, then the bone.
Clothes, then my skin, then the sinew,
then the bone. I was completely devoured.
Sinew, then the bone. I was completely
devoured. The only evidence remaining was
I was completely devoured. The only evidence
remaining was the toy panda... And the 10
the only evidence remaining was the toy
panda... And the 10 badgers with bloody teeth.
The toy panda... And the 10 badgers with
bloody teeth. >> So, you would have come back?
Badgers with bloody teeth. >> So,
you would have come back? >> Yes.
So, you would have come back? >> Yes.
And you would have told me
yes. >> And you would have
told me what it all meant?
And you would have told me what it all
meant? >> K. Roth, life is not like one
what it all meant? >> K. Roth, life is
not like one of your word problems.
K. Roth, life is not like one of your word
problems. There's no equation for life.
Of your word problems. There's no equation
for life. >> I guess life would be a very
there's no equation for life. >> I guess
life would be a very long word problem.
I guess life would be a very long word
problem. But you implied that there was a
long word problem. But you implied
that there was a definitive answer.
But you implied that there was a definitive
answer. >> There's no answer, just a
definitive answer. >> There's no answer,
just a decision... a decision you made
there's no answer, just a decision... a
decision you made long ago, k. Roth.
Decision... a decision you made long
ago, k. Roth. >> And what was that?
Long ago, k. Roth. >> And what was that?
To live in the world of
and what was that? >> To live in the
world of possibilities, to embrace
to live in the world of possibilities, to
embrace thoughts as something not to be
possibilities, to embrace thoughts as something
not to be ignored but shouted from the
thoughts as something not to be ignored
but shouted from the highest tower.
Ignored but shouted from the
highest tower. >> So...
Highest tower. >> So...
You're dead...
So... You're dead... Right now?
You're dead... Right now? >>
I thought you figured that
right now? >> I thought you
figured that out in the tent.
I thought you figured that out in the tent.
Yes. No one can see me but you.
- Out in the tent.
- Yes. No one can see me but you.
- >> What's the matter with him?
Five minutes. >> Oh. Oh, but
I was supposed to earn.
Oh. Oh, but I was supposed to earn
my seat at the table of eternal
oh, but I was supposed to earn my seat
at the table of eternal literary greats!
My seat at the table of eternal literary
greats! I have no goal completed!
Literary greats! I have no goal completed!
You have tried.
I have no goal completed! >> You
have tried. >> And I have failed.
You have tried. >> And I have failed.
I am not a sculptor.
And I have failed. I am not a sculptor.
I am not a writer.
I am not a sculptor. I am not a writer.
I am not a painter!
I am not a writer. I am not a painter!
I am not a dancer!
I am not a painter! I am not a dancer!
I am a stupid, drunk, scared,
I am not a dancer! I am a stupid,
drunk, scared, dying man!
I am a stupid, drunk, scared, dying man!
I am... A dead man!
Dying man! I am... A dead man!
Perhaps you are all of these
I am... A dead man! >> Perhaps you are all
of these things, k. Roth, but you have
perhaps you are all of these things, k.
Roth, but you have never been scared.
Things, k. Roth, but you have never
been scared. Why should you be now?
Never been scared. Why should you be now?
You're right, father.
Why should you be now? >> You're
right, father. >> Four minutes.
You're right, father. >> Four minutes.
I-I can be stupid.
- Four minutes.
- >> I-I can be stupid.
- I-I can be stupid.
- And... and I can be drunk!
And... and I can be drunk!
I'm kind of faced right now!
And... and I can be drunk! I'm kind of faced
right now! But I was not, could not, have
I'm kind of faced right now! But I was
not, could not, have never been scared!
But I was not, could not, have never
been scared! And I vow for the next four
never been scared! And I vow for the
next four minutes, things will be no
and I vow for the next four minutes,
things will be no different!
Minutes, things will be no different!
That's my boy.
- Different!
- >> That's my boy.
- That's my boy.
- I-I have become so very strange,
I-I have become so very strange,
father!
I-I have become so very strange, father!
You have only become
father! >> You have only
become yourself, k. Roth.
You have only become yourself, k.
Roth. Come now.
Yourself, k. Roth. Come now.
It is time to finish.
Come now. It is time to finish.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It is time to finish. >> Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Could... could I not just stay a
whoa, whoa, whoa. Could... could
I not just stay a little longer?
Could... could I not just stay a little
longer? Um, mills will be lost without
little longer? Um, mills
will be lost without me.
Um, mills will be lost without me.
You know it's time, k. Roth.
- Me.
- >> You know it's time, k. Roth.
- You know it's time, k. Roth.
- They're playing your song,
They're playing your song,
k. Roth.
They're playing your song, k. Roth.
The one from earlier.
K. Roth. >> The one from earlier.
But I don't know the words.
The one from earlier. But I don't
know the words. >> Don't worry.
But I don't know the words. >> Don't worry.
They'll come to you.
¶ And so I take my final bow
¶ ¶ and though the curtain's
final bow ¶ ¶ and though the
curtain's halfway down ¶
¶ and though the curtain's halfway
down ¶ ¶ I'll speak my piece ¶
halfway down ¶ ¶ I'll speak my piece
¶ ¶ I'll shout it out to all of.
¶ I'll speak my piece ¶ ¶ I'll shout it out
to all of you who've gathered 'round ¶
¶ I'll shout it out to all of you
who've gathered 'round ¶ I do know it!
You who've gathered 'round ¶ I do know it!
¶ three-piece suit ¶
I do know it! ¶ Three-piece
suit ¶ ¶ kerchief peeking out ¶
¶ three-piece suit ¶ ¶ kerchief
peeking out ¶ ¶ shoes to boot ¶
¶ kerchief peeking out ¶ ¶ shoes
to boot ¶ ¶ you see me, you know
¶ shoes to boot ¶ ¶ you see me,
you know I-I-I-I-I-I-I'm... ¶
¶ you see me, you know I-I-I-I-I-I-I'm...
¶ ¶ dressed for death ¶
I-I-I-I-I-I-I'm... ¶ ¶ dressed
for death ¶ ¶ got my ticket ¶
¶ dressed for death ¶ ¶ got my
ticket ¶ ¶ I'll take the express ¶
¶ got my ticket ¶ ¶ I'll take the
express ¶ ¶ to the other side ¶
¶ I'll take the express ¶ ¶ to the
other side ¶ ¶ my last breath ¶
¶ to the other side ¶ ¶ my last
breath ¶ ¶ won't be wasted on you,
¶ my last breath ¶ ¶ won't
be wasted on you, death ¶
¶ won't be wasted on you, death
¶ ¶ I'm the better man ¶
death ¶ ¶ I'm the better man ¶
¶ and when I no longer dwell.
¶ I'm the better man ¶ ¶ and when I
no longer dwell inside this well-worn
¶ and when I no longer dwell inside
this well-worn human shell ¶
inside this well-worn human shell
¶ ¶ I'll either laugh at all
human shell ¶ ¶ I'll either
laugh at all my woe ¶
¶ I'll either laugh at all my
woe ¶ ¶ or I'll just be dead ¶
my woe ¶ ¶ or I'll just be dead
¶ it's too bad the vagina's not
¶ or I'll just be dead ¶ it's too bad the
vagina's not more involved in death.
It's too bad the vagina's not more involved
in death. Just as I was getting used to
more involved in death. Just
as I was getting used to it.
Just as I was getting used to it.
Mills, Baton!
It. Mills, Baton!
¶ don't be sad ¶
mills, Baton! ¶ Don't be sad ¶
¶ simply think of the times
¶ don't be sad ¶ ¶ simply
think of the times we had ¶
¶ simply think of the times we had
¶ ¶ all the laughter and the tears
we had ¶ ¶ all the laughter
and the tears we shed ¶
¶ all the laughter and the tears we
shed ¶ ¶ eh, you won't remember them
we shed ¶ ¶ eh, you won't
remember them when you're dead ¶
¶ eh, you won't remember them when you're
dead ¶ ¶ so drink and laugh and live ¶
when you're dead ¶ ¶ so drink and laugh
and live ¶ ¶ 'cause life's not supposed
¶ so drink and laugh and live ¶ ¶ 'cause life's
not supposed to be an exercise in misery ¶
¶ 'cause life's not supposed to be an
exercise in misery ¶ ¶ it is a carnival where
to be an exercise in misery ¶ ¶ it is
a carnival where everything is free ¶
¶ it is a carnival where everything is
free ¶ I'd tell you to lose the old
everything is free ¶ I'd tell you to lose
the old man, but seeing as I'm leaving,
I'd tell you to lose the old man, but seeing as
I'm leaving, well, maybe we'll run into each
man, but seeing as I'm leaving, well, maybe
we'll run into each other in the void.
Well, maybe we'll run into each
other in the void. >> Hey!
¶ Dressed for death ¶ ¶ don't you
see that I'm dressed to die? ¶
¶ don't you see that I'm dressed to die?
¶ ¶ and in parting, I have one
to die? ¶ ¶ And in parting,
I have one request ¶
¶ and in parting, I have one request
¶ ¶ show your face, death, to
request ¶ ¶ show your face,
death, to these few guests ¶
¶ show your face, death, to these few
guests ¶ ¶ because they'll meet you, too,
these few guests ¶ ¶ because
they'll meet you, too, someday ¶
¶ because they'll meet you, too, someday
¶ ¶ if you meet them now, you'll
someday ¶ ¶ if you meet them now,
you'll get it out of the way ¶
¶ if you meet them now, you'll get it out
of the way ¶ ¶ when you meet them again and
get it out of the way ¶ ¶ when you meet them
again and it's their turn to die, you'll
¶ when you meet them again and it's their
turn to die, you'll be old friends ¶
it's their turn to die, you'll be old
friends ¶ >> stop this nonsense!
Be old friends ¶ >> stop this nonsense!
It's gone too far.
Stop this nonsense! It's gone too far.
If you think that's
it's gone too far. >> If you think
that's ridiculous, mother, wait till
if you think that's ridiculous,
mother, wait till you see the finale.
Ridiculous, mother, wait till you
see the finale. ¶ Take me now! ¶
you see the finale. ¶ Take me now!
¶ ¶ I'm quite ready ¶
¶ take me now! ¶ ¶ I'm quite
ready ¶ ¶ come on down ¶
¶ I'm quite ready ¶ ¶ come on down
¶ ¶ with your blade and your long,
¶ come on down ¶ ¶ with your blade
and your long, black gown ¶
¶ with your blade and your long, black
gown ¶ ¶ a smile will greet you, not
black gown ¶ ¶ a smile will
greet you, not a frown ¶
¶ a smile will greet you, not a frown
¶ ¶ because I've reflected upon
a frown ¶ ¶ because I've
reflected upon my life ¶
¶ because I've reflected upon my life
¶ ¶ and I think it's done, and I
my life ¶ ¶ and I think it's
done, and I think it was right ¶
¶ and I think it's done, and I think it
was right ¶ ¶ and if I'd never lived this
think it was right ¶ ¶ and if I'd never
lived this life, it would have never been
¶ and if I'd never lived this life,
it would have never been lived ¶
he's... Dead.
I was right.
I will try my best to get
them in.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
That's what you get for
trying to steal a man's dame.
You were all right.
A little strange, but all right.
Yeah.
¶ Dressed for death ¶
¶ don't you see that I'm dressed
to die? ¶
¶ If you meet them now, you'll
get it out of the way ¶
¶ when you meet them again and
it's their turn to die... ¶
Whoo!
Yeah!
Thank you very much!
Whoo!
One more take, one more take.