Where monsters rampage,
I'm there to take them down!
Where treasure glitters,
I'm there to claim it!
Where an enemy rises to face me,
victory will be mine!
I'm Lina Inverse, sorcery genius!
We finally made it to Sairaag
and found who was behind all this.
The one who falsely accused us
and put a price on our heads...
...was a sorceress named Eris.
And it turns out she's
one of Rezo's followers!
Things were tight, but we were
saved by good old Zelgadis.
And just as we were about to
strike back, a new foe appeared.
I think it's time we found out
exactly what's going on here!
Rezo, the Red Priest?!
I got it...
- You just LOOK like him!
- You mean he's a fake?
He can't be the real one!
It has to be some
kind of horrible joke!
They did a great job of finding
a double for him, didn't they?
Well... Actually I can't exactly
remember what he looks like.
Gourry,
would you just SHUT UP?!
Right, Zel?
Yes. A very clever fake!
Why are you all so sure
he's an imposter?
Because we fought Rezo before...
...and we managed to kill him!
WHAT?! Rezo, who everyone says
is a great sage?! You killed him?!
Miss Lina, you're all really...!
Incredible?
I was going to say "villains."
- We're what?!
- But...! But...!
And who's he?! He's so
creepy and suspicious-looking!
Well, excuse me.
Amelia, anyone who judges
people by looks or rumors...
...gives justice a bad name!
Okay, Zelgadis may seem
suspicious at first glance...
Well, excuse me!
...but he's sort of okay.
Sort of?!
Rezo, the Red Priest, wasn't the
great sage people said he was.
Really?
Really! That's why he
has to be an imposter!
I know it's a longshot,
but maybe he IS the real one.
No way! He's a fake!
Now you're judging people by
rumor and appearances, Miss Lina.
That doesn't apply here!
Anyway, I say he's a fake!
Rather than asking if I'm
the real one or not...
...isn't there a question that
needs to be answered first?
Meaning what?!
The one of whether you
really killed me or not.
We killed him! Meaning you
aren't the real Red Priest!
Well, then...
Why don't I try my luck?!
Well, you've got
the attitude down pat!
Fireball!
Take this! Ghozu Vro!
Impossible!
I see. You aren't just
some imposter, are you?
Well, then, allow me
to make the next move.
Man, he's powerful!
This protection field
isn't going to hold out!
Oh, I've hardly even begun!
Damn! I don't have
time to recast the spell!
What was that?! Someone just
cast a major protection spell!
Sylphiel!
What are you doing here?
Well, I was worried
about dear Gourry...
...so I thought I'd
go looking for you.
You looked like you
were being attacked.
Looked, nothing!
We WERE being attacked!
Oh, how terrible!
Oh, of all the...! Never mind.
With Sylphiel here to protect us...
...we can give him the works!
- Run for it!
- Hey!
Damn! We have no choice!
Miss Lina!
Wow, so that's who
you are, Mr. Zelgadis.
And you two are a Seyruun princess
and a friend of Gourry's.
Now that we've calmed down,
anyone know who the Rezo twin is?
And why did he let us escape
without trying to follow us?
Search me. Anyway, as long
as we don't know who he is...
...we consider him an imposter,
although a powerful one.
Right.
You're sure he
isn't the real one?
Well...
I'm sure we killed Rezo!
We must have...
Well, maybe you killed
the imposter instead.
Uh, no...
That's not possible.
Oh...
The one we killed had
to have been the real Rezo.
Then who was
the Rezo we just saw?
Maybe another copy.
If it was a copy of Rezo...
...how is he able to
cast spells that powerful?
It's not my area of expertise, so
I'm not clear on the details. Okay!
What are you going to do?
Go ask an expert!
We won't learn anything
just hanging around here.
All right, and I'll try some
other things in the meantime.
What are you doing?
I have a few things
to investigate.
I'll meet you here
tomorrow at noon. See you.
Sure thing. Be careful!
Anyway, Miss Lina, do you
have any sorcerer friends...
...who are experts
in copying people?
Well, not friends exactly.
But there's a dark
sorcerers' guild nearby...
...that specializes in chimeras!
NOT AGAIN!!!
Stop doing this to me!
Hey! I see it! There it is!
Please, you can't
go in there!
Come on, you let people in
for study, right?! Move it!
What's the big idea,
you uncivilized hoodlums?!
No, singular. Just her!
They want to study and
give us a big donation.
A donation?! So, what
do you want to know?
How much of the original's
power can a copy have?
All of it!
Really?!
Well, I'd like to say that.
Which is it then?!
Well, it can have all of the
physical abilities of the original.
Strength, speed, reflexes...
This is our latest
copy cultivator.
It can copy an ordinary person's
memories and experiences.
An ordinary person's?
Well, we don't have any
extraordinary people here.
Like a sorcery genius or
an expert swordsman.
We've no idea how much of those
special skills we can duplicate.
Why don't you experiment?
Geniuses and experts don't
grow on trees, you know!
We don't have any samples.
I see... Okay, you can
use US as your samples!
You mean it?!
Take cute little Gourry over here!
Despite appearances, he's
actually an expert swordsman!
Oh, that's right!
He... He's what?!
So, you need a bucket of his
blood as a sample, right?
Not at all!
A lock of hair will do!
Not a problem!
Stop! I refuse!
- C'mon, Gourry!
- Don't be ridiculous!
Sylphiel, please! Stop them!
Okay!
Wouldn't it be wonderful
to have more of you?
I can't see the sense of it,
but you did it, Sylphiel!
Quickly, give it to me!
You, too, Sylphiel?!
You, too?! How could you?!
So, how long till it's done?
A day and a night.
- We don't have that long!
- No, cut that out!
Oh, relax! I'm just
adding more growth culture.
Hey, Pops! Can I use
the one over there?
She's a sorcery genius!
I guarantee the power!
Oh, that's right!
Oh! Really? Really?!
Hey! Stop it, Gourry!
I'm just doing to you
what you did to me!
Stop kidding around!
Why, you...!
- Adding the growth culture!
- No, that's too much!
How could you rip my hair out?!
Ah, they're finished.
Hi!
That's the cutest
thing I've ever seen!
What happened?
It's tiny!
You rushed the growth,
so it didn't mature fully!
I'm hungry!
Well, it's definitely got the
original's personality.
What's that supposed to mean?
This one's finished, too!
Yo!
I'm hungry and demand some food!
Looks like it's got the
original's personality, too.
Meaning what?!
Lina Kick!
What was that for?!
Wow, they're
exactly like you two.
Huh?! What's happening?!
Victory! Yay! Yay!
All right! Great job!
Guys, you suck!
Bye-bye!
What's wrong?!
What happened?!
You overloaded the machine!
Thanks for the help!
And don't come back!
No hard feelings, okay?
For crying out loud!
Is this what happens when
he exerts himself a little?
Your beloved Rezo?
Get out...
I said get out!
Sure thing. Sorry to bother.
What happened to you?
Oh, morning, Zelgadis.
It's afternoon.
So, did you find out
anything about copies?
Not much. Just that it's
possible to make a perfect copy.
No answers there.
So, what were you checking out?
Oh, just some stuff on Rezo.
On Rezo?
What I checked on wasn't
about the fake Rezo.
I mean on the real Rezo.
So, what did you find out
about the real Rezo?
Well...
C'mon Zel, why so gloomy?
Rezo told me something
a long time ago.
About an ancient laboratory
he sealed away...
...which contains the books of
spells and sorcery he's collected.
Rezo's sorcery collection?
They couldn't help him
cure his eyes, apparently.
But it seems there are some
extraordinary magic books in it.
If Rezo collected them,
they've gotta be extraordinary!
Where is it?! Where? Where?
Sairaag.
Sairaag! Well, lucky
we're here, isn't it?!
Once I learned that
from my investigation...
...I discovered something else.
Rezo's sealed laboratory is in
the ruins of old Sairaag!
The old city?!
Out there?!
- You know about it?
- It's a long story.
The ruins of old Sairaag...
They're not far from here.
On the other side of the
great holy tree, Flagoon.
It's a desolate
place of ruins now.
Will you guide me there?
Sure! Sure she will!
She'll do anything!
And I'll come along, too!
Hey, you sure you should?
We may learn who
"Rezo" really is.
Just knowing he's
powerful isn't enough.
With Rezo's collection
of treasure...
I mean spells, we may be able to
find a way to fight this imposter!
Hm, you seem serious, but...
Well, at least she's
honest about her greed.
Okay, it's all settled!
Okay with you, Zelgadis?
Be my guest.
But the old city is a
very dangerous place now.
Be that as it may,
I'm still going.
Right! Let's go
for that treasure!
All I want is to find a way
to turn myself back to normal!
Um, before we go, may I go
back home and tell my father?
Huh?
We have to be careful of
Eris and the others.
And the city guards are
as prevalent as always.
Let's go together when
it's dark, Sylphiel.
Right!
Is it much further?
I can see it!
No way!
We've been waiting! Now give
the Sword of Light to me!
Man, oh man.
You people never give up!
Gourry! This time
we settle things!
You know, you're really
starting to annoy me.
Shut up!
If Gourry's taking him on,
then I'm fighting you!
As you wish.
Zel, wait! You want to fight
in the middle of the city?!
Don't worry! This time I'll
test his powers with one shot!
Why, you...!
I don't know who you really are,
but my righteous blood is boiling!
Your evil shall be...
Shut up and stay out of this!
But I already climbed up here!
Why is Rezo so confident?
Zelgadis is hitting him
with all his power!
You see, my power is far
greater than even this!
RUN FOR IT!
Everyone, over here!
You, too, Gourry! Move it!
Huh?! Why?!
Retreat, Zangulus!
Retreat if you want to live!
Damn it! To hell with this!
We have to get out of here!
It's almost too late!
- Zel, give us wind!
- Right! A wind barrier!
Wait for me!
Sylphiel, give us a
protection spell from above!
Right!
Amelia, gimme a
levitation spell!
Right!
And I'll reinforce
the wind barrier!
I don't know what the spell does,
but it's serious black magic!
Are we gonna make it?!
How... How could it
be so destructive?!
Was that a Mega Brando?!
No, that's impossible!
It definitely has the
effect of a Mega Brando.
But the magical power
is much, much larger!
Miss Lina! Sairaag is...!
Half the city is gone...
Sylphiel!
F- Father...
FATHER!!!
NO!!!
Whether he was real or not
didn't matter now.
The man we were fighting
was unbelievably powerful.
And extraordinarily cruel.
That much was clear.