[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Woman ]
Chime magazine.
[ Phone Ringing Continues ]
[ Woman ]
Yes. Please hold.
[ Typing ]
[ Woman ]
He's in a meeting right now.
Can I take a message?
[ Woman ]
Great. I'll have him
call you back.
[ Man ]
Wow. You're Danny Collins.
[ Danny ]
Yeah.
Jesus H.!
You mind if we listen
while we talk?
Sure.
♪♪ [ Guitar ]
[ Danny On Record ]
♪ Caught out in the rain ♪
♪ I was on the street ♪
♪ Went into a bar ♪
♪ Strangers always meet ♪♪
♪♪ [ Continues ]
[ Man ]
Uh, is this cool?
[ Danny ]
Sure. Yeah.
Smoke?
No.
No, thanks.
Well, the album's
gonna be massive, kid.
Who got you there?
[ Danny ]
Uh... I'm sorry?
[ Man ]
Your influences.
Who do you dig?
Who makes you hard?
Oh. [ Clears Throat ]
Well, um--
[ Coughs ]
I guess I--
If I had to think--
Hold on.
June 30, 1971.
Guy DeLoach...
with the apparently
prepubescent
Danny Collins...
for Chime mag.
[ Clears Throat ]
More than anything,
it's your writing.
You write like
fucking Lennon, man.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, well, I--
That's, um--
[ Clears Throat ]
Thank you.
I guess he's probably
the one who, uh, make--
you know, who makes me
the hardest, um--
[ Laughing ]
Jesus H.!
Well, you're gonna
be huge, kid.
Richer than rich.
Famous as shit.
More women than
you know what to do with.
I'm telling you this,
and I've gotta ask,
why are you sitting there
staring at me,
looking like
that information...
scares the livin' shit
out of you?
Because it does.
[ Laughing ]
[ Groans ]
Jesus H.
[ Crowd Chanting ]
Danny! Danny! Danny! Danny!
Danny! Danny!
Danny! Danny! Danny!
[ Inhaling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Crowd Cheering, Faint ]
[ Radio: Man ]
5-1, ready to go.
[ Man Speaks, Indistinct ]
[ Radio: Man ]
Standing by.
[ Radio: Woman ]
The man says
he's ready to go.
Break a leg, Danny.
Just tell me whose.
Good job!
Hey!
[ Man ]
Hey.
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
How you doing?
[ Crowd Continues Chanting ]
Danny! Danny! Danny! Danny!
Danny! Danny!
Danny!
Danny! Danny! Danny!
[ Cheering ]
Hello, LA!
It's good to be back!
Danny!
♪ Hey, baby doll ♪
♪ What's goin' on? ♪
♪♪ [ Backup Singers
Vocalizing ]
♪ Sweet baby doll ♪
♪ I'll sing my song ♪
♪ For you ♪
Sweet!
♪ You were strong
when I was weak ♪
♪ With a kiss ♪
♪ Upon my cheek ♪
♪ We could fly so far away ♪
♪ From here ♪
♪ My baby ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Hey, baby doll ♪
♪ What's goin' on? ♪
♪♪ [ Backup Singers
Vocalizing ]
♪ Sweet baby doll ♪
♪ I sing my song ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Hey, baby doll ♪
♪ What's goin' on? ♪♪
[ Chattering,
Laughing ]
Excuse me. Mr. Collins?
Do you think I could bother you
for a quick picture?
Just real quick.
Real quick.
My mom will die.
I hope not.
Oh! Awesome.
Beauty.
I will tweet this
to you.
Awesome.
It was a good show
tonight, kid.
Awesome.
Hey, Sylvia Plath,
are you okay?
If what I just did
qualified as singing,
I'd be great.
Mm-hmm.
You know.
Little birthday blues,
I guess.
Uh-huh.
All right, everyone.
My guy needs
a little rest here.
[ Man ]
Good night, Danny.
Sally, thank you
for coming, honey.
Tell your dad
I said hello, Kate.
See those Golden Girls
in the front row?
Mm-hmm.
Eating licorice
the entire show.
You can't choose
your fans, Danny.
Three of them.
Each one
older than the next.
[ Chuckling ]
Made one pack of licorice
last the whole show.
Just sat there
gummin' it for two hours.
[ Laughing ]
New billboard
went up on Sunset.
You should check it out
on your way home, yeah?
All right,
enough of this crap.
So your birthday's tomorrow.
Is that your big problem?
Pregnant women in Africa,
feeding half their village
from their titties.
Those ladies
got problems.
Not you.
You're so right.
Yeah. Of course I'm right.
I'm always right.
So you go home now
to your stunning,
half-your-age fiancée...
who insists on
throwing you this massive
surprise party tomorrow,
which I didn't just
tell you about,
and then go tell...
the sore-titted
African ladies
your problems.
Okay?
Okay.
See you at
my surprise party, buddy.
♪♪ [ Guitar, Man Singing ]
[ Laughing ]
- Hey.
- Yeah?
It was a good show
tonight, kid.
Really.
[ Man ]
♪ By giving you no time ♪
[ Sighs ] Okay.
♪ Instead of it all ♪
♪ Till the pain is so big ♪
♪ You feel nothing at all ♪
♪ A working-class hero
is something to be ♪
Yeah, just wanted
to let you know--
♪ A working-class hero
is something to be ♪
We'll have to get that
fixed for you, Mr. Collins.
How was the show?
♪ They hurt you at home ♪
♪ And they hit you
at school ♪
♪ They hate you
if you're clever ♪
♪ And they despise a fool ♪
♪ Till you're
so fucking crazy ♪
♪ You can't follow
their rules ♪
♪ A working-class hero
is something to be ♪
I'm home!
♪ A working-class hero
is something to be ♪
♪ If you want to be
a hero ♪
♪ Well, just follow me ♪♪
Babe?
♪♪ [ Continues, Fades ]
[ Woman ]
I'm in the shower.
I-I'll be out in a minute.
I'm just finishing shaving.
What'd you do tonight?
Just busywork
around here.
You're always
doing busywork.
We have a big house.
Running it keeps
a girl busy. Right?
Oh, uh, hon?
Yeah,
just a sec.
You know--
Oh, Jesus, Sophie.
What?
Okay.
Uh, the kid out front?
Could you maybe
say something to him?
Because I don't need
a half-hour of chitchat
every time I pull into my house.
He's your fan.
He's just trying
to impress you.
Well, he's failing.
I'm gonna go rest
before my surprise party.
Oh, goddamn it!
Fucking Frank!
Surprise!
Oh, no!
No way!
You did this?
[ All ]
Aww!
Aw!
You guys should know better.
You know, you don't
surprise a guy my age.
You'll give me a heart attack.
[ Man ] ♪ Whatever gets you
through the night ♪
[ Cheering ]
[ Sniffs ]
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ It's your money
or your life ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Don't need a sword
to cut through flowers ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Whatever gets you
to the light ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Out the blue
or out of sight ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Don't need a gun
to blow your mind ♪♪
♪♪ [ Fades ]
She looks like
a young Jackie 0.
[ Chuckles ]
I look absurd
with her.
Yes, you do.
[ Mutters ]
Yeah.
We have to make her sign
a prenup, don't we?
Yes, we do.
[ Sighs, Sniffs ]
I'm way too old...
to be putting
this much shit
up my nose.
Yes, you are.
Oh, Jesus, Frank.
Don't give me
all the good stuff
at once, will ya.
You're really earning
that 10% tonight, pal.
What do you
want me to say?
"Oh, no, Danny,
you look perfectly normal
standing next to
a coked-up teenager...
who can't
keep her nipples covered
for more than five minutes.
Prenup?
Who needs a prenup?
I mean, sure,
you've gone through
three wives already,
but, uh, this one seems
like the real deal.
Oh, look!
I can see
her vagina again."
[ Laughing ]
That's cute.
Thank you.
I try.
[ Sighs ]
So--
I know how fanatical
you are about Lennon.
So I started futzing around
on the Internet, and I, uh--
[ Chuckles ] I get in touch
with this one guy.
He's a collector.
And I tell him
that I'm looking to
get you something special.
Holy shit.
[ Laughs ]
I've been holding on to this
for three months.
No, no, no, no.
Wait, wait.
Hang on. Wait.
Do you remember
doing an interview
when you were a kid?
Something called,
um, Chime magazine?
Fella named DeLoach?
Yeah. Maybe.
I don't know. Yeah.
I don't know what you said.
You must've mentioned
Lennon or something.
But that doesn't matter.
The point is,
Lennon read it.
The interview.
And... he wrote you
a letter.
What the hell
you talking about?
John Lennon...
wrote you a letter,
pal,
in 1971.
He sent it to you
care of this DeLoach guy.
Now, DeLoach smells money,
so he holds on to it,
never tells you.
Then DeLoach dies.
But he's not the point.
The point is...
he sold that letter...
to a collector.
Can you believe
this shit?
I'm not following this,
Frank.
Open the box.
John Lennon wrote you
a handwritten letter
in 1971.
Can you fuckin'
believe it?
Read it!
[ Chuckles ]
[ Gasps ]
"Dear Danny Collins,
Y-Yoko and I
read your interview.
Being rich and famous
doesn't change
the way you think.
It doesn't corrupt your art.
Only you can do that.
So what do you think
about that, Danny Collins?
Stay true...
to your music.
Stay t-true to yourself.
My phone number
is below.
Call me.
We can discuss this.
We can help.
♪♪ [ Piano ]
Love, John."
It's crazy, right?
I've been
holding on to this
for months now.
[ Lennon ]
♪ Imagine there's no heaven ♪
♪ It's easy if you try ♪
♪ No hell below us ♪
♪ Above us only sky ♪
♪ Imagine all the people ♪
♪ Living for today ♪
♪ I-I, ohh-ohh-ohh ♪
♪ Imagine
there's no countries ♪
♪ It isn't hard to do ♪
♪ Nothing to kill
or die for ♪
♪ And no religion too ♪
[ Engine Stops ]
♪ Imagine all the people ♪
♪ Living life in peace ♪
♪ Yoo-ooh
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ You may say ♪
♪ I'm a dreamer ♪
♪ But I'm not the only one ♪
♪ I hope someday ♪
I'm home!
♪ You'll join us ♪
♪ And the world ♪
♪ Will live as one ♪♪
What you doin'?
Packing.
Oh.
Where are we going?
Well, we're not
going anywhere,
but I'm going away.
Where are you going?
Where?
Where is he?
Who?
Whoever you were
just in bed with, that's who.
Danny, I don't know
what you're tal--
Oh, come on, Sophie.
I didn't pull in
the way I usually do,
so the kid outside
couldn't call you
and stall me.
Okay, listen.
I'm not mad.
I promise you.
I am not mad.
I just want to know
who the fuck is in my house.
That's all.
Hey, wherever you are,
it's okay, I promise!
I'm not mad.
I just wanna
see your face.
Jesus,
just come out.
It's okay.
Busywork.
Judd.
No, Busywork.
I'm gonna call you Busywork
because she's always
doing busywork.
Now I understand.
Okay, kids,
you and Busywork here,
I want you to stay here
for a while if you wish.
It's fine by me.
You're young. Have fun.
I'm looking
for my address book.
'Cause I need an address
in my address book.
And I found it!
Sophie.
I was gonna make you
sign a prenup anyway.
You know?
So you're not missing out
on the big bucks.
If that makes you
feel better. Hmm?
I guess it does
a little.
Okay, you guys, I'm off.
And, Busywork--
Um, take care of her.
Okay?
My parents
had their first dance to
one of your songs... sir.
Yeah.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, that's fucked up
in all kinds of ways,
now, isn't it?
♪♪ [ Guitar ]
[ Danny ]
Hey, man.
Uh, listen.
I need a plane.
Jersey.
♪♪ [ Continues ]
Yeah, New Jersey.
[ Lennon ]
♪ Hold on, John ♪
Yeah. Uh, a car.
You know what I like.
Make it red.
Yeah.
I'm changing shit up.
♪ You're gonna
win the fight ♪
♪ Hold on, world ♪
What are you doing?
Place is dead.
♪ World, hold on ♪
There's a dental convention
here this week.
Like, four people
have been here.
[ Engine Racing ]
Oh, shit.
♪ Oh, and when you're one ♪
♪ Really one ♪
♪ Well, you get things done ♪
♪ Like they've never
been done ♪
Oh, shit!
All right!
♪ So hold on ♪♪
Welcome to the Hilton,
Danny Collins.
I mean, Mr. Collins.
I mean, uh--
- Welcome to the Hilton, sir.
- It's good to be here
at the Hilton.
But you can call me Danny.
And what should I call you?
Uh, N-Nicky Ernst.
Nicky Ernst.
Absolute pleasure
to meet you.
You got a great face,
Nicky.
May I give you
a hundred bucks?
Try not to drool
on the car, Nicky.
Okay.
Welcome to the Hilton.
Do you have a reservation?
No.
But I hope that's
not a deal-breaker,
because I am rapidly
falling in love
with this here Hilton.
Holy shit.
Holy shit!
[ Laughs ]
I get that a lot.
What's your name?
Um, uh, Jamie.
Jamie.
- I'm Danny.
- Yeah, I know who you are.
How about
that guy out front?
Nicky Ernst.
He's a great guy.
Great face.
Why don't you let him
take you out for a ride
in my car?
You'll fall in love.
Oh? Okay. Okay.
Look at that face.
Why does everybody here
have such great faces?
And so young.
Why are you all
so young?
We're just college kids.
Just graduated, or--
I-I'm off for the summer.
- That explains it.
- [ Laughs ]
Uh, how long will you be
staying with us, Mr. Collins?
Well, I don't know.
My GPS tells me
that this is not far from
Hillsdale, New Jersey.
Now, is my GPS lying
or giving me
the straight shit?
Straight shit.
You're five minutes away.
Okay.
I will stay here.
Indefinitely.
Um-- Hang on.
Mary!
Man, if another
wonderful face
comes out of there,
I-I don't think
I can handle it.
Oh!
That's it.
I definitely
can't handle it.
[ Giggling ]
Look who it is.
I see.
[ Laughs ]
Hi.
He wants to stay indefinitely,
and I can give him
the honeymoon suite, but--
He doesn't want
the honeymoon suite.
It's not my honeymoon.
And I'm not very sweet.
Any room will suit me fine.
And what college
do you go to, young lady?
[ Snickers ]
Ha.
Ha-ha?
[ Laughs ]
[ Laughing ]
So you're staying
indefinitely? Here?
Yeah, I'm a huge fan
of this Hilton.
- Are you married, Mary?
- Uh-- I'm sorry?
Are you currently
betrothed?
- No.
- Good. Dinner.
- You're asking me to dinner?
- Yes. I think so.
- Jamie, I asked her
to dinner, didn't I?
- Yep. Yeah, you did.
Proof.
- I'm sorry. Are you on drugs?
- Currently or in general?
- Currently.
- No.
- Dinner?
- No. I'm gonna
have to decline.
- You're not a fan?
- Currently or in general?
- In general.
- No.
Oh, that's too bad.
But we have good patter.
[ Laughing ]
Don't we?
Don't we, Jamie?
You following
any of this, are you?
No.
Look, I'll check you in.
Okay?
While you're checking me in,
I'll check you out.
[ Laughs ]
- Oh, my God.
- [ All Laughing ]
[ Chuckles ]
Okay.
[ Door Closes ]
You know, I never--
I never actually saw this
being done.
[ Danny ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[ Thuds ]
- Damn!
- Watch the door. Okay.
[ Grunting ]
[ Muttering ]
Danny?
Hey.
Frank. Oh, man.
Come to Papa.
[ Chuckles ]
Good to see you,
buddy.
Oh, what a trip, huh?
Got on
the first flight out.
Thanks, Frank.
You been here before?
The bar at
the Woodcliff Lake,
New Jersey, Hilton?
No.
[ Laughs ]
[ Sighs ]
Oh, man.
I, uh, spoke to Sophie.
She said, uh, you--
I did. I did.
Josh,
you wanna give us
ice water...
for my handsome
young friend here?
Frank, I decided to make
some changes in my life.
Uh, s--
some of the changes
may come as
a bit of a shock.
Some may actually
affect you financially.
I'm, uh, here
as your friend, Danny,
not as your manager.
I want to cancel
the rest of the tour.
I'm sorry?
I'm not sorry.
I'm done, Frank.
Done.
So help me God,
I will never be forced
to sing those songs again.
Danny, you're spiraling.
Are you on something?
What are you taking?
I'm done with
all of that shit too.
No more.
No more drinking,
no more drugging.
You're drinking
right now, Danny.
True.
L-Let's forget
about what I said
about drinking.
I mean, I'm not
running for pope.
And this is
because of Sophie?
[ Laughing ]
Frank, please.
Give me a little
credit, will ya?
Sophie?
Okay.
What would have happened
if I'd got that letter
when I was supposed to?
I would have
called him.
For as sure as shit,
I'd have called.
Maybe my whole life
would have
turned out different.
No. No, you're--
You're too hard
on yourself, kid.
You always have been.
Come on.
Frank.
I haven't written a song
in 30 years.
[ Scoffs ]
Thirty years.
I'm a fucking joke.
I'm an emcee.
Fuckin' court jester
with a microphone.
I was the real thing
once.
Right?
I was
the real thing.
One album,
my songs didn't sell.
They handed me
their songs to sing.
And I sung 'em.
Mmm.
I gave up.
Danny,
you're having a breakdown.
I hate to tell you,
buddy.
I've been breaking down
for 40 years.
I'm broken.
Ain't nothin' left
to break.
I've been abusing my body
for the better part
of four decades.
If I'm gonna find
any kind of redemption,
I can't waste
any more time.
But why the fuck
New Jersey?
One shock at a time,
Frank.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
Hey, Jamie. You talk to
that kid Nicky Ernst
about that ride yet?
Not yet,
Mr. Collins.
Gotta do it.
Uh, meet me at 7:00
for dinner.
Still gonna
have to pass.
Mary, you keep passing,
I'll keep making passes,
and we'll see who quits first.
Have a nice day,
Mr. Collins.
Big day.
Big day for me.
I'm meeting someone
for the first time.
How do I look?
Honestly?
If this relationship
is gonna go the distance, Mary,
I think we should be
honest with one another.
Okay.
Well, you--
you look
slightly ridiculous.
Nah.
I look sharp.
See you at 7:00.
No, you won't.
Hey, Jamie.
Don't forget about Nicky.
He's a wonderful boy.
Don't say anything
to anyone.
Nicky Ernst!
It's ready for you,
sir.
Oh, man, I don't know
what you did to that girl
inside, but, wow!
All she does
is talk about you.
You should ask her out.
- Jamie?
- That's the one.
Don't go after Mary.
Mary's mine.
[ Tires Screech ]
[ Engine Revs, Stops ]
I like your lawn.
Thank you.
Hello!
- Hello.
- [ Woman ] Hope, you're not to
open the door to strangers.
He's not a stranger.
We saw him on TV!
Told you.
Oh.
[ Hope, Singsongy ]
I told you.
You didn't listen,
but I tried to tell you.
I was unsure of, um,
what was appropriate.
- He's at work.
- I-I--
I brought bagels.
[ Hope ]
One, two, three.
♪ The itsy-bitsy spider
came up the water spout ♪
[ Danny ]
Yeah!
♪ Down came the rain ♪
♪ And it washed
the spider out ♪
♪ Out came the sun ♪
♪ And dried up
all the rain ♪
- ♪ And the itsy-bitsy spider ♪
- ♪♪ [ Singing Along ]
♪ Climbed up the spout again ♪♪
That's beautiful.
You have
a natural singing voice.
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
Oh, my God.
Just comes out
naturally.
How did you
find us?
Oh, well, you know,
I had tracked him down
years ago, you know.
Just never got the nerve up
to, uh, come see him.
I want a bagel!
- Can I have a bagel, Mom?
- Yeah, okay. Let me get--
Wow.
On so many levels,
wow.
H-How far along
are you?
Oh, w-- Oh.
Um, six months,
more or less.
Oh.
Uh, boy or girl?
Do you know?
It's a boy.
Oh. Boy. Wow.
On so many levels.
[ Danny ]
Yeah.
I have to call him.
[ Danny ]
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, sure, sure.
I just finished
the first grade.
And my teacher
is named Mrs. Williams.
Can you grab him for me?
Her aunt died last week,
so we had a substitute.
[ Whispers ]
He had a mustache.
- She had a mustache?
- He.
Oh, it was a he.
Oh. Okay.
Why are you on TV?
Because I'm a singer.
Are you
a good singer?
Well, I don't know,
you know. Not really.
[ Whispers ]
I didn't think so.
[ Mother ] Hope!
- You didn't think so?
- [ Hope Giggles ]
A-A-And why--
why didn't you think so?
Because when you were
on the TV, my daddy said,
"Shut it off, Samantha!"
And Mommy turned it off
really fast.
And Mommy said, "Tom!"
And Daddy said, "N-O!"
And that was that.
Wow.
Well--
- But I thought you
were great. Really.
- You thought I was good?
Um, Danny Collins
showed up at our house.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
He's having bagels
in the kitchen with Hope.
- Why don't we
take a break from that.
- Okay. Let's just color.
[ Danny ]
Look at this.
I'm starting to get it.
- What was I supposed to--
- Well, you do it really slow.
I do.
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Bye, honey.
- [ Hope ] Didn't I
already tell you that?
- You did?
You told me that.
Well,
he's coming home.
- Yay!
- Daddy's coming home.
That should be,
uh, interesting.
This is gonna be
Interesting.
- ♪♪ [ Singing ]
- Mommy, look!
It's Yo Gabba Gabba!
I see it.
The orange alien guy
has one eye
just in the middle!
Look what's on TV!
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, Hope.
Settle. Calm.
[ Sighs ]
Thank you.
Okay.
Uh, you know,
she seems
a little, uh,
energetic, you know.
Or severely hyperactive.
You know-- ADHD.
It's the thing.
Learning issues,
behavioral stuff,
all of it.
We do the best we can,
but it's-- it's a battle.
Why are you here?
Well, you know,
[ Sighs ]
I'm just, uh,
making some changes
in my life, so--
It's a little late
for that, isn't it?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I hope not.
Tom's the best man
I've ever met.
He's solid and kind.
Funny.
We've had one fight in 12 years.
We've had one serious fight.
A couple years ago
I got backstage passes
for one of your shows.
I thought it was--
You know, he should
at least meet you. Right?
After all this time.
He disagreed.
He--
He disagreed strongly.
So this is not
gonna be pretty.
I wouldn't think so, no.
Okay.
S-So you think maybe,
uh, you know,
you could help
grease the wheels
a little?
[ Sighs ]
Mr. Collins.
My parents are dead.
His mom is too.
I mean, I would love
for our children to know
their one remaining grandparent.
I-I would love for my husband
to-- to know his father.
In a few minutes,
my husband's gonna
walk through that door,
and when he does I feel
pretty confident this'll be
the last time I ever see you.
And despite
your celebrity...
and despite what I want
for my own family,
I will not
try to stop that.
You did this.
You did this to yourself.
Shame on you.
That was good.
Thanks. I've been practicing
since you gave me the bagels.
[ Laughs ]
No, it has
a certain feel to me.
Oh, he married well.
He did.
I'm great.
Yeah.
You see
what you missed out on?
Perfect daughter-in-law.
[ Vehicle Door
Opens, Closes ]
[ Footsteps ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
i-i-i-introducing--
Well--
Daddy! Daddy!
Look who it is!
It's the man from TV
that we saw singing!
And Mommy said, "Whoa!"
And he brought bagels!
Okay, whoa. Easy.
Mommy called you!
And you're home early!
Hope,
your favorite flower
is a--
Rose.
To smell it
you breathe through your--
[ Inhales ]
Keep it in,
long as you can go.
Then let it out
in one big...
[ Exhales ]
blow.
- Hi, honey.
- Hey, baby.
Can I speak to you
outside for a second?
Of course. Sure.
Okay.
Um, if I have,
I am truly very sorry
that I missed out on you.
Thank you
for the bagels.
Okay.
Hope, say good-bye
to Mr. Collins.
Good-bye, Mr. Collins!
Mr. Collins,
say good-bye to Hope.
Good-bye to Hope.
Come here.
You're so tall.
I'm sorry.
What exactly do you want?
Oh, you know--
Are you sick?
Is that
what you're doing here?
Are you dying?
No, I'm not sick.
You have every right
to be angry.
No, no. I'm not angry.
Really, I'm not.
I'm a little confused
and, strangely,
not interested.
So if you have anything
to ask me, just go ahead,
'cause this is the last time
we'll see each other.
So what do you do
for a living?
I work construction.
Local, residential.
It's not my dream job,
but it's steady...
and, you know, Princeton
wasn't exactly in the cards.
What else?
Your mom.
She-- She, uh--
She died of cancer
10 years ago.
Never married.
Never spoke about you.
Except to say that it was
a wild thing she did
when she was 23...
and got drunk backstage
after one of your concerts.
I use her last name.
Anything else?
- You're clearly angry.
- I don't care enough
to be angry.
I am wondering what
I'm gonna tell my little girl
about who you are.
And I'm thinking I have to be
back at work in 20 minutes.
Are we done here?
- I sent checks.
- I ripped them up. Okay?
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Have a good life.
Are you happy?
Am I happy?
I don't know.
You--
You have a happy life?
[ Scoffs ]
I hate my boss.
Fucking Mets
break my heart every year.
But I have
the most amazing wife
in the history of wives...
and an amazing little girl,
one that I wish
I could do more for.
That I really wish
I could do.
But if it makes you
sleep better at night,
yeah, I'm happy.
And fuck you,
you selfish prick.
I am angry.
♪♪ [ Ballad ]
[ Lennon ]
♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ Close your eyes ♪
♪ Have no fear ♪
♪ The monster's gone ♪
♪ He's on the run ♪
♪ And your daddy's here ♪
♪ Beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful ♪
♪ Beautiful boy ♪
♪ Darling,
darling, darling ♪
♪ Darling boy ♪♪
Mr. Collins.
Mmm.
How we doing tonight?
[ Sighs ]
Peachy.
Thank you for asking.
Oh, good.
I'm really glad
to hear that.
Mr. Collins,
I was wondering if you could
help me with something.
Shoot.
Okay.
When a famous musician
starts getting fall-down drunk
in a hotel bar...
and you're the manager
of that hotel,
is there a protocol on
how to handle the situation?
Because actually,
we have had a shortage...
of famous fall-down-drunk
musicians lately.
I'm a bit
out of my depth.
I see.
Well, you know,
I had a bad day.
Oh. Okay.
This is just water.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's just because
you drank all the booze
and the ice is melted.
Don't be mean to me.
I really had a bad day.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, I had a bad day too.
Oh, yeah?
Can I buy you a drink?
A Bay Breeze?
A wine spritzer?
Maybe even
one of them frozen--
Josh, give me tequila,
rocks-- something añejo--
and a splash of soda.
Right away, boss.
You're not
the only rock star
in this hotel.
Apparently not.
[ Sighs ]
So...
you had a bad day?
Mmm.
Why'd you have
a bad day?
Okay, I work with
a bunch of well-meaning--
Thank you--
but remarkably dim
20-somethings...
who are just passing time
until they go back to college.
One of them screwed up
the computer system,
and it took me half the day
to reprogram
every reservation manually.
Mmm. Ah.
What about you?
I tracked down
my grown son...
who I never met before.
And I met him, his wife,
my granddaughter.
And then he told me,
quite emphatically,
to fuck off and to die.
Well, it was
every reservation.
Each one had to be
reprogrammed manually.
I hope I made that clear.
Can I ask you
a question?
Not if it's about
why I never met my son
till today.
Oh, shit.
Well, that was my question.
We lost our patter.
Mmm.
It's gone.
You know,
I saw you in concert once,
about five years ago.
- You did?
- Yeah, my husband was--
my ex-husband,
he was a big fan.
Oh, he loved it.
And you?
I-- I appreciated your zeal.
Oh, shit.
What?
Zeal is not awful.
Zeal's not great.
Hear us?
"Zeal's not awful."
"Zeal's not great."
[ Laughing ]
We got our patter back.
How about that?
We should take this
on the road.
You and me,
the new Nichols and May.
Well, May and Nichols.
I-I would want top billing.
You're good.
I want to drink to you.
Toast.
O-Okay.
You'll have to come
a little closer.
Oh, that was so good.
See how I work it?
What does that drink need?
It needs a lemon.
No!
Okay!
Ohh!
Then he writes,
"What do you think of that,
Danny Collins?"
John Lennon?
John Lennon writes,
"What do you think about that,
Danny Collins"?
Yeah.
Well, you know, John,
I think...
maybe, uh,
you should have sent
the letter to my house.
And then maybe
I could have avoided...
living such a bullshit life
for the past 40 years.
That's what I think,
John.
Well, I may have
that last sip.
[ Laughing ]
I-I'm sorry.
I'm a little giddy.
No, I usually don't
drink this much.
You've emptied it.
I wonder
if anyone's noticing.
There's one of those people
at the desk--
No, the girl at the desk.
She's the one that screwed up
the computer.
This is
Danny Collins.
Oh, geez.
He's our guest.
Do you have
a name, sir?
Uh, Hiroshi.
That's nice.
Hiroshi.
This is my daughter.
She's 18.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Wow.
Don't say it like that.
[ Laughing ]
I'm ready.
Okay.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, my God!
It just turns me on!
[ Mary ]
Rick and I split last year.
Most parents, they try
to wait till their kids
leave for college.
But we actually
did the opposite.
We tried to do it at the time
that it would really
screw her up the most.
[ Danny ]
Well, did it work?
Yes.
Yeah, perfect.
She's a complete mess.
Hates us both.
Guess what.
What?
She hates him more.
Oh, that's perfect.
My second wife
actually was one of the stars
of Gilligan's Island.
Ginger.
No.
Mary Ann?
Yeah.
Wait. That's insane.
I know.
You were married
to Mary Ann?
Yes.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, my God.
So what's she like?
I don't remember.
"Doesn't corrupt your art.
Only you can do that.
So what do you think about that,
Danny Collins?"
That is unreal.
Yeah.
You know, you better have
something to play me,
because if this is
just a lame attempt
to get me to your room, then--
[ Both Laugh ]
I have something
to play you.
Oh.
- Yes.
- You're really gonna play?
Now, I haven't
written anything
in a long time.
Uh, and piano's
not my first language.
Piano's my first love,
but it's not
my first language.
- You're nervous.
- Yes.
I love that.
So what?
So bear with me.
♪ It's spring ♪
♪ In my mind ♪
♪ But the autumn leaves ♪
♪ They fall ♪
♪♪ [ Chord ]
Oh, keep going.
Keep going.
That's it.
That's as far as I got.
Honestly, this kinda
was just a lame attempt
to get you up to my room.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, no, no, no,
don't g--
Good night, Danny.
No, stay.
Come on.
I'm an old man
with 10 scotches in him.
What am I gonna do?
[ Laughing ]
Please.
The chances of anything
risqué happening
is so fucking remote--
Good night, Danny.
Good night, Mary.
Good night.
You know, that song--
it's beautiful.
It's just a little short.
But other than that,
it's beautiful.
Thank you.
And you know what we were
talking about before?
You shouldn't give up.
I agree.
Yeah.
Dinner tomorrow?
Not that.
Your son.
Oh, yeah.
I know.
Okay. But don't give up
on dinner either.
Oh, dinner!
Uh, tonight?
[ Door Closes ]
She'll have dinner with me.
That's right.
A six-year-old girl.
Well, money's no issue, so--
I'm running my operation
out of the business center.
He said he was
sending it to me.
[ Chattering ]
Well, I haven't
gotten it yet.
Yeah, it's for
my granddaughter.
What's he doing?
He's bitch-slappin'
the business center
is what he's--
Hey.
[ Bus Horn Honks ]
[ Brakes Hiss ]
Hey, Ray!
Steve, Mr. Collins.
Ah, y-you'll always
be Ray to me.
Ha!
Fine.
- Oh, fuck me.
- Language, dear.
We don't want
your music!
You don't want my music?
Tom explained to Hope
how you're a musician,
and sometimes musicians
travel door-to-door
to sell their music.
Just like Girl Scouts
sell their cookies.
And sometimes you don't
want Girl Scout cookies,
so we're not being rude.
- Yeah, we're not rude.
- Just don't want any.
I get it.
Okay.
Possibly
a more complicated
explanation...
than is required
for a seven-year-old.
Possibly.
You know what?
I get it.
- Mommy, do you see this?
- [ Danny ]
Hey, Jimmy!
- Hey, Hope-- Sorry. Hope.
- No, no, it's okay.
See?
No, no, he's got her.
Thank you, Jimmy.
So what, are you just
out running some errands?
Yeah, I was
in the neighborhood,
so, you know--
Are you fucking kidding me?
[ Danny ]
Look! There's three of us.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- You heard of the New
Compass School in Manhattan?
What?
It's the most progressive
private school in the country.
It's got, uh,
"a multimodal
approach...
toward treating children
with learning issues,
particularly ADHD."
I pulled some strings
and you have an interview
in two hours.
[ Hope ]
It has a shower!
I know.
You can go in there.
It doesn't work.
Do you really think
we haven't looked into
every school there is?
Not this one.
How do you
know that?
Well, you know,
you can't afford it.
[ Sighs ] Steven,
would you mind your own
fucking business, please.
I'm sorry. You mean
that we have an interview
as our family. Today.
In two hours.
At the New Compass School.
People wait two years
for such an interview.
Two years.
You have it in two hours.
Just give me a day
to do something good
for you.
And then, you know,
I'm gone, forever.
And you still go to heaven
because you're so damn tolerant.
And I will still go to hell
because, you know,
you can't buy redemption.
Everybody wins.
Let's do this thing.
Come on.
Bring your friends.
You have friends?
We got room.
Hey!
[ Hope ]
This thing's insane!
This school,
it's not like there's
a two-year wait.
It's, like,
there's a six-year wait.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I'm gonna get Hope
and you put on a shirt
with some fucking buttons.
Hey, Hope.
Come here, baby.
[ Brakes Hiss ]
Everything
is back there!
I love it!
It's so cool!
- And I love
everything in it!
- [ Tom ] Okay.
It looks like
it could be a house!
Maybe he lives in here!
Shh.
I'm sure he really does,
but it's still cool!
And I can't even
stop talking!
[ Danny ] I wrote him,
and then I talked to him
on the phone.
So, do you know
Dr. Kurtz?
Sometimes he does
a talk-back thing
on his blog.
On his what?
His blog.
He writes a blog.
What's a block?
A blog.
It's a--
I can't believe
I'm gonna meet him.
Everything
is on this bus!
[ Woman ]
We're all gonna draw
our inner animals.
This is a school?
The blog
doesn't do it justice.
I know.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry I'm dressed
like Jack LaLanne.
Elastic only on the weekends.
I'm Dr. Kurtz.
I--
Shock-a-ma-lyah!
You really are
Danny Collins!
Yes, I am.
You're really Dr. Kurtz.
You really are
Danny Collins!
Tom Donnelly.
My wife, Samantha.
My daughter, Hope.
My balls are in her purse,
in case you wanna
meet them later.
It's a lot different
than talking on the phone.
Well, I hope so.
You must be Hope.
I'm Tom.
Tom.
Then you must be Hope.
Hi. Samantha Donnelly.
I follow you on Twitter.
Well, thank you, but--
She reads your blog.
Then wh-who's Hope?
I'm Hope! Over here!
That's me! I'm seven!
I'm Hope!
How are you?
Let me show you around!
Come on, you.
You started all this.
[ Danny ]
Oh, I did.
- Mom, Dad! You're not
gonna believe it!
- Hope. Hope!
She's okay.
She'll be all right.
She's fine.
It was in the first grade
when we started to notice that
she was having some trouble.
Yeah, we got a tutor
for her once a week,
and I do these exercises
with her every night, really.
Every night.
But she's got trouble
with focus.
It's been a real struggle
for us. Really.
Yeah. Yeah.
Most schools try
to train children like Hope
to fit into their systems.
We prefer to tailor a program
to the child's needs.
It's like one big IEP here.
Individualized
Educational Program?
IEP?
You've been doing
your homework, Mr. Collins.
Got it right here.
[ Chuckles ]
Come on. Let me
show you the rest.
Do you remember who did
the original assessment?
You having fun?
A little, yeah.
I'm very excited.
[ Kurtz ]
We're only half speed
during our summer programs,
but you can still
get a sense of the place.
[ Danny ] Oh, yeah.
I got a sense of it already.
How about that, huh?
[ Samantha ] So, is this just
"K" through five, or all the way
"K" through eight?
No, elementary and middle.
We'd carry her through the
eighth grade, then place her
in one of our accredited--
No, no, no.
We live in New Jersey.
We can't come all the way in.
No, she'll have a driver.
Every day to
and from school.
Every day,
through college.
I'll put that
in writing.
Guaranteed.
A more formal interview
is required, obviously,
but considering Mr. Collins's
generous donation and what
I see in Hope's records,
I suspect the interview
will go well.
You have a lot to discuss,
but trust me, you want this.
This can change
the course of Hope's life.
I'll give you guys a minute.
- Thank you, Doc.
- Got a good grandpa.
Thank you, man.
Thank you so much for--
Thank you.
Yeah.
So, now that
the educational portion
of the day is over,
uh, let's get
to the fun stuff.
What fun stuff? I--
No, we're just gonna
go back home. Right?
No, you said a day.
Remember?
No, I didn't.
We agreed to it.
Samantha!
- Yes, he did.
- I don't think "agreed"
is the word.
- I didn't agree to a day.
- Samantha. For God's sake.
Okay.
Samantha,
you were there.
We agreed.
We agreed to a day.
And when I check it,
day ain't over yet.
It's not over, Dad!
Ha-ha-ha!
Every single thing
he says upsets me.
One day. It's just one day.
[ Brakes Hiss ]
[ Samantha Sighs ]
[ Tom ]
Got her?
- Stay here. I got her.
- Kiss?
Stay there.
Okay.
I wanna say something,
but I'm afraid
I'm gonna be too nice.
Good night, Samantha.
Thank you.
Jimmy, you wanna
help her, please?
Watch your head, honey.
Thank you so much, Jimmy.
Thank you, guys.
Hey, Jimmy.
Give us a minute?
Thanks.
You are
a ridiculous man.
You know, I've spent
my entire life...
trying to become
the man that you aren't.
But I'm exhausted.
You have no idea
how exhausting that has been.
You know,
when I met your mom,
I was so strung out...
on God knows what.
And when I found out,
you know,
I, uh--
I tried to help.
Send money.
She wouldn't
have any of it.
Refused it.
But, you know,
my life was so extreme.
It was so full
of drugs and women
and traveling...
and all that
rock star shit.
I always thought,
whoever you were,
that you'd be better off
with a more normal life,
more normal people.
I-- I don't know...
how I allowed it
to go on this long.
What you did today--
Your slate's clean with me.
But that's as far
as this goes. Okay?
I want to be
a part of your life.
It's not a good time right now.
This is not the right time.
Okay?
Why is this
not the right time?
It's not the right time.
What's the matter?
I'm sick.
Shit.
You're sick?
What do you mean?
It's what Mom died--
It's in the blood.
It's pretty bad.
Fuck.
You're kidding me.
[ Sighs ]
I just met you.
You gotta be
fucking kidding me!
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
Obviously, that
wasn't a great thing,
a great reaction.
I'm sorry.
No, that's okay.
It's okay, man.
Look-- Look, I'm the one
that should be sorry.
I mean, after all, you're--
you're Danny Collins, right?
I mean, uh, who the fuck am I
to get in the way
of your happy ending?
Tom. Tom.
Let me ask you
something.
How did you think
this was gonna end--
that little movie you've
got going on in your head?
What, you thought
you'd just show up
out of the blue,
out of nowhere really,
and fix my little girl...
and then what--
you and me hold hands and cry
as the music swells?
Is that it?
Don't you fucking touch me.
Don't fucking touch me!
All right.
Hey, you want a little bit
of the real world, huh?
You wanna do like normal?
How's this for normal,
superstar?
I got a $200,000 mortgage.
I got a pregnant wife.
And, oh, yeah, I got
this rare form of leukemia...
that's probably
gonna kill me.
Welcome home, Dad.
See what you missed?
- I don't know what to say.
- I don't need you to
say anything, man.
I just need you to leave.
Let me go back inside
and talk to my wife...
before she asks me
what we're talking about.
Wait, wait. Hold it.
She doesn't know?
[ Scoffs ]
Are you crazy?
That's no good, man.
Look, I got a great doctor
in New York.
He's talkin' about three weeks
of this target therapy shit.
I'm not gonna lose my hair.
Within a month,
they know if it's taken.
If it's taken,
then maybe I stand a chance.
And if it doesn't,
then it happens quick.
But Sam is six months
into a rough pregnancy,
so I'll tell her
after the baby.
I'm going to Delaware
on a job.
That's what she knows.
You're going to need help.
You have a friend?
She's my friend.
Then, uh, whatever.
I'll be there.
I mean,
what else is there?
Be where?
Wherever.
I mean, you need me,
I'll be--
No, no, no, no.
I don't need you.
No, you do.
That's not what
this is about.
It's not open
for discussion.
But--
This is not open
for discussion.
You're gonna have to
deal with it...
because I'm here
to fuckin' stay.
[ Lennon ]
Three, four!
♪♪ [ Pop ]
♪ Everybody's talking,
but no one says a word ♪
♪ Everybody's making love
and no one really cares ♪
[ Loud Clattering ]
[ Branch Snaps ]
♪ There's Nazis in the bathroom
just below the stairs ♪
♪ Nobody told me
there'd be days like these ♪
there'd be days like these ♪♪
Hi.
Hey.
So, how'd it go?
Well, yeah.
You know, it was just--
You know, yeah.
No, I get it.
I get it.
Family can be messy.
Right?
Yeah, that is true.
That is definitely true.
In this case, yes.
Exactly. I mean, you're
meeting your grown son
for the first time.
You didn't expect it
to be easy, right?
I thought it'd be
fuckin' easier than this.
[ Laughs ]
Right. Yeah.
You know, every part
of me right now...
would like to just go in there
and get soused with you.
But... I'm going to
go upstairs instead.
That's good, right?
Yeah. No.
There's a piano up there
with your name on it.
Only if my name is Steinway.
So we got
our patter back.
You're cool.
I-- I am not cool.
Yes, you are.
I am not cool.
[ Danny ]
♪ It's spring in my mind ♪
♪ But the autumn leaves,
they fall ♪
♪ As I ♪
It's just a few weeks--
♪ Am walking by ♪
♪ I collect them all ♪
[ Doctor ]
Now, I have had success
with this in the past,
but I'm not gonna lie
to you, Mr. Donnelly.
The next several weeks
aren't gonna be pretty.
♪ Like the people I have known ♪
Most people are a little alarmed
at how awful it can get.
And that will get worse.
♪ And the people
I have known ♪
So, uh, this okay here?
♪ Their names ♪
♪ Upon a scroll ♪
♪ And the list
goes on and on ♪
[ Together ]
Who is Jackie Joyner-Kersee?
[ Sighs ]
[ Buzzing ]
♪ I carried my burden ♪
♪ Like it was never there ♪
[ Danny ]
You don't like
chicken noodle soup?
How the fuck can you not
like chicken noodle soup?
I don't like noodles.
Okay?
Make me think of worms.
♪ I'm walking blind
upon this road ♪
♪ In search of
higher ground ♪
Surprise.
♪ Don't look back ♪
[ Tom ]
My uncle took me fishing
one time.
He took the worm, put it
in his mouth and he ate it
just to fuck with me.
And now, whenever
I see a noodle,
I think of my fat slob
of an uncle eating a worm,
and it freaks me out.
♪ And I want ♪
♪ To be strong ♪
[ Whispering ]
Well, look at this.
This technique.
[ Samantha ]
You made the picture.
I made the picture.
Yeah.
Don't get cocky.
What kind of uncle
screws up a little kid,
makes him phobic
about chicken noodle soup?
That I don't get.
Get out!
♪♪ [ Piano ]
♪ In my mind,
it's still spring ♪
"A," "B" minor, C-sharp.
I don't know
what that means.
No, no.
Let me teach you.
[ Sighs ]
Let me teach you,
you petulant little fucker.
♪ Stumbling round
strange houses ♪
Okay, Tom,
so three weeks from today,
we'll go over
the test results together,
and that'll dictate
what our next steps should be.
But for now let's just
hope for the best.
Stay positive, all right?
Yeah, thank you.
Thanks, Doc.
Thank you.
♪ For the light ♪
♪ And I'm walking blind
upon this road ♪
♪ In search of higher ground ♪
♪ I'm walking blind
upon this road ♪
♪ In search of higher ground ♪
♪ Walking blind
upon this road ♪
♪ In search of higher ground ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ And don't look down ♪♪
[ Knocking ]
Ah. Come in!
It's the "unbolty" thing.
[ Door Closes ]
Hi.
Yeah, so,
I got your note.
Yeah? So?
What do you think?
Well, okay. Okay.
"Pictures from my life
as I'm walking down the hall.
♪♪ [ Tentative Melody ]
As I'm walking by,
I collect them all."
What do you think?
Well--
You're aware that
I have no basis in musical
knowledge or theory.
Okay.
Okay?
So, you still
want my opinion?
Of course.
Well, I think I kinda
liked it better the way
it was-- with the leaves.
Really?
Yeah, the leaves and--
Yeah.
Me too.
- I just wanted to get you
back in my room again.
- Oh!
So now I can ask you
out to dinner. Right?
Play this in a concert, okay?
Then you can take me to dinner.
[ Knocking ]
You're a dinner tease.
- I am not a dinner tease.
- You're a huge dinner tease.
I found you out!
Oh, you're terrible.
This is my second time
in New Jersey in two months.
I am not happy about that.
Frank. Oh, gee.
I owed you a call.
Oh, Frank.
I'm so sorry.
But you know
what it's like
when I'm workin'.
[ Door Closes ]
I've been so busy.
Yeah, apparently.
[ Frank Chuckles ]
May I?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
This is Frank Grubman,
my manager
and my best friend.
Hello.
This is Mary.
She's my new girlfriend.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, really?
Well, I'm working on it.
You know, I mean--
She's a big dinner tease.
I am not.
Yes, yes, yes.
She keeps moving
the goal post. No?
[ Clears Throat ]
Mary, would you mind if I had
a word with Danny in private?
Oh, no, of course.
Of course. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Yeah, I think
you've said enough.
[ Laughing ]
Okay! Dinner tonight.
You know,
you're ridiculous.
- She's lovely.
- And age appropriate.
- No, not really.
- Baby steps.
Yeah. Sit, sit, sit.
We need to talk.
I know.
There's a lot I want
to tell you, pal.
Unfortunately,
I have my manager hat
on right now.
Okay.
What's up?
I've been going
over things with Bill.
And you're not exactly
where you think you are.
Okay. Where am I?
A little ahead
when we sell properties,
but only a little.
I mean, we shouldn't
have sold your publishing
rights so early.
All those properties--
the housing market
has collapsed.
The private plane,
your lifestyle.
The Madoff thing--
that absolutely killed you,
as you know.
But you're not bankrupt
or anything.
It's just that
you need to understand
how serious it is.
Okay.
So what do I do?
One of two things.
You start living
like a normal human.
You buy a Prius,
you fly Continental.
You know,
that kind of shit.
Or you go back on tour.
And this last tour
was my retirement plan
for you.
I mean,
we had a big piece.
I know.
Concessions!
Merchandise!
I know. I know.
I'm-- I'm writing, Frank.
Oh, Danny.
I'm telling you,
it's good.
Mary thinks
it's really good.
Oh, the Woodcliff Lake
hotel manager?
Oh, oh, okay.
Well, now I feel
much better.
Just get me a gig.
A gig?
A gig, yeah.
Something small,
not a big arena.
Just, you know,
something like Springsteen
would go do.
[ Laughing ]
Like Springsteen
would do.
Yeah, he just pops
into these places.
Oh, Danny, Danny,
Danny, Danny.
Do you even
hear yourself?
This stuff is good.
Just give it a chance.
And then we'll tour.
And the bonus
is that, uh,
I won't think about
killing myself every night.
Okay?
Okay.
[ Glass Clinks ]
Okay, I'm going to
make an announcement.
All right.
Are you ready?
Yup.
Uh, I'll be playing
a gig in a bar.
Oh, a gig.
On Friday night.
Gig.
What's a gig?
A gig.
A gig is where I sing
in front of people.
- I wanna hear you sing.
- And I want you
to hear me sing.
I want you to hear me sing
more than anything in the world.
But we have to check it out
through Mom and Pop...
and see if it's okay.
- It's at a bar, huh?
- I'm gonna go to a gig
at a bar.
Oh, it's an upscale bar.
You know, it's got--
What's an upscale bar?
With the appropriate
cocktail menu.
- Cover charge.
- Cover charge. Really?
You're doing things
with cover charges now?
This place big enough for you
to be able to do your moves?
Oh, man, nothing
holds my moves back.
That's what
we're looking for.
Your moves.
Huh? Another Danny Collins?
I think it's called
the Danny Collins.
♪ Hey, baby doll
What's goin' on? ♪
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't want that
to start.
So what do you think?
Show starts 7:30.
Done by 9:00.
9:00?
Yeah, that's late.
[ Tom ]
That's late.
Not too late.
You sure your crowd's gonna be
able to stay awake till 9:00?
- They gonna be conscious?
- [ Laughing ]
We're going to
have to call the club
and let them know...
there might be
a whole room full
of snoring old ladies.
I'm going to give them a call
and give them a heads-up,
make sure they know.
Oh, you're so kind.
So what are we going to do?
We going to get your permission?
Are we going to get
Mommy and Daddy
to say yes, it's okay?
Because
it's a big thing for me.
And it would help
if I had these cheeks here.
These cheeks
will be there.
There you go.
[ Laughing ]
From the cheeksy-mouth.
[ Coughing ]
Babe.
Do you hear this?
It's been going on for--
When are you going to get
yourself to the doctor already?
Just a little bug.
It's not a little bug.
It's been happening for weeks,
at least since you got back.
Hope. Is your daddy
the most stubborn man
on the planet?
Don't be so stubborn,
Daddy!
- I'm fine, baby.
- Don't be so stubborn, Daddy.
He'd rather walk around
like the living dead instead
of just get antibiotics.
[ Hope ]
Listen to Mama!
Listen to Mama.
Gonna listen to Mama.
That's a good idea.
Stubborn man.
♪ Hey, baby doll
What's goin' on? ♪
Yes, all the way.
Yes!
[ Lennon ]
♪ So long ago ♪
♪ Was it in a dream? ♪
♪ What more can I say? ♪
♪ On a river of sound ♪
♪ Through the mirror
go round and round ♪♪
♪ It's spring ♪
Jesus. You look like
Lee Trevino.
[ Laughs ]
Samantha took me shopping.
Oh?
You ever hear of this place?
The Banana Republic?
Yeah.
It's an amazing place.
Yeah? Yeah, okay.
The house is packed.
Well, that's good.
Band's out there,
ready.
Phil can step in on piano
if you need him
for the new stuff.
Family's
up front.
Oh.
And I saved a spot
for Mary.
- She's with them.
- Speak of the devil.
Break a leg, kid.
- Just tell me whose.
- [ Laughing ]
Come on in.
He'll be thrilled
to see you.
Well, thank you.
Thank you.
Bye. See you later
out there.
Oh, my God. Thank you
for the VIP ticket.
I am right
in the front row.
I thought I'd come back
and see how you're doing.
You know.
Are you nervous?
Oh, Mary, I've done this
a zillion times.
I'm never nervous.
- Hand to God, not once.
- Not once?
But I'm nervous now.
[ Laughs ]
No, that's nice.
So this--
I mean, I guess
this means that finally...
you'll let me
buy you dinner?
Let's see how you do first.
[ Laughs ]
Give me
a little more pressure.
Just what I need.
You know, this is
kind of weird to say,
I know,
because I really haven't
known you very long.
But I am very proud
of you, Danny.
Well, that is
fuckin' weird, Mary.
[ Laughing ]
You're sweet and weird.
There you go.
Just how I like 'em.
Okay.
Well, there you go.
Have a great time.
You're going
to be fantastic.
Oh, thank you.
I love you, Mary!
[ Laughing ]
That's
a show business expression,
you know.
Kinda means
I-I sort of like ya.
You still there?
[ Chattering ]
You look really nice.
You look
really nice too.
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Oh, right.
You know
what I mean?
[ Cheering ]
Hi, Grandpa!
Grandpa!
Thank you.
Thank you again.
- Thank you three times.
- [ Laughing ]
My granddaughter,
ladies and gentlemen.
Give her a hand.
Okay.
[ Woman ] "Baby Doll"!
[ Woman #2 ]
"Baby Doll"!
♪♪ [ Ballad ]
[ Man ]
Come on, Danny,
play "Baby Doll"!
- Whoo!
- Play "Baby Doll," Danny!
[ Woman ]
Hey, I wanna hear
"Baby Doll!"
[ Man ]
"Baby Doll"!
[ Voices Shouting, Echoing ]
- "Baby Doll," Danny!
- "Baby Doll"!
- Play "Baby Doll," Danny!
- Play "Baby Doll"!
Phil.
[ Whispers ]
Can you just, uh--
Hello, everybody.
[ Man ]
Hi, Danny.
Just working out
a little something.
Uh, but I know
what you're here for.
[ Cheering ]
♪♪ [ Piano: Upbeat ]
I think
you know this one.
♪ Hey, baby doll
What's going on? ♪
[ No Audible Lyrics ]
[ Cheering ]
Danny!
[ Laughing ]
Hey!
Sophie!
Hey.
Danny Collins!
[ Chuckles ]
- What are you doing here?
- Well, we heard about the gig.
We're like,
let's go support
our sugar daddy.
Oh, yeah.
I used your credit card
for the flight.
I hope that's okay.
What's up?
What do you got on you?
What do you mean?
Come on. Come on.
What do I mean?
Babe, he wants to party.
I want a taste.
I got it all, baby.
I got it all.
Mmm? Mm-hmm.
Here you go, Danny.
Man.
Yeah.
It's good.
Mmm.
So, I fired the pool guy
and the gardener.
I really didn't like
the way he looked at me.
- I decided to start a career--
- Grandpa!
Grandpa?
Come here.
♪ Hey, baby doll ♪
♪ What's goin' on? ♪
- Hey. Come here. Come on.
- Dad!
What are you doing?
It's okay.
- What are you doing?
- Weren't doing anything.
I didn't know, uh--
I didn't know.
Hi, Samantha. Hi.
This--
This is my friend Sophie
there.
And her friend Busywork.
So what's goin' on?
What's the look?
Oh. You just keep
judging me, Tom.
You just judge me. Go ahead.
You judge me all you want.
It's fine.
That's what you're good at.
And when you're done,
you know, being
so fucking perfect...
and honorable,
you should talk to your wife
about what you did in Delaware.
Wh-What's that?
What's he mean?
Tom?
I'll tell you
when we get home.
Stay the fuck away
from my family.
Tom.
Let's go.
Bye, Hope.
[ Sighs ]
Oh, man.
Come on.
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
♪♪ [ Rock ]
[ Lennon ]
♪ Temperature's rising ♪
♪ Fever is high ♪
♪ Can't see no future ♪
♪ Can't see no sky ♪
♪ My feet are so heavy ♪
♪ So is my head ♪
Who are you?
♪ Wish I was a baby ♪
Oh, I'm sorry.
I-I work for the hotel.
Oh, good. That's good.
Um, we need more towels.
Can you do that?
[ Danny ]
Mary!
And some beer.
I'll get you some towels
and some beer.
[ Metal Clangs ]
[ Sophie ]
God.
Mary.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mary, please.
It's not--
What happened
last night?
Well, you know,
it just--
it wasn't right.
It wasn't the right time.
What are you
talking about?
You've worked so hard,
and your whole family
was there.
I know.
Come on!
I just couldn't--
I-I--
I lost my nerve.
Oh, well, you lost
your dinner too.
Okay.
You should have played
the song, Danny.
You should have at least played
the one fucking song.
Take care, Jamie.
You too, Mr. Collins.
You be good to Nicky.
He's a good boy.
You got a wonderful face.
Yours isn't so bad either,
Mr. Collins.
Oh. Wow, look at that.
Now we're gettin' patter.
Okay.
[ Loudly ]
You know, for the record,
uh, Mary Ann...
from Gilligan's Island--
her real name
was Dawn Wells.
And she was Miss Nevada
before she got famous,
and she couldn't hold
a fuckin' candle to you.
Bye.
Nicky.
Oh, Nicky.
What a pleasure it's been.
Pleasure's definitely
been all mine, Danny.
I'm gonna miss you.
Gonna miss you.
Look at this.
Ran out of hundreds.
Don't even worry about it.
Come on.
I'll tell you what.
I'm in a giving vein
today.
What--
[ Chuckles ]
Come on. Get outta here.
What are you talking about?
The second
you stop appreciating
this piece of machinery,
then you give it
to somebody else.
Deal?
Deal.
[ Laughing ]
Go ahead,
man.
God bless you,
Danny Collins.
- Back at ya.
- Whoo!
Hey, how much
does insurance even cost--
Fuck it. I don't care.
I don't care.
- Watch your head.
- Okay, Danny.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Whistles ]
Okay, Danny.
I don't want
the last thing I ever
said to you to be mean,
but I don't want
to say anything nice.
So, Mr. Collins,
on behalf of
the Woodcliff Lake Hilton,
we'd like to thank you
for your stay,
and we hope that you will
make Hilton home wherever
your travels take you.
I'm grabbing a cab.
I see that.
I gave Nicky
my Mercedes.
You gave your Mercedes
to Nicky?
You are fucking crazy.
It's been said, yes.
I can afford it though.
Frank called me this morning,
and we're going back on tour.
I need the money.
I got a family now,
so--
They hate my guts,
but, uh, I'm told
that's what families do.
Yeah, that's right.
I've taught you well.
Yeah.
I'm gonna play
my new songs.
Some of them.
Oh.
We'll see what happens.
I know
what will happen.
Yeah, they'll
throw tomatoes at me.
Yeah, and onions.
You know, I'm gonna be here
in a couple of months.
You know, in the area.
We're playing the Garden.
Oh.
Maybe you'll come by,
see the show.
We'll have, uh,
dinner afterwards.
[ Laughs ] You know
what I like about you?
You never give up.
Some dinners
are worth fighting for.
I left something, uh,
in the room for you.
Yeah, you probably
left me a big mess
is what you left me.
Well, you know,
rock stars.
So, uh--
Another life, huh?
You never know.
[ Engine Starts ]
Oh. Hi.
Hey.
Oh. I-I'm sorry.
I don't think we met.
I'm Mary,
the hotel manager.
You must be Busywork?
Uh, I'm Judd.
Judd, right.
Okay. Very good.
Well--
Yeah.
Anyway, checkout's noon.
Sweet.
Christ. What,
did he send you out here
to check up on me?
Well, the hotel
didn't know what to do
with the damn piano,
so I thought
you might want it.
I don't want
his piano.
Yeah?
Well, it took six hours
to move it out
of the Hilton,
and I don't know
anyone else in New Jersey,
so tough shit.
Look, it's a $30,000
instrument, Tom.
Sell it, for all I care.
How's your health?
I find out
in a few days.
Ah.
Your age.
You know, when I was in my 30s,
I started drinking, heavily.
[ Sighs ]
Long line of drunks
in my family.
All with the usual
bullshit excuses.
[ Rumbling ]
Hey!
Careful, gentlemen.
- That is a Steinway.
- Yes, sir.
Anyway, we were on tour
in the Bay Area.
I fell asleep at the wheel.
Almost killed myself
and others.
Danny bailed me out.
5:00 in the morning,
he shows up at the
San Jose police station,
whacked out of his skull.
[ Laughing ]
He drives me six hours...
to this, uh,
Hollywood rehab joint,
drunker than I'd been
the night before,
the dumb shit.
He visited me
every Saturday...
till I got dry...
and then once a week
for 37 years,
I get four cases
of bottled water
sent to me...
wherever I am
in the world.
Always
with the same note.
"Drink as many
as you want-- on me.
Danny."
[ Sighs ]
Best friend I ever had,
your father.
Yeah, the man saved my life
and got me stone-cold sober...
and was three sheets
to the wind...
the whole time
he was doing it.
I'm sorry, but I'm not
seeing your point.
The point, my boy,
is that he's got
a good heart.
He just keeps it
up his ass half the time.
What you do with that
is up to you.
My waters will keep coming,
no matter what.
All right, boys.
Let's move that puppy...
so I can get the fuck
out of New Jersey.
[ Sighs ]
[ Danny ]
So I'll see you guys
in Pittsburgh?
Yeah. Frank is setting up
the other dates.
Okay. Talk soon.
[ Lennon ]
♪ Love is real ♪
♪ Real is love ♪
[ Chattering ]
♪ Love is feeling ♪
♪ Feeling love ♪
♪ Love is wanting ♪
♪ To be loved ♪
Have fun
at the doctor.
Your favorite flower
is--
Rose.
To smell it,
you breathe through your--
[ Inhales ]
Hold it in
as long as you can go,
and let it out
in one big--
♪ Love is touch ♪
♪ Touch is love ♪
♪ Love is reaching ♪
♪ Reaching love ♪
♪ Love is living ♪
♪ Living love ♪
♪ Love is needing ♪
♪ To be loved ♪♪
[ Sighs ]
Hi.
Tom Donnelly
for Dr. Silverman.
Have a seat,
Mr. Donnelly.
Thanks.
So, uh, she's pissed?
Nah, she's thrilled.
Thanks for asking.
Oh, that was such
a horrible night for me.
It's no excuse.
Well, I can assure you,
it was a worse night for me.
So she's not
gonna come at all?
She can barely move.
Doctor's got her
on full bed rest now.
Plus whatever this news is,
I'd rather she heard it
from me, not some doctor.
Mr. Donnelly?
[ Sighs ]
Listen, if this news
is bad, um--
Tom.
No, listen to me.
If it's bad,
Samantha, Hope
and the baby--
They'll be
taken care of, Tom.
Don't even think about it.
Okay. Good.
Thank--
Thank you.
I am not ready
to leave them.
I'm not ready.
You know, Tom,
I've been thinking.
I noticed something
very interesting.
Whenever this doctor
comes in here,
he either calls you
Mr. Donnelly or Tom.
You ever notice that?
Always one or the other.
Now, when he calls you
Mr. Donnelly,
it's never good news.
Next thing you know,
he's shooting you up
with some stuff...
that makes you throw up.
Or he doesn't like
your levels.
But when he calls you Tom,
it's always good news.
I mean, the time he liked
your white cell count.
Remember that?
He called you Tom.
It's here.
I've been taking notes.
Literally,
every time...
it's a good thing
when he calls you Tom.
So this is what
we want right now.
We want him
to come in here,
open that door,
call you Tom.
That's what we want.
You understand?
So let's--
let's focus...
on that.
Okay?
Okay.
Everything's going
to be all right, Son.
It's gonna be
all right.
You promise?
Have I ever
let you down before?
You're a ridiculous man.
You know that?
I know.
I've been told.
Okay.
Yeah, he's gonna
come in here,
and he's gonna
call you Tom.
And everything's
gonna be okay.
All right?
Everything's
gonna be okay.
[ Knocking ]
[ Door Opens ]
Okay, Tom,
so here's where we are.
♪ It's spring in my mind ♪
♪ But the autumn leaves,
they fall ♪
♪ As I am walking by ♪
♪ I collect them all ♪
What happened was I did an
interview with a magazine
called ZigZag...
in 1971.
Just after I had
my first album out.
And in it
I was asked by the fella
who was interviewing me...
whether I thought...
if I, um-- If I became,
you know, rich...
beyond the dreams
of avarice, you know,
whether it would
affect my songwriting,
you know, detrimentally.
And I thought--
I said I thought it would.
Anyway, John,
for some reason,
took exception to this
and wrote a letter in.
He was really offended
at that.
And he finished it
with, "Well, what do you
think of that?"
He had his own home telephone
number in Ascot,
so if I had got the letter
when he sent it,
I would have rung him.
[ Man ]
Right. Yeah.
So that's
the frustrating thing,
you see.
[ Lennon ]
♪ Instant karma's
gonna get you ♪
♪ Gonna knock you
right on the head ♪
♪ You better
get yourself together ♪
♪ Pretty soon
you're gonna be dead ♪
♪ What in the world
you thinking of ♪
♪ Laughing
in the face of love? ♪
♪ What on earth
you tryin' to do? ♪
♪ It's up to you
Yeah, you ♪
♪ Instant karma's
gonna get you ♪
♪ Gonna look you
right in the face ♪
♪ Better get yourself together,
darlin' ♪
♪ Join the human race ♪
♪ How in the world
you gonna see ♪
♪ Laughin' at fools like me? ♪
♪ Who on earth
do you think you are? ♪
♪ A superstar?
Well, right you are ♪
♪ Well, we all shine on ♪
♪ Like the moon
and the stars and the sun ♪
♪ Well, we all shine on ♪
♪ Everyone, come on ♪
♪ Instant karma's
gonna get you ♪
♪ Gonna knock you
off your feet ♪
♪ Better recognize
your brothers ♪
♪ Everyone you meet ♪
♪ Why in the world
are we here? ♪
♪ Surely not to live
in pain and fear ♪
♪ Why on earth are you there ♪
♪ When you're everywhere? ♪
♪ Come and get your share ♪
♪ Well, we all shine on ♪
♪ Like the moon
and the stars and the sun ♪
♪ Yeah, we all shine on ♪
♪ Come on and on
and on, on, on ♪
♪ Well, we all shine on ♪
♪ Like the moon
and the stars and the sun ♪
♪ Well, we all shine on ♪
♪ Like the moon
and the stars and the sun ♪♪
[ Needle Stuck
In Record Groove ]