I don't hear people there.
Let's go away to California.
Let's go to the beach.
I never been to the beach.
- Never?
- Never.
- Neither have I.
- I've never seen the ocean.
Bet it's beautiful.
- You want to come?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Let's just run away forever.
Yeah.
I mean never come back.
But you have
so much going for you...
- Really?
- Yeah.
- We can do it.
- Your family's okay?
Yeah.
Wait. Dad!
What are you doing?!
Who the hell are you?
Dad, let him go!
Let him go!
Who are you?!
- Please!
- Get out of here.
- Dad! Don't.
- Dad, don't.
- Sorry little bastard.
Pack up and get off my ranch.
- Please.
- No, no, get off by sunrise.
You're not to make this ranch
into whore house for queers.
- You hear me? Not on my watch.
- Okay.
- Go to your mother's house!
When you straight out,
you can come back, all right?
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay?
Read your goddamn Bible!
Then you can come back!
Get out of here,
you disgusting little prick!
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch, my son.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe this shit.
I can't believe
this shit.
I always knew.
Buttercup,
what are you doing?
What are you doing, huh?
What are you doing out here,
huh?
You sleeping in the barn now?
Let's go to the house with me.
That's a good girl.
Good girl, yeah.
Good girl.
Come on, girl.
Let's up to the house.
What?
Don't wake up, Pedro.
Don't wake up him.
What? What?
What?
Easy, easy.
Yeah. Hello?
Maria.
Oh, what's that?
Hold on.
Hold that chucker.
I'll be right there. Hold on.
I'm coming. Hold on.
I'll be there.
All right!
Party's over, boys. Back off.
Get off my property
and away from my people.
I mean it now.
Go back to your own country.
- All right!
- Go on.
This guy, his wife died,
that's his son,
and he wants a better life
for the boy here.
They want him back over there.
Thank you.
You saved my ass.
You hear that?
We're gonna keep him.
Now go on. Go on back.
Yeah.
Take him back to your place
and get some food and rest.
And call the proper authorities
or maybe not.
I'll leave that up to you,
all right? Okay.
Yeah. Let's go. Come on.
Go on now.
Go on back. Go on.
If you come back,
I'll shoot your legs
right out from under you.
I can do that.
All right?
Don't cross this river again.
Stay off my property.
Stay out of Texas.
Texas Rangers!
Hey, children.
What is your name?
Hey, sweetheart.
Show me your cars.
You ready to come out?
- Yes.
- Yes? Let's go.
Come. Come with me.
There you go.
Yes, let's go.
- All right, there you go,
sweetie, come on.
- Here's your car.
This is dispatch.
What's your situation?
- Leave that car.
- Sheriff, it's the captain.
This is a bad one,
real bad.
I need some help over here.
Please send Scott over here
as soon as you can.
Let me see your motor,
your car.
Wow!
Where is the fastest car here?
This one.
This car is the fastest.
Come on.
Come on. Okay.
Have you ever thought
about quitting the Rangers?
Yeah, I have.
I hope someday that I never
have to interview
another rape victim
or a burned child
or see another
mutilated body.
Not many people
can do our job, Sam.
Most people would go insane.
Hi, it's me.
You doing your homework?
You going riding later?
Okay.
We'll have dinner tonight
in a fun place, okay?
All right.
Hugs.
Bye.
Absolutely, yes.
I was explaining to Ms. Davis
that we never close a cold case.
I'll leave you two
to talk about it.
Thank you very much.
So I'm sorry about your loss,
Mrs. Davis.
Thank you very much.
What was your son's name?
Jimmy.
What else can you tell me
about your son?
Well, he was a very good,
very good, wonderful person.
I want you to find out
if my son was killed
and who killed him.
I will speak
with the head Ranger,
the Captain that you just met,
and we'll go into the files
and we'll do our best
to give you an answer.
Thank you very much.
Who was in charge
of the Jimmy Davis case
- 15 years ago?
- That would have been
Ranger Jackson,
- and he retired
about two years ago.
- Yeah.
He was in charge
of the office back then.
You know, quite honestly,
Sam, I don't...
I know about the case,
but I don't know much
about the details.
But I did find the case file.
I want you to have it.
Good thing is,
Ranger Jackson is gonna be here
day after tomorrow
for the town barbecue.
It'd be a really good time
for you to sit down with him
- and get the details on it.
- Sure.
Yeah, I really wanna work
on this case,
- if it's okay with you.
- You got it.
Get those feet out
in front of you, Buster.
You're doing
pretty darn good, Buster,
for a little squirt your size.
Watch me.
Easy on the bit.
Come on.
Come on, Buster.
Maybe someday you can
outride me.
Let go of that horn, Buster.
I'm starting
to ride like John Wayne!
Riding like John Wayne's cousin.
Buster, your grandpa's here.
How am I doing, grandpa?
You're doing pretty damn good.
Don't talk to me.
Just listen to KC, all right?
He'll teach you.
Starting to get good enough
so's he can ride your horse.
- That's not gonna
happen for a while.
- That's what I told him.
She can do it,
but he can't, no.
Hey, I wanna show you
something.
Hey, kids.
Come on!
Got a strange phone call
last night
with some woman's voice
attached to it.
Didn't belong to me.
Wrong number.
Yeah, it's hard enough
to make one work, Pop,
let alone two at the same time,
it ain't easy.
Yeah, well, don't join
my divorce club.
Try to avoid that.
Tell you that right now.
Watch,
you'll get an education.
Reminds me of when
you were a teenager.
Hey.
Go get him, Pa.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
- Come on.
Shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh.
You boys have good touch.
That's a good girl.
Come here, touch her.
Come on. Yeah.
Put your hand out here.
Yeah.
Bite his hand off.
That's good. That's good.
You've been working him good,
son.
Good work.
Everybody down.
Let's go.
Who's hungry?
Last one in the truck's
a rotten egg!
Gonna be you, old man.
Grandpa is gonna be
the rotten egg.
Who's the rotten egg?
Scootch over, Lizzie.
Come on, Augustus.
Come on, buddy.
Attaboy. Let's go.
Who's the rotten egg?
- You.
- Me?
- Grandpa's the rotten egg!
- Yeah, I'm the rotten egg.
- Who's the rotten egg?
- Grandpa!
Hey, Buster.
Okay. Okay, go on.
Get on. I'll be right down.
Come on, Augustus!
- I gotta go change.
- Come on, boy.
Go ahead.
I'll be right back.
Hey!
- Hey, Buster.
- Hey, Buster!
Get your hand out of there.
What'd I tell you about eating
other people's food, huh?
How you doing?
Milo,
don't overcook that meat.
Yeah.
Good to see everybody.
Right. Have a good time.
Good to see you.
Hey, Pa.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Just looking at those horses
over there.
I wish your ma could've come.
- Me too.
- Yeah.
You think, uh...
you think your mom
would let me move back in?
- Of course.
- Are you serious?
Yeah.
She was talking about you.
She saying she want me there?
Yeah?
Why do you think
she don't want you there?
I don't know.
You know your ma.
She changes her mind a lot.
Well, that's who I got it from.
I got all jacked up.
- Mr. Briggs, how you doing?
- Good to see you, sir.
I wanna introduce you
to Texas Ranger Samantha Payne.
- Hello, sir, nice meeting you.
- Yes, ma'am.
- My son, Cody.
- Cody, good to see you.
I'll see you guys
in a minute.
Thank you.
Yeah, I never met
a lady Ranger before.
I didn't know they had 'em.
Yeah,
we can vote now as well.
That's good.
Buster... Buster?
Buster Briggs,
where you at?
I want you to meet
a lady Texas Ranger.
- Hi,
- Hello, sir.
Nice handshake.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Good. You having fun?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Excellent.
- That's her son Cody.
Nice to meet you.
Maybe I can be a Texas Ranger
when I grow up.
- You want to?
- Yes, sir.
I thought you said you wanted
to run the ranch with me.
Yes, sir, but even
if you're 100, I could do both.
No, wait a minute.
What do you mean you'll do both?
I don't know about that.
Well, we'll see.
Let me think about it.
You're not very good
at work, son.
Go learn to be a cowboy.
Go on, get out of here.
Cody, go get some...
I'll see you in a minute.
Oh, God almighty.
- Yeah, they're something.
- They are.
- Listen,
let me ask you something.
- Yes, sir.
- in two weeks, we're gonna have
a competitive cook-off.
- Okay.
I would like to invite you and
your son as my special guests.
Well, I appreciate that.
And thank you so much
for having us.
Very nice party.
Thank you, sir.
- Ma'am.
- Nice meeting you.
Look what rolled in.
Nice to see you, sheriff.
- How are you, Scott?
- Good to see you.
Good to see you.
- Deputy, good to see you.
- Good to see you, too.
Well, I don't know
if Ranger Captain mentioned,
I took over
the Jimmy Davis case,
and the files and notes
indicate
that the kid maybe,
possibly committed suicide.
Well, little lady, first thing,
I don't think it was suicide.
And I said the obvious suspect
in this case was Scott Briggs.
And what was the evidence then?
Well, his son,
the day he sent him off,
the young boy disappeared.
Then Pedro or whatever
the hell his name was...
Pedro had looked after
the horses...
He disappeared.
Briggs had a lot to lose
in this thing,
and I've had
that gut feeling for years
that everything starts
and ends right here.
Right here.
Now, them two young boys liked
to ride horses
and have a good time together,
and they played...
They played a little grab-ass
or whatever goes
on between them.
That's their business.
It's none of mine.
These were young boys.
They're human beings.
They deserve the protection
of the law.
That's the way I feel about it,
and that's the way I see it.
But I had a couple of beers
one time with Scott Briggs,
and he told me
that all gays were evil.
So that's something
to think about.
Well, Sam, you're gonna
have to use old-fashioned
investigative techniques
on this one.
Really turn up
the heat on this.
But remember,
don't ever forget the obvious,
'cause those clues will lead you
where you need to be.
290, 290.
Good to see you, sheriff.
Enjoy. Enjoy.
Thanks for the good work.
You got a really good man here.
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey, kids.
Scott?
The kid is gone.
Those guys came back
and took him back to Mexico,
and I couldn't do
anything about it.
You stay up
with Buster tonight, okay?
- I'll take care of it, okay?
- Okay.
I'll take care of it,
all right?
I'll take care of it.
Yeah.
They took the kid back,
and now they're trying
to smuggle drugs over here.
Those dirty sons of bitches.
You hear what I'm saying?!
Good shot. Good shot.
Good shot.
Let's get out of here.
Terrific.
Great. Great.
- Mrs. Payne.
- Hello, Mrs. Davis.
- How are you?
- Fine. Thank you.
- I would like to show you
my son's bedroom.
- Sure.
His room seems more quiet
than the rest of the house.
I sometimes...
I like to sit down
and...
think about the good times.
Your son seemed
to love water and horses.
He loved to swim,
but the horses
were everything to him.
How often did he visit
the Briggs ranch?
I really don't know.
What kind of relationship
did he have with Ben Briggs?
- They were very close.
-  Mm-hmm.
But...
some people liked to say
it was more than that.
Was your son on antidepressant
medication?
Yes.
He was.
Did he try to commit suicide
prior to his disappearance?
Yes.
Do you mind
if I keep this picture?
- Take anything you need.
-  Thank you very much.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
So I'll call you as soon
as I learn something.
- Thank you very much.
You're so kind.
- Thank you.
Good morning.
Is Mr. Briggs in?
He'll be over in a minute.
- How can I help you?
- Are you the lady of the house?
No, I live with the family.
I have for years.
I help run things
around here.
Well, there's a lot to do
on a ranch this size.
- That's for sure.
- Maria, can I talk to you?
How you doing today?
Good?
Good morning, sir.
- My granddaughter Maddie.
- How are you?
She can ride a horse,
let me tell you.
Okay, go tell your brother,
I need him here
to do some work for one time,
okay, for once.
Kind of early, aren't you?
Nothing's too early
for me, sir.
No, I mean,
the cook-off's in two weeks.
- Well, that can wait.
- Mm-hmm, well,
what is it you came for?
I came to ask you about a man
that once worked here,
Pedro Alvarez.
I believe he used
to take care of your horses.
He did. He did.
What's it to you?
Well, it could
possibly mean a lot.
We reopened a case
of a young man
who disappeared 15 years ago,
Jimmy Davis.
How come I knew that as soon
as I heard a knock on the door?
I have no idea, sir.
Okay.
Good luck with your procedures,
but in the meantime,
I don't want anybody,
you know...
snooping around my property
asking questions
because this is
private property.
- I hope you understand that.
- I understand that.
And I respect your privacy.
Perhaps we can have a more
formal meeting in the future.
- Perhaps.
Thank you.
So what do you want me
to do about it?
Keep track of everything
she does.
What is "everything"?
"Everything"
means everything.
Just keep her off her game,
whatever it takes.
Within reason, okay?
- All right.
-  We'll talk later.
All right.
Asshole.
Grandpa!
Come on, Buster.
Let's go. Come on, buddy.
Yeah!
Thanks, man, for taking my kids
to my wife's house.
- Appreciate it.
- Maddie, Maddie.
I'll make some bunk beds.
You can stay forever.
- Give me a hug.
- Bye, grandpa.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
Okay.
Johnny have the horses ready.
Let me kiss you.
Tell your mom I love her, okay?
We'll be back together soon.
All right?
You, you be good.
Hey, Grandpa,
I'm a Texas Ranger.
If you don't let me
take over your ranch,
I'll arrest
your bow-legged ass.
I love you.
That little bastard.
He always get me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, come back soon.
Come back soon, right?
- I'll be damned, bye-bye.
- Bye.
All I've seen is this.
I don't wanna go crazy with it.
I just wanna
scare her out of here.
Chica nuevos.
What am I supposed
to feed my dogs?
Why don't you feed your dog
your tiny dick?
Yeah, man, this interaction
isn't for blood,
or it's not about money.
It's more about...
maybe we get a little pussy.
- Right?
- Oh, hell, yeah.
All right, everybody get
a shovel and dig your head
out of the pussy
'cause you can't see straight.
I'm talking to you about this.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
I'm saying no firearms.
There's gonna be no shooting.
Right?
Just scare her. That's it.
I don't think
you understand, though.
What if she's shot?
That's not gonna be good for
any of us if she gets killed.
This is the Texas Rangers,
all right?
There's gonna be
repercussions for it.
But what if?
If she gets killed,
then I suggest
you get across
the river back to Mexico.
You can go to goddamn China,
wherever you want to.
I'm asking you
you in or are you out?
Are you in or are you out?
I'll find somebody else
like that.
- You in...
- You know what? I'm in.
- All right.
- Okay.
All right.
And you're out.
Okay. Let's go.
We're done.
Haven't talked
in nine and a half years, okay?
How many you put
in the ground since then?
Only... only two, huh?
Better than I am.
Listen to me, for once.
Listen to me.
I... I need...
I need...
All right, okay, I need...
Yeah,
I need Ben to call Maria.
It's very,
very important, all right?
City boy.
Look who's here.
Coming here to drag us
into the 21st Century or what?
- Maybe.
- Yeah?
- Good to see you
- Good to see you, too.
Maria, hi.
- Johnny.
- Good to see you.
Pop.
Man, boy, good to see you.
Welcome home.
I'm here to see my brothers
and Maria
and take care of that will.
Yeah, well, that's the only way
I could get you to come here.
Through Maria.
Maria knows best.
She's the boss.
Welcome home.
Your... your room's
is waiting on you, okay?
I remember where it is.
- See you up there.
-  See you.
Good to see you, son.
Thank you, Lord Jesus.
How are you?
I'm good, how are you?
How's the family?
Uh, the family?
Well, you know my mom died
seven years ago.
- Mm-hmm.
- And, well, my father,
he left,
and I never heard from him.
- Mm.
- You know, he vanished.
Yeah.
But you're my family, so.
You look good.
You look very handsome.
Have you been eating well?
Yeah.
I don't know if I'm gonna...
- go eat dinner.
- What?
I'm just gonna stay here,
maybe take a walk.
No.
It's weird.
No, it's not weird,
and supper's ready,
and I'm gonna sit with you,
and everything's gonna be fine.
- You're gonna sit with me?
- Of course.
I'll be next to you.
If you sit next to me,
then I'll go.
Yes.
Yeah?
I missed you so much.
You're the brother
I never had.
Yeah.
I'm lying.
I think I always had
a crush on you.
Oh, really?
Really.
Well, I wish I had known that
earlier.
We could have saved
a lot of problems.
Yeah, I think so.
Let's go.
Come on.
- I'll help you with that later.
- All right.
Hello. Welcome.
Hey, Johnny, how are you doing
out Atlanta all day?
God dang,
I heard a lot about you.
Good to finally meet you.
Everybody sit down.
Known your old daddy a while.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'd just like to say
that I'm very...
I'm very pleased and moved,
I really am,
that my sons, my three sons
the first time in many years
are being here together,
and it makes me very,
very happy.
And very emotional.
Okay?
Benny, I'm so happy
that he's here.
I am very happy.
But are we okay for now?
Are we okay for now?
- Are we okay?
- Yeah. I'm asking you.
Yeah, we're okay, dad.
- Okay, good.
- It's good to be here.
- Yeah.
- It's great to see y'all.
So did you meet LD?
He's been my partner.
- All right.
- Ben, good to meet you.
Heard a little bit about you.
Pretty crappy
business partner.
Hadn't earned me a damn cent,
but he's...
I've been saving that for you.
I'm holding it for your boy.
Yay!
I'm not used to saying grace,
but maybe we should say
a little grace.
Maybe somebody
should say some.
KC or...
yeah, you or which.
Come on.
Somebody.
There's no before
and there's no after.
There's only now and love.
So let us love each other
like Jesus said.
I love Jesus,
but I like to drink a little.
Let us pray
for our brother Ben.
Give him love
and welcome him home.
Thank you.
And the food, too.
Amen.
- Amen.
-  Amen.
Yeah, now
we got a surprise for you.
Okay, I'm ready.
Milo?
Come on.
- Oh, no!
-  Good God!
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
What do you got there,
Milo?
This was my favorite kid goat.
That was your favorite goat?
What was his named?
His name, uh, is Billy.
- Billy Goat.
- That was Billy.
In honor...
In honor
of Benny's homecoming,
Benny, I cooked him
especially for you.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you, Milo.
Can't wait to dig in.
I'm glad you kept
the teeth in that.
Applause for Milo.
- Where you going, Benny?
Where you going?
- I'll be back.
I'll be back.
- Where are you going?
He said he'll be back,
Pop.
-  Hola.
- Hey.
Thank you.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Did you have a good time?
It was all right.
Oh, gosh.
Freak show.
What are you doing?
Dance with me.
No. No.
Your father dances with me.
- What?
- Yeah.
My dad dances with you?
Yeah, like...
No, no, no, no, no.
- Like this?
- Yeah, I swear.
That's my daddy.
Let me dance with you!
I'd rather dance
with my horse!
He's in love with that horse.
Almost love you
as much as my horse, Maria!
Dad, what you did to me
that night...
I'll never forget it,
and I'll never understand it.
You told me to read the Bible,
and I did.
Leviticus.
Is it worse for two men
to lie together
or for King David
to send a man to battle to die
so that he can lay
with his wife?
What's worse?
Nothing to say?
You always protected yourself
with silence.
I guess you still do.
It turns out
that Pedro Alvarez
stays at
Isabel's Convenience Store,
and I really need
to speak with him.
He's Isabel's relative.
I would like to go to Linda Rosa
to meet with them.
Okay, I'll arrange
for Rogers to go with you.
He knows the town well.
- I don't need that clown, sir.
-  No, you go with him.
- Yes, sir. Okay.
- Did you get that car
for Cody?
Yeah,
I'm driving Cody's new car,
and I think
he's going to like it.
What the hell was that?
I just got shot at,
sir.
Dad...
where's Jimmy?
What happened to him?
I have no idea whatsoever.
- He's around, huh?
- Absolutely.
I'm only concerned about you
and the rest of us,
- the family, that's it.
- The family?
Yeah, what there is of it,
yeah.
I've been going a little
downhill since you left.
I feel better now.
I think back
to this particular time...
when I got bucked off a horse,
and you told me to get back on,
and...
you did it in such
a kind way, I...
I just like to think about it
'cause it kind of offsets
what happened.
It's not enough
to make me forget,
but it helps a little bit.
Yeah.
Thank you, son.
Come in, fellas.
Okay.
Special day.
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
Have a seat.
Maria,
come over here.
Over here.
You're late.
You're always late.
Sorry.
Yeah. Okay.
There you go, darlin'.
- Your dad wanted me to go over
a few things...
- Hold on.
How come we're here like this?
A will is a totally
private family thing, right?
- Private?
- That's what I was
about to explain to you,
if you'd just
give me a second.
Okay, go ahead.
Your dad wanted everybody
here together as family
because he wanted the entire
family to understand everything.
He wanted... he wanted it
all out in the open.
-  Is that right, Scott?
- Yes, sir.
So we've laid out
a very simple plan.
Basically, the 40,000 acres
be broken up equally
in four ways.
What are you talking about,
four ways?
Pop.
Hold on a second here.
No, no, no, no.
Let him finish, all right?
Go head, John.
Let him finish.
Your dad's laid it out
in very simple terms,
laid it out very nicely.
10,000 acres
to each of the boys,
10,000 acres and the ranch house
to Maria Anna Gonzalez.
Pop, Pop...
I know what you're gonna say.
Right, Maria's not
a part of this family.
- Not really.
- I know.
- Right, Maria?
-  I know.
-  This is a family deal here.
- I know.
I love Maria,
you know we all do,
- like a sister, but, Dad...
- Hold on a minute.
As I said before,
this is probably
the happiest day of my life
as well as the toughest.
I'd like to say she's
not just like a sister to you.
Excuse me.
She is your sister.
Jesus.
And a daughter
that I care for and love
maybe more than anyone.
I want you all to know that.
All right?
Maria?
Explain yourself.
I can't right now.
I can't.
Any further questions
at the moment,
you can ask John.
I have to...
get some fresh air.
We can talk later, Maria,
if you'd like.
But, uh...
in the meantime,
I want you all to remember this.
This is your sister.
She's blood now.
Well.
Maria.
Welcome to the family.
Come here.
- I...
- Come here.
I'm just glad I'm gay,
otherwise I would've
married my sister.
She still in there?
Of course
she's still in there.
She's waiting.
She... she didn't go out
the other door?
Hey, Pop.
This is the only door.
Okay.
Yeah. All right.
I guess I better go back in.
Think I should?
Yeah, I think so.
All right. Okay.
Well, looks like we got
us a beautiful Mexican sister
and a homosexual brother.
You call it "gay," Johnny.
I don't know about that.
We'll figure it out.
Hey.
If you hadn't given her
10,000 acres,
I would have given her mine,
and I still might.
I don't understand.
Why was I always treated
like a daughter,
but never told
I was a daughter?
That's beyond me.
Yeah,
I know it makes sense to you,
but certainly not to me.
And who was Tomás?
Just a make-believe father?
Maybe he ran off,
left your mother.
I wonder why.
So why are you telling me now?
Why what?
Why didn't you tell me
long before this?
Were you ashamed?
Why would I be ashamed?
You're my daughter.
I don't know.
You seem to have
all the answers.
Are you ashamed
because I am the product
of your unwed Mexican maid?
Might that have
something to do with...
Listen... no listen to me.
I loved your mother. I did.
You didn't answer my question.
It didn't look right
in this particular
community of yours.
Is that it?
Maybe.
There doesn't seem
to be a maybe here.
Yes or no.
Hey, I'm a coward.
Oh, yes, you are.
Don't play the victim
on me here now.
It's too late for that.
Well, I hope someday
that I can be forgiven.
Oh, please.
Don't do that.
If I ever decide
to forgive anybody,
it would be me who decides,
not you.
This one time,
my dear father,
you can't decide.
I won't let you.
Go home and rest.
I'm sure you need it.
I have things to do.
Is that like... is that like
a southern turn-on?
Did we ever play
smear the queer with you?
- What...
- Did we?
What the eff
is smear the queer?
- Smear the queer, man.
- What is that game?
Tell me about that game.
Cow patty on your face
with a bamboo stick.
Actually, you know what?
I think you did.
- And that's why I turned gay.
- I think that's probably why.
I think you turned me gay,
brother.
- No way.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
- He says gay.
How do you call it?
- Yeah.
I say why can't
you just say "homosexual"?
Sometimes,
we pronounce it "g'ay."
G'ay?
That's like you're choking?
What is that?
G'ay?
You lost it.
You drank way too much, Johnny.
Johnny,
ignorant son of a bitch.
- Just shut your trap.
Shut your trap.
- I wanna know!
What do you wanna know?
Tell me what you wanna know.
Who gets on top first?
-  What?
- Who swings the bat?
-  No, I'll lay it out.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Who gets on top first?
- Yeah.
Well, we flip a coin.
That's how we do it.
Sometimes, Rochambeau.
- Rochambeau?
-  Rochambeau.
- What does that mean?
- Paper, rock, scissors.
"I'm a dumb
redneck heterosexual."
What's the dirtiest,
wildest sex you ever had?
Shit.
Johnny, stop.
Stop!
Hey,
knock it off over there.
It's not a library, man!
- All right, come on.
- Shut up!
- Or you come over here
and I'll kick your ass.
- Let's get out of here.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, Johnny.
All right, all right.
Hey,
stick it up your ass, pal!
Hey, he didn't mean it.
- You!
- Come on, come on.
Hey, hey, hey,
you all right?
- Take a couple of deep
breaths. Walk it off.
- Come here, come here.
Fresh air.
Getting excited.
Hey, jackass.
You want a piece of me?
- Yeah, I do.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'm not talking to you,
asshole.
- Yeah, you're talking to me.
- Who's the asshole?
I got this. I got this.
I got this.
- Back off, man, I'm not
talking to you, little faggot.
- What?
- Who's the faggot now, huh?!
- Yeah, get out of here!
- Get out of here!
- Come on.
Get the fuck out of here.
That was awesome!
You're starting trouble, man!
Awesome.
You were a buzz saw in there.
- Thank you, sir.
- Papa's right.
You must have been a hell
of a street fighter
when you were younger.
Yeah, pop taught me
a thing or two.
I was a little off my game.
I got bumped into something,
but how'd I do?
Oh, you were an animal.
You weren't worth a shit
even though you started it.
- Come on, man!
- You weren't worth shit!
I thought I got someone.
You remind me of pop
a little bit sometimes.
How's that?
I was told when my pop
was a young man,
he'd got in a fight
with the sheriff
and knocked that guy on his ass
in front of a bunch of people
on account of a guy
called him a draft dodger
during the Korean War.
Guy never mentioned anything
to pops again.
- Never said shit.
- I believe that.
Chip off the old block,
both of you.
- What happened to you?
- I don't know, man.
- A lover of all things.
- A gentle heterosexual.
Straight.
- Go, go, go, go.
- Go get him, Cody!
Get him, boy!
- All right.
- Way to go, Cody.
Good job.
Good roping today.
Your dad would be proud.
So how come you never
talk about your father?
Every time his name comes up,
you change the subject.
Why?
Because he was
a very violent man,
and at the same time,
I love him very much.
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Hmm.
Well,
last time I saw him,
he came storming
into the kitchen like a maniac,
and you never knew
what set him off...
and as violent as you can
imagine a man can be.
And...
you can only see his hand...
going to my throat,
and then you feel the wall.
And I was just so tired
of being afraid,
so tired that I decided that
that was going to be it.
So I stare at him.
And I said,
"Well, go for it."
I said, "Go for it."
And you can see his fist
going by my face
and hitting the wall.
And I opened my eyes,
and I stare at him,
and he looked like a...
demon,
and, um...
And he just walk away.
And that was it.
We're set.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Give me a hug.
Oh, I love you so much.
So much.
Lock the doors.
We're closed,
but how can I help you?
Hello, Mrs. Isabel?
Yes?
Hi, I'm looking
for Eduardo Valdez.
And who wants to know?
We do,
the Texas Rangers.
Well, he's not here.
He comes and goes.
Oh, I see.
Should I tell him that
you are looking for him?
Yes, please.
I just left my business card.
If he can call me
whenever he has a chance,
- I will really appreciate it.
-  I'll do that.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
Have a good night.
- You're welcome, good night.
- Good night.
Be careful out there,
it's kinda dangerous.
- Yeah, take care yourself. Bye.
- Thank you.
I went to Joe's Bar.
Bartender told me there was
a in town,
a new guy,
so I followed him out,
pulled him over.
That's not bad
for a new guy.
- Yeah?
-  Yeah.
- Looks great.
- Squeezing on it like it's
a pair of titties
ain't gonna get you
any closer to getting a job.
- Yeah.
-  Yeah.
- Listen, man...
- Hey, man. Hey, man...
We talk about business here.
This stuff in your hand
has no value.
No value?
Why are you here
if it has no value?
How are we gonna sell that?
Let me make a point to you.
You're fighting
for 70% of this, yeah?
You want 70% of zero,
nothing, nada?
Or you want 60% of this?
It's your call.
What do you want?
I want 40% instead of 30.
I'm not doing 30.
No way, man.
No way, asshole.
Hey, we can talk.
You don't have to call me
an asshole.
Call me asshole again, I'm gonna
slap you in the goddamn mouth.
- Just give it a try.
- Just talk.
You want to do business,
to business, but just talk.
- You need me to sell stuff.
- I don't need you.
I need somebody to sell stuff.
You think I can't get
somebody else,
you're wrong, my friend,
you're wrong about that.
- Mm-hmm.
- 40.
All right.
Let's do the deal, asshole.
That comes out your end.
Look my face of concern.
Look your face of concern.
- All right.
- Look my face of celebration.
-  All right. Good.
- Yeah, 40. Deal.
Hey, Sheriff, what's your 20?
67 and 11.
Okay, good.
You're right behind me.
Listen,
I got a text from Sam.
It was real vague,
but apparently,
she stumbled on a drug deal
going down
at that warehouse in Minarosa.
You gotta know this...
Your Deputy Rogers
is inside that building.
10-4
Here you go.
You got a girl?
No.
You seem sad about it.
- It's not our business, man.
-  Huh?
- That's not our business.
-  You want to talk business,
let's talk about the $1,000
you owe me that I paid you
to scare a Ranger
and nothing happened.
-  What? What? What?
- What do you want?
Want a refund or a credit store
or something?
- Who?
-  A store credit.
- In English. What's that?
- A store credit.
- Store credit?
- Yeah. How about that?
That's business,
what you want to talk about.
All right, man,
take from the cut.
- All right? No worries.
- No worries.
It's a good thing for you
and me both
- that kid got killed, too.
- I know.
You'd be in prison...
- Let me see your hands.
- Down, down, down, down!
- Hands behind your back.
- Don't move.
Y'all got here two seconds later
I don't know what.
Asshole.
Yesterday, you were teaching
these kids about drugs,
and now you're
doing this shit?
Si!
I don't know who you're
working for, asshole,
but you're a disgrace
to our profession.
- You understand?
- Answer him.
- Yes, sir!
- Get your ass up.
Get this crap up around here.
Come here. Sit up.
Sit up.
I'll say it again.
There's no Pedro Alvarez.
I'd hit the road
if I were you.
Whatever you say, bud.
Thank you, Mrs. Isabel.
Thank you for helping us.
Oh, you're welcome.
The one that lived in Mexico
and now you live here?
Back and forth.
I'm with the Texas Rangers,
Mr. Alvarez.
And I came to ask you
about Ben and Scott Briggs.
Do you know what happened
to Jimmy Davis
who took care of
Briggs' horses?
In my pueblo,
there is little...
This little tiny bird
that is brilliant red...
Rojo, rojo...
Red with little black wings.
He flies up
and down the canyon.
And what does he do
all day long?
He lives to catch flies.
Can you help us?
I am very sorry
it didn't work out.
I'm sorry.
Don't feel bad.
This generation of Mexicans
hate the Texas Rangers.
I know.
Hello, Mr. Scott.
The Texas Ranger Samantha Payne
is waiting in your office.
Oh...
Well, just open the floodgates,
you idiot.
Open the floodgates!
Please be seated.
What can I do for you?
I came to ask you
about Jimmy Davis.
Jimmy Davis?
What about him?
Did you know that your son
and Jimmy Davis had an affair?
No, no, that never happened.
That's just small-town rumors.
That confirms
that they did have an affair.
So?
I believe his disappearance
was a hate crime.
A hate crime?
How long you been doing
your job, young lady?
Because you have a picture
of a man who is missing,
you come to the simple
conclusion that me
or anyone out here
had anything to do
with this man's disappearance.
You can't go and start arresting
people anywhere you look.
I mean,
everybody has someone to hate.
I have someone.
You have someone.
And let me tell you something.
The Mexicans hate the blacks.
The blacks hate the white.
My white neighbor hates women.
And my liberal lawyer hates
my Republican friends,
and my Republican friends hate
my liberal lawyer.
But the work gets done.
Do you have anything to do with
Jimmy Davis' disappearance, sir?
I have never done
anything to that man,
and if you think I have,
then what can I say?
I understand
you have made comments
that you do believe
that gay people are evil.
Those are strong feelings
of hate, Mr. Briggs,
and hate can bring confusion
to a man
that wants to control everything
and everyone around him.
I believe in justice
just like everyone else.
Do you, Mr. Briggs?
Yes, I do.
Now please leave my office.
I met with Pedro Alvarez.
Pedro Alvarez.
And what did he say?
He said plenty.
He said what?
Who lets the Texas Rangers
onto my property?!
Who does that?
My goddamn cook!
He not only cooks the soup
and my fried chicken
and lets anybody onto
my property that he wants me to!
I don't get it!
You know, they arrested
that Rogers guy in a drug bust.
They what?
Yeah,
they got him in custody.
- They got him.
- Okay, now, you listen to me
and listen good.
I don't want some
cheap Texas Ranger bitch
roaming around this property
asking a bunch of questions.
I don't want her on this
property or anywhere near!
You hear me?! Nowhere!
If she does, only I talk to her!
You understand?
Only me! Only me!
Where's Ben?
He's never around here.
-  Where's Ben?
- She's just doing her job.
What are you getting
so worked up for?
- Give her a pass.
- Give her a pass?
For what,
you friggin' retard?
You friggin' retard!
Give her a pass.
Who's the retard?
We invited her
to the barbecue next week.
-  Who invited?
- Not me, old man, not me.
- You did.
- Then uninvite her.
Get her on the phone
this goddamn minute
and uninvite
that sneaking bitch!
- You hear me?
- No way.
- What do you mean no way?
- No way, you do it.
Oh, I do what you...
Oh, you thimble-headed redneck
son of a bitch.
Yeah? Yeah?
Step up!
Now, listen to me...
I don't want that bitch
anywhere around me,
you understand me?
Nowhere around me.
Now...
clean all this shit up,
clean it up before supper.
Clean it up yourself,
you asshole.
Kiss my ass 27 times,
you prick.
Speak up, Johnny.
You never say anything.
Get out of my way.
Don't you pick it up.
I wanna ask you
about Jimmy Davis.
Sure.
What do you want to know?
You were having an affair
with Jimmy Davis.
Well,
that's nobody's business.
I'm not here to judge you,
Mr. Briggs.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sure it was
very difficult for you
to be a gay man in a town
of machos like the one we're in.
It's like you'd expect.
I pretended to be straight.
Uh-huh.
I made sure to date
the prettiest girls.
I was the one to always
start the fights
- so no one's starting with me.
- Mm-hmm.
Just pray to be like
everyone wanted me to be.
How'd your father react
when he learned you were guy?
My father is a tough guy.
And you can't tell him anything.
But my mother...
she told me
to go live my life.
Some people,
they'll never accept it.
That's true.
Was anybody with you and Jimmy
the last time you saw him?
The last time I saw him?
-  Yeah, was anybody with you?
- No.
- No?
Do you believe that blood
runs thicker than truth, sir?
No. I don't know why you're
asking me that, but no.
It's okay.
I found this.
Anybody out there?
Who's hungry?
She's got me.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Red.
Red? Red who?
Your redneck prick
son of a bitch son, that's who.
What do you want smashed
before you pick it up, huh?
- You want this?
- Pick your spot,
pick your spot.
Yeah.
I missed you guys at supper.
Where's Johnny at?
Johnny's getting divorced,
Pop.
Tell him not to worry.
It's not the end of the world.
Probably best not
to tell him anything.
No, you're right,
you're right.
So this whole little court
chitchat gets caught up, okay?
- I gotta get going.
- What do you mean?
You just got here.
I'll see you in the morning.
We can bust up more shit.
- Who's gonna clean it up?
- You are?
- Me? Oh, bullshit.
- Walk me to the door.
All right.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh, yeah,
I wanna ask you,
things with Sandy
are better, I hope.
Better. Thanks.
Yeah. Good girl.
Don't let her go, son.
She's too good,
tell you that.
- She's great.
- Yeah.
I finally cut off
that other deal.
I gotta stay
at what's right for me.
Can't let it be said
that the apple or whatever
doesn't fall far
from the tree.
Yeah, right, hey, hey,
hey, hey, get out of here.
- Right.
- Yeah. See you tomorrow.
Right.
One other thing.
They're coming after me again.
Yeah, I know.
- You hang in there, Pop.
- Okay.
All right.
Looking good.
Where's Johnny at?
He told me
to saddle your horse.
Just warming him up for you.
I hope you don't mind.
- Why would I mind?
- Okay.
Hadn't lost
too much there, son.
Good. Yeah.
Getting long
in the tooth here, so.
Need all the help,
I can get.
Yeah. Thank you.
Thank you, darlin'.
Whoa. Whoa. Yeah.
Once I'm up here...
I feel a lot better
than I do down on the ground,
that's for damn sure.
You know, you never answered
my question about what happened.
Of course I did.
You just don't listen.
I have no idea.
So he just disappeared.
Seems kind of impossible,
don't you think?
I been over this
a thousand times.
How many teen suicides
do you think there are
yearly in America,
let alone Texas?
- I don't know.
- Well, look it up
on your Google deal.
Lake Brownwood
or any of these other lakes
throughout the state?
All right?
Just chalk another one up.
That's all you have to say.
Well, what else is there?
You know...
I missed you, Dad.
Even if I don't understand you,
and I'd like to know you better.
But I guess both
of our hearts are closed.
Maybe that's the problem.
Maybe.
And I guess you'll never accept
that I'm gay.
Benny, Ben boy, I... I...
I mean...
why you do what you do,
whatever you do,
but I'm working on it,
son.
You are?
Then why don't you listen to me?
Why don't you put yourself
in my shoes?
We'll switch roles
for a minute.
-  Why would I do that?
- I tell you why.
What do you think happens
between two men?
What do you think we do
when we're in private?
I'm not so sure I want to know.
It makes no sense to me, son.
Well, I can explain it to you.
I can tell you.
I can tell you
exactly what happens.
Want to hear?
I'm not talking about
slow dancing and honky-tonk.
I'm talking about what happens
in the wee hours.
Want me to tell you?
I don't think so.
We could wait until another day.
- All right?
- All right.
Well, you can think about
or you cannot think about it,
but that's the situation.
That's what's going on.
15 years ago
is the same as today.
So you can put another gun
to my head and say,
"Get the fuck
off the Briggs ranch,"
or you can be a real man
and accept what's going on.
You just think about it.
Another thing...
Congratulations.
"Love" was a non-existent word
on this ranch.
And I heard you use it
the other day
when you were expressing
yourself to Maria.
I'd never heard you utter
that word once,
not even to mother years ago
before you run her off.
So congratulations.
Buried that word
a long time ago.
I feel uncomfortable
up here, you know?
I feel uncomfortable.
My mind goes round
and round and round and round.
Grown men do strange things,
Maria.
Grown men do strange things.
There's only two things
in my life
I wanted to tell you,
all right?
I already told you one.
And the other?
It'll have to wait...
to another day.
Let's go up top, okay?
Did you bring picnic?
What'd you cook?
- Yeah, it's right there.
- Oh, yeah where?
The day you cook.
I'm trying... trying to remember
when you were a little girl,
we planted a tree.
It was there over there...
I can't remember which...
Which one.
It was you...
me and your mama planted it.
I don't really remember.
Oh, you...
You don't remember?
Well, you were
too busy chasing boys.
Liar.
- What?
- Liar.
No liar.
No, I'm not a liar.
You always sing the same song,
but never finish it.
I never finish it?
Well.
Let's go on up here.
Let's see what's up here.
You always...
You always liked
this horse, didn't you?
You always said it was
the best horse you ever sat on.
That's for sure.
Well,
starting tomorrow morning,
he's no longer mine,
he belongs to you.
You're gonna ride him
from here on in.
- Are you serious?
- Oh, I'm serious.
He's my gift to you, Maria.
Just enjoy it.
I won't be needing him
anymore.
Wow.
How many sunsets
has a person seen
in a lifetime, I wonder.
Quite a few, I imagine.
No, the deal is,
how many are left?
- Let's go on back.
- Let's go.
Watch out for the holes.
I interviewed your son,
Ben,
and I know that you and him
are lying about Jimmy Davis.
I also know that you
and that Peter Rogers
had an agreement concerning me
and possibly my son.
You think you're above
the law, Mr. Briggs.
People like you don't make
the world a better place.
You think you do.
I'm going to find out
what it is that you do
when nobody's watching you.
Ezekiel...
Can't forget...
I forget where it is.
It's, uh...
The Lord thy God loved thee...
having ingrained thee
upon the palms of my hands.
You don't like what I like?
- No, I don't like it.
- Why not?
You can change the damn thing.
Change it.
What do you like?
What's, what's...
- Oh, reggae, you like reggae?
- Not reggae.
Why don't you sing something?
- What?
- You sing something.
All right. Turn it off.
I'll sing you a song
that I sing to Maria,
and I'll give you $50,000
if you can get the end of it.
- All right?
- All right.
My uncle sang it.
That's all he knew.
He was drunk all the time,
but, you know.
I gotta guess the end?
You don't even know the end.
No, I don't know the end.
So how you gonna know
if I have the right end?
Well... I'll know.
I'll know.
Let me hear you,
let me hear your...
Ramp it up, ramp it up.
I'll finish it.
Getting horny for what?
Okay.
I'm very sorry...
that I couldn't
understand you.
I'm sorry that when
you were all grown up,
I made it all about me
because like most men,
I wanted a perfect family,
but like most men,
I was not a perfect husband
or father.
Yeah.
And I'm sorry because I know
we cannot start over.
And that's what I'm most
sorry about. So.
But I want you to know...
I accept you as you are
because you're my son.
I'm sorry, too.
- I've missed you.
-  Yeah?
And I accept you as you are
because you're my dad,
and you're the only dad I got.
Yeah.
- All right?
- Yeah.
You're a good boy.
What are we doing here?
Well...
there's something
I gotta do, Benny.
- Dad...
- No, no.
I gotta make things right.
Yeah. Trust me.
Let's go.
This won't take too long,
I hope.
Hello? Anyone home?
Hello? Anybody home?
Hello? Hello?
Who are you? What are you doing
in my house?
Uh, I knocked.
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear it.
Uh...
I wanted to tell you
what happened to your son.
- My son?
-  Yes. Yes, ma'am.
Who are you?
I know you.
I'm Scott Briggs.
We met before.
This is my youngest son.
He knew your boy.
They rode horses together.
Yeah.
You are really Scott Briggs.
Yes, ma'am, I am.
And you have to hear
what I'm gonna tell you.
It's difficult.
A horse kicked your boy,
kicked him and...
killed him instantly.
A what?
How do you know?
I was there.
Easy son, easy. Move slow.
I know this horse. Easy.
Come on out.
No one's gonna hurt you, son.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Oh, Lord, what do I do?
What have I done?
Oh, son, son.
And I couldn't face anyone
'cause everything I did
caused it, but I didn't do it.
It was kinda like a...
a hit and run,
but I didn't do it.
What happened?
Where's my Jimmy?
-  Your Jimmy?
- Yes.
Tell me!
Oh! Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am. I will.
I got confused, went crazy.
- Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
- Dad!
Dad, let him go!
Let him go!
My mind broke down
and went in...
went in circles.
I didn't know what to do.
So what I did was
the cowardly thing.
I... I buried him.
I dug a big hole,
and I buried him.
And I had to come
tell you this today.
I had to.
I'm sorry.
What kind of man are you?
Well, lady, grown men
do strange things sometimes.
We had to make... a grave.
The storm washed it away
four years ago.
You ungodly thief.
You... you had a grave with...
With our body.
You left us without nothing.
Without nothing!
It was an accident.
- No!
-  It was an accident.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
Please go. Please go.
Don't... don't touch me.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
You walk hand in hand
with the Devil.
I had to come to you today
'cause my time's up.
Please go.
- Hey, hey.
- No. No.
Don't touch me.
It's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
What kind of a man you are.
What kind of a man
you are.
It's okay.
My son.
Thank you for coming, Ben boy.
I'm a coward.
Thank you. Thank you.
Dad...
I never wanna see you again
for the rest of your life.
Okay.
I knew you might be coming along
this way today.
How you know that?
I just do.
That's how I am.
I hear your son ropes
pretty good.
Yeah.
Texas state champion.
Johnny says he knows
your husband.
- Says he's a pretty good guy.
- You're blocking my door.
I'm sorry.
Hell of a Marine.
- Yeah, Marine pilot.
- Mm.
My dad's a good guy, too.
I hope you know that.
I want you to stay away
from my father.
I don't care if you're a...
lady Ranger or whatever.
He's the only father I've got,
and I gotta make sure
I look out for him.
What can I do for you?
Don't interrupt me.
I want you to stay
away from my dad.
He doesn't need this.
That's the bottom line.
I hope you hear me.
Anything else?
No, ma'am, not right now.
You're very brave
or very stupid.
Excuse me.
You have a good day.
Oh...
I think I'll take a little...
A little snooze here.
Yeah. Yeah.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too,
Ben boy, little Benny.
I love you, too.
Yeah.
If God won't forgive me...
maybe you will someday...
I hope.
Ooh..
You're a good boy.
There she is,
the girl of my dreams.
You've been saying
that since we were kids.
When we were kids,
we would play cowboys
and Indians like the kids do.
You know, only we would do it
with real horses.
And guess who always...
always got the role
of the Indian girl.
But now the Indian girl
wears a badge.
Yeah.
You wanna go for a ride?
You bet.
Let's go.