What?
Who might be
interrupting me prayers?
Oh, it's you patty.
Well, why would you
be talkin' to me?
You know, i'm just
a poor cobbler.
What can i do?
Ahh, i see.
But, why me?
Well, i'll do me best.
Aye. Well, i've always had
a lot of faith in you, too.
Knock it off!
Excuse me, sir.
How much farther?
You're going to
erinville, right?
Yes, sir.
Oh, not
too much further,
i'd say erinville is right
at the end of that rainbow.
Got a pot of gold waiting
there for you, do you?
Pot of gold?
Well sure!
Leprechauns hide
their gold
at the end
of rainbows.
What's a leprechaun?
Why, i thought everybody
knew about leprechauns.
A leprechaun is an elf from ireland
with special powers of his own.
If you capture one he's got
to take you to his pot of gold,
and grant
you three wishes.
But be careful, if you let him
out of your sight for one moment
he's gone
and owes you nothing.
Do you think there's
leprechauns in erinville?
I recall a rumor that there's
a leprechaun around erinville.
But mind you,
it was just a rumor.
Where did it go?
The rainbow?
Don't be worryin'
yourself none, laddie.
I know where
we're goin'.
You don't think you're being
a little too obvious, do you?
No. As a matter
of fact, i don't.
It's part
of the plan.
Seems to me the last thing
sam needs is a dreamer.
Why don't you just
help me with the ladder?
Why don't you just ask her to
marry you and get it over with?
Cause she'll say no!
You two boys need to have
some faith. Learn to believe.
She needs someone who has at
least one foot on the ground.
What she needs
is me,
and fortunately
i'm available.
Right on time.
See ya, boys.
Good morning,
good morning!
'Morning.
The usual?
Yes, indeed.
So Alex, what
kind of scientist
are we studying
to be today?
An epidemiologist.
A what?
An
epidemiologist.
Somebody who studies epidemics-
you know, like the black plague?
Sounds pretty
serious to me.
It is.
Your niece and
nephew coming today?
Yeah.
How long since
the plane crash?
Almost 6 months.
Well, if anybody can help
them face reality, you can.
I hope so.
Ta, ta!
See ya.
Come in.
Getting settled okay?
I'm glad you decided to
come up here for the summer.
Mom said being here was
like being in heaven.
So i figured maybe that will
make it easier for him to find me.
Hey, you're going
to have a great time.
And i'm sure you'll have
all sorts of adventures.
Adventures?
Well sure.
Hey, just look out there.
Who knows what adventures
are waiting for you out there.
Why don't you come
downstairs for a bite to eat?
Okay.
Are you coming?
Be right there.
Becky?
Becky!
We were just about
to have some lunch.
What?
I said we were just
about to have lunch.
No thanks.
Are you sure?
I made some
chicken...
i'm not hungry.
Okay...
star gazing?
Yeah.
Did you ever
see so many stars?
There's the
big dipper.
See it?
Yeah.
And there's
the north star,
it's helped many a lost
soul find their way home.
Really?
Alex has
a telescope.
Maybe tomorrow she can
show you how to use it.
Okay.
Time for bed.
Goodnight,
aunt sam.
honey.
Goodnight,
ace.
I sure hope dad knows
about the north star.
Vrooommm...
ready for landing?
Ready!
Okay, here we go!
Again! Again!
Sorry, Tommy. It's
time for me to go.
Tell me what it's
like up there, again.
It's beautiful.
You feel like you're floating
over and through the clouds
and the earth's
real small below.
It's heaven!
I wish i could
go up with you.
We'll see to it that
you get your wish.
When i get back,
i'll fly you up there.
Promise?
With ace as my
witness, i promise.
Guys, breakfast!
Hey, you're late.
The shop's open.
Not to worry my dear
friend, not to worry.
All right,
i'll bite.
Why aren't you
across the street?
It's part
of the plan.
Today, i go in
a little late.
Each day
a little later.
Til she misses me
and i won't go in at all.
Yeah, so?
That's the night
i ask her to marry me.
I'm telling you,
it'll work.
Ted, you
missed a spot.
Good morning.
The usual?
Thank you
very much.
Hello.
Don't i get a "good
morning" out of you?
Good morning!
Who's your
new friend?
My cousin,
Tommy.
Hi, Tommy.
Welcome to erinville.
I'm rick callahan.
Are you
a policeman?
No, close though.
I'm a fireman.
Ever see a real
fire truck up close?
Mine's across the street.
Want to take a look at it?
Yeah!
Come on,
i'll race you!
Wait!
We keep some of our
emergency equipment in here.
This ladder will get us up as
high as 3 floors if we need to.
More emergency
equipment here.
What's
that thing?
What, this?
This is the main
water hook up.
You hook this up to the
fire hydrant on the street
with the hoses here.
Jump up here and
i'll show you the cab.
That's spot.
We rescued her from
the top of a tree.
Found she
had no owner,
so we kept her.
Haven't seen
a mouse since.
Never saw
one before.
That may
be true, but...
i see mr. Conners
has caught your eye.
Full of blarney he is,
but he's loved
by the whole town.
He's a leprechaun
if there ever was one.
A leprechaun?
There's no such
thing as a leprechaun.
No such thing?
That's right.
Fairies and all that
stuff are just made up.
They don't really exist.
How can you
be so sure?
Because you can't
scientifically prove it.
That may be true,
but there was
once a time
when scientists couldn't prove
bacteria and viruses existed.
They were laughed at
'til the microscope
was invented, right?
Yeah, you're right.
That discovery
led to vaccines and cures.
That's exactly right.
So don't be so quick
to disbelieve
because you can't see
or prove something existed.
You might miss
some pretty neat stuff.
Remember belief
precedes the miracle.
Rick, i believe
in eating!
Where's our food?
Uh-oh, gotta
go guys, i forgot!
See you guys later.
I still say there's no
such thing as leprechauns.
And i say there are
and he is one.
Is not.
Is too.
Mr. Conners is just
a nice old man
who tells stories
down at the diner.
He is one, and
i can prove it.
How?
We'll capture him!
Yeah, right.
Then, we'll get our wish.
I still say
he's a leprechaun.
Is not.
Is too.
Is not!
Look it up.
An irish elf
who works as a shoemaker.
See!
A shoemaker?
He keeps a pot of gold.
Upon capture, the leprechaun
must disclose his location of gold
and grant his
captors three wishes.
Told ya!
Whoa!
Stay down! Keep low!
Hurry! Hurry!
I see him.
He's coming.
Don't forget,
if he gets away,
he doesn't have to
give us three wishes.
I know, i know.
That's if he's
a leprechaun.
Don't!
He'll see you.
But how are we
supposed to see him?
We should be
hiding over there.
That way we
can watch him.
Okay, but let's make it
quick so he doesn't see us.
The next time
he stops, we'll run.
What happened?
I think he saw me!
Are you sure?
No, but he's
still coming.
Then he probably
didn't see you.
Let's go!
Hoo hooo!
Halt!
You're captured!
What's this?
Miniature bandits?
We're not bandits.
But we know
who you are!
And who might that be?
You're a leprechaun,
and since we caught you,
you have to take us
to your pot of gold
...and grant
us three wishes.
A leprechaun is it?
My, my Alex!
I never realized
you were a storyteller, too!
Tommy thinks
you're a leprechaun.
Tommy is it?
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
Liam patrick conners,
at your service.
What gives you this notion
i'm a leprechaun?
And don't think you
can get away from me.
I'm sure i couldn't, even
if i were a leprechaun.
I told you
he isn't one!
I didn't say that!
Then
you are one?
And i didn't
say that.
So are you a
leprechaun or not?
What if i told you
i was an angel?
Angels have wings.
Oh they do,
do they?
And what might
a leprechaun look like?
Like you.
You two have got me
in quite a spot here.
If i tell you i'm not a
leprechaun you'll think i'm lying
so i can be on my way.
Tommy, you can't
judge a book by its cover.
Especially an old one.
Huh?
It's not what a person looks like
that makes them what they are.
It's the intent
of their hearts
and the good they are willing
to do for others that matters.
He's trying to tell you
he's not a leprechaun, Tommy.
So you can't grant
me three wishes?
No, i can't.
If only we could find
the lost faeden...
the what?
The what?
Surely you've heard the
legend of the lost faeden?
What's a faeden?
The faeden is
a small gold flute,
the king of the fairies uses to
play the song of the creator on.
It helps all the other
fairies see the glory
and the wonder
and the beauty of life.
And Tommy, it's also what
he uses to grant wishes.
And it's lost?
Aye.
That's quite a story.
You see, one day
the king of the fairies
comes to me
with a special order...
to make shoes
for all the fairies.
They've got this
wonderful ball coming up.
They're going to
have funny fireflies hanging...
but that's another story.
But anyway,
after he left
i realized he'd left
his faeden behind.
I put it in me safe for
safekeeping awaiting his return.
But that night,
as i was working late,
a young man busts into me
shop and demands all me money.
And i give it to
him, every cent.
But that wasn't enough for him,
he wanted the faeden as well.
I told him,
"it's no use to you"
"since you don't know
how to use it."
But he took it anyway.
I chased him
as far as i could,
but i lost him.
He got away from me.
But he didn't get
away from the others.
What others?
Why, the fairies,
of course.
He tried to make his get away
through these fields and woods.
But he never made it.
What happened?
Well, the police found
his body in the river.
Poor soul.
They never knew for sure
what happened to him,
but i do.
What?
C'mere.
The pooka.
The pooka?
Shhh...! Aye,
an odd fairy that one.
Comes at night
in the shape of a horse,
and beckons you
to ride him.
But if you
mount his back,
he'll take you
on a death ride
that you'll
never survive...
unless you're one
of the bravest at heart.
Wait a minute.
If they got
the thief,
then the king
got his faeden back!
No lass, seems that he lost
it somewhere on the fairy ride.
Then the fairies know
where it is, right?
No, according
to the legend,
this area is still filled with
fairies all looking for the flute.
Really?
Aye lad, and they'll
find it someday.
But i kinda feel
responsible for it
and i'd like
to find it first
so i could give
it back to the king meself.
So i come here everyday
looking for it.
It's here somewhere,
in these fields and woods.
But alas,
the going's slow because
me eyes aren't
what they used to be.
We could help
you look for it.
It'll be like
a treasure hunt.
Aye, you could
at that,
and a fine treasure
we might find.
But i don't know...
look, look, look there!
What do you see?
I don't see
anything.
Nothing?
Trees.
Only trees?
And look,
what's that over there?
Clouds!
Clouds.
And
that's all?
What about
the wind? Listen.
Did you hear 'em?
Ahh, never mind.
I can see i've
got me work cut out.
You've got
a lot to learn.
This is not a task for
the faint of heart, you know.
I'm brave.
Are you now?
The fairies don't want anybody
else to find the faeden.
You'll have to be smart
to avoid their traps.
I'm very smart.
Aye, i knew
that about you.
You'll have to learn to
believe in many wondrous things.
These fields and woods
are full of things
you've never
seen or heard before.
We'll learn.
You will?
You'll learn.
Well, that's different!
Why not, then?
We'll meet
back here tomorrow,
and that's when
our journey will begin!
That is, if it's all right
with your mother, Alex.
Let's see what
time it is here?
Here, hold that.
Ahh, it's
getting late!
She's going
to be worried.
Off with you, now.
Go on, go on!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Leprechauns, is it?
Well, why not?
What?
What do you mean you don't
like the way i'm doing it?
I am a storyteller,
not a preacher.
No, you can't put angels
with leprechauns and fairies,
it would
ruin the story!
Besides, you could play
one of the fairies.
Well, you've got
the wings for it.
Ah, patty,
where's your sense of humor?
So, how was
everyone's day?
Great!
We caught
a leprechaun.
We snuck up behind a stump,
jumped out and caught him.
That's great, honey.
Becky, how was your day?
Fine.
Tomorrow take a book
and go down to the lake.
I didn't bring any books.
We can fix that.
Mr. Conners said we could help
him look for the lost faeden.
Then maybe the fairy king
could grant us three wishes.
Could i be excused?
The lost what?
The lost faeden.
A gold flute that
was stolen from him.
Could i be excused, please!?
What is wrong?
I've had enough!
You're excused.
Can we please help him
find it, mom?
Find what?
The faeden.
Look, i don't want you
two bothering mr. Conners.
I know he
likes to tell stories,
and they're nice to
listen to but you can't...
but,
he needs our help.
And besides it'll be
like an adventure. Yeah!
I'll talk to him.
Yes!
When did that happen?
I'm on the phone.
I needto
talkto you.
It's my aunt.
I got to go. Bye.
Come in.
I'm sorry.
Just sometimes i get
so tired of hearing
about what Tommy
and the stuffed bird did.
I see.
I seem to recall
a little girl
who wouldn't go anywhere
without sebastian.
That was different.
You're right.
Sebastian wasn't the last
gift your dad ever gave you.
Do you know why he carries
around that dumb bird?
He thinks dad's
coming back.
If he doesn't have
it, dad won't find him.
Look, he's only seven.
You sound just
like my mom.
Why don't you just
make him understand
that dad's never
coming back.
I know losing your
dad still hurts,
but i promise, in time
the hurt will heal.
You may feel like there's
nothing left to believe in.
Like there's a big empty
place in your heart.
What am i supposed
to put in there?
I wish
i knew, becky.
I wish i knew.
Good morning to ya.
And what
have we here?
A metal detector!
A machine that...
my, what a good idea!
And that's not all.
A map, so we know
where we've searched.
Aren't you
the smart one?
I'm glad you're
on this hunt with us.
Look! Here's where we are
at the edge of the woods.
We've got all this
area here to cover.
Whoa...
that's a
lot of area.
Well, if you've got
something better to do?
No.
Tommy, today
you're the leader.
Where we gonna go?
That way.
All right, then...
onward!
½ it's heard on the wind
and the wings of summer. ½
½ softly it sings
ta-loo ta-lee. ½
½ echoing sweetly
as we once wondered ½
½ where can we find
the answers we seek? ½
½ so sweetly
its melody shows the secret ½
½ to all with
a broken heart to heal. ½
½ it's found in the dreams
of the child that seeks it ½
½ the end of the rainbow
is always so near. ½
½ look to the sky when your
heart feels like flying. ½
½ race with the clouds
til the sun sets. ½
½ look deep inside
when it's joy that ye seek. ½
½ it is easy
when you but believe. ½
½ when looking
through eyes of imagination ½
½ all that surrounds
you blossoms anew. ½
½ from fields of clover
to sweet carnation ½
½ the colors of life
now burst into view. ½
½ so tarry awhile
in this land enchanted ½
½ found in that
place deep within. ½
½ there you'll find peace. ½
½ there you'll find joy. ½
½ it is waiting
if you but believe. ½
½ open your eyes
and believe. ½
we've covered
a lot of ground.
I think it's
time for a rest.
How about under
this fine house?
It's
not a house.
It's our tree.
Your tree,
is it?
Looks like a fine
solid house to me.
Tommy?
Looks like
a tree to me.
Let's take a seat
under your tree.
Come on, help the
old man down here.
Easy does it.
Oh, my goodness.
Well,
i can see you two are
going to need a little help.
What are these?
Training wheels for
your imagination.
Someday you won't need them,
but for now put them on.
All right now, both of
you, close your eyes.
Alex, you're no
longer a little girl,
but a sweet,
gentle squirrel.
And Tommy, you're a little
bird, a beautiful blue bird.
Now think.
Both of you think.
Now, squirrel, open your
eyes, and what do you see?
I see grass...
really tall grass.
And bluebird,
open your eyes.
Tell me what you see.
I see brown, just brown.
It can't be just
brown, must be something,
sometimes you have to
stand back to see the truth.
The tree!
Aye, the tree!
Squirrel,
do you see the tree?
Uh huh.
Okay, both of you up the tree.
What do you see?
Explore the tree.
Squirrel,
you've come to a hole.
Take a look inside.
Tell me
what you see.
It's my house!
Ahh,
your house is it?
Bluebird,
can you find your house?
Found it!
All right,
you can come down now.
Now tell me, what
are you sitting under?
A house.
You can take your
glasses off now.
Alex, i'm sure if you
imagined hard enough
you could see things from
a squirrel's point of view,
but you didn't
actually become one.
Do you understand?
I guess so.
But how could
it seem so real?
I don't know.
But there's always a logical,
rational, explanation,
even if i can't
think of it right now.
Okay?
Bye, honey.
Bye, mom.
Bye, rick.
Bye, Alex.
Do you always tell her
there's a rational
explanation for everything?
Oh, sure.
It's disquieting
to kids to give them
all sorts of fantastical explanations
and silly reasons for things.
It makes
them unsure.
But what about the
things you can't explain?
We won't be
too late.
Take your time. I
get paid by the hour.
Yeah. Well?
Look, nothing's
come up, yet.
Yeah, but it might. Then
what are you gonna do?
½ ll-de-di, ll-de-di,
ll-de-di... ½
what are
you humming?
Oh... that's a tune the fairy
king plays on the faeden.
C'mere, c'mere.
Listen,
can you hear them?
Who?
The fairies,
of course.
I don't
hear anything.
Nothing?
Just the birds.
Aye, the birds and the
wind through the trees
and the animals
rushing through the field.
During the day, the fairies play
along with the sounds of the meadow
and at night to the
crickets and the owls.
If you listen very
carefully, you can hear them.
Well, come along now.
But be careful!
Don't let their
music distract you.
If you're
not very careful,
they could lure
you into a fairy ring.
A fairy ring?
Aye,
step in one of those
and the fairies
will have you dancing
to their tune
for seven years.
Hee, hee, hee!
½ ll-de-dl-de-
dl-de-di... ½
whoo! I think i'm
caught in a fairy ring.
Tommy, can you
help me, please?
Alex, do you think you
can pull us out of here?
You're kidding!
Oh, i wish i was there.
You're not going
to believe what i'm looking at.
My deranged brother and my misfit
cousin are dancing around with,
get this, a leprechaun
they caught yesterday.
Don't ask.
I wish i was
anywhere but here.
What about the
faeden? The what?
The faeden.
We were looking
for the faeden.
Oh,
that's right!
Look, we're safe now,
and it's all because of you.
What did i do?
You reminded us
of our goal
and it broke
the fairies' spell.
Let's sit down.
How come?
You see, fairy rings
only work on people
who've forgotten what's
important in their lives.
Once they
do that,
the fairies have them
chasing here and there
after
frivolous things,
running around in
circles and going nowhere.
Why would
they do that?
Because fairies
love to laugh.
You must admit,
we looked pretty silly.
We outsmarted
them that time,
but i think we'd
better mark the map
so we don't venture
into that ring again.
We were right about
there, don't you think?
I think we've covered enough
ground for one day, don't you?
Tell me, do you
still hear the music?
Yes.
½ ll-de-di... ½
½ la-la-la-la-la-la-la... ½
What are you
humming, honey?
I'm humming
to the fairies' music.
The what?
The crickets and
owls and the wind.
Ohh.
Darn.
Maybe
a fairy did it.
Maybe a chicken bone
fell in.
See? A bone.
No fairy.
Maybe a fairy
put it there.
A fairy didn't
I did.
Probably because i
wasn't paying attention.
Maybe a fairy
distracted you.
A fairy had nothing
to do with this.
Alex, you
know better.
There are no such
things as fairies.
But how do
you know that?
Because, i say so.
Now enough
of this nonsense.
Well, because... there's no
scientific evidence they exist.
Not yet,
but where would we be
if people didn't believe
in creatures so small
you couldn't see
them with your eyes.
They were laughed at.
Gosh,
i'm tired, Alex.
And, who tells you the answer to
your test when your mind goes blank,
and all of the sudden
it comes back to you
as though somebody whispered
it to you in your ear?
Maybe you
should study law.
Oh, i see him.
Yeah, and he's being
chased by a caterpillar.
Where's the legs?
Oh, i see him, yes!
Wait a minute,
he's a tyrannosaurs.
Well, hello there.
Would you
like to join us?
I said, would you like
to see the parade with us?
Yeah, you just missed
the catapilla-saurus.
I think
i'll pass.
Aunt sam
wants you guys.
Oh, it's time
to go, then.
Oh, man...
the parade will be
back another day.
Wanna race me home? Yeah!
How about helping an
old man to his feet?
Up we go.
Hello,
i'm liam conners.
The leprechaun.
I guess you've been
talking to Alex and Tommy.
You must be Tommy's
sister, becky.
We were just looking
at the clouds.
There's so much
to see up there.
In the clouds?
Aye, you have to
know how to look.
Look again.
Do you see that little
girl floating in the air?
Yeah, i guess i do see her.
Aye, but she looks
sad and lonely
as if she misses someone
who was very special to her.
My boyfriend never called
yesterday to wish me happy birthday.
Oh, but a lovely
lass like that...
she must have
many friends.
No, i think this is someone
who's very special to her
who she's
angry at.
Who might
that be?
My dad.
If he hadn't died
then i wouldn't be here,
alone and forgotten
on my birthday.
I wish i was home.
Now, don't
be like that,
always wishing you
were somewhere else.
You're missing out
on what's here.
Here?
What's here!
There's not
even a mall.
What good is a mall?
A place to go out
with my friends.
Well tell me, what did
you do at this mall?
I dunno.
Just hung out.
Oh, i see. You did
nothing at the mall.
You could be doing
the same thing here.
What else?
What do you mean
what else?
What else do
you like to do?
You know, i've learned
everyone has a secret wish
deep down
in their hearts.
Something they
want to do
more than anything
else in the world,
if only they had
the courage to try.
I guess i always wanted to
learn how to ride a horse.
Ahhh...
what?
Yes, i know.
No, i... yes,
no, no...
i quite agree.
Who are you
talking to?
Listen.
I don't hear
anything.
Nothing?
The wind?
Aye. I frequently
ask the wind for help
when i have
a problem.
Does it
ever answer?
Aye, if you're patient
and sincere in the asking.
The wind always answers in
its own way and its own time.
Maybe i should try.
Aye, lass,
maybe you should.
Did you hear it?
I hear the breeze,
but i don't hear any words.
Aye, lass.
It isn't easy,
but this i know,
when it's truly important
for you to hear
what the wind
has to say,
you'll hear it.
But you won't
hear it here,
you'll hear
it right here.
And with practice
it gets easier.
Then you can
ask it anything...
what to do
on a sunny day,
the answers
to your problems,
how to fill the
emptiness in your heart.
How does
the wind know?
The wind is only
the messenger.
But how does...
mr. Conners?
Mr. Conners?
I'm afraid of horses.
You see it?
Yeah.
It's a bird.
Hey, that looks like
where my nest was.
You guys, c'mon.
Lunch is ready.
Last one to the
porch is a pooka!
Go!
That's not fair!
No way!
I won!
You're the pooka.
You got
a head start.
I'm not the
pooka, you are.
I won. That means
i'm not the pooka.
Yes, you are.
I'm probably going
to be sorry i asked,
but what's
a pooka?
The pooka is a bad fairy
that looks like a horse
that takes you on a ride
that you'll never survive
unless you're
very, very brave.
Oh yeah? I'd say neither
of you are pookas.
Come on.
Wait, i left
ace in the tree.
Get him later.
No, we have to
be ready to fly.
What?
Scott and cindy?
I don't believe it!
That's just
great, lori.
Yeah, thanks for calling.
Now i know what kind
of friends i have.
One less question
for the wind, i guess.
Where to now?
I'd say that way.
Hold it! Hold it!
What's wrong?
I'm not sure, but i
just got a funny feeling.
Do you feel
anything different?
Sorta.
Aye, i thought so.
We'd better put our
jackets on backwards.
Why are we
doing this?
Pixies!
We don't want to
get pixie-led in there.
Pixie-led?
Aye.
Have you ever
been on a trip
and suddenly the trip was over
you can't even
remember the trip?
Yeah, that
happened to me
on the way to
grandma's last year.
More than likely a pixie
caught your attention.
You were
pixie-led, Tommy!
That doesn't
sound so bad.
That's only
the first step.
Given enough time, a pixie
will get you so confused
that you'll start looking for
happiness in all the wrong places.
And once you
get pixie-led,
unless someone
else helps,
you could stay
lost forever.
So how does it help to put
our coats on backwards?
Don't you see,
it confuses them.
They can't tell whether
we're coming or going.
Bring the map.
Ready for bed?
You still miss him,
don't you?
Yeah, i wish he'd
hurry and come back.
Tommy, you know
that he can't...
i mean you do know
where your dad really is?
He's in...
heaven.
That's
right.
And when people go to
heaven they don't come back.
But he always
comes back.
He promised
he'd come back.
Ace was
his witness.
But what if he
can't come back?
Me and ace have
figured it out.
He's been pixie-led,
we'll fix that as soon
as we find the faeden.
Good night, Tommy.
Good night, ace.
Boy, you're really
dragging it out, today.
I ain't going
in today, boys.
Part of the plan.
Oh yeah, the plan.
Take a look at this,
tonight is the night!
Good luck!
We'll be standing by when you
get blown out of the water.
You think so?
I don't think so.
I'm a pretty
lucky guy.
A man with a plan.
Nothing today, again.
All this time i've been
dreaming of finding it
but still nothing.
Aye, i've been dreaming
about it as well.
But maybe it was only
meant to be a dream.
What's the point
of a dream
if it doesn't
come true?
Now hold it,
hold on, both of you.
What was it that christopher
columbus was dreaming of?
I know, a new way
to get to india.
Aye, and it was that dream
that gave him the courage
to brave the unknown
perils of the ocean.
But, he didn't find
what he was looking for.
Exactly, instead he
discovered a whole new world.
But we didn't
find anything.
Ah, didn't you now?
More often than not
the search proves more
valuable than the treasure.
I promise you, you've both
found far more than you realize
and you're closer
than you think.
Come along,
then.
The faeden's
waitin'.
Don't run,
you guys.
Did you talk
to mr. Conners today?
Don't answer.
It's a trap.
Ahh, you two,
hold on, hold on!
You're wearing me out...
an old man like me.
It's time
for a rest.
No, not there.
Follow me.
Why out here?
As a precaution,
of course.
The bad fairyies can't
hurt you in moving water.
Who's got the map?
Let's see
how we're doing.
Look, only one
section left.
Darn, i wish
we could find it.
Shush, don't go
throwing wishes around.
Why not?
Because they
might come true.
What's wrong
with that?
It might not be
what you really need.
I don't understand.
I once heard
of a woman
who all of her life
wanted to be very rich.
One day, she caught a
fairy and she got her wish.
The next day, she got a big
check from an insurance co.
Because her poor husband
had died in an accident.
She got her wish, but became
a lonely old widow for it.
It's the nature
of fairy magic.
They can't give
without taking.
Well then, what
should we wish for?
If you must
wish for something,
wish for strength of heart,
inspiration and courage.
Always wish for things
you're willing to work for.
What if a fairy wish was the
only way a wish could come true?
Then you're wishing for
things that shouldn't be.
I still wish i could
find the faeden.
Well in that case, i'll just have
to make sure you get your wish.
Promise?
With ace as my
witness, i promise.
The banshees!
No, not yet,
i tell you.
I need more time!
Mr. Conners,
are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm all right, dear.
Just lost my breath
for a moment.
What's the banshee?
The banshee?
Well, it's a
messenger of sorts.
What did it say?
It said
i may be goin' away.
Where will
you be going?
Where the
wind lives.
No.
You promised.
I didn't say it would
be easy now, did i?
Do you still want
to find the faeden?
You've learned to
trust your hearts
and believe in things
you can't always see?
What happens now is all
up to you, don't you see?
I was only
your guide.
You don't
need me anymore.
But we'll miss you.
Aye, i'll
miss you, too.
But don't be sad. There's
a purpose to everything.
Close your eyes.
Do you remember
the morning
when we danced
to the fairies' music?
Tell me what
you see and hear.
The birds.
The fields and the
woods... the forest.
Anything else?
I see Tommy... and you.
Tommy, do you
see me, too?
Yeah.
Whenever you need
to see me,
all you have to do is
to close your eyes,
listen for the
music of the meadow
and i'll be there.
Storm's coming in.
I cannot believe
you took me to a drive-in.
It was fun,
though.
It was okay.
What was the name
of the movie?
I knew you were
having a good time.
A falling star!
Make a wish... hurry!
Oh no,
not you, too!
What?
Oh, it's Alex.
Seems like since she's started
spending time with mr. Conners,
she can't stop talking
about fairies and magic.
What's wrong
with that?
She's eight years old.
She's got a
great imagination.
What's wrong
with it?
Yeah.
The other day she
takes one of her books
and renames
everything in it.
She crosses out
tree and writes "house."
She calls
the acorns "dinner"...
because she thinks she's
been changed into a squirrel.
I must have
missed something.
I don't get
the problem.
The problem is what if she
starts believing this stuff?
Starts believing
in fairies and magic
and inanimate objects
that are alive.
She's having fun.
Fun?
I don't think
it's fun.
I don't want Alex
believing in fairy tales,
and men in shining armor
and prince charming.
Don't you think you're going
a bit overboard with this?
What's wrong with a girl
believing in the dream
that a wish
will come true?
What's wrong
with it?
Yeah.
How about what's
going to happen
when some of those wishes
don't come true, huh?
I just think
that we can do
without the fairy tales
in my house.
Unless they're
your fairy tales.
What are you
talking about?
How about the one
that everything in life
can be explained rationally
or scientifically?
Oh, come on.
How about why her dad
never comes to visit her.
Try those fairy
tales, sam.
That's enough. I
think you'd better go.
I'd never tell
a little girl
that prince charming is
going to come into her life,
kiss her and take
all her troubles away.
Come on.
Maybe i do believe
there's a...
are you done?
Just forget
it, okay?
Fine. Forget it!
No, as a matter of fact,
i'm not done.
Just because you lost
all your hopes and dreams
doesn't give
you the right
to keep Alex from
having any of hers.
Now i'm done.
Why'd i ever put
you up there.
No angel has ever
listened to my prayers.
Can i talk to you for
a minute, mr. Conners?
Yes, i'm always willing
to listen and help.
That's what i want
to talk to you about.
You're not helping anybody
with all of your stories.
Now why would you be
saying a thing like that?
Because i'm concerned
about the effect
you and your stories are having
on the children's reality.
Their reality?
It's their reality that's
been harming them, miss gayle.
A little boy
who waits
for a father
who can't return.
A little girl
who believes that science
can answer
all her questions.
And a teen
who's afraid to dream
for fear of what
her dreams may contain.
You sound just
like rick.
Aye, and a fine
man he is
with both feet
on the ground.
Both feet!
He's a dreamer.
I don't think he even has
one foot on the ground.
Miss gayle...
try to focus for a moment
on the miracle of two words...
"what if?"
What if?
Aye, "what if?"
Isn't it those two words
that lead the scientists
to new discoveries,
the dreamer
to new worlds,
the weary to hope.
Where do your stories about
leprechauns and fairies lead?
I hope they lead to
that place in the heart
that reality
can't touch.
Do you remember?
What if?
Aye, what if.
Go ahead.
Try it.
I'm sure there's dreams
still living in your heart.
Allow yourself to feel
them, just one more time.
Aye, i see you
found the spot.
Go ahead, miss gayle.
Let your
heart believe...
believe even that
there may be angels
right here in erinville
that do hear and
answer your prayers.
Something is wrong
with mr. Conners.
Like what?
B-a-n-s-h-e-e...
A spirit whose wailing
foretells a coming death.
Death?
What are you doing?
Listening to the wind.
Is it sayin' anything?
Yeah, that i pick
lousy friends.
Still upset about scott not
calling on your birthday?
I'm sure he was
just... probably out.
Yeah, out with my
best friend, cindy.
Lori called
and told me.
Honey, i'm sorry.
Well, maybe this
is for the best?
What do you mean?
I suggested
to your mother
that maybe you should
all move up here.
It might make all our
lives a little easier.
She didn't say anything
to me about it.
We were waiting.
We figured once got here,
you wouldn't want to leave.
Yeah, right!
It's just something
to think about.
I'll ask
the wind.
Think it could answer
a few questions for me?
Couldn't hurt to try.
Hi, bill.
Hold on a second.
Kids,
time for dinner.
What brings
you about tonight?
I know the kids have been seeing
a lot of mr. Conners, lately.
So, i thought
you should know.
Liam's had a heart attack.
Is he going
to be okay?
They're not sure.
He's pretty bad.
What am i going
to tell the kids?
If you want,
i can tell them.
Tell who what?
Alex... Tommy...
come sit by me.
Tell us what?
Mr. Conners
is sick.
Sick?
What do you mean?
He had a heart attack
and is in the hospital.
Is he going
to die?
He may.
No!
Honey,
i'm sorry.
Alex?
Yeah?
What are you doing?
We have to
find the faeden.
find it, tonight.
We can't. It's dark.
We'll look tomorrow.
No, maybe it
will be too late.
We have to
find it, tonight.
Wait!
I'm going with you.
Alex, Alex?
Tommy?
The sooner we go, the
sooner we get back.
The woods look
scary in the dark.
Let's get ready.
Ready?
Ready!
Let's go find it.
Becky?
Huh?
Have you seen
Tommy and Alex?
No.
I better call rick.
Got any idea where
they might be?
Hi rick, it's me.
The kids are gone.
This way.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I think.
Yeah,
okay. C'mon.
It's all right.
I promise you
we'll find them.
They're good kids
hiding somewhere.
We just have to
figure out where.
I've called the firehouse,
the hospital,
and checked all the roads
to get there.
We're going to have
to search the woods.
All right,
let's do it.
You get the guys together
and let's get moving on it.
Hey, c'mon, it's
going to be all right.
We'll find them. I
promise you, all right?
Okay?
Okay.
Tommy, i think we'd better
stop and check the map.
Okay.
Do you think you know
where we are?
No. I don't
recognize anything.
We might have
been pixie-led.
Now what?
If we're lost, i think we
should stay right where we are.
But this i do know...
when it's important
enough for you to hear
what the wind
has to say,
you'll hear it.
Mr. Conners...
okay,
you know the drill.
It's going to be tough
to see because of this rain.
Work your area thoroughly.
Let's follow
all standard procedure.
Let's not forget
that these 2 kids
are cold and tired and
probably huddled up somewhere.
Keep your eyes peeled.
God be with us all
and good luck!
What was that?
Just the wind.
We've got to
get out of here.
But which way
do we go?
Let's turn around
and go back.
But which wy
is back?
The banshees!
They're after us!
The pooka!
The one who
got the robber!
Let's go!
Deputy, grab a
couple of people.
Check that ravine
over there.
What have you got?
Nothing to the north.
Make sure you
get up on the south ridge.
Look under rocks. There's a lot
of holes they could be hiding in.
Alex!
What's that sound?
It sounds like water.
The stream!
The bad fairies can't hurt
us if we're in the water.
Let's go!
Tommy!
We have to
go across.
But we don't know
how deep it is.
Do you think the
pooka will get us?
I don't know.
Do you think
we lost them?
Maybe.
I think we
should wade.
Stay close to the side
and follow the stream?
Okay?
Okay.
C'mon!
Be careful!
Look out!
Help! Help!
Grab the log!
Meg, what's that?
Bill,
i've got something.
Yeah, meg,
what is it?
It looks like
a metal detector
and a couple
pair of glasses.
Help! Help!
I need to see
liam conners.
Visiting hours aren't
until 9:00 a. m.
No, you
don't understand.
Is there a problem
i can help you with?
Yes, i need to
see mr. Conners.
My brother is lost and
he may know where he is.
Help! Help!
Trail ends here!
You sure?
Yeah.
Tommy!
Take the dogs up there
where it narrows.
See if you can't pick
up a scent over there.
Bill and i will
go down river.
You know where
this river goes?
Help!
Help somebody! Help!
Help! Please!
Tommy's?
Yeah.
I'm going to
cross here
and work my way
down to the falls.
Mr. Conners?
Mr. Conners,
it's becky.
It's about
Tommy and Alex.
I think they went to search
the last part of the woods.
I was hoping you'd
know where that was.
Follow the rainbow.
Let him sleep.
The medication
makes him hallucinate.
Where are we?
Behind
the waterfall.
We were lucky the log
caught onto the rock.
What do we do now?
We can't go forward
and we can't go back
the way we came.
I guess we'll
just have to wait.
I hope ace is okay.
Believe that there are angels
right here in erinville.
That do hear and
answer your prayers.
Dear god, please,
please help them.
The rainbow!
I don't think anyone's
gonna find us, here.
If only we
had the faeden,
then we could
wish our way out.
Look, what's that?
I don't know.
Liam patrick conners...
mr. Conners!
Open it!
That's it!
The faeden,
we found it.
Just like
mr. Conners promised.
Now we can
get our wishes.
Go ahead, Alex,
make your wish.
I don't know how
to use it, do you?
No.
Oh, that's right.
Mr. Conners said the
faeden was useless
unless you know
how to work it.
Oh great!
Tommy, why was
it so important
that you found
the faeden anyway?
I thought it was the only
way i could get my wish.
Great thinking.
If i'd known this
was going to happen,
i wouldn't have
wished for it.
Sorry.
It's all my fault.
What did mr. Conners mean
when he said we were close?
We couldn't
look in here.
So if there's a purpose
to everything, why here...
...behind the waterfall?
There's got to be more.
Look...
Alex, look!
What does
it say?
When you can't hear the
music of cricket and owl,
and the wind
isn't telling you answer,
when you look to the
sky and see only cloud,
to the forest
and see only tree, play me.
I'll open your eyes
and your heart.
Once again you will
see all the wonder
of the cricket, the owl,
the cloud and the tree,
and the wind-borne
song of the maker.
With hope you will see
you are never alone...
for someone who cares
will always be there.
One wish of the heart,
a child's simple plea,
each heard the same
if you play...
and believe.
Tommy?
Alex?
You said,
"follow the rainbow."
I followed it.
So, where are they?
Believe in what?
Magic?
Fairies?
Wishes?
No. Tommy,
think about it.
None of those things
are real.
We have to believe
in something bigger,
like the power
that made everything.
That's what mr. Conners
has been trying to tell us.
Okay,
but you go first.
We wish for
strength of heart
and the courage
to get out of here.
No, stop!
Those are the only things mr.
Conners said we should wish for.
That might count
as two wishes.
You might
be right.
We shouldn't
take any chances.
Go ahead, Tommy,
make the last wish.
Wish for your dad,
that's what you've
been waiting for.
I wish...
i wish...
i wish that mr. Conners
can have a good, long life.
My dad's
dead, Alex.
Wishing can't
change that.
He's in
a better place.
Please be there.
Please help us.
I don't understand.
They're behind
the waterfall.
Tommy! Alex!
I'll go get help.
The pooka is a bad fairy
that looks like a horse,
and will take you on a death
ride that you'll never survive,
unless you are
very brave.
Everyone has a secret wish
deep down in their hearts.
Something they want to do more
than anything else in the world...
if only they had
the courage to try.
I found them!
Hold on! Calm down.
Where are they?
Behind the waterfall
at the mountains.
Hold on.
Take it easy.
Rick. This is ted.
I think i've got
something for you.
Are they okay?
I don't know,
they're in the waterfall.
Yeah, go ahead, ted.
Yeah, becky is here,
says she found the kids.
Are they okay?
I don't know, she says
they're in a waterfall.
Let me talk to her.
Rick, they're
at the waterfall.
Becky, i was
just there.
Tell me
where they are.
They're behind
the waterfall.
Behind the waterfall
or in the waterfall?
They're behind
the waterfall.
Rick, crazy
leo used to tell us
about that secret
cave behind the falls.
Maybe it's true.
That's where
they are.
The wind told me.
Please, you've
got to believe me.
I believe you.
Ted, call old man baker
and have him
get his crane up
to miller falls, now.
Miller falls?
Are you crazy?
They'd never survive.
Let's hope you're wrong.
Have a little faith, pal.
Have a little faith.
I'll meet you there.
You are a very lucky
young lady.
I'd say your guardian angel
was working overtime last night.
So would i!
Yeah, mom.
We're fine.
No, i know,
don't worry.
And mom, if you're still thinking
about moving to erinville...
it's okay with me.
Well, then, who might
you be looking for?
Mr. Conners!
It gave us the courage to get
out from behind the waterfall.
The courage didn't
come from here.
It came from what
you believed, in here.
Mr. Conners!
Oh, Alex! Look, the three
of us, together again.
Oh, i love ya!
½ dl-da-dl-de-dl-da-di... ½
hey, dan.
'Morning, rick.
Giving your horse
a tour of the town?
Lightning hit my fence
last night. He bolted.
Strangest thing,
you know?
See you later.
You had a visitor
this morning.
Left you something.
Ted,
you missed a spot!
Rick, thank you
for saving my princess
and for helping me remember
the dreams i'd forgotten.
Dinner tonight? Sam.
½ when clouds of darkness
close in around you ½
½ look to that place
hidden inside. ½
½ there you'll find love
to wrap around you. ½
½ it's close to your heart
if you've eyes to see. ½
½ look high to the trees
and over the rainbow ½
½ to that secret place
deep inside. ½
½ there you'll find peace ½
½ there you'll find joy ½
½ it is waiting
if you but believe. ½