AGE OF
TOMORROW
No, I didn't leave
Lindsey home by herself.
No, the dog is there.
Sue, come on, don't you think
you're overreacting here?
Lindsey is almost 17,
I think she'll be fine.
I know it's my weekend with her.
Look I'll make it up to her okay?
Hello?  Sue?
Damn it!
Hi, you've reached
Lindsey Meyers phone.
If you're important,
please leave a message,
unless you're Jerry, then you
can go fuck yourself.  Thanks.
Hi Linds, it's dad.
Please change your voice-mail.
Anyway look.  I want to make
it up to you for working today.
So why don't we go to the movies tonight?
I'll see if I can get off early, okay?
Oh, and please remember to feed the dog.
And why don't you just stay home tonight?
The last time you went out,
your phone battery died
long enough for you to
come home stumbling drunk.
Next time your mum's gonna kill me.
Okay, gotta go.
I love you.  Bye.
Want to tell me what's so important
you couldn't tell me over the phone?
Last night's  meteor shower
caused a lot of damage
all over the country.
Nothing we can't handle.
- But Colonel.
- But what?
We've got bigger problems.
General Magowan.
How bad is the situation?
Mac, the president is so concerned,
my phone's been ringing off the hook.
The Pentagon is running scenarios.
Their expert, some physicist,
is coming in any minute.
I told you my name is Dr. Gordon.  I
need to speak with the General right away.
Ahh Dr. Gordon.
Make it through security okay?
Yes, you can go, soldiers.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Gentlemen, for the last 10 years
I have been liaison between
NASA and the US military.
Keeping them appraised of all
potential near earth objects.
And by the look of this, we've
got a big one headed right for us.
Oh my God,
how big is it?
Well, with all due respect, sir,
if this was the size of a
satellite, I wouldn't be here.
This is a quarter of our moon.
We are talking end of days here.
End of life as we know it.
- And judging by its speed, I'd say...
- We are looking at a 48 hour window
before it collides with earth, Mac.
- Get the Colonel a cup of coffee.
- Yes, right away, sir.
- Get the gravity of the situation?
- Yes, sir.
I need to keep monitoring this
thing.  I will keep you informed.
Good.
Mac, you've trained the best.
Now we need the best.
We need to fly some of our own onto that
rock and blast it out of earth's path.
We have a Captain
James Wheeler coming in.
Are you familiar with this mission?
Sir, he's a liability.  He lost
a man on his last mission.
Well, I'll let you decide
that once he arrives.
Right now, we need to
issue a nation wide alert.
Start moving people into
bunkers and bomb shelters.
- God help us.
- Yes.
It had to happen on my day off, huh?
I'm sorry, Chris.  Five guys didn't
come in today.  Not even a call.
- Oh!
- Man.
The meteor shower did
really a number on us,
we got fires popping
up all over the city.
I want hoses in those
windows up there now!
Come on!
- Anybody left inside?
- No, LAPD said everybody made it out.
I don't think so.
- Ready, kid?
- Yeah, how about you, pop?
Let's bring the heat.
- Got it?
- Oh man, we gonna need backup.
- There's no backup, it's just us.
- Great.
Come on, pal!  We're running
out of time!  Let's go!
I heard those screams,
she's up here.
LA Fire Department.
Is anybody in here?
They are clear.
Jesus, it's coming down on us, Chris.
We got to find this lady and
get the hell out of here.
I know.  I know!
Is anybody in here?
There's a room.
Clear.
- Where is she?
- She's not here.
Going up.
Come on, it's coming from up here.
Let's go.
There... there she is!
Stay where you are,
we're coming to get you.
Sully!
- You okay?
- I don't know, I think it's broken.
- Yup, yeah, it's broken.
- We gotta get you out of here. Come on.
Well, what are you gonna do?  Go
after her by yourself?  Come on!  Go!
What you gonna do?
Stop me?  Come on.  Let's go!
You're gonna be okay.
Come on.  We are almost
there... almost there.
Come on, get him.
His leg's broken.
- I'm going back in.
- What?  Chris!
Chris, what are you doing?
Come on!
Is he crazy?  That roof
top's going to give way.
- And what's taking so long?
- Come on, Chris.  Come on.
Well, I think I got him.  Look!
- Jesus Christ, Chris what are you doing?
- The elevator was broken.
- How's your leg.
- It's been better.
Glad we didn't take
the short way down.
Excuse me, General... Colonel.
Captain Wheeler, thank you for coming.
Do you know Colonel McCanless?
Only by reputation.  I heard he
was the best pilot in the Air Force.
We're glad you decided to
come in on such short notice.
Well, I don't think I had much of a choice.
Your goons are very pushy.
But at least now I can make myself
clear.  Whatever it is, it's no.
- I'm done.
- Done?
Then how come you're still
wearing those tags, Captain.
- I said I'm done.
- He is very reassuring.
How much longer are you
gonna torture yourself?
It's been two years.
You lost one man, and
saved several others.
It doesn't mean anything.  Now
there's nothing I can do to change it.
How about saving lives of billions?
Why exactly am I here?
The meteor shower that's
been sweeping the world.
Right now, going the path of a
mass of asteroid heading for Earth.
We're being told from the sheer size
of it, on impact, nothing will live.
Do we have your attention now?
What do you want from me?
We want you to go up
there, dig, plant charges
and blow this thing to
hell before it reaches earth.
- How much time do we have?
- Impact in 46 hours.
I am afraid this is a
time sensitive situation.
So we're going to need
an immediate response.
- If I do this...
- Captain, it won't be like before.
We're not sending you
behind enemy lines.
It sounds like you're
sending me to hell.
Jim, please.
We need you.
You can watch the world burn, or
you can do something to change it.
My mission, my team.
No exceptions.
Are you sure about this man, General?
Sometimes, Colonel, you
just have to act on faith.
At ease.
General Magowan.
Sergeant Clayton, Reconnaissance.
Sir.
- Corporal Cabrera, Demolitions.
- Sir.
- Lieutenant Southard, Communications.
- Fitzpatrick and Sanchez, Pilots.
- Sir.
General, meet the roughnecks.
- Relieved yet?
- I will be, once you get back.
Captain Wheeler.
Allow me to introduce Dr. Gordon.
- The Pentagon's most brilliant physicist.
- Oh, I don't know about that.
Very nice to meet you,
Captain Wheeler.
May I introduce you to your shuttle?
The SI-22 Astraeus.
The Astraeus was
designed as an interceptor
for satellite and
base station emergencies.
We filled her up for
exactly one round trip,
so don't take her sightseeing
in between or anything.
We've loaded the
equipment and schematics
as to exactly where to dig
and bury the explosives.
- We're not getting weapons?
- For the asteroid?  No.
But for security reasons there
is a locked case with firearm.
We wouldn't want you guys
getting all... trigger-happy.
Great, so we've got tickets
to the end of the world,
and we don't have any damn guns.
Don't worry, the US government
will be rewarding you all handsomely.
- How handsome?
- Three.
- Hundred thousand?
- Million.
Get this mother started,
I'm ready to go!
- Alright, let's do this.
- Suit up.
- Well, I guess we'll see you up there.
- We?
Uh yeah.  Unless you've got...
someone who knows interstellar
rock formations better than I do.
- I mean, if you do, that's cool.
- We it is.
You didn't think I was gonna
let you have all the fun, did you?
So, take her out easy.
I've just waxed her.
Launch.  Minus five minutes.
- Think you got this?
- Oh sure.
I've got a 30-minute
crash course in piloting
a billion dollar government
funded space shuttle.
- It's not to get.
- Thought so.
- Well, hold tight back there.
- Take-off is in 30 seconds.
Once you're on the rock you may
have difficulty with radio transmission.
Well, that's why we've got this
satellite beacon, to amplify our signal.
Better stay tight.
- You ready?
- You know I'm ready.
You were born ready.
Jesus!
Whoo... oooo.
- They serve refreshments on this flight?
- Shut up.
We made it.
Not yet.
Still a way to go.
How's the ride?
Okay, that can't be good.
What the hell...
What the hell is that?
Talk to me.
Our planned course is incorrect.  We're
on collision course with the asteroid.
What?
That doesn't make sense.
Based on its speed, we knew
how much to compensate
for that travel time
for it to be much easier.
- It seems to be slowing down.
- What?
If we check the distance from
earth we're faster than that
- instead we're slowing down.
- Well, that can't be good.
To say the least.  Oh no,
everyone back in your seats.
- Why?
- We're going in too fast.
This is going to be rough.
Hang on!
Fire the front boosters.
Oh, my God!
Come on!
- Crap yourself?
- Get real.
Wow, what is this, Gonzo rock?
Watch ***.
Now you all have your coordinates.
Locate your targets and
mark them with a tracking rod.
Got it, sir!
Clayton, you make your
way cutting and drilling.
Cabrera and Southard, you hustle back
to the ship and prep the explosives.
Stick together.
Fitzpatrick and Sanchez,
you'll prep the shuttle for take-off.
Read you, Captain.
- The clock is ticking! Squad move out!
- Sir, sir.
Okay!  Let's go.
Don't look at me.
She's your tourist.
I'll start here.
One asteroid root
canal coming up now.
- That's odd.
- What is it?
I'm drilling, but I'm only 50 feet in.
Just having a hard time
getting any deeper.
- That's not deep enough.
- Keep at it.
Yes, sir.
- Come on, get more locations marked.
- It's got a chamber.
What?
There, you see that?
A cave.
If there are passages, then maybe
there's a cavern that leads
to this asteroid's epicenter.
We could plant the charges there,
and then we won't have to dig in
order to completely destroy this thing.
Squad, we're going to scout a nearby
cave as a potential detonation point.
- Stay the course.
- Whoa!  What!  A cave?
Just be careful, I mean, we're only
near them craters.  Watch yourself, sir.
- Come on, this way.
- Easy, Doctor.
Captain James?
What do you got?
Look!
Well, this doesn't make sense.
- Captain, come in!
- Go ahead, Southard.
- There's something out here.
- What?
Cabrera and I were marking
our coordinates and...
And what?
Something moved about here.
I saw it went right by us.
- Debris?
- Captain, where are you?
Stand by guys.
What the hell is this?
This is weird.
I don't like this.
I've never seen anything like this.
What's that?
Don't.
Okay, this is not an asteroid.
Everyone, back to the ship.
Now!
Whoa, the whole
damn thing is shaking.
Hey, jump!
Come on!
Jump!
You got this.
- Good jump, girl.
- What the hell is going on?
I don't know.
Oh my God.
Go!
What is that?
Control!  We have hundreds of bogeys
about to enter Earth's atmosphere.
Say it again, I'm afraid.
Enemy aircrafts. Can you read?
Alert everyone.
30 kilometers outside of
Saint-Guilhem-le-Desert, France.
Jesus...
What the...
Oh my God.
Fuck!
Please, not now.
No! Come on!
Come on!
No!
You think that was enough
excitement for one day.
Yeah, relax would you?
- Have you ever seen anything like this?
- What is that?
Station 2-4-9, this is Hansen.
Do you copy?  Are you seeing this?
- Coming in too fast there.
- Halt.
Look out!
- Turn off your engine.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
- I'll call you back.
What the hell is going on out here?
- This is a restricted area!
- What are you talking about?
Our department is only a block away.
We have direct orders
to start relocating
everybody from downtown
to a safe military bunker.
Relocating?
Under whose authority?
That's on a need to know basis
which you don't have to.
- So get back in your truck,
I'll have my men...
Incoming!
- Captain, what's going on?
- It's an invasion!
What?
What the hell's going on?
- This isn't what we think it is.
- Yeah, no kidding.
We need to get the hell out of here!
Oh, God.
Sanchez... Fitzpatrick...
Hostiles.
Get back!
- Alright everybody!  Into the cave!
- What?  I'm not going in there.
Cabrera, get down!
- Cabrera!
- No!
Come on!
I don't think she's actually dead.
- This isn't positive.
- We're trapped. What are you doing?
- There's got to be some way.
- Take cover!
How the hell did you do that?
I think this is the same
thing that happened to Cabrera.
I think they've discovered some
sort of teleportation technology
or wormhole or something.
Earth to Wheeler!
They're not giving up here.
It's our only way out.
I'll see you on the other side.
- Where did she go?
- She's crazy!
- Maybe not!  Go!
- What? I was wrong, you're crazy!
- I said go!
- Yes, sir.  Let's go, Clayton.
- You guys alright?
- Ah, I think so.
I'm alright.
Where are my men?
- Don't shoot.
- I'm not going to shoot you.
Whoa ssh...
That thing is coming around.
Where did it go?
Ssh, get down.
Shit, it's on the truck.
- What the hell were those things?
- I don't know.
I didn't get a good enough look.
They destroyed the
radio and killed my men.
Whatever they are, they're patrolling,
eliminating any hostile threat.
- I can't see anything.
- It's because we are under a truck.
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
It is Lindsey.
Lindsey.
Dad!  I'm so sorry.
Dad, please  come and get me.
They came out of nowhere,
and we're trapped.  Dad?
Where are you?
Are you all right?
Yeah I'm okay, there are some
other people here with me.
What do you mean?  You're
not at home?  Where are you?
I'm downtown.
Dad, what's going on?
I'm scared.  We keep hearing
noises and screams, and I just...
Okay baby, I know.  Listen, wherever
you are, just lock yourself in tight.
Don't go anywhere near the
doors or the windows, okay?
Okay.
Now tell me exactly where you are.
They chased us into some old
office building near Union Station.
Dad, what are these things?
They are dead because I'm coming
to get you.  You just sit tight, okay?
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you too.
What's the plan?
- Major?
- Blake.
- Chris Meyer.
- Nice to meet you.
Okay, look.
They got us surrounded, but I think they
starting to leave away from our position.
I think we can sneak out
if we go out that way.
And I could salvage
any weapons I still have.
What's the plan, boss?
I'm going to get my daughter.
- His daughter is not worth it.
- She's not that cute.
Dad, where are you?
No! No! Get away!
Let's go.
- Glad you could joined the party.
- Where are we?
I thought we were history.
Look at that.
- We're not in South Central.
- What did I tell you?
These things have mastered
technology far greater than ours.
They are traveling to
earth through wormholes.
That's great, but how do we get back?
Good question.
It's not like we
could just call for help.
Our radios are crap out here.
Sure, we can.
We can use this beacon to
increase our signal and send an SOS.
But it's only good
for one transmission.
Alright, fine.  Do it.
It's gonna take some time to charge.
Give it an hour.
Fine.  Do it.
Nobody leaves here without
my say so, understood?
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
What are you doing, genius?
We're on an alien planet, you
don't even know if there is air here.
Don't worry, it's breathable.
As you are.
Well, that smells good.
- I miss LA.
- Hey Captain?
I think you better
take a look at this.
I think we're in their backyard.
Son of a...
That's not all.
We're not the only ones out here.
They're herding humans.
- Doc, that absolutely needs an hour?
- Unfortunately, yes.
Alright.  Now we send out an SOS
and just hope help will arrive?
A whole lot of waiting.
Yeah, in time for
those things to find us.
Wait wait wait.
What about all those people?
What about them?
We have to get out of here!
Ah yeah!
And go where?
Alright.
Saddle up, we're moving out.
What?  Where to?
We're going down there,
we're going to save those people.
- Are you crazy, what about us?
- Stand down, Lieutenant!
Those are innocent
people who need our help.
The rest of you can either follow me
or sit here with your thumbs up your ass.
- I said saddle up!
- Yes, sir.
May I bother one of you for a weapon?
Thank you.
Let's move out.
Try this. The bigger they are,
the harder they fall.
Hey, right here.
Come over here!
Yeah, over here.  Over here.
That's right, come and get it!
That's right!
Get him Mike!
That's right!  Over here!
- I'm glad I stayed under here.
- Come on!
Deb, Deb, where is Shawn?
Where did you see him last?
He couldn't have just disappeared.
I can't come home till they get back.
There are fires all over the city.
Call the police.
Then try them again, Deb.
Deb, baby, Deb, Deb stop crying,
stop crying, we'll find him, okay?
I promise.
Okay?
Deb?
Hello?
I hope you know where we're going.
We can't keep running like this.
Don't worry, we're close.
Okay, come on.
- Holy Mother Mary. Are you all right?
- Not exactly.
- Samon, thank Christ you're alive.
- What the hell is going on out there?
Well, it's the end of the world.
Must be.  I haven't
seen anybody else all day.
The others took all
the working engine.
That one's transmission is busted.
- Well, let's take my truck.
- It's payback time.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...
- Nice.
- Whoa!  Where's the fire?
- I'm going after my daughter.
And there are some out
of towners out there.
They aren't too friendly.
If I were you, I'd arm myself.
You're serious?
Oh my God! My family, man!
I got to get to my family.
I got to see my family!
I got to...
Tim! Come with us.
Here, sorry.  But if it as bad as you say
it is then I need to collect my family.
If the power lines are down...
I need to go, man. I...
Alright.  Just stay focused.
Be careful out there.
- Good luck, Chris.
- Take care of yourself, Tim.
Chris, I can't thank you enough.
I got to get back to base.
- This is war.
- So give 'em hell!
Well, you drive.
Sully...
- Why don't we back seat this one.
- Game on, boss.
Captain, what is it?
There.
Where?
What is it doing?
What's going on?
Something's not right.
How do you know?
They're hunting us.
And that one is a decoy.  They rest
are going to flank us from all sides.
- Orders, Captain?
- Run!
As fast as you can.
Hurry, this way.
- It's gone.
- Oh Jesus.
My heart can't stop pounding.
It's war.
Get used to it.
Hey.
You okay?
- I should never have left her alone.
- Hey, Chris, come on.
Well, if she's anything at
all like you, she's doing fine.
She doesn't want to
be anything like me.
I break every promise,
I'm never there.
Don't worry, we're gonna find her.
Hey!  Hey!
We're gonna find her, okay?
- Guys guys, we got company!
- Oh crap!
- Come on, let's go.  Faster, faster!
- Hang on!
Lose him man!
Lose him!
- Put some lead into it!
- This thing can't go any faster!
Oh God Chris, when you last
time you got a tune-up?
- Will, get us out of here! Now!
- Hang on, hang on.
Chris, look out!
- Thanks.
- Now we're even.
- Sully!
- Oh Jesus Christ, they got Sullivan!
- That thing is still following us.
- Eyes on the road!
- What what...?
- The brakes are...
What do you mean?
What?
- Guys, get ready to jump.
- We gotta jump.
- What do you mean?
- We gotta jump, we gotta jump!
- We gotta jump... you ready?
- Jump!  I'm sure not jumping...
Wait?  What?
It's cool guys.  We got it.
Don't worry about it.
- One more crap you'll stop.
- Mm hm.
This is incredible.
Ssh!
You go where we go,
or get left behind.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry.  Be smart.
- What are you doing?
- We're bringing them back.
He was already dead.
There's nothing you could do for him.
Plus we don't know how
many more there are.
- We got to be smart.
- Guys, will you shut the hell up?
Take that, bitch!
Southard!
Cabrera!
Get back, get back, get back!
- You see anything?
- No, it's clear.  Come on. Let's go.
- Where is your daughter, Chris?
- One block up.
Well, let's get you there.
- No no!
- Should we double back?
No, into there!
Go go!
Come on.
Go go go go go!
Whoa whoa.
Wait! Wait!
Hide hide hide.
Cover yourselves.
Do you think it will come in here?
I'm thinking yes.
- Hey Chris, what are we gonna do?
- We got to get rid of that thing.
How?
Doing...
Come on!
SCREW YOU
Look out!
Go, go find your daughter.
Why exactly am I here?
The Meteor Shower that's
been sweeping the world
Nothing will live.
- We're not sending you behind enemy lines.
- Sounds like sending me to hell.
Wait wait wait.
What about all those people?
What about them?
We have to get out of here.
We going down there,
we're gonna save those people.
Are you crazy?
Southard!
Cabrera!
Get back! Get back! Get back!
Mankind needs you.
Who's there?
What are you doing?
I'm getting out of here.
Why?
So, I can get you to safety.
From this side?
From them?
Come on, I'm gonna get you out of
here.  You're gonna be alright.
Please.  You don't understand.
They've already taken my children.
Please...
- They've already killed me.
- Stop.
- But I'm still alive.
- Stop, stop.  I can't do that!
Please, please.
I can't do that.
I'm not going to do that.
Do you have any children?
Do you?
If you did, you'd understand.  They
become your life, your reason for living.
- Please.
- Sorry.
Please...
If not for me, do it for my
Ashley, Annie and George.
You remind me of him.
Please.
Please...
- Gordon!
- Hurry, they're holding us captive.
- Quick, get me out of here!
- It's locked.
Hang on.
Oh, God, Clayton.
Just focus Captain.
There's still hope for you.
You and the doctor
can bust out of here.
Summon the beacon.
There is still hope for all of us.
Captain, they can't find you here.
You have to get out of here,
they'll kill you in the worst ways.
- You have to.
- I'm sorry, soldier.
The heck!
Hey! Hey!
You stay away from him!
You leave him alone!
Can you understand me?
You can't, right?
Can you?
You aren't going to do it, are you?
You oughta make a run for the
beacon and get the hell out of here.
Just do it!
And get out of here.
Come on!
Bring it! Come on!
No, don't!
Don't!  Please!
No, no, no! No!
Look out, look out!
How long has it been?
Nearly six hours since Captain
Wheeler's last transmission.
Just over eight since he
confirmed the loss of SI 22.
Stay on it.  Keep scanning
for the distress beacon.
Sir.
We're assembling men for the assault but
we need more.  You think Wheeler's team?
We lost radio contact hours ago.
Any more civilian survivors?
Not many.  There's no
telling how many more left.
With your permission, sir,
I would like to start rounding up
anyone with military training
to prep for the assault.
Permission?  We are talking about the
last effort to save our civilization.
Our lives, our world.
This isn't war, this is survival.
- Get as many as you can.
- Yes, sir.
Damn it!
Quick, get us something to block...
Run!
Come on, Lindsey!
Lindsey, Lindsey!
Dad?
Dad!
Lindsey!
No!
No! No! No!
Damn you!
No!
Lindsey...
Lindsey!
We've cleared the area,
come with us, you'll be safe.
Stop!
Chris!
Hey Meyer!
You got through, I don't believe it.
As for my team though...
they weren't so lucky.
Your daughter?
Gone.  Taken.
Well, you're here now.
If anyone can keep you safe, it's us.
I don't think there
is a safe place anymore.
You're still alive.
I thought they'd killed you.
What did they do to you?
I know their plan.
They showed you?
She told me.
- She?
- Your queen.
She got into my head.
And she told me.
They are a dying race.
Going planet to planet
harvesting for her.
Their last queen.
And they're keeping her alive.
Oh my God.
I have seen their plan.
And we're all going to die.
No no no!
Don't lose hope.
Look, I need you.
Look look look.
We still have the beacon.
It should be charged now.
We can contact Control.
Tell them to bring the fight here.
Get these bastards where they live.
How?
Just stay strong with me.
- Southard.
- Ah, Captain.
- Are you all right?
- No, please tell me there's a plan.
We're working on it.
Oh!
Kill good, you bastard!
- James!
- Hang on!
- Oh, it hurts!
- Gonna get you out of here.
Oh, no, get out of here!
Go! Get out of here!  Go!
Oh God!
Mission Control, this is Captain
James Wheeler, do you copy?  Over.
Mission Control, this is Captain Wheeler.
Do you copy?
I hope you're reading this.
We have encountered...
...alien hostiles.
And found that they are abducting humans
and bringing in to their home planet.
There are several...
hundreds more in captivity.
We found a way to travel through
one of their orb transports
and I suggest you do the same.
They are a dying, desperate race.
There is still hope for
us to wipe them out.
The asteroid is a launching dock.
Fly to it and fire a nuke into the cave
near the tracking rods that we've marked.
That will blast it from its core.
My...
My entire team, they died as heroes.
Please, don't let
their deaths be in vain.
You give 'em power
and the best of luck to you all.
If you are listening to this,
you are the resistance.
Mankind’s final hope.
Over and out.
They're coming.
And they're gonna
wipe out your entire race!
Chris! Chris!
You gonna want to hear this.
Soon, we'll be deploying the
greatest assault in our world's history.
Against a threat like never before.
Early this morning we
received a transmission
from United States Marine
Captain James Wheeler.
In it, he told us that they are
holding several civilians captive.
Lindsey.
But he also told us
how to fight them.
Where we can take this
battle to their doorstep
and make them wish that they
never stepped on to our planet.
Captain Wheeler and his squad
gave their lives for this information.
And now it's our turn
to honor their sacrifice.
This isn't about politics, or national
interests or protecting resources.
This is a struggle for
all mankind to survive.
And we will!
We will survive.
Now and forever.
And the universe will know
that this... this is our world!
Two teams will fight simultaneously.
Assault and Rescue.
Assault will be travelling to the
alien rock outside of our atmosphere.
We will focus our attack on
the designated marked target.
A clean shot should
blow it from its core.
- As for Rescue... Colonel.
- We capture one of the alien craft.
We'll take the civilians
via weaponized portal,
immediately transporting them
back to their home planet.
Rescue, you'll move heavily armed,
eliminating any hostiles on site...
retrieve any civilians
back to the portal.
Let's teach this brave new
world the meaning of fear.
I'm trying, baby.
Are you ready?
Let's do this.
Dad, will you help me?
The SI 22's are fueled up and ready.
Space.  It will be a new
part of experience for me.
Don't get lost up there, Colonel.
We're counting on you.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I almost got it.
You might feel a tingling sensation.
Eagle Star 1.  Fighters all in.
Locked on **.
Roger!
What the hell?
- Anyone else coming?
- More coming.
Let's get our bearings and
keep pushing forward.
Looks like it up there.
Okay, listen up.
We're heading to their compound.
We're going in loud.
Heavy gunners,
I want you blasting the living hell
out of everything that is inhuman.
Ready?
Let's move up!
They know we're coming.
Come on.
Let's keep moving.
Look out turning the left.
Go to the main entry.
Enemy craft.  Enemy craft.
Fighters engage!
Is that all you got?
Lindsey! Lindsey!
Dad!
Oh, I found you, I found you!
Are you okay? Let me see you.
- Dad, it was terrible.
- Oh I know, I'm so sorry.
- Come on, we gotta go! Come on!
- Let's get you out of here. Come on.
No!
Lindsey!
- Dad...
- Oh, God.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
- Dad.
- You gonna be okay.
- Take me home, Dad.
- Okay.
Okay baby. Stay with me.
Let's go home now.
- I'm out!
- We're out of missiles!
Damn!
- Am I late?
- General Magowan?
That's right.
Get these guys off so
I can get a clean shot.
You heard the General.
Evasive maneuvers, let's go.
Target locked.
Welcome to oblivion.
Fighters, pull back!
- Excellent job, sir.
- My pleasure.
Lindsey no!  Stay with me.
Open your eyes, baby. Open your eyes.
No Lindsey, open your eyes,
Lindsey.  Stay with me!
Dad.
Please, it's over.
Please...
It's not.
It's not over.
Not yet.