Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hey.
Bring it on, daddy.
Sam, dance With me.
Come on, come on.
You knoW you Want to.
Come on.
I got this great idea.
It's this little game
called Bra in the PilloWcase.
Girls, just simply
drop your bra in the pilloWcase.
Guys, the bra you pick
is the girl you get.
Huh? Very nicely done.
Very nicely done.
Bump, bump, bump.
Oh, Whoa!
All right, all right.
Oh! What a shot. What a shot.
What a shot.
Can We hear it
for the lovely Samantha?
All right, all right, all right.
I'll do it for you.
For you, Jack.
All right! All right.
Okay, big Ricky!
Feel lucky?
All right. Get in there.
Get in there.
Come on, come on!
That ain't no fair.
All right, all right.
Way to suck it.
All right, let's go, let's go.
Okay. All right.
All right.
All right, all right.
Should We...
Bye, Jack.
Lookir for a date?
Not tonight, baby.
What are you lookir for then?
Just to talk.
Come on, man.
What are you arresting me for?
Look, I'm not Vice.
I'm Homicide.
I just Wanna talk.
So What the fuck?
What's Homicide
got to do With me?
Nothir, if you're lucky.
Come on, man.
You tryir to freak me out?
I got enough stuff
to be freaked out about.
Look, honey, there's a killer out there
lookir for girls just like you.
Hookers.
NoW, come on. Get in. I Want you
to take a look at this sketch.
Maybe you've seen the guy around.
You could help me out.
All right. Keep your hands
to yourself, okay?
No cop freebies, got it?
Here.
You're not a cop, are you?
No!
That's cool, man.
Go on, man. Give it a shot.
Wake up, Wake up, Wake up.
Wake up, Wake up,
Wake up.
We got a little surprise for you.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
You gotta Wake up.
You need to Wake up.
- Good girl.
- Yes.
Yeah. Come on.
Oh, yeah! Fuck!
Easy.
You're dessert tonight.
Come on.
Come on, darling.
Man.
Sammy, get up, baby.
You got a phone call.
Who is it?
It's Jillian.
- Yeah.
- What does she Want?
I don't knoW.
She said it Was important.
So, did you have a good time fucking
my best friend last night?
Yeah. It Was a ball.
- Cool.
- Oh, God.
So, it Was pretty good, huh?
I could ask you the same thing.
- I guess you could. You gonna?
- Jack, don't.
God! This is your game.
I told you he'd pick me.
- Save it?
- Yeah, save it.
- Save it out?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- God, you're such a baby.
- This Was a good idea.
Thanks.
Hey!
- What's going on?
- Hey, Jillian.
- What?
- Little sell-out crime busters.
Yeah, okay.
No, I'm just surprised that you thought of me.
Well, What can I do?
You have the right to remain silent.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Yeah, anything.
Hey, Jillian, thanks.
I'll be right there.
Okay. Bye.
What the fuck does she Want?
Sell-out bitch.
Jack, shut up.
Dr. Samantha Stone.
I'm here to see Jillian Dunne.
- Sam, thanks for coming.
- No problem, Jillian.
Sergeant, can We get a badge here
for Dr. Stone, please? Thank you.
Sure thing.
Why don't you sign in for me?
Right here, sWeetheart.
Nice outfit.
Remember When Walked
doWn Haight naked.
- We Were protesting.
- What are We doing noW?
His name is Kenneth Bianchi.
He's 27 years old.
They arrested him late last night.
And Why do the detectives think Kenneth
is the Hillside Strangler?
Circumstantial evidence, mostly.
He Was near the crime scene.
Started to run When
he saW a police cruiser.
And he hasn't talked
since he's been here.
Running from the cops
hardly makes someone guilty.
True. And his blood type doesn't match
the type found in the other victims.
We're Waiting for the lab
results on this last girl.
HoW did you get his blood type?
What, did they beat it out of him?
No, We found medical records
When We searched his house.
His girlfriend's house, actually,
Where he lives With their baby.
A serial killer With a family?
Look, the detectives think
that this is the guy.
And they're pressing me
to file for murder, but...
But you don't have
any hard evidence.
You Want me to illicit a confession under
the guise of determining Whether he's insane.
So that's Why you thought of me.
I thought of you
because I trust you
and because I thought
you could help me out.
So, tell me about the victims. Are you sure
they're connected With the others?
Look, there's something I should
tell you before you go in there.
These are especially
violent acts.
Eight girls have been raped,
murdered, strangled With rope,
cuts marks dug in their necks,
arms and legs.
This last girl found
Was 14 years old
and she had blood
oozing out of her anus.
She had cleaning fluid
injected in her veins.
So hoW long do I have With him?
Until his laWyer gets here,
Which could be any minute.
And he hasn't spoken a Word?
With these bulls threatening him,
of course he's gonna keep his lips tight.
Well, I need you to open them,
so to speak.
Oh, my God. It's the hippy
dippy head shrinker.
- Bring that Ouija board?
- Detective.
Counselor. So, What's happening?
HoW's the bleeding heart?
- Better than a bleeding soul.
- Oh, hoW professional.
Welcome, ladies.
Detective Smith,
you remember Dr. Stone, don't you?
- I remember. Pleasure.
- Hi.
Kenneth, this is Dr. Stone.
She's gonna have a Word With you.
- Could you give us a minute?
- No.
- It's all right.
- All right, Well, let's...
- No, no, no.
- This is bullshit!
All right, Romeo.
Put your hands on the table.
Is that really necessary?
Yes, head doctor,
this is very necessary.
Thank you, Detective Bryant.
NoW, Kenneth, you've already been advised
of your right to remain silent.
Thank you.
It's just you and me, Kenneth.
It's okay.
Look, I knoW you're scared.
I Would be too.
You can trust me.
Do you understand
that I can help you?
So I assume you understand Where
you are and What's going on?
Look, Kenneth, I'm not a cop.
I don't even like cops.
I could be on your side.
It's up to you.
The district attorney doesn't
knoW What to do With you...
Whether to file murder charges
against you.
And since you're not talking to anyone,
she thinks you might be guilty.
They...
think I killed those girls.
They think I'm a serial killer.
You're a... psychiatrist?
Yes.
I have a private practice.
And occasionally
I Work With the accused.
HoW do you...
HoW do you Work
With the... accused?
I talk With them,
see What they have to say.
See if they're competent
to be questioned.
If there's an issue of competency
or state of mind in a trial,
sometimes I'm called upon
as an expert Witness.
What does that mean...
competent to be questioned?
Sometimes I come across a person
Who doesn't realize he said anything Wrong.
Somebody's vieW of the World
is different than most.
Some of us is crazy?
I don't use those Words, Kenneth.
But semantics aside,
that's... that's What you mean.
I met this Woman last year...
Whose mother had died tragically.
And When she Went
to this funeral, she...
saW a man there
she had never seen before.
He introduced himself to her,
and this particular young Woman
fell for him instantly.
Yeah?
And?
Next Week she stabbed her sister
to death With a kitchen knife.
NoW, Why Would she do that?
L... I don't...
I don't knoW.
What the hell is she doing,
using him to analyze her other cases?
She knoWs What she's doing.
With all due respect,
her methods are unorthodox.
Hasrt gotten to him.
Well, he's talking after five minutes,
Which is better than you tWo could do
in 12 hours, so shut up.
Can I ask you
a personal question?
What's your opinion
of Women, in general?
I don't...
I don't have an opinion
of Women in general.
I mean, I have opinions
of people.
But l... I don't stereotype
like those cops do.
You knoW,
I Would never thought somebody
like you to Work for the police.
I don't Work for the police.
I Work for the district attorney
on cases that I choose.
Right. Sorry.
L... I kneW you Were different
the second you Walked
through that door.
You just make me feel at ease.
I'm glad I put you at ease, Kenneth.
I'm gonna advise you to take this
interrogation very, very seriously.
You're being accused of raping
and murdering eight young Women.
Interrogation?
I thought it Was just...
an examination.
It's an examination With the purpose
of determining Whether or not
you could have had something
to do With these murders.
You're not here to help me.
They're just using you.
Maybe.
Depends upon you.
Come on, Sam.
Keep him talking.
Really?
Assuming you're not guilty,
assuming you didn't
kill those girls,
that makes What's going to happen
to you next even more traumatic.
They're gonna turn
your life upside doWn.
Every friend and acquaintance
is gonna be interrogated.
Every detail of your life is gonna be poked
and prodded, every stone looked under.
- But I didn't do anything.
- You ran, Kenneth.
I have a child myself. I've never been
arrested before in my life.
Kenneth, if there's
anything you knoW,
if you saW something,
if you Were there but even if you didn't do it,
noW Would be the time to tell.
I didn't do it.
But I think I knoW Who did it.
Kenneth, you think
you knoW Who did it?
I think so.
Who?
He'Il... He'll kill me.
Who Will kill you?
Kenneth, Who killed those girls?
Steve. Steve. Steve. Steve.
Steve Who?
I don't knoW his last name.
He's this guy I kind of knoW.
"KnoW him" as more like
I knoW him through somebody.
But not personally?
Not exactly.
You never seen him
face to face?
He's gonna kill me.
Get the fuck outta here!
You gotta be...
You ain't falling for
this bullshit, right? Right?
He doesn't knoW the guy's last name
but he knoWs he's a serial killer?
That night,
my cousin called me.
He said some guy named Steve
needed help With a car.
Needed me to pick it up
and drop it off at his house.
My cousin Was into
fixing up cars.
And I said, "Sure."
That's When I saW the dead girl.
But I got so scared,
I started to run.
Kenneth, did you see Steve
before you ran?
No. There Was
nobody else there.
Nobody but the dead girl.
Kenneth, What Was the address
you Were supposed to drop off the car to?
What do you Want With...
That Will be all, Doctor.
And I Would like to have a Word
With my client, please, alone.
That's your right.
You can take as long as you Want.
- Can I just talk to him...
- No. Nobody says a Word to Mr. Bianchi.
The intervieW's over.
Thank you.
Kenneth, I Would suggest you not talk
to anybody regarding this matter.
Except me, okay?
If you could just...
If you could just give us that.
Thank you. Appreciate it.
And if you're not gonna press charges,
I think Mr. Bianchi has helped you enough.
- Absolutely.
- Thank you.
You all right, Smitty?
Here's What We got on him.
Angelo Buono... assault,
attempted abduction, statutory rape...
a real piece of shit.
- What about this Steve fuck?
- Get Angelo. See if he talks.
And just to let you knoW, I gotta let this guy go,
so We don't have a lot of time.
- What?
- His blood type doesn't match up,
his house is clean, as you can see
he's all laWyered up.
We're doing this one by the books, boys.
No mistakes.
Hey, I need to talk to you.
- Sorry it got so crazy in there. You okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
I totally lied to that poor guy.
Poor guy? I Wouldrt be
so sure he's innocent.
I'm not even sure about anything,
except that I might have put him in danger.
I Wanna speak to him
before I leave.
LAPD! Hands in the air!
Clear!
Smitty. Detective Smith?
All right, Kenneth, here she is.
Be quick and concise
because I'm taking him home.
Home? I can't go home.
It's not safe.
Kenneth, you're gonna be fine.
I promise.
No, it's just not safe.
I mean, if Steve doesn't get me,
these cops Will.
I'm in a bad place here.
Nobody's gonna touch you,
Kenneth, okay?
Look, you don't knoW Steve.
You don't knoW hoW sick
and tWisted this guy can be.
But he doesn't knoW
you gave his name to the police.
- He doesn't even knoW you've been arrested.
- He'll find out.
I gotta... I don't knoW
What I'm gonna do.
Look, if you Wanna talk,
about anything, give me a call.
I'll make sure he doesn't.
Thank you very much.
Kenneth, everything's gonna be okay.
Smitty? Smitty, come on.
You should see this shit.
Where are you?
Smitty... Oh, Jesus Christ.
What the hell happened here?
- Did you get a look at the guy at least?
- No.
Captain, I Want a perimeter set up
around the entire block. Stop everyone.
I Want this guy. I need tWo guys to stay here to
make sure he's still not on the premises.
You old fuck.
Hey, baby. Jilliars here.
It's good.
Thanks for lunch.
You gonna explain it to me.
Your client goes to a funeral.
Meets a hunk.
And then kills her sister.
It Was a case study
done six years ago.
The scenario Was randomly
presented to 2,000 people.
They Were all asked the same question,
"Why Would this Woman kill her sister?"
And almost all of them
came back With the same ansWer.
- Which Was?
- They didn't knoW.
- Doesrt solve my problem.
- The same scenario Was presented
to over 100 schizophrenics and psychopaths
and they all gave the same ansWer,
"The Woman killed her sister in hopes of seeing
this mysterious stranger at the funeral."
- A litmus test.
- Something like that.
- And our boy Kenneth failed.
- Quite the opposite.
- He passed.
- So you think Kenneth is telling the truth?
- I think he is.
- Seems like so long ago.
Maybe for you.
So, Sam, I Wanna bring you on the case.
Officially, I need your help.
But I thought they found evidence
at the bungaloW linking Angelo to the murders.
- So Why do you need me?
- Because We can't find Angelo,
We still don't have anything
on this Steve character,
and you're the only one
that Kenneth Will talk to.
Look, if you bring me on this case,
no more favors.
Whatever conclusion I come to,
Whatever evidence I find on Kenneth,
I need you to be prepared
for the truth.
Please close the blinds.
You're so fucking paranoid.
Why don't you take another Valium?
It's just pot, Sam.
Yeah.
So you expect me to sit on the corner
of Sunset and Highland
and Wait for a truck
full of fucking Mexicans?
No, man. It's a blue Chevy truck,
just like the one you had in high school.
If it's so easy,
you fucking do it.
Sometimes you are such
a fucking pussy.
You knoW What?
I knoW her number.
I could call your mom right noW
and ask her if it's okay.
- You Want me to do that?
- Yeah, do that, please.
- A little gratuity.
- Arert you guys tired of this shit?
Don't bite the hand
that feeds you, all right?
Oh! Thank you.
Goddamn it!
It beats a real job, right?
- These beaners better be fuckir straight up.
- No, man. It's Raul.
- I don't fuckir care.
- You met him last Week.
Jesus! Fuck!
Who the fuck are you?
What, you can't speak?
Stuck on yesterday's riddle?
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- Sorry. L...
Dr. Stone gave me this. I thought...
- What the fuck?
- I thought this Was her office.
- I'm sorry.
- God!
Hey, Sam.
Did you order a fucking fruitcake?
'Cause you got one out here.
You better not be fucking around.
Jack, it's okay. I knoW him.
Give me a second.
- Kenneth, What are you doing here?
- I'm sorry.
I Was so afraid, I didn't knoW Where to go.
I had no place to go.
- I just need to talk to somebody.
- I told you to call me.
Kenneth, this isn't
a good time or place.
Please, they're folloWing me.
You're still a prime suspect.
They're gonna be folloWing you.
It's not the police.
I'm sorry.
This is my home, Kenneth.
- Bring him in here before he pisses himself
- Give me a minute.
- And attracts attention from the neighbors.
- Just give me a second.
- No, in or out.
- Give me a second!
You fuckir see this shit?
- Come on.
- Sam, in the house, please!
Sam, thanks to your neW friend here,
I gotta go handle this.
So, I'll be back.
I Wort be long.
Why don't you Wait for me?
Well, because I can't, okay?
You be nice.
By the Way,
I'm really sorry about that.
I hope it's okay.
I don't mean to cross any lines With you.
Frankly, Kenneth, it's not okay.
But since you're here,
I'll be happy to talk to you.
I Want you to knoW that I'm Working
on your case noW.
My case?
If there's an issue
of psychiatric concern,
I'll be called to testify.
Doctor, you gotta
believe me. L...
I'm not making any of this stuff up.
It's all real. It's...
I don't think you are.
Crazy? You think I'm crazy,
is that What you Were gonna say?
I don't knoW you Well enough
to say, Kenneth.
Doctor, come on.
I mean, What?
So if I Was to come in here and tell you
that I killed those girls, What then?
I mean, What Would you do?
I'd call the police and turn you in.
Come on.
You're saying I'm crazy.
I'm not... A crazy person
says crazy things, you knoW.
Isn't that hoW it goes?
Do you think
you're crazy, Kenneth?
I mean, hoW do you decide?
HoW do you decide
if one is crazy,
or isn't?
You knoW, I mean,
What's it take to get into
one of these books, really?
I mean, is it paranoid schizophrenia?
Is that What it is?
I don't knoW. I haven't looked in one
of those books since I Was in school.
I base my practice, my judgment,
more on instinct
than anything else.
You're a unique lady.
WoW, look at these.
These are so beautiful.
I mean, look at them.
And this... this one.
Kenneth, Why did you
come to see me?
- I got scared.
- And I Wanna be able to help you.
I thought I could
talk to you. L...
What can I do for you?
Has anyone been talking
to my cousin Angelo yet?
Look, I'm not a detective, Kenneth.
I don't knoW anything about the investigation.
Look, my cousin
Angelo, he...
he's had a problem With...
With girls in the past.
I remember. He...
He beat up my aunt real bad.
I hated him for it.
I mean, What kind of person
hits their oWn mother, right?
I mean, he beat her.
He called her a Whore.
And it Was just terrible.
Kenneth, tell me about your relationship
With your mother.
Did I say something Wrong?
Are you okay?
Kenneth, are you okay?
Oh, Jesus. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I gotta go.
Clear!
Back side! Back side!
Thanks for coming in on such short notice.
We have him for an hour.
And he's Willing to talk as long
as you ask the questions.
- I need to talk to you for a second.
- Yeah?
Kenneth came to
see me last night.
- Sam, are you fucking this guy?
- What?
- Are you?
- What the hell does that mean?
- I'm asking.
- No, of course not.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
You might Wanna flip
to page 14 of his file.
You'll see you're not
the only shrink on this case.
It seems Kenneth posed as a psychologist
for a couple months.
Only problem Was he faked
his credentials and his diploma.
But since most of his clients
Were uneducated girls off the street,
no one seemed to mind
his lack of professionalism.
- HoW did you get his IQ?
- Impressive, right?
Maybe even smart enough
to run a game on us.
I'm not that gullible. Did his laWyer
agree to let me hypnotize him?
No, his laWyer did not,
but Kenneth insisted.
Do you realize hoW rare it is to have
a suspect agree to be hypnotized?
It's only rare because
most suspects are guilty.
They are.
Are you in your relaxed
and peaceful place?
Yes.
We'll count backwards
from five.
When you get to one,
your subconscious mind Will come forward.
Five, four,
three,
tWo, one.
NoW open your eyes, Kenneth.
I Want you to think back
tWo years ago.
Did you impersonate
a psychologist?
Yes.
Did you take prostitutes
as clients?
Yes.
Why did you do that?
For sex.
I Want you to be honest
With me, Kenneth.
I Wanted to have sex With them.
There isn't many Women
Who Wanna take part in my sexuality.
Do you think I'm an idiot? You promised me
the questions Would be about Steve...
- She's getting there.
- She better get there quick.
I need you to think real hard.
Kenneth, Where is Angelo?
Your cousirs doing bad things.
You Wouldrt Wanna
protect him, Would you?
No. No.
Where is Angelo?
He's hiding.
I don't knoW Where.
No one really knoWs.
They're looking for him.
Is it Steve?
Where is Steve?
He's not afraid of you.
You better hope
you don't find him.
he doesn't find you.
You fucking cunt.
Did you knoW Angelo
and Steve Were killing those girls?
Why? You Wanna get
fucked too, bitch?
- That's it! This intervieW is over!
- Don't fuck With me, Whore!
I need everybody out
of the room noW. Kenneth?
Look at me. Calm doWn.
Look at me. Shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Put your head doWn. Breathe.
Breathe. It's gonna be all right.
Calm doWn.
- Breathe.
- Not so sure he's innocent anymore.
Every forensic psychiatrist
We met With
said this is exactly the type of behavior
that this killer Would have.
It's consistent With
every profile We've gotten.
But it's not consistent
With Kenneth.
I hope you're right,
'cause I gotta let him go.
- You Wanna come in for a nightcap?
- I can't.
It's late.
Jack's out With his friends.
We haven't hung out for a While.
I knoW.
You got a joint?
Yes.
- Here you go, babe.
- Thank you, my friend.
So I'll see you
bright and early, okay?
You sure you don't Wanna
come in for a drink? I'm buying.
I'm sure.
Drive safe.
- Bye.
Fuck! Jack.
- Who is this girl?
- Hi.
Come... Come join us.
Who is she?
Sam, this is...
It's Nicole.
This is Nicole.
She came here... for you.
Come on. Come join us.
Baby, I love you.
Baby, come on.
- Hey.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Where's Jack? Is he okay?
What the fuck are
these cops doing here?
I need you to come outside
and I'll tell you, all right?
Come on.
He's taunting us noW.
- Go back. Move it back.
- Hey, get the fuck out of here.
ShoW some respect, Will ya?
Oh, my God.
- Sam, you knoW this girl?
- Shit.
Sam, What's going on?
Have you seen her before?
I knoW her.
Jack, I need to ask you
some questions.
Bull-fucking-shit. Get the fuck outta here
and take those fucking pigs With you.
Jack, a girl Was found murdered
in front of your house.
- Sam says you slept With this girl last night.
- What the fuck is this?
Jack, do you realize that your semen is in
this girl? You understand What that means?
I didn't fucking kill anybody.
Are you fucking crazy?
- Who is she, Jack?
- She just shoWed up. I didn't knoW her.
- I thought Samantha sent her.
- You don't knoW the girls you fuck?
- I have girls up here all the time. I don't knoW.
- Jack, shut up.
I knoW the last thing you need
is the cops searching this place.
So you have a couple of hours
to make it clean.
But you're gonna have to ansWer
some questions at some point today.
Goddamn it, Sam. Why do you
bring this shit into our house?
Don't lecture me about my life.
Don't judge me. You're better than that.
- So are you.
- Sam isn't so fucking innocent, either.
Sam, come on.
Hey, you guys grab the feet,
I'll get the head.
On the count of three.
You ready? One, tWo, three.
Cause of death: Electrocution.
And asphyxiation
due to strangulation.
Semen samples Were found
in the vaginal area, the anus...
Open your eyes, Samantha.
Jesus! Fucking amateur hour.
Sam, come here, come here.
Are you okay?
- Come here. Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Yeah.
- I just got spooked.
Okay, okay.
Why don't you go home
and just take the night off.
- Just get some rest.
- Okay.
Baby.
What's the matter?
You gotta get your mind
off that case.
Just leave your baggage
on the outside of the party.
I just Wanna solve it.
Will you take me home?
- Here, just take this.
- Would you, please, take me home?
- Have another bump.
- I just Wanna go home.
Baby, baby, baby.
Look, it's fun.
Hey, Jack.
Have you guys seen Jack?
- Where's Jack?
- I haven't seen him.
Hey, you guys seen Jack?
Hey, I kneW you'd come around, baby.
Come here.
What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck you, Jack.
Hey!
- Don't leave, you fucker!
- Shut up.
- Where the fuck do you think you're going?
- Fuck you.
I've been Waiting for you all night.
- God! What are you gonna do, Walk home?
- Fuck you!
You knoW What I've been
going through. So...
- You're ruining the fucking party...
- Shut up!
Shut up?
Oh, you feel like a big man noW?
Is that hoW you feel?
- Maybe.
- Fuck you.
Maybe. Maybe I do.
- Maybe I fucking do.
- Oh, God, you're so fucking tough.
- Get out of my Way, Jack.
- Get the fuck off her, dude.
- You're pathetic, Jack. You're so...
- Jesus Christ, Jack!
Goddamn it!
If you Would just shut the fuck up!
You shut up!
- You fucking get over...
- Don't touch me.
- Don't fucking touch me!
- Don't touch you?
Sir, come on.
I just need you to come in here
and cool out for a second, okay?
- Thank you very much.
Take it easy.
Ma'am, do you Wanna
press charges or What?
- Has he ever hit you before?
- No.
- Do you guys have these drug orgies a lot?
Hello?
No, no. I'm up.
I'm up. What's going on?
Fuck you, motherfucker.
I kicked your ass, didn't I?
Shut the fuck up!
You knoW Where you are?
That attitude is not
gonna help you in here, Angelo.
So I moved
a couple of Whores.
Banged a couple of little sluts Who
lied to me about their age.
I'm the Italian Stallion.
I mean, What can I say?
A Warming little story, Angelo.
That's not Why you're here.
Tell you What happened.
You Wanna knoW about my sex life?
HoW come? Because the only sex life you
get is When he's fucking you up your ass.
Don't start no shit With me. I'll stick this
motherfucking chair up your ass!
Calm doWn! Calm doWn!
Hey! Tell us hoW you
killed all those girls, huh?
Nine names, With photographs.
Any of these ring a bell?
Ding.
I don't knoW any of those little cunts.
I mean, I Wish I did, but I don't.
Well, your cousin Kenneth
told us that you do.
- He told us everything.
- He didn't tell you fuck all.
He's a smart man.
Very, very smart.
Then hoW do We knoW about you guys
posing as detectives?
- He'd run circles around you, pigs.
- He told us everything.
Little nervous noW?
About time my fucking laWyer got here.
Where is he?
Is that the same JeW laWyer that let Kenneth
tell us you killed all those girls?
All them girls.
Too bad he can't represent you.
Conflict of interest.
'Cause he already turned on you.
Bullshit he told you
I killed those girls, huh?
- Idiot fucking cocksucker faggot.
- That's What he's saying.
- He's got an expensive laWyer backing him up.
- Big-ass laWyer.
His story is that
you and Steve did it all.
Who the hell's Steve?
What the fuck you talking about,
Who the hell is Steve?
- Does his blood type match?
- It's a match With the first eight victims.
But not With the last girl...
the girl you kneW.
- Maybe they're not connected.
- They are.
I had the lab double-check
the blood type of this last girl
and it kept coming up inconclusive.
One thing, though. There Was only
one semen sample, but no blood type.
NoW, With the first eight girls there Were
tWo semen samples and one blood type.
- There Was only one killer for this last victim?
- Yeah.
And after all the testing,
the lab determined
that one of the semen samples
from the first eight victims
Was What doctors call
a nonsecretor.
Which means you can't determine
the blood type from the semen or saliva.
The second perp.
And that's Who killed this last girl?
Have you checked to see
if Kenneth is a nonsecretor?
We can't find him.
Hello?
- Operator.
- Operator, get me the police.
One moment, please.
- LAPD Can I help you?
- Someone is breaking into my house.
- An address?
- It's 7665 RomorroW Drive.
- I'll send someone right over.
- Please hurry. Please.
Kenneth, get out
of my house! God.
- Doctor, please help me.
- Kenneth, you're bleeding.
Steve chased me. He's close by.
I need help, Doctor.
I called the police.
They're on their Way.
Shit. Come here.
Oh, God.
Steve did this to you?
He found out... He found out I told...
the police about him.
And he tried...
he tried to kill me.
- HoW do you knoW he didn't folloW you here?
- I don't. I don't.
The police... Make sure
the police are coming.
He knoWs about this place.
He knoWs about you.
He knoWs about your boyfriend.
He knoWs everything.
What?
Yeah. He knoWs
about your boyfriend.
HoW do you think he kneW
to send that girl here?
He tried to frame him.
I'm telling you,
you gotta... OW!
- Just relax.
- He's a very smart and bad man.
He Wort stop at anything.
He's terrible.
Kenneth, you gotta make
me understand.
Angelo told the police he never heard
of a guy named Steve.
They think you and Angelo killed those girls.
You and Angelo.
Then Who did this to me?
I'm telling you, it Was Angelo's doing.
You gotta believe me.
I'm not lying to you.
I'm not lying to you, Doctor.
It Was Angelo and Steve.
Well, I didn't knoW Angelo's
involvement until just noW.
Who do you think killed those girls?
It Was them.
I'm telling you, it Was them.
Angelo's more afraid
of Steve than me.
He Would... He'd never rat him out.
Kenneth! God, stop it!
I Want you to leave.
- I thought We had a connection.
- What?
You and me.
Well, We're...
We're both the same.
We see things... the same Way.
Goddamn it, bitch! Turn the fuck around
When I'm talking to you!
- Back up.
- Who the fuck is Kenneth, bitch?
Yeah, you like it like that,
fuckir cunt.
Dirty little fuckir Whore.
Yeah, come on. Let's play.
I knoW it's you.
Just let me talk to Kenneth.
Fuck that pussy!
He's long gone.
- Just let me talk to him a second!
- Shut up!
Just for a... Kenneth.
- Kenneth, please.
- Shut up.
Shut up.
Shut up. Shut up!
Fuck you, slut.
Doctor? Doctor?
I need help. Doctor, please.
My head.
Doctor, it hurts.
Please, I don't remember anything.
I need help.
Please, please, I need help.
Please, please, help me.
Please, please, please.
Angelo's gonna turn state's evidence
and testify against Kenneth
in order to avoid the death penalty
unless Kenneth cooperates and testifies.
One of them is gonna get a break.
Is it going to be your client?
No, Jillian, my client
doesn't need a break.
Samantha, are you okay?
I've been calling you all morning.
They're one in the same. Kenneth is Steve.
He's the classic multiple personality.
It's a textbook case. I think he's unaWare
of the crimes committed by Steve.
Get out of my office right noW.
I'll talk to my client,
tell him What you advise,
and I'll think about What
your psychologist just said.
- Goddamn it, Sam.
- The guy needs help, not the gas chamber.
- Did the medical examiner look at his Wounds?
- Yes.
They Were self-inflicted,
Werert they?
I'm gonna offer a plea agreement.
Otherwise, I think he's gonna Walk.
- On What grounds?
- He's not sane.
- What? What?
- The guy needs help.
You're the one that needs some
psychiatric counseling! Goddamn it!
There's not a goddamn DA
in their right mind in this country
Who Would drop a murder trial
With that kind of evidence in their face.
Do you knoW he murdered Women?
- Think you can see things other people can't?
- Yes, I do.
Well, can you see this?
Fuck you!
Dick.
- Sam, let's go.
- Just give me a minute.
For What?
The damage is already done.
You think I'm Wrong, don't you?
Remember the litmus test?
You said Kenneth passed.
Get your stuff.
Get all your stuff.
It's not gonna happen again, Sam.
I knoW.
So you Wanna hypnotize
my client again?
Yes, I believe both Kenneth
and Steve inabit the same body,
but are different personalities
and different people altogether.
- And I can prove this.
- HoW do you go about proving this?
- I need to see both of them again.
- Through hypnosis?
Yes.
- Whatever.
- I need to speak to my client first.
- We're ready.
- You sure about this, Sam?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- Okay.
This is Dr. Samantha Stone.
Present With me
is Kenneth Alessio Bianchi.
Observing are Assistant
District Attorney Jillian Dunne,
Detective Bryant,
Detective Smith
and Jacob Kantor,
counsel for Mr. Bianchi.
This is a voluntary hypnosis
of Kenneth Bianchi
in order to determine
multiple personality disorder...
to meet the personality of Steve
and any other personalities
that may be manifested.
I don't understand.
Other personalities?
Schizophrenics generally suffer
from multiple personalities.
They never just have one
alter ego.
Kenneth, I Want you to relax.
You ready to begin?
Close your eyes.
I Want you to think about
your most relaxed
and peaceful place.
Breathe in deeply.
Exhale.
Breathe in.
Breathe in deeply.
And exhale.
Breathe in.
Exhale.
I Want you to free your mind.
Forget everything...
every sight, every sound.
Just you and me.
Just the sound of my voice.
Just you...
and me.
I'm gonna count backwards
from five.
When I get to one,
you'll be in a completely
different state.
We'll be able to speak freely.
Five,
four,
three,
tWo,
one.
Open your eyes, Steve.
Who am I speaking With?
You knoW Who the fuck I am.
Where the fuck you going?
I just need to move
this chair right here.
What the fuck Was that all about?
Nothing. I'm sorry.
You're damn right you are.
You better behave.
Do you Want me to fuck that sWeet,
little, tight ass of yours?
Tell me about the girls.
What about them?
You choked them,
you raped them.
Oh, I did more than that.
I fucked them, killed them.
Shot one of them up
With cleaning fluid.
Why, I fucked one so hard...
in the ass,
she needed a tampon
just to stop the bleeding.
HoW do you like that, honey?
Does that shit turn you on?
So tell me about the first victim.
The first girl you killed.
The girl With the locket. Silver necklace.
Ah! The hooker.
Angelo picked her up.
I Waited in the street.
He drove around to Where I Was.
I got in the car.
I fucked her, killed her.
We dumped the body off.
And that Was it.
Nothir to it.
Tell me about the others.
You knoW about the others.
You and Angelo Buono
killed them.
Angelo's damn near
too fucking stupid to do shit.
But yeah, he got a piece.
Steve Was the brains
behind the operation.
That's right.
Steve's running the shoW.
So tell me about the last girl.
The little hooker bitch?
The one you knoW real Well.
And I mean knoW
in a biblical sense.
She begged for it.
She Wanted these hands
around her neck.
Begged for it.
And then she realized I...
Wasrt gonna let up.
I'm speaking to Kenneth noW.
You sorry for that?
Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so, so...
What the fuck you Writing, bitch?
You got a goddamn
tape recorder running?
Just psychiatric notes.
Don't Worry about it.
Please, go on.
No, no, no, Steve's not here.
No. No, no. No Steve.
I'm not...
Steve's not here. No.
No. I'm Billy.
I'm Billy, ma'am.
- Billy?
- Billy, Billy, Billy With a "B".
Were you there for the killings?
Well, yeah.
I Was there for some of them.
Oh, yeah. I Was there for all of 'em.
Yeah, me and Steve and Angelo.
So you're saying Billy
took part in these murders?
That Billy actually
killed some of these girls?
Yeah, yeah. I mean,
I had some fun too With the girls.
All right.
- I Wanna talk to Kenneth again.
- Already?
Please?
NoW close your eyes.
I'm gonna count backwards
from five.
When I get to one,
you'll be back to reality.
Five, four,
three,
tWo,
one.
Open your eyes, Kenneth.
Is this Kenneth Alessio Bianchi?
Yes.
Kenneth, look me in the eye.
No, Kenneth.
- You failed.
- Failed? Failed What?
Doctor?
You're a liar,
and I knoW you killed those girls.
I don't remember anything, Doctor.
No, Doctor.
Doctor, you can't leave me noW.
Doctor, no!
Doctor! Let go of me!
No, don't leave me!
Failed? What the fuck are you talking about?
HoW did he fail?
He failed because he's a fraud.
He failed because he's a liar.
This is outrageous. You said you were
gonna prove it was Steve who did this.
There never was a Steve.
True multiple personalities are separate
and distinct. They do not merge.
It was just an act
the whole time.
Then why doesn't Kenneth
remember anything?
He's lying about everything.
He was playing me from day one.
How do you know that?
How do you know it was an act at all?
Well, he invented a third personality,
Billy, as soon as I suggested it to him.
Any time he thought he needed
to show me something, he would.
He was under hypnosis. How can he be
playing us if he's under hypnosis?
He was never hypnotized,
and I proved this.
Under actual hypnosis, if someone
is given a physical obstacle, like a chair,
and they are truly hypnotized,
they will recognize it.
If not, they will do what Kenneth did
and walk right through it.
- This doesn't prove anything.
- It proves he's a fake
and proves he never
let me hypnotize him.
- This is entrapment. You set him up.
- You agreed to it.
- I'll see you later.
- Yeah, I'm buying.
Thanks, Doc.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org