Journal entry number 11345-1.
3:20 p.m., Thursday, June 6th.
The concentration of serotonin
has been increased
by two milligrams...
and dissolved in
a 0.8 saline solution.
Uh-uh, point 5.
Correction, 0.5 saline.
Yesterday's slight increase
didn't make any difference
in tissue absorption.
Mmm.
We're optimistic that
the serotonin increase
will be sufficient to produce
an intensified level of aggression
without causing harmful
side affects.
Where's McConnel'!
(sighs )
( beeping )
( exhales )
(continues to breathe deeply)
(rapid heartbeat)
If this new solution proves
effective in the animals...
we will begin human testing.
(door crashes open)
Hey...
the gang's all here.
All right...
final phase.
We hope to be able to show
that aggressive behavior
is triggered by fluctuations
in brain chemistry,
as well as fluctuations in
neurotransmitters, such as serotonin.
- ( Glove snaps)
- Spank me harder, baby.
- ( Animals screeching)
- Oh, sorry.
Ethanol oestradiol, LHRH.
Maintained at minus
15 degrees Celsius.
If we can prove
Dr. Burns' theory...
then we believe by manipulating
the level of MAO-A enzyme,
which breaks down neuro-
transmitters...
we should be able to control
aggressive and hyperactive behavior.
( Hisses )
One milligram of ethanol oestradiol
to increase plasma
testosterone.
(computer beeping)
Computer voice:
E-Mail for Doctor Irwin Burns.
Urgent.
Now whatl'!
(electronic beeps)
What's going on'!
All right.
Increase the serotonin
by 25 milligrams...
and add 20 milligrams
of the amantadine.
Hello?
What are you guys doing?
Dr. Burns had carefully
measured that.
Exactly! Carefully,
carefully, carefully.
Breakthroughs aren't made
carefully and conservatively,
daddy's little girl.
Science is about taking risks
and pushing boundaries.
But we've been making
such progress.
Okay, 25 more milligrams
of ethanol oestradiol.
You think so'!
I've made more progress
in one day with my own testing
than your father's made
in three goddamn years.
Not that he'd now it of course,
because he never listens to me.
What are you talking about?
He highly values your expertise.
Bullshit! He keeps everything
under lock and key.
He's so secretive,
he's gotta do it all himself.
Cause he's a paranoid,
old wimpy geek.
It's time we made some
goddamn progress around here.
Hmm.
Toshi, how can you betray him'!, how can you betray him'!, how can you betray him'!
She's just as sick
of your father as I am.
- But he is in charge of this.
- Not any more.
And there's nothing
he can do about it.
Sixteen milligrams of rubidium,
and ten milligrams
of ethyl alcohol.
Don't bother.
I changed the key code.
(electronic buzzing )
Open this door.
I demand that you open
this door!
Irwin!
Oh shit!
It's reacting.
(shouts )
Kat h ryn ?
That shouldn't be happening.
We checked the calculations
three times.
McConnel:oh,shit!:oh,shit!:
Oh, shit!
I; Dad:
- ( alarm sounds)
- Kathryn!
Oh, God...
Kat h Kat h Kat h fyn!!!
Kathryn! Aaaah!
Oh, God.
Kathryn.
( Hissing )
( hissing )
- (screams )
- Kathryn!
Kat h ryn! Kat h ryn!
Come on.
Row, row, row your boat,
gently down the street...
...merrily, merrily
life's a bowl of treats.
Row, row, row your boat
gently down the street...
Row, row row your boat
merrily, merrily, merrily
merrily, merrily, merrily...
pop goes the weasel.
- (screams )
- ( laughs )
I'm telling.
You're in big trouble.
Scaredy cat. Scaredy cat.
Scaredy cat.
I hate you.
I'm telling mom.
Looks like you'll be around
a couple more years.
Well, the Mrs.'ll be disappointed.
So, I'm not having
a heart attack, huh, Brad'!
It's probably just
a had case of indigestion.
But let me go check
on those test results.
Maybe it's just
Betty's sausages.
Mmm. I'm gonna miss those.
I'll be right hack.
(whispering ) Poor thing.
Brad breakin' her heart like that
That's not what I heard.
I heard he wanted her to move
to the city with him...
but she turned him down flat.
What a shame, those two
were made for each other.
Maybe she'll change her mind.
She's got too much
of her father's stubbornness.
You know those Biddies.
Maybe he'll change his mind.
Thanks, Sam.
Have a nice day.
Just as I thought,
everything's fine.
If you weren't carryin'
around this baby...
you'd be a whole lot
better off.
This baby's the lifeblood
of this town.
And I can guarantee
a couple of inches
by the end of the festival.
Rumor has it, Juergen's outdone
himself with this years brew.
Mm-mmm. So I'm told.
You do plan on hanging out
with us small town folk
at least through the weekend,
don't you'!
Nope. Gotta go tomorrow.
Well, we're all gonna miss ya.
Especially a certain
pretty cop I know.
Who happens to get her
good looks from her daddy.
I'm only four hours away.
(hysterically) Dr. Kagen, something's wrong.
I don't know what to do.
He won't talk, I found him
lying in the woods--
Slow down, Mrs. Stills.
Take it easy.
Let's just get him
on the table.
Let me get out of your way.
Grace, don't worry, the doctor
'll take care of Mikey.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Thanks, Mayor.
I've never seen him like this.
I can't get him to respond.
- What's wrong with him'!
- He's in shock.
I can't even get him
to let go of his toy.
(rattling - gunshot)
Let's go.
I got him.
25 yards.
Northeast.
Son of a bitch.
I see him.
Watch out! Watch out!
- He's right there.
- Shoot, damn it. Shoot!
Damn!
All right, Jesse.
Kickin' ass!
The bushmaster!
(hollering - laughing )
Oh, man, what a chase.
Let's see the trophy, Jess.
No more hoppin' for you
Mr. Rabbit.
- ( laughs )
- Oh, man.
( Whistles )
Hey, Corky.
Hey, girl.
Come on fetch.
Damn lazy dog.
( Hissing )
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got something for you.
Thanks.
That was, uh, that was sweet.
Oh, cool.
This is the exact one I wanted.
How'd you know'!
Where'd you get it'!
Jesse doesn't carry this one.
I had him, um, special order
that for you.
It's got 256k. You got rolodex,
you got dayplanner.
Plus an alarm, world time, map,
reminder, password access.
Yes, yes, yes.
And you can hackload it all
on your computer.
I know this is the one I wanted.
They're great.
I was gonna get one for myself,
but um...
you know me, I'm more of
a paper and pen kinda gal.
Besides there's nothing like
the smell of a good leather hinder.
What am I doing?
(sighs )
It's so easy to slip hack.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Jo.
You know how
I feel about you...
but I, I can't do this.
It's not, it's not fair
for either of us.
I don't want to change my mind.
There's just...
there's just
so many things that I...
that I want to accomplish,
things I'm never gonna get
to do in a small town.
I mean you have to go to
the city, the big city...
to be a specialist,
to be at the big hospital...
I'm tired of everybody knowing
everybody else's business,
and I...
I know, I know we've been
through all this before hut...
I wish you would change
your mind and come.
(sighs )
Just, just come with me please?
We have been through
this before.
The timing's off.
Your wants and needs are...
are different than mine.
I'm happy here and you're not.
Beside's we're like, what,
only four hours away'!
Yeah.
Police radio:
Jo, you there'!
Jo?
Yeah, Ben, go ahead.
Call just came in from
old man Simpson's.
Sounds pretty serious.
Find Pat and bring him
with you.
Dr. Kagen's still fishing.
He won't be hack till tomorrow.
Damn...
Has Brad left yet'!
I think he's still around.
Well, find him.
We need him.
Be right there.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Brad, glad you're still around.
Ya just caught me,
I'm leaving tomorrow.
- Nice to see you, Brad.
- Yeah, you too, Bud.
So whatta we got'!
Well, we got a call
from Jimmy Ray.
He was delivering groceries
when he found Simpson inside.
- What's wrong with him'!
- Well, he's pretty dead.
What happened'!
Tryin' to figure that out.
Seems old man Simpson was
chopping wood here,
when somethin' must a surprised
him and attacked him.
Somethin' what'!
Tryin' to figure that out.
And he struggled to make it
all the way inside.
What's this from'!
You're trying to figure
that out.
Uh-huh.
You know guys,
Simpson had a dog.
Yeah, that's right. Corky.
- Hey Bud, would you'!
- Yeah, I'll take a look.
Hey, Bud.
Watch your step.
Somethin' wanted to get inside
pretty damn bad.
Jeez.
Ugh. What is that from'!
I'm not sure.
Bud:
Corky.
(whistles )
Corky?
Come here, girl.
(whistles )
- ( rusting noise)
- Corky!
(whistles )
Come on, girl.
Got a nice big bone for ya.
Okay, a big juicy steak.
That's my final offer.
Jesus Christ.
Hand me my forceps.
Is that what I think it is'!
- I've never seen one so--
- ( door opens)
Hey, get a load of this.
Grab this end.
Jesus...
I guess we're not gonna
find Corky.
Haemotoxins cause a breakdown
of the blood cells
leading to local bruising
and internal bleeding.
Neurotoxins affect the central
nervous system
especially the part controlling
respiration and the heart.
As much as you got.
(thunderclaps -
computer shuts off)
(sighs )
Yep. Perfect.
I said two p.m., guys.
(thunderclaps)
(hissing - screams)
(phone rings)
Where is it'!
(breathing heavily)
- Yeah'!
- Jo, it's me.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hey thanks.
Power company's got an
a.m./p.m. learning disability.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Dr. Burns'!
- Speaking.
- Phil, City Hospital Pharmacy.
I just received an unusual
antivenin request
that I think you want
to know about.
It's from a town
in close proximity.
This year's hops have a real
unique aroma, flavor, and character,
making the new Fillmore Lager...
Juergy, Juergy, Juergy.
- Juergen.
- You're so cute.
As if I really care
what hops are.
For me. Hops'!
( chuckles )
A bunny rabbit hops.
This is not about beer.
This is about,
I know it sounds funny...
it's about image.
Coolness. Prestige.
If you're not drinking
Fillmore Lager you're out.
Passe. Like roller-skates,
record players,
and Riunite on ice.
You know what I mean'!
No. What I know about...
is that this year's brew
is the best it's ever been.
And everyone's going
to know that.
- Juergy.
- Juergen.
Whatever.
This is how it works:
You start with a good product,
which you have.
Yah, we use only the finest
malt, rice, yeast.
Exactly.
You're the hrewmeister.
Then you need a consistent
message like...
"Fillmore up.
The big-time small-town taste."
Which we will kick off
at this year's festival.
Juer, Juergy.
Thank you.
We got these bands.
We got the babes, we got the boys...
we got nationwide coverage.
All you have to worry about
is keepin' the beer flowin'.
It's gonna be huge.
It's not only me
that's counting on this.
(rock music plays throughout)
It's out of the question.
But Mayor, this is an extremely
dangerous medical situation.
If we have a problem here,
let's solve it.
Let's not blow it outta
proportion.
It's already out of proportion.
Ben, are you tellin' me
we can't handle one stinkin' snake'!
Until I know what I'm up
against I can't answer that.
Jesus!
How many snakes did we shoot
when we were kids'! Come on.
You didn't see what this thing
did to Simpson.
And he had an ax in his hand.
Snakebites usually aren't fatal
Tell that to Simpson.
He probably had
an allergic reaction.
He was old, he had a weak heart
which would make him
more affected
by the hemolytic principle
in the venom.
And he lived alone
in the middle of nowhere.
Did you see the size
of this fang'!
The venom disintegrated
half his face.
I saw the body, Brad.
A lot of people got a lot
riding on the future of this brewery.
Including most of us
in this room here.
And if I cancel this festival...
Fillmore Lager remains a great
beer that only locals know about.
And it's gonna cost
this town a lotta money.
I got a responsibility to see
that that don't happen.
Mayor, mayor,
with all due respect...
people are here now.
People who don't know their
way around nature.
City people.
There's a lotta camping gain' on,
a lotta drinkin'...
and we don't know what this
thing is capable of.
Let's send 'em home now.
I won't do that.
At least, let's move it
somewhere safer.
- That's got better crowd control.
- What about Central Avenue'!
Let's make it a street festival.
Yeah, then we can block off
the other streets.
Biddle Park's been the
tradition...
that's why a lotta people
come here.
We're talkin' about
a snake here.
A creature that eats rodents,
small animals and other snakes.
Maybe that's why the crops
are so good this year.
- Because of a monster snake.
- ( knocking at door)
Pardon me for interrupting...
I was told I could find
Dr. Kagen here.
I'm Doctor Kagen.
What can I do for you'!
Dr. Brad Kagen?
I'm Brad Kagen.
- Who are you'!
- I'm Doctor Irwin Burns.
I understand that you have
requested a large amount
of polyvalent antivenin.
- You're from City Hospital?
- No. I'm a biochemist.
And what can we do
for you, Dr. Burns'!
(counting in Spanish)
( giggling )
- ( hollers )
- (screams )
(rattling heard in distance)
(Speaking Spanish)
(rattling continues)
(rattling nears)
(screaming )
If I can confirm the presence
of these chemicals,
then we'll know for sure
if it was Seth.
Venom entered through a bite
on the lower left calf.
We also found traces of venom
in his eyes,
probably causing blindness
prior to death.
I was surprised that he was
able to make it to the house.
There's also two puncture marks
indicating a bite
behind the right ear,
just under the hairline
which I initially missed.
That would account
for the hemorrhaging.
So, uh, what caused the accident?
My lack of people skills.
Damn needle in a haystack.
( Rattling )
We need a herpetologist.
I know someone.
- You're sure it's him'!
- There's no doubt.
The sloughed skin and chemical
compounds confirm it.
Oh, now that we know what
we're dealing with...
I think we should call
City Hospital hack
and get the proper antivenin.
Polyvalent may be insufficient.
We gotta find Seth and destroy
him before he kills again.
Man:
Nice, very nice.
Confidence.
It's all about confidence.
Pressure to the head.
Steady.
- ( Intercom beeps)
- Good.
- Yes'!
- Hash...
you have a very important
phone call.
Thank you.
I'll take it in my office.
I gotta take this call, okay'!
You keep working.
Don't get too cocky now.
Expect the unexpected.
- ( Light bulb pops)
- Damn.
Penelope.
(sighs )
( cat screeches)
I'm comin', I'm comin'.
You naughty girl.
Penelope?
(cat toy jingling )
Oh come on,
I wasn't away that long.
Fine, more for me.
( Hissing )
( hisses )
( rattling )
(music playing -
crowd cheering)
(music ends - cheering)
This is Eric Anderson
broadcasting from Biddle Park.
We're at the Fillmore
Lager Beer Festival.
We're coming to you
with some crazy people here,
we've got Fumes.
(crowd chanting)
Brewfest. Brewfest.
(music continues)
Please leave a message.
( beeps )
Dad, you there'!
Burns confirmed that Simpson's
death had to be from his snake.
The Mayor's being really
stubborn about this
and I think you're
gonna need to, um...
just give me a call
when you get this.
Hey, hey whoa, guys.
Slow down.
Party's the other way.
Nothin's gain' on around here.
Good night.
Wyatt Earp.
Keeper of the peace.
It's a livin'.
Sheriff told me
I'd find you here.
So how's it goin"!
Oh, drunk guys, I can handle.
30 foot snakes,
I don't know about.
Burns called in
a herpetologist.
- A herpewhat'!
- Snake expert.
Supposedly, he's one
of the best.
Should be able to help
you guys out.
Right. Right.
So you're still goin"!
They're expectin' me tomorrow.
I'm already late.
Who's gonna administer antivenin
if this thing can't be stopped?
The town doctor, Pat Kagen.
Okay.
So, where's your dad anyway'!
I didn't see him at the festival.
I don't know. I haven't
seen him since this morning.
I left a message for him
on the answering machine.
I go on patrol in about
ten minutes.
If you like, I can
check in on him.
Yeah, I'd appreciate that, Jo.
Thanks.
I gotta go finish packin'.
Yeah, sure Brad.
Dr. Kagen.
DI'. Kaye“?
Pat!
Pat.
(door creaks open)
- ( cat screeches)
- (screams )
Look, we don't know for sure.
Maybe he got away.
Let's not have any
false hopes here.
Even if he did get away
the venom would've killed him
and we'd have found
his body by now.
I'm sorry.
That's all I can say.
I'm truly sorry.
I'll shut it down now.
(loudspeaker: )
There's no immediate danger.
Repeat, there's no
immediate danger.
I always wanted me a pair
of them snakeskin boots.
From what I hear we could open
a goddamn store.
Let's go kick some ass.
Well sir, the Still's
sighting was here.
The two teenagers
disappeared here.
Simpson's place is here.
And the most recent
attack of, uh...
...was here.
Okay, and that's all the
attacks you know about?
Yeah. That we know about.
Well...
it's pretty clear that he's
marked out his territory.
That's a pretty large area,
my friend.
He's a pretty large snake.
Dr. Burns...
how did you manage to cross
an African King Cobra,
with an Eastern Diamondback
rattlesnake?
Gene splicing.
Interesting.
Why would anyone want
to combine
two of the most deadly species
of poisonous snakes'!
We wanted the most aggressive
animals possible for testing.
Fascinating.
Foolish.
So, how do we get rid of it'!
Well, first we have to find it,
of course.
I want to make sure that
we all know and respect
exactly what we're
dealing with here.
Respect'!
Yeah, um...
you see in order to overcome
a deadly opponent...
you have to learn
to think like it.
I hate snakes.
All right.
Consider, Deputy Fuller...
snakes kill in one year
more people
than sharks kill
in 100 years.
They are responsible
for more deaths
than all the other dangerous
animals in the world combined.
Now that is a power
you have to learn to respect
just a little hit.
Let's consider
Ophiophagus Hannah,
0l'I...
the African King Cobra.
Its venom, a tablespoon,
even dried,
could kill 165 people
or 165,000 mice.
Oh, and then there is
Vihoras de Cascaheles.
Spanish for rattlesnake.
Rattlesnakes can strike
at ten feet per second.
It has the most highly
developed fangs
of all the venomous snakes.
Now, my whole point is...
as if nature wasn't good enough,
and thanks to science...
we now have here...
a specimen with all these
beautiful traits.
Come on, Buck!
Over here!
Check it out.
We're gonna need bigger guns.
Hey, hey.
Snakes pick up on vibrations
in the ground.
Okay, so we want to make as
little noise as possible.
But here's the game plan.
We're gonna pound stakes
into the ground,
that's the reason
for the rubber mallet.
We're gonna attach the razor
wire to each stake with this wire
and that's the reason
for the cutters and the gloves.
So remember,
work as quietly as you can...
look out for anything
that might be moving...
and, um, expect the unexpected.
Is that all you got'!
Yeah. Why?
Don't you have some kind of modern
technology to fight this thing?
These are the tools
of my trade, Brad.
I've been at this for over
25 years.
But this is not an ordinary snake.
The methodology for
catching a snake doesn't change.
Besides I've made some
modifications.
Why don't we just shoot
the damn thing?
Sure, let's shoot him,
be my guest.
Go on shoot 'em.
He's that tree over there.
Shoot.
Fine you want me to shoot him'!
I'll shoot that tree.
If you want to kill him
instead of just pissing him off,
you're gonna have
to hit him in the head.
That's that rock about six
inches off the ground.
No, that's not him, there he is
over there, he's that tree.
He's going through the leaves
through the leaves...
there he is at ten o'clock.
Go ahead shoot him, man.
Okay, okay, I got the idea.
You better get it...
because if you don't
you're dead.
Now you're calm right now.
But you see this guy
eyeball to eyeball
your adrenaline is going to
kick in and you will not be calm.
There's probably two people
amongst us here...
okay, maybe one...
that maybe, maybe could get
off a shot...
if we get lucky
and if we get a chance.
Believe me, guys...
the gun is not the way to go,
at best it's only a backup.
You're gonna go up there now'!
Yeah, thought I'd take a look,
check some things out.
I'll come with you.
No, you'll stay here.
What happened to never being
alone in case of a bite'!
You know, I am qualified for that.
Ah, I almost forgot, doctor.
Can you ride a hike'!
Yeah, I think so.
There's an extra one in there.
Why the bikes?
Less vibrations.
Gets you closer to the action.
Besides I ain't
a very good runner.
I'm Japanese.
Japanese were not built to run,
we were built to last.
Brad, be careful.
Jo, you there'!
Yeah, Ben, go ahead.
How's it 9°I"9'-'
We're setting up camp.
Brad and Hash went
to take a look around.
Do you guys see anything by you'!
- No sign of it.
- Where are you guys'!
Oh, about a mile past
Canyon Creek.
Gonna head over toward
Jackson farm.
You guys be careful.
Yeah, you too.
What is that'!
Shit.
I think it's him.
Jeez.
Holy shit.
I think it's him.
Jesus, this sucker's huge.
Son of a bitch.
It's already dead.
Hey, saws!
I got 'em.
He's already dead!
( Rattling )
( rattling )
(screaming heard in the distance)
Billy.
Billy!
Jesse, Conrad!
Oh my God, oh ml!-
Come on!
- Billy!
' ( Saying )
Billy what happened'!
Did you get bit'!
Billy show me where you're hit.
Get his clothes off
so we can see where he's hit.
Jesus Christ, his pulse
is going through the roof.
Get a tourniquet ready!
Billy, hang in there, buddy.
Billy!
Jesus.
Oh shit man, come on,
do something.
Try CPR.
He's dead.
No, no he can't,
he can't he...
if we suck the venom out,
he'll be all right.
He's dead, Buck.
No, no, he can't he.
He can't he.
Buck!
God damn it!
It can't be far,
let's go get it.
What about Billy'!
There's nothing we can do
for him now.
We'll come hack for him.
All right, spread out.
I wanna get that
son of a bitch.
Oh God.
I don't wanna die.
Buck!
Get it together!
Come on.
( Crow caws )
( rattling )
Time to die you son of a---
(screams )
(screaming heard in distance)
Oh shit, we're screwed,
we're screwed!
Conrad.
Conrad!
( Groaning )
( Saslli?y )
Conrad!
Oh God.
Get out of the way.
Oh shit. Hold still.
Jesse move.
( Hisses )
(hisses - loud screech)
They play dead'!
Yeah, like a dog.
Cohras'll do that sometimes
to lure their prey in.
They're very clever.
What is it?
Here, hold this hack.
Snake shit.
That's uric acid crystals,
nitrogenous waste.
Snake piss.
It's still pretty fresh.
He can't be too far.
What'!
You see something?
Shh!
Someone's coming.
There.
That's Buck.
Buck!
Buck. Buck.
What are you doing?
What happened'!
What are you, what,
what happened'!
Huh?
What happened'!
(branches cracking)
Oh shit.
Back up slowly...
one step at a time.
Calm, calm.
Ben!
Open the door, Ben.
Ben, open the door, man!
Open the damn door.
(loud bang on door)
Let's go man!
Let's get the hell out of here!
Will you shut up'!
We're not gain' anywhere.
We finally found the damn thing.
Okay, buddy boy, respect it,
love it.
Maybe it knocked itself out.
(tire flattens )
Guess not.
I'll be a son of a--
It's popped the damn tires, man!
Good deduction, Sherlock.
Where the hell is it, man'!
Tryin' to figure that out.
Maybe it left.
- So go check.
- Are you crazy, man?!
I almost lost my love jones
out there.
I ain't gain' nowhere!
( Rattling )
(Bud screaming)
Oh shit.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Blld!
Hang in there, Bud.
Blld.
( Hissing )
So, what's in the syringe?
Saltwater base with a high
concentration of King Cobra venom.
I thought you said a spoonful
would kill a hundred men.
Yeah, it would.
But I've been bitten
so many times...
and injected myself with increased
dosages over the years that--
That you body's built up the
antibodies to counteract the venom.
Jeez, he's like a walking
supply of antivenin.
Somethin' like that.
(sighs )
You okay?
I'm all right.
How many times you been bit'!
A few times too many.
How often you inject yourself'!
Couple times a month.
See, I can't let my
antibodies slide...
otherwise I gotta start all
over and build 'em up again.
My blood has saved a few lives
over the years.
When I kick the bucket,
no one will care about my organs,
but my blood could be
worth millions.
So what was your worst bite'!
Well, none of 'em were
exactly pleasant.
But, this is quite a story.
I was working with
a Black Mamba some years ago...
Called him "Sammy".
But I got a little too lax
in handling him one day...
and uh, Sammy put his fangs
in right here...
they went all the way through
and came out here.
Luckily, I kept my head...
so I milked Sammy and pulled
him out of my hand
without getting too much venom
into the wound.
You might even say we were
blood brothers from then on.
He even sends me a card
now and then.
That's amazing, Hash.
- Jo, he doesn't really send me--
- Hash, I got it.
I meant the story.
So, uh, Hash, you got a plan
for tomorrow'!
Yep.
Well, enough campfire stories
for tonight, huh'!
I think I'll go relieve Burns.
I figured he had a plan.
I was just kinda curious
Yeah, you addressed that point.
You do think he has a plan,
don't ya'!
Oh, yeah I'm sure he does.
(together)
Yeah, I'm sure he's got one.
That looks good to me.
You think we need more'!
That should do it.
Ben, this is Jo, come in.
Bud, are you guys there'!
I'm really worried about them.
They can take care
of themselves.
I'm sure they're okay.
(low pulsating tones)
Wow, that's pretty strong.
Yep.
So now what'!
Well, once we finish
covering it up...
we wait.
How is this supposed
to work again?
The vibrations from
the thumper box
will attract Seth to the area.
Hopefully.
Oh, he'll come.
I designed that box myself,
it always works.
And when he sees the gourmet
meal that we have catered for him...
lunch time begins.
Then, while he's digesting...
and becomes a little
sluggish...
the show begins.
I'll wrangle him into
the tube...
you guys will seal the tube,
after he's cleared, of course...
and then you lock it in.
I'll turn on the gas...
and our overgrown elapid
will go night-night forever.
Are you certain there's enough
gas in there to kill it'!
Absolutely.
Well, what if you can't get him
into the tube'!
Jo, you guys
hired me for a job.
Now you're all gonna have
to trust me.
(cocks rifle)
Dr. Burns, come on,
you're not going to need that.
Let's hope not.
Maybe it's moved on.
Nah, he's out there.
I can feel it.
How can you tell'!
Shh.
(bushes rustle - goat bleats)
You see it'!
Quite.
There.
Jo: Where'!
Shh.
(deep hissing sound)
Jesus, listen to that.
It sounds hungry.
Let's hope he likes goat.
Keep it down.
Look at the size of him.
(hissing - branches snapping)
(goat bleats)
Oh, he's beautiful.
Come on, Seth.
Come on.
Come and get it.
( Rattling )
( rattling )
( hisses )
Come on. Come on.
What's he waiting for'!
What the hell are you doing?
I can get him.
That's not the plan.
I've got a perfect shot.
No!
- Stop;
- ( glln fires )
What the hell's the matter
with you'!
I had the shot!
Shut up, that was not the plan.
Never mind the plan.
It'd be dead by now.
- Bullshit you'da missed!
- Not if you hadn't interfered.
- You screwed everything up!
- Your plan wasn't working.
( Gun fires )
There's no time for this!
Let's just figure out
what to do.
There's nothing to figure out.
We gotta find him and get him
into the goddamn tube
before he kills us all first.
Look, I had the shot.
Why didn't you just stick
to the plan'!
The plan, as far as
I'm concerned...
is to kill it, no matter how.
I had the shot and he knows it.
(breathing heavily)
Aaaah!
My thigh!
( Gunshots )
I got him, I got him!
Stay with Burns.
' ( Groaning in pain)
' 5t°P moving! Stop moving!
You're gonna be okay.
You are a big boy, Seth.
Yeah, yeah, ya like this'!
You like this, Seth'!
Come on baby, show me something.
( Hisses )
( rattling )
Stay down.
Come on, Irwin.
Stay with us.
( Hisses )
Antivenin going in.
Come on, Sethy boy.
You're gonna have to show me
something better than that my friend.
Come on, stay with us.
Come on, give me more, more!
Come on!
( Chuckles )
Is that the best you got'!
Check his pulse.
It's hitting through the roof.
Aw damn, polyvalent's not
working.
Oh, you're good, baby.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
I got you now, big guy.
( Hisses )
Jo, get the tube closer.
Hash'! Hash!
Get away from him!
- ( Rattling )
- Die! Why won't you die!
(loud hiss - screeching)
- Brad!
- Hang in there.
- Brad.
- ( rattling )
Get away from her!
- ( Hisses )
- Brad!
I'll lead him into the tube!
Go for the other end.
Open it up.
Brad, wait!
It's stuck!
Brad!
Come on!
Jo!
- Come on!
- Jo!
- Damnit!
- Now would be good.
.J°!
. ( hisses)
I am going to die in here!
( Loud hiss )
He's gain' for the other end!
Shit!
We'll never make it!
Go for that tree,
we'll jam him in.
Go! Push!
Faster.
Come on, go!
I got it!
Close the vents and gas him.
Good! Good!
(thrashing sound)
(thrashing decreases)
( quiets )
- ( crashing )
- (startled scream)
(soft hiss )
What's this?
A little somethin
I got for ya.
You know there's nothin' like
the smell of a good leather hinder.
Except for the smell
of a cadmium lithium battery.
I took the liberty of fillin'
in some important dates for ya.
Oh You did, did you?
Yeah.
Wow, looks like a busy week.
It is.
I called Dr. Brown...
and I told him that I had been
offered a better position
somewhere else.
I turned down the hospital job.
Are you sure that's what
you want'!
I think there's plenty of
excitement right here.
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything?
You are, but that's okay.
The helicopter'll pick it up
late this afternoon.
Thank God it's over.
Yeah!
Are you okay'!
It's all right.
It's okay.
(helicopter whirring)
(rattling heard)
(banging from inside)