♪ ...SET YOURSELF
IN THE THICK OF IT ♪
♪ SET YOURSELF
IN THE THICK OF IT ALL ♪
♪ THERE'S THE SUN
YOU WON'T SEE THE SHADOWS... ♪
Woman: WHOO!
Second woman: OHH!
Man: ALL RIGHT.
First woman: OH, MY GOD!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
CRANK IT UP! CRANK IT UP!
I LOVE THIS SONG!
RACHEL, SIT!
PUT YOUR SEAT BELT BACK ON!
OH! OH, YEAH!
YEAH!
YEAH, YEAH. ACTION
NEWS REPORTER.
OH, YEAH!
HA HA HA!
HEY, WHERE AM
I GOING TO CHANGE
WHEN WE
GET UP THERE?
YOU CAN CHANGE
ANYWHERE YOU WANT,
'CAUSE NOBODY GOES UP THERE
DURING THE WEEK, SO--
REALLY?
OK, MARK, SHOOT ME.
ALL RIGHT.
SHOOT ME. ALL RIGHT?
OH, YEAH!
AHH OOH!
♪ CHANCES ARE
I WILL BRING IT AROUND ♪
♪ THERE'S NO REASON
TO BE SITTING HERE-- ♪
[TURNS OFF RADIO]
HA! THIS PLACE IS AWESOME!
MMM. HI, THERE.
[CAMERA CLICKING]
HA HA HA!
THAT IS ENOUGH.
AHEM!
AHEM! AHEM!
OH, MY GOD.
NOBODY TOLD ME
MARRIED PEOPLE HAD SEX.
YEAH, YOUR LITTLE SISTER'S
REALLY FUNNY, ISN'T SHE?
GOD, IT'S REALLY
BEAUTIFUL OUT HERE.
OK. WHAT AM I
GOING TO WEAR?
UH, I LIKE THE BLACK ONE.
YEAH?
HEY!
THIS IS MINE!
YEAH?
AND WHO BOUGHT IT
FOR YOU?
Rachel: YOU.
IT LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
YOU WANT TO EAT FIRST?
YOU STARVING?
NO. LET'S GO TO WORK.
PRETEND LIKE YOU HAVE
THE GRASS SKIRT ON, PLEASE.
OK, THAT'S GOOD.
NO. BACK, BACK, BACK. WHERE YOU WERE.
RIGHT THERE. THERE!
[CAMERA CLICKS]
THAT'S GOOD.
OK. HANG ON.
ALL RIGHT.
[CLICK]
PERFECT.
[CLICKING]
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH UP THERE, BABY.
YOU'RE GETTING
A LITTLE CLOSE TO THE EDGE, OK?
COME ON, MARK.
YOU WANT A GOOD PICTURE FOR YOUR PORTFOLIO.
THIS IS IT.
WELL, YEAH,
IT'S A LITTLE DANGEROUS THOUGH, SO COME DOWN.
THAT'S WHY IT'S GOOD.
CARLA, PLEASE!
JUST TAKE THE PICTURE,
SCAREDY-CAT.
WELL, IF YOU WANT
TO BE DARING,
THEN COME OVER HERE
AND SIT ON THE RAILING.
WOULD YOU JUST LISTEN
TO THE MAN, YOU LOSER?
I AM NOT
GOING DOWN THERE
TO SCRAPE YOU UP
IF YOU FALL OFF.
I AM NOT FALLING! I'M FINE.
CARLA, PLEASE!
COME DOWN HERE.
SIT ON THE RAILING.
I WILL BE
THE GLAMOUR GIRL.
RACHEL, DON'T.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WANT, MARK.
ALL RIGHT, RACHEL.
QUIT SCREWING AROUND.
YEAH, RACHEL,
IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
RACHEL, QUIT
SCREWING AROUND.
OH, I FEEL LIKE I'M FLYING!
AAH!
RACHEL!
AHH!
Mark: CARLA,
BE CAREFUL!
GRAB MY HAND! GRAB MY HAND!
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
OH, HONEY, HOLD ON.
DON'T LET GO!
DON'T LET GO! PLEASE, GET ME UP!
HOLD ON.
OH, GOD, PLEASE
DON'T LET ME GO.
RACHEL, DON'T LET GO OF ME.
JUST HOLD ON.
DON'T LET GO.
I'M AFRAID. DON'T LET GO.
I'VE GOT YOU.
HELP!
[RADIO PLAYS LOUDLY]
HELP US!
OVER HERE.
WE NEED HELP!
PLEASE, HELP ME.
NO! AAH!
NO! NO!
HOLD ON!
RACHEL!
AAH! CARLA!
HELP!
OH, MY GOD!
PLEASE DON'T LET GO!
RACHEL! HOLD ON!
PLEASE DON'T LET ME FALL.
DON'T LET GO!
JUST HOLD ON.
DON'T LET GO.
Mark: DON'T LET GO!
OH, MY GOD!
AAH!
RACHEL!
Man: CARLA AND RACHEL WERE
CLOSER THAN MOST SISTERS.
CARLA WAS HER GUARDIAN,
HER CARETAKER.
RACHEL, CARLA'S BEST FRIEND
AND SPICE TO HER LIFE.
TWO YEARS AGO,
WHEN WE GATHERED HERE,
WE BADE FAREWELL
TO THE PARENTS
OF RACHEL AND CARLA.
TODAY, TRAGICALLY, WE COME
TO BID FAREWELL TO RACHEL.
IN A MOMENT,
HER MORTAL DUST WILL
JOIN THAT OF HER PARENTS ON THE LAKE,
EVEN AS HER SOUL JOINS
THEIR SOULS IN HEAVEN.
CARLA HAS ASKED ME TO READ
NOTHING GOLD CAN STAY BY ROBERT FROST
AS SHE SCATTERS THE ASHES
ON THE LAKE.
"NATURE'S FIRST GREEN
IS GOLD,
HER HARDEST HUE TO HOLD."
"HER EARLY LEAF'S A FLOWER,
BUT ONLY FOR AN HOUR."
Girl: CARLA!
"THEN LEAF
SUBSIDES TO LEAF."
Girl:
I'M AFRAID, CARLA!
"SO HEAT SANK TO GRIEF."
Girl: CARLA!
"SO DAWN GOES DOWN TO DAY."
I'M AFRAID,
CARLA!
COME ON. JUST TIP IT
AND LET HER GO FREE.
JUST LET HER GO.
"NOTHING GOLD CAN STAY."
AAH!
RACHEL.
[MURMURING]
RACHEL?
SHE WANTED
TO PULL ME IN.
HEY, HEY. SHH! SHH!
I COULDN'T BREATHE.
SHH! SHH! SHH!
SHE HAD HER HAND COME OUT--
Mark: IT'S OK.
[CROWD MURMURS]
I WANT TO GO HOME.
CARLA, WHAT AB--
NO. I WANT TO GO HOME NOW!
THE ROSES ARE BEAUTIFUL.
THEY ALWAYS WERE
HER FAVORITE FLOWER.
MAYBE IT'S BETTER
SHE STAYS WITH US A WHILE LONGER.
YOU THINK?
CAN I SEE?
WE ALWAYS WERE TOGETHER.
AND THE WAY SHE BELIEVED
IN LIFE AFTER DEATH AND KARMA,
IT'S PROBABLY BEST
SHE'S HERE.
AFTER ALL, MOM AND DAD
DID LEAVE THE PLACE TO BOTH OF US.
CARLA...
LOOK AT ME.
WHAT HAPPENED AT
THE LAKE WAS NOT RACHEL.
SHE'S GONE.
IF SHE'S GONE,
IT'S BECAUSE I LET HER GO.
DON'T DO THIS
TO YOURSELF.
I WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR HER.
RACHEL DEPENDED ON ME
FOR EVERYTHING.
SHE WAS LOOKING
INTO MY EYES,
AND I COULDN'T HOLD ON.
I CAN SEE HER FACE,
THAT LOOK OF HORROR
AND BETRAYAL.
I CAN SEE IT NOW.
I CAN SEE IT
WHEN I SLEEP--
THAT'S NOT REAL.
IT'S NOT RACHEL.
YOU KNOW THAT.
Girl: I'M AFRAID.
CAN'T YOU COME UP
AND GET IT, CARLA?
YOU'RE SO MUCH BIGGER.
JUST REACH, YOU SISSY.
DO AS I TELL YOU.
CAN'T YOU COME UP
AND GET IT, CARLA?
YOU'RE SO MUCH BIGGER.
I'M AFRAID.
COME DOWN.
DOWN WHEREVER
YOU ARE.
DOWN, DOWN,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
COME UP, PLEASE.
RACHEL!
AAH!
[DOOR OPENS]
GOOD MORNING.
HI. DIDN'T SLEEP WELL
LAST NIGHT, DID YOU?
UH, NO.
I HAD A BAD DREAM.
YEAH? WHAT ABOUT?
WHEN RACHEL
AND I WERE KIDS,
THERE WAS A KITE
STUCK IN A GUTTER.
I CONNED HER
INTO GOING UP TO GET IT,
AND I NEARLY GOT HER KILLED.
SHE FELL
FROM THE ATTIC WINDOW.
DID THAT REALLY HAPPEN?
YEAH. IF IT HADN'T HAVE
BEEN FOR THE HEDGE, SHE WOULD'VE DIED.
I SPENT THE REST OF MY LIFE
TRYING TO REGAIN HER TRUST.
YOU NEVER
TOLD ME THAT BEFORE.
ARE THESE THE PICTURES
FROM THE MOUNTAINS?
NO, I THREW THOSE AWAY.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO THAT.
I COULD'VE HANDLED IT.
I KNOW. I JUST THINK
IT'S BETTER WE MOVE ON.
I'LL TAKE SOME NEW ONES.
I DON'T NEED NEW ONES.
I THINK
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER WITH NEW ONES.
I ALSO THINK
MAYBE WE SHOULD FIND
A DOCTOR FOR YOU TO SEE.
I'LL BE FINE, ALL RIGHT?
ALL I NEED
IS A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
OTHERWISE, I'M HUNKY-DORY.
OK, THEN, HOW ABOUT
NOT GOING TO WORK TODAY?
GOING TO WORK
IS THE BEST THING THAT I COULD DO.
BESIDES, I'VE GOT
AN EXCLUSIVE WITH SENATOR BILLINGS.
HE'S RESIGNING,
AND I'M NOT GOING
TO LET HARRIS GET THE STORY.
I'M OK.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE
AT THE STUDIO.
OK.
WAIT UP.
HE'S IN 3415, RIGHT?
YEAH. PENTHOUSE.
OUR TAX DOLLARS AT WORK.
[DING]
Woman: I'LL MEET YOU
IN THE CONFERENCE IN DETROIT.
Man: DID YOU
NOTICE IF THEY HAD A LAUNDRY SERVICE?
Woman: SEE YOU LATER.
Man: YEAH, THEY'VE GOT
A LAUNDRY.
THEY'LL DO IT FOR YOU,
ACTUALLY.
WHAT FLOOR ARE YOU ON?
[MEN TALKING]
HEY, UH, I HEARD
THIS THING FELL YESTERDAY.
HA HA HA.
[WOMAN WHISPERING]
Carla.
[RACHEL'S FLUTE MUSIC
PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BELL DINGS]
Man: UH--UH--UH.
SHE'S WAY OVERLOADED.
[BUZZER]
EXCUSE ME!
I NEED TO GET OUT.
HEY, HEY! THIS IS 25.
WE NEED THE PENTHOUSE.
I'LL MEET YOU UP THERE.
I FORGOT SOMETHING.
GEE, WHAT'D YOU DO, WALK?
COME ON.
THEY'RE GETTING ANTSY.
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S IN THE BEST LIGHT
OVER HERE.
YEAH. IF YOU'D
JUST GET IT NOW.
HERE SHE IS.
SHE'S JUST COME IN.
IF WE GET GOING NOW.
NO, LISTEN, SENATOR--
UM, YOU KNOW
BRADLEY.
CARLA, WE'RE DYING HERE.
WHY DON'T WE
DO IT INSIDE?
HE WANTS TO BE
INTERVIEWED WITH THE CITY IN THE BACKGROUND.
YOU WANT TO BE THE ONE
TO TELL HIM TO COME INSIDE
AND LOOK LIKE
A COUCH SALESMAN?
I CAN'T.
CAN'T IS NOT
IN OUR VOCABULARY, CARLA.
YOU KNOW THAT.
NOW, COME ON.
Man: I UNDERSTAND THAT, OK?
LET'S GO.
HELLO, SENATOR.
I THINK WE'RE
JUST ABOUT SET.
SOMETIME IN THIS
CENTURY, I HOPE.
UM, UH, WHY DON'T YOU
STAND OVER HERE,
SO WE CAN GET THAT
NICE BACKDROP FOR YOU?
PUT YOUR HAND
ON THE RAIL.
UH, SENATOR--
AAH!
WHAT?
Cameraman:
COME ON, CARLA. LET'S GO. LET'S DO IT.
[HORNS HONKING]
JUST STAY CALM.
WE'LL DO THE INTERVIEW.
FORGET THE INTERVIEW.
I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
JUST TALK
AMONG YOURSELVES FOR A SECOND.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
RIGHT BACK.
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH TIME
FOR THIS CRAP, YOU KNOW.
WE GET HER OUT HERE
AND SHE'S GONE!
CARLA...ALL RIGHT,
HE SAID FORGET THE INTERVIEW.
HE'S GONNA MAKE A STATEMENT
TO THE CAMERA.
YOU KNOW,
THAT TALKING HEAD THING?
LISTEN, IT'S GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
I'LL JUST TAKE CARE
OF EVERYTHING.
JUST SIT BACK AND RELAX.
OK, CARLA.
Senator: SEND A WOMAN
TO DO A MAN'S JOB.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
HA HA HA.
WHAT IS SHE HAVING,
A HOT FLASH?
Mark: SO I CONCENTRATED
ON ACROPHOBIA.
THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANTED, RIGHT?
RIGHT. FEAR OF HEIGHTS,
FEAR OF FALLING.
OK. WELL,
HERE IN THE CITY,
WE DO HAVE
SEVERAL PSYCHIATRISTS
WHO SPECIALIZE IN TREATMENT
OF PHOBIAS.
I'VE ALREADY
CHECKED THEM ALL WITH THE A.M.A.,
AND THE CLOSEST
WAS THIS GUY DR. OLIVER BARRETT
OVER AT MOUNT SINAI
HOSPITAL,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY
HE JUST DIED.
IT'S LIKE SHE JUST WENT
NEXT-DOOR FOR A MINUTE.
IS THIS YOUR FIRST TIME
IN HERE SINCE--
çi
THIS IS THE SCARF SHE WAS WEARING ON THE CLIFF.
IT CAN'T BE, CARLA.
SHE PROBABLY HAD
A COUPLE OF THOSE.
NO. IT'S THE EXACT ONE.
I BOUGHT IT FOR HER IN BERMUDA.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
ALL THOSE SOUVENIRS
COME FROM
THE SAME FACTORY IN CHINA.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DESTROYED ALL THE PICTURES?
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT THE NEGATIVES?
YEAH. EVERYTHING.
CARLA, IT'S NOT
THE SAME SCARF.
SO WHAT DO YOU GOT?
WELL, THERE IS
THIS NEW GUY,
DR. PAUL SADOWSKI
OVER AT THE UNIVERSITY.
HE'S CURRENTLY
CONDUCTING A STUDY ON ACROPHOBIA.
HE'S WRITTEN A BOOK.
PERFECT.
WHAT'S HIS NUMBER?
WELL, I'M NOT SURE
HE DOES THERAPY.
HOW WOULD I
GET IN TOUCH WITH HIM?
PSYCH DEPARTMENT
AT THE UNIVERSITY.
[HEART POUNDING,
BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HORN HONKS]
[HONKING]
HOW LONG DID YOU HAVE TO SIT
BEFORE YOU COULD MOVE?
15 MINUTES...
BUT I THINK I GOT DOWN,
ONCE I GOT MOVING,
IN ABOUT 2 SECONDS FLAT.
DO I GET POINTS
FOR THAT?
NO ONE'S
KEEPING SCORE HERE.
I AM, AND I THINK
I'M FAILING.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, WHEN
I'M IN A HIGH PLACE,
I FEEL THE DROP
PULLING ON ME,
AND ALL I CAN
THINK ABOUT IS FALLING.
YOU WANT TO JUMP.
YOU DON'T WASTE
ANY TIME, DO YOU?
LIFE IS SHORT,
AND YOUR CASE IS NOT
THAT UNIQUE, BELIEVE ME.
I WOULD SUGGEST YOUR ACROPHOBIA
IS TRIGGERED BY ASSOCIATIONS
REMINDFUL OF YOUR
SISTER'S DEATH.
NOW, HEIGHT WILL ALWAYS BE
THE STRONGEST ASSOCIATION,
BUT ANY ASSOCIATION--
SIGHTS, SMELLS, SOUNDS--
HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO PUT YOU ON THE BRINK,
WHICH IS THE CLASSIC PLACE
FOR THE ACROPHOBIC--
TO FALL, TO JUMP,
TO BE OR NOT TO BE.
I GOT TO GET PAST THIS.
I CAN'T LIVE
LIKE THIS.
IT'S AFFECTING
MY MARRIAGE, MY WORK, MY SLEEP.
I'LL PUT YOU IN TOUCH
WITH A NUMBER OF GOOD THERAPISTS
THAT WILL HELP YOU
WITH RELAXATION, HYPNOSIS--
NO. I WANT
TO WORK WITH YOU.
NO, I'M A RESEARCHER, CARLA.
YEAH, AND YOU'RE
ALSO HEADING A STUDY RIGHT NOW WITH PATIENTS.
THE INTERNET KNOWS ALL.
WELL, UM, I'M WORKING
WITH ONLY 4 PATIENTS.
IT'S COMPLETELY
EXPERIMENTAL.
AND THEY'RE ALL
EXTREME CASES.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO BE FINE.
I THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE PEACE WITH THIS.
I GOT TO GO. OK?
THANKS FOR YOUR TIME.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I CAN DO THIS.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Young Rachel: CARLA!
I'M AFRAID, CARLA!
CARLA!
[SIREN]
[HORN HONKS]
[HORNS HONKING]
[JACKHAMMERING]
[CACOPHONY OF CITY NOISE]
♪ CARLA, JOIN ME ♪
[ECHOING]
♪ CARLA, CARLA ♪
♪ JOIN...CARLA...
CARLA...JOIN ME... JOIN ME ♪
♪ CARLA...CARLA...
JOIN ME...JOIN ME... ♪
COME DOWN, COME DOWN,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
[ECHOING]
COME DOWN, COME DOWN, WHEREVER YOU ARE.
COME DOWN, COME DOWN,
WHEREVER YOU ARE...
I'M SO SORRY, RACHEL.
COME DOWN, COME DOWN,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
THE MAN WHO SAVED HER SAID
IF HE HADN'T GRABBED HER,
SHE'D BE DEAD.
WELL, IS SHE OK?
WHERE IS SHE?
SHE'S RIGHT OVER HERE.
SHE SHOULD BE
UP IN RECOVERY,
BUT WE COULDN'T GET HER
INTO THE ELEVATOR.
WELL, SHE'S A LITTLE
AFRAID OF ELEVATORS RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, YOU'RE TELLING ME.
LISTEN, SHE'S BEEN SEDATED,
SO KEEP IT SIMPLE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
IT DOESN'T MATTER. OK?
I TOLD THE DOCTORS
I WASN'T GOING TO JUMP, BUT I WAS.
OH, GOD, MARK,
I'M SO FRIGHTENED.
I DON'T WANT TO END UP
IN A PSYCH WARD.
CARLA, THAT IS NOT
GOING TO HAPPEN.
THEY WANT ME TO SIGN
VOLUNTARY COMMITMENT PAPERS.
THEY WANT TO SEND ME
TO GREENDALE.
SHH! SHH! SHH!
I WILL NOT LET THEM
DO THAT, OK?
I WILL STAY WITH YOU
EVERY SINGLE MINUTE, IF I HAVE TO. OK?
I THINK, UM, MAYBE
WE SHOULD GO SEE DR. SADOWSKI AGAIN.
OH, MARK, HE DOESN'T
WANT TO TAKE ANY PATIENTS.
IF HE DOESN'T TAKE YOU
THIS TIME,
I'LL PUNCH HIM
IN THE NOSE.
HE'S VERY TALL.
I'LL PUNCH HIM
IN THE NECK.
OK?
MM-HMM.
LET'S GET YOU
OUT OF HERE, ALL RIGHT? OK.
I TRIED TO JUMP OFF
THE FIFTH STORY OF A PARKING GARAGE.
WHAT MORE DOES IT TAKE?
YOU'RE ASKING TO BE PART
OF SOMETHING YOU DON'T COMPREHEND.
YOU THINK THIS IS ARMY
BOOT CAMP.
WHAT I DO IS NAVY SEAL
STUFF, GET IT?
I'M WORKING ON A TECHNIQUE
CALLED "FLOODING."
IT PUTS THE SUBJECTS
IN UNRELIEVED CONFRONTATION WITH THEIR PHOBIAS.
NOW, THE THEORY
IS THAT THIS WILL ALLOW A BREAKTHROUGH,
BUT THERE'S NO
GUARANTEE OF THAT.
JUST AS LIKELY,
THEY'LL CRASH AND BURN.
IT'S FOR CASES THAT HAVE
NO OTHER HOPE OF RECOVERY.
WELL, OK, THEN LET'S--
NO, BUT DO YOU THINK
IT'LL WORK?
WELL, IT ALREADY HAS WORKED
IN PRELIMINARY TESTS.
BUT I'M TRYING TO ANSWER
A BIGGER QUESTION HERE.
IF ACROPHOBICS IMPROVE
WHEN THEY CONQUER THEIR GENERIC FEARS--
AIRPLANES, ELEVATORS,
ROOFTOPS--
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THEY
BREAK THROUGH TO THE UNDERLYING CORE TERROR?
WHAT WAS HIDDEN
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR SISTER?
OR MORE SERIOUSLY,
YOU WILLING TO RISK
THE POSSIBILITY...
IS THERE ANY HISTORY
OF MENTAL ILLNESS IN YOUR FAMILY?
UM...
MY MOTHER SUFFERED
FROM SCHIZOPHRENIA.
THAT'S NOT ALWAYS
HEREDITARY, THOUGH, IS IT?
WELL, WE DON'T KNOW.
BUT VERY OFTEN IT IS.
LOOK, THIS RATCHETS
THE STAKES WAY UP FOR YOU AND CARLA.
IF CARLA WERE TO ENTER
MY TREATMENT,
SHE MIGHT BREAK THROUGH
HER ACROPHOBIA INTO CLARITY ABOUT HER SISTER,
OR SHE MIGHT BREAK THROUGH
TO SOMETHING FAR MORE DEVASTATING.
OK, SO IT'S...
ME AGAINST THE BOGEYMAN.
I'VE BEEN AFRAID OF THAT
MY WHOLE LIFE.
I WANT TO DO IT.
Mark: ARE YOU SURE?
Carla:
I THINK IT'S WORTH IT.
HOW DOES IT WORK?
WE WORK AS A GROUP.
SO I'M FLYING
FOR THE AIRLINES
AND--AND 15 YEARS WITHOUT
AN INCIDENT, BUT...
ONE DAY WE'RE ON--
WE'RE ON APPROACH TO PITTSBURGH,
DESCENDING TO 27,000 FEET,
WHEN, LIKE, THIS...THIS DOOR
OPENS UP IN MY MIND
THAT I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WAS THERE
AND OUT--OUT STEPS
THIS--THIS URGE TO J-JUMP OUT OF THE PLANE.
I WAS PARALYZED--
THE COPILOT HAD
TO LAND THE PLANE.
OLD BENNY HERE,
HE COULDN'T MOVE.
DO YOU MIND IF I TELL
MY OWN STORY, ZAK? DO YA, HUH?
THE DOC--THE DOC'S
HELPED ME TRACE IT BACK
TO WHEN I WAS IN THE ARMY.
I WAS A FIRST INFANTRY
PARATROOPER--THE SCREAMING EAGLES, YOU KNOW?
UP IN THE PLANE WITH MY
JUMP BUDDY, IVAN IRELAND--
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT NAME?
WHO NAMES THEIR KID
IVAN IRE--
IT WAS A FREEFALL EXERCISE.
IVAN JUMPED FIRST,
BUT HIS CHUTE DIDN'T OPEN,
AND I DOVE OUT, AND I
TRIED TO CATCH UP TO HIM, BUT I WAS TOO LATE.
IF I HADN'T PULLED MY OWN
RIP CORD, I WOULD'VE GONE IN WITH HIM.
I WATCHED HIM FALL.
I SAW HIM HIT THE GROUND.
YEAH, BUT YOU DID
THE BEST YOU COULD.
I SHOULD HAVE GONE IN
WITH HIM.
THE FACT IS, HE...
HE WASN'T FEELING RIGHT
THAT DAY.
HE DIDN'T EVEN TRUST HIMSELF
TO PACK HIS OWN CHUTE.
I DID IT.
OOPS.
LISTEN, YOU STUPID
LITTLE PUNK!
OKAY!
WE HAVIN' FUN YET?
COME ON, BENNY.
READY TO HIT THE TRAIL?
LET'S GO.
OH, OH, ZAK!
GET A LIFE!
Sadowski: YOU OK, BENNY?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M OK, YEAH.
YEAH.
WHOO!
WHOA! COME ON, BEN!
WHOO-HOO! BENNY,
COME ON OUT HERE!
HE'S GONNA FALL.
OH, YEAH.
WE SHOULD BE SO LUCKY.
NO, UNFORTUNATELY,
HE'S JUST SHOWING OFF.
Hallie: HE USED TO BE
LIKE THE REST OF US,
THEN HE GOT CURED
TOO WELL.
NOW HE'S COUNTER-PHOBIC.
OBSESSED WITH PROVING
HE'S NOT AFRAID OF HEIGHTS.
Sadowski: HEY, ZAK!
KNOCK IT OFF,
WILL YOU?
SHOW SOME RESPECT
FOR OTHERS.
COME ON, BEN!
HE EVEN GOT A JOB
WASHING WINDOWS ON CLARKE TOWER,
JUST SO HE CAN LOOK
DOWN.
OH, BEN, MAN,
IT'S GREAT!
I'M HOPING HE DIES
FROM THE CURE.
BOO!
OK, BEN, YOU'RE NEXT.
NO WISECRACKS.
WE SUPPORT EACH OTHER.
Zak: PIECE O'CAKE, BUDDY.
COME ON.
COME ON, MAN,
YOU CAN DO IT.
I'M SUPPORTING.
THAT'S SUPPORT, ISN'T IT?
Sadowski: OK, BEN.
COME ON.
FOLLOW MY VOICE.
COME ON. ONE STEP...
THEN ANOTHER.
FOLLOW MY VOICE.
KEEPING MOVING.
DON'T STOP. KEEP MOVING.
THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
COME ON, BEN.
WHY THE BLINDFOLD?
SO HE CAN CONCENTRATE
ON DOC'S VOICE.
Sadowski:
YOU'RE DOING GREAT. YOU'RE DOING GREAT!
I DON'T THINK I CAN DO THAT.
Sadowski: FOLLOW IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
TOO FAR ON YOUR FIRST TIME OUT.
BUT HE'LL PUSH YOU.
IF YOU DON'T DO
WHAT HE SAYS, HE'LL COUNT TO 3...
AND THEN IT'S OVER.
YOU'RE OUT OF THE GROUP.
FOLLOW MY VOICE.
COME ON, BEN!
[WHINES]
STAND UP! NO, NO, NO!
STAND UP! STAND UP!
THAT'S IT. COME ON,
KEEP COMING. KEEP COMING.
FARTHER THAN LAST TIME.
THAT'S IT. STOP!
[WHINES]
LOOK AROUND.
NOT BAD.
MUCH BETTER
THAN LAST TIME.
THAT'S A LOT FARTHER
THAN THE LAST TIME.
Hallie: YOU'RE
DOIN' IT, BEN!
WE LOVE YOU, BEN.
NOT!
CARLA, HAVE YOU
SEEN THE DROP?
IT'S 300 FEET,
STRAIGHT DOWN.
PLEASE DON'T.
[IMITATES
FALLING OBJECT]
KNOCK IT OFF, ZAK!
JAGGED ROCKS,
WATER BOILING UP--
STOP IT!
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
UM...
I'M SORRY.
Sadowski:
DON'T SAY "I'M SORRY."
SAY "I'M SCARED."
I'M SCARED.
WELL, THAT'S NOTHING
TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
I CAN'T.
[CLUCKS]
UNH.
[COUGHS]
BUT YOU HAVE TO DO IT.
YOU'RE COMMITTED TO DO IT.
WELL, I CAN'T.
ONE...
COME ON, CARLA.
JUST CLOSE
YOUR EYES, CARLA.
2...
MMM.
OK. OK.
COME ON.
STEP.
UHH...
THAT'S ALL I WANT YOU
TO DO TODAY. JUST TRUST ME.
MMM...
YOU KNOW WHY I LET ZAK
SHOW OFF THE WAY HE DOES?
NO, I GUESS NOT.
BECAUSE HIS COURAGE
IS CONTAGIOUS.
SO IS YOUR FEAR.
FEAR CAN'T HURT YOU
UNLESS YOU SURRENDER TO IT,
BUT ONCE YOU DO,
IT CAN KILL YOU.
JOCELYN, YOU'RE NEXT.
[MARK LAUGHS]
OK, GIVE ME SOME...
RIGHT HERE.
WELL, YOU LOOK BETTER
THAN I'VE SEEN YOU LOOK IN WEEKS.
IT'S THE BEST I'VE FELT.
I'M WITH PEOPLE WHO
UNDERSTAND ME.
IT'S AMAZING HOW FAST PEOPLE
CAN BOND WHEN THEY HAVE A COMMON ENEMY.
I'M THINKING I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GO BACK TO WORK.
YEAH.
I THINK YOU'RE PROBABLY
THE HEALTHIEST ONE OF THE BUNCH, AREN'T YOU?
HAS HE ACTUALLY EVER
CURED ANYONE, THIS DOCTOR?
YES!
ACTUALLY,
THIS KID ZAK.
HE'S, UH, WELL, ACTUALLY,
NOW, HE'S A COUNTER-PHOBIC.
COUNTER-PHOBIC?
YEAH, DON'T YOU--
HE'S, UH...
AFRAID OF COUNTERS.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HE FREAKS OUT
IN DINERS.
EXACTLY.
NO, HE HAS TO PROVE
HE'S NOT A PHOBIC.
HE WASHES WINDOWS
AT CLARKE TOWER JUST TO KNOW HE'S OK.
OH, YEAH, HE'S HEALTHY.
THE DOCTOR'S WORKING ON
A SPECIAL PROGRAM FOR HIM, BRING HIM BACK TO NORMAL.
WHATEVER THAT IS.
HEY, MR. PETERSON.
IT'S ZAK.
Peterson: YEAH.
UH, BOB NEVER
SHOWED TODAY.
YEAH,
AND THERE'S NO ANSWER AT HIS HOUSE EITHER.
YEAH, I GUESS
I CAN DO THE WORK.
IS HE GOING TO SHOW UP,
THOUGH?
YEAH, HEY, NO PROBLEM.
I MEAN, I DO MOST
OF THE WORK ANYWAY, RIGHT?
SO DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE, UH, GOING TO PAY ME DOUBLE TODAY?
[CLICK AND DIAL TONE]
WHAT? HELLO?
[BEEP]
THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE RUDE.
FEEL THE RUSH!
WHOO!
[FOOTSTEPS]
BOB?
[GRAVEL CRUNCHES]
[SCREAMING]
Female Reporter:
THE 19-YEAR-OLD UNIVERSITY STUDENT, ZACHARY CARTER,
FELL TO HIS DEATH
JUST BEFORE DAWN TODAY
FROM THE WINDOW CLEANING
SCAFFOLD HE WAS WORKING ON.
THE SCAFFOLD ITSELF
WAS INSPECTED AND FOUND TO BE IN WORKING ORDER.
POLICE SAY THE YOUTH WAS
WORKING ALONE, HOWEVER,
WHICH IS AGAINST
OSHA SAFETY RULES.
[EXCITED CONVERSATION]
HI, GUYS.
HI.
WHERE'S SADOWSKI?
HE'S IN HIS OFFICE
WITH THE POLICE.
WHAT ARE THE POLICE
DOING HERE?
THEY THINK HE'S
INVOLVED SOMEHOW.
ZAK WAS BLINDFOLDED.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
NO.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO KNOW THAT DOC USES A BLINDFOLD.
WE KNOW IT
WAS NONE OF US,
BECAUSE NONE OF US
COULD GET UP ON THAT ROOF ALONE.
UNLESS SOMEBODY'S
FAKING IT.
OHH!
LISTEN. DO ME A FAVOR...
[TALKING QUIETLY]
EXCUSE ME.
DETECTIVE YERXA, RIGHT?
YEAH.
CARLA ENGEL, KCEI-TV.
OH, RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU COVERED THE CARLSON CASE.
VERY GOOD.
DOING A STORY ON THIS?
UH, NOT EXACTLY.
DO YOU THINK THE DOCTOR HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT?
SADOWSKI SAYS HE WAS
AT A CONFERENCE IN ALBUQUERQUE LAST NIGHT.
I'D BE ASTONISHED
IF HE'D LIE ABOUT SOMETHING
WE COULD EASILY CHECK
WITH A PHONE CALL...
WHICH PHONE CALL
I'M ABOUT TO MAKE, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
IS IT TRUE THAT ZAK
WAS BLINDFOLDED?
YEAH.
MAYBE THE KID WAS
PRACTICING THE STUFF THE DOC TAUGHT HIM.
PRETTY CRAZY, THIS DOC,
IF YOU ASK ME.
TAKE CARE.
HEY.
I'M SORRY ABOUT ZAK.
WELL, HE KNEW THE RISK.
WE ALL DID.
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
Woman: YEAH, I'LL--
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT.
WHEN ONE FALLS IN LIFE...
THERE ARE 2 POSSIBILITIES:
EITHER ONE CANNOT GET UP,
OR ONE GETS UP AS BEST
ONE CAN AND MOVES FORWARD.
THOSE WHO CANNOT GET UP...
ARE KNOWN AS BABIES,
THE ELDERLY, COWARDS,
OR THE DEAD!
THE PEOPLE WHO GET UP
ARE KNOWN AS WARRIORS.
ANYBODY HERE WHO CONSIDERS
HIMSELF OR HERSELF AMONG THE FORMER,
PLEASE RAISE YOUR HAND.
AND WHO HERE CONSIDERS
HIMSELF OR HERSELF A WARRIOR?
LET'S SEE IF THAT'S SO.
Sadowski: COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON. ONE STEP
AT A TIME. COME ON.
DON'T THINK ABOUT
WHERE YOU ARE. THINK ABOUT MY VOICE.
COME ON.
Sadowski: REMEMBER...
ANY FEAR CAN BE OVERCOME
BY A GREATER FEAR.
IF FLAMES WERE LICKING
AT YOUR BACK, YOU'D MOVE.
IF YOUR CHILD WAS ABOUT
TO FALL OFF THAT EDGE,
YOU'D BE THERE
IN A HEARTBEAT.
ONE...
COME ON, HALLIE.
2...
YOU CAN DO IT, HALLIE.
YOU DID IT BEFORE.
UH...THAT WAS ANOTHER ROOF.
MUCH LOWER.
THERE WAS A RAIL.
LAST TIME WE HAD ZAK!
DON'T THINK ABOUT ZAK!
I CAN'T HELP IT. OHH!
3.
[HALLIE SOBS]
I'M SORRY, HALLIE.
LAST TIME YOU MADE IT
OUT TO THE PIPE.
NO, I CAN'T.
ARE YOU GOING TO LET
WHAT HAPPENED TO ZAK
RUIN EVERYTHING
THAT WE WORKED FOR?
HMM? YOU KNOW WHAT
ZAK WOULD BE DOING IF HE WERE HERE?
HE'D BE DANCING ON
THE EDGE OF THIS ROOF,
LAUGHING AT YOU!
HE'D BE ASHAMED OF YOU!
YOU MAKE A MOCKERY
OF HIS DEATH!
OR IS IT SOMETHING ELSE?
YOU THINK MAYBE I HAD
SOMETHING TO DO WITH WHAT HAPPENED TO ZAK?
DO YOU?!
I DON'T THINK YOU DID IT.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE
NOT SURE, ARE YOU?
AND THAT TINY LITTLE
SHADOW OF A DOUBT, NO MATTER HOW SMALL,
WILL BE THE RUINATION
OF EVERYTHING THAT WE'VE WORKED FOR.
BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T
TRUST ME COMPLETELY,
IT'S OVER.
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW!
Sadowski:
FEAR CAN'T HURT YOU UNLESS YOU SURRENDER TO IT.
ONCE YOU DO...
IT CAN KILL YOU.
COME ON, DOC.
YOU CAN MAKE IT.
Hallie: I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT.
IT WASN'T ME.
IT WAS LIKE I WAS
STANDING OUTSIDE MYSELF, WATCHING.
OH, I SAW YOU MOVING FORWARD,
GETTING CLOSER TO THE EDGE.
I THOUGHT YOU
WERE GOING TO JUMP.
OH, SO DID I!
OH, I WISH I COULD
HAVE SEEN US.
WHEN SADOWSKI SAID
THAT WOULD BE THE END OF THE GROUP, I JUST...
I SNAPPED, YOU KNOW?
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
I SAW MY WHOLE LIFE
FLASH BEFORE MY EYES.
I JUST KEPT THINKING
ABOUT MY KIDS.
THAT'S WHAT GOT ME
OUT ON THE ROOF.
HOW MANY KIDS YOU GOT?
UMM, 3.
PICTURES, PICTURES.
YES, YES. HERE.
THEY DON'T TALK TO
ME ANYMORE, THOUGH.
WHY NOT?
OH, WELL, THE LAST
COUPLE OF YEARS GOT SO BAD
I WOULDN'T EVEN COME UP
OUT OF THE BASEMENT.
THAT'S WHEN THEY
SENT ME TO GREENDALE.
2 YEARS, STRAIGHTJACKET,
HELMET, WHOLE 9 YARDS.
BUT...THEY KEEP ME
GOING.
IF I DIDN'T EVER THINK
I'D SEE THEM AGAIN, SOMETIME, SOMEHOW,
I'D END IT ALL TOMORROW.
DO YOU HAVE ANY KIDS?
AH, NO...NOT YET.
BUT WHEN I DO...
I HOPE THEY LOOK
LIKE HIM.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
MMM...OOH, WHAT A HUNK!
WHERE WAS THAT TAKEN?
Carla: UH, BERMUDA.
WE MET LAST AUGUST.
MY SISTER
AND I WENT THERE AFTER MY PARENTS DIED,
AND MARK WAS DOING
A PHOTO SHOOT,
AND, ACTUALLY,
RACHEL MET HIM FIRST. SHE INTRODUCED US.
WELL, YOU LOOK
GREAT TOGETHER.
♪ ...WHO WILL
TAKE OUR LAST CHANCES ♪
♪ WHO WILL UNMAKE THINGS
GONE WRONG ♪
Rachel: CRANK IT UP,
CRANK IT UP! I LOVE THIS SONG.
♪ WHO WILL
TAKE OUR LAST CHANCES... ♪
YOU CAN'T LET GO OF ME!
AAH!
HEY, IT'S ONLY ME.
WH-WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I'M SO SCARED.
I THINK RACHEL'S
STALKING ME.
WHAT?
THE SCARF.
WHAT SCARF?
THAT SHE WAS WEARING
ON THE CLIFF.
I PUT IT RIGHT HERE
THE OTHER DAY. WHERE IS IT NOW?
I...MAYBE THE HOUSEKEEPER
PUT IT AWAY.
NO, THE HOUSEKEEPER
DOESN'T COME TILL TOMORROW, MARK.
RACHEL HAS IT.
I SAW HER.
SHE WAS WEARING IT.
I SAW IT ON HER TONIGHT!
OH...
I'M CRAZY.
I'M CRAZY!
YOU'RE NOT CRAZY, OK?
YOU'RE JUST EXHAUSTED.
COME ON. I GOT AN IDEA.
I WANT YOU TO SAY
WHAT I SAY.
RACHEL, I LOVED YOU
WITH ALL MY HEART.
AND I DID
EVERYTHING THAT I COULD TO SAVE YOU.
AND I DID EVERYTHING
I COULD TO SAVE YOU.
BUT NOW I HAVE TO GO ON
WITH MY LIFE
AND PUT THIS TERRIBLE
PAIN BEHIND ME.
MAYBE THAT DOCTOR IS...
PUSHING YOU TOO FAST.
[SIGHS]
THIS GROUP IS MY ONLY HOPE
OF GETTING BETTER.
YES, BUT--
I'M NOT GOING
TO LEAVE IT, MARK.
CARLA...
[DOORBELL RINGS]
MARK, JUST LEAVE IT.
JUST LEAVE IT.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I SHOULD GET IT.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
SORRY TO DISTURB YOU,
SIR. DETECTIVE YERXA.
IS YOUR WIFE IN?
GOOD EVENING, MA'AM.
I'M AFRAID I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO ASK YOU TO COME DOWN TO THE STATION.
WHAT IS IT? WHAT'S WRONG?
WE HAVE WHAT
LOOKS LIKE A SUICIDE,
AND YOUR NAME APPEARS
AT THE SCENE.
WHAT?!
WRITTEN BY THE VICTIM...
IN HER OWN BLOOD
BEFORE SHE DIED.
WHO?
Yerxa: A WOMAN BY THE
NAME OF HALLIE BARNES.
HALLIE'S DEAD?
YES, MA'AM.
IT APPEARS SHE JUMPED
FROM THE ROOF OF HER APARTMENT BUILDING...
3 STORIES.
AMAZING SHE COULD WRITE
ANYTHING AT ALL.
SHE EVER MENTION
THINKING ABOUT SUICIDE?
SHE DID SAY
SHE MIGHT TRY IT
IF SHE COULDN'T
GET HER KIDS BACK,
BUT I'M SURE
SHE WASN'T ACTUALLY THINKING ABOUT IT.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED AT
WHAT PEOPLE THINK ABOUT.
THEN AGAIN,
IF THERE WAS FOUL PLAY,
THE LAST THING SHE DID
WAS WRITE YOUR NAME,
WHICH MIGHT BE
SIGNIFICANT.
I WAS HER FRIEND,
FOR GOD'S SAKES.
WAIT A SECOND.
IF ANYBODY COULD'VE GOTTEN
HER OUT ON THAT ROOF,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
DR. SADOWSKI.
WE'RE LOOKING INTO THAT.
SHE WAS BLINDFOLDED,
YOU KNOW.
SHE WAS?
MM-HMM. SAME AS THAT KID
ON CLARKE TOWER.
YOU KNEW HIM, TOO, RIGHT?
SEE, THIS IS THE ONE
WE TOOK OFF HIM COUPLE DAYS AGO.
AND HERE'S THE ONE FROM
HALLIE BARNES LAST NIGHT.
LOOKS PRETTY SIMILAR,
DON'T IT?
FACT IS, LAB SAYS THEY'RE
THE VERY SAME KIND OF CLOTH.
THAT ISN'T EVEN
THE MOST INTERESTING THING.
SEE?
THIS IS MINE.
AAH!
MY, MY, MY.
GET HER SOME WATER.
SHE HAVE A HISTORY
OF THAT?
YOU GOT A HISTORY
OF BEING AN IDIOT?
ARE YOU ACCUSING HER?
HUH?
'CAUSE IF YOU ARE,
JUST COME OUT AND SAY SO, OK?
I'M JUST POINTING OUT
SOMETHING INTERESTING HERE.
SHE'S A MEMBER
OF THE PRESS, NO?
I MADE NO ACCUSATIONS
THAT I RECALL.
IS SHE UNDER ARREST?
CERTAINLY NOT.
FACT IS,
THERE'S NO EVIDENCE
THAT ANYBODY WAS
ON THAT ROOF WITH HER.
NO SIGN OF STRUGGLE.
NO MARKS
ON THE LADY'S BODY,
EXCEPT FOR IMPACT
WITH CONCRETE,
I'LL PROBABLY WRITE IT UP
AS A SUICIDE.
IT'S JUST THAT HER NAME
WAS RIGHT THERE ON THE SIDEWALK.
RACHEL IS DEAD.
YOU'VE GOT TO START
ACCEPTING THAT OR--
OR WHAT?
I'LL GO CRAZY
LIKE MY MOTHER?
NO. THAT IS NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT
RACHEL IS OUT THERE?
SHE'S ALWAYS
DISTRUSTED ME.
EVER SINCE WE WERE KIDS.
AND NOW THAT I LET HER FALL,
SHE'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME.
CARLA, COME ON.
YOU GOTTA FIGHT THIS.
I HAVE LIFE,
AND RACHEL DOESN'T...
AND IT'S MY FAULT.
SHE'LL NEVER LET ME REST.
SHE'LL KILL EVERYONE I LOVE
AND THEN TEAR ME DOWN
WITH HER.
I WANT YOU
TO QUIT THE GROUP.
NO, I WILL NOT
QUIT THE GROUP!
NO. LISTEN, HOW WELL
DO YOU REALLY KNOW THESE PEOPLE?
BY NOW YOU ALL HAVE
EACH OTHER'S
PHONE NUMBERS
AND ADDRESSES.
YEAH.
THE HOUSE WAS OPEN
ALL DAY WHEN I WAS AT MY STUDIO.
SOMEBODY WHO KNEW YOU,
WHO KNEW YOUR STORY,
KNEW YOUR VULNERABILITY,
COULD EASILY
HAVE GOTTEN IN HERE TO TAKE THAT SCARF.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
HELLO.
IT'S BEN FROM THE GROUP.
HI, BEN.,@
YEAH. HE QUESTIONED US
THIS MORNING.
HE THINKS
IT'S A SUICIDE--
WHAT--WHAT DO YOU--
BEN, NO! BEN, WAIT!
[HANGS UP]
HE'S QUITTING.
YEAH.
SEE?
I THINK THAT'S
THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
MAYBE THAT'S
WHAT RACHEL WANTS.
YOU KNOW,
TO ISOLATE ME.
THAT IS CRAZY.
WRONG WORD, MARK.
WHERE YOU GOING?
I HAVE TO TALK TO HIM.
CARLA...
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
EXCUSE THE MESS.
WANT ANY WATER
OR ANYTHING?
NO.
I CAN'T STAY LONG, BEN.
LOOK, I JUST--
I WANTED TO SEE YOU
FACE-TO-FACE AND TELL YOU
YOU CAN'T
QUIT THE GROUP NOW.
NO? WATCH THIS.
BEN, PLEASE DON'T LET
HALLIE'S SUICIDE RUIN ALL WE'VE WORKED FOR.
HALLIE WASN'T A SUICIDE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
CAN'T TELL YOU.
DID YOU TELL
DETECTIVE YERXA?
I CAN'T.
WHY?
MAYBE BECAUSE I'M CRAZY.
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ME.
I'M PACKING MY THINGS.
I'M LEAVING.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE I'M GOING.
MAYBE KANSAS. I UNDERSTAND
IT'S REALLY FLAT THERE.
BEN, I'M NOT THE POLICE,
ALL RIGHT?
I'M JUST YOUR FRIEND.
YOU CAN TELL ME.
IT'S NOT THAT
I WANT TO QUIT.
I DON'T HAVE ANY CHOICE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I GOT A PHONE CALL.
FROM WHO?
I CAN'T TELL YOU.
BEN, JUST TELL ME.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE GUY
I TOLD YOU ABOUT FROM THE ARMY?
YOUR FRIEND? THE ONE
WHOSE CHUTE DIDN'T OPEN?
IT WAS HIM.
YEAH.
IVAN IRELAND HIMSELF.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
HE DIED.
HE DID.
THEN HOW
COULD HE CALL YOU?
THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M NOT HANGING AROUND
TO FIND OUT THE ANSWER.
BEN, YOUR FRIEND
IS DEAD, ALL RIGHT?
DEAD PEOPLE
DON'T MAKE PHONE CALLS.
I KNOW THAT!
MAYBE EVEN
YOU KNOW THAT,
BUT APPARENTLY
HE DOESN'T KNOW THAT 'CAUSE IT WAS HIM.
HE KNEW EVERYTHING
ABOUT THE PLANE.
HE KNEW ALL THE DETAILS,
AND HE KNEW WHAT I
WAS DOING HERE, TOO.
HE EVEN TOLD ME
ABOUT HALLIE BEFORE THE POLICE EVER CAME.
tw
WHAT...
WHAT ABOUT HALLIE?
HE TOLD ME SHE WAS DEAD.
HE KNOWS
WHO KILLED HER, TOO.
SOMEONE FROM HIS SIDE,
HE SAID.
SAID HE DOESN'T
KNOW HER NAME OR WHAT SHE LOOKS LIKE
BECAUSE SHE KEEPS
HER FACE ALL COVERED.
BUT SHE'S
A FELLOW FALLER.
HE WANTS TO MAKE ME
SUFFER FOR WHAT I DID.
JUST LIKE THE GIRL
IN THE SCARF
WANTS THE ONE THAT'S
RESPONSIBLE FOR HER FALLING TO SUFFER.
GIRL IN THE SCARF?
YEAH. HE SAID
HE KEEPS HER FACE COVERED
BECAUSE IT'S
ALL BROKEN AWAY FROM THE ROCKS.
Rachel:
YOU CAN'T LET GO OF ME!
BEN...
I CANNOT EXPLAIN
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
I JUST KNOW...
WE NEED THE GROUP.
YOU CAN'T QUIT.
WE NEED EACH OTHER.
YOU, ME, AND JOCELYN.
I JUST SPOKE TO JOCELYN.
SHE'S QUIT, TOO.
Young Rachel:
♪ CARLA, JOIN ME ♪
♪ CARLA ♪
SO, HOW DID YOU FIND ME?
I WENT TO YOUR HOUSE.
SOMEONE HELD UP A NOTE.
THAT WAS MY MOM.
SHE HASN'T TALKED IN 5 YEARS.
SHE'S PHOBIC
ABOUT EVERYTHING, INCLUDING PEOPLE.
LOOK, JOCELYN,
WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT--
LOOK, I DON'T BELIEVE
IN GHOSTS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO ZAK,
BUT HALLIE
KILLED HERSELF.
AND I KNOW WHY.
SAME REASON I TRIED
LAST YEAR.
I JUMPED OUT OF
A THIRD STORY WINDOW.
SPENT 8 MONTHS
IN THE HOSPITAL.
RIGHT NOW I FEEL LIKE
I COULD DO IT AGAIN.
LOOK, JOCELYN, I DON'T SEE
HOW HALLIE COULD'VE DONE THAT.
WELL, WHEN YOU'RE
DESPERATE, YOU DO IT.
IT GOT SO BAD
THAT I'D GO TO BED AND PRAY, "PLEASE, GOD,
DON'T LET ME WAKE UP
IN THE MORNING."
I MEAN, WHAT WAS I
LIVING FOR?
TO KEEP MY MOTHER
OUT OF AN INSTITUTION?
TO KEEP MYSELF OUT?
YOU'RE GETTING BETTER,
RIGHT?
AND HALLIE WAS
GETTING BETTER, TOO.
WELL, IF YOU STOP NOW,
YOU'RE JUST
GONNA BE RIGHT BACK WHERE YOU STARTED.
I DON'T KNOW!
WHAT I DO KNOW IS
THAT I DON'T WANT TO END UP LIKE MY MOTHER.
AND I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
WE CAN BEAT THIS THING.
I'M SCARED, CARLA.
I'M SCARED, TOO, JOCELYN!
THIS IS NO WAY TO LIVE.
WE CANNOT QUIT NOW.
JOCELYN,
WE COULD DO THIS.
DEAL?
DEAL.
I APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BUT I'VE
MADE UP MY MIND.
WHY? BECAUSE
THERE'S ONLY 2 OF US?
NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
BUT I CAN'T PUT YOU OR
MY REPUTATION AT RISK
WHILE SOMEBODY'S TRYING
TO SABOTAGE MY WORK.
WHO WOULD HATE YOU
THAT MUCH?
I DON'T KNOW.
COULD BE A COLLEAGUE
WHO WANTS TO SEE ME FAIL.
COULD BE
A FORMER PATIENT.
BUT YOU'RE PUTTING US
AT RISK BY QUITTING.
I WOULD BE DEAD NOW
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU.
SO WOULD I.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HALLIE IS DEAD BECAUSE OF ME.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO ZAK,
ALSO BECAUSE
OF ME.
WHAT ABOUT
THE PHONE CALL TO BEN?
WELL, I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY CALLED BEN.
I THINK THAT WAS
JUST AN EXCUSE TO QUIT THE GROUP
OR TO GET OUT OF TOWN
BEFORE THE POLICE
START ASKING TOO MANY QUESTIONS.
I SAW BEN.
HE WAS TERRIFIED.
MM-HMM. WELL, BEN'S GOOD
AT BEING AFRAID.
HE ALSO HATED ZAK.
NOTHING'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO ME ANYMORE.
YOU TOLD US IF WE
FACED OUR WORST TERROR, WE WOULD BE CURED.
IT WAS JUST
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SOMEBODY
ELSE GETS HURT.
THEN LET'S NOT
WASTE ANY TIME.
LET'S GO FOR BROKE.
NO HALF-MEASURES.
YOU'RE HARDLY READY
FOR THAT.
I'M TELLING YOU,
WE ARE.
I'LL GO FIRST.
IT'D BE YOUR
WORST NIGHTMARE.
FEAR CAN'T HURT ME, RIGHT?
Dr. Sadowski:
YOU READY IN THE BOAT?
WE'RE ALL SET.
WE'RE READY AND WAITING.
STEP OUT
ON THAT PLATFORM.
[PANTING]
TAKE A STEP.
DO IT.
ALL RIGHT,
KEEP GOING.
TAKE A STEP.
AND ANOTHER.
JOCELYN, MAKE ME PROUD.
YOU CAN DO IT.
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT.
KEEP GOING.
A LITTLE FARTHER.
YOU'RE THERE.
JUST PUSH ME!
NO!
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO DO IT, JOCELYN.
DO WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
IT'S WORKING.
[STATIC]
Rachel: CARLA!
[LAUGHING]
CARLA!
I'M NOT AFRAID ANYMORE.
Rachel: CARLA!
JOCELYN!
JOCELYN,
DON'T DO IT!
HA HA HA HA!
I'M NOT AFRAID ANYMORE!
JOCELYN,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
DO IT.
DON'T JUMP!
AH! I FEEL LIKE
I CAN DO ANYTHING!
DO IT, DO IT, DO IT.
DON'T DO IT!
DON'T JUMP!
AH!
AAH!
WHOO-HOO! YEAH!
WHOO!
Jocelyn: OH, I DID IT!
HA HA HA HA!
OH, YES! YES!
YOU DID IT, JOCELYN!
OH, LOOK AT ME, GIRL!
WHOO! AH HA HA HA!
IS THERE ANYWHERE ELSE
I CAN FIND INFORMATION ON THIS GUY?
WELL, I SUPPOSE IF YOU
HAD A TISSUE SAMPLE,
YOU COULD DO
A DNA TEST.
OTHERWISE, AT THIS POINT,
I WOULD WAGER THAT
YOU KNOW MORE ABOUT HIM THAN HIS MOTHER DOES.
WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING.
Carla: HOW DO YOU FEEL?
Jocelyn: OHH!
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
IT WAS SO AWESOME.
JUST WAIT AND SEE.
HA HA HA!
OK. I'LL GET THE CREDIT CARD,
YOU CHOOSE THE RESTAURANT.
AND DON'T SCRIMP.
I'M SORRY YOU HAVE
TO WAIT OUT HERE.
I UNDERSTAND.
MAYBE I'LL GET HER
TO COME TO THE WINDOW AND WAVE.
OK.
[RACHEL GIGGLING]
[GIGGLING]
AAH!
SHE FELL.
CARLA!
WHAT HAPPENED?
MY MOTHER.
SHE'S...
WHAT?
SHE FELL
IN THE BATHROOM.
SHE'S DEAD.
OH, I SHOULDN'T HAVE
LEFT HER ALONE!
IT HAD TO HAVE
BEEN AN ACCIDENT.
SHE WAS SO HAPPY FOR ME.
SHE KNEW WHAT
I WAS GONNA DO TODAY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I SAW
WHEN I FIRST WALKED INTO THE HOUSE?
IT WAS
RIGHT ON THE TABLE ON THE DINING ROOM.
Carla: THE ROSES
ARE BEAUTIFUL.
THEY ALWAYS WERE
HER FAVORITE FLOWER.
ALL SHE WROTE
ON THE CARD WAS...
"CONGRATULATIONS."
[DOOR CLOSES]
CARLA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M CRAZY.
NO. I JUST ASKED YOU
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE NEVER IDENTIFIED
THE BODY PROPERLY.
HER FACE WAS
SO BADLY SMASHED,
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF IT WAS HER OR NOT.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT TO KNOW
IF THIS IS HER OR NOT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GONNA FIND IN THERE?
I THOUGHT MAYBE I COULD
FIND HER GOLD FILLINGS,
BUT THEN I REALIZED
THAT THOSE PEOPLE AT THE CREMATORIUM,
THEY WOULD'VE STOLE THAT.
BUT THEN I REALIZED
THEY WOULD MISS THE PIN IN HER WRIST
THAT THE DOCTOR PUT IN
WHEN SHE BROKE IT.
IT'S NOT HERE.
SO?
THE TITANIUM,
IT WOULDN'T MELT.
OH, BUT EVEN IF IT WOULD,
THEY WOULDN'T WANT IT.
JUST WHAT IF
THIS ISN'T HER?
ALL RIGHT, WOULD YOU
LISTEN TO YOURSELF?
I'M TRYING TO
FIGURE THIS OUT, MARK.
I'M SEEING HER!
I'M HEARING HER!
WHY?
I MEAN, MAYBE...
MAYBE IF THIS ISN'T HER,
MAYBE SHE'S ALIVE.
NO!
SHE'S DEAD!
THEY HAVE THOUGHT
OF EVERYTHING.
MAYBE IT'S SADOWSKI.
MAYBE IT'S BEN.
I'VE EVEN THOUGHT
IT COULD BE YOU.
ANYTHING IS EASIER THAN
BELIEVING IT'S RACHEL.
HOW ELSE AM I GONNA
EXPLAIN ALL THIS?
YOU WANT AN EXPLANATION?
LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK AT IT.
YOUR DR. SADOWSKI IS NOT
WHO HE SAYS HE IS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I FOUND OUT WHO HE WAS
BEFORE HE BECAME A DOCTOR.
SEE, LOOK, HE USED TO BE
A MOUNTAINEERING GUY.
AND ON HIS LAST TRIP,
HE TOOK A BUNCH OF PEOPLE UP TO MOUNT RAINIER,
AND NONE OF THEM CAME BACK.
EXCEPT FOR SADOWSKI.
AND THE REST OF THEM,
THEY FELL TO THEIR DEATHS
OFF A 3,500-FOOT CLIFF.
THIS SOUNDS
LIKE AN ACCIDENT--
MAYBE, OK?
BUT THE BEAUTY OF BEING
THE ONLY SURVIVOR
IS THAT YOU GET TO SAY
WHAT HAPPENED.
I THINK
THIS IS A SICK GUY
WHO NEEDS TO TAKE PEOPLE
UP TO HIGH PLACES
AND WATCH THEM SUFFER
AND POSSIBLY DIE.
THAT'S WHY HE NEEDS
DESPERATE PEOPLE.
PEOPLE WHO WILL DO
WHATEVER HE SAYS.
BUT HE CURED ZAK
AND JOCELYN.
THEN LOOK WHAT HE DID.
OK, MAYBE HE THINKS
THAT HE CURED ZAK.
MArYBE HE THINKS
HE'S HELPING JOCELYN.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE PHONE CALL?
HUH? SADOWSKI COULDN'T HAVE
KNOWN ALL THAT STUFF
THAT BEN SAID
THE GUY KNEW.
CARLA, YOU CAN EASILY
FIND THAT STUFF IN THE LIBRARY
OR IN MILITARY RECORDS.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND
IN JUST A COUPLE HOURS.
NO!
CARLA, OPEN YOUR EYES.
YOU WERE SO DESPERATE
TO BELIEVE THAT LUNATIC,
YOU CAN'T SEE WHAT'S
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOUR FACE.
COME HERE.
JUST COME HERE.
SHH.
NOW, LISTEN TO ME.
MAYBE HE'S DANGEROUS,
MAYBE HE'S NOT,
BUT HE CAN'T BE
THE ONLY DOCTOR THAT CAN HELP YOU, OK?
WE WILL FIND
SOMEBODY ELSE.
WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
MOVE TO ANOTHER CITY,
I DON'T CARE, CARLA.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE SAFE.
NOW, I MADE SOME COPIES
OF THESE DOCUMENTS FOR THAT DETECTIVE.
BUT I WANT YOU TO
PROMISE ME SOMETHING.
PROMISE ME THAT YOU
WILL NOT GO SEE SADOWSKI IN THE MORNING, OK?
I PROMISE.
I LOVE YOU, CARLA.
AND I'M NOT GONNA
LOSE YOU.
[RACHEL'S FLUTE MUSIC]
[FLUTE]
Rachel: CARLA...
HA HA HA HA!
Rachel: CARLA!
NO.
HA HA HA!
Rachel: CARLA!
NO.
NO!
Rachel: HEE HEE HEE HEE!
YOU CAN'T LET GO OF ME!
CARLA!
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO.
HELLO. IS CARLA THERE?
WHO IS THIS?
UH, THIS IS DR. SADOWSKI.
MAY I SPEAK TO YOUR WIFE,
PLEASE?
SHE'S NOT EVEN HERE,
THANKS TO YOU.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING WITH HER?
WELL, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE SHE IS?
NO, I DON'T.
WHERE WAS SHE
SUPPOSED TO BE, ACCORDING TO YOU?
WE HAVE AN APPOINTMENT.
WHAT, AT THE CLINIC?
NO. AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET HER
ON THE ROAD
TO LOOKOUT MOUNTAIN.
IF SHE CALLS IN WILL YOU
TELL HER THAT, PLEASE?
I'M GONNA BACK UP THERE
AND WAIT FOR HER.
NO!
DON'T GO NEAR HER,
YOU SON OF A BITCH,
OR I SWEAR TO GOD,
I WILL KILL YOU.
Mark: YOU'RE GETTING
A LITTLE CLOSE TO THE EDGE,
SO COME OVER HERE AND
SIT ON THE RAILING.
Rachel: I AM NOT FALLING!
I'M FINE!
Echo: I'M FINE!
I'M FINE! I'M FINE!
OH, I FEEL
LIKE I'M FLYING!
AAH!
RACHEL!
PLEASE DON'T LET ME FALL.
RACHEL, I'VE GOT YOU.
AAH!
CARLA, COME AWAY
FROM THE EDGE.
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER.
CARLA,
YOU'VE ALREADY DONE IT.
YOU'RE CLOSE ENOUGH.
YOU'VE WON.
NO, THERE'S
NO WINNING FOR ME.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
COME WITH ME
FOR ALL THE PEOPLE
YOU FAILED ON THE MOUNTAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, CARLA?
MOUNT RAINIER.
LOOK, WE WERE ON A RIDGE
300 FEET FROM THE SUMMIT.
WE WERE FOLLOWING
AN ESTABLISHED ROUTE.
THERE'S A BIG CORNICE
OF SNOW AND ICE.
IT GAVE ALL SIGNS
OF BEING STABLE.
I WENT FIRST.
I CHECKED FOR CRACKS.
HOW'D YOU DO IT, THEN?
D'YOU CUT THE ROPE?
WHAT?
PUSH 'EM?
NO! IT WAS NOTHING
LIKE THAT AT ALL!
THEN HOW DID THEY DIE?
WHEN I STARTED BACK,
THE ICE PACK
STARTED TO FAIL.
THE SECTION
THEY WERE STANDING ON BROKE LOOSE.
I LOOKED DOWN.
IT HAPPENED SLOWLY.
I THINK I COULD'VE
SAVED THEM.
I KNOW I COULD HAVE.
I HAVE THE TRAINING, BUT...
BUT WHEN I LOOKED DOWN,
I COULDN'T MOVE.
I COULDN'T EVEN BREATHE.
I KNOW.
I KNOW WHAT THAT KIND
OF FEAR FEELS LIKE.
WERE THEY YOUR FRIENDS?
THEY WERE CLIENTS.
ALL EXCEPT FOR ONE.
WE WERE ENGAGED
TO BE MARRIED A MONTH LATER.
HOW DID YOU DO IT?
HOW DID YOU
GET OVER IT,
THE FEAR, THE GUILT?
I DIDN'T.
WHEN I'M ALONE
IN A HIGH PLACE,
I'M AS DIZZY AND
FRIGHTENED AS YOU ARE.
BUT WHEN I'M TEACHING
OTHER PEOPLE NOT TO BE AFRAID,
I'M NOT AFRAID.
IT'S OK.
COME ON.
MARK!
I TOLD YOU TO STAY AWAY FROM MY WIFE.
MARK, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
WAIT, WAIT.
WAIT A SECOND.
I THINK THERE'S BEEN
A MISUNDERSTANDING HERE.
Carla: STOP IT, ALL RIGHT?!
MARK, JUST LISTEN TO ME!
HEY, BACK UP NOW.
HOW DOES IT FEEL, DOCTOR,
TO BE ON THE BRINK YOURSELF,
THIS TIME, HUH?
Carla: MARK, STOP IT!
STOP IT. LOOK, YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO CALM--
STOP IT, ALL RIGHT?
CARLA, STAY BACK.
MARK! MARK!
MARK, STOP IT!
MARK!
HOLD ON, OK? HOLD ON!
MARK, THERE'S A ROPE
IN THE VAN. GET IT.
UH...
I DON'T THINK SO.
LOOK, WHAT HAPPENED
ON MOUNT RAINIER WAS AN ACCIDENT.
ALL RIGHT?
JUST GET THE ROPE!
IT'LL BE A MINUTE.
JUST HOLD ON.
NONE OF THAT MATTERS,
CARLA.
YOU KNOW...
YOU COULD'VE MADE THIS
A WHOLE LOT EASIER...
IF YOU'D HAVE JUST
DONE WHAT I SAID IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
I TOLD YOU TO SIT
ON THE RAILING.
I RIGGED IT TO BREAK
FOR YOU, NOT RACHEL.
YOU KILLED RACHEL.
NO.
YOU DID.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DIDN'T
SIT ON THE RAILING
LIKE I TOLD YOU TO!
YOU WANTED ME TO FALL?
WHY?
AAH!
WHEN I MET YOU,
I DIDN'T HAVE 2 NICKELS
TO RUB TOGETHER.
YOU HAD YOUR PARENTS' MONEY
AND THAT BIG OLD HOUSE.
AND I COULD'VE HAD
ALL THAT.
EVEN RACHEL IF I WANTED.
SHE WAS SO MUCH MORE
CONTROLLABLE.
YOU...
YOU'RE STUBBORN.
YOU MAKE EVERYTHING
A MESS.
THAT'S WHY WHEN
THE DOCTOR CAME ALONG,
I FIGURED, "HEY,
HOW MUCH MORE PERFECT COULD THIS BE?"
A GUY WHO LIKES TO PUT
PEOPLE ON CLIFFS
AND SEE
IF THEY'LL JUMP?
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
FROM THEN ON,
I HAVE TO SAY IT WAS
ACTUALLY KIND OF FUN.
I KNEW YOU WERE TERRIFIED
OF COMING DOWN WITH YOUR MOTHER'S MENTAL ILLNESS,
SO I JUST
HELPED YOU ALONG A LITTLE BIT
BY DOSING YOU
FROM TIME TO TIME
WITH THE WORST
HALLUCINOGENIC I COULD FIND.
THEN ALL I HAD TO DO WAS
SIT BACK AND WATCH YOU FREAK OUT!
ADD A BIT OF SUGGESTION...
A LITTLE INCENSE HERE...
MOVE THE SCARF THERE.
THE REST OF IT
WAS YOUR IMAGINATION.
OH.
THEN THERE WAS
THAT DAMN GROUP...
AND ALL THEIR SUPPORT.
THEY HAD TO GO.
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
YOU SHOULD'VE PICKED
AN AMATEUR.
AAH!
CARLA!
Dr. Sadowski: HANG ON!
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
GIVE ME YOUR HAND,
CARLA.
THE ROOT WON'T HOLD!
IT'S GONNA BREAK!
LET HIM GO!
CARLA, GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
MARK!
MARK, PULL ME UP!
AAH!
TAKE MY HAND.
COME ON, CARLA.
DO IT!
AAH!
HANG ON!
CLIMB THE ROPE, CARLA.
CLIMB IT.
COME ON, CLIMB IT!
CARLA, YOU CLIMB
THAT ROPE NOW!
YOU'RE FINE.
YOU'RE FINE, CARLA.
IT'S OK.
BYE, RACHEL.
[RACHEL'S FLUTE]
Rachel: CARLA...