You know what they're saying?
That you're the ringleader.
That it was all your idea.
You give us who we really want,
we'll get you into a new school...
wipe your record clean.
You're just 15 years old.
He took advantage of your youth.
- Your ignorance.
- Your innocence.
You've done a lot of growing up,
haven't you?
And now you know the difference
between right and wrong.
You do know the difference,
don't you?
Right?
Wrong?
- Don't you?
- Wrong? Right?
Cheaters - AKA: Trapaceiros
"What matter here
if I be still the same...
and what I should be
all but less than he...
whom thunder hath made greater.
Here at least we shall be free.
The Almighty hath not built here...
for His envy will not
drive us hence.
Here we may reign secure
and in my choice...
to reign is worth ambition,
though in Hell.
Better to reign in Hell
than serve in Heaven."
Thank you, Asha.
So, what do we think Satan meant
when he said...
"Better to reign in Hell
than serve in Heaven"?
Anything?
Any ideas? Anybody?
Okay. What if you had a choice?
What if you could live
in a mansion in Highland Park...
but you have to be the chauffeur...
or you can live in a shelter
on lower Wacker Drive...
but you would be the king
of that shelter, which would you choose?
If I'm the chauffeur,
what kind of car I drive?
- You ain't even got a license, fool.
- Who the hell you callin' fool, fool?
Who you callin' fool?
You want some?
- Slap that blonde weave off your head.
- Okay. Thank you.
Pride, that's what it's all about.
Lucifer was too proud to play runner-up
to someone he felt superior to...
so he set up his own shop.
And what did Dante say was written
on the gates of Lucifer's shop?
"Abandon all hope
ye who enter here."
That's what it should say
on the door to this school.
"And they outcast from God are here
condemned to waste eternal days..."
"In woe and pain."
Doesn't sound very pleasant,
does it?
What's the alternative?
Living like a drone?
Why do Adam and Eve get in trouble
in the first place?
- They ate the apple, baby.
- They ate from the tree of knowledge.
They just wanted knowledge.
- God was testing them.
- But He didn't tell them why.
He was just, "I'm in charge here.
Do what I say."
And He said, "You can eat from any tree
in the garden, just not from this one."
So, of course, what are they gonna do?
- It's human nature.
- Already been through that, girl.
But, hey, that's just my opinion.
Okay, Michael, are you gonna handle
the bowling club again?
Don't let the kids drop their balls
in the gutter.
Sorry. Sorry about that.
All right, good.
Janie?
- How about the prom committee?
- Yes.
Let's try to get started at least
a week before the prom this year.
I'll try.
Wonderful.
Now, the position...
that strikes terror
in all our hearts...
brings out the masochist
in the best of us...
coach of the academic
decathlon team... Jerry.
What do you say?
Give it another shot?
Couldn't do worse
than he did last time.
That's the nice thing
about finishing last.
Third time's the charm.
Sorry I'm late.
What, is the meeting over?
- Thanks for helping me out.
- Are you kidding? You're helping me out.
You're the only one who thinks we can
compete in anything besides basketball.
Most teachers aren't like you.
They don't like to challenge us.
But you actually think we're capable
of some intelligent thinking.
Jolie, I am continually amazed by the
things that spring out of your mouth.
I'll show you where the smart kids are,
but I can't guarantee they'll show up.
So $40 worth of burritos
will guarantee you an audience.
See that guy over there?
That's Dominik Wesolowski.
SATs 1410. 4.0 GPA.
They announced
the honor roll yesterday...
and he made the mistake
of being on it.
Kurgan, Paul.
SATs 1120. 3.8 GPA.
I tried to get him on the team last year
but he was busy running for president.
Actually deluded enough
to think he can make a difference.
Agnieska Maryniarczyk.
SATs 370, 3.7 GPA.
She's a virgin.
- Is that relevant?
- If you're her, it is.
Darius Bettus.
1520 on his SATs. 3.9 GPA.
If he weren't so good looking,
I'd have to kill him.
Flickas, Irwin. 3.0 GPA.
Has not taken his SATs yet.
Personally, I can't stand him, but he
does have a pretty vivid imagination.
Kur, Matt.
2.9 GPA. SATs 1040.
But look how cute he is.
We're putting a team together,
not a dating pool.
Could be both.
Hello, and welcome to
the United States Academic Decathlon...
the nation's foremost
scholastic competition...
where you can match your intellect
with students from top high schools...
across America.
The academic decathlon brings a sense
of pride and accomplishment...
to the high school environment...
placing academic achievement
at the forefront of the school...
and the community at large.
High school students
from all across the country...
compete in this extraordinary event...
pushing themselves to new heights.
There are ten exciting areas
in which the students compete...
consisting of written tests
in six core subjects...
as well as an oral speech,
an interview...
and essay and Super Quiz.
And the winning team
from each state...
will compete for the pride,
prestige and scholarship money...
that comes with being
national champion.
That winning team gets to go to
the White House and meet the president.
The United States
Academic Decathlon...
building the skills that work
in corporate America.
Now...
Guys, take it outside.
You wanna know
why you should do this?
So we can embarrass ourselves
in front of the entire city.
Because no one thinks you can.
'Cause you don't think you can.
- Sir, we know we can't.
- Speak for yourself.
I just came here
for the free food.
It's pretty damn funny, isn't it?
The idea of you guys competing
against kids that are really smart.
They're not just smart kids.
Kids from Whitney Young.
Why are you so insecure? We're just
as smart as them. We could beat them.
Don't kid yourself.
It won't be easy.
Whitney Young, they live
and breathe the decathlon.
- They've won the state championship...
- Nine years in a row.
Nice years in a row.
They recruit for it.
They have unlimited budgets,
air conditioning...
parents who care,
toilets that work.
That's right.
Even a coach
who knows what he's doing.
Which is why when we beat them
it'll be so satisfying.
Do you wanna get into Harvard?
You'll get into Harvard.
On a full scholarship.
You'll be in the newspaper,
on television.
- You're gonna make us famous?
- No, we're gonna make him famous.
I just want you to know
what it feels like to win.
Because once you've had that feeling,
you'll never let it go.
But if we're gonna win
this thing...
here's what I'm gonna need
from you.
Everything.
Spare time?
You aren't gonna have any.
I will need you two hours before
school, five hours after school...
and all day on weekends
and holidays.
You have to be totally committed
and willing to do...
whatever it takes to win.
But understand this.
I will never abandon you.
And I will never hang you
out to dry.
And the knowledge that
I'm prepared to give you...
it will change your life forever.
What do you guys think?
- I think he's a full-on freak.
- I heard he still lives with his mom.
I heard he dates Mr. Silver.
- He's not gay.
- How would you know?
Dr. Plecki's really cool.
Okay?
When we were reading Slaughterhouse
Five, he took us all to meet Vonnegut...
who was doing this reading
and signed all of our books.
And these kids that would rather trip
on a book did an amazing thing.
They actually read the book.
He just wants to help us out.
He's doing this because he thinks we can
compete at something and we're smart.
And we are smart. We just need
an opportunity to prove ourself.
Dr. Plecki's amazing.
He's a really good teacher.
What's he doing here?
I volunteered to coach
the academic decathlon team.
Again?
We've got a really good group
of kids this year.
I think we may have a shot.
It just takes so much time.
I spoke with your brother today. He got
a promotion at the publishing house.
He's now a regional sales manager...
responsible for hiring 20 people.
I have a job, Mother.
I know you do.
How are we supposed to get any studying
done if you show up at 6:18?
A Shakespearean sonnet
is always written in?
I'll take lambic Pentameter
for 500.
- What activates NMDA receptors?
- Glutamate.
If Darius is shooting
four out of seven...
what are the chances of him
making this next shot?
Fifty-seven percent.
What did Ivan discover was the key
to survival in the GULAG?
- Routine. It was the daily routine...
- Booze.
No. Conditioning.
He made himself believe
that one piece of bread was good.
So that when he got two,
he felt great.
What kind of an idiot feels great
with two pieces of bread?
Hear how the song repeated the melody
from the beginning? What's that called?
- A da capo.
- Right.
The year 1820 was said to be
the beginning of what musical era?
Romantic Era.
The distinctive characteristic
of the work of Leopold is?
Naturalistic.
Eukaryotes differ from
prokaryotes because?
Prokaryotes have no nucleus.
PET measures concentrations of what?
Concentrations of radioactive
isotopes of living tissue.
- What are neurons composed of?
- Cell body, exon and dendrites.
Of ancient empires,
the largest was?
I don't know.
Daoism was founded by?
The distinctive characteristic
of the work of Leopold is?
No smoking.
Good morning, decathletes. Welcome to...
Here's another question for you.
What do we do to the competition?
- Sweep 'em out of the way!
- That's right.
You are prepared for this.
We are the best team here...
and the only way we won't win
is if we defeat ourselves.
Hands in.
We've got the brains, the hunger.
What are we gonna do?
Win!
Go Whitney! Go Whitney!
Don't worry about them.
We got 'em right where we want 'em.
Overconfident and
underestimating your abilities.
Our abilities? We're not even a factor
in their equation.
You can't control
what they think.
What you can do is remember
everything we've drilled.
Okay? Watch out for lead distracters.
If an answer seems too obvious,
it probably means it's the wrong answer.
Don't second-guess yourselves.
Your first answer is always
your best answer.
- If you draw a blank, you choose...
- "C."
Consistently.
Okay, I taught you discipline.
Use it. And anticipate.
Never panic. Stay focused.
Now is your chance to show everyone else
how smart I already know you are.
Do not open your test booklets
until instructed to do so.
You will have 30 minutes to complete
each section of the exam.
At the conclusion of the written portion
of the exam...
you will proceed to the speech
and interview rooms.
Please remember which group
you have been assigned to.
While you are taking
the written test...
keep all books and supplies
under your desk at all times.
Here's 20.
That's what we need,
a little adventurous spirit here.
You never know with these kids.
New kids every year.
You can't count on anything.
Jerry, you wanna get in on this?
Twenty dollars pays...
800 for Steinmetz to win.
No guts, no glory.
"And if the employer can be part
of the overall solution...
then we will not feel...
as much...
'despiring'...
despairing."
Okay, students. It's time for
the Super Quiz. Question number one.
Alteration of the amino acids
of Thermolicyn could...
A: Reduce PKU likelihood...
B: Reduce taste likelihood...
C: Reduce hypertension likelihood...
D: Reduce Down's Syndrome likelihood
and E: None of the above.
The correct answer is "C."
Reduce hypertension likelihood.
The correct answer is "E."
The correct answer is "D."
The correct answer is "A."
- Are we having fun today?
- Yeah.
I had a lot of fun too.
And did we learn anything?
- Yeah!
- All right!
No big problems?
- None at all. I think it went fantastic.
- Me too.
- So how'd you do?
- Okay, I guess.
That was so easy.
Guys, Alexander Hamilton
was the first chief justice, right?
No, John Jay.
Guys, listen.
I don't care what happens.
I don't care what the final tally is.
I couldn't be more proud of you.
In Language and Literature,
the bronze medal...
from Whitney Young,
Sandy Lee.
Well done, Sandy!
The silver medal,
from Whitney Young, Josh Haden.
And the gold medal...
from Whitney Young,
Sarah White.
The bronze medal,
from Whitney Young...
The silver medal,
And the gold medal,
from Whitney Young...
And now,
the five top scoring teams...
who will advance to the Illinois State
Academic Decathlon Finals.
In first place...
for the tenth year in a row,
Whitney Young High School.
Whitney Young is number one!
What an accomplishment.
Ten years in a row.
- The winners!
- In second place...
Kenwood Academy.
In third place,
Bogen High School.
In fourth place,
Lane Technical.
And in fifth place,
Steinmetz High School.
Jerry, here.
I can't take your money.
You didn't know
what you were up against.
See you at State.
It's not over.
I know it isn't.
Get back at it on Monday.
Study even harder.
Maybe take another trip
to the art institute on Thursday.
I just wish we could've
done better for you.
Please, don't be silly.
You did wonderfully.
Thanks.
Sure.
Fuckin' chair.
Irwin, can I speak with you
for a second?
Yeah. Cool.
What's up?
I'm going to switch you
and Dominik for the State.
You had the lowest scores
at the regional competition...
so he's gonna compete at State
and you take the alternate position.
That's not fair. No one told me you
couldn't choose more than one answer.
It's called multiple choice.
We'll switch back
if we go to Nationals.
He can barely speak English.
Give me another chance.
- He's your teammate.
- Come on, Plecki.
- Where are you going?
- Work.
- See? He's gotta leave.
- Sit down.
Mr. Butera says he will replace me
if I take any more time off.
- I'll talk to him again.
- That's all right. I should go.
- Would it help if I went with you?
- It won't help.
- I have to be at work.
- Agna, where are you going?
I need to get home
to take care of my sister.
My mother's working late.
I don't want her to be alone.
Nobody else can help?
We have no money
to afford baby-sitter.
Guys, come on.
This is crunch time.
Nothing is supposed to get in the way
of your studying.
If you have to
stay here all night, then...
No one wants to take care of her,
and she's...
Wait a second. Dr. Plecki, I don't know
what world you're living in...
but we finished 12,000 points
behind Young.
- They killed us.
- That's what I'm talking about.
We simply have to work harder.
Whitney Young is working...
so we'll work twice as hard
and beat them.
I appreciate your optimism,
but the fact of this is...
no matter how hard we study
and work for this...
Young is gonna take that thing
for the tenth year in a row.
So if Dominik wants
to keep his job...
and Agnieska wants to make sure
her sister gets fed tonight...
instead of studying...
cytoplasmic binding proteins
all day, that's...
Look, I love the dream
that you gave us.
No, I really do.
But there's a certain point...
where you have to just wake up
and realize...
you know,
it's just a fuckin' dream.
It's just a dream.
- We can't use the copy machine.
- Why not?
Mrs. Fadely says we can't.
You know what they say about Elizabeth.
She has a lot of growing up to do.
Excuse me.
I'll call you back.
- Where do you think you're going?
- To make copies.
- For the decathlon?
- For the decathlon, that's right.
Extracurricular activities
are only budgeted $50 a semester.
- You saying I can't use the machine?
- You exceeded your budget.
- He can make all the copies he wants?
- Athletic department has its own budget.
What is it, a penny a page?
Here.
I hate to take a dime away from
the school board's $4 billion budget...
and do something really outrageous
like spend it on kids.
- You can't make any more copies.
- Go upstairs and tell those kids...
if they wanna be in a basketball
tournament, we'll throw money at 'em...
but if they wanna be in an academic
tournament, they are on their own.
- Don't be gettin' smart with me!
- You go tell them.
- Don't come in and get smart with me.
- You go up!
Jerry, what's your record?
My record?
You 0-4, 0-6?
We're 11-0.
Congratu-fuckin'-lations.
That's why I get to use
the machine.
I get it. So, if we don't win,
why even bother trying to compete?
That's not what I'm saying.
If you can't win, you should think twice
about entering the competition.
That you, Jerry?
Yes, Mother, it's me.
Did you remember
the furnace filters?
They're in the car.
That was a tight game we played.
You gonna be around tomorrow?
Definitely.
Yo, yo, Matt.
See ya later, man.
What's up?
Listen. You're on that team, right,
the one that takes tests and shit?
The academic decathlon.
Listen. If I show you something,
will you give me 20 bucks?
Dad, I gotta take a pee.
- What the hell? I been here ten minutes.
- Sorry, man.
Down here.
Tests, tests, tests.
Shit, they were right here
yesterday.
Damn it.
You're wasting my time.
They're here somewhere.
I know they are.
Here you go.
Beautiful.
Let's get out of here.
Here you go.
What the fuck, man?
What's up? I got that copy
of Fantastic Fable you wanted.
The one where Starhawk
beats up Pogo. What's that?
Nothin'.
Can't be nothin'.
Let me see it.
- It's nothin', dude.
- Just let me see it.
- Chill out.
Holy shit!
Is this the real thing?
Hello!
What?
Is Dr. Plecki around?
Sure. Come in.
What's going on?
Let's go outside.
- I got the test.
- The what?
I got the test.
Check it out.
Oh, my God!
Where did you get these?
I didn't get 'em. Matt got 'em,
but he wasn't gonna share 'em.
- Look at this. It's the real deal.
- I know.
Are the rest of the children
coming over to study?
Not today.
What's the matter?
We should get 'em over here right now.
This is the real deal.
- I don't believe this.
- What's the matter with you? Come on.
I'm a teacher.
I couldn't.
I'm a teacher. I'm supposed
to spout the same platitudes...
you've heard
a million times before.
"Cheaters don't prosper."
"It's not whether you win or lose...
it's how you play the game."
This may not be approved curriculum,
but guess what.
Winning does matter.
Cheaters do prosper.
I'm sure your father came to this
country thinking like mine did...
that a democracy
was a meritocracy.
No one worked harder
than my dad.
He never understood why after giving
24 years of his life to his job...
he could get laid off simply so they
could not have to pay his medical bills.
Look, I'm a teacher.
Listen up.
We all know the state competition
is tomorrow.
An opportunity...
has presented itself which...
I would be remiss in not bringing
to your attention.
Paul, wake up!
Now, there are those who don't think
you're mature enough...
to make a decision based on the choice
I'm about to offer up.
- I don't think there's a more...
- What is it?
- I got the tests.
- You got the what?
- I got the tests for the state finals.
- I'm the one who got the tests.
- You were gonna keep 'em for yourself.
- Shut up, faggot!
Shut up.
Let me see.
Sit down. Sit down!
Just be cool.
- No one sees these...
- What?
Unless we are all comfortable
seeing them.
- We do this together or not at all.
- I'm so comfortable with seeing them.
Can you see the look on Young's face
when we win? They're gonna shit.
- You're okay with this?
- I got the damn things, didn't I?
I wouldn't mind taking a look
at them to...
see how hard they are.
If we can get the tests,
I'm sure Whitney Young has them too.
Of course they do. Doesn't the decathlon
have their offices at Whitney Young?
I mean, you do the math.
So, two wrongs make a right?
Two wrongs make it even.
Guys, won't we get caught?
Only if you talk,
and then we'd have you killed.
Okay.
Isn't cheating wrong?
Get down off of your crucifix.
This is the ultimate affirmative action.
- We can level the playing field.
- No one will be pressured into cheating.
This isn't about cheating.
This is about winning.
We all know winning isn't everything.
It's the only thing.
What should we do,
Dr. Plecki?
I'm a teacher, so I'm supposed
to spout the same platitudes...
you've heard a million times before.
"Cheaters don't prosper."
"It's not whether you win or lose...
it's how you play the game."
Well, this may not be approved
curriculum, but guess what.
Winning does matter.
Cheaters do prosper.
I used to run a business
supporting Irish crystal...
and let me tell you what happens when
you don't pay off the right people...
or inflate sales claims
or be creative with your accounting...
you don't stay in business
very long.
Try telling the truth on your loan
application, you won't get one.
This is a results-oriented city.
That girl doesn't care about
how that guy got where he is.
All she cares about
is where he is.
Think Bill Gates fired those who stole
Apple's operating code to give to him?
He probably promoted them.
Do you think he would ever send his kids
to a Chicago public school?
They call this place a public school.
Uses public money.
But what it is is a private school...
operating within
the public school system.
These kids get the best education
your tax dollars can buy.
You get to go to school here if your
parents know how to work the system.
Maybe they don't even live
in the city limits...
so they keep a mail drop
in Bucktown or...
they lie about your address...
your income...
your ethnicity.
So?
Okay.
- It's about fuckin' time.
- You okay?
- Where are the answers?
- How about thanks for getting the test?
We don't have a lot of time.
Jolie, you take language and lit.
Got it.
Matt, music.
Darius, mathematics.
- Right here.
- Science.
Agnieska, take social science.
Economics, Dominik.
Flickas, art.
Everybody focus.
I know it's late, but I'm struggling
with this math question...
and I thought since you are
the best math teacher at Steinmetz...
May I speak to somebody
in the music department, please?
What are you doing?
No, it's not.
Burning the midnight oil?
We won't rest until
we're number one, sir.
I like that.
That's the Steinmetz spirit.
I'll try to stop by tomorrow.
You definitely should. I think we're
gonna do better than anyone expects.
Very good. All right,
keep up the good work.
We will.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't resist.
Okay.
Let's get back to work.
12 "C", 13 "B"...
14 "C", 15 "E"...
16 "D", 17 "E"...
18 "D", 19 "E", 20 "A"...
This is a waste of time. Just write
the answers on your hand, man.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to get caught?
If you're gonna cheat,
cheat smart.
- Do you have that gum?
- Yeah.
You can write the answers
on a stick of gum.
I'm not gonna read answers
off a piece of gum.
We wouldn't wanna cross that line,
would we?
Guys, put 'em on the bottom
of your shoes.
Wait, listen.
Everybody give me your calculators.
I'll program the answers in,
then you can just bring 'em up.
Guys, who's got a beeper?
I mean, we could program them
with the answers.
All right, Agnieska!
Welcome to the team.
Thanks.
I'm telling you,
shoes are the key.
We could wear skirts and we could
write the answers on our thighs.
Yeah, I'm gonna wear a skirt.
I'm not gonna wear a skirt.
I mean, you can wear shorts.
Math answers are 1 "B"...
- I need to speak with you.
- Sure.
In private.
Have you talked to Dominik, 'cause he's
acting like he will still be competing?
We agreed Dominik would compete at State
and you would compete at Nationals.
- Agreed? I got you the exams.
- I know you did.
- I've already sent the names to State.
- That's just crap!
- I can't change that.
- I put my ass on the line.
But you'll reap the rewards
at Nationals.
That's crap.
I can't believe it.
I fuckin' worked my ass off,
I got the fuckin' exams.
Do you wanna participate
in State finals?
- Yes!
- Okay, good.
I think I know of a way you can.
So then you just press
the "shift" button.
And then the "memory" button...
and all the answers should come up
and then you just scroll through it.
What if a proctor comes by?
What do you press?
- "AC" button clears the whole screen.
- Does it come back?
Yeah.
Remember, nobody's ever gotten
a perfect score on the math section...
so don't set a precedent.
Jolie, you get two wrong, Darius, three,
the rest of you at least four or five.
- What?
- Four or five.
I think I should score the highest.
That would arouse the least suspicion.
- I did the best on the essays.
- No, listen.
This has already been decided.
No arguing.
Now, don't be surprised if you see Irwin
in the Speech and Interview room.
Each school has to supply
two alumni volunteer judges.
Irwin's gonna get here on his own...
and he's gonna disguise himself
using a friend's ID.
Here's your badge, Mr. Tully.
It's nice to have a college volunteer
helping us out.
- Got it?
- Thank you.
Come here a second.
All right, just remember.
Get some answers wrong.
The only way we get caught
is if we do too well.
All right.
Good morning, decathletes.
Good morning!
Good morning, decathletes,
and welcome...
to the State Finals of Illinois
Academic Decathlon.
What a wonderful thing to see
so many bright young kids here today.
You know...
I was trying to explain
to my 15 year old...
what the academic decathlon
was all about.
And he said...
"You mean those dorks
take tests for fun?"
I thought that was kind of...
But I know that you know
that hard work...
and determ... and dedication...
are the keys to achieving
your dreams.
And you are...
And you are our hopes
and our future.
Good luck, decathletes. Let's show
the world all about youth power.
Okay?
Go Whitney! Go Whitney!
Hey, Jerry,
you want in on this?
Remember?
Come on. A buck? Two bucks?
Something.
You gotta be in it to win it.
How about a hundred?
- All of it?
- Yeah. I'm feeling lucky.
Everything going as planned?
I had to kill a proctor
who was onto me, but other than that...
Let's go over the signals.
Point up, it's "A".
- To the left ear...
- "B."
- Right ear?
- "C."
To the neck is "D."
Eraser's "E." Got it?
And now, your starting line up
for your Super Quiz.
Introducing from Whitney Young...
The number of base pairs
of human DNA is...
A: Nearly two billion...
B: Nearly three billion...
C: Nearly four billion...
D: Nearly five billion...
or E: Nearly six billion?
The correct answer: "B."
DNA fermentation first occur
at which level?
A: P1...
B: P2...
C: P3.
The number of base pairs
of human DNA is...
Lambda exonuclease comes from...
Map the 100,000 human genes.
Well, it's been a great day. I see
a lot of anxious faces in the crowd.
I'm just thinking I'll go home
and maybe announce it tomorrow.
Are you ready to find out
what happened here today?
You give me a team cheer if you think
you're gonna take home the medal.
Here we go now.
In Language and Literature...
the bronze medal goes to
Steinmetz's...
Agnieska Maryniarczyk.
The silver medal from Steinmetz,
Darius Bettus.
And the gold goes to
Steinmetz's Jolie Fitch.
The bronze medal goes to Steinmetz...
And the winning team.
The winner of the Illinois
Academic Decathlon for 1995...
scoring 49,166 points...
Steinmetz High School.
All right.
Steinmetz in the house tonight.
Let's hear it.
Come on now.
Reach to the top, yo
Reach to the sky, The time is high
We're used to be number five
But now we're number one from the slum
You know we have more fun
than Whitney Young
Praise to teach and now we on our way
My main man Plecki and the capital "J"
Agnieska on my left, Matt on my right
Darius and Dominik be rockin' tonight
You can't go in there. If one of the
other kids that you judged saw you...
with one of your teammates or if you
got your picture taken by somebody...
It's not fair.
I'm the one that brought you the tests.
Just lay low for a while.
Let the hubbub die down.
In a week or so, nobody will remember
you. They won't know your face.
That is bullshit.
- You guys had a hell of a night.
- I know. It's unbelievable.
Yeah, unbelievable.
Tell me about it.
I've only got $180, but...
Oh, keep it. Keep it.
You didn't know
what you were up against.
Of course they cheated.
The only question is how.
I understand that.
It's statistically impossible
for any team...
to increase their score by 10,000 points
in three weeks.
Just take it easy. No.
Listen to me.
You don't jump from a tricycle
to tooling around in a Mercedes.
It's not like the Mavericks
beating the Bulls.
Those kids aren't in the same league.
It's like a bunch of five year olds
beating the Bulls.
Because I don't have proof.
Could you please get me all the scores?
And crunch the numbers.
Yes, that's all...
Yes, good. Thanks.
That was so cool.
How many of you saw the look
on Haden's face when we won?
That alone was worth the price
of admission. It was so cool.
They were such poor losers,
sulking in the corner.
They wouldn't even shake my hand.
They just walked right out.
- Because he thought we cheated.
- We did cheat.
He doesn't know that. He thinks we're
too stupid to win without cheating.
- It's so insulting.
- Guys, listen up.
It was amazing what you did.
Really, I look at all the medals.
We got medals in Speech and Essay
and Interview competition.
Those are areas we didn't have
any advanced preparation.
Agnieska, your speech was beautiful.
It really was.
And a bronze medal.
Dominik gets a gold
for the essay.
Jolie loses all the answers, and look at
all those medals. I don't believe it.
You were all beautiful.
Just a beautiful job today.
I'm very proud of you.
But now comes
the really hard part.
Keeping quiet.
This will be the real test
of your skills.
Right here.
You cannot say anything.
Not to your parents...
your friends,
if you still have any.
Not to your teachers.
Not even to your priest.
You can't.
Benjamin Franklin said...
"The only way three people
can keep a secret...
is if two of them are dead."
Let's see if we can
prove him wrong.
Gonna fly now
Looking strong now
Flying high now
Gonna fly now
Gonna fly
They said it couldn't be done.
They said that a general enrollment
school could never beat Whitney Young.
They were wrong!
Faculty members,
these kids are your creations.
Stand up, faculty members, please.
Let's have a round of applause
for your teachers.
The boos are unnecessary.
But now, most of all...
we salute Dr. Jerry Plecki.
Jerry, you inspired these kids.
You taught them how to win.
I don't know how you did it...
but I want you to keep doing it.
I notice that we have some media here
and I would assume...
we could have some positive images
for our school for a change.
Thank you.
It's true that our school does not have
the most up-to-date facilities.
And we don't have as much money
as some other schools.
But we have something that I believe
is much more important.
- Good weed!
- We have heart.
Years from now they'll still be talking
about the stunning upset...
at the Illinois Academic Decathlon.
The architect of this
amazing triumph is Dr. Jerry Plecki.
We all think Dr. Plecki's
the best.
He taught us if they won't let you in
the front, sneak right in the back.
If it weren't for him,
we wouldn't even be on this team.
There would be no team.
There would be nothing.
- So a lot of studying they had to do?
- Months! Months and months.
I mean, holidays, weekends,
the whole deal.
Birthdays, everything.
And you got a place in
your trophy case for all of these?
I'm sleeping with it, actually.
It's gonna replace my teddy bear.
- The Nationals are coming up.
- The Nationals. We're excited about it.
- We're gonna win. You better watch out.
- We're gonna kick some ass.
Did I say that? Sorry.
That's okay.
- Thanks, and good luck.
- Thank you.
Hi, Mom.
Those kids were in here night and day.
They didn't think they were winners
and they are.
All kids need to be
part of a team, right?
And he did that for them.
He made them part of a winning team.
He worked hard, like his father
taught him to work hard.
I wish that his father was alive now
so he could share this joy.
The kids were great. They really
worked hard and, I mean, tireless.
Months and months of...
And it paid off.
Listen, he's so humble,
but he deserves the credit.
It seems all of Chicago is relishing
in this Cinderella story.
But now it's back to the hard work of
studying for the National competition...
which will be held here in Chicago
at Palmer House on April 14.
We wish them well.
Were there any surprises
on the exams?
Not really.
We tried to study everything...
so there would be no surprises.
- So what are we gonna do now?
- Do?
- At the Nationals?
- We're gonna do well.
- We are?
- Yeah.
So what are we gonna say
when we drop 9,000 points...
and the team from North Dakota
edges us out of 43rd place?
That's not gonna happen.
You know what I think? I think
you could've won State without any help.
Please.
No, I do. I really do.
All having the test did
was give you a psychological boost.
It's all up here. It's all about having
the confidence, the cockiness...
to think you can do it, to know that
you can beat anybody in that room.
You know what I think?
I think that if I can get
the State tests from DeVry...
I should be able to get the tests
for the Nationals from the same place.
I guarantee they haven't
even tightened security...
because they don't even know
it was breached.
Good, good, good.
Okay if we get some pictures
with everyone?
Absolutely. Come on, guys.
- Get in there tight.
- Always strategizing, huh?
Always.
The following story is true.
The names have been changed
to protect the innocent.
Well, heck, they've been changed
to protect me.
I stress the need for total privacy.
Somehow, I...
I rushed into Dr. Plicky's house,
thinking if he knew...
how easily the test could be gotten,
he'd call the proper authorities...
and launch a full-on investigation.
But when he saw the tests, he got that
sneaky smile he's so used to modeling.
He'd lost control of his senses.
Soon the group began to congratulate me
for such a wondrous deed.
My brain spun as they discussed
cheating techniques.
I could almost taste
the madness to come.
Dr. Plicky decided I could
help the team even more...
by posing as a speech judge.
This information came as
a bit of a surprise.
If I'm not competing,
I won't get any recognition whatsoever.
If the decathlon team as a whole
would benefit, Steinmetz would benefit.
I had to do it.
I shook hands with Dr. Plicky
after the contest.
I hope he noticed that would be
the last time...
he would see me holding
any respect for him.
He turned a simple contest among friends
into a competition of deceit.
I now know what it's like
to sell my soul to the devil.
I can't begin to imagine
how my teammates must feel.
Guilt must clot their veins.
What is this?
It's a story.
I know that, Irwin.
But is there any truth to it?
Well, I think
that every good writer...
draws on inspiration
from his own life.
It's really a very simple question.
Either you had the tests
or you didn't.
Okay, well...
Here's what happened, see?
I just thought, you know,
what a funny story it would make...
you know if the decathlon team,
you know, the "Cinderella Team"...
that's getting all the attention,
you know...
if they only won 'cause they cheated.
How funny would that be?
Irwin has always been one of
our more imaginative writers.
- Thank you.
- He wants to be a screenwriter.
Well, I am a screenwriter, really.
I have written several...
drama and action kind of pieces.
Well, Irwin...
I think you've written
a very dramatic story.
- Thank you.
- But I'm not sure you understand...
how damaging this can be
in the wrong hands.
You may have written this
as a flight of fancy...
but there are a lot of people out there
who would like nothing better...
than to destroy
the pride and prestige...
and self-esteem
that this win has brought the school.
And this may create real problems
for you...
your teammates
and the entire school.
So I have to ask you...
right here and right now...
in plain, simple English...
is this story true or isn't it?
Yes or no?
- You're sure?
- Yeah.
It's a tall tale.
A fantasy. A kind of
sciency fiction thing.
All right. You'll have to write
a recantation.
A what?
You had idle time.
You orchestrated
a fictitious story.
I can't tell you
exactly what to write.
Just explain why you wrote
what you wrote...
should this thing
ever become an issue.
How do you spell "orchestrated"?
- Calm down! Calm down!
- I can't believe you did this!
- I changed the names.
- Oh, yeah, "Dr. Plicky"!
- How fucking original.
- I'm gonna tear you apart!
- Guys! Guys!
- He's probably wearing a wire!
I'm not wearing a...
Let's talk about this.
- Stupid motherfucker!
- Leave him alone!
- Sit down!
- Fuck off!
- Piece of shit.
- Get back there.
Sit down.
Shut up. Do you understand
why they're upset?
Confessions are for priests...
not English teachers.
You write that kind of story,
make those sorts of explosive charges...
who's the one you're hurting, huh?
You're the one who's not gonna
go to Nationals.
You're the one admitting stealing tests,
impersonating a judge.
- I've never...
- Look, look.
I understand why you wrote it.
You're upset about not getting
the credit you deserved.
- Yeah!
- All right. I feel badly about that...
but it was too risky for you
to get any kind of media exposure.
If just one kid from another school
recognized you...
as a judge at the competition,
we'd all be in big trouble.
- Especially you.
- I'm so fucking sick of this guy.
Jerry.
- Hey, Connie, what's up?
- Can I see you a minute?
Sure.
- Get over here!
- Can we just talk about this?
- I'll talk about my fist in your eye!
- I changed the names!
Get him, get him, get him!
Absolutely. I think so.
Hello, Dr. Plecki.
I'm Joan Isenberg...
from the Illinois Academic
Decathlon Association.
- Hello.
- And this is Bruce McCaully...
from Hartcourt Brace.
I want to congratulate you
on your win, Dr. Plecki.
- Thank you.
- And I want to inform you...
that your team will have to
take the test again.
We've performed random number
probability experiments...
using a mixed model methodology
and utilizing a two-way analysis...
of your team's performance
at State versus Regional.
Now, the high and low scores indicates
statistical variances...
beyond normal parameters.
Would you like to put that
in English for us?
Whitney Young's scores went down from
the regional to the state competition.
Your scores went up, way up.
You had the highest scores
in decathlon history.
Yeah, well, that probably has
something to do with us winning.
If I could just take you through...
some of the original scores.
In mathematics, for example.
Kurgan, Paul:
Regionals 300, State 900.
Kur, Matt:
Regionals 175, State 875.
Fitch, Jolie:
Regionals 575, State 975.
- Who hired you?
- Dr. McCaully was retained...
by the decathlon committee
after anomalies were detected.
Come on. Let's talk about
who's really behind this, okay?
I can just imagine the phone calls
you got from Whitney Young...
demanding to know why
you let us crash their little party.
- We're just doing our job, Dr. Plecki.
- Then good.
Why don't you investigate Young's scores
for the past nine years?
You won't because
you're in bed with them.
- Are you questioning my integrity?
- I don't need to.
I call your office,
the phone rings at Whitney Young.
We have not had our office there
for two years.
- Please! The whole system is corrupt.
- That is not true!
Are you, like, serious?
Just one second.
Let's be calm here a second.
Dr. Plecki, if you have anything
to say to us, just say it now.
We cheated.
We cheated a system that tries
to make it impossible...
for a general-enrollment school, or
anyone who is not Whitney Young, to win.
And that must piss some people off.
You have completely misunderstood
the situation, Dr. Plecki.
- I have not misunderstood anything.
- Oh, for heaven's sake!
- I know exactly what...
- Let's be calm for one second.
What, in your view, do we have to do
to remedy this situation?
Your team has to take
a validation test this Thursday.
And if there's no significant decrease
in the scores...
they'll be eligible to compete
in the Nationals.
It's so unfair.
Would they ask Whitney Young
to retake the test? Of course not.
You go to a good school,
and they expect you to do well.
It's so much easier to cheat.
What about just taking the test again?
- No, no, no, no.
- What?
You know, we should just sue them.
- For defamation of character.
- Yeah.
- And violation of due process.
- Pain and suffering.
- Guys, look.
I'm glad to hear we've got a handle on
cause of action, but we're not suing.
- What are we gonna do?
- "What are we gonna do?"
We're gonna do some research.
Your students averaged fewer than
four wrong on the multiple choice...
where other schools average
14 to 18 incorrect answers.
Then we found out that most of your kids
finished the test with time to spare.
They should be rewarded, not punished.
- That's right.
- In this country...
one is innocent until proven guilty,
not the other way around.
- Those scores wouldn't be questioned...
- Right on.
If my kids did not have Spanish surnames
and come from barrio schools.
You know that!
If you're so confident
of your students' abilities...
why not encourage them to retest?
- Why should I?
- If they don't...
everyone will assume they cheated.
Everyone will assume they cheated
if they do!
- Bingo.
- I want to see the tests, please.
We feel that by honoring
your demand for a retest...
we would implicitly accede
to the reason behind it...
the suspicion
that cheating has occurred.
We thereby notify you, that unless you
have direct evidence of wrongdoing...
we reject your ultimatum
and refuse to be retested.
Well, then...
I have no choice but to proceed
with this course of action.
As a result of scores
that indicate statistical variances...
beyond normal parameters...
and your refusal
to submit to a retest...
you are summarily stripped
of your championship...
and eligibility to participate
in the national competition.
All trophies and medals
should be returned immediately...
to the Illinois Academic Decathlon
Association Representative...
Miss Joan Isenberg.
Miss Isenberg, if you try to take
our championship away...
we will see you in court.
Do what you have to do, Dr. Kiamos...
and we'll do what we have to do.
You're those kids
from Steinmetz, right?
Yeah, I saw you guys on TV.
Go kick some ass at Nationals, man.
You know we will, man.
You know we will.
Oh, my God, we are so high up!
- Wow.
- Check this out.
Look at this view, man. Whoa!
- Hi, I'm...
- I know who you are, Dr. Plecki.
We've been expecting you.
I'll show you to the conference room.
Guys, I think I can see Steinmetz.
Paul, sit down.
Hey, guys, I'm sorry
to keep you waiting.
Everything all right here?
When Constantine told me what they were
trying to do to you, I was outraged.
It's bullshit. Pardon my French.
I come from the streets,
just like you.
I didn't go to the right schools.
I didn't know the right people.
I don't speak the queen's English.
Everyone assumes I got where I am today
by lying, cheating, stealing.
- Mr. Clifford?
- What?
Tell him I'll call him back.
And by the way,
you didn't cheat, did you?
All right. I had to ask that.
But, obviously, you know
where my sentiments lie.
I wouldn't have
taken this case pro bono...
if I didn't think there was
a real wrong being perpetrated here.
And that's why I've invited
the press down to meet with you.
The press?
- To meet us?
- Yeah.
If we're gonna win this thing, we're
doing it in a court of public opinion.
So sit tight, all right?
All right.
Look what I'm wearing.
All right, all right.
As you can see from the press releases
in front of you...
these young people
are the cream of the crop.
They're our future leaders.
Honor roll students
taking AP classes.
But they're here today because they
are accused of being too successful.
Our firm, Robert A. Clifford
and Associates...
is filing a motion
seeking injunctive relief...
and a temporary restraining order...
barring the Decathlon Committee
from stripping the team...
of its rightfully won title and
its ability to compete at the Nationals.
Whoa! One question at a time.
Of the 5,000 students
who took the state tests...
only 12 scored 900 or better
in the math section.
Six were from Steinmetz.
Okay, so we'll try to do better
at the Nationals.
And of the 105 students
in the state finals...
only 17 could answer
one difficult calculus problem...
yet all six from Steinmetz
answered it correctly.
Props to our math teacher.
You're the best, Dr. Miller.
How do you explain the high scores,
though? I mean, there must be...
Hold on. Let me explain.
Can I just say something?
If we didn't have Polish surnames...
or come from a poor school...
these scores would never
have been questioned.
The Steinmetz team's defiance...
of the state board directives
is being viewed...
as a brave and courageous stance...
in a city now gripped by
"did they or didn't they" fever.
Those Whitney Young whiners
should just shut up.
Learning how to lose gracefully is
just as important as knowing how to win.
No one's proven these kids guilty.
They worked hard. They're innocent.
If these kids cheated
and managed to keep it quiet...
they're even more talented
than I thought they were.
Hey, guys, call me.
I will hire you in a heartbeat.
Absolutely. We reached those heights.
We achieved those scores.
Until and unless someone comes along
to prove that we didn't...
we're going to stand by
this year's scores.
If it is discovered that they cheated,
should they be stripped of their title?
All I have is accusations
from people whose voracity I question.
- I have absolutely no reason...
- Fuck.
To believe that this isn't...
a very clear case of people jealous...
of those who they don't expect
to beat them.
What do you think this says
about the city of Chicago?
I don't think it says much
about the city itself.
The school system
might be punished for it.
But along the lines of the city,
the city's still a very respectful city.
You don't think this gives us
a black eye nationally?
Hi. Yes. Can I speak
to a Gloria Abrams, please?
- Hello?
- Dr. Plecki?
- Yes?
- This is Gloria Abrams...
from the Sun-Times.
How did you get this number?
Irwin Flickas gave it to me,
and he also gave me...
a very interesting essay concerning
some stolen decathlon materials.
We're going to print it
in tomorrow's paper...
and I was wondering if
I could get a comment from you.
Dr. Plecki, do you know Irwin Flickas?
Dr. Plecki, are you...
Jerry? You okay?
I'm fine. Go back to sleep.
It's okay. Go on.
Jerry?
What the hell are you doing?
Jerry, my paper!
- Hey, did someone get killed?
- Yeah, you.
This is so messed up.
I can't believe that he would...
- This is no good right here.
- Excuse me?
Get the hell out of here, man!
What are you doing, huh?
You want some of this?
Get out of here!
Don't give them what they want!
I can't fucking believe this!
I'm never gonna get into college now.
This is ridiculous!
- I look so fat!
- I'm gonna kill him.
- Am I that fat, for real?
- Yes, you are.
- Why would he do that?
- Maybe we should give back the medals.
What?
Maybe we should just
end this insanity.
Let Whitney Young go to Nationals.
Let all this craziness just fade away.
- Maybe we should just tell the truth.
- No, no, wait! Hold on!
Hold on! You were the one
that taught us...
to take charge in each situation,
to get our foot in the door.
Now you want them to slam it
in our face?
I mean,
what evidence do they have?
Some kid wrote an essay
who can't even spell.
We have to let people know
who Flickas really is.
He's this kid pissed off
because he's dropped from the team.
Yeah, yeah, he's just jealous
of our success.
We don't hate him.
We're not mad at him.
- Yeah, we feel sorry for this kid.
- We can survive this.
We can. You taught us
how to survive anything.
We just have to stick together
and keep our stories straight...
and take the offensive.
All right.
But you understand this:
Things are only going to get worse.
The media is going to lie to you,
they're gonna threaten you...
they're gonna try to turn you
against each other.
So look around.
Those are the only faces
you can trust.
- Talk to me!
- Did you cheat? Did you steal the test?
Get out of here!
Leave my son alone!
We just want to let him tell
his side of the story!
If he doesn't defend himself,
who will?
- I'm coming down there to kick your ass!
- Yeah, beat his ass, Dad!
Listen to me.
I'll take you to New York.
I'll put you in a nice hotel room.
I could get you courtside seats at
the Bull's game. What's your shoe size?
Do you like musicals?
I'll take you to Cats.
Get away from my house!
I've had enough of this!
Agnieska is not a cheater.
She is a good student! She won!
Are you sure about this?
- Out!
- George, keep it going.
I see your son, this boy here...
as the bright shining light
in this whole sordid affair.
The only one with the courage,
with the honesty to come forward...
and blow the whistle
on those disciples of darkness.
- So, who's gonna...
- So, who's gonna play me?
- Shut up. This movie's not about you.
- Wait a minute.
- Don't tell me to shut up.
- They're making a movie about me!
All right. Let's examine the essay
for a moment.
So, first of all, we have
this tragic hero, Irwin Flickas.
And then there's the suffering victim,
Irwin Flickas.
And then finally, we have
this redemptive act performed by...
Irwin Flickas.
I mean, it's kind of an interesting
profile, don't you think?
- You're wearing the shirt I gave you.
- I gave 'em the usual "whatever."
You didn't have to give an exclusive.
Wow, I got screwed.
My dad's screaming,
"I'm gonna kick your ass!
Get the fuck off
my private property."
Connie Chung's people called me.
They want to take me out for breakfast.
Jeff, I'm outside the Sheraton
Chicago Hotel and Towers...
where I've obtained an exclusive
interview with Angela Lam...
the captain of last year's
Steinmetz Academic Decathlon Team.
- Switch to channel two.
- All right, all right, all right.
She says that her former coach,
Dr. Jerry Plecki...
came to her during the competition
with a slip of paper...
containing the answers to the Super Quiz
portion of the decathlon.
Quick, turn to channel two.
Right now.
- Who is that?
- That girl went to our school.
I admit it. I cheated.
This girl's full of it.
Could be true.
She looks to happy to be on TV.
Their overall score didn't allow them
to advance to state finals.
This year's team did much better,
winning the state championship.
But Lam's admission tonight raises more
questions about this year's victory.
I'd just like to say to the members
of this year's team...
if you did cheat,
it's time to come clean.
- Oh, come on!
- Cheating is not all right.
It is wrong, wrong, wrong.
The integrity and morality are more
important than winning the contest.
Oh, please!
God, man, what is she doing?
What's wrong with her?
This is not good at all.
In an essay, he claims Steinmetz
obtained an advance copy of the test.
This comes only weeks after
Steinmetz won the academic decathlon.
- There you are!
- Mom, please!
If it wasn't for him,
we wouldn't have gotten caught.
- Come on. We'll be fine.
- It would suck if we got caught, man.
But the investigation is ongoing.
Reporting live from downtown Chicago,
I'm Lisa Martin.
Dr. Plecki, is Angela Lam
telling the truth?
- Jerry, go home.
- Okay. Look, I can explain.
I just got a call from Argie Johnson.
The school board has ruled that you
are suspended until this mess is over.
Suspended? On what grounds?
I don't know. Dereliction of duty,
fucking with other people's livelihoods.
Take your pick. If you want to see
your union rep, I think you should.
Can I use the phone in your office?
You can't conduct business
on school property.
Where are my kids?
They're on their way
to the school board headquarters.
Listen to me.
I've been here 26 years.
I don't think I'm gonna survive this
debacle. Let me give you some advice.
By the way, no contact anymore
with the students. That's the ruling.
I think you should go home, don't answer
the door, don't talk to any reporters.
Just lie low, okay?
- Do it?
- Yeah.
Two minutes! Come on, Plecki!
Was Angela telling the truth?
Did you cheat last year?
- Come on, Plecki!
- Talk to us!
Hi, Jolie.
My name is Jerry Marconi,
and this is Corinne Davis.
We're attorneys working
with the board of education.
Now, we know that cheating occurred.
That's a given.
What we need to know now
is whether Dr. Plecki stole the tests.
- Coerced you into looking at them.
- Threatened you if you talked.
- Offered you alcohol.
- Drugs.
- Sex.
- That doesn't matter.
You're just a kid.
He took advantage of your youth.
- Your stupidity.
- Your innocence.
You did a lot of growing up lately,
haven't you?
And now you know the difference
between right and wrong.
You do know the difference
between right and wrong, don't you?
Right?
Wrong?
Don't you?
- We didn't cheat.
Well, well, well!
Look what I just got.
Signed confessions
from your teammates.
And guess what they're saying.
That you were the ringleader.
That is was all your idea.
Come on, Dominik.
It's time to get it off your chest.
You're a good Catholic like me.
We both go to church,
share the same confessor.
Remember what the Bible says.
"Repent so that your sins
may be blotted out...
less Satan take advantage of us.
For we are not ignorant
of his devices."
You gotta let it go.
The truth has to come.
You gonna live with that shame
for the rest of your life?
Come clean.
Open up your heart.
You can't live with a lie.
You can't. How are you
gonna fill that hole?
You can only fill it with the truth,
Dominik. The truth.
Tell me the truth.
Did you cheat?
All right. I know you all want to
make your deadlines, so I'll be brief.
We have cracked
the Steinmetz cheating conspiracy.
I have in my hand
a signed confession...
from a Steinmetz team member,
admitting that...
he did, indeed, receive stolen copies
of the academic decathlon test.
Says the team was instructed...
- on how to cheat...
- I won!
By their former decathlon coach,
Dr. Gerard Plecki.
Now, while Dr. Plecki did not personally
obtain the stolen tests...
he made sure that all the students
studied with the test.
He directed the cover-up,
and he attempted to maintain...
a code of silence
amongst the conspirators.
As a result, we are considering pursuing
criminal charges against Dr. Plecki.
Those charges may include conspiracy
to defraud the decathlon competition...
theft of a scholarship and perjury.
How did Dr. Plecki get them to cheat?
These kids are a very tight-knit group.
Like a cult, if you will. And Dr. Plecki
is the leader of this cult.
He brainwashed them, made sure they'd
follow him to the gates of hell...
and then break them down for him.
And let me just tell you something.
I've dealt with hard-core rapists,
serial killers, you name it...
but these kids may be some of the most
skilled liars I've ever encountered.
They looked me straight in the eye
and lied to me. They scared me.
Mr. Marconi, is it true...
one of the team members
is a bisexual witch?
I can't comment on that aspect
of the investigation.
Mr. Marconi, there have been allegations
that perhaps there was some sort...
of sexual relationship going on between
Dr. Plecki and one of his students.
I can't comment on that aspect
of the investigation.
Sir, where is Dr. Plecki now?
His whereabouts are unknown to me
at the moment.
Will the students be expelled?
Cheating is a serious infraction...
in any educational institution...
and it's something that I
will not tolerate in this system...
by any teacher or anyone else.
They should hold that adult responsible
as a teacher. They should fire him.
What it does is tell me how far
we've come in our society.
When I was in school,
cheating was a monumental offense.
Honor was held in high esteem.
He's a moral midget.
I always had a bad feeling about Jerry.
I knew something was going on.
Kids coming and going late at night.
One time I saw a teenager
leave at 1:00 in the morning.
A crisis management team
has been called in...
to counsel shocked students
and team members.
Steinmetz is a school in pain.
There he is.
Get that fuckin' snitch!
- Get him!
- Help! Get 'em off me!
How could you do this?
How could you betray those kids?
It's not that simple, Mother.
Yes, it is. It's that simple.
Teachers don't teach kids
how to cheat.
Believe me, those kids
didn't need any instruction.
Yes! Yes, they did.
They needed someone to tell them
that it was wrong.
Your father was so proud
when you became a teacher.
He never cared
how much money you made.
He just wanted you
to reflect well on us.
He lived a decent, honest life.
Yeah, and look what happened to him.
He got screwed.
He had this bullshit immigrant notion
that if he worked hard enough...
and wanted something badly enough,
all his dreams would come true!
All your dreams would come true!
That's why he worked so hard.
So that you would have the opportunities
that he never got.
That's why he worked at that factory!
Inhaling those diesel fumes
so you wouldn't have to!
The minute he got sick,
they laid him off!
They took his pension,
they took his medical insurance!
They killed him!
They fucking killed him!
That was his reward! That was the reward
that he got for all his hard work!
- Right there!
- Listen.
No matter what happened
to your father...
he never used it as an excuse
to do something that was wrong.
You're not the victim here, Jerry.
What you did was wrong.
And nothing you say
can ever make it right.
Guys, I'm leaving tonight.
As I'm sure you know,
the only question left unanswered...
is whether to form a lynching party
or just burn me at the stake.
So I think it's time
to head for friendlier climes.
Or at least someplace
where there isn't a bounty on my head.
Have you considered Somalia?
Now, obviously,
we made some mistakes.
- Getting caught, for one.
- No, no, no.
This isn't about getting caught
or being punished.
I look at what we did as kind of
a civil disobedience.
Or maybe that was a mistake.
Maybe I owe you an apology.
I don't know anything anymore.
I just know that sometimes...
you need to break the rules
in order to change them.
And things will change because of this.
- They'll make the tests harder to steal.
- Yeah, probably will.
But they'll also have to justify
holding a competition that isn't real...
where the same team wins,
year after year.
They'll have to justify
warehousing you...
while a chosen few
get a quality education.
But I want you all
to put it behind you.
If anyone asks,
you tell them I got the tests...
forced you to look at them...
threatened you if you talked.
'Cause it doesn't matter to me.
My career is over.
Yours are just beginning.
Here.
We got something for you.
- A little something.
- Well, that's...
Thank you very much. That's...
"Dear Dr. Plecki,
the skills you've taught us...
will serve us
the rest of our lives.
You were the best teacher
we ever had.
The '94, '95 Steinmetz
Academic Decathlon Team."
These were children.
And it incenses me that an adult...
would seduce and corrupt
innocent children in this manner.
I am just so upset by this.
I cannot even believe...
Everyone in my school cheats.
It's like brushing your teeth.
Only the stoners don't cheat, because
they don't even care about their grades.
But don't you realize
that when you cheat...
the only one you're hurting
is yourself?
Yeah, I'm in a lot of pain. I cheated in
high school and got into a good college.
I cheated in college and got into
a really great law school.
I cheated in law school
and got into a great law firm.
Now I'm bagging,
like, 700 grand a year...
and I never regretted not learning how
to do that calculus derivative stuff.
I'm just glad I got out of high school
and got an "A" in calculus.
People always ask me...
"Having gone through everything
you went through...
would you do it again?"
And I always give the same answer.
"In a heartbeat."
I learned more about the way
the world really works...
from my nine months on the decathlon...
than most people
will learn in a lifetime.
Eventually the media siege ended...
and we returned to school.
We took some grief for ruining
Steinmetz's reputation...
as if such a thing were possible.
We had to write an essay on ethics.
Matt copied his from
the Dalai Lama's autobiography...
which we all thought
was pretty amusing.
And then we just drifted apart.
Most of the kids just wanted to
put the whole thing behind them.
They think I'm crazy
for talking to you...
but I've never
buried my head in shame.
And I'm not very big on apologies.
I spent my senior year half asleep...
which made it
a whole lot easier to blend in.
I haven't seen Dr. Plecki
since that day by the lake.
I heard something about a business
near Wicker Park.
I thought about trying to find him...
but I never did.
I figure we'll meet up again
when the time's right.
That's right. That's me.
I got into college...
a good one...
just like Dr. Plecki promised.
I think the admissions officer thought
my decathlon experience built character.
I'm getting good grades...
and no, I'm not cheating.
Don't laugh, but...
I'm thinking about
becoming a teacher.
There's no more noble job
than shaping young minds.
So what would I do if I caught
one of my students cheating?
I'd turn the little bastard in.
But if they can get by me...
then I know they'll be ready
for the real world.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
Done by (c) dCd / January 2015