I need more red.
Don't move.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Stay still. Stay still.
I'm doing the mouth so don't...
No talking.
I'll be right back.
Don't talk.
Don't move.
Hey. Hey, excuse me.
Can you please help?
We need to send
"Green Sunbeam" to New York.
Impossible.
It's going to be in
Berlin at the same dates.
How about...
"Curves of the Universe"
instead, Francoise?
No, no, no! No way!
Nothing from the 1995 series.
Can you picture it? At the MOMA?
It would clash with the space.
We promised "Green Sunbeam"
to the Hamburger
Bahnhof months ago.
They're really counting on it.
Hello Lilas, it's Annabelle.
- Are you okay?
- I'm great. You?
Are you sure?
Your mum is worried sick.
Leo called and said
you were missing.
I can't be missing
if I'm talking to you.
You know exactly what I meant.
So what?
I have more than 500
pieces in my catalog.
Something will find
grace in their eyes, no?
Listen, Lilas, deep down,
she just wants you to be happy.
But you should let
her know how you are.
Look, Stephane, honey,
I'm just not feeling it.
Find a solution.
I want "Green
Sunbeam" in New York.
Why is she
talking about New York?
The MOMA is
having a retrospective
of her work in two weeks.
She hasn't told you about it?
Will she be there?
No, it looks
like she will be in Berlin.
So, Annabelle
what's the word?
She's saying that everything is fine
and that you shouldn't worry.
Pass me the phone.
Your mum wants to talk to you.
Lilas, are you completely
out of your mind?
How long am I going
to have to endure your childishness?
I didn't ask for anything.
I am tired.
I have more important
things to do.
You are the one who calls me.
I can't believe you passed
on the best art
school for this crap.
So, you will do as you are told,
and come back to Paris.
Annabelle will book
a flight for you.
See you tomorrow!
Surprise.
Hi! What's
with the suitcase?
What suitcase?
Lilas...
Yeah?
Did something happen with Leo?
No.
Well, stop filming me.
Tell me what happened.
Nothing happened.
I just needed a little
bit of fresh air.
Listen, I'll be done in an hour.
We'll figure it out. Okay?
- Why do you work?
- What?
Why do you work?
What's your dream?
Hey honey. It's me.
I'm just calling to
say that I am running
a little bit late tonight.
Shouldn't be too bad hopefully.
Should be home a
little after 11:00.
Yeah.
Mr.,
I mean I think I spoke
to you a little bit
about him, but he passed
today, so it's
been a little hard.
Make sure to give
Maggie her food.
I left it in the fridge
and hopefully she'll get
in bed at a time...
Well she should be in
bed right now, but okay.
I miss you both, bye.
...that then through a complicated
series of molecular
attractions lead to the
psychedelic effect.
It's not especially well
understood, currently,
but maybe one day we'll
know a little bit better
exactly how the
effect is produced.
That kind of sounds
like a Randy Newman song.
Yeah.
That should
have been in Toy Story.
Let me tell you about this one,
since we're talking about capitalism
and how he's a corporate sell out.
I mean it's kind of like
this idea that we're
all being watched
by the one eye.
Hey guys. Guys.
This is that book, the
book, Give it to the People.
Inside here are all
the ideas we need to
break the bad karma of
this capitalist society.
I didn't know you could read.
No, I'm serious.
Look, this is a very
unique single copy.
This is the only copy
in the whole wide world
and it's this book right here.
You know, I share your etiology,
but there I just don't agree.
Yeah, he's definitely right.
You can't change the
world with a single copy book.
Hear me out,
hear me out, hear me out.
This is participatory.
This has been around
since the '70s.
Okay?
And what happens is
when the owner of this
book gets it, he reads
it and then inside he
puts an enlightened idea.
Then when he's done
he passes it on to
another person he trusts
and the idea is to
build enough ideas.
Just to build a society
based on happiness
and creativity.
That's bullshit.
Well, if you're not nice to me
I'm going to give it to
somebody else after I'm done.
Then what?
The second
couch is a little small,
but you're not too big
so it should be okay.
Okay. Are you
sure it's going to be
okay with Leeward and Mary.
Yeah, absolutely.
Excuse me. Oh,
I'm Jocelyn by the way.
- Do you want some fruit?
- No thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Are you sure?
I have strawberries.
Are you sure Shiraz?
I'm fine, thank you.
See you up there.
See ya.
Now the junkyard on the right.
See the dim and fading light.
Thank you.
I got it fresh this morning.
Up the hill and up the stairs.
Give a shout nobody cares.
Hey guys.
Hi Rainbow.
Move your asses.
I'm Lilas.
Nice to meet you.
How's your tea?
Oh, it's beer.
Hey there Mr. Leeward.
Nice to see you Gus.
Did you make that?
Yeah. No.
You're a great
musician, like your dad.
I became afraid of
dinosaurs and my fears
became so irrational.
My bar has this crazy open mic
night next week.
You should definitely
come down and perform.
- Okay yeah, yeah.
- Yeah?
Sure.
Cool. Oh, this is my friend Lilas,
by the way.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Actually, I think
we already met once.
- Really?
- Oh, you're the French girl?
- You're French?
- Yes.
Okay, bonjour.
Bonjour, bonsoir.
She actually
really needs a place to crash.
I was wondering if
she could stay here
for a few days, just a few days.
Yeah, okay.
Sure a few days.
Thank you.
Yeah, sure.
See!
I am going to get a beer.
Can I get you something?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
All right.
One, two, three.
It's Mary.
What's the password?
I forgot my keys.
That's not the password.
Not very funny.
Open the door.
You're not even close.
Open the fucking door.
All right. Come on guys.
We should go somewhere else.
Hey Mary!
Who are all those people?
What people?
Come on.
Did you just have a party?
Well what would you call party?
Come on Benjamin,
there's a three
year old in the house.
Can you pick this up?
Did Maggie eat her dinner?
Yes. Yes,
Rainbow ate her dinner.
Her soup?
Half of her
soup and a Mr. Freeze.
A Mr. Freeze?
Mr. Freeze is
an ice cream without
the cream. It's so
good. It's good.
No, I know
what a Mr. Freeze is.
It's good.
We wrote a song though,
we wrote a song.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Together.
Did she ask about me?
Tonight?
No, but that's just
because she was...
There was a million other people here
distracting her?
Probably.
- How many?
- 20.
- 20?
- Yeah, thousand.
20,000?
People.
Seriously, how many?
15.
14, 13, 12.
Hey, Benjamin,
whose suitcase is that?
Which suitcase?
That suitcase.
Oh, that suitcase.
That's Lilas'.
That's Shiraz's friend,
the French girl.
Why is Lilas the French girl's
suitcase in our kitchen?
Um, she didn't
have any place to go.
So where exactly is
she going to stay here?
Under the couch?
Maybe under the
couch, behind the couch
or something like that.
Seriously, how
long is she staying here?
A couple of days.
A couple days. Okay?
Did you call Ted?
Ted?
Ted, the commercial guy. Ted.
Oh, you mean
Ted the commercial guy.
No.
Did Ted call you?
Yes.
What did he say?
He said like, "Hey, this is Ted.
I'm the commercial
guy. Would you like
to do a commercial with me?"
What did you say?
I said, "I'm
not sure that I want
to do that Ted."
You told him
you don't want to do
the commercial?
I said I'll think about it,
but obviously I
don't really want to.
Benjamin, it's $5000.
You have to compose one song.
It would be so easy for you.
That would not be easy.
It would not be easy
just to compose one song.
This kind of thing would
kill my artistic integrity.
Do you realize that it's twice
my monthly salary?
Come on, Benjamin. I
really need your help.
I do help. I do help.
I found Shiraz.
I just can't.
I just can't live
like this anymore.
You know Maggie is
in our room with us.
We have no privacy.
Rainbow's very happy.
That's not the point.
The point is is that I'm too
old to have all these roommates
and now there's two women living here.
Come on.
All right, I
will find some money
somehow.
I just don't want to
do the commercial.
Do whatever you want to do.
I'm really tired.
I'm going to sleep.
What's your poison?
Rum and coke.
Rum and coke all right.
Thank you.
You should meet my friend Lilas.
She's an amazing artist.
Oh yeah?
Yeah. She's
here actually.
- She's in the bathroom.
- Really? I would love to meet her.
Always looking for new talent.
Speak of the devil.
Hi, I'm
sorry. I need to go.
My mom just sent me
a flight to get home.
Wait, what?
I'm going back
to Paris tomorrow.
No, no, no, no.
You can't leave now.
I just met a curator. A curator.
Shiraz, Shiraz.
I should introduce you.
I'm serious.
Adam, this is my friend Lilas.
Hey it's very nice to meet you.
Hi.
I heard you make great art.
Um, well I'm trying to.
Yeah? What kind of art?
Visual.
I make experimental videos
and that kind of stuff.
Very cool. Very cool.
You should come
show me something.
I would love to see your work.
Come visit me at the
gallery some time.
That's kind
thank you, but I can't.
I'm leaving New York
for good tomorrow.
Tommorrow? What time?
7:00 pm. Why?
That's perfect.
Just come in the morning.
Well...
Well yes.
You should go.
Come on. I hate
to miss a talent.
I'll try. I'll
do my best, but...
- You should.
- I can't promise...
I'm telling you.
Okay well give me your number
just in case.
What is it?
It's 606-555-7966.
7966. Okay. Lilas?
Yeah. Lilas.
And your last name?
It's de Castillon.
- D-E C-A-
- Wait a minute.
Are you related to Francoise?
She's her mom.
Are you serious?
I love her.
Her early stuff is absolutely...
Brilliant! Brilliant!
- Brilliant.
- She's amazing.
Do you want a
drink or something?
No, I'm fine.
Can I just get a drink.
- Hey.
- Oh. Hey.
How are you?
I'm good.
How are you doing?
How was your night?
Very good.
The bar was nice,
but apparently that
wasn't the place to be.
What?
You mean? Oh here.
This looks nicer.
Yeah, it's
cool. It's so cool here.
It's hot. You want to sit down?
Yeah, sure. Thank you.
Oh, this looks cool too.
Yeah, yeah.
Where did you find it?
Oh, no I
built it. I built it.
You built all that stuff?
Yeah, I'm
calling it a magic globe.
See here put your hands...
Put your hands on it.
Like that?
Oh.
Yeah.
This is actually magic.
Just keep doing that.
Up, down there we
go. Okay here we go.
This is your song
that you played tonight.
Yeah.
I don't get a
chance to tell you,
but I love that song so much.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I would love to get it on
a CD if that's possible.
Impossible.
I don't have a CD.
You don't have a CD for me?
No.
- What?
- I've never recorded it.
You've never recorded a CD
in your entire life?
No. No I mean, yeah I've never
recorded an album or anything.
Why?
Oh, I don't know.
What about you and your art and
your projects and all that.
What are you going to...
Do you have any plans?
Actually, I'm
going back to Paris
tomorrow.
Really?
Yeah, so you see
that's why I need the CD.
Why would you...
I don't understand.
Why would you go back to Paris?
I mean New York is a great place
for an artist.
- It's the best place.
- Yeah, yes I know.
It's crazy for
example even tonight
at the bar I just met with
a curator or something
and he told me that he
wants me to show him
my work.
See that's good.
I mean that's what New York's
all about is meeting people.
That's awesome.
That means you
should probably stay.
My visa is going to expire and
I don't even know if I
want to show my work.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe it's going to
be hard but maybe...
I think you should
probably give it a try.
I mean it's worth
giving it a try.
Maybe you're right.
- I think you should too.
- What?
Record your album.
Record an album. No.
I have an idea.
If I go to that
gallery you go record
your first album.
Oh you mean like a deal?
Yes, like a deal.
Oh, no. Noway.
You go record an album.
Okay, and you go to the gallery.
- Hey, do you want a blanket?
- Yes, thank you.
All right. Good night.
Good night.
I don't dream that much.
I mean I dream I
guess, but I rarely
remember my dreams.
When I do remember them
I don't understand them.
Last week, for
example, I had a dream.
There was a tiny green
door in the middle
of the desert.
On the other side
of the door was the
exact same desert except
I wanted to be there.
I could have bypassed the door,
but no I wanted to go through it.
I tried again and again
but I was definitely
too big.
Thus, I just sat in
front of the door
and contemplated the other side.
So, what are you saying?
How much can you count to?
21.
Why can't you
can't to 22 though?
Why?
I don't know.
Morning.
Hey, why don't you sit down
with us and have some orange juice?
No?
Maggie, I need you
to finish your cereal.
Okay?
Finish it up
or you don't get the prize.
No, no.
Not until she
finishes her cereal.
Here.
I think your mom would
like some cereal.
Tell your mom. Tell your mom.
No, no I don't want...
Come on. Here we go.
Come on.
Momma, eat.
No.
Hey. Hi.
Hi.
Hi, I'm Lilas.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Thank you very much for letting
me stay at your place.
Yeah.
I'm very grateful.
- Hey Rainbow.
- Hi.
You look cute today.
Thank you.
Well, I need to go.
Bye.
Do you want to see
a 2-D movie tonight
or a 3-D movie?
We have Shabbat dinner tonight
with your parents.
I'm picking you up at 7:00.
This is for lunch.
I didn't have time to
make something. Maggie...
Okay thanks.
Give mommy kiss.
I love you.
I've got to go.
Bye.
It looks like you
have a whole bunch...
Okay you have way
to much milk left.
Are you going to drink it?
Do you think we should waste it?
Okay.
This is what we do.
Do you know why
your name's Rainbow?
What do you like better?
You like Maggie better
or do you like Rainbow better?
- Rainbow.
- That's a good choice.
I think Maggie is a shitty name,
if you ask me personally.
Okay you ready?
Watch it carefully.
Watch carefully.
Wow!
Whoa! Did you see that?
All right, do not
drink that milk.
Hello Studio.
Hey, this is Leeward.
I mean my name is Leeward.
How much does it cost to record?
We can
do one-day recording
and burn 100 CDs for
you for only $999.
That's $999?
Yeah, dollars.
I'm getting very busy.
Do you want to book a day now?
No. Okay. I
was just wondering.
Okay, just let me know.
Thanks.
Hi.
Yes.
- Is Adam here?
- He should be downstairs.
Probably be up in just a minute.
Okay, thank you.
Now what was I just saying?
Iptal?
Iptal. Right.
It means cancelled in Turkish.
The X.
So he's in this...
Hi.
How are you?
Thanks for coming.
Thank you for inviting me.
So what did you bring me?
I brought a roll of film.
It's a sample of
the video project
I'm working on.
Great.
I brought the projector.
Perfect. Let me just find
somewhere to plug this in.
Okay, great.
- Adam?
- Yes?
What is this?
The labyrinth.
That is called Mad Mice Maze.
It's by the Italian artist.
He aims at showing
the fragility of life
and the severity of destiny.
It's tremendous.
Really? You like it?
Like it? I love it.
I mean it's beyond
my comprehension.
I don't even know
how to explain it.
Actually, you're
the first one to see it.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
I just finished the
editing yesterday.
I love it.
I mean it's just...
the way you capture
people's emotions it's
like there's no camera at all.
It's magical.
Listen, my boss George
he's been commissioned
by PS1 to find new and
emerging talent for
his upcoming show.
Now, he's very demanding
but if you can promise
you can get a project
to me, a full project...
Sure.
Two weeks.
I'm going to see
what I can do okay?
That would be amazing.
Thank you so much.
Well I mean it was amazing.
I have to do it.
It's the least I can do.
I don't know what to say.
Just say you'll do it.
Allo?
Mom?
No, no! I'm not coming back.
I'm staying in New York.
I met a gallery curator and...
How could you say that?
You've never even seen my work!
Allo?
I can't hear you,
I'm on the subway!
You're breaking up!
Bye, bye, bye!
Okay, occupation?
I'm an artist.
Okay, do you have any proof
that your art has been shown
in an official art venue?
No, actually it
hasn't been shown in
an official venue.
Okay, but to get a visa
as an artist you can't
just say, "I'm an artist."
You know?
I mean I could say, "I'm
an artist. I'm an artist."
But that doesn't
make me an artist.
Okay? Unfortunately,
then we are not able
to do anything for you.
It has to be shown
at an official venue.
But it will
probably be part of the PS1
upcoming show.
Okay.
All right then. So
you come back and you
see me at that point. Okay?
How can I come back if I'm not
allowed to stay in the meantime?
But you need something
to back it up.
- You can't...
- Yeah, I know.
All right, well I'll ask my boss,
but I really don't think that
there's anything that we can do for you.
All right?
Hang on.
Okay, so the best
we can do is give
you a 10-day extension.
Okay, but that would be it.
You would not get
another one after that.
Okay, sure.
All right?
Thank you. Yeah.
Okay, out we go.
Take my hand.
Come on.
- Benjamin what are you doing?
- Just putting on my tie.
We're going to be late.
Um, I'm going
to do the commercial.
What?
I'm going to do the commercial.
When?
Oh, there's
a hug for capitalism.
Do you love it?
Thank you for participating hug.
Oh I do it for you.
Oh Maggie!
Daddy's song is going
to be on TV.
Yeah, on the television lady.
It's open.
It's going to be unbelievable.
People are going to be like...
Okay, imagine you're watching
television and
there's a commercial.
There's a hamburger
and there's my music.
It's going to be juicy
and there's going to
be a hamburger and
my music and people
are going to hear the
music and they're going
to be like, "I love
this music. I need
a juicy hamburger!"
Is that exciting to you?
Listen to me.
She doesn't care about
the hamburger or my music.
I'm really proud of you.
You love it. Really?
Are you proud?
Yeah, I think
it's a really great first step.
Yeah.
First step to what?
To the participation
of the wellbeing
of your family.
That's great.
I don't know,
maybe we could move.
What?
Oh is that...
- I didn't know... What'd you say?
- So absurd.
No, what'd you say?
No, I just said
maybe we could move.
You know?
Yeah, move right.
- You know I make a little money.
- You make a little money.
Well just because I work for Burger Mama
doesn't mean I want to be a property owner.
I understand that.
I just thought
maybe we were moving
past some of these
infantile notions of...
Oh, man. Come on.
- Capitalism.
- Really?
What?
Right. You
should read GTTP.
What is GTTP?
You know what it is.
Give to the People.
If you read it you would see...
I give to the people.
You give to the people?
Yeah.
What would make
me happy would be
to spend some time
with my family
and hang out with...
Yeah.
Hi.
Hey. Look.
How are you?
Hey, what's going on?
Nothing
special. How about you?
You're very dressed up.
Yeah.
We're going to a family thing.
Cool. I love family things.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Do you like this kangaroo?
Is it sweet?
It's soft.
Look, he likes her.
PS1 that's great.
Does that mean you're staying?
Yes.
Actually a week or two.
Would it be possible by
chance to crash on your
couch a few more days?
Yeah, sure.
Woops.
Excuse me.
Sir!
Would you fill up for me please?
Put it on. Put it on.
You hear me?
Yeah?
Would you fill up for me please?
What the
hell are you waiting for?
I don't have all goddamn
night. Move your ass.
Finally!
No. Don't film me.
Please, please, please.
Thank you.
Here.
No, no, no.
He paid for it.
They're here. Hello.
Shabbat Shalom.
This is our friend Lilas.
Hi Lilas.
- Hi, Mary.
- Hi Jacob. How are you?
Mary! You
don't feed him or what?
Doesn't she feed you?
- Nice to meet you Lilas.
- She barely feeds me.
Oh, what have you got there?
What is that?
This is a box for you.
It's a hat box.
Well, what do you think?
- Do you think it's for you?
- Is it for me?
Okay, it's for you.
- Do you know what it is?
- Neither do I?
Here we
go. Look at that.
Oh wow! Oh my God!
Oh, it's so elegant and big.
Where will I wear it?
I'll wear it to...
Oh the ladies in the
mahjahonng club will...
Wait until they
see, and it's pink.
- What do you think?
- My favorite.
Let's see it.
We celebrate the seventh day
of rest and family reunion.
You cannot have any
activities that relate
to work.
Okay. Like what?
It means you can't
handle money, you
can't handle fire.
And that's why people
who are late who are responsible
for us having a cold meal
tonight and no smoking.
Are those for me?
That's really beautiful.
You know it's your
birthday next week.
We're going to have
a big party for you.
Do you know how old
you're going to be?
Four!
Wow!
You're a big girl now?
So big.
She's going to school next year.
Why does she have to go to school?
Look how well she draws.
And she makes music too.
She learns a lot with her daddy.
Listen.
School is bullshit.
Parents who don't care
for their children
well they just send
them to school.
So, how is your music going?
Well if you guys want to know
the honest truth I
am going to record
an album.
What?
An album really?
Oh that's great.
I'm just
joking. Stupid.
That's not great.
But actually
he's composing music
for a commercial.
Yeah,
yeah. A commercial.
Isn't that going to interfere
with working on your own music?
It's going to be for hamburgers.
I'm going to make juicy music
for juicy non Kosher hamburgers.
Oh, that's terrible.
You're going to lose
your creativity.
Don't do it!
It's a very, very creative job.
It's a very creative job.
Commercials are evil.
You should all be talking to...
What do you want me to draw?
You know anything
you want sweetheart.
And it's bringing good
money. So that's great.
Come on. Let's go.
Well, that's your business.
Well he isn't a child.
He can hold down a job like the rest of us.
He works.
He has a lot to
do with his music.
What do you want a drawing of?
Can you draw me a house?
Sure I can.
Okay.
Thank you.
What does Leeward really mean?
Oh Grandma, come on.
I told you a million
times, come on.
I know you did, but my brain
is old and I'm
just getting older.
Anyway, I have a little
something for you.
Okay?
Here.
My favorite
candy. Thank you.
Yeah, well it's not all.
I have something else.
I know it's Sabbath
and I know I should not
handle money, but you need it.
So, I felt justified.
It's $2000. It's all
I had, but I hope it's
going to be enough
to keep you from
making that commercial.
Grandma this is too much, $2000.
This is too much money.
No, no, no.
It is what I was
going to leave you
as your inheritance,
but I may not be dead
but I maybe around a
longer time than I thought
and you need it now.
All right. Okay.
Hey Jacob, dinner is ready.
Okay.
Dinner's ready.
Leeward, come on in.
We're ready to it.
I'm sorry,
but I just don't think I can do it.
Then the tight
rope walker took off
his shoes gingerly
but unceremoniously.
He climbed up again, took
a step, lost his balance
and fell, but he knew
how to fall, like a cat.
Eventually he climbed
the rope and took a step
and then started dancing
from foot to foot
to the applause
of the onlookers.
He got to the end, he
turned around, danced
back to where he
started and he finally
agreed to reveal his secret.
He told them I keep
my eye on where I'm
going, but never
think of falling.
And then he said, "You
know what the hardest
part is? The hardest
part is turning around
because when you
turn around you lose
sight of your goal for a second.
The hardest part
is turning around."
Amen.
Mom wee-wee.
Okay.
Okay, wait for me.
You all right?
I'm sorry I hit you in the eye.
She got it in her eye.
Here's some water.
No, keep your eye closed.
No, she needs to put some
water on her.
Mom wee-wee.
No, it happened to your father
once and he was told
keep the eye closed.
She can't stay with her eye
closed all night.
Yes, she can.
It's almost bed time.
One eye open, one eye closed.
What difference does it make?
Keep it closed.
Mom, wee-wee.
All right.
Your eye feeling any better?
Yeah, it's fine.
Wee-wee.
Come on. Wee-wee.
I'm really fed up
with your family though.
If you don't start
asserting yourself,
Benjamin, they're
just going to keep
treating you like a child.
Here we go.
Come on. Wee-wee.
Wee-wee. Wee-wee. Wee-wee.
There is a game we play where
I blow on her like a
dandelion and she falls.
She falls onto the
bed in one piece.
Small people can fall that way.
Yesterday she said
wechother instead of
each other.
I don't think I'll correct her.
She, he, we chother.
Oh. Woo!
Surprise.
Surprise me?
But I thought it
was your birthday?
It is.
Happy Birthday birthday girl!
I can't believe
she's four years old.
Can you believe
she's four years old?
No.
Time goes so quickly.
Yes, no.
You're such a big girl.
Pretty soon you're going to
have to have your own bedroom.
Time for a triple cuddle.
Get over here.
Triple cuddle.
All for you.
What did you make me?
Toast, orange juice and tea
and a banana.
I thought that was a telephone.
A telephone
banana. Okay?
Hello? Yeah,
no the birthday
girl is right here. Hold on.
- It's for you.
- Oh, hello?
How the commercial is going?
It's like it goes...
Hamburger!
Hamburger.
Hamburger time.
It goes hamburger.
Tell him that it
sounds good so far.
It sounds good so far.
Well thank
you. Thank you.
Tell Daddy it's for him and ask
him why he never
wrote mommy a song.
- It's for you.
- Hello?
Why didn't you
never wrote mom a song?
Maybe I
have. Maybe I haven't.
Okay. Have they paid you?
The commercial?
They gave me $1000.
When are they going to pay you
the other $4000?
Soon.
Soon like this week?
Well, the $1000
is just an advance.
But they like the music, so...
I have a surprise for you.
- For who?
- For you.
What is it?
I can't tell
you. It's a surprise.
Will you meet me
tomorrow at 4:00?
Meet me outside the hospital.
Really?
That sounds weird.
Kind of.
You're being mysterious.
Will you do it?
Yeah we'll be there.
- I'm late.
- Yeah? Wait.
Bye, bye.
What do you want to do today?
Listen! I have the
most important thing
I have to tell you.
I have to tell you
something very, very...
No I'm serious.
This is going to save your life.
You're not listening.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm sleeping.
Okay. Goodnight.
Hey.
Hey, how's it going?
Oh is that the project?
- Yes.
- Oh, that looks nice.
Thank you.
How you feel?
I think that I'm
pretty happy with it.
That's cool.
Can you watch Rainbow?
Yes, of course.
All right. Thank you.
Bye, see you.
Lila, it's mom.
I need you to call
me right away.
It looks like you're still
buying that PS1 crap.
Being an artist is not
that easy, you know?
Some buy led you on
and you fell for it.
You know what?
I'm canceling my appearance in Berlin
because of you.
I'm coming to that MoMa thing
and I'm bringing you home.
Leeward did you say?
Yeah.
- That's an unusual name.
- Yeah.
- Well anyway, how are you?
- Yeah wow.
- Check it out.
- Cool.
- It's a nice place, right?
- Yeah.
Anyway, this is why you want
to come to a studio,
all this kind of gear.
So we have a good
selection of mics.
Yeah.
We have old back there.
We have all kind of...
- Can I see this?
- Yeah, go ahead.
It's a tube mic.
- What's this?
- It's a powerful mic.
It's a tube mic.
We've got all the mics
you're going to need.
Believe me.
Here we've got a
piano, keyboards.
We've got a B3.
This was at Woodstock
with Sly Stone.
Knock yourself out.
We've got Annie Lennox
and Dave Stewart in here all the time.
Wow.
Yeah, he
lives around the corner.
All these people
pretty much recorded
here and live in
the neighborhood.
Really?
- The Eurythmics?
- Yeah, Annie Lennox?
- The Cars?
- Yeah, absolutely.
Ric Ocasek. Yeah.
Whoa.
What do you think? Sounds good?
Yeah.
If you need any drums
I'm here for you.
- I have funny drums.
- Okay.
Electronic funny drums.
All right, sure.
Well we can make that happen too.
- You know Gigi Allen?
- No.
I... used to play with him
when I was a kid.
- Who is it?
- This guy was like an outlaw punk.
Yeah.
He was supposed to kill
himself on stage.
What are these his teeth?
This is his real teeth.
When I was a kid I
used to play with him.
He took a mic and
smashed his teeth.
I picked it up and
my friend made a necklace out of it.
Anyway, we've got a lot
of history in this place.
It should make you...
Take it in and use
it for your recording
and make it what you want.
So $999.
Okay, and so I've got cash.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's what I accept.
US is good too.
I have all this cash.
It's already ready to go.
Okay. All right.
All right.
I trust
you. I'll count it later.
I trust you.
Absolutely. No problem.
Don't be upset. It's
going to be all right.
It's going to be all right.
I'm excited.
All right here we
go. Let's do it.
Come out of there.
Get out of there.
Here we go dry you off.
Dry you off. Okay.
Are you ready? Are you hungry?
Yes. Yes.
Okay, okay. Here we go.
Guess what we're going to have?
We're going to have
guacamole. Are you ready?
Guacamole?
Guacamole. Guacamole.
Guacamole.
Go, go, go, go.
Get dressed. Get
dressed. Here he comes.
Go get dressed.
Fernando, here he comes.
Your favorite food.
I can hear him
coming up the stairs.
Your favorite food.
Come on here he comes.
I can hear him
coming up the stairs.
Here he comes!
Come on! Here we go! Here we go!
Woo! Woo!
Oh he's almost here.
He's almost here.
Here comes your food.
Hey.
Hi. Is Shiraz here?
No.
You don't happen to know
where Lilas lives?
Um, no I don't.
Can you have Shiraz
give this to her?
From Leo.
Shiraz to give this to Lilas.
- I see. Okay.
- Please.
- Oh, Fernando.
- Hi. For deliver.
It's 15 bucks.
Will you give this to him?
Will you give this to Fernando?
Give that to him.
Tell him to keep the change.
Keep the change.
Thank you.
Have you guys eaten?
Fernando, have you eaten?
Not yet.
Nothing special.
The free special.
Yeah.
It wouldn't just
fly to us by itself.
Right.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
- Thank you very much.
- Okay.
Bye.
I need to speak to.
Hi.
Just one second.
Si, si.
Hold on one second. Okay?
I just... Let me.
I don't care that he's
in a fucking monastery in Bergamo.
I need to speak to.
Don't put me on hold.
Don't put...
Fuck!
What happened?
The snake died.
One of the mice must
have had a disease
or something.
I'm sorry.
Listen, just put that there.
I'll call you as soon as
I handle all this. Okay?
Don't worry about anything.
Everything's going to be fine.
No, si, si. Por favor
okay?
- I need to speak...
- Good luck.
Thank you, bye.
I need to speak to
. Okay?
Just put somebody
on the phone that
speaks English. Okay?
Rainbow!
Daddy. There's Lilas.
- Oh hey.
- Hey. Hi.
Hey, how's it going?
How are you?
Good how are you?
Good. Where
are you going?
Come on Daddy.
We're just well...
You want to go in the fish shop?
I guess we're going
in the fish shop.
- How'd it go?
- I don't know.
No, they're going to love it.
You think so?
Yeah, they're
going to love it. I bet.
Wow. Do you
see all these fish?
They're like you.
They're rainbows.
How does it do with its mouth?
Wow, what is this backpack?
This is very cool.
My dad made it for me.
Really?
It has headphones and speakers.
Wow.
So I can listen
to my dad's music.
To what?
She said Justin Bieber.
- You know him?
- Seriously?
- Justin Bieber.
- That's not what she said.
Hey. Wow
look at these fish.
I want that one.
- Which one?
- That one.
This one?
I want that one.
Okay, wait,
wait, wait. I got it.
Seriously, are
you going to do it?
No, no.
Hey, could you come
here for a second?
Is he going to record?
I was just wondering how much
this fish costs.
The orange one with
the wierd head there.
That one 50 dollars.
The small one.
How much is that one?
This one 20.
Okay. Look at that one.
No, I want that one.
I know, but
this one is 20 dollars.
Just look into his eyes.
I think this one
was born for you.
I want that one.
You see that one?
You see how pretty it is?
It's a princess fish,
so try this one.
You like this one?
Let's get this one.
- We got this one.
- No, I want that one.
You see how his
head is shaped strange?
No, I want that one.
Let's just say you'd make
somebody very happy if you...
How about 25 dollars?
50 dollars.
Charging people 50 dollars
for this tiny little fish
that you got for free in the ocean
and then you bring it here
and you put it in
this cage of water,
and then you expect
people to spend 50 dollars
on this small,
little, tiny fish.
Fish 50 dollars.
You don't want to pay
you catch yourself.
All right. Okay.
So you're sure it's 50?
- 50 dollars.
- Okay. Let's see.
Okay, wait a minute here.
Here, that's 50 bucks.
Actually can I
get a 10 for that?
Thank you.
Actually can I get
two fives for this?
And just maybe...
There, that makes 20.
Thank you. Sorry.
Wait actually can I just get...
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Can I get one five
and five ones?
Thank you. This is
perfect. Thank you.
- Now get out.
- Perfect.
You're making us very happy.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I gave him ten dollars
and then I got 50 more.
- So, I made 40 dollars.
- Hey, whoa.
That's crazy?
How did you do that?
I have an infallible strategy.
Oh. What strategy?
Well, it's a secret.
It's a big secret.
I can't tell you.
Do you hear that?
Gosh, that's driving me nuts.
Okay, how are we doing?
Are we almost there?
Hey Ruth, how are you doing?
Almost ready.
Okay. All
right. We will.
Okay bye.
Surprise!
Happy little birthday girl.
This is chill Phil.
Hello.
A new friend.
How are you everyone?
Happy, happy birthday to you.
Happy, happy
birthday to Rainbow!
I'm Rainbow and you're Maggie.
No. I'm Maggie and
you're Rainbow.
Yes. That's what I said.
No, that's what I said.
Besides I'm the only princess.
No, I'm a princess too.
Hey Rainbow. How are you?
Good.
All right get in.
Hi.
I hear that parents
that take baths
with their children,
it helps the children's
creativity.
- Is that from Give to the People?
- Yeah, Give to the People.
This guy Joseph White.
Whoa. Here, you have these.
This guy Joseph White
in 1976 he wrote that.
And what is
Leeward going to write?
- What am I going to write?
- Yeah.
I don't know yet.
I still have to
finish reading it.
I've got 15 more pages.
Do you have an idea?
No, not yet.
Ask her to come with us.
Can you come with us?
Where are you going?
Through the ditch, past the pool
where we met after school.
Past the hotel
you're aloof where we
threw shit off the roof.
And those radiators in
the junkyard, they're
all runaways.
Got straight up and ran away.
In the tower on the
hills, just a relic from
the old days.
Let's pretend that
we're runaways.
we're radiators.
Let's pretend that
we're runaways.
Hey, this is
Leeward leave a message.
Hi honey. It's me.
I'm here. I'm waiting
for you. I don't know
where you are, but
I'm just going to go
directly there so meet
me directly at this
address, 57 Rosarie Street.
It's in Jersey City.
Okay?
Okay, I'll see you.
I know you'll be
very happy in this house.
Thanks, you have my
numbers call any time.
Thank you.
Mary, it's good to see you.
So there's a lot of interest?
Oh, yes. Good people.
They love this place, but
they haven't put their
name down on anything so
it could still be yours
if you haven't
changed your mind.
No, no, no. Of course not.
I'm just waiting for my husband.
He should be here any second.
You know I'm just
going to call him.
He's been working so
hard on that commercial.
He should be here any second.
I understand.
I do need to see a client.
They're only five minutes away.
So if you don't mind
I'll just go take care
of that and I'll be right back.
Hopefully your husband
will be here too.
Would it be all
right if I were to wait
inside?
Sure. Door's unlocked.
I'll be right back.
- That was awesome. Yeah.
- Oh thanks. I really like your music.
- You did a great job.
- Really?
Yeah.
Thank you. Yeah. I like this studio.
It's awesome.
Tell some other people and come
by and do some more too.
Thank you.
I'll have
your CDs in about an hour.
An hour? Okay.
Yeah, so just come back
in like an hour.
Great, all right thanks.
See you later.
So you guys want to get ice cream
or something for an hour?
Ice cream?
Okay, I'll see you.
What do you want to do?
Well, I don't
want to lose this house.
I'm aware of that.
I have a good feeling about you.
Now, I'm not
supposed to do this,
but this is what I propose.
You pay half of the
first payment right now.
I'll hold the house
for you for two days.
Now in a couple of days
if you change your mind
the house goes back
on the market and you
lose your deposit.
It's the best deal I have.
Let me just...
Let me just call
him one more time.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
It's my only offer.
I do have to go to
another meeting.
Okay, what do I do?
Okay, so that's a yes.
I need you to sign right here.
All right I will
need a check from you
for real estate.
All right 6% of
119,000 divided by...
That will be $3570.
Okay.
You did it.
Congratulations.
Now you can listen to...
Does it work?
Want some?
Free CDs.
Giving them away.
Hot. Hot. Hot.
Free CDs.
Free CD for you.
CDs. Free CDs.
CDs. CDs. Free CDs.
Free CDs.
Hey, are you coming to
Shiraz's bar for the open mic?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, hey. Don't
tell your mom about
the CDs okay?
Okay.
Hi.
Allo?
Hi, Adam. How are you?
Oh, wait a second I
can't hear you very well.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. I mean...
I was waiting for
you for a while.
Why? What do you mean?
Because of...
Oh.
You forgot obviously.
The surprise
day. Oh. Sorry.
Ted called and I had to go.
The client was unsatisfied
so there was a problem
so I had to go fix the problem.
I had to go over
there. I'm sorry.
What do you mean the
client was unsatisfied?
He was just unsatisfied.
But they're
going to pay you right?
I don't think so.
It didn't sound like it.
They have to pay you if you've
done the work. You
have to get paid.
The client's
unsatisfied with my music.
Yeah, it doesn't
matter if they like
your stuff or are happy with
it or not happy with it.
If you did the work
you have to get paid.
So call him.
Right?
Yeah. That's
what I'm saying I
just talked to him.
I was just there.
I talked to the guy.
I talked to them.
Let me talk to them.
- There's no reason for you to call him.
- Yes there is.
First of all, I know Ted.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to call him up?
And I just think I'm better at handling
these matters than you.
You want me to call him
and chew him out in front of you.
- Is that what you want me to do?
- Yeah. I want you to...
All right. I got
it. I got it. I got it.
Go, go, go, go.
Jeez.
Do whatever you're doing.
Ted, it's Leeward.
I'm just calling
you about the money
situation.
Yeah, I mean I understand that
the client's unsatisfied
but I still don't understand
the part where I
am not getting...
Paid for
the hours that you put in.
I'm not getting paid for all
the hours that I
worked and put in.
I mean no, I know you
don't like the music.
I worked very hard on it.
That's not the point.
Sorry.
- Let me talk.
- No, no, no.
No, I know him Benjamin.
Let me talk to him. Stop it.
Okay, listen.
I'm not going to
work with you if
you act like this.
This is not a fucking joke.
It's not a fucking joke.
You motherfucker.
See nothing worked.
He said the
commercial's canceled.
It's completely canceled.
So he's not going
to pay me at all.
That's insane.
- The whole thing is canceled.
- What?
The whole thing's canceled.
What do you mean
the whole thing is canceled?
That's what
he said? Yeah, anyway.
Oh well.
I need you to
get that money somehow.
Can you not do that for a second
and have this
conversation with me?
Okay, what do you want to talk about?
I just need you to...
I'm sorry.
It doesn't sound like it's my fault.
I don't know whose fault it is,
but I know that you had
a job and that you worked
and I'm telling you.
I don't feel like
you're hearing me,
but we really need that money
because I did something.
The best thing we can do is just
pretend that the commercial never existed.
Right?
You have an idea that
we have this money that we don't have.
What are you going to say?
There's nothing you can say.
He's not a good person.
Just don't talk to him.
Let me see this.
Stop it.
Okay. Don't get mad.
The commercial,
I wasn't even going to do the commercial.
I never did the commercial.
What? What?
- Don't get mad.
- I'm not mad!
Look at me you're getting mad.
You're getting mad.
I'm not mad.
I'm trying to understand
what the fuck is going on?
What do you mean you
didn't do the commercial?
Don't touch me right now.
- Did you lie to me?
- No.
Yes, you did.
I was under a lot of pressure.
I don't care
what kind of pressure.
- Stop it.
- Oh, come on.
You're being...
Don't do this in front of her
Come on.
Okay, this can't
happen any longer.
You have to go.
- What are you doing?
- She has to go.
- You know what?
- Yeah right...
This fucking book has to go.
Yeah right.
You want me to go do this commercial?
Yes, I can't believe
that you lied to me
about this that you...
Hold on. Just give me a second.
I'm sorry.
What?
Mommy, why isn't my fish moving?
Oh, wait,
wait, wait. Honey.
Oh God.
Where you going to go?
Hey it's Adam.
You know how much I
liked your project.
I tried talking to them.
I'm really sorry.
The committee felt
like it lacked originality.
I mean maybe if your
mother could intervene
they might listen to her.
Lilas?
Man hanging upside Hey Lilas.
Long time no see.
Hey.
Come in. It's open.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
A little what?
Hi. I got your letter.
I'd like to say
that I'm sorry for
the way I left.
What do you want?
I don't know.
You want to leave again?
You love me?
You want to be an artist?
You want to be an animal?
You want to be safe?
You want to be pretty?
You want to love me?
You want to leave?
You want to be tied up?
You want to be let go?
Why are you still painting that?
Because I love this painting.
And who's that girl?
Christina, from
Hungary, is lovely,
but she wouldn't be here
if you didn't leave.
Yeah.
And you're still
here. Look at who it is.
Yeah, I guess I should go.
- Why?
- Why did you come?
I don't know. Bye Leo.
Hi.
What's up?
Where is Leeward?
I don't
know. He didn't show.
Why?
I don't know. He's
supposed to go on at nine.
We had to put someone
else in front of him.
That bitch.
That's fantastic.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
PS1 found my art shitty.
I'm so sorry.
My visa is going
to expire in two days,
but I'm really
fine. Can't you see?
Don't put the fuck about
the visa. Okay?
Do like I did, okay?
I come here, I meet
this guy Pablo.
I sleep on his
floor for one year.
Nothing come from me. Okay?
You just overstay and rock on.
Rock on girl!
Do like me, I've
been fucked by Pablo
and all the other jankies in this pub,
but that's fine.
I don't need a visa for that.
That's great.
Give me the glass.
Rock on girl.
Okay, you need to stop.
Do you want to talk?
Lilas?
Well, I assume the PS1 thing
didn't pan out or you
would answer the phone.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Your message has been deleted.
New message.
Lilas, I asked
you to call me back.
I don't have any news,
I'm starting to worry.
So, callm e back.
Call me right away!
Your message has been deleted.
New message.
Lilas, it's very late in Paris.
I'm going to bed.
I'll be in New York tomorrow
for the MOMA retrospective.
I hope to see you there.
I miss you.
Hey.
Can you sing a song for me?
Please.
Yes.
Let's see...
Flashlights on the concrete,
today in every paper
we read that he never
made a sound, drove a
gentle boy from town.
So, latch the windows as
families take their rest
and she said this is how
I like the house the best.
- What are you...
- Come here.
What are you doing? Come here.
Come on. Lay down.
Come on. Here, here.
Just lay down okay.
Here. There you go. All right?
You should go to
sleep, all right?
Okay.
Hey.
Finish the song.
Flashlights on the concrete.
Today in every paper we read
that he never made a sound.
Drove a gentle boy from
town so latch the windows
as families take their
rest and she said this
is how I like the
house the best when all
I hear is nothingness.
Maggie, what kind
of pizza do you want?
Maggie!
I'm sorry. Can you
hold on one sec?
Hey!
Maggie.
Can you take your headphones off
for a second honey?
I'm talking to you.
Come on take these off.
Hey!
One at a time please.
Mister with the blue shirt,
what is your question?
- I
- don't mean to be rude,
but don't you think it's
a little bit too easy?
Do you think art can be
just one color or one plan?
How can you account
for the simplicity of your work?
You know, by letting the
untouched parts talk, I
allow reality to take over.
I merely act as a sort
of catalyst, a filter.
Do you understand?
I don't really understand.
What's the link
between emptyness
and reality?
Emptiness is filled by the face
and the voice of the Other.
You often refer to the
How would you explain your
relationship to the art.
Mrs. de Castillon?
The artist is irrelevant.
So is the piece.
What matters is what
emanates from it.
What people allow
themselves to see in it.
That's beautiful, but
concretely I mean...
What do you see?
Honestly?
First I see nothing.
Then a deep nothing,
and then if I really
try hard I can just
my out my shadow.
Interesting.
It speaks volumes
about your relationship
with reality.
Now if you'll excuse me.
Mrs.
Castillon says it's part
of the show.
Yeah, she'd like the
lights to be switched off.