Last week's sudden storm
is nothing new for the people...
Slow down, will ya?
Relax, Rob.
Easy for you to say.
You don't have Amelia Lewis
waiting for you back home.
Amelia Lewis, the Amelia Lewis?
-The one with the...
-Yeah.
Obviously we can't crash now.
We gotta get you back to Amelia Lewis.
You're just jealous.
-Did you hear that?
-The Curse of Marguerite has been blamed...
I think you broke something.
Then go check it out.
I'm not going to check it out! You broke it.
Go ahead in back, check it out.
You know what we're hauling?
You really think I'd let somebody put
something on my truck,
I didn't know what it was?
Do you know what's special about them?
You know what they are?
Yeah, I heard the same thing, too.
I don't believe any of it.
Pete said they shot them up with
a bunch of drugs and then they started...
Pete needs to learn to keep his mouth shut.
...of Marguerite's ghost.
Check it out!
What? Are you scared?
-I'm not scared.
-Amelia Lewis doesn't like scared boys.
Flood waters quickly receding
and meteorologists
reporting a beautiful
weekend forecast, though.
Just watch the road, okay?
If you're scared, just remember Amelia Lewis.
-I gotta get back to Amelia Lewis.
-Shut up, okay?
What in the world? What the heck is that?
Oh, man!
You did break something!
No.
What?
You did break something.
No! No!
Rob?
It's started.
No! No! No!
No! No! No! No!
Stay away from me! No! No!
No! No! No!
I now pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Yeah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present to you Mr. and Mrs. Hamilton.
Yeah!
Come on.
Cheers!
-Hi, how are you?
-Good. Wasn't it beautiful?
It was beautiful.
I mean, it's been a long time coming, huh?
-Those guys are great.
-They're great together.
Oh, my God! So happy for you.
It was so beautiful. Let me see. Let me see.
I'm so happy for you guys. It was amazing.
I'll be right back. So happy for you.
-Hello, darling.
-Hi.
You didn't have to come to her wedding.
You kidding me? This is great.
Let's get away for the day.
I got plans this weekend.
I was gonna hole myself up in my room
and listen to Lionel Richie and cry.
Come on.
Remember when we were kids and our folks
would always take us and Bryce out...
Chris, I'm so sorry. I'm such an idiot.
When's the last time we were out
at the point together?
I haven't been there in a long time, Ash.
Place doesn't exactly conjure up
good feelings for me.
Yeah, but, I mean, we should go.
I go out all the time,
and Ian's got his family boat for the day.
I don't want to hang out with Ian.
He hates me.
Please! Come on, Chris.
Sam's going, of course. Kerri will be there.
-You trying to set me up right now?
-It's not a set-up.
I don't need a pity date, Ash.
It's not, you'd be doing me a favor.
Ian always gets so plastered
every time we go out on the boat.
If you guys don't come, he's just gonna
want to mess around the whole time.
And I want somebody who can
actually carry a conversation, you know?
You got problems in paradise?
No, just Ian's Ian.
You know how it is.
Frat parties were fun at first,
but, I mean, you gotta grow up sometime.
Please, please, please, please.
You have to come.
All right.
Okay, you will not regret this.
-I regret it already.
-I'm so excited.
Can you slow down, please?
I'm trying to be somber here.
Please tell me some good news.
So tell me, Hutch, those tech guys
that called this in, were they right?
Looks like it.
On a scale of one to ten,
one being, "Let's go get some coffee."
Ten being,
"How do you want to spend your last night
on earth," what are we looking at?
Ten? Looks more like a 20.
That's what I was afraid of.
"Specimen 0," what's that?
I don't know, but whatever it was,
it was a lot bigger than the others.
You shouldn't be out here!
Unless you prepared for what you might find!
Better get back, sir! It's not safe just yet!
No! No!
The danger just getting started!
It's gonna be
one of those backwater towns, huh?
Salvage what you can.
I want an expanding perimeter on the swamp.
Yes, sir!
Hey, Chris, it's me.
Why don't you give me a call?
I'm just thinking about you.
I told her, "Look, honey, Trevor is my man."
Yes, I did.
I told her that she lost her chances with him
that last night at bingo,
and that if she didn't like it, well,
then I'd be happy to walk on over there
and shove my foot right up...
Morning, Marge.
Marge! Marge!
Will you get that damn hearing aid fixed?
-Lucille.
-Ranger Hardin.
You know, that Davids boy was out
past my property the other night
blasting his dynamite again.
Yeah, well,
I'll go have a little talk with him, then.
Well, you best head on down to the dock,
then, 'cause he's there right now.
And I hear Chris is with him.
My Chris?
This is Specimen number five.
-Is that the last one?
-No, I got a few more to collect.
-Do you hear that?
-Yeah.
-We should go check that out.
-All right, come on.
-Did you hear that?
-I did.
-It's over there.
-Let's go.
All right, let's do this.
I'm excited, and you?
-Yeah, I know.
-You know I am excited.
I know, Chris, Chris, Chris,
that's all you talk about.
Yeah, well, we haven't done this in so long.
Just hang back with the boat,
I gotta go find Chris.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, partner, there's some good-lookers
down in the swamp today, eh?
Drop dead.
Make me wish I was 20 year younger.
Oglin' the coeds again, boys?
Sorry, Ranger Hardin.
Just enjoying the Blackbriar sights.
Hey, Chris, you made it!
Hi!
Chris.
Hey. Fun.
Don't worry about him, you're here with me.
Hey, Ashley! How are you? Good to see you.
Chris, what's up?
Right this way, dear wench.
-Shut up.
-What?
Hey, Chris, like my new swimsuit?
It's cute, thank you.
You need help with the beer
or anything like that?
Come on, let's go.
You chuckin' your line today, Brutus?
Sure. You want us to bring you back a big,
old gator head?
You can hang it on your wall?
You get brave on us, Sheriff,
come out on gator water with us, huh?
Chipmunk said
you should come out to the boat with us.
Well, maybe sometime I'll surprise you,
but in the meantime,
be careful and watch the drinking, huh?
Yeah, don't be so scared.
So you actually went to that wedding.
What a loser.
-Sucker.
-Stop it.
It was a sweet gesture.
A true gentleman can admit
when he's been defeated.
Yeah, but what loser
wants to be a gentleman?
Stop it. Stop.
If this is going on all weekend,
I'll shoot somebody.
Hey, Ranger Hardin.
Hey, Ashley.
Mom. I'll be right back.
Just wait up.
Mom, what are you doing here?
I have been calling your cell phone for days!
I've been busy, Mom. I'm sorry, okay?
So, how was the wedding?
I mean, I thought maybe
you'd want to talk afterwards.
It was fine. Whatever, I don't care.
It was nice.
Is that the Davids' boat?
Yes.
My office has gotten a few calls
about Ian doing some dynamite fishing.
Now, I haven't caught him yet,
but if I do catch him and whoever he's with,
they're gonna be in some big trouble,
so I'm hoping that is not what
you were planning on doing this weekend.
No, we're just going out
to have some fun, all right?
It's not a big deal, it's innocent, okay?
Okay, you just be careful.
That swamp, it can be mean.
Dad told me that you filed the other day.
I thought you were
gonna try to patch things up.
Honey, it's not that simple.
And are you sure that this is
the right move for you guys?
-Christopher, honey.
-It's fine. It's fine.
Kerri Ponter, is that you?
Yes, ma'am.
-Does your grandma know you're here?
-Mom.
-Are you nuts?
-What?
She's underage for drinking
and you're dragging her out
-to your wild orgy.
-She's not drinking.
Wild orgies, what are you talking about?
Where do you get this stuff from?
-Do you think she'll call my grandma?
-No.
We're just going out on the boat
to have a little fun on the water.
Man, come on. You coming? I'm shoving off.
-All right, I gotta go.
-Wait, wait.
-I gotta go.
-Wait, wait, wait, listen...
Honey, I really want to hang out with you, so,
how about I make you some dinner,
something like that?
Maybe. Yeah, no, that'd be nice. I'd like that.
-Let's do it. I'll talk to you.
-Okay.
Be safe.
Au revoir, Ranger!
Be careful out there.
I like her!
Can't stop us now, we're going!
We're going over this way.
Let's head back to the station.
Yes, ma'am.
I tried to hold you off, but you keep pushing.
These people,
they ain't the ones hurting you.
No!
Haven't you been in pain long enough?
Let it go.
What's it gonna take for you to be satisfied?
It's war, then.
Keep going, it's right up there.
Who got it better than us, Brutus?
Every day a good day in the swamp.
Even bad day a good day in the swamp.
You got that right, my friend. That's all true.
How much further
until we get to that other line?
We should be there by now.
Hush, hush, looky there.
Looky there.
That's a big, old gator track there.
Yeah, yeah, I think we coming up
on something big, man.
We got him on the run, too,
the way that line is all tight.
Come on, let's get in there and get him.
-Y'all want fish for dinner?
-We don't have any poles, though.
-Oh, my God!
-Here you go. Here you go.
Yeah, baby.
Everybody, lunch is almost ready! Lunch!
Y'all want to fish first?
What a day, what a day...
She big like pig, where she go...
Brutus, what's this?
Hey! Anybody there? Are y'all hurt?
We're gonna have
to call this in to Ranger Hardin.
Hey!
Hey?
Marge!
Damn it, Marge,
would you turn up your hearing aid?
Blackbriar Parks and Recreations,
this is Ranger Hardin speaking.
Hey, Brutus. Did y'all get me
that gator head you promised me?
All right, I'm gonna assume that you're
sober while you're giving me this report,
so was it a pick-up or a semi?
No, it's a delivery truck,
ran into a tree stump.
Right.
Yeah, there's white containers in the water.
There's more on the ground laying on a tarp.
There's more in the back of the truck,
there's some blood.
Blood?
This truck, it's got blood all in it.
There's more containers in there,
big container, too, that's all busted open.
Yeah, I thinkin' Marguerite
is getting pretty riled up.
Okay, you steer clear.
Matt and I are gonna come and check it out.
-What'd she say?
-She said steer clear.
They gonna come check it out.
Meanwhile, let's go find that line you lost.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Make-up's gonna come off
when you get in the water anyway, huh?
So, what happened with your mom?
-Nothing.
-Nothing?
Yeah, no, we're fine, it's good.
It's good, I'm just happy to be out here.
Having fun, I'm glad you invited me.
-Yeah, I'm glad you're here.
-I am, I am.
-You're such a loser.
-All right, let's do it!
It's what y'all came here for, right?
Later!
Amazing!
Come on, you coming?
All right, I'm up.
It's perfect.
That is the only one-piece
I have ever enjoyed.
You sure you're okay
with the whole Kerri thing?
Yes, it's fine, it's stupid.
-She really likes you.
-That's... No, I'm not interested.
Do you have a lighter or a bottle opener?
Come on, get in!
-I don't know, y'all. I don't know about this.
-You're gonna drown me.
Come on, get in! The fish aren't gonna bite.
Okay, all right.
-I'm not a raft, you can't pull me down.
-Get off me.
Looks like little Miss Kerri Ponter grew up.
Shut up!
-Shut up.
-What? Look at her.
Come on, let's go! That's what we're here for!
-Are you sure you're okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
-You just seem a little...
-I'm fine, I'm having fun.
-Okay, I'm sorry.
-I'm having fun, and you know what?
-I'm jumping in. All right.
-Okay.
-Okay? I'm fine.
-Yeah.
-Have fun.
-Don't worry about me.
-I'm worried about you.
-Don't worry about me. I'm all right.
Sorry.
Come on! Get in! Get in, come on!
There you go!
The classic Prayer Dive, huh?
Very nice, hard-on.
Ash, get in! Let's go.
No, you guys, you guys have it.
Ashley! Ashley! Ashley!
Jump in my arms, baby!
How's the water down there?
Down! You're going down.
I found the line.
I told you there's another line out here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Here we go. Here we go.
Oh, yeah. That feel like a good one.
This be present for fair Ranger Hardin, huh?
I think she got crush on me.
-Here it comes, get ready! Get ready!
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-What did that?
-Haven't seen that before!
My God.
I dropped the line.
Easy, now.
It's tangled up.
Get your hand out of there.
Get your hand out of there!
-What's the matter?
-Get your hand out of there.
Get your hand out of there!
Brutus!
Do we have to really
walk through this swamp?
Come on, you big baby. I'll take care of you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So you can't really blame your mom.
I mean, I love your dad, but he's not very...
Attentive?
Yeah. He can get a little preoccupied.
And your mom's been really sad
for a long time, ever since...
Bryce. You can say his name, you know.
My dad's been so sad ever since
my mom left, it was really hard on him.
I mean, all of us, obviously,
but I just wish I knew how to help him.
You know, help both of them.
I don't know what to do.
Sometimes you can't help.
People grow apart.
It happens.
Why don't you just break up with him?
Because, I don't know, I'm just...
I'm so used to being us,
I don't know how to be me anymore.
I know who you are.
You're just a punk
with questionable taste in dudes.
You're such a jerk.
Fine, you're mildly decent, then.
This is nice.
I know, this is exactly what I want.
I want one.
No, try again in a couple of years,
when you're actually of age.
Really?
Just looking out for you.
You suck.
Whatever, you'll thank me eventually.
You okay?
It's like he doesn't even see me.
Kerri, Chris is actually
one of the good guys, okay?
You don't want to come off as easy.
Do that and you'll attract guys
like my old man or Ian.
-Trust me.
-Head's up, ladies!
-How did I know he was gonna do that.
-Oh, my God!
You're such an ass.
I ruined my back. Why, you got wet?
-Kerri, did you get wet?
-Ian!
Little Kerri kind of got wet, huh?
-Stop.
-You got wet?
Oh, Kerri! What are we gonna do?
Where is all this water coming from?
Where's it all coming...
Where's it all coming from?
Have a blast!
What?
Sam, come on.
Whatever. I'm over this. Have fun.
Really?
What's her problem? Is this her beer?
Yeah.
Where's your beer?
She doesn't let me have one,
but now that she's gone...
Boy, I sure am hungry for lunch.
I'll tell you that much.
Me, too. Look at right over there.
Yeah.
You think Marge got us something good?
I doubt it.
-No way, huh?
-No way, babe.
All righty, let me tie us up.
You need some help?
-I think I got it.
-Okay, good.
Let me grab you over here.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Thanks.
Watch your step.
-Thank you.
-Good job.
He wasn't lying.
Looks like we got a big, old truck
crashed in our swamp, Carly.
Yeah, we sure do.
I wonder what they were hauling.
Think it could be toxic waste or something?
I don't know, but obviously
an investigation has been started.
Somebody should be here.
Where the hell is everybody?
Blackbriar Curse strikes again.
-Right?
-That's not funny.
Sorry, I'm just saying, this is crazy.
Great, now I gotta make phone calls
all afternoon to try and figure out this mess.
Isn't that Brutus?
Yeah, probably got drunk
and fell asleep again.
Old moonshine.
Hey, Brute! Chip!
Why don't you go check out that cab.
I'm gonna check out that boat.
Copy you.
Brutus?
Chipmunk?
Oh, God! Brutus.
-What is it? What's wrong?
-Marge, Marge, it's Ranger Hardin, come in!
Marge! Damn it!
What did you see? What happened?
Matt! Stay away from the water!
Matt!
Matt! Matt! Matt!
I need help! Help me! Help! Help!
Matt! Matt!
Matt!
Chris?
Ashley?
Oh, my God, you creep! Don't do that!
What? Did you think
it was the Blackbriar Curse?
Old slump hag coming to get you.
-Shut up.
-What?
I thought you liked a little excitement.
Remember?
Are you crazy? Ashley's right over there.
Well, I mean, that makes it kind of hotter,
though, right?
No, it doesn't.
What?
That was a mistake, okay?
That's not how you felt before.
I was drunk, and it was stupid,
and you're a creep.
Come on, come here.
What are you gonna do?
Maybe I'll go see if Kerri wants to party, then.
Keep doing that,
and you can expect one of those
every day for the rest of your life, jerk.
You know what? You're right.
I'm having a really nice time out here.
-Good.
-This is good.
I can see why my brother loved it so much.
It's got a charm.
-I'm glad.
-I haven't been here in so long.
Don't give me that look.
Okay, fine. You want to talk about it?
Please!
Fine. The wedding, it was nice.
It was, she's happy, she looked great.
Her man is nice, which I hate.
I don't know, I'm happy for him. They...
I'm over it!
Sure you are.
Do not start with me like that.
Don't start what?
Don't start something you can't finish now.
Come on, you scared of a girl now? Let's go!
Come on!
Easy! Watch it!
Problem?
I'm not sure. Come on.
Sam?
Where are you guys?
Guys! Get off of me!
Something! Something out there!
-Sam! Get off of me! Help!
-Something out there!
-Kerri!
-Get off of her!
Kerri!
Come on, you okay?
-Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-Kerri!
Come on. Come on.
I got you. Come on, easy! Easy!
Something out there! Something out there!
We gotta leave! We gotta leave!
I want to get out!
No gator! No snake!
Easy!
-He's all covered in blood!
-What's wrong with him?
Probably just some drunk fool,
fisherman falling out of his boat.
I don't see any boat around, man.
We can't leave this guy here, okay?
We gotta take him somewhere.
Look at him!
What if he has a disease or something?
We gotta get this guy back to town.
Screw that, dude.
This dude is not getting in my parents' boat.
Ian, we have to get him to a hospital!
This bloody fool
is not getting in my parents' boat!
We're not gonna leave him here.
Now help me get him up.
Let's go! Right now!
-Come on, come on.
-I'm not helping, just get him up.
-All right, man, we got you.
-Just get on the boat, guys.
We got you. Come on, you're all right.
Thank you.
Come on, Ma. Pick up the phone.
Pick up the phone, Ma. Come on!
It's the one time I call her,
she's not answering.
There's no one at the station. I don't know.
We're gonna get home.
What's the hold-up here? Let's go!
Can we get him something to drink?
Something other than beer?
Here you go, old man,
this'll make you feel better.
No, no, no, go quick, quick, quick, get out!
Something out there I never seen!
Not gator, not snake, not fish! Too big.
One ate Brutus! It gobbled him gone!
Come back for us next.
Dead! Dead!
This old coot's not drunk, he's nuts.
Was there an accident?
Not accident, no, snakefish!
Ate Brutus dead! He dead!
Great, thanks a lot, Ash.
Exactly how I wanted to spend my weekend,
babysitting some old drunk.
Don't be an ass, okay?
It wouldn't hurt you
to think of someone else for once.
-Sam, it's okay.
-The hell it is, okay?
-Quit apologizing for him.
-All right, enough!
This isn't helping anybody.
Ian, you take me, Sam and Kerri back.
We'll take care of him, and you and Ashley
come back and have some fun.
No! I'm coming with you.
What?
Ian can have his boat all to himself.
What do you say, Kerri?
You want to stay here with me,
or do you want to go with them?
-Look at that! Look at that!
-What the hell's your problem, old man!
See? See? We got to kill them,
before they kill us all dead!
What is that? Fish?
What is that?
I've never seen so many of them.
-It's like a school of fish, right?
-What do they want?
Maybe they're hungry.
Let's throw Sam in and see...
-Oh, my God!
-Man, stop!
-I'm joking!
-We got to kill that thing!
-You're crazy!
-We got... They...
What are you talking about?
Nobody understands!
Idiot kids! Do something!
Don't even think about it, old man!
No, stop! Stop!
Are you all right?
-Back up!
-Mistake...
Kerri!
-Right here. I'm right here.
-I'm okay.
-You all right?
-Yeah, she's fine, everyone.
What is your problem?
Get...
-Kerri! Take her hand!
-Come on!
Come on!
Kerri! Kerri! Kerri!
Help! Somebody help...
-Kerri? Kerri, get out!
-What happened?
Kerri! No...
-Get us out of here!
-Yeah.
Oh, my God!
Where's Kerri? What happened?
They killed the motor.
Oh, no, we got to leave.
We got to go, not safe.
The engine's dead. We're stranded.
Marguerite,
I didn't want to have to do this.
Where are you?
Marge, I need you to make a call!
Ranger Hardin?
And you are?
I'm Trooper Mark Simon
with the Louisiana State Police. Can I...
-Carly?
-Jim...
Thank God! Are you okay? What happened?
Ranger Hardin, can I talk to you in private?
Anything you have to say to her,
you can say in front of me. I'm her husband.
Ex-husband.
Soon to be ex-husband.
It's complicated, forget it.
Let's go, you guys.
-All right, guys, ready?
-Yeah.
Ready, hut.
One Mississippi, two Mississippi,
three Mississippi.
So what the hell is going on in Blackbriar?
Early this morning, a delivery truck
carrying a cargo of Channa micropeltes
crashed down by 8-Mile Ditch.
Snakeheads?
They're indigenous to Southeast Asia,
but they're not found in Louisiana.
I teach at the community college,
a biology professor...
Associate instructor.
I mean, tenure is so very political...
Point is, I know my fish.
Channa micropeltes is...
Well, it's the most aggressive
of the snakehead species.
No kidding.
Well, there have been infestations
in the States before,
but usually it's some yahoo gets a couple
as pets and decides to dump 'em in the river.
Did you know that it only takes them
two years to reach maturity
and that a fully grown female adult
can lay as many as 15,000 eggs at a time.
It takes quite a lot to feed that many babies,
and it's not long before snakeheads
have wiped out all other marine life.
And we're a half day behind this.
There was an infestation in Maryland.
Now, the authorities caught the fish,
but the new R&D team decided
they wanted to sterilize it.
-What happened?
-When I got off the phone with them,
they were still figuring out
what was going on.
The serum they used made the fish
more aggressive, bolder and smarter.
Before long,
they could become the perfect predator.
Chris!
Chris is on the water with his friends!
-Use this.
-I don't know how to use this, Carly.
Just aim this at the man-eating killer fish,
and then you pull the trigger, okay? Do it.
Marge! Marge!
Marge, turn up your hearing aid. Okay, listen.
I want to quarantine the beaches
and the swamp until further notice.
I want everybody out of the water
and off the shore. Got it?
Closing off the swamp won't be enough.
He's right, snakeheads have kind of
an air chamber in their skulls
that can act as a makeshift lung.
They can breathe on land
for up to three days.
By using the muscles in their fins,
they can almost walk.
And that's just a normal snakehead,
without genetic modifications.
Who knows what
these snakeheads are capable of.
Three days' time,
they could have the whole town overrun.
My God! Nowhere is safe.
Here, I'm open!
Catch it! Yes!
Oh, my God! Let's get out of here!
It's okay, it's okay.
Just breathe, just breathe, just breathe.
It's okay.
Just breathe, just breathe. Just breathe.
It's gonna be okay.
-Would you let go of him?
-Get your hands off of me!
What the hell are those things?
What did you do?
-I do nothing!
-Leave him alone!
Ian, stop it! You're not helping anything!
You, we wouldn't even be out here,
if it wasn't for you.
You think I don't know why
we're all really out here?
-It's all about him.
-Me?
-It's always about him.
-Get over yourself.
Should just toss him overboard,
just like Kerri, right?
You son of a...
-Don't say that!
-Forget about it!
We have more important things
to worry about.
The lines are still busy.
Your dad doesn't have a radio on this boat?
Dad was supposed to fix it on Tuesday.
Of course he was.
Look, look! Looky there!
Maybe we're not all done for yet!
What is he saying?
Maybe God will not kill us, or what?
Look, look, see?
We gotta get to that house.
First good idea all day.
So what?
We get through the swamp
and then call for help?
Yeah, and who do we call
when there's a killer fish epidemic?
-What was that?
-The fish! The fish!
-They're everywhere!
-Oh, my God!
The fish are everywhere! They're coming.
The fish, they're coming back!
They're everywhere.
Just calm down!
We just have to work together.
-Get out of the way, Sam.
-Just calm down!
-Get away from me!
-Oh, my God! They're breaking through!
We are so gonna die out here.
We're not gonna die, all right?
We're gonna get to that house.
How? There's no way to kill these mother...
-Wait.
-What?
Dynamite. The rumors were true.
That's good.
I got you! I got you. I got you.
-Thanks, man.
-Yeah, no problem.
Yeah!
That's a good one. Yeah.
How you doin', little guy?
That's what I'm talkin' about.
You gonna make a good meal. Yes, you are.
You are such a big fish.
That's gonna be a good dinner.
Where's my cleaver?
I'm gonna kill something.
It was just here. Am I losing my mind?
Holy mackerel! Where'd he go?
He's gone? I just had it!
Do you remember when the boys were little
and we'd bring Bryce and Chris
down to the bayou?
Bryce would get up in the bow,
and start waving his arms like he was a bird.
-There's a lot of good memories.
-Jim, don't.
Look, I'm...
I took you for granted for a long time,
I realize that,
but I never stopped loving you.
We've already been through all of this.
We're different people.
We want different things.
I want us to be a family again.
What do you want?
We need to make sure
that everyone's safe near the water.
Wait a second,
I thought we were out here looking for Chris.
We don't have time to stop
and warn everybody up and down the bayou.
That's Jessup's boat.
Maybe he saw where Chris was headed.
Jessup?
Jessup!
It's Ranger Hardin
from Blackbriar Parks and Recreation. Here.
Oh, God!
It's twice as big as it was before.
I got this.
Jim, the safety's on!
What?
Watch out, Jim! Watch out!
Ranger, come on up. Hurry!
Come on.
What are you doing here, Mr. Boudreaux?
The swamp, she's angry.
Marguerite's up to her old tricks again.
You can't stay here. The swamp isn't safe.
It's not safe for none of us
until the swamp get paid...
...what she got coming.
All these years,
I tried to make her happy, but...
We really have to go.
When I give you the word,
you run like hell to the boat.
You need to go home.
We have to find her, Ranger.
She's the heart of this bayou.
You have to fight her.
Go home! Lock the doors and stay there.
Okay, are you ready?
Yeah, I think we've got
a clear path so far, so...
Run.
Give me the gun. You drive.
So, let me get this straight.
Not only do we have an infestation
of killer fish, but they're getting bigger.
If they sprout wings and fly, I'm done.
I don't know what they did
to these snakeheads, but it has cranked up
the evolutionary process
and kicked it into overdrive.
They are adapting at a far greater rate
than mother nature ever intended.
I don't know what
these researchers did, but...
Or it could be what William Boudreaux said.
It could be
the Curse of the Blackbriar Swamp.
God knows this swamp
has taken enough out of our family.
Carly, we'll find our boy.
We'll find Chris.
We gotta get rid of these things,
and we gotta make a run for it.
All right, I'll take some of the dynamite
with us, and you take the flare gun.
-Okay.
-Keep it in the bag, all right?
-Right.
-We gotta get out of here.
-All right, ladies, let's go.
-Where are we gonna go?
-We're going to that house.
-But they're gonna take us over.
No, they're not.
That's for Brutus, you damn snakefish!
Stick this where you live, Marguerite!
You stinking witch!
Are you actually insane, man?
You're gonna kill all of us!
Look out!
Let's move! Come on, let's go, let's go!
Come on. Come on.
Let's go. Come on!
-Come on.
-But the fish!
We still have to make it
through the whole swamp!
I'm gonna take care of you. Come on.
There you are.
Oh, Marguerite. What you done done?
Come on, keep going! Keep going!
-I can't.
-Don't stop!
Are you okay?
Are you all right, man?
Yeah.
Shoot it.
Come on, shoot it! Let's go! Come on!
Come on, man, shoot him!
-Doesn't work, great. Let's go.
-Come on!
Come on!
We got it beat! Come on! We need help!
-Please help us!
-Hello?
-Hello! Hello!
I don't see anybody.
-You see anybody?
-No, I don't see anyone!
Is it open?
Someone help us.
Come on, kick it in. We don't have time.
Hello? Is anyone here?
Come on, we gotta block these doors.
I don't see 'em anywhere, man.
There!
How are they crawling like that? They're fish.
I think they're growing.
They look bigger, too.
-Why?
-The Blackbriar Curse.
No, no, no. I don't believe that.
I don't care if it's the curse, or radiation,
or psycho fish from space,
we have to kill those things.
Ian's right, okay,
we gotta barricade the house.
We gotta make sure it's secure.
Look for weapons, axes,
a machete, a gun rack, whatever, okay?
We gotta close all the doors
and the windows.
Ian, check this room, okay?
I'm going this way.
Look, I don't remember making you leader.
Now we can work together,
but I'm not taking orders from you.
Ian! Just do it! Come on, I'll look with you.
Come on, let's get to work.
God, I hate this swamp.
I never should have stayed.
Why did you?
For you and Chris,
you both loved it so much.
Chris had his friends here, and I know
how much you admire your students,
and I thought if I were a ranger,
you know, I could help make things safer.
Keep something like what happened to Bryce
ever happening to anyone again.
You can't always stop the bad things
from happening, Carly.
I grew up hearing about that curse,
that curse, that curse.
-I never believed it.
-You can't blame a curse for what happened.
Bryce was... It was an accident.
Well, who can I blame, then, Jim?
Well, you seem to be doing
a fine job of blaming me.
I don't blame you.
Isn't that why you left me?
I told him he could go out
on the bayou that night with his friends,
after you told him he couldn't.
-It's my fault.
-Jim...
It's my fault. It's my fault.
Jim.
I don't blame you for hating me.
It's what I'd do.
Jim.
I've already lost too much, all right?
I can't stand to lose any more.
What's that?
That's Ian Davids' boat. Oh, my God! Chris.
What if Chris...
What if something happened to Chris?
No, no, Carly.
Carly, look, we're good, we're good.
I mean, look,
they might have swum ashore, huh?
Yeah. Okay.
-We're good, we're good.
-Okay.
Let's get in there and check it out.
Molotov cocktails.
We could throw them at them,
while we make a retreat.
You know, Bryce died two years ago.
Since then,
I thought a lot about how I might die.
Not one time did I ever consider killer fish.
We're gonna make it through this.
Kerri didn't, the old man on the boat didn't.
But we will.
Yeah, just stay here
and keep an eye on them, all right?
I'm gonna go look around just in case
the whole fire bomb thing doesn't pan out.
It would work.
Sam. Sam!
Come see.
What?
Oh, my gosh, what in the world is this?
Pretty freaky, right?
That's disgusting.
What's all this for, anyways?
Don't mess with it. It's like voodoo.
It stinks, is what it is.
-What was that?
-Grab that knife.
What?
Garage door's open.
I'm gonna have to close it,
before those things get in.
What if they're already inside?
There's a radio in there.
Okay, let's go.
We should probably go get Chris and Ashley.
Screw Chris.
Ashley probably already is.
-Shut up, go close the door.
-Don't push me.
Hello, is anybody there?
Hello, is anybody there? Please!
They're outside.
Hello, is anybody there at all?
Please, please!
If anybody's there, please respond!
They're inside. Hide! Hide.
Sam! Sam, help me!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Ian! Ian, wait! Ian! Ian!
Open the door! Ian, let me out!
Ian!
Let me out! Ian, let me out!
Choke on that, coward.
-You hear something?
-What was that?
-Come on!
-Wait!
We're sorry,
we didn't know anybody was home.
What are you doing here, gal?
The swamp, it ain't safe.
There were snakes outside,
and we were just trying to protect ourselves.
Swamp, she's angry this time.
Marguerite's gonna
get her vengeance tonight.
-What are you talking about?
-Curse of Blackbriar Swamp.
No, I refuse to believe that.
It's just a story.
There's no such thing as a curse.
That's where you're wrong, little gal.
Marguerite, she has her ways.
So that's Marguerite Boudreaux.
I wasn't even sure if she was real.
She's real, all right. Marguerite Boudreaux.
My great, great-grandmother.
She was a powerful mamba.
Lived in Blackbriar nearly 200 years ago.
Marguerite took payment for healing the sick
and serving as a priestess to the Loa
for the Haitian immigrants.
They called her Queen,
"Queen of the Swamp."
Yeah?
I heard she was executed for murder.
For killing a little kid.
I heard she put a hex on a slave owner,
and that's what did it.
Everybody hears it different.
-Maybe they're all right.
-Or maybe none of it's true.
She's dead, all right. That's a fact.
Murdered by the people of Blackbriar.
After that, the swamps turned mean.
These here swamps, Marguerite's.
She they queen.
And them creatures out there,
she brought 'em back to her swamp
to do her biddin'.
This is ridiculous. Why now, then?
Maybe she just been waitin'
for the right time, the right opportunity.
Or maybe you're full of voodoo crap.
My little brother died in these swamps,
and at the time,
everybody said that it was an accident.
But I knew I felt something.
I knew there was something there.
The swamp, she wants blood for blood.
This is crazy.
Are you sure about that?
Ian! What happened?
They got inside, in the garage.
I locked them in, but they killed Sam.
-No!
-I tried to save her, but they almost got me.
I'm just glad you're okay.
All right. Who the hell are you?
William Boudreaux,
and this is my house, boy.
We need a phone.
We gotta call help.
I lost my phone when our ship went down.
Me, too.
No one to call, no one to help you now.
Marguerite ain't gonna stop
until the swamp gets her full of blood.
Not unless we stop her first.
She been mad before, storms, floods, death.
Marguerite threw a tantrum
every now and again.
No! No!
This time she gone too far.
What happens if we don't get to her?
Then we all dead.
Marge! Marge, do you copy?
Marge! Do you hear me?
Marge!
Damn it!
-Anything?
-No.
Can't even raise her. She can't hear anything.
The whole town is probably gone by now.
Well, maybe she's napping.
This way.
We're almost there. It's just down a way.
The Boudreaux home, it's just up a ways.
Carly, what is this place?
It's Boudreaux's house.
-Boudreaux?
-Just follow me.
Okay.
What the hell is he mumbling about?
-It's the curse.
-It's the curse?
Yeah, I see all your damn hoodoo
and whatnot.
Bunch of crap, is what I say.
Mr. Boudreaux, can you stop this?
My whole life I tried
to keep Marguerite happy.
Take care of the swamp,
and she take care of you.
That's what my momma told me.
But now...
What is this?
She got a demon protecting the grave.
You're gonna need a heat bag.
Little agrimony, tobacco, goofer dust.
Goofer dust.
You use it to ward off the spirits.
But only fire can burn out evil.
She's at the heart of the swamp.
You got to help me destroy her.
If you knew that Marguerite
was the cause of all of this,
why haven't you done anything until now?
Why?
Same reason we don't go killing all the
gators in the bayou because of a few attacks.
Nature has a balance.
Marguerite kept the balance.
But she's out of control now.
Chris, it's your mom!
Mom.
Shame what happened
to your friend out in the garage.
Yeah, it is.
Be careful, boy.
Marguerite got it out especially for betrayers.
-Get in here!
-Thank God!
-Get in, get in!
-I'm all right, I'm all right.
What are you all doing together?
Are you talking again?
We gotta get out of here, okay?
This place is gonna be crawling
with those things any second now.
My boat is down by the dock.
Wait, Ian's here and William Boudreaux.
What about Sam and Kerri?
Oh, dear God!
-Ranger Hardin, what are we gonna do?
-We are going to survive.
Ian, what are you doing?
I'm not dying here
because of some stupid fish, okay?
Now come on, old man.
You said before you know how to stop this?
Spill it.
-Let him go!
-Shut up!
We've gotta find her heart, destroy it.
She wrecked that truck
at the source of her power.
-Now let me go.
-What the hell does that even mean?
She's in the swamp, in its trees, in its water.
You can't escape the swamp.
-Busting through the door!
-Run!
Eat this!
We're out of here now!
This way's clear! Hurry!
Ian, come on! What are you doing?
Let's go, we gotta run, man!
Let's go!
Somebody's gotta kill these things.
Oh, no! You need to put that out!
-Mom!
-Carly!
-Mom! Mom! Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Chris, you need to go.
Guys, the house is gonna collapse.
-Chris, you need to go.
-We have to get out of here.
-No! I'm not going to leave her!
-I'm not gonna lose you like I lost Bryce! Go!
Mom!
Come on! We have to go!
No!
Come on, sweetheart. I got you.
-Come on! We can't stay here!
-Mom!
-No! Mom!
-Come on!
The house is gonna fall!
Son.
She's all right.
We lost you for a while there.
Yeah, well, don't lose me again.
I won't.
We have to find
Marguerite Boudreaux's grave.
We have to end this.
I'll go. I'll go.
Mr. Boudreaux,
he said something about a truck wreck.
I know where that is.
She could be buried there.
Well, we don't know that for sure.
But we have to do something.
Chris, son, there isn't anything we can do.
The fish are continuing to evolve.
Blackbriar is lost.
-No!
-We need to leave while we can.
No! This is our home,
and we have to fight for it.
We're not gonna give up on family.
We have to do this for Bryce!
Sweetheart,
what if Mr. Boudreaux was wrong?
What if there is no grave when you get there?
Mr. Boudreaux, he believed in this enough
that he was willing to die for it.
I have to try. I have to.
Ian's getting away!
There's not a house around here for miles,
we are gonna be stranded.
I am gonna go to the grave.
I know where it is. I can get there.
I can walk there from here,
but you get that damn boat.
And if I don't return,
then you get out of Blackbriar
and you get some help.
And I don't care
if you call the whole damn Army.
I'm coming back,
and I'm bringing the cavalry, okay?
-I'm coming with you.
-No, no, no, you can't.
Your leg is all messed up.
You're just gonna slow me down.
Then I'll go with you.
You shouldn't go alone.
What about Chris?
I got Chris covered, go.
Okay, you stay safe until we return. Okay?
Ian! Ian! Stop!
All right, you can't take the boat.
We need that. My family needs that.
Listen to me,
we can make it out of this together, okay?
-You have to...
-I have to?
I'm done taking orders from you!
What do you think, you're a hero?
You have no idea what those things are,
and I'm not dying in this swamp,
so stay out of my way.
Chris!
We don't have to do this.
You know,
I never got what Ashley saw in you,
but you can have her.
I used her all up anyways.
Say goodbye, Hardin.
Ian! Ian! Come on.
Ian!
Come on!
Ian, come on!
Where is he? I don't see him!
Come on! Come on!
Ranger Hardin, do you hear me?
Hello? Who is this?
This is Trooper Simon with the State Police.
Who is this?
Where's Ranger Hardin?
I'm her son, Chris.
Where's your mom? I've gotta talk to her.
The National Guard is here.
They're pushing the fish
back into the swamp,
but we're not out of this yet.
So what is that supposed to do, anyway?
Honestly, I don't even know.
Mr. Boudreaux said it'll help fight the demon
that's out here protecting the grave.
Do you see that?
-Come on.
-There it is!
Do you really think that
this is all because of the Blackbriar Curse?
I don't know, but right now,
I'm willing to believe just about anything.
I couldn't get a shot off.
I couldn't help him,
but you're all right, though, right?
-It's his own damn fault.
-Thank goodness.
When did you learn to shoot like that?
Well, when a fish tries to eat you...
Look out!
Trooper Simon!
Mr. Hardin, where is your wife?
No, she's all right. She's all right.
She and Ashley went
back to the wreck to try and...
No, that's not good!
We're rounding up the survivors,
and we have to get them
out of the swamp right now.
Why? What's happening?
We've got the snakeheads on the move.
We have to make a "Hail Mary" play
to clear them out, okay?
The Air Force has been called in.
Your mom's in danger! Take it, it'll help!
It'll help!
-Thanks, Marge.
-Take it!
Besides, I just got off the phone
with the guys who created these fish.
Apparently, there's something worse
that was on that truck
than just these snakeheads.
What do you mean, "worse"?
-You gotta be kidding, right?
-No.
What is that?
I have no idea, but whatever it is,
it's a hell of a lot bigger than the others.
What does that mean, "Specimen 0"?
I don't know. Let's go to the other side.
I never got to tell you how sorry I was
about what happened to Bryce.
And I want you to know
that I'll take care of Chris.
I know that you will, Ashley, and thank you.
Marguerite Boudreaux.
-Ashley!
-Help me, Ranger Hardin! Help me!
Ashley! Stay with me!
Help me!
No, no, just stay with me!
Please, no! Please help!
No, no, no, no!
Don't leave me here, Ranger Hardin, please!
Help me!
Come on, let's get you to cover.
-You can do it. Good?
-Yeah.
Okay, great.
-It's okay, you're gonna be okay.
-What is that?
Oh, God, it's its eggs.
Finish this off!
-Jim?
-Mom!
Chris!
Mom! Where are you?
Are you with Ashley?
Yeah, we're at the crash site.
It's past the 8-Mile Ditch.
Ashley's with me, she's hurt.
She needs a hospital.
There is a monster here,
it's just the worst damn one yet.
-All right, listen to me!
-Oh, my God!
That's the mother!
She's the original test specimen!
-She's pregnant!
-It's worse, she's already laid her eggs.
Ranger Hardin!
All right, the Air Force are on their way,
the National Guard, to kill the rest of the fish.
But the only way to stop the infestation...
-Go on, Chris, tell me.
-They're carpet-bombing the swamp, Ma.
Oh, my God!
Chris, I love you.
No! I'm coming to get you!
No, don't! We're never gonna make it!
I'm not gonna give up! Now get down!
Okay, get down.
Let's go!
You ready?
Go! Go! Go!
I hate this damn swamp, anyway.
The fire's not working, she's following us.
It's not to kill her, it's to control her.
We're leading her somewhere.
You mean, we're the bait?
Hold on.
Help Ashley. Let me have the gun.
Ranger Hardin, move! Let's go!
Jim! Jim!
-Come on.
-We gotta get across the swamp!
I know, I think you're right.
Let's go, Chris. Let's go!
The bullets aren't doing anything!
Go! Jim, take this! Marge! Let's go!
Marge! Marge! Let's go!
Come on, Dad!
Ash, fire bomb.
Chris, what are you doing?
Trust me.
Chris, are you ready?
I think the curse has finally been broken.
I think that I've been hanging on to this
a little too long.
I thought maybe you might want it back.