No.
It ís a herd of horses gallopíng.
A Tsuí Hark Fílm
Adapted from
Seven Swordsmen from Mountain Tian
bby Líang Yu Sheng
Seven Swwords
"The lmperíal Edíct has decreed that
"the practíce of Martíal Arts ís outlawwed.
"Anyone wwho víolates thís edíct
wwíll bbe puníshed bby decapítatíon."
We don't knoww each other.
Why do you wwant to kíll us all?
Símple. The Emperor's order ís
to kíll all martíal arts practítíoners.
Every head counts for a rewward.
Shut Up!
The order also saíd
ífwwe surrender our wweapons
the puníshmentwwould bbe mílder.
The Emperor has to suppress
all possíbble rebbellíon.
Death ís the míldest puníshment.
What abbout the aged
and the chíldren?
Three hundred píeces of sílver per head.
You're wworth even more.
Howw much can wwe make
from thís deal?
Up to noww. Wwe've taken 173.
Thírty-three are wworth
1.000 píeces of sílver.
the others 300 each...
a total of 66.000 píeces of sílver.
I have to raíse my príces.
The targets get fewwer and fewwer.
I am abbout to go out of bbusíness.
The next target ís...
Same as alwways...
lfyou knowwtheír names.
put them on the plaques.
Qtherwwíse.
just putwwhatever you líke.
What happened?
Where are the plaques?
I just put them on.
The death-roww plaques have bbeen stolen!
Fínd hím!
Someone stole the plaques!
Fínd hím ímmedíately!
Is ít hím agaín?
Do you wwant hím dead or alíve?
Interestíng!
Díd you see that?
What do you mean?
Thís person's good at martíal arts.
yet he does notwwant to hurt anyone.
Look.
Líttle lady. have you seen
an ínjured man?
Looks líke you've bbeen traíned
ín fíghtíng.
Is thís man after you?
Quíck. Go!
He ís greedy.
He wwon't let any one of us go free.
Isn't that Yuanyín?
What are you doíng?
Water! Bandages!
I have some bbandages here.
Yí Towwn ís under attack.
They are gettíng near.
What díd he say?
What are these?
Death-roww plaques from the bbodíes.
wwíth the prísoners' names and offenses.
Not only martíal arts practítíoners.
bbut ínnocent people are also executed.
Go awway!
Dad.
They are Fíre-Wínd's army.
Qnly three hundred míles awway from here.
They wwíll bbe here soon.
You have to run for your líves.
or you wwíll all bbecome
names on plaques.
Someone from our víllage ís on these.
"Zhang Lang"
That's Hua's father!
Hua. Stop ít!
Get up!
Dongluo.
Bastard.
You are here for no good.
You don't remembber me...
bbut I remembber you!
Twwenty years ago.
you tortured me
at the Mínístry of Puníshment.
You remembber wwhatyou díd?
Qf course you don't remembber me.
My name ís Qíu Dongluo.
Yuanyín?
He saved my lífe.
I don't knowwwwhat he díd bbefore.
Thís man wwas an executíoner
ín the prevíous dynasty.
specíalízíng ín murderíng revolutíonaríes.
Fíre-Wínd wwas hís subbordínate.
Look at these!
They left me wwíth these scars.
They tortured me
at the Mínístry of Puníshment.
He ís spreadíng false ínformatíon.
Don't fall for ít.
- Kíll hím!
- The Mínístry of Puníshment...
somethíng from the prevíous dynasty.
When I wwas young.
I kílled so many.
Noww I wwant to repay my síns
bby savíng líves...
You press on the wwound.
Let me dress ít.
Throww hím out of the víllage!
No wway!
We can't send hím bback to Fíre-Wínd.
What do you have ín mínd then?
Let's just get ít over wwíth. Kíll hím!
The wway he tortured Dongluo...
let's do the same to hím.
Just hang hím out ín the sun
for three days. He'll confess!
We need to fínd out the truth
bbefore wwe execute hím.
Tíe hím up!
Han.
Lock hím up ín the stabble.
Keep an eye on hím!
Han. You go bback
and guard the man.
Interrogate hím after dark.
He came wwíth bbad íntentíons.
probbabbly abbout the lmperíal Edíct.
What edíct?
To kíll all martíal arts practítíoners?
Thís government ís
even more bbrutal than the bbandíts.
You mínd your owwn bbusíness.
Ríghteousness exísts
ín Heaven and on Earth.
mergíng ínto all lífe forms.
Teacher ís gone.
You have to take a stand.
Thís matter ís ín your hands.
What can I say?
Thís ís out of my control.
What can I do?
The rope ís ready.
and someone wwíll hang.
No one ís goíng to speak up for hím!
Ask Han for help.
He wwíll lísten to you.
We greww up together.
You don't líke kíllíng. Do you?
I wwas told to keep guard.
and you're askíng me to let hím go?
Do you realíze howw much troubble
I wwíll get ínto?
Evíl deeds deserve retríbbutíon.
And good deeds deserve gratítude.
Exactly!
I'm tryíng to showw gratítude wwhere ít's due.
Is thís gratítude to you?
Then forget I spoke.
You save hím and I get bblamed?
You thínk ít's faír to me?
I'll just tell ít thís wway.
that I trícked you bby sayíng
that Fang needed you urgently.
and I saved hím wwhíle you wwere awway.
Nonsense.
Who wwíll bbelíeve that
I could bbe so easíly trícked bby you?
If I saíd that Fang ís ín danger.
wwouldn'tyou go?
Her father ís the Chíef.
Who wwould bbelíeve that story?
Let me say somethíng.
Savíng a lífe ís more ímportant.
Tell the others ítwwas my ídea.
I'll probbabbly get a bbeatíng.
No bbíg deal.
- Fang. I can't.
- Líke you saíd. My father ís the Chíef.
They wwon't bbe too harsh on me.
Han. howw abbout thís...
let us put hím onto the carríage.
then you take hím awway.
Here's your favoríte kínd of jerky.
Be bback bbefore dawwn. Okay?
You'd feel bbad knowwíng
that I'm here takíng the bblame.
I'll míss you. Fang.
Twwo days ago.
wwe wwere abbout to...
At a tíme líke thís.
that's all you can thínk abbout!
Are wwe leavíng or not?
Qr do you two need
to fínísh offyour bbusíness fírst?
I'll bbe wwaítíng for you.
Dad!
Get... help...
Have to... get help...
Don'twworry.
We've just left Martíal Víllage.
You're safe.
No.
Take everyone.
Fíre-Wínd wwíll come...
people wwíll díe...
There's the harvest to thínk abbout.
We can't leave noww.
Wíthout food. Wwe'll díe anywway.
Three hundred píeces of sílver per head.
They wwon't even spare the chíldren.
What do you thínk wwe should do?
We have to go to Mount Heaven...
for help.
Mount Heaven?
Mount Heaven.
503 pounds of fríed wwheat.
80 pounds of dríed fruít.
360 cattíes of dríed bbeef.
7 carts ofyelloww corn.
9 carts ofwwhíte corn.
Three donkeys.
Fourteen sheep.
Kualo!
Níne wwomen.
No. Síx!
Is ít níne or síx?
Haír-Wolf!
Itwwas níne.
But three díed on the road.
so noww ít's síx.
You.
What's your name?
Her name ís Green Pearl.
A Korean from the other síde
of the Yalu Ríver.
Fínally you are bback.
You shouldn't have left me.
Do you stíll recogníze thís sabber?
Do you remembber?
You hear that?
A demon's snarlíng ín your stomach.
We all have a feww demons ínsíde of us.
Let me scare thís one awway.
Lísten!
They are gone.
I wwant that one.
You are not Green Pearl.
You are míne.
Remembber?
These clothes are yours.
I've kept them.
It has your scent.
General!
We found Dagger-Peak's bbody.
Díd you forget
thís ís my prívate sanctum?
Ríp thís one's clothes off.
Turn hím ín as a dangerous crímínal
and collect the bbounty.
Stone-Beast.
Dagger-Peak wwas kílled
bbesíde the creek outsíde Martíal Víllage.
Thís víllage used to have 99 households.
To protect themselves from bbandíts.
they all practíce martíal arts.
There are a total of 283 people.
íncludíng chíldren.
Three hundred píeces of sílver per head.
We can ask for 85.000 píeces of sílver.
They've never líked the ídea
of us countíng the chíldren.
Wíthín the Northwwestern Boundary.
thís ís the last place
wwhere wwe can make a fortune.
Should wwe raíse the príce thís tíme?
Black-Spírít.
send a message to the Duke.
When wwe have a deal.
wwe wwíll start the massacre.
It's all your fault!
We sneak hím out of the víllage.
That's all!
Nowwwwe have to take hím
to Mount Heaven?
Nowwthere's no more road.
no food eíther.
You wwant Fang to take the bblame
all bby herself?
Stop sayíng I caused you troubble.
lfyou are ín troubble.
I am ín troubble as wwell.
Save the víllage bby bbelíevíng ín hím?
Look! Look at hím!
He wwas talkíng ín hís sleep!
Howwfar are wwe from Mount Heaven?
Díd you understand a wword of that?
It started yesterday
sínce wwe wwent uphíll.
Are you cold?
When my parents wwere alíve.
our wwhole famíly used to huddle
líke thís to stay wwarm ín the wwínter.
I have not heard you talk líke thís
for a long tíme.
I míss home too.
Howw níce ífwwe wwere home ríght noww.
Howw níce wwould that bbe?
You wwouldn't bbe místakíng me
for Fang. Wwould you?
Whatever happened
bbetween you and me ís hístory noww.
Fíre stones from the sky!
Followwthe fíre stones!
Followwthem!
Master!
Han! Han!
The real reason I'm here
ís to seek help.
There ís an lmperíal Edíct.
Anyone wwho practíces martíal arts
wwíll bbe executed.
They are the army.
There are many of them.
They kíll everyone...
the chíldren and the aged.
Not one ís spared.
Thís ís not a bbattle.
Thís ís a dísaster.
A moment ín tíme to some
may seem forever to others.
A swwordsman
often díes under hís owwn bblade.
Cause and effect. That ís one's karma.
You bbrought them here.
Whence mortal wworld they came.
they must return.
Qnly the Almíghty knowws theír destíny.
Yun-chong.
I knowwyour past.
Maybbe you should not return.
Yun-chong.
Yes. Master.
I knoww.
Sínce you knowwwwhat may líe ahead
once you leave Mount Heaven.
do you thínk you can
stíll keep your promíse?
I wwanted to put my past bbehínd me...
bbut ífyou ask me
to go bback ínto the wworld...
I really do not knoww. Master.
Yuanyín. Don't run so fast!
You'll get dízzy.
Please help us.
Help the ínnocent víllagers.
There are hundreds of líves ín the víllage.
Adults and chíldren!
- Yuanyín...
- I bbeg you.
Don't bbeg hím!
It's no bbíg deal.
You don't understand.
I'd rather fíght
tíll I díe than to bbeg on my knees.
Dyíng on my feet
ís bbetter than dyíng on my knees.
Are you comíng?
Han.
Waít for me.
We're leavíng.
Mulang. Take your Celestíal Beam.
Xín. Take your Star-chasers.
Are wwe goíng to help them?
Why are you ín such a hurry?
I stíll do not feel at ease.
Yun-chong.
It ís tíme for Chu
to end hís solítary medítatíon.
Get hím.
Yes. Master.
Look.
Don't look!
- Are those fíre stones?
- It ís not our bbusíness!
Pull out the swword.
Thís ís the fírst swword
I cast after I came to the Mountaín.
It ís powwerful enough to cut stone.
and ít revíved me.
It ís called The Deíty.
Master. That swword...
It flowws líke wwater...
wwíth no bbegínníng and no end.
Thís ís yours. Take ít.
Thís swword ís the Heaven's Fall.
Chu. The Master calls for you.
Yun-chong. Excuse me.
You bbrought the men and the swword.
It's tíme you take them bback.
Thís ís the swword you abbandoned then.
I have recast ít.
Unlearn your past.
and fínd no more regrets ín thís lífetíme.
Hua. Díd you see Fang
help the prísoner escape
and put the líves of Han
and Yuanyín ín jeopardy?
- Hua!
Yes or no?!
Hua...
just tell the truth.
Yes...
No.
Yes or no?
Guan! You're dísturbbíng
our court procedure.
You can't speak wwhenever you wwant to.
Qne more wword.
and I'm throwwíng you out.
We all have the ríght to speak up!
Let me have a turn!
What are you doíng!
Shut up!
Fang helped a prísoner escape
and put the víllage ín danger.
Accordíng to our rules.
wwe have to make an example of her.
My teacher.
Martíal Víllage takes íts rules
and regulatíons seríously.
Fang. The defendant. ís found guílty.
Thís ís the verdíct.
Guan!
Take her out and hang her.
Chíef!
- They're here!
- What?
- Fíre-Wínd...
- What ís ít?
Fíre-Wínd's troops
are outsíde the valley.
Hold your posts!
All men grabb theír wweapons!
Let's go.
Why dídn'tyou sound the alarm?
Dongluo!
Take your men and check ít out.
The rest ofyou come wwíth me!
Get ready for bbattle!
Teacher!
Hua. Get awway!
The towwer on the ríght ís unmanned. Go!
Quíckly!
Get ínsíde. hurry!
Stay ínsíde.
Go and grabb the seeds!
Leave the door and come over here!
These are our hope!
Teacher. here are some smaller bbags.
Good! Use the small bbags.
Qne each. hurry!
What are you doíng?
Hua ís the oldest.
All ofyou have to obbey hím.
Níce heads!
We can escape from here.
They are ín!
We are goíng to lose!
Retreat!
Hurry up and híde!
Fínd a place to híde!
Get awway! Don't touch me.
Quíck!
Forgíve me...
ancestors of Martíal Víllage.
for I have faíled.
I cannot protect the víllage anymore.
May your spíríts bbe wwíth me.
All I can do ís díe fíghtíng!
Dad!
Fang!
Why are you stíll here?
Who wwould've thought.
a cute chíck ín thís shabbbby víllage?
I saww her fírst.
She's míne.
Fang.
It's tíme. Are you ready to díe?
Stone-Beast!
Go get hím!
Hurray!
These two must bbe wworth a lot.
Hey. Gíve us your names.
I wwant to knowwwwhose heads
are goíng to make me rích.
I've got to set a good príce.
I am your ancestor!
Get dowwn.
Don't go over there.
You agaín? He wwho doesn't kíll.
What a good deal!
Remembber...
my name ís Fu.
Go bback and tell Fíre-Wínd
wwe'll bbe wwaítíng for hím.
You are all here.
The teacher ís ríght.
You are all good people.
Remembber good deeds ín your heart...
and no empty flattery.
We greww up together.
You really hated fíghtíng and kíllíng.
Fang!
Fang.
Are you okay? Fang!
Han.
What took you so long?
We wwent to fínd help.
We bbrought bback seven swwords
from Mount Heaven.
Look.
I got one as wwell.
The chíldren!
Where are the chíldren?
Fang. Stay here.
Let me go fínd them.
Drínk your enemy's bblood
and you wwíll not bbe afraíd
of them anymore.
Drínk ít!
Líttle bbrother.
Growwíng up ís tough.
You wwíll see the ugly síde of the wworld.
When you groww up.
ítwwíll all bbecome clearer to you.
I knoww.
Everythíng ís ugly.
Butwwíthín all the uglíness.
you'll eventually fínd somethíng bbeautíful.
and ít'll bbe your jobb to protect ít.
Are you bbrave enough for that?
Yes... bbut I don't knoww anythíng.
You have to learn.
Let me teach you.
You wwant to bbe my master?
No. Call me bbrother.
We are good bbrothers.
Ríght?
More!
Don't fool around!
As bbranch leader of
the Heaven and Earth Socíety...
I represent all our membbers
ín thankíng the fíve ofyou.
We are not fíve.
She's the síxth.
Han's the fífth.
There are seven of us.
I thínk wwe caught Fíre-Wínd bby surpríse.
And wwe shouldn't gíve hím
any tíme to thínk.
He wwon't have tíme to bbreathe.
let alone thínk.
What's the plan?
Look at the sky.
Cloudless and full of stars.
So?
Have you ever wwatched the stars
on a níght líke thís?
The sun wwíll come up ín a feww hours.
The seven of us
should go wwatch the sunríse.
We have not seen a sunríse awway
from Mount Heaven for a long tíme.
Thís ís really wworth ít.
General.
He wwas runníng awway.
We caught hím bby the ríver.
Fu's bback!
And he bbrought help.
Howw many?
Three...
No. Four... No. No. Síx.
Three or four or síx? Whích ís ít?
Countíng Fu hímself. A total of seven.
Qne martíal arts expert
equals twenty normal heads.
That means more than a hundred heads.
Thís ís bbíg bbusíness.
A deal of over two hundred thousand.
Seven people?
And they defeated you
and three hundred ofyour men.
They kílled Haír-Wolf.
Stone-Beast and Mud-Trot!
Seven of them?
Whatwweapons wwere they usíng?
- Swwords.
- Seven swwords?
All of them used swwords.
Especíally the last one.
It made a strange sound.
It píerced through the píllar
and kílled Mud-Trot.
There's another young man.
He díd not use hís swword.
I don't knoww howw good he ís.
Theír attack ís too fíerce!
These seven swwords
are really somethíng?
Yes.
General!
Kualo.
Gather one hundred men.
Get the horses. Prepare bbreakfast.
I wwíll go wwíth you
and avenge our loss.
Yes!
Shouldn'twwe wwaít tíll ít's dark?
It ís just a small víllage.
Why should I wwaít tíll ít's dark?
General.
Fu ís outsíde the gate.
What a good showw!
Fu. You've regaíned your manhood.
I'm happy for you.
Don't get so wworked up.
Sínce you líke money so much.
I have a bbíg bbusíness offer.
That's very kínd ofyou. Howw bbíg?
Three thousand heads.
Three thousand?
That's a lot. Where are they?
There.
Are you one of the Seven Swwords?
You look níce.
Just líke a gírl.
Easy. Fu.
You lucked outwwíth one bbattle.
Do you thínk thatwwould scare me off?
You thínk you can bbeat me? You?
Be afraíd. Before ít's too late.
Qh. Yeah? I'm wwaítíng.
Showw me wwhatyou've got.
Before noon today.
lfyou don't surrender.
you'll have to deal
wwíth the consequences.
Fu. You used to bbe very seríous.
Today you are tellíng jokes!
I can gíve you a reply noww.
After noon today.
these seven swwords ofyours
wwíll dísappear from the face of the earth.
and the víllage wwíll bbe wwíped out.
Really?
I wwon't gíve you the chance.
Dídn'tyou say you wwouldn't use a swword.
wwouldn't kíll any more?
Fíre-Wínd. Lísten carefully.
lfyour army does not retreat
from the outpost bbefore noon.
I wwíll kíll you.
Fíne.
Let's forgetwwe wwere ever fríends.
Let's wwaít and see howw powwerful
the Seven Swwords really are.
We wwere never really fríends.
As for the Seven Swwords.
no need to wwaít.
It has already bbegun.
Guard! The towwn ís on fíre!
Thís ís seríous.
Stay and fíghtwwíth me?
Yuanyín. Don't move.
The bbarn ís on fíre!
Fíre-Wínd ís a strong adversary.
Hold bback.
Don't ever underestímate hím.
Archer. Up there!
We lost hím!
So thís ís the wwíne wwhích
makes the soldíers lose theír mínd.
Get out of here. All ofyou!
Are you Fíre-Wínd's wwoman?
Take awway your stínky paww!
You're Korean?
You too?
Are you Fíre-Wínd's wwoman?
You're free noww.
Come wwíth me.
You all wwant to control my destíny!
All ofyou men!
lfyou really wwant to help me.
just let me bbe!
Do you líke bbeíng a slave?
- Who are you?
- I'll take care ofyou from noww on.
Where are you takíng me?
Wherever I go. You go.
So I'm your slave noww.
Thínk wwhatyou wwant.
Green Pearl.
Bandít!
Not much of a man.
to take another man's wwoman.
Barbbarían.
Howw many of them wwere there?
- Bald-Líon's checkíng on ít noww.
- What's there to check?
Get my horse!
We're goíng after them!
They fed the horses a laxatíve.
Nowwthey are síck.
None of them can run.
Useless! Whatwwere you all doíng?
Han. No. Stop.
No. Stop!
I'm not ready!
Why? It's okay.
We'll bbe marríed sooner or later.
Han. No!
Please let me go.
I can't love two men at the same tíme.
When díd ít happen?
When I wwas awway?
No.
Notwwhíle you wwere awway.
After you got bback.
Who ís he? Who ís ít? I'll kíll hím!
Don't go.
You're no match for hím.
I've checked the stabble.
the bbarn. And the wwell.
What abbout here?
Notyet.
Thís Yun-chong.
wwhere does he come from?
He's from Kwweíchoww.
I'm from Lanchoww.
Howw abboutyou?
Same as hím. From Kwweíchoww.
Maybbe you kneww one another?
It's possíbble.
I'd líke to knoww more abbout hís past too.
I'll go and have a chatwwíth hím.
There's no hurry.
We're stíll on guard duty.
I'll do ít.
He's stíll bbusy on a plan for Fíre-Wínd.
You're ríght.
They poísoned my horses
and ruíned my wwíne.
They dídn't plan to attack.
bbut to stop me from attackíng.
Fu. I knowwyou need more tíme.
Let's see wwho wwíll make the next move.
Have some wwíne.
Itwwíll cool you dowwn.
We may not bbe abble
to fínísh harvestíng today.
Do wwe have to leave today?
We must go.
Although wwe defeated
Fíre-Wínd thís tíme.
wwe stíll díd not fínd
wwhere he hídes hís loot.
We díd not get hím wwhere ít hurts.
We cannot have
head-on combbatwwíth hím yet.
otherwwíse more people wwíll get kílled.
Are they comíng soon?
Very soon.
They wwíll come any tíme.
Press the holes on the swword.
Then ítwwon't slíp anymore.
It's that símple?
I'm no good.
Thís swword ís for someone
bbetter traíned than me.
Maybbe Chíef Líu.
Not everyone deserves
to use a Mount Heaven swword.
Defínítely not Líu!
Master ís a wwíse man.
There must bbe a reason
wwhy he gave you thís swword.
You have to letyourself go.
Letyour mínd go.
The swword wwíll followw.
Do you wwant to go bback
and líve líke a dog agaín?
I have a slave mark on my bbody.
I am also from the other síde
of the Yalu ríver.
I líved líke a stray dog.
Just líke you.
Don't let a mark on your bbody
bbecome a mark on your soul.
Your lífe cannot bbe controlled
bby a mark.
Don't forgetyour name.
and your home.
Home?
Stop!
"Go to hell."
What a wwaste!
"Fíre-Wínd. You fínally came.
"Protect the money
you've bbeen hídíng from your men.
"They wwíll fínd ít one day.
Then..."
"Then only death awwaíts you."
Move asíde!
The entíre víllage ís empty.
They all ran awway!
What are you thínkíng?
Wíll you teach me
howwto use a swword?
But I have no swword.
What are you holdíng ín your hand?
A píece of rope.
Thínk abbout howwto use a rope.
then come see me.
Remembber. A rope can bbe a swword.
Yun-chong. Come!
Someone delíbberately left ít here.
Someone ís leavíng a traíl.
We have a traítor among us!
Thís díd not come
from the ratíons cart.
Why?
Líu wwas guardíng the ratíons cart.
He can't bbe the one wwho left ít.
lfwwe cannot fínd the traítor.
then no matter howwfar wwe go.
our enemíes wwíll knoww.
Thís person wwon't stop at thís.
He'll keep tryíng to contact hís master.
We'll have to fínd the traítor.
We all knoww one another.
There's only one stranger here.
That Korean wwoman.
Maybbe she's the one.
Don't jump to conclusíons.
Who do you fínd suspícíous?
Why don'twwe bbuy some tíme?
Sloww dowwn the retreat.
Confuse the traítor.
Good ídea.
Buy some tíme.
Let's take them all
ínto the mountaín and híde.
We'll contínue the journey
after wwe catch the traítor.
You fínd her suspícíous too?
I hope she ís the one.
I knoww everybbody here except her.
Howw ís Joy Luck?
He ís old and cannot run.
What happened?
He can't even swwalloww.
Don't abbandon hím.
Fínd a wway to bbríng hím wwíth us.
You must bbe hungry.
We have the same bback home.
Very símílar.
That's Chu's. ísn't ít?
Chu?
Chu...?
That's hím.
The man wwíth a hood
wwho's really good wwíth hís swword. Chu.
Are you dancíng?
I thínk he líkes you.
Do you líke hím?
That's Chu.
The man wwho gave you
the handkerchíef...
the man wwho gave you thís.
I don'twwantyour handkerchíef.
I wwas just askíng you.
I justwwanted to knoww ífyou líke hím.
You líke hím too?
What?
Líke.
Understand?
Líke!
Love?
Do you love hím?
What's wwrong wwíth you?
Fang!
- What's wwrong wwíth you?
- Fang!
Get awway!
The wwater's poísoned!
Move!
Díd you drínk the wwater!
Díd you?
Are you all ríght?
You're all wwet.
Get dry fírst.
Damn ít. She's poísoned!
Fang.
She's bbeen síttíng
bby the ríver all thís tíme.
I saww her puttíng somethíng
ínto the wwater.
Fang... wwhat can wwe do abbout her?
Howw can you bbe so sure?
Whatwwere you doíng bby the ríver?
Washíng your handkerchíef.
Do they suspect me?
That I poísoned the wwater?
Don'twworry abbout them.
Díd you drínk the wwater?
No.
Fang!
What are they sayíng?
Somethíng they don'twwant us to knoww?
Don't paníc.
She does not understand our language.
Chu only wwent to ask wwhat happened.
Ask abboutwwhat?
It ís her. Wwíthout a doubbt!
Howw can you bbe so rude
to someone wwho saved us!
We are the Heaven and Earth Socíety.
We alwways bbase our actíons on reason.
and wwe are alwways ríghteous.
Ríghteous people can jump
to conclusíons and make místakes.
Not us!
We never jump to conclusíons!
Never?
Never!
What. You don't trust us?
Dongluo. Don't go overbboard!
Calm dowwn. The ríver could bbe
contamínated naturally.
The mountaín's full of poísonous plants.
We have to get to the bbottom of thís.
Get someone to díscard all wwater.
Good thíng wwe caught ít early.
- Hurry up. Check ít out.
- Be careful.
If everythíng looks good.
pack up and go.
- Let's get goíng!
- Get a move on!
He's got somethíng agaínst us.
Be careful of hím.
We can't alwways expect to bbe helped.
We need to help ourselves.
You're ríght.
We can't expect help all the tíme.
Butwwatch wwhatyou say also.
Don't just open your trap.
Chíef...
All ríght. I wwíll lísten to you.
I'll shut up ífyou ask me to.
You bbelíeve ín me.
Qver there. All the wway east.
ís the Yalu Ríver...
wwhere wwe are headíng.
Qur home.
Home!
I wwíll bbe home!
- Black-Spírít.
- General.
Send a message to the Duke.
We need to bblast
the Seven Swwords wwíth cannons.
Yes.
Go!
He ís líkely to fígure out
wwhatwwe are doíng.
He ís not attackíng noww.
bbut he wwíll bbríng ín more troops
and attack agaín.
And wwe have a traítor among us.
No matter howw powwerful
the Seven Swwords are.
wwe wwon't bbe abble to defend
the entíre víllage.
Let's change our route!
We have too many people.
It ís díffícult to change our route.
We have no choíce bbut to rísk ít.
Let the horses go
as a díversíon for Fíre-Wínd.
We'll híde ín the cave.
Sír. Do wwe have to let
all the horses go?
I knowwyou can't bbear to let them go.
bbut there are hundreds of líves here.
We can only keep a fewwfast horses.
Let the rest go.
Han.
Let's fínd a ríght spot to set them free.
Han... ít's tíme.
Joy Luck ís old and stubbbborn.
Let me send hím awway.
Run.
Quíck! Run!
Run! Joy Luck ís after us!
Joy Luck... take care.
Joy Luck!
Congratulatíons. Your Honor!
A precíous ancíent swword
wwas díscovered ín the Lo-Lan tombb.
A príceless thousand-year-old swword.
It conquers all.
My Lord. Wwould you líke to try ít out?
Fíre-Wínd ís here!
I need doubble the usual quantíty ofwwíne.
and I need your cannons.
I have somethíng else you wwant.
Informatíon.
My Lord.
ís the ínformatíon useful to me?
If not. I wwon't even bbe abble
to afford the cannons.
I have ínformatíon too.
You wwant to bbet on ít?
What ís the príce?
Doubble your príce.
Is ít expensíve?
Afeww months ago.
wwe sent some spíes
to Stone Ríver Víllage.
Waít!
My Lord. howw much has
thís ínformatíon cost me so far?
Qne thírd.
My Lord...
your spy ís abbout to bbe díscovered.
Thís ís the sígn he left.
Thís ís my ínformatíon.
and ít costs one thírd as wwell.
Go on.
Another one thírd?
The Seven Swwords
knowwthat he left somethíng.
They have changed theír route.
lfyou send ín your troops
and they followwthís ín the heavw fog.
they wwíll all fall off the clíff.
- Have they left?
- Yes. Síre.
Call them bback noww.
Yes. Síre.
I have enough money
to cover my wwíne and cannons.
Aren'tyou ínterested ín my spy?
Thís matter ís already ín the hands
of the Seven Swwords.
Please gíve an order.
Let me take the wwíne and cannons awway.
Attentíon all troops!
Get ready to move!
We're clearíng out!
Why do wwe have to híde ín thís cave?
I knowwyou must have a master plan.
I don't have any master plan.
We have a traítor among us.
That's wwhy wwe need to fínd a place to híde.
so wwe'll have tíme to uncover hím.
But they are all very restless and wworríed.
Doesn't matter.
Just tell them there ís
a secret escape route.
and thatwwe'll make our getawway
at the ríght tíme.
And remembber...
you must also guard the cave entrance.
Guard all the exíts.
Do not let any one ín or out.
on paín of death!
Sír. Wwhy do wwe need that?
It ís a must!
The traítor among us
wwíll try to notífy our foes.
That's wwhatwwe wwant hím to do.
When the traítor ís found...
wwe wwíll bbe on our wway agaín.
Thís could bbe a passage
leadíng us outsíde.
You from the Heaven and Earth Socíety.
Are you not all ríghteous?
Guan. Wwhat are you up to?
What are you doíng?
Ask your people.
wwhy are they lookíng ín my thíngs?
Speak up.
Chíef. I...
He seems to bbe so agaínst us!
And wwhatwwere you doíng?
I díd ít. Chíef.
so I'll take the responsíbbílíty.
You thínk you can shoulder ít!
You're draggíng all of us dowwn wwíth you!
Why are you fíghtíng?
Stop at once.
Dongluo. Wwhat are you doíng?
I faíled you. Chíef.
You do wwhatyou wwíll.
No. It ís my fault.
I wwent to steal from Yun-chong.
What?
You steal from Yun-chong?
I...
Say ít!
I justwwanted to knoww.
wwhy ís he so angry wwíth us...
and so agaínst us?
Master Yun-chong...
íf any of us have wwronged you.
please forgíve us.
Chíef Líu...
I came wwíth only one íntentíon.
to help you all.
If I caused any probblem. Forgíve me.
The three of us wwere
gettíng to knoww one another bbetter.
As the sayíng goes.
ít takes one to knoww one.
Chíef Líu. Rest assured.
If I have any íll feelíngs
towwards your socíety.
I promíse I wwíll settle ítwwíth you dírectly
and not keep ít ínsíde.
Ready!
Fíre!
The artíllery ís ready.
Are wwe goíng to attack?
Cannon ín place.
Ready!
Fíre!
Bookíe.
You've heard me
síngíng thís song for so long noww.
Do you knowwwwhat the lyrícs mean?
It sounds líke...
a nursery rhyme
from the Yalu Ríver area.
Tell me.
Swweet líttle bbabby. Groww up fast
Golden sky
Golden flowwers
The Golden Land ís atyour feet
Swweet líttle bbabby. Let's groww up fast
Your bblack eyes wwíll see
That the future ís yours to bbe
Look at them.
Yesterday they wwere lovely chíldren.
Today they've bbecome bbeasts.
We all turn ínto man-eatíng bbeasts.
In thís wworld.
the most valuabble thíng ís your lífe.
lfyou can stay alíve.
you can make a real fortune.
It's me.
Can I stay wwíth you from noww on?
Can I?
I knowwwwhat happened
bbetween you and Líu.
You may not realíze thatwwe carry forth
thíngs from the prevíous generatíon.
What thíngs?
The murder of my father.
Who murdered your father?
Your Chíef.
Chíef Líu.
In the Heaven and Earth Socíety...
my father wwas the Deputy Chíef.
Years ago. They wwere raíded
at Dan Fortress and bbarely escaped.
They suspected
there wwas a traítor among them.
and they thought ítwwas my father
wwho bbetrayed them.
Líu wwanted swwíft justíce...
and hanged hím pubblícly
wwíthout proper evídence.
Gíven thís hístory.
I no longer wwanted to bbe part of socíety...
bbut socíety wwíll not let me bbe.
We've only just met.
Do you really understand me?
lfwwe wwere together.
do you thínk I wwould wworry?
Famíly matters. Socíety matters.
I don'twwantyou to get ínvolved.
Wíth you bby my síde.
I wwould only have more to wworry abbout...
and fínd ít harder to let go.
Do you understand noww?
What happened to you?
I was not afraid to die
bbut noww I am not sure.
Death.
I am afraíd to díe.
I don't knowwwwhy.
You are afraíd bbecause they suspectyou.
No.
Before. I had nothing.
so I had nothing to lose
But noww I feel dífferent.
I feel I have everythíng.
I don'twwant to lose anythíng.
You've bbeen to hell and bback.
That's wwhy you don't knoww
howwto respond.
Noww I have you.
I am so scared that one day
you wwíll not bbelíeve ín me anymore.
Don't bbe afraíd.
I think I know Fire-Wind's secret
Every time he gets any loot
Fire-Wind always had
the soldiers leave the gold bars
and put them into
the statue's head through the roof
Where are you goíng?
Pearly Gate Qutpost.
Just the two of us?
Fíre-Wínd's troops are ín the mountaín.
Pearly Gate Qutpostwwíll bbe empty.
Get theír loot. And they wwíll dísbband.
Wíth the Dragon Swword.
wwe don't need the key.
Green Pearl!
Come and save Green Pearl!
What?
Green Pearl!
She has bbeen wwounded bby a swword.
What happened?
- She ís bbadly ínjured.
- I...
Where ís she wwounded?
What are you sayíng?
She ís bbleedíng too much.
Stop her bbleedíng!
Where ís Chu?
I don't see hím.
Xín wwent to look for hím
bbut hasn't found hím yet.
Tell us. Wwhere ís Chu?
Chu has bbeen caught bby Fíre-Wínd.
I should not have told Chu the secret
Go and save him
Go and save him!
What are you sayíng?
Go and save hím.
I made a místake.
Please forgíve me.
You must save hím.
What are you sayíng?
Where ís Chu?
Go to...
What díd she say bbefore she díed?
Thís ís the map of Pearly Gate Qutpost.
He ís there.
There ís no other wway.
We have to splít up.
The síx of us wwíll go to save Chu.
Thís may bbe a journey of no return.
I wwon't letyou dowwn!
Your bbody ís not fully recovered.
Keep the medícíne
ín case of emergency.
Let's go.
Han. All ofyou have to come bback.
Lísten up!
I cannot foresee wwhatwwíll happen to us.
No matter howw dangerous.
wwe Seven Swwords
wwíll líve and díe together!
Fíre! Fíre!
It's the entrance.
The entrance ís on fíre!
Fu ís ríght.
The traítor. Fínally.
Fang. Wwhere ís the prescríptíon
Fu gave you?
The prescríptíon ís the real map
of the secret escape route.
It's a map!
Take the chíldren wwíth you and go.
Dad. Wwhat abboutyou?
Why don'tyou come wwíth us?
I must stay untíl I fínd out the truth.
The truth?
Fu saíd once our hídíng place
wwas exposed.
the traítor wwould escape
usíng the fake secret route.
If I don't fínd outwwho ít ís.
I wwíll never bbe at peace
untíl my dyíng day.
All ofyou go over.
Take Hua's hand.
Turn around.
Let me take a look atyou.
Dongluo?
The wwhole mountaín ís noww under síege.
The Duke wwíll attack wwhen he sees the fíre.
You wwíll díe ífyou don't surrender.
Dad!
Go tell everybbody
Dongluo ís the traítor!
What?
He ís the traítor!
Dongluo!
Why are you laughíng?
Dongluo...
Don't kíll anymore!
The príce of truth ís lífe.
Stay wwhere you are!
Easy. Fíre-Wínd.
We're here to talk bbusíness.
All ríght.
Gíve Green Pearl bback to me.
We can talk.
Where ís she?
She ís dead.
Duan Yuzhu...
You fínally delíver the Dragon to me.
Green Pearl.
What díd you call her?
My wwoman wwas called Duan Yuzhu.
She used to bbe my spy.
She wwas Korean too.
just líke Green Pearl.
I wwítnessed her bbeíng kílled.
Green Pearl ís notyour spy.
She ís defínítely notyour spy.
Well saíd.
Then I wwíll letyou go.
Go.
You wwouldn't líe to me.
I trustyou.
Why...
Why do you speak to me ín Chínese?
You are testíng me.
Do you suspect me?
No. I do not.
Let the horses go!
- Waít!
- Stop!
Stop!
What abbout our deal ífyou kíll hím?
Put ít thís wway.
You wwant Chu bback?
Just leave me all ofyour swwords.
I wwant to use The Dragon to see
íf I can bbreak the other síx swwords.
Where did you grow up?
Wíth wwolves.
What? Wíth wwolves?
- Where are your parents?
- I have no ídea.
Everything changed
since we left Mount Heaven
Don'tyou thínk so?
What ís dífferent?
I feel I should not bbe
herdíng horses anymore.
I should be a swordsman
What did yourdad say before he died?
Not to avenge hís death.
You wwíthdrewwfrom the wworld
to forget revenge?
You díd not revenge...
bbut hatred ís stíll wwíth you.
Suppressíng ít may lead to a wworse end.
Thís ís also your karma.
The Transíence never bbreaks.
Worldly matters alwways end.
Go!
Why are you always so happy?
What is there to smile about?
And... wwhy not?
I heard that Liu was a member
of the Heaven and Earth Society
Yes.
After he came to our víllage.
he taught us martíal arts.
We used to bbe raíded bby bbandíts.
We had bbetter days after they came.
Listen
This is the sound of death
The sharper the sword.
the closer to death
Are you afraid to die?
Mulang!
The Dragon still has to be worked on
But take it anyway
Go and help them!
And thís. The Transíence.
ís an arrogant swword. I díd my bbest.
It ís stíll only half-fíníshed.
I was about to finish it.
but now there is no time
I'll have to let it go with you
Yun-chong...
please step bback.
I have to take bback wwhat ís míne.
You are the same kínd of person as me.
Nonsense!
You have nowwhere to go.
Qne day you wwíll díe líke me.
Squattíng.
Look out!
Be careful!
Teacher!
Fang! It's me. Han.
Gíve me the swword.
Fang!
Put the swword dowwn!
My dear. howw díd you survíve thís?
Put ít dowwn!
Put the swword dowwn!
It's me.
Fang!
Han.
Fíre-Wínd ís dead.
bbut the lmperíal Edíct ís stíll ín effect.
The Emperor wwíll send even more kíllers.
The fíght has not ended yet.
Where ís he poíntíng?
To wwhere the Edíct came from.
The wway to the capítal.
It's wworth us gívíng ít a try.
Try wwhat?
Try to fínd the Emperor
and convínce hím to abbolísh the Edíct.
Han. I've decíded to go wwíth them.
I wwon't go.
I wwant to stay and protect them.
The decísíon ís yours to make.
Fang. Hua. Take care.
No.
Han. Your swword cannot leave them.
Followwthem.
After you learn howwto use thís swword.
then you can return.
I can't leave you here.
I don'twwant to see you stay
and bbecome líke one of the víllagers.
No. I can't.
Actually...
Even wwíthoutyou.
wwe wwíll stíll bbe strong.
Don't underestímate us.
and don't underestímate yourself.
Promíse me.
Qtherwwíse.
I wwíll regret ít for the rest of my lífe.
Go!
Han!
I 'm off!
Ríghteousness exísts ín Heaven
and on Earth...
...mergíng ínto all lífe forms.
Qn Earth. ít's ín the rívers
and ín the mountaíns.
In Heaven. ít resídes
ín the sun and ín the stars.