Jenny!
Where you going?
This place is
going to be perfect.
You're perfect.
Why?
Help me!
You're helping me!
Jenny, thank you.
I should have my father sue
your practice for everything
that it's worth.
You mark my words.
By the end of this,
you'll regret you
had anything to do with this.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Not what we're looking for.
Good job though.
Yeah.
We're just looking for something
really specific, you know?
You've kind of got,
like, a blonde Sandra
Yeah, yeah.
And we're looking for more
like a blonde Cate Blanchett
or a blonde Whoopi Goldberg.
Yeah.
Your eye contact throughout
was impeccable, I thought.
Yeah, Phenomenal eye contact.
Is that you?
Yeah.
Good.
I'm taking the car.
I've got to be at work
in, like, 15 minutes.
OK.
How about putting some
gas in it for once?
Okey dokey, artichokey.
) Hey, what's up?
Hey.
) Can I call
you back in a few minutes?
I'm almost at the club.
Yeah.
You going in already?
It's, like, six o'clock.
) Well,
Ricky wanted me in early.
You said you were
going to give me a ride.
) I forgot.
Fuck it.
Charlotte, did you
clean the kennel?
No, give me a minute.
Do it.
The back porch smells
like puppy shit.
Do you feed her
people food again?
Can you give me ride to work?
No, I've gotta go.
Look, I would.
But if I'm late again, William
says I don't get the raise.
And if I don't get the raise, I
have to live with you forever.
I think I'm going to go
crazy if I have to live here
for another six months.
You have my lighter, mom?
Um, no.
Just use the stove.
Bye.
Love you.
) Good stuff
coming right back at you.
Good afternoon, Broadleaf.
We're into the evening
really on the way.
It's going to be a hot
one tonight tonight.
Incredible day on
the coast today.
Music coming up will be hot too.
Lots of people calling
in killer requests.
And whatever you're up to,
thanks for taking us along.
Wherever you're headed,
we'll get you through.
And I want to say
shout out to our buddy,
Mike Kirkpatrick,
local TV news photog.
Hey man, if you're
listening, call in, Mike.
Or if anybody's seen him,
kind of a missing person's
thing now.
They always say those news
guys are on assignment,
but this is a bit much.
I'm sure she's cute,
Mike, whoever she is.
But call in, buddy.
Hit us up on the studio line.
Took you long enough.
Hey, come here a second.
What?
You should smile
a little bit more.
Here.
You forgot my tip.
Ow!
Mother fucker, man!
Asshole!
You don't have to grab me, man.
Jim, what the fuck
is your problem?
Jesus.
Get the fuck off him.
Are you OK?
Shit.
Hey.
You care so much
about these assholes,
you clean that shit up.
Just trying to a
shot of the building.
I got your camera
too, dickhead.
Hey, you got a car?
Mmm.
Pumpkin spice.
My favorite.
You want a hot dog?
Your mom bought five today.
Shut the hell up.
$1.60.
You need anything else?
You sure you don't
want a hot dog?
Hey.
You alive?
I'm cold.
Here.
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
You OK?
Did you give me this blanket?
Yeah, I did.
Where'd you get it?
Up the road.
It's pink.
Yeah.
What's your favorite color?
Green.
Yeah.
Why?
Like the ocean.
Do you always hang
out with strange people
and drive their cars around?
I do.
Every time I get the chance.
It's like a hobby of mine.
Should I be scared?
Do I scare you?
No.
Do you scare-- do I scare you?
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm bleeding.
Yeah.
You got the shit
knocked out of you.
What do you do?
I make movies.
Yeah?
You make movies?
No, not really.
Um, I'm an actress or, you
know, I'm trying to be at least.
There's not a lot going
on right now, you know?
What do you mean?
I've done a couple, like,
music videos and stuff,
but I want to work on
projects where I actually
have a speaking part, you know?
Yeah, that would be nice.
You gonna smoke that thing?
Yeah, are you down?
Yeah, I'm down.
Where are we?
You don't mind
getting blood on it?
It's cool.
Careful.
Don't hurt yourself.
I didn't spill
anymore coffee, did I?
No, you're good.
You're good.
Hey, you're really cool.
Thanks.
I'm Charlotte by the way.
David.
David what?
David, your friend.
We are friends, huh?
Yeah, we're hanging
out like friends.
I don't have many friends.
Yeah, me neither.
I'll be right back.
OK.
Hey.
Um, here.
It's a head shot.
Um, not to sound
cheesy or anything,
but just keep me
in mind if you ever
have any projects or anything.
I will.
Cool.
OK.
Hold on a second.
This is my number.
Give me a call anytime.
And whenever you figure out
the situation with the camera,
just--
Yeah.
Yeah, I will.
I'd really-- really
appreciate it.
Yeah, no problem.
Bye.
Hey!
Fuck!
Fuck, dude.
You scared the fuck out of me.
Fuck, man.
Are you rolling on this?
Is this rolling?
Yeah.
OK.
Hey, Jay Harper.
Nice to meet you.
Very excited to be here.
Ah, shit, man.
Good to meet you.
You must be David, right?
Yeah.
You talking to me or the camera?
Um, I'm talking to you
and the camera, David.
Oh, shit, man.
Well, cool.
What are we doing today?
You're going to do a little
bit of everything today.
OK, alright, great.
I mean, I can edit,
shoot, direct.
I can load.
I'm casting my own feature
right now so it's just like,
you know, but whatever
you want, man.
I'm a jack of all trades.
Master of none.
Yeah, master of--
master of none.
So what are we doing first?
I'm going to have
you take the camera--
OK.
--and you're going to
capture beautiful moments.
OK.
So do you want me to just
roll with it all day?
Yeah, yeah.
How much tape do we have left
on this just so I know before
we run out because
I don't want to--
Don't worry about
technical aspects, OK?
OK.
I got it handled.
I just want you to
take the camera.
We're going to make this movie.
All right, man.
Here.
You ever been back
this deep, Jay?
Oh, yeah, man.
I've got family in all
parts of the state.
So I've been around.
It's great back here, man.
Yeah it is.
I love the way
this thing handles.
Oh, I know.
It's perfect for the offroading.
What are you going
to do with that?
You gotta protect
yourself out here, man.
What?
Yeah, you don't know
what's going to happen.
Bears and shit.
Whoa!
Hey, Jay.
We're doing an
establishing shot.
I need you to walk
towards the barn.
All right.
Wait for action.
Go back to one.
And action!
So where's the
rest of the crew at?
Ah, don't worry
about that, Jay.
I'm going to have you act today.
Can you act?
Sure, yeah.
You good?
I mean, I can stand in.
Yeah.
I like that attitude.
How do you feel about nudity?
Partial nudity?
Just your shirt?
Are you going to
be rolling on that?
Yeah, I'm going
to be rolling, man.
Why?
Why do you need to
see me partially nude?
I told you earlier, Jay, we're
going to capture every moment.
And besides, I want to know
what you look like on camera.
So take your shirt off.
Just the shirt?
Yeah, just the shirt.
I promise.
You got a bug bite.
Your zipper's down too.
Hey, dude, what the fuck?
It's still down.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get it all the way.
Zip it up.
Just tell me.
I'm just trying to
help you out, man.
Come here.
Relax.
I'm hands on.
Look at this place.
It's beautiful.
It's a perfect place to
shoot a murder-- horror.
You OK?
Relax, man.
Relax.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
So what do we've got to do?
We're going to
shoot this movie, OK?
OK.
You're gonna do good.
Come on.
You need to buy
some new deodorant.
On-set etiquette.
Come on.
Let's go.
Man, look at all this shit.
Hey, Jay, what are you doing?
I'm just catching
some B-roll footage.
We don't have for
that shit, man.
I want you to shoot the
artsiest thing you can in here.
All right.
We got a lot to do today.
F-stops, light balances,
shutter speeds.
ISOs.
All that shit is happening, man.
Shoot some artsy shit.
All right.
You see that light coming in
over there through the boards?
Yeah, yeah.
How do you want me
to turn that up?
Go ahead and move to
your left a little bit.
All right.
I'm gonna go get
you the tripod, man.
You need it.
I like you though, man.
God, that's a
weird mother fucker.
That's a lot of hunting.
Jay!
The movie, Jay?
Come on!
Jay!
You did good, buddy.
You did real good.
Wave.
Bye!
Hey, Jay, Jay.
Listen up.
I've got something to tell you.
Don't be scared.
You're part of something
special, something
bigger than both of us.
Good night.
Good night, Jay.
The movie, Jay?
Come on, Jay!
I'm not gonna shoot you.
Jay!
You did good, buddy.
No, no, no, no.
You OK?
Huh?
Ah!
Give it to me!
You're tricky, huh?
You were born
to feed on others.
Born to take advantage.
Latching on, digging deep.
Drinking your victim dry.
Blood-sucking parasite.
Your days are numbered.
Hey, you know what?
You know what?
I am telling you, my friend,
this is easy money for you.
Yeah.
It's a cake walk.
I'm telling you.
All right?
So I'll see you in
about a half an hour.
OK?
You guys have a drink,
relax, I'll see you.
OK, bye.
Holy God Almighty.
What?
No, I'm heading over
there right now.
OK?
I'll call you when I'm done.
Look, I've got
this under control.
It's no big deal.
OK?
This is an easy sell for me.
I got it under control.
What did I just say?
I said I would call
you when I'm done.
All right?
Bye.
) Oh, well, yeah.
Well, I hope you can
sell this thing, Frank.
Mother fucker.
You've got to be kidding me.
Why don't you just
shut the fuck up.
) Why don't
you shut the fuck up?
I'm going to offer him the
same percentage this time, man.
)
That's not enough.
They're going to put down 80.
) OK.
You know?
You take 20, buy that
fucking TV you always wanted.
I take 20.
)
That sounds good.
I guarantee you, we can shoot
this thing for 30, no problem.
)
I'm sure we could.
And that leaves us 10
for the wrap party, man.
) Red
carpet time, baby.
You know what?
This time, no more
cheap fucking champagne.
I want Dom this time and
I want a stretch limo.
) I hear you.
And some strippers.
Exactly.
And all we've gotta come up
with is 20 to pay the crew.
) Yeah.
Fellas, this is
a fail-safe plan.
I've seen the drama.
I know how it works.
I own the DVD set.
I want Blu-ray.
Hey, what's it take to
get a fucking drink?
Alright.
Before we get crazy--
Don't get crazy on me.
--what's our guarantee?
Guarantee.
How do we know we're going
to get our money back.
I'm just kind of concerned
about the timeline.
Me and my girl, we just got
engaged when I got back.
to eat.
Are we doing good over here?
Doing well.
Thanks.
What I want you guys to do is I
want you to take this contract,
look at it tonight, sign it,
get back with me tomorrow.
OK?
It's going to happen
with you or without you.
We are going to make a
lot of money on this.
You can buy air time?
Yes, we can buy air time.
And we are going to make a
shitload more money selling
advertising.
OK?
Just think about it.
This is our chance
to do something big.
So I'm in.
Let's do it.
Ah, fuck it.
Balls.
It takes balls.
And two have got them.
Yeah.
I've got the money.
They signed on the dotted line.
Yes, that they-- I
told you they'd do it.
You got to relax
just a little bit
and trust me a little more, OK?
I trust you.
But what if your little soldier
boys want a return right away?
Well, what then?
They always want
their money back.
If they want their
fucking money back,
they reenlist another
two fucking years.
I don't give a fuck.
What's it, four years?
I don't know.
Listen, I don't give a shit.
I'm counting on you.
Huh?
What?
Hold on.
I gotta call you back, OK?
Alright, call me back later.
Fill that up.
Oh, that is wonderful.
That is really good.
Frank.
Did you drink too much again?
Wanna go for a ride?
You don't mind if I take this
for a spin, do you Frank?
You're really living
the life, man.
That's a beautiful picture too.
You ready to party tonight?
We're going to have
fun, just me and you.
We're gonna roll down the strip
and check out all the chicks.
I got a producer in the car.
Oh, yeah.
Woo!
That's luxury, Frank.
You ready?
He wasn't even in the club, OK?
He said he wasn't going
to come around anymore.
Jim just took it.
I know what Jim did.
Look, I don't have time
for this right now.
I got a lot going on.
I got a busy schedule.
Hey, Raven.
Get your little ass in here.
Look I need it OK?
We're working on a
project together.
Fine.
Take the fucking camera.
I heard about that little stunt
you pulled the other night.
He's a big spender,
a high roller.
Next time, keep your
fucking hands to yourself.
You want to be an
arm's length away,
slide your ass up on that stage
and go swing on that pole.
If it happens again, just smile.
Pretend you like it.
Deep down, I know that you do.
You're such a fucking asshole.
Get out of here.
I got work to do.
God, she's such a bitch.
Yeah, she is.
Oh, yeah.
be here by 6:00 tomorrow.
Yeah.
That's good.
Hey, I hope you're comfortable.
Sorry about the
restraints, Frank.
Just take this off.
Please take it off.
I had to make sure you're not
going to move around too much.
God damn it.
Help!
Nobody's gonna help you, Frank.
I got you, man.
Mother fucker.
Just take this fucking
shit off of me please.
What do you want?
I will give you
whatever you want.
Look at the camera!
That's what I want.
OK, I'm looking at the camera.
All right?
I'm looking at your
fucking camera.
Shh.
Listen.
Listen This is the last time
you could actually listen.
I have something I
want you to know.
It's special.
It's so special.
What is it?
I want you to
remember something.
What do you want
me to remember?
Just tell me what it is.
When you go to
the other place,
I want to know what it's like
because I'll see you later.
I'll see you later.
Help!
Hey, what's your name?
What is your name?
Come on, man.
What the fuck?
God damn it!
You like my sculpture?
It's almost done.
Please take these off.
Hey, you want money?
You want money?
It's not going to hurt you.
I'll give you as much
money as you need.
I'll give it to you.
No!
How does that feel, Frank?
Yeah!
Hello?
Hey, David.
It's Charlotte.
Hey, I got your camera back.
Thanks.
I got this project I want
to talk to you about.
Maybe we can get
together this week?
I'm free tomorrow.
I'm not working.
Um, is there a place maybe
we can get together, like,
near your house or something?
Yeah, you want to meet me
down at Greenfield Lake maybe
around 4 o'clock?
You know where that is?
Uh, huh.
Yeah.
I'll find it.
Hello?
Yeah, I'll find it, man.
Good lord, save me.
The devil's hand holds me.
Bright light I see.
Jesus, guide me.
Hey.
You found me.
Yeah.
You're pretty easy to find.
How are you?
I'm great.
How are you doing?
I'm doing good.
Cool.
You want to sit down?
Yeah.
Thanks.
What's with the producer tag?
Oh, it's just a stupid show
I'm working on right now.
It's cheesy.
You wouldn't like it.
I think I've seen
something on that.
It's the one-- the guy with
all the one-liners, right?
Yeah.
That's cool.
They messed up my
picture and my name.
Oh.
Um, here.
I brought your camera for you.
I forgot I had this.
Really?
I got a lot of them.
Right.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, not a problem.
It's really sweet.
It's not a big deal.
Did you have a hard
time getting it back?
I quit.
You quit?
Yeah.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I just got tired of doing
something I hate every day
so I could be happy later.
You know?
What is that, like, waiting
for your life to start?
Life is right now.
It's just--
This is our life.
Yeah.
I'm just ready to go somewhere.
I wish I could do
something big, you know?
I think fate
brought us together.
That's big.
You believe in that?
Destiny?
Yeah.
I think everything happens
for a reason, for sure.
It's so beautiful out here.
I know.
It's gorgeous.
I would love to just sit under
this tree with you all day.
I gotta get going though.
You have somewhere to be?
Yeah, I gotta be on set.
Oh, that's cool.
You want to go with me?
Really?
No, I can't take you.
Oh.
No, it's fine.
I've got somewhere to be anyway.
I still want to
work with you though.
Yeah?
I think we're
going to do-- I know
we're going to do
beautiful things together.
Cool.
I'm down with that.
Me too.
Well, I've got
tons of free time
now so you know how
to get up with me.
I'll be around.
I'll just run
into you somewhere.
Yeah.
See you later?
OK.
Bye.
We've got four bodies.
Three male, one female.
And they all appear
to be decapitated.
Well, John, I guess
they should have quit
while they were still ahead.
All right, cut, cut.
That's good!
Hey, check the gate.
If the gate--
I think that's as
high as it's going to go.
Listen, Sydney.
I told you $8,000 and that's it.
But they
don't have the money--
I pay your fucking mortgage
with the commission,
so shut the fuck up,
do what I tell you.
Listen, I'm
doing the best I can.
Shut the fuck up!
Jesus.
Where's that water I asked
for five minutes ago?
God damn, Neanderthals.
Woohoo!
Hey, Nathan!
You're looking good, man.
You killed that last scene.
Thanks.
Who are you?
I'm a producer.
I got this--
Before you go on, you
need to talk to my agent.
OK?
And if you don't have a budget,
fucking forget about it.
All right?
Give me that.
I've got some shit to do.
If you see me walking towards
you, get out of the way.
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm the star.
Can I get a fruit cup please?
Who's
got eyes on Marco?
I need Marco.
Somebody get Marco.
I've been watching you.
I've noticed your beauty.
You're cunning.
You're sneaky and I like it.
These traits, these masks that
you wear, they don't fool me.
They won't help you
escape your fate.
Woohoo!
Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, bro!
What are you doing?
I can't hear you.
My ears are under water.
I love your place, man.
Oh, I would live
here in a heartbeat.
You really made it big.
Get the fuck out of here
or I'm calling the cops.
OK?
Be cool, man.
I think-- I think you're,
uh, misjudging me.
I'm David.
We met earlier, remember?
On set?
I was that guy that
had that project
I wanted to talk to you about.
Yeah, yeah.
I got it.
All right.
Listen, you have 60 seconds
to get the fuck out of here
or I'm gonna smash your face in.
OK?
This shit is really good.
You want a glass?
Are you drinking my--
Uh, huh.
I also saw that picture
of your wife inside.
She is hot.
What the fuck is
wrong with you, man?
You know she's hot, man.
But I got this and I would
love you to sign it for me.
To David, my number one fan.
I love you.
You're fucking kidding me.
Come on, bro.
It's all good.
No.
Fuck no.
I'm calling the cops
before I kill you.
Look.
I got this project I want
to talk to you about.
I think you're going
to be perfect for it.
Nathan!
Wake up, sleepy head!
Woo!
I see you!
I'm so happy you decided
to do this project, Nathan.
I hope you like that wardrobe
I picked out for you specially.
Are you excited?
You look good in purple.
What the fuck is going on?
Listen.
Don't jump the gun, Nathan.
I know you're a bit
of a method actor,
but you're going to have to
fucking read the script first.
You better appreciate
what I'm doing for you.
What are you talking about?
Where the hell am I?
We're not playing
games all night, Nathan.
I paid you upfront
to do the job.
Now do it.
Check your left breast
pocket in your jacket.
I know you like money.
Is this a joke?
No.
Huh?
Are you kidding?
Get the fuck out of here, man.
Uh oh.
No running!
No running, Nathan.
Just acting.
Good acting.
Pick up the script and
read your fucking lines.
OK?
You would have had a lot
more time if you just
woke up earlier.
That means hurry the fuck up.
The cameras are rolling.
We gotta go.
You don't want to disappoint me.
This is fucking ridiculous!
Fuck!
OK!
If I didn't walk out
that door, I would--
Fucking stop doing that!
Stop!
I'm not buying it, Nathan.
It's bullshit.
You're way better than this.
I handpicked you because of it.
I would have resented her
for the rest of my life.
For the rest of my life.
I am not dealing
with you bullshit anymore.
It's not bullshit, Charlotte.
I'm telling you the truth.
You know, you have never been
good at making decisions.
Your-- your priorities
are all wrong.
What are you even
saying to me right now?
Look, I just-- I just think
that you need to have something
to fall back on, OK?
I mean, living like you're
going to get rich, make it big.
That doesn't happen
to people like us.
You are a regular person.
OK, you need to focus
on, you know, being happy
in your life right now.
You ain't going to
be no movie star.
Jesus.
Regular person, huh?
What, like you?
Where are you going?
Hello?
Hey.
David, it's Charlotte.
I was just thinking about you.
Ah, yeah.
I was just needing to get
out of the house, I guess.
I don't know.
Are you busy?
Yeah.
I got-- I got this stuff
that I gotta finish up.
How about we meet up at
whitey's around 8:00?
Yeah.
OK.
That works.
Yeah.
Bye.
Oh, Charlotte.
Do you have a date?
Oh, that's awesome.
Get a date.
Don't get a job.
Just go get a date.
That's a good idea.
Oh, my goodness.
Not the finger.
Nathan!
Wake up, sleepy head!
We got a lot to do tonight.
I got a date!
Aren't you excited?
What are you doing, man?
What are you doing?
I'm loving you.
I'm loving every minute of this.
Why are you doing this?
What did I do to you?
I want you to
sign this head shot.
Listen.
We can talk about this.
Yeah, let's
talk about it.
We can talk.
Before that
though, sign it.
If you're trying
to make something--
Say, to David,
my number one fan--
I can't sign!
--I love you.
XOXO.
I can't fucking sign!
Sign it!
You almost got me!
Oh, my God.
Are you--
You're so
pathetic, Nathan.
Yeah!
Listen.
You're making a movie, right?
You're making a movie?
I can fund it.
I can fund your movie.
I'll be in your-- no!
I love you, Nathan.
I'd stay and hang out with you,
but I've got some stuff to do.
I'm leaving and
I'm taking the car.
No, you're not.
I have an early shift.
You better be back on time!
It's my fucking car!
Grow up!
What are you doing
leaving the door open?
You're letting all
the freaking bugs in.
What's the matter with you?
Do you ever stop bitching?
Hey.
Did you already order?
Yeah.
I took a wild guess and I
got you that cup of coffee.
Thanks.
I could use it.
What's going on with your car?
Did you steal that
one from a rich guy?
No, it's mine.
I'm just joking.
My mom's just always borrowing
it to get to work, you know?
Somehow that just
doesn't seem fair to me.
It's not.
She's driving me crazy.
She started drinking again.
You guys know what you want?
I'm not really hungry.
You sure?
It's on me.
No, it's cool.
Get something.
I think, um, I
think I'll just have
a basket of fries with cheese.
No bacon please.
Cheese.
No pork.
All right.
You sure you don't
want anything, honey?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just ate.
Thank you.
So what did you tell
your mom about me?
Not a lot.
Just that you were
making a movie
and you want me to be in it.
Basically, I just want to focus
on my acting again, you know?
Yeah.
She doesn't believe in
that though, does she?
No.
It's like whenever there's
good news or an opportunity
for something, she just never
takes anything I say seriously,
you know?
I don't want to
end up like that.
No.
I don't think you can.
Where did you say your,
um, mom worked again?
She works at Everybody's.
I know, right?
Thank you.
I don't want to sound rude,
but you forgot my cheese again.
Cheese?
Mhm.
That's what I asked for.
All right.
Thank you.
I just wish
she'd hurry up and move out.
It's like everything
I say, you know?
She's so righteous about it.
It's like she thinks
I'm going to fail
and she's trying to
save me or whatever.
I just think she
can't stand to see
her daughter do
more than she has,
which isn't even that
much sadly, you know?
I don't think you have to
worry about your mom anymore.
She's going to be out of
your life soon, trust me.
You're going places.
I wish she'd hurry up an leave.
Yeah, like that's gonna happen.
Charlotte?
She's all right, I guess.
I know, we're kind of getting
on each other's nerves
a little bit.
Well, I mean, you know?
It's just mother daughter shit.
Whatever.
OK.
You know what?
She's got these guys
that are kind of, um,
looking at her for
some acting stuff.
I know!
It would be great.
I'm so proud of her.
I mean-- well, it's obvious
where she got the talent from.
From me.
God, I mean, don't
you remember--
Before I got knocked up,
everybody used to say,
you should go to Vegas.
Yeah, you should be dancing
in one of those shows.
Me and Jimmy at the Honey Club.
Oh God.
When we use to dance together.
We looked so good together.
I kind of miss those days.
That's so sweet.
Not as sweet as you, Charlotte.
I wonder what that feels like.
You'll know.
You'll know when you feel it.
So when can I see a script?
I'm still working on it.
I'm on my last revision now.
I'm still building it.
You're gonna like it.
Well, what's it about?
Tell me.
I mean, what kind
of movie is it?
I like to think of it as an
art film, visceral and alive.
It's raw meat.
Something that everybody
can connect to and feel.
It sounds like a masterpiece.
I'm excited.
I'm so glad you're excited.
I run across a
lot of people that
lack that kind of excitement.
Do you want to get out of here?
Yeah.
Where do you want to go?
Yeah!
You're good.
Strike.
You're up.
I haven't done this in awhile.
OK.
You suck!
It's all right.
You get another turn.
I need one.
I want to know about you.
What do you want
to know, Charlotte?
Where are you from?
How'd you start making movies?
I've been making
movies my whole life.
But I used to work for
somebody else, writing scripts.
And that didn't work out.
How?
There was a project
I was working on
and, uh, they made
a lot of promises.
And?
And nothing.
Nothing happened.
They forgot about me
and everybody else
that helped them.
Go ahead.
Bowl for me.
Serious?
Yeah.
I'm having so much fun.
I forgot what it
was like to bowl.
How could they do that?
Easy.
They just did.
They forgot about me.
They'd forget about you too.
Who's they?
I wouldn't worry about them.
They're not doing
anything anymore.
I guess it all
caught up to them.
You seem pretty
sure about that.
Yeah, yeah.
I am sure about it.
And I'm sure about something
else too, Charlotte.
That's why I'm making
my own project.
You're the one key
piece of talent.
You are!
What?
It's going to be beautiful.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm gonna roll a good
one for you, Charlotte.
OK.
You ready?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Did you see that?
It was beautiful.
I saw.
Just like you.
Did I tell you that before,
that you're beautiful?
All right, I'm off to
make the big dollars for you.
I'll see you around 11:00.
Like a fucking teenager.
Shh.
Help!
Let me out!
Let me go!
Please, let me go!
Please!
Let me go!
What are you doing to me?
Mom?
Why are you doing this?
Don't you come near me!
Mom, where are you?
Mom?
Charlotte!
I was surrounded by
negativity for so long,
I became blind to what I had.
What are you doing?
I'm making magic!
But after seeing you, I knew
what I was doing was right.
Come on, Mary.
Talk to me.
Talk to me!
I don't know what you want.
You know what I want.
I want you to tell me the truth
for once in your fucking life.
I want you to understand
that your appearance is corruption.
By showing it to you,
showing you what not to be.
It really is all about you now.
Not them.
You're so beautiful.
Fuck you!
You want some of that?
I know you do.
You were right.
No, no, no, no.
Please, no!
You should think
about your daughter.
Right?
We're in another situation
where you're just
talking about yourself.
Fuck Charlotte, OK?
Is that what you want?
You're right.
I hate her.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
Is that it?
Because now you've got it, OK?
Can I please leave?
She ruined my life.
I was going to have a career.
Not her.
Me!
So you're saying
that your life is
more important than hers?
I-- I had something really
special and then she fucking
came along and I
couldn't do anything.
I think I might believe you
because I'm almost gonna cry.
Because you're so fucking--
They were just the
tools, the pieces I needed
in this greater creation.
This rebirth.
Your rebirth.
Charlotte!
The first time I saw you
I knew you were special.
You're the one.
She's gone!
She didn't love you!
I love you, Charlotte!
I gave you what you wanted.
You can be whoever
you want to be.
I created all this
for you, Charlotte.
It's always been about you.
You're free!
You're free.
You can do whatever you want.
You can be whoever--
No!
I want you to like it!
I would recommend
at this point walk away.
You've had your share of
lies and hurt and venom
that I've saved in
my cold blue veins.
Bumping with fear and pain.
I'm not sure exactly how
it's easy trusting you.
Hung out and manipulated,
I've called myself
a fool again and again.
One damn foolish man.
The tragedy has ended.
The angel has ascended
from the pedestal I put her on.
When you awake, I will be gone.
Charlotte, Charlotte, It's true.
My love, this is just for you.
Charlotte, Charlotte, it's true.
You are now free to pursue.
The years the clock
has spun, I've
questioned long and hard
motives that may be driving me
and will they leave you
scarred as I start to see?
Pieces of you and me.
So step up to the plate.
Let's see what you can take.
I built these walls
around my heart
to block out all the pain,
but you broke right through.
There's something good in you.
The broken is now mended.
And I never intended for you
to fall face first into my arms.
I promise I will help.
I will do no harm.
You've showed me that your pure heart
can offer us a new start.
Yeah, I'm living
and letting it grow.
And I just wanted
for you to know
in my own weird way I love you.
My damaged soul feels
rescued from a sea of lies
and of regrets.
So let's turn the page
and see what happens next.
The tragedy has ended.
Oh Charlotte.
The angel has ascended.
Hey, yo.
I think we all get a
little crazy sometimes.
I think we all get
a little David Long.
I'm David Long He's David Long.
She's David Long.
We're all David Long.
I'm David Long.
He's David Long.
She's David Long.
We're all David Long.
David Long.
Keep the guns.
Give me the knives
and the gasoline.
A car battery, box
cutter, and a casket.
Like Michael Myers and
remake all of his action
scenes, and walk around
with a lumberjack
axe and my baggy jeans.
You aint' half as mean.
You  as Queen.
What?
You ain't get the memo
through your fax machine
that I was coming to phase
you out like a track machine?
I'm trapped in dreams.
When we slash, they bleed.
Look them in the eye and ask
them do they have to scream?
I'm a savage wreaking havoc
in the blackest deeds.
But if you haven't, you can
splatter like a flower screen.
Like the ring boy coming
through your plasma screen.
Don't make me drown you in your
tub until your ass is clean.
I'm  so watch
what you asking me.
I bet it's hard to talk shit
when you're lacking teeth.
Take your leave.
No pressure, all
stress relieved.
See, basically, there's a
David Long in all of us.
And locked inside, there's a
David Long that follows us.
Wherever we go,
he's going there to follow us.
Release the crazy things
that we keep bottled up
with David Long.
I'm David Long.
He's David Long.
She's David Long.
We're all David Long.
I'm David Long.
He's David Long.
She's David Long.
We're all David Long.
David Long.
Give me five or pump
three for my chainsaw.
It's called a chainsaw,
but I call it my pain saw.
I have you leaking different
colors like crayons.
Do the job and leave,
like I just got laid off.
You think you got me figured
out, but you're way off.
You can't control me like a
game when it's turned off.
You go soft.
I go.
Catch them with a bullet and
hit them in the.
Me cleaver, chop your
fat off like a cigar.
These are stars I
throw like ninja.
You can run all you want, but
I promise you won't get far.
You're a pussy
like a your sister.
I'll hit you til you see stars.
And now you can barely stand,
but I'm the fucking retard?
You're probably gonna need arms,
but your hands are tied up.
And I'm gonna dump you where
them garbage cans line up
and leave you there.
They smell you
before they ride up.
David Long.
Basically, there's a
David Long in all of us.
And locked inside, there's a
David Long that follows us.
Wherever we go,
he's going there to follow us.
Release the crazy things
that we keep bottled up
with David Long.
I'm David Long.
He's David Long.
She's David Long.
We're all David Long.
I'm David Long.
He's David Long.
She's David Long.
We're all David Long.
David Long.