Clyde?
I've always loved you, Bonnie.
I've always loved you.
How long is it gonna take?
Till it cools off.
Hey, keep them kids out of there!
Hey, hey, hey!
Slow down!
- Get back.
- Come on, let's see what's here.
Did you hear me?
Get back over here!
What is it?
Get back. Come on.
Boys, get away from there!
Get them out of here!
Do you hear me?
I was born Clyde Chestnut Barrow...
...in Telico, Texas,
on March 24th, 1909.
Being Christian,
I don't much believe in astrology...
...but I'm told I'm an Aries.
Three and seven
are my favorite numbers...
...end I keep e horseshoe
under my bed for good luck.
I like fast cars...
...girls you wanna talk to
much as undress...
...and my mama.
When I was 9 years old...
...I contracted e fever
of unexplained origin.
Almost died
before I really started living.
My great-grandma said
that was why the Lord saw Ht...
...to bless me with what she called
"the second sight."
Clyde?
What on earth
do you think you're doing?
Know what'll happen
if you get yourself better, little Clyde?
I 'll be out there waiting on you,
that's what.
I don't think he dead yet.
Come on.
- It needs more pepper.
- No.
I made what you like, you'll eat it
the way I make it. Now, have a seat.
I think it needs more pepper.
- Daddy, can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
- Do you believe in angels?
- Of course I do.
You got one there on your shoulder.
Of course,
you got a devil on the other one.
Ob, baby, baby, baby.
No meat again?
You're a keen one,
you know that, Marvin?
Told you I don't wanna be called that.
- He wants to be called Buck.
- That's right.
How about we compromise
and call you a horse's ass?
Now, sit down
and eat your damn peas.
Hallelujah.
Clouds be gone.
Clyde Chestnut's got better.
You're my little ray of sunshine,
aren't you, Clyde?
My criminal career
began with my brother Buck...
- Hurry up.
- ...stealing chickens.
- I'm trying.
- We gotta go.
- Hey!
- Come on, Marvin!
It's Buck, doggone it!
- Go! Go, go!
- I'm going!
Run!
- Stop!
- You old coot!
Maybe if I hadn't found Bonnie Parker...
...all I'd ever be known for
was stealing chickens.
Come on!
You got music in your bones,
little man.
Is something eating at you, Clyde?
I saw something again, Mama.
Something happening to Buck.
Something might happen to Buck,
Clyde...
...but I don't need Great-Grandma's
second sight nonsense to know that.
Ain't nothing to it, you hear me?
Nothing.
What a smart kid does,
and that's what you are...
...he don't wait around
for visions of the future.
He starts to make the future happen
by what he does today.
You ain't just smart,
you got a good heart.
- Now, get your little butt to bed.
- All right.
Marvin.
Time to wake up.
Buck. Get your ugly butt up...
- ...got a hard day's work.
- No.
Hey, Clyde.
Ever seen a car like that?
That's a Ford Model A Victoria...
...four cylinders, leather back...
...about 40 horses under the hood.
Do about 50 without blowing a gasket,
maybe 55.
Sound like booze to you?
Don't think we're dressed
for the occasion. Let's go home.
What we lack in tailoring,
we'll make up for with charm. Come on.
Come on, free drinks.
All right, all right, hey, hey!
Hold it. I'll need all the boys
that ain't hitched yet...
...to come to the middle of the floor.
Leg, please.
Right on time.
Oh, this one's mine, boys,
this one's mine.
Here it comes.
I think you been gawking at the bride
long enough.
Why don't you and your buddy...
...take your party-crashing asses
out of here?
L-Hey.
- You hear me, boy?
- Oh, I hear you...
...but unless you plan on using that,
don't touch me again.
Come on, Clyde. Company ain't worth
a good goddamn anyway.
Thanks for the drink, sport.
Jesus, Clyde, that girl's
playing to everybody. Come on.
But I didn't see it like that.
I thought Bonnie Parker
had always been looking for me...
...like I 'd always
been looking for her.
Jesus.
Look, I'm pretty sure
they're wearing a watch on us.
- Hey.
- Go on.
- And .... Miss, that's right.
- Jesus.
It's the damn gun.
Blanche not only got
the tight hind quarters...
...she got a cousin out in Pantego
makes white lightning.
Since I did most of the work, I figure
I get first cheese on choosing Blanche.
- What?
- Yeah.
Look, I could be flexible.
Jesus. Enough killing them damn cans.
I got prime out at the ready.
Oh, man, she's all yours, all right?
Them hind quarters is for you.
I ain't got no interest in that poontang.
Gonna be gone a couple weeks.
I got some business in Amarillo.
What about my business?
What, you mean show business?
You know how many girls out there
are dreaming that same dream?
- No, Roy. How many?
- Too many.
You saying we aren't going to New York
in the spring like we talked?
Just saying we're going to Amarillo first.
And Los Angeles in the fall.
Yeah. And Los Angeles in the fall.
You're full of shit, aren't you, Roy?
Jesus.
You expect me to just waste my life...
...wearing out my feet and hands down
at Marco's greasy spoon, don't you?
This... This ain't living, brother.
This is dirt getting
so far up my butt crack...
...it's starting to leak into my damn head.
You're lazy, you know it?
Lazy people never get nowhere.
Hey, know that butt crack
I was talking about?
Why don't you give it a big kiss?
They say everyone's a product
of their time and place.
Well, Bonnie and my time
was the dirty '30s...
...and our place in it
was pretty close to rock bottom.
Never told me
what you thought about my plan.
Ain't a plan. That's a blueprint to get
your ass thrown in the hoosegow.
You go in on a Saturday
when they're closed...
...they ain't gonna have enough money
to last the weekend.
You'd have to steal wheels
to get away.
There isn't any woods to hide in
for a half mile.
- So you have thought about it?
- No, I haven't.
Well, you got a better idea?
Maybe.
All right!
- Yeah!
- We got it!
I knew it'd work! I knew it!
We got laws.
Go! Step on it!
Come on!
Never catch Clyde the Drive!
Clyde.
Ain't nobody
gonna catch us Barrow boys.
Evening, folks!
Hell, Clyde, it's a dead end.
- Let's go. Hey, leave the damn safe.
- The hell with that.
- Leave the damn safe.
- No.
Hold it! Stop, police!
Stop, police! Freeze!
Give it up, boy!
This way!
Down there, by the pond!
Hold it!
Slow down, boy! You can't get away!
We got him!
Just got back
from the pen in Huntsville.
- Marvin all right?
- How come you haven't been?
Not a big fan of penitentiaries.
Well, he asked about you.
He asked if you were being safe.
Told me to tell you it wasn't safe
to go swimming out in Colter's Pond.
He said "safe," like, four times,
like it was code or something.
Well, Buck isn't as sharp as you, Nell.
I doubt he has the smarts
to talk in code.
- Hey, why aren't you in school?
- Because school's for saps.
What'd you just say, little sister?
- Relax. Mrs. Rose got sick, sent us home.
- All right.
- And you didn't finish school.
- Well, I should.
I should've.
You want to be like brother Buck?
Or you want to be like idiot Clyde?
Hey, I got some gossip
you might find interesting.
- Really?
- Don't we have an arrangement?
All right, this better be good.
- You extortion Annie over here.
- So rumor has it Roy took off again.
It's the third time he done it.
And Ella Jean told Iris Cantor's sister,
who told me...
...what Bonnie wrote in her diary
on New Year's Eve.
She said if Roy didn't come back
by the stroke of midnight...
...her and Roy was all done.
She moved in with her mama.
Unless you've got the money
to purchase...
...you mind keeping your grubbies
off my Silks?
You seem more of a cotton
kind of fella anyway.
Well, today I'm feeling kind of silky.
Come on. Don't you think silk's
a little pricey for a fella like you?
- You getting fresh with me?
- No, ma'am.
I sure as hell
wouldn't get fresh with you.
You know what?
Why don't you just go back
to whatever hole...
...you got your fingers so dirty
digging out of?
All right,
but before I climb into said hole...
...could I buy
all five of them here shirts?
Got the money right here.
You get out of here. You go on.
You get before I call the laws.
Go on.
People are always trying to blame others
for what goes wrong in their lives...
...but the real culprit's
usually a lot closer to home.
Bonnie?
What happened, Bonnie?
What's wrong?
Whatever it is, honey, whatever it is,
it'll be okay.
They said no, didn't they?
It'll be okay, sweetheart.
Your time will Come.
You're a precious thing.
The most precious thing.
You've got to learn
to keep yourself calm.
Scared the daylights
out of your mama.
Worst fit you ever had.
I'm almost 20.
My husband left me...
...and I'm stuck here in Cement City
with prospects none, Mama.
You will do no such thing. You will
keep this with your special things.
Most girls don't even have
the gumption...
...to get a rejection letter
from a movie studio.
So there.
Up, up!
The memories you've given me.
You know there were over 100 kids
trying to win this?
And why Texas Monthly
didn't publish your poems ....
The squirrel makes his case
Yappy, quite sure that his song is elixir
Melancholy's cure
Mama, they're not that good.
And when all those kids froze up
and forgot their parts...
...you got that audience clapping.
Cartwheels, handsprings.
Who's got the moxie
to just take over like that?
- You gave them what they wanted, Bon.
- But I never even got to my soliloquy.
Maybe I'll never get to my soliloquy.
I will never forget this day.
And now Miss Bonnie Parker
would like to sing a song for her father.
This was my daddy's favorite song.
Evening, Mrs. Parker.
I'd like to see your daughter,
as I've got intentions to take her out.
- Is she expecting you?
- No, ma'am.
We've never really met.
Bonnie?
Believe you've got a gentleman caller.
- Mr...?
- Barrow.
Clyde "Champion" Barrow.
You were at my wedding.
I was.
Friend of the groom's'?
You talked to Roy recently, have you?
Guess you're not one much
to let the kettle cool.
Not me.
Is this car yours?
Tonight it sure is.
Keep them both on the wheel, huh?
All right.
What can I get you?
- Two fingers of whiskey'd be nice for me.
- Whiskey sounds good.
- How about you put a little soda in hers?
- Yes, sir.
You gonna be all right for a minute,
Bonnie Parker?
Sure. Where you going?
Well, music's calling,
I'm just answering the bell.
I don't know if I can remember a night
that can hold e candle to this.
It's almost like it's meant to be.
Like you and me.
You can't talk about meant to be
when we haven't even kissed yet.
I didn't say I wanted to kiss you.
Yeah, you did.
So you're convinced after one date
and one middling kiss...
...that I'm the girl's gonna make
your dreams come true?
Nope.
I'm convinced I'm the man's
gonna make yours come true.
I get clear, I'll come calling.
Hold it! Stop!
- All right, don't nobody move!
- Get out of the way!
- Move!
- Get on the back door!
We're shutting the joint down!
Don't nobody move!
You're all under arrest!
This is an illegal establishment!
Don't nobody move,
and nobody gets hurt!
Where do you think you're going?
I know you.
He's the other joker
who stole that safe.
You want a slice of Cobbler with that joe,
Ted?
Just coffee today, Bonnie.
Something on your mind?
Yeah, actually.
Heard you got dragged
out of a Speakeasy last night.
Who you seeing
taking you to a place like that?
What do you think
your mama would say?
What are you gonna do, tell her?
No.
Herald might.
Things slow down at Marco's'?
Nothing new about that.
It's nice of you
to try to spare me the indignity...
...but Mrs. Haskell called
as soon as she saw it.
She tried to sound so distraught.
She got on the party line...
...and clucked about my
wayward daughter to all the hens.
Well, you're the one that let him in.
Get that out of here.
Choices made.
Roads gone down
or turned away from.
From my experience...
...trying to figure out why people
do the things they do defies ell logic.
Clyde Barrow.
And Bonnie Parker.
Clyde and Bonnie.
Bonnie and Clyde.
Maybe if somebody left open
a door they shut...
...maybe if we were living in times of
milk and honey instead of grit and piss...
...Bonnie might have just faded off
into obscurity.
Maybe if they weren't celebrating
anyone who dared rise up.
Hell, maybe if I wouldn't have promised
to make all her dreams come true...
...Bonnie would've forgotten
all about me.
Lord knows she should've.
Can I help you with something?
I hope so.
I wanted to see one of your prisoners.
Mr. Clyde Barrow.
I'm Clyde's wife.
That's a nice ring.
And I'd like to help,
but we're just a holding tank here.
There's no visitation allowed,
even spousal.
- Oh, ma'am, you all right?
- I don't know.
We hadn't even gone
on our honeymoon yet.
And he's gonna be sent away
to hard time, I know it.
And I'm gonna be left alone
for God knows how long.
Your wife's here, Barrow.
Hello, honey.
Let's make it short and sweet.
Jesus, Bonnie,
I can't believe you're here.
What are you doing?
Where'd you get that?
- It isn't important.
- Bullshit, it's not.
- Don't want you getting mixed up in this.
- For Pete's sake, Clyde, take the gun.
Don't take it.
- We'll be in federal lockup by Friday.
- Well, nobody asked you, cracker.
You got one minute.
Clyde Barrow,
if anything's meant to be between us...
...I think it better start being now.
- it's empty.
- Well, I didn't know that.
And neither will they.
I borrowed my uncle's car. I'll be waiting
by Miller's Creek until midnight.
Lord have mercy.
Stop!
Ain't nowhere for you to go!
Hold it right there!
- We got you, Turner!
- Barrow!
That's it.
Move over.
That's the way.
Barrow! Don't you do it!
Ain't even in third yet.
I got your suit in the back.
Even got us a place to go.
What?
I used to keep a horseshoe under my bed
for good luck.
You aren't the only one feeling lucky,
Mr. Barrow.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, I bent the rim on my Ford.
You do any wheelwrighting?
Yeah, I'll help you out
as soon as I'm done with him.
- That's your horse out front?
- I think I'm more his than he's mine.
Not a bad idea
if you're the man riding him.
Yeah, I sit around eating
more than I used to.
It's one of the downsides of retirement.
- What'd you used to do?
- I was a Texas Ranger.
You don't say.
I bet wrongdoers hated having you
with that big mount of yours on their ass.
That'll be two bits, Mr. Hamer.
Hamer?
- Are you Frank Hamer?
- I used to be.
Frank Hamer.
- You didn't tell me what you do, son.
- Oh, I'm looking for work.
Pretty good with cars, if you know
anybody looking for a grease monkey.
I'll keep an eye out.
You seem personable.
You don't find a job right away,
don't stop looking.
A lot of people falling in the wrong line
of endeavor these days.
Not that I'm suggesting you would.
Appreciate the fatherly.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Hamer.
Rumor had it
Hamer could see #red bullets...
...hear sounds before they were made.
The press had even given a name
to his .45 Colt: Old Lucky.
Which had nothing to do with the chances
of the outlaws who met up with Hamer.
Right then, I made a pact with myself
One job to give me and Bonnie a stake.
That was gonna be it.
- Clyde?
- Yeah?
Some guy's here to see you.
Says his name's Methvin.
- Good.
- What's he here for?
The oil refinery job.
But I thought you said
that was a two-man job.
Yeah, it is, and he's the other man.
What are you talking about?
We planned that together.
I'm the one that did the casing.
More than you should've.
Methvin's got experience. It's gonna
be better for everybody, all right?
Now, could you please
get me my pants?
Get me my damn pants.
- Excuse me, what's your name again?
- Methvin, Henry Methvin.
Well, Clyde's changed his mind,
Henry.
- He won't be needing you.
- Now, hang on, Bonnie.
Hey, Henry. Hey, good to see you.
- Just a little misunderstanding.
- Damn it, Clyde Barrow.
We had an agreement
to do this together, me and you.
Yeah, well, you gonna carry a gun with
these heels and that little purse of yours?
- Those are nice shoes.
- What if you need to run in these shoes...
...because somebody's trying
to put buckshot up our asses?
Well, I'll kick them the hell off.
Now, tell Mythman here...
...that we don't need him.
Fine. Fine.
All right. All right, already.
All right, heretofore...
...the oil refinery is a three-man job.
Are you happy now?
- Well, show him a smile.
- Yeah.
All right.
Clyde, the turn to the oil refinery's
back there.
But the guns are stashed out here.
- Out here?
- Yeah.
Where?
Just yonder.
That old wagon right there,
just under the hay.
You want me to get them?
You want to be a part
of this three-man job or not?
In here?
Pick you up in a couple hours
when it's over!
Clyde!
Clyde, you...!
Goddamn it, Clyde!
I think she could've managed
the lookout.
Need a lift, miss?
What'd they do?
Broke into an oil refinery.
- Tried to take the payroll.
- Would've gotten it too...
- ...if we'd had a lookout.
- No lookout.
Imagine that.
Huntsville's bad.
But unless you get Eastham Farm,
you'll be all right, which you shouldn't.
Small-time stuff you done
and being only...
- How old are you?
- Twenty-one.
Unless somebody screws up
or you bone the warden's daughter...
...neither of you will get the Farm.
I'm Bud Russell.
And I'm tougher than all
you guys put together.
Driven this chariot
over one-and-a-half million miles...
...and only lost one con in all that time.
And that eats at me
every single minute.
Do not think
you're gonna be number two.
- Hell you looking at?
- I ain't looking at nothing.
- You got attitude, boy?
- I ain't got no attitude.
I'm thrilled to be here,
what with you the warm welcoming sort.
You're shit. Shit going nowhere.
Get your worthless ass
in that one-way wagon.
Pretty sure that just bought you
the Farm.
You tell me you're going to church,
and you wind up here.
You snuck him in that gun, didn't you?
Oh, don't look at me like that.
You had any sense, you'd know
the best thing could've happened...
...was he got hauled right back in.
There is no reason a girl like you
cannot find a good man.
Don't you go into
one of your fits over him.
Do not let that happen.
Settle your breathing,
like I taught you, you hear me?
He's better for me than Roy, Mama.
That, my daughter, isn't saying,
excuse my French, jack-the-F-shit.
You deserve yourself
way better than Clyde Barrow.
Ted Hinton told me
they gave him 14 years.
You need to stop this.
You need to look me in the eye...
...and tell me you won't waste another
moment thinking about that boy.
Pick up the pace!
Man, Honolulu ain't got nothing
on this place.
Get digging, Barrow!
Get on deep in that ditch, boy!
Think he's getting
sweet on you, Clyde?
I don't know what's worse, the high rider's
whip or the big guy's affections.
I'll take the high rider.
Hey, Sunday after church,
my parents are having a picnic.
My dad makes killer ribs.
Not a big rib girl, Ted.
Well, now, you don't have to eat.
There'd be... There'd be plenty to do.
You know, I do some barbershop
with the boys at Dallas P.D.
I know you're into musicals,
maybe you'd like it.
Well ....
I'll think about it, huh?
- Thanks, Ted.
- Hey.
Before you go, I was...
I was thinking maybe we should kiss.
Ted...
...I'm not gonna listen to you sing,
or catch any more rides home with you.
L... I like you, but nothing...
...more.
Well, I hope we can always be friends.
Got enough darn friends.
The hell you doing?
- It was itching to be smelled.
- Yeah? Smell these.
I hope you don't mind
that I write every day.
But it's the only way for me
to cope with the loneliness...
your incarceration
has visited upon me.
I wonder what your days are like.
Hope things there at Eastham
aren't as bad as folks say.
And I hope the knowledge that
you've got a woman waiting for you...
...makes it somehow more tolerable.
But I hope these poetic stanzas
I've authored for you...
...will bring some solace
to your time there.
And she thought of herself
As only a stone
Drifting the cosmos so terribly alone
Days turned to years and eons
And still
She found not her orbit
No gravity until
The music of the spheres
Revealed it clear
Spinning alone
And suddenly so near
The moon found her earth
They danced all that night
And forever they would
Because that's what was right
Stop standing around! Get to work!
So the incident with Mr. Hamilton
was just an unfortunate accident?
No, sir, it was a very painful one.
Yeah. That's some nice work there.
You ever think about mounting
any wayward inmates?
On the wall, I mean.
You know, I voted no
on the leniency owing to your injury.
But my vote's but one of seven.
I'm sorry you're in the minority there,
but I just want to thank you...
...for all the lessons I learned
in this lovely facility.
Yeah, you won't be seeing
Clyde Barrow again.
Oddly, I believe I will.
I'm sure you know that...
...you were near to pardon even if you
had kept all ten of your little piggies.
Your mother
and a gal named Bonnie Parker...
...have been writing letters
to the governor on your behalf.
Apparently, he was about
to have me send you home.
Oh, Barrow?
Hope you don't mind.
I kept one.
Why didn't somebody tell me
the governor was about to pardon me?
Well, the notion one of us had
was to keep it a surprise.
Well, l... I thought it'd be nice.
I love surprises.
Well, I do too.
Maybe you ought to let Bonnie drive.
She's the one who borrowed the oar
from some friend of hers.
It ain't like my damn neck's
broken, Mama. I can drive.
You're gonna come in, aren't you?
Your daddy'd want to see you.
No, I'll probably come by Sunday.
Get some of that
wonderful ham of yours.
What?
Just don't know.
Just don't know that she's
gonna be good for you, Clyde.
No, she's fine.
Now, maybe she don't measure up
to you, but trust me...
...Bonnie's more than good enough
for me, all right?
Bonnie?
No need to rush things.
Probably sounds crazy.
Guy like me, convict and all...
...but I ain't afraid
of making a commitment.
I ain't afraid of making a baby.
I'm giving up criming.
I'm going straight-arrow.
I want to do it for you.
I don't know how to say this,
but I sort of ....
I seen our future.
I seen us in a big white house...
...with big columns...
...on the prettiest lake you ever saw.
I'm gonna build you that house, Bon.
And we gonna fill it with as many
little ones as you want.
That is, if that's what you want.
Of course it's what I want.
I just didn't expect we'd start
the making-babies part just yet.
Want some time
with just the two of us first.
If that's all right with you.
How much you think
they'd sell that for?
That house?
Probably like 5000.
Seems like it might as well be a million.
How do you reckon
we get that kind of money?
- I don't know. I can find work.
- Well, raising kids isn't Cheap either.
There's doctor bills and clothes.
You spend a lot of money
on clothes for girls.
And day-laboring ain't gonna be
enough for all that.
I know cars. If I could get someone
to front me some money...
- ...I could open my own service station.
- I can just see all the bankers...
...falling all over to see who can give
the convict the biggest bundle.
Hey. Ex-con.
Why don't you give it a rest, huh?
Well, you're the one
with all the big dreams.
Calling Car 28, Car 2-8.
There 's a holdup at 4th and Main.
Come on, baby, we got something
hot on the platter here.
- You seen this before?
- What?
Well, right before the exciting parts,
you keep squeezing my hand.
Well, of course I do.
I can tell when they're coming,
what with the music...
...the way they put it together and all.
Bonnie never told me
exactly how to keep her happy.
She never told me one last job
wouldn't be enough.
She just kind of let me
figure it out for myself.
Next, please.
I'd like to make a withdrawal.
Put it down!
- Put it down!
- Drop it!
Get his gun! Everybody,
get on the ground right now!
Hey, there, you stupid?
Put your head down!
- All right, take it easy. Take it easy.
- Ain't gonna hurt nobody!
All right. Give me all your cash.
Come on.
Well, that's it?
Yeah, that's it.
Let's go to the vault. Come around!
- Move. Move!
- You too. Move!
- Move! Move!
- Easy, now.
- There's no money in the vault.
- He's clearly lying.
He's a banker, that's what they do.
- Why isn't it locked?
- Well, like I said...
...there's a depression on.
The bank's closing.
- Everybody, in the box!
- I'm claustrophobic.
- Well, I'm Baptist. Get in.
- Look, we won't tell.
We won't call the cops or nothing.
- Don't mess with Bonnie and Clyde.
- Do as they say.
- Everybody, in the vault!
- Get in the vault!
Get in! Get in the vault.
- Right inside, there you go!
- Just get in, move.
What the hell you tell them
our damn names for?
Don't go shooting your damn gun.
Half the town probably heard.
What you yelling for?
I got them where you told them to go.
Because it ain't damn
"Bonnie and Clyde," all right?
It's "Clyde and Bonnie."
That's right.
You look a lot more womanly
when you let your hair down.
I followed you from work,
and the door wasn't locked.
I've been reading your articles
in The Herald.
You do a great job...
...considering you're under the strictures
of reporting just the facts.
Oh, I'm not criticizing. I just ....
What with all the foreclosures
and woes of the stock market...
...seems like people could stand
a little less black-and-white truth...
...and a skosh more being entertained.
What are you doing here?
I'm just a fan.
Oh, I gotta say, I was surprised
when I found out P.J. was a woman.
You always called yourself P.J.?
Or was that your boss's idea...
...to stop your readers from finding out
you were a Patricia?
Maybe it's me, but seems like things
are moving forward for our gender.
What with that Amelia Earhart
fixing to fly across the Atlantic...
...and you in the newsroom
writing about crime...
...and me out there committing them.
I couldn't help but notice...
...you only put Clyde's name down.
Nice of you to mention me
only as "female companion."
Wasn't my idea.
My editor said if a girl was involved
in an armed robbery, it had to be...
- ...her man making her do it.
- Really?
Imagine that.
Would you please
get out of my house?
Oh, yeah, sure. Sorry.
Oh, goodness, P.J.,
I never introduced myself.
I'm Bonnie Parker.
A la Bonnie and Clyde.
I'm busy. Looks like you got something
going on in that fine-looking head...
You wanted my story twice as interesting,
but out out the interesting part.
A woman used a shotgun
in a strong-arm robbery...
...and I get a quarter of a column on
page 12 and I can't even use her name?
- So, what do you want from me?
- Let me follow the story.
Write it the way I want
or I'll go find a paper that will.
Maybe you'd better start finding...
...because a skirt trying to act like
she isn't, that I don't need.
You know, when you keep putting guns
in people 's faces...
...the gods tend to frown
on such behavior...
...and all sorts of things can go awry.
- Clyde? You ran us out of gas.
- Gauge said it was a quarter full.
Well, laws will be on us.
Damn it.
All right, let's go. Come on.
Come on, run. Come on. Let's go.
Go!
- Do you know where we're going?
- Not at the moment.
- All this for $46 in the rm.
- $46.32, baby.
Get down. Get down.
- Did you get them, Clyde?
- Ain't trying.
I ain't killing laws. No future in that.
Y'all better give up!
Come out with your hands up!
Do we give up, Clyde?
If I do, I'm 20 years in jail.
Then you go. You go. Run. Run.
- I ain't gonna leave you, Bonnie.
- I ain't got a record.
They'll throw me in jail.
I'll talk my way out.
Give it up, Barrow!
- You told those bank clerks your name.
- Well, that was clear across the state.
Nobody put my damn name
in the paper anyway.
All right, ma'am, on your feet.
Let's go.
Promise to tell the truth,
the whole truth and nothing but the truth?
I do.
Funny, when you're an outlaw,
you tell so many lies...
...after a while, you don't know
what's a lie and what isn't.
And Bonnie, she could really
spin e story.
I must admit,
I fell under the sway of Clyde Barrow.
Believed like... Like a schoolgirl,
I could right what was wrong in him.
And when the criming started,
I couldn't stop it.
I tried to get away,
but Clyde wouldn't let me.
He wouldn't sleep till he put
a out of leather between my lips...
...and bound me up in rope
in nothing but my underclothes.
And this limp of mine.
Clyde tied me up so tight...
...I lost circulation all the way
from my ankle to my thigh.
Bondage, it's horrible.
Truly God-awful horrible.
Almost more than a woman can bear.
And when Clyde wanted his way with me,
there wasn't much I could do.
I only weigh 106 pounds
and Clyde was so strong.
And l... Forgive me, Jesus.
... I was so weak.
What me and Bonnie done,
those we stole from and the laws...
...they'd probably tell things different.
Hell, even Bonnie, sure she would too.
Bonnie 'd surely tell it with more flair.
Take some water, ma'am.
Take some water.
Thank you.
I can't tell you how good it is
to see you out of that godforsaken hole.
Jail is no place for a lady.
- Like the new 'do.
- And I was fond of your performance.
- Haven't seen your byline in a while, P.J.
- Yeah, well, things are tough all over.
- What was she talking about?
- She's a reporter.
- Gotta talk about something.
- Gee, you looked good, Bonnie.
I picked up that little old chest of yours.
It's right where you said it was.
So, what do you want to do?
Go to a show?
Maybe buy a new dress?
I got a little money saved.
Gr, you're worn out. You just want
to go home and do each ether's nails?
- Afraid I'm not going home, Mama.
- What?
Some of what I said in that courtroom...
...it wasn't true.
- Clyde never took me, Mama.
- Of course he did.
You've been telling me he did since
the first time I sat with you in your cell.
You're saying he didn't take you?
Everything you've been telling me,
everything you said before that judge...
- ...that was all just an act.
- Mama.
I'm sorry, Mama.
- Bonnie.
- Yeah?
- You'll come see me, won't you?
- You know I will, Mama.
So give me the corrected story
first thing in the morning.
We'll give you three-quarters
of page two...
...800-, 900 words,
nothing more, nothing less.
So, what makes you think
I'm gonna give you your job back?
You don't want
to be stuck at the station...
...on the biggest story that's about
to start racing down the tracks.
Who's that?
She sold the Kaufman County
Grand Jury...
...the biggest load I ever saw
shoveled down anyone's throat.
You're going to rehire me
to write about her.
Her name's Bonnie Parker.
She's got more personality than
nine movie stars put together.
She's romantically linked with a
rebellious, disenfranchised son of Texas.
Unless I'm wrong, the two of them
are about to embark on a crime spree...
...with lots of violence, glamour
and car chases.
And it isn't just the man
shooting the guns.
So you're saying there's sex too.
Come on, Barrow.
There's the dreadful girl's mother.
- Just awful, shameful.
- It is.
- Clyde Chestnut, what the hell?
- Supposed to be in prison, big gorilla.
Yeah, warden made the mistake
of making me a trustee.
- I made the mistake of busting out.
- Mistake of busting out?
I'm gonna spend the rest of the
weekend with this lovely thing here...
...and then I'm gonna
turn myself back in.
- Hearing a lot about you, Clyde Chestnut.
- Clyde Chestnut?
- He told me it was Champion.
- Champion?
Trying to impress me, I guess.
I tried my best to do right by her.
Well, don't beat yourself up.
They're gonna go
the way they're gonna go...
...pretty much no matter what we do.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, Blanche, you mind
grabbing us a beer?
All right.
We're the luckiest women
in the world, huh?
You done good, boy.
Anybody ever turn themselves
back into Huntsville, Marvin?
How the hell should I know?
I mean, Blanche's father's a preacher.
And she said she won't part
her sweet haunches till I marry her.
Her father won't marry us
till I do the rest of my time.
Right. I think I could launch myself...
...clear to the moon.
I'll tell you one thing.
Preacher's daughter or not,
she is one fine load of naughty.
Well, not that that's everything.
Right?
- What's Mom so pissy about?
- She's always pissy.
- She took the money I gave her.
- We need the money.
It ain't the criming that's got her goat.
Should've hit you boys more.
She doesn't like Bonnie, does she?
She doesn't like
that she's married not to you.
Yeah, should've hit him more.
You know, Bonnie'd get divorced
if she could...
...but just kind of a legal proceeding,
you know, and legal and us ....
Doesn't mean she couldn't take off
Roy Thornton's ring.
It's a nice piece of jewelry, Mom.
Bonnie likes jewelry.
And fine clothes and expensive shoes
and getting famous.
I'm just wondering how much
she really likes you.
Oh, she likes me fine.
I was making a record. Remember
what I used to call you, Clyde?
Your "little ray of sunshine."
Wrote down where we gathered,
here at Perkins' barn.
What we ate, what we drank,
who was here.
Know I'm only gonna be seeing you
here and there from here on out...
...and I don't want to forget
any of the here and theres.
I love you, Mom.
The robbery in Hillsboro, right from
the get-go, just felt different.
Jesus, Clyde,
you're making me nervous.
I could've stopped it.
I should've.
Because after tonight...
...nothing was ever
gonna be the same.
My old buddy Fults
wasn't two weeks out of jail...
...before I got him back doing what
landed him there in the first place.
Come on.
- Please don't hurt me.
- You do what we say...
...just be another good story
to tell your buddies at the Moose Lodge.
Hang on a second. Hey.
This doesn't seem right.
- What are you talking about?
- Like this might not be the right job.
- Don't even. We're already doing the job.
- We need money to eat tomorrow.
- If you hadn't spent so much on clothes...
- I can't go back...
You guys wanna argue
about shopping, be my guest.
But I'm doing the damn job.
Come on. Come on.
Faster.
Come on, open it.
Come on.
Hear that?
Just the cash.
Put it in the purse. Come on.
A little faster.
Come on.
- All right, let's go.
- Come on.
- What y'all gonna do with me?
- Nothing.
Go upstairs, stay there till the sun
comes up. You're done with us.
Despite all the things we done...
...bullets flying north, south,
east and west...
...no one had been killed before.
A few here and there
may have collected some lead...
...but no one had been killed.
Miss Lane, I'm Captain Grace.
- Anything we can help you sort out?
- Seems clear.
I was hoping you could tell me
the ABC's of it in your own words.
Well, plates matched a vehicle
they stole in Topeka.
Looks like they got money and some
jewels from the safe here and ran.
Not before obliterating Mr. Bucher,
apparently for the thrill.
All fingers seem to be pointing
at who as the triggerman?
Clyde Barrow.
I just spoke to the widow.
Told me she could see the whole thing...
...from her bedroom window.
I showed her the picture of Clyde.
She said he couldn't have
possibly pulled the trigger.
All I know is those maggots came to steal
money, now an innocent man's dead.
Now, I'd appreciate it if you'd get
your smart ass off my crime site.
Nobody meant for it to happen, Bon.
The press could've hung us worse.
You shouldn't be drinking.
I'm a horrible person, Clyde.
That poor man's dead...
...and I'm all bent because the paper
used my stupid sophomore photo.
- You're not a horrible person.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I am.
- You're just honest.
Gonna get out of town before sunup.
Gonna be all right while I jack us a ride?
Yeah.
Cly?
- You really think I don't look stupid?
- Not at all.
But you definitely look better in person.
"Bonnie and Clyde."
You know what
I've been thinking, Clyde?
I think we should do bigger jobs.
Maybe we shouldn't do any more jobs.
Well, fine...
...but if we're gonna,
they ought to be big ones.
Aren't gonna get that lake house of yours
doing five-and-dime stickups.
And stuff can go wrong
just as likely doing them.
Don't feel comfortable doing bigger jobs
just the two of us.
Maybe we should hook back up
with Fults.
What, so he can gun down
some poor SOB...
...who done nothing wrong
whatsoever?
Well, what about your brother?
He's done his time, hasn't he?
Yeah, and he ain't looking
to do any more.
I ain't getting Buck involved in this.
Well, somebody else, then.
Gonna pull bigger jobs,
we need bigger guns too.
Well, then somebody else
and bigger guns.
Weren't you just crying about
that poor son of a bitch in the p.j.'s'?
For Pete's sake, Clyde,
I'm not saying we use them.
If we pull big guns on people...
...they're gonna do
exactly what we tell them to.
All right, look here.
Just so you know, who's in the gang...
...what we do,
what kind of guns we use...
...or if we go and join a damn monastery,
it's all up to me.
I make the decisions.
All right?
Fine. Just a thought.
Sorry I had one.
Come on, let's go.
- Barrow?
- Miss me?
- Where'd you get the suit?
- Just picked it up from a tailor.
Damn crazy.
... three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
Herman?
We got one too many convicts.
Now you're about to have one too few.
Don't move.
Gonna shoot me, are you, Barrow?
Go! Go!
Outrun them.
Move around, other side.
Through here.
They're heading for the road.
Down, get down!
- Bonnie, Ray. Ray, Bonnie.
- Like your choice of weapons, Bonnie.
It's the warden.
- Watch this.
- Clyde.
- What are they doing?
- They're busting out.
- Clyde, you really need to?
- Yup.
Barrow.
Oh, God.
Ma'am. I'm here to see
Colonel Simmons.
- I'll let him know you're both here.
- Thanks.
You're Frank Hamer.
I'm Ted Hinton,
deputy of the Dallas P.D.
I know Bonnie.
- I know both her and Clyde by sight.
- I know who you are.
And I know what you know.
They share a posse, Frank,
but I would put them on the spot...
...make sure it's them,
and shoot everybody in sight.
That's about the run of it.
- Any questions?
- Just one.
Hope I'm not hearing the idea
is to shoot first...
...and ask them to put their hands up
when they're too dead to do it.
Before she met Barrow...
...Bonnie Parker was a good girl
from a good family.
Yeah, well, bringing them to trial
would be best in any case.
If you collar Barrow,
it wouldn't displease me.
- We'd love having him back.
- Not a question of if, just when.
Let's keep the press out of this.
If Barrow finds out we're on their trail,
it'll just make our job a lot harder.
Anything you can tell me
from Barrow's time here...
...that might help in tracking him?
Distinguishing characteristics or the like?
He just might be limping
on his left side.
Barrow paid the guy he busted out
to hack that little piggy off.
Always heard legends seemed smaller
when you met them.
Was wondering if I could buy you dinner
on the Herald.
- Would like to do a full-on feature on you.
- The Herald?
You must be P.J. Lane.
I read some of your pieces, Miss Lane.
- You ought to be writing fiction.
- How's that?
It's inventive now you made
law enforcement the bad guy...
...for insinuating Barrow
had something to do...
...with the murder of that store owner.
What would dinner on you get me?
Keep you from having to read the same
baloney written about you before.
About being able to hear shots...
...before they're
fired and gunning down 56 outlaws.
Fifty-seven, Miss Lane.
Have a good one.
Come on.
Going to write about you either way.
At least tell me what about Bonnie
and Clyde brought you out of retirement.
It was the publicity.
- Stop! Police!
- You with the bag!
Get in.
Stop!
I think you picked the right bank
to spring, Clyde.
You smoke, Bonnie Parker?
Nope. I was raised Christian.
You dropped something.
Do yourself a favor, Ray.
Grab a cold bath.
What's for breakfast?
Lady at the bakery said
these are best damn doughnuts ever.
- Great.
- I got you something else too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What?
Kodak Folding Autographic, all right?
It's got focusable lenses,
eight pictures per roll, the whole deal.
Figure it's time we do something about
that old sophomore photo of yours, huh?
Yeah. So I wanna shoot you down there,
get you on some rocks.
- Clyde.
- Clump of trees.
- We aren't shooting the photos today.
- Why not?
Problem with that photo, I didn't know
they were taking them that day.
Girl's gotta get clothes,
tailoring to get the fit.
You're asking for trouble
if you don't get a makeover.
- What's a makeover?
- You could stand some new dude.
Not to mention a cut.
- Your hair is strictly '20s.
- Hey there. You be nice.
Been in there forever. My turn for a dip.
Unless you want to double dip.
You got water in those ears?
I'm talking to you.
You all right, Clyde?
We need to stop.
What?
Did you see this?
- You see who they hired to hunt us?
- Looks like he's seen better days.
Yeah. You know,
I met him back at the blacksmith shop.
I knew it was a sign
that we needed to stop all this.
Frank Hamer's
the meanest son of a bitch.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I seen something.
It wasn't good at all.
This is about one of those things
you see?
- You don't understand.
- I understand.
Keep talking like that, they'll put you
in a place worse than prison.
We need to get out while we can,
Bonnie.
Forget about Ray and robbing banks.
- All of it.
- And get into what, missionary work?
And if I have a dream...
...about a purple nine-eyed demon
under our bed...
...should we give up sleeping together?
- You think I'm kidding around here, huh?
- No.
We just risked our necks
to bust Ray out...
...so that we could get done
what we both agreed we were gonna do.
- So we could get what we both wanted.
- Yeah?
Well, maybe I already got
what I wanted.
And if I say it's time to shut it down,
it's time to shut it down, all right?
- Well, maybe it is.
- Maybe it is.
Bonnie?
I'm fine, Clyde.
Yeah? It's almost midnight.
You gonna come to bed?
When I'm done bathing.
Since when you smoking?
What's going on, Bon?
You had some premonition
or something.
I guess I gotta try and understand that.
But I knew there were gonna be
lawmen after us.
And whatever this Frank Hamer is to you,
he's just another one to me.
And I gotta tell you,
what I see looking forward...
...isn't dark and foreboding at all.
I see the two of us waking up one day
with all this behind us...
...with everything we ever dreamed of.
Now, maybe the road we're taking
to get to dreamland isn't the greatest.
But it's the road that called us.
And if you're demanding
we stop this thing we're doing...
...then I don't know.
Maybe I'm gonna have to find some other
way to get where I'm supposed to be.
You ain't going nowhere.
Hey, not like I break the lens or anything.
Snap a couple of me and Bonnie.
All right.
Get more of a close-up.
You're way back there.
You can hardly see our smiles.
- Go ahead.
- What?
- That'll make you look mean.
- Not to mention sexy.
Hey, Ray,
you got some tobacco on your lip.
Yeah, let me see that.
- I get it?
- Right there.
Damn.
Come here.
Got a little something for you.
Snap one like this first.
- All right.
- Oh, wait.
Make it even better right here.
Make it look mean. Come on.
Was excited to near Colonel Simmons
got you on board, Captain Hamer.
We can use all the help we can get.
We narrowed it down to a five-state area.
Barrow's only committed a couple
of his crimes outside of here, Texas.
You can tell by the density on the map
where he's done most of his damage.
We've got all the information
on the crimes in this journal...
...every detail you could imagine.
We've recovered some of the clothes.
You can take a look at them
if you want.
If we weren't prohibited from crossing
state lines in our pursuit...
...we'd already have him by now.
Well, I ain't prohibited.
What I'd like is for you to just stop talking
for a minute, sheriff.
Give me a pencil.
One that works.
What we got here is a creature of habit.
Unless he's changed his spots...
...I'd say where he'd be next is
somewhere in Missou'.
Thought you might be interested
in this.
The man Bonnie and Clyde busted out
got picked up trying to thumb a ride.
Where?
Joplin, Missouri.
Here. Thank you.
Thanks, Smoot. We'll be in touch.
Well, that's why
they bust you out, Ray?
No other jobs
they might need another gun for?
Yeah.
Told me they wanted
to track down Frank Hamer...
...bust a cap on him
when he was sleeping.
You know, Ray,
I grouse-hunt with Judge Wexler.
Might be worth your while
to tell us something we don't know.
I ain't no stool, Hamer.
You do right by Barrow,
but I'll tell you...
...he done you no favors
by busting you out of Eastham.
Colonel Simmons ain't fond of runners,
and he's tight with Judge Wexler.
I don't intervene on your behalf,
you ain't got one day left...
...without Simmons' thumb
stuck up your ass.
They were talking
about getting back into banks.
Getting some banks
with some real money.
Bonnie thought we'd pull some jobs
the size of what Pretty Boy was...
...we could get out of criming sooner.
I don't know. Probably try to find
somebody to take my place.
Got any specifics on which banks?
Who the somebody might be?
No. They kept the planning
to themselves.
You'd better tell me something I don't
know about Bonnie and Clyde, Ray.
Come on.
They stay in campgrounds.
Or just camp out,
unless Bonnie can talk Clyde out of it.
He tends to run careful...
...drive all night if he's spooked,
always the back roads.
Keeps a stack of license plates,
always switching them.
And Fords.
Clyde loves big-block Fords.
Won't jack a car unless it's a V-8.
You done us all a favor, Hamilton.
I'll talk to Wexler for you.
Get a mug snot of Bonnie and Clyde
to every bank in the five-state area.
Find out from Simmons
who Barrow consorted with in the pen...
...who's no longer in the pen.
Doubt he'd break in again.
See if we can get local law to keep an eye
on the cons, an eye out for Barrow.
There was a burglary around big D...
...and it wasn't just Clyde
we went looking for.
Should think about getting somebody
on his brother Buck.
Good. See it's done.
But where am I gonna find you?
If Barrow drives a V-8,
we gotta upgrade our horse.
On the road with Bonnie and Clyde.
Coming.
- I'll be damned.
- How you doing, big brother?
Good. Good. Real good.
You look good yourself.
Bonnie.
Well, you guys come in.
Her and Blanche can bump gums.
We'll all catch up.
Well, it may be best if you come out
to the car. Got a little hooch.
Come on.
Sit there and drink.
Bonnie.
Big money.
You told them no, didn't you?
After the whiskey,
what'd he promise you, the moon?
No, he didn't promise me the moon.
Just enough scratch
to get us a home of our own.
- We're doing all right without them.
- We're living at your father's house.
He orders me around.
We ain't doing all right.
- He's giving you an opportunity.
- And so is Clyde.
Besides, he's my brother.
He needs me to look out for him.
You'll both end up in prison.
Ain't nothing bad gonna happen,
all right, darling? Just start packing.
What do you think you're doing?
We're married.
Well, I'll write to you.
Daddy?
- She ain't Coming?
- Probably for the best.
All right.
Let's go.
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Looks like she changed her mind.
Am I stopping?
- You expecting any laws for supper?
- Maybe they heard you was in town.
Clyde the Drive.
Go, baby.
Baptism by fire, baby.
America 's crime wave
became a full-fledged hurricane...
...as Charles Arthur "Pretty Boy" Floyd
made headlines in Kansas City...
...committing a brazen daylight attack
to free Frank Nash...
...e prisoner being returned
to Leavenworth.
Pretty Boy and his associates
opened fire with guns blazing...
Why ain't we up there?
... outside the train station,
killing five lawmen...
...in what is becoming known
as the Kansas City Massacre.
Let's go.
Hands up.
The heck you do that for?
I thought I saw something.
Don't think the workday's over.
Shouldn't you be out
trying to put a bullet in someone's head?
You know how most outlaws get caught,
Miss Lane?
- Enlighten me.
- Tips.
From John Q. Public.
Problem with Bonnie and Clyde
is we're not getting any.
Now, I appreciate you're trying
to make your star on their skin.
But let me tell you the next beat
in this story of yours.
Pretty soon
somebody else ends up dead...
...and there ain't no way
you can perfume that.
You'll be wondering if you hadn't painted
Bonnie and Clyde like Garbo and Gable...
...maybe somebody
would've stepped forward...
...and this husband or that father
wouldn't be dead at all.
If I don't write this story,
someone else will.
I suppose, but I don't see anybody else
throwing out these photo spreads.
- How'd you run across these pictures?
- I'm good at what I do.
I don't compromise my sources.
I'm gonna need to see
the uncropped versions of these.
I'm not inclined to give them to you.
I thought you might see it that way.
That's why I got a warrant.
Believe we got ourselves a shindig
in Stringtown.
What do you say
we take a break, Clyde?
Probably best not to mix and mingle.
Come on,
we could all stand to shake a leg.
Been in this car all damn day.
Could jump a new car here
as well as anywhere.
Besides, I gotta tinkle.
Come on, sugar, let's have some fun.
- How about something jumpier?
- How about staying quieter?
- And keeping that corn mash out of sight.
- Hell with these people.
Gotta get to work.
- Keep an eye on big brother.
- All right.
- Come on, let's dance.
- No. It's too fast for me. I don't want to.
- Come on.
- No, I don't want to.
Hey, give me that.
Go dance with your sister-in-law.
It's killing her being a wallflower.
- Bonnie?
- All right.
All right.
Try and keep up.
Come on.
Buck, you got a little Shimmy
in your shake.
Hell, honey, you ain't seen nothing yet.
- Mind if I out in?
- Yeah. This ain't no kiddie dance.
Girl needs a man. Beat it, sport.
- What the hell you looking at, cracker?
- Your ugly mug.
Let's go.
Get out of here.
Hey, buddy.
Get in.
Go, Clyde, go.
Nine-sixteenths.
Damn it. I said nine-sixteenths.
- What?
- Gave me the wrong damn wrench.
And you stole the wrong ride.
What happened, Buck, is you got drunk
and stupid, and we killed a law.
Kill a law, the others ain't gonna stop.
Bonnie got everyone looking our way,
playing to every farm boy...
...like she played all those stuffed shirts
at the wedding.
She was acting like a hussy.
She's right, but Bonnie's got you too tight
by the balls for you to see it.
You better shut your mouth, Marvin...
...or I'm gonna leave you and
brain-dead Blanche in a goddamn ditch.
Are you threatening me? Are you
threatening me? You want a taste of this?
- Dumb-ass baboon.
- That's it.
That's it.
Son of a bitch.
Get his eyes, Daddy, get his eyes.
Buck, you wanna blame me, that's fine.
Clyde, you wanna blame Buck,
that's fine.
None of it's gonna do us any good.
Lawman's dead.
None of us are happy about that,
but better him than us.
Come hell or high water, we're family.
We start fighting amongst ourselves,
we might as well be pissing in the wind.
You all right?
- No, you hit me with a damn wrench.
- Yeah.
Had to against that right hook of yours.
Let's put on them out-of-state plates.
Come on.
A dozen witnesses said they were sure
it was Bonnie they'd seen dancing.
Description of the fella that crippled
Maxwell matched Buck Barrow.
Nobody got as good a look at the man
who put a bullet in Eugene here...
...but pretty sure it was Clyde.
Eugene has three little ones.
So the witnesses said that the driver,
the man you think was Barrow...
...fired just once?
Seems to be the consensus.
Well, I'll leave y'all to it.
You think he was lucky, Ted,
the man who fired once...
...and shot middle of forehead?
It's hard to say.
Just so you know, I make my own luck.
I get a shot at the man who done this,
I'm shooting before he does.
Suggest you do like.
Nobody appointed you executioner,
Frank.
This man's doing it right now.
If Barrow stays to form, he'll head east.
Alert police in Missouri and Louisiana...
...Bonnie and Clyde might be looking
for refuge in their campgrounds...
...driving their back roads.
But I wanna widen the net.
As of tomorrow, I wanna be reading police
reports from Alabama, Georgia, Florida.
I thought we determined
they'd stay within that circle of yours.
Yeah, but I think killing cops is gonna
push him out of his usual circles.
Slice of heaven, huh?
I'm fair-skinned.
Too much lying in the sun
ain't good for me.
Not to mention
what you're doing to my lungs...
...with those stupid Havanas
Buck stole.
All right, princess, let's go for a dip.
Shouldn't we be getting back
to work soon?
You know, for being on holiday,
you seem kind of on edge.
Well, you're always on edge.
No, I'm not.
- Oh, no!
- Go down.
- Gonna get him now!
- No.
Don't splash too much.
Watch my book.
Don't get my poetry wet.
Frank, you getting the idea
it might be time to head back to Texas?
Nope.
I was thinking it's time
to scratch my balls.
Missouri.
And those pictures.
- Where are those damn pictures?
- What pictures?
Them newspaper photos. Those pictures.
Yeah.
Son of a bitch. Get the car, Ted.
We're going to Florida.
Help you with something?
Doubtful, unless you got any guests
registered to Missouri plates 89983.
Supposed to be my day off.
Instead I got called in
on this scavenger hunt to nowhere.
Been to every hostel and inn and ....
Well, hello, nurse.
Ain't getting nothing but a whole lot
of butt sweat for my efforts.
In Bungalow 7.
Oh, shit.
- Your phone. I need your phone.
- Hey, no need to get riled.
- I saw them drive off this morning.
- Goddamn it.
But they're coming back.
They ain't even checked out.
Who y'all looking for?
Bonnie and Clyde.
Dale McClanahan. I'm in charge here.
Heard a lot about you, Captain Hamer.
Saw your snipers out there, Dale...
...and the cruisers,
and there's more men here than we need.
I'd recommend him and him
go get in the cruisers...
...and drive themselves
back to the station.
Your snipers, I want them in here
where Barrow can't see them...
...and I can tell them
what I need them to do.
You do speak English, don't you, Dale?
Let's go.
When we get back,
I'm gonna fry these up...
...and we can call this fish rodeo
a success.
I don't eat fish. Too fishy.
Well, now you tell me.
You've read the story of Jesse James
Of how he lived and died
If you're still in need
Of something to read
Here 's the story of Bonnie and Clyde.
They call them cold-blooded killers
They say they are heartless and mean
But I say this with pride
That I once knew Clyde
When he was honest
and upright and clean.
But the laws fooled around
Kept taking him down
And locking him up in a cell
Till he said to me,
"I'll never be free
So I'll meet e few of them in hell."
What are you doing?
McClanahan.
We found the car, Captain Hamer.
Missouri plates 89983,
abandoned in Biloxi.
We got no lead where Barrow
and his gang might be.
Why'd you do it, Frank?
Why'd you come out of retirement
for Bonnie and Clyde?
For the money.
Heard you were making more
as a union buster.
Well, it's not just the salary.
Remember that pickled toe of Barrow's
that Simmons threw at me?
I got that in a cupboard at home.
It's Barrow's saxophone,
Bonnie's typewriter...
...their clothes, their guns.
It's memorabilia, Ted.
There's a whole network out there.
You get as much notoriety as those two...
...their stuff will sell for hundreds,
thousands.
Longer you hang on to it,
the more it's worth.
So all them other outlaws
you took care of ....
Is there much money in memorabilia?
I could give two shits
about memorabilia, money.
I came back
because there is no better feeling...
...than putting a bullet
in the brain of somebody...
...you and God and any half-decent person
knows needed a bullet put in them.
This the best this damn thing can do?
How's that?
Sometimes something happens,
something terrible avoided...
...but that don't mean
it was for the better.
If I wouldn't have had that inkling
about Hamer...
...it'd have all been over in Florida.
Bonnie would've gotten
her biggest headline.
And there 'd have been
e lot less mess.
Everybody get on the ground
right now!
Don 't mess with
Bonnie and Clyde.
Get in the vault.
Everybody on the damn ground
right now!
Ain't nobody gonna catch us.
- That's perfect right there.
- Okay.
This thing doesn't wanna stay on there
for some reason.
- Cookies.
- Oh, look at that, huh? Thank you, honey.
Oh, and they're nice and warm too.
You want one?
- Cookie.
- Good job on that.
Doyle.
What the hell?
Hey! Hey, stop!
Hey, get out of my car!
Hey! Hey!
- Clyde.
- You open this door.
- Let go!
- Hey.
Doyle?
Doyle? Doyle? Doyle?
Doyle! Help! Help us!
Help!
It's Christmas.
Could've just pushed him off.
Christmas day.
He had a gun. You all saw it, right?
How you gonna perfume this,
Miss Lane?
Ma'am.
Where's the body?
How many bullets?
Where's my story?
I'm not sure
if I can cover them any more.
Try saying that different. A lot different.
I just Can't help thinking
I've been aiding and abetting, sir.
We sell newspapers, P.J.
It isn't our fingers pulling the trigger.
You know this story better than anyone.
You gotta turn it
so you can live with yourself, turn it.
If Bonnie and Clyde are the bad guys,
make them the bad guys.
She thought he had a gun, Buck.
- I didn't say nothing.
- Yeah, well, don't.
All right? You neither, Blanche.
Hi.
- How's your mother?
- Oh, she's just fine, yeah.
Thanks for asking.
All right.
Maybe you ought to lighten up.
Prohibition's over.
You lighten up.
You got a play on your jack of hearts.
I saw that.
Wish she'd just shut up.
She don't even mean it.
Why do they always get
the bigger room?
Why's she always the one
divvying up the money?
Can we just play dominoes?
She talks about family,
us all sticking together...
...but she's just out for herself.
She's shorting us, Buck.
That little hope chest of hers?
Notice how she never opens it
when anyone's around?
No, I haven't.
It's probably just her underthingies.
In any damn case,
it's none of your damn business.
Like hell, it isn't.
And I was right there behind her,
and I sure didn't see no gun.
Gotta go, gotta go. Buck?
Buck, we got company.
- Daddy?
- Get the light, get the light.
Daddy, what's going on?
L-Hey.
Get down. Get down.
This is the police.
We've got you surrounded.
Come out with your hands up.
You got one minute to exit the building.
- Stay low. Grab our stuff.
- All right, all right.
- No.
- Leave the damn box.
No. No, I'm not leaving it. No.
The hell you doing?
Let's go. Let's get going.
Daddy!
No, Daddy!
Come on.
What the hell were you doing,
cutting your damn toenails?
No, Daddy! No, Daddy!
Daddy, no.
Daddy, no. No!
Daddy, no! No, Daddy!
Go on! Go on!
Daddy!
- Howdy.
- Evening.
Evening to you.
If I could get some...
Just a can of coffee and some beans...
...and a loaf of that bread there too.
Some ice. I could use some ice.
Yeah.
Yeah, also some of those bandages
over there too.
And how about a can
of that lighter fluid right there?
Yeah.
Is that it?
- What's the damage?
- That'll be 1.75.
All right.
- Can I help you with that?
- No, no, no. Oh, my...
Yeah, I sprained my shoulder
playing baseball with friends.
Yeah.
Keep the change.
We brought everything we had
and gave it good.
They just got lucky.
Lucky?
Unless I'm mistaken,
didn't you and I have a conversation...
...that I'd be here in the morning
and take charge of the apprehension?
We had reason to believe
that they might be gone come morning.
Really?
Had nothing to do with you
wanting to make a name for yourself...
...by collaring Bonnie and Clyde?
It was like nothing I've ever seen.
It was like the Fourth of July.
It was Bonnie doing the shooting.
I only saw her for an instant.
I'll never forget her.
She was the one firing that tommy.
Good girl, Ted?
Jesus, you're sweet on her.
Just got word out of Iowa.
Clerk at a market, works as a marshal,
just ID'd Clyde Barrow.
- You tell them to wait till I got there?
- Tried...
...but my deputy heard it
from a dispatcher.
Sounds like the train...
Damn big one, from what he understood.
... just left the station.
Why's every idiot with a badge
gotta try to out-idiot the other?
It's cold, Bonnie. We're cold.
Got a good fire burning now.
It'll be okay.
Can't take no more of Daddy's hurt.
Gotta do something
about Daddy's hurt.
Put some ice on his head.
Should take down the swelling,
ease his pain.
There's also bandages
in the other one.
- Can't hardly see, Clyde.
- I was talking to Bonnie.
Your brother walked five miles into town
to get you this ice, Buck.
- Gonna get you home.
- Don't got a home.
Daddy. Daddy.
No!
No.
Mama.
They're coming.
Come on. Wake up right now.
Daddy. Daddy, come on.
Come on, wake up.
Come on. Coming right now.
Ready.
Fire!
Everybody out.
- Daddy. Daddy, come on.
- Come on.
- Down by the creek.
- Go on, go on.
I'm on them.
No! Daddy!
L-Hey.
Barrow, that's enough. It's over.
No, Buck. Clyde, help us, please.
- Please. No.
- Drop your weapon.
Come out with your hands up.
Do you hear me, Barrow?
You're finished, Barrow! Come on out!
No.
No, please.
No laws are after us, Clyde.
Listen.
I loved Buck. I couldn't be more sorry
about what happened to him.
Well, look on the bright side.
- You'll probably get a nice headline.
- That isn't fair.
What isn't fair is my brother lying back
there with half his damn head blown off.
- I didn't want him involved.
- Well, he got involved.
And even if he dies...
...people are gonna remember him.
Clyde...
...Buck got to be a part of something,
something bigger than all of us.
You know now many people get nothing
but 60 years...
...of nobody knowing they're alive?
- Absolutely nothing?
- And that's all you care about, isn't it?
People knowing who you are.
I said you weren't a horrible person,
Bonnie, but I was wrong.
You don't care about Buck.
You don't love me.
No, I'm just a footnote
in the story of you.
Every time the blood was leaking out
of some bastard...
...you figured just as much ink flowed to
building up the legend of Bonnie Parker.
And Christmas,
that wasn't cause for mercy, was it?
No, that was just reason for the papers
to print your picture bigger.
You never saw a goddamn gun,
did you?
- Did you? Did you?
- Clyde!
Bonnie.
Get me out, get me out, get me out!
Right through here.
Daddy.
At least one of them got banged up,
maybe burned.
They'll be looking for safe harbor.
I wanna get word out to every
gang member ever worked with them...
...to the families
of all the gang members...
...there's full pardons and reward money
for anyone who gives up Barrow.
Well, I hope someone does.
Been on this a while.
And we'll be on it...
...till it's finished.
Gonna get you better, Bon.
You should have just let me burn.
If you meant even half of what you said,
I got no reason to keep breathing.
You got every reason.
Hush now.
Remember when Clyde
didn't even trust you to be a lookout?
Pretty Boy himself would run away
if he ran into you now.
Probably loves you, though.
You pushed him right off the front page.
Pretty keen on staying
out of the limelight now, Henry.
Understood.
No better place to do it
than Nowhere, Louisiana.
Really appreciate you putting us up.
Hell, ain't no skin off my teeth.
It's a honor to do it.
Sure your father doesn't mind
us bunking down here?
Don't worry about him.
Hiding three fugitives
is no harder than one.
You keep us in groceries,
he'll be happy enough.
Hell, breakfast with Bonnie and Clyde.
I had a dream, Cly.
- What'd you dream about?
- Johnny.
He was the cutest little thing,
all bundled in his crib and laughing.
Not a care in the world.
I dreamed we had a baby.
Johnny didn't have his father's
funny little nose, did he?
He had the most perfect nose,
curly blond hair.
Blond?
And pretty green eyes like his daddy.
Iverson Methvin.
Yeah, I got them both.
You sure you can make everything my
boy's done dirty come clean, Mr. Hamer?
I don't know how much longer.
A few days, maybe a week.
She ain't doing real good.
Okay. There's a reward, right?
Bienville Parish, Louisiana.
- Where we going, Clyde?
- Texas.
Figure we should see your family,
your mama and mine...
...get some new clothes.
But you bought that Easter ham
for the Methvins.
Yeah, we pretty much played out
our welcome.
Mama will be so happy to see us.
Yeah, you are so cute.
Missed that one.
They were selling
these little darlings, Clyde.
They were practically
giving them away.
No, I don't like rabbits. They're dirty.
He's a heck of a lot cleaner than you.
I don't want that thing in the car.
It's a present for my mama, Clyde.
Fine, if that's how you feel...
...just take the dirty little bunny
and give it back.
- What you drinking, Mama?
- Whatever I please.
It don't look to be pleasing you.
You look miserable.
What in the hell would I have
to be miserable about?
It ain't helping anyway.
I ought to get me
some of whatever pharmaceutical...
...Roy Thornton's wife's
floating on over there.
She's in a lot of pain.
Pretty sure the two of you have given
a lot more than you've gotten.
These days with the suns,
those are the days you'd come visit.
No matter what you did, I was always
happy to see my little ray of sunshine.
But Buck, he was trying to be good.
The fact that you done so much bad,
you couldn't go to your brother's funeral.
- Mom.
- You're the reason he's dead and buried.
Not the oops that shot him,
not the fates.
It's just you.
Look at your cute little ears.
I was thinking we need to start
weaning you off that Amytal.
You are so cute.
Mama's just gonna eat you up.
You hear what I'm saying?
Yeah, but right now I've just gotta say,
it's just making things easier.
You know what?
Mama's not gonna appreciate you
near as much as us.
We're gonna keep you, sonny boy.
What do you think about that?
L-Hey.
- You folks all right?
- We're as right as right can be.
Just enjoying the day.
Fixing to have a little picnic
just over there by that tree.
- That's a fine enough spot for that, right?
- Yep.
- Just wanted to make sure you're okay.
- Thank you.
All right. Happy Easter, miss.
See how his head bounced, Clyde?
Just like a rubber ball.
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
He leadeth me beside the still waters.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the paths
of righteousness for his name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death...
...I will fear no evil,
for though art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me ....
My great-grandma said the Good Book
called the apple Eve ate...
"the fruit of knowledge."
I never understood
why knowledge was thought...
...to be the root of so much suffering.
The ongoing saga of Bonnie and Clyde
took another dark turn Easter Sunday...
...es two lawmen, E.B. Wheeler and
Holloway Murphy, were gunned down...
...outside the notorious outlaw couple's
hometown of Dallas.
Wheeler's widow, slated to marry
the man the following weekend...
...found herself wearing her wedding
gown to a much less festive affair.
And while Bonnie and Clyde had
at one time been virtual folk heroes...
...e rancher who witnessed the event
was fer from impressed.
After she shot that lawman, she said,
"See how his head bounced, Clyde?
Like a rubber ball."
That's what she said.
Do you believe that?
"Like a rubber ball. " Man, oh, man.
The hunt continues for Bonnie
and Clyde, believed to be in Louisiana.
Police have set up roadblocks
on all roads to other states.
But on that Easter Sunday,
I tasted the apple.
And the knowledge it gave me...
...of what I needed to do...
wasn't sweet at all.
Methvin residence.
Yeah.
It's Clyde Barrow.
Yeah. All right, I'll see you then.
- Hamer.
- This is Methvin, Iverson.
Everything's been arranged.
Barrow's on his way here.
- Should be here in a couple of days.
- Thank you, Mr. Methvin.
We'll make good on our promises
to your boy.
What are we doing back here,
Clyde Champion?
Called Methvin while you were dozing.
Gonna pick him up.
Figure we could pull a few jobs
in Louisiana...
...maybe push into Arkansas.
Nobody knows us in Arkansas.
Too soon to be thinking about retiring
to that lake home, huh?
Not just yet.
You know what I been thinking, Clyde?
- I ain't no mind reader.
- We should lie in wait for him.
- Who?
- Frank Hamer.
Put one in him
instead of the other way around.
- Get us a hell of a headline too, huh?
- Who gives two damns about that?
Just be nice
to be able to sleep better at night.
Yeah.
Something wrong, Clyde?
No.
Just enjoying now beautiful
everything is.
You don't have to shoot, Ted.
Yeah, Frank, I do.
That's Methvin's truck, isn't it?
Clyde?
I've always loved you, Bonnie.
Mr. Hamer.
Mr. Hamer, you shot them down
in cold blood?
What do you say to the accusations
you shot them down in cold blood?
You think it was fair, Mr. Hamer...
...that you didn't give Bonnie and Clyde
a warning, just executed them?
Ma'am, I'm afraid
what we all gave Bonnie and Clyde...
...was exactly what they wanted.
Mr. Hamer, Mr. Hamer.
Sometimes I like to think
that fever of unexplained origin...
...that I never came out
of the other side...
...end the rest of my life,
none of it ever happened.
Especially that part
where I got shot 37 times...
giving my Bonnie Parker
her big ending.