[Ali.Gh.M]
ali.chenseus@gmail.com
Fight!
Uh, I’mma tell you that you not my competition
I’mma always win, throw me in and I’m going in
I ain’t running, I’mma come until you leave
I'm 'bout to get it,talk about it
‘cause I really live it
On them nights on a mission,
no fear, no hope in my vision
Don’t need no intervention,
you ain’t down to rider
And even if you was I come out, point ‘em out,
they all gon’ be missing
Wonder why I’m still here act a fool if you met me
You try to be brave
and step up with you crew it’s too scary
Plus I’m too legendary,
It’s what we go hard for
I’m rocking your block,
you on top you get knocked off
I’m taking your place yeah,
I'll make it my property
May be a game to you, probably,
that’s a way of life for me
And so it’s only right for me,
annihilate ‘em if they in my way or sight
Keep 'em up off of me,
a weakness in you only make an appetite
Anytime I get into it I be looking at them,
looking pitiful
And their condition it be critical,
nothing less than original
Cross me once that's the end of you
WHO'S NEXT?
Next next next .......
FINISH HIM!
Mortal Kombat X
Coming Soon In 2015!
Get over here
[Ali.Gh.M]
ali.chenseus@gmail.com
ME,ME,ME Please