It's coming for us,
Captain!
It has eyes
as big as basketballs.
It can see everywhere,
even in the pitch black water.
It has a beak
like Mom's parakeets,
but a thousand times bigger,
that can cut you
right in half,
and eight legs that can
rip a blue whale's head off,
and tentacles that feed it
to its beak.
If it gets me, I'm toast.
If it gets you,
you're a bacon sandwich.
Watch out, Captain!
The leviathan has the ship!
We're going under, Wee Wee!
Hey, Johnathan?
- Johnathan.
- What?
Man, I told you to check
the traps, not go swimming.
- We went fishing.
- You can't fish underwater.
- And who is we?
- Me and Wee Wee.
Don't molest that pig, and go
get ready for school, please.
Naw. Take your medicine.
Mm-mm! All of it.
Come on.
Chew it up.
I wanna see it gone.
Linda!
- Hello.
-  You have a collect call from--
Caller, say your name.
- David.
- Do you accept?
Yes.
Hey, Dad.
Is Jo there?
No, she's not.
Would you like me
to give her a message?
No, never mind.
I wrote her a letter.
When are you gonna come home
and take care
of your business, son?
Okay, well, uh...
I gotta go.
- I'll try it later then.
- Listen to me, if you--
So what do you want
to study in school today?
Sea monsters.
Sea monsters
are not a subject.
Let's do math instead.
Okay.
I'm nine years old,
and you're 27.
Yes, sir.
That means you were 18
when you had me.
Yeah, well, let's not
do math today either.
Why don't we study science?
We can do dinosaurs.
How about prehistoric
sea creatures?
Okay, fine.
So long as they're real.
Which one's this?
Predator X, which is
a pliosaur with 12-inch teeth.
So was that the baddest
creature in the ocean?
Some people say this one's
the baddest, a megalodon.
But pliosaurs are cooler
than sharks,
and the megalodon
only had 8-inch teeth.
Do you think there
was really an asteroid
that killed them
like that book says?
I guess so.
Well, you know,
I think that's dumb.
I don't think an asteroid
can destroy everything
that's on the whole planet.
I don't even think
a nuclear bomb can do that.
We dropped a couple of those
on Japan in World War II,
and it didn't do nothing.
I still got a radio from the 90s
that was made in Japan.
But they say that asteroid
was a million times stronger
than an atom bomb.
- Hey, hombre!
- What's up, Curtis?
What's up, buddy?
- Hey, Curtis.
- Hi, Jo.
- We got a question for you.
- Okay.
What do you think
killed the dinosaurs?
Well, there was a polar shift,
and Earth's magnets
got reversed.
It went from being 80 degrees
to like 500 degrees
in the shade,
and they all melted
and became tar.
That's where oil comes from.
Fossil fuels.
Now we fight wars over
dead dinosaurs... and drugs.
- Probably right about that.
- I totally am.
Let me guess.
You want a yellow one?
Yes, and some birdseed, please.
You know, you don't have to
buy the parakeet, Curtis.
I know, but you know
what they say.
When in Rome, do as Romans do.
Shit in the pope's hat.
Something like that.
Well, here's your, uh,
medicine.
- Thank you, Doc.
- Mm-hmm.
The FDA would not approve.
But screw 'em.
This is a pilgrimage.
- What's a pilgrimage?
- Precisely.
This day in modern medicine
has made the pilgrimage
an anachronism.
Kind of like a spider
or something? A tarantula?
No, yeah, an old one that's
out of fashion, lost its touch.
How many birds you got now?
Just this one.
And just a little
something extra for...
I don't take money
for the medication.
- Extra for the beautiful--
- I don't do that.
It's for the beautiful
parakeet, Jo.
It's my favorite one.
Bye, Curtis.
Bye, girl.
Bye!
Woo-hoo!
- Got you something.
- Thank you.
Thank the jellybean stalk.
Thank you,
jellybean stalk!
Ohh!
Whee!
- Hey, Mark.
- Hey.
- Hey, Grandpa.
- Hey, buddy.
- You hungry?
- Yeah.
Grandma's cooking dinner.
She got some of that
chicken casserole you love.
Hey, Johnathan, will you
take that stuff inside
and then go help Grandma?
- Grandpa and I are gonna talk.
- Okay.
We'll see you in a minute,
buddy.
What's up?
Well, David called.
- What'd he say?
- Not much.
I told him you'd had your
electricity disconnected.
And?
Well, he asked me if it'd
be okay if you moved home.
- I am home.
- No. I mean with us.
Well, it's a good thing Linda
wants that as much as I do.
Sweetheart, I don't think
he's coming back.
Linda says she's fine to have
Johnathan stay with us
till things get
a little better for you.
She doesn't think I can take
care of my own son, huh?
I didn't say that.
Are you gonna have dinner
with us or what?
JoLynn!
- Hey, Grandma.
- Hey. Let me see your hands.
Oh, Lord, go wash those
mud mitts right now.
No, no, no, not there.
I'm preparing food.
Go to the bathroom.
And don't touch anything!
Fingernails too.
Is your mom giving you
your eye medicine?
Yeah, twice a day.
Straighten.
Oh, go on.
Hey, Grandpa,
will you tell me the story
about the sea monster
in the lake?
Okay. We were dropping anchor,
and this green ensign--
Now, when I say green,
I mean greener than
a bullfrog's nipple,
greener than them beans
right there, okay?
Has no idea what he's doing.
He's letting that chain
run out into the ocean,
and that chain has links on it
that are this big.
So before we know it,
that guy is ripped
clean off the deck,
and the only thing sitting there
is a severed leg
and a trail of blood
leading straight overboard.
- Whoa.
- Have we heard enough?
No, Grandma,
this is the best part.
Now, you eat those vegetables,
and I'll continue.
So now I have to dive in
to try to retrieve the body.
I mean, for proper burial,
right?
How did you know he was dead?
'Cause I had to swim through
a cloud of blood and sharks.
Did the sharks eat him?
Probably. I don't know
'cause I never found the body.
It was too dangerous,
so I just froze and watched.
And all of a sudden,
up from below came something.
I swear I don't know
what it was,
but it had these big
tentacles that came down
and wrapped themselves around
this full-grown tiger shark
like it was
a little bitty football.
Was it a giant squid?
Maybe, but it jetted back
into the deep blue
before I could get
a good look at it.
I will promise you this,
though.
There is nothing
in the entire ocean
that would ever stand a chance
against a creature like that.
All right, are we done?
'Cause I have completely
lost my appetite.
Can I be excused?
Can you be excused?
May I be excused?
Fine.
Hey.
What do you say?
Thank you, Grandma.
You're welcome.
I love you.
Love you too.
Bye, Grandpa.
Bye, Captain.
Can you please
pass the salt?
Pretty please?
With shark guts on top.
- Hey, baby, what's the matter?
- My head hurts.
Let me see your eyes.
Here, lie down. I'll get you
some medicine, okay?
Here, baby, here.
Come lie on Mama's lap.
Come lie down.
Chew it up.
The pressure's gonna go down.
It hurts real bad tonight.
I know.
Just hang in there, okay?
Just keep chewing.
Johnathan!
Ah!
No! No!
Johnathan,
no, no, no, no, no!
No!
Come on! Grandpa's gonna be here
in a couple minutes.
Go get cleaned up.
I got a favor to ask you.
Ask away.
It's kinda hired for me,
but I'm, uh...
I'm a little behind
on my rent.
Oh, boy.
How far behind?
About three months.
Three months?
Good Lord, JoLynn.
You know I'd love to help you,
but I gotta be honest with you.
The way they've cut back
my retirement,
we just flat
don't have it, honey.
When David called, did he say
he wasn't coming back?
He didn't say anything.
I don't know
what he's gonna do.
That's the truth.
Honey, I will do everything
I can to help you out.
Okay? No promises.
Thanks.
- You all set?
- Mm-hmm.
His headaches have gotten
a lot worse.
He's been sick to his stomach
a lot.
Johnathan, please.
I know the trab was our big hope
after the laser surgeries,
but often it takes more than one
procedure to lower the pressure.
With glaucoma, many times
surgeries just don't work.
Now, you and your husband need
to prepare yourselves
for the fact that Johnathan
may just need to take meds
for the rest of his life.
So the drops are working to
control the pressure spikes?
Yeah, they make his vision
blurry though.
He complained about-- Well,
he complains about it a lot.
Well, he needs them though.
You need to make sure
he takes them.
After that allergic reaction,
he's afraid of the drops.
I'm gonna keep him
on the myotics.
The spikes are just
too dangerous.
I'm going to have to add
an oral inhibitor,
and we'll see how he does.
Contact me immediately
if he experiences
any shortness of breath.
Now, my adding these
may make him...
a little tired and weak,
just a little sluggish.
But that could be good for you.
Boys can be a handful.
You ready, Johnathan?
Let's go.
Can I go check the fishing lines
at Mr. Upshaw's pond?
Yeah, that's fine.
Just don't get caught, okay?
- No swimming.
- Yes, ma'am.
I got to go give her a hand
in the garden.
This is how I maintain
my girlish physique.
Hey, Mark?
Yeah.
Thank you for taking us
to the doctor today.
Of course.
You know as well as I do
that those are not hog tracks.
You know where they came from.
Did you talk to Johnathan?
Yeah. He denies it.
Seemed a little dodgy
to me though.
If she would just
keep an eye on that boy,
teach him some respect
for property.
Don't start.
What are these doing out?
It's okay, fishy.
I'm here to save you,
so Mommy don't eat you.
Hah! Gotcha!
I don't think
you taste good anyway.
Johnathan, you went swimming.
Come on, let's go.
- Where are we going?
- We're going home.
But we're going
to Grandma's for dinner.
Look, I don't want you going
to Grandma's again, okay?
- Not without me.
- Why?
Because I said so.
Look, she's pissed because
you keep breaking all her stuff.
I didn't mean to.
I know, I know.
It's just shit anyway.
The whole house
is full of shit.
We're not going there anymore.
Look, I'm gonna take care of you
from now on, okay?
Till Daddy comes back.
Okay.
Come on.
From now on, nobody can
come in the house, okay?
Nobody.
Especially
Grandma and Grandpa.
- You hear me?
- Yes, ma'am.
Go!
1, 2...
3, 4...
I can't do it
if you don't hold my feet.
- Hey, JoLynn!
- Oh, God. It's Natalie.
Hey! Sorry to drop in
unannounced.
What happened to your phone?
- Oh, it just got shut off.
- Oh, well, ain't that shitty.
Hey, Johnathan,
looking like a stud.
Hey, Aunt Natalie.
Hey, I wanna tell you something.
Hey, 20 more minutes of P.E.
while we visit.
Wee Wee, help!
Come on,
you never get out anymore.
I know, but I can't just leave
Johnathan here by himself.
He can take care of himself.
I mean, really, what's
the worst that can happen?
A pig get in your house?
It wouldn't be the first time.
All right.
Hey, if me and Aunt Natalie
went out tonight,
- would you be good?
- Yes, ma'am.
And I don't want you to let
Wee Wee in the house,
and I don't want you
going down to Grandpa's.
Okay.
All right,
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
- Bye, sweetie.
- Bye.
Where are y'all going?
Get rent money.
G-49.
Hey, are you sure
he's got this?
Relax. We can't lose.
He's like a computer genius.
Hi. We need six computers
split two ways.
That's $90.
It'll be 45 apiece.
Natalie, that's all
the money I've got.
Okay. Stop bitching.
Pretty soon we are gonna be
splitting jackpots.
First number out
will determine the wild number,
and it's gonna be a nine.
Oh, there he is.
Mark everything
ending in 9 through 69.
- Hey, cowboy.
- Hey, ladies.
- This is JoLynn.
- Looking good!
- Nice to meet you, JoLynn.
- Hey, it's nice to meet you.
What have we got here?
Good. Bingo Bill gave you
lucky number six for me.
That's my hot box.
Are y'all feeling
the fortune tonight?
- Oh, yeah.
- Me too.
Now, let me go do
whatever it is I do, all right?
I told you
he was cute as hell.
Here you go.
Don't tell Mama, Wee Wee.
Bad pig! Bad pig!
You're a naughty pig! Bad!
- G-49.
- Damn it. I'm on.
Come on, 63!
Or an 18.
B5.
B1.
Bingo!
Sorry.
- It's a winner.
- We have a good bingo.
- What the hell?
- Look, I'm sorry, all right?
No! You said we had this!
You'd pull
your dumb-ass strings.
You really think I could
rig a damn bingo game?
Are you that damn stupid?
What is this,
some shit line?
Look, I got lucky.
Sorry you didn't.
- You son of a bitch.
- Natalie...
Get out of here,
you trashy ass.
- Hey, hey!
- Don't touch me.
Oh, one whore sticking up
for another?
- That's my sister.
- Oh, must run in the family.
You don't know shit
about my family.
Oh, I don't? What's that?
Bet your husband has no idea
you're out here whoring it up
at a bingo parlor for a dollar.
Please.
Yeah, give me a call sometime.
We can do that.
- Your sister's got my number.
- Get out.
I got it, I got it.
Sorry about that, y'all.
Bitch.
Sorry. It's cool.
Oh, look at these tomatoes.
Oh, they look so ripe.
Yeah! Tomato guts!
Tomato man!
So how's David?
I don't know.
You tell me.
I haven't heard from him
in over a month.
I haven't either.
Mark offered for us to move in
with him and Linda.
- Why don't you?
- What do you think?
- Till David comes back.
- Oh, please.
Hey, at least the man's trying
to do something with his life.
It's about time.
- Yeah, must be nice.
- At least you got one
that's trying to make something
out of himself for you.
Must be nice.
David asked you to call
and check on me, didn't he?
He leaves me for two months
with nothing but a letter,
but he calls you?
You don't got no phone.
Well, I'm not the one that
racked up a $500 phone bill,
booking a tour
all over kingdom come either.
I'm just trying to help.
Chill out.
Help? You just helped me
lose everything I had.
You think I wanted to drag
your lame ass out of the house?
Then why did you?
You never come over
unless you want something.
Maybe I just don't want
to see you end up like Mom.
You really think I'm gonna
drink myself to death
- because a man left me?
- I don't know what you'd do.
You've always been
the depressed, serious type.
Maybe if you relaxed for once,
you could find someone better.
- More coffee?
- Yeah, fill 'er up.
She likes it black.
Get a new wig, bitch.
Kiss my ass!
Ow. Stupid thing.
Come on!
Hey!
Go, Wee Wee!
Go, go, go!
Woo-hoo!
I'm so sorry.
I will talk to Johnathan
in the morning.
No. No.
No, this time you're
gonna do something.
What do you want me to do?
You let her run all over you,
and now her boy too.
Why don't you do something?
They're your family too.
All right, I will.
- Good.
- I will take care of this.
What the hell?
Johnathan!
Wee Wee, what are you
doing in here?
Oh, my God.
Johnathan!
What the hell, Johnathan?
What did you do to my plants?
I wanted to make brownies.
Are you an idiot?
Why would you do that?
- That's your medicine!
- I don't know.
It's a gonna take me months
to grow 'em back!
Fuck!
Can I come in?
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
I'm sorry, Mama.
I don't know why I did it.
You did it
'cause you're a kid.
I keep asking you to be
a man for me, but...
you just need to be a kid.
I miss Dad.
Me too.
You'll never leave me,
will you?
I will never leave you.
I love you.
I will always,
always love you.
No matter what.
No matter
what you become and...
no matter if you grow up
and do bad things.
I will love you
more than God does.
- Sheriff Cole, you're back.
- I'm sorry, JoLynn.
How come with all
the deputies you got,
you come see me personally?
Could you step outside,
please?
I'm fine right here,
thank you.
Well, I need to know
where your pig is.
How come you asking?
Well, your neighbor
down the hill here,
they pressed charges
this morning.
My neighbor?
That's my husband's parents.
I understand that, JoLynn, but
I have to issue you a citation
for trespassing and vandalism
perpetrated by your pet pig.
I know.
Come on.
I'm also gonna need to know
the whereabouts of your pig,
currently.
Well, you're looking at her.
Where-- God dang!
That's not funny, JoLynn!
I'm gonna tell you something
right now, and I mean it too.
You contain your pig,
all right?
If I catch him off the premises
one more time,
I'm gonna confiscate and
the euthanize the damn thing.
That's bullshit!
Ham and egg bastard.
Pig shit everywhere.
Get away from me!
Ham hock-lookin'
son of a bitch.
Yah!
Hey.
Well, Linda, they gave me
a $250 ticket. You happy?
I didn't want for you
to get a ticket.
Well, then why did you
call the cops on me?
I wanted to make a statement.
Well, I'm here now.
Make your damn statement.
Say what you want
to say to me.
- Okay.
- Say it!
You need to get your kid
under control.
And maybe you should
teach him not to steal,
while you're homeschooling him
sub-kindergarten skills.
Kind of like you did your son?
The one that walked out
on his family?
At least I teach my son
to be a human fucking being!
That's enough. Outside.
You gonna run me out
like a little dog now?
Get outside. Now.
Come on.
- Damn it!
- Will you please calm down?
She doesn't like the fact
that I'm a high school dropout,
and I'm homeschooling my son,
but yet he can't see
the damn chalkboard.
I need to tell you something.
No! You know, she's refusing to
accept that he's going blind,
even though she's
constantly complaining
that he's breaking
her little shit.
Shush! Let me talk, okay?
Wee Wee just didn't get into
her garden last night.
Johnathan led her there.
Tore the whole thing
to pieces.
- You saw him?
- Yeah.
I fired a shot up into the air
to run him off.
You have got to get this
situation under control, okay?
If you can't afford
to pay rent or utilities,
you damn sure can't afford
to feed a 300-pound nuisance.
David gave him that pig.
He loves her.
A full-grown pig
is not a pet.
You wanna tell
your grandson that?
No. I'm not trying
to tell you what to do.
I'm just saying that
with your circumstance,
you have got to explore
some options.
Come here.
I gotta go. I'm sorry.
- Who's there?
- Uh, it's JoLynn.
- Hey, buddy. Hi.
- Hey, Curtis.
I was just, uh,
I was just riffing.
I got cooler songs.
I was just riffing around.
- Do you mind if we come in?
- Please, please, come on in.
- Come on in.
- You got a fish tank?
Yeah, yeah, saltwater.
Where's all the fish?
There's just one.
I used to call him Neptune.
- Now I call him Inept-tune.
- What kind of fish is he?
He's an octo-wuss. Might as well
be a chocolate starfish.
He's a shit fish.
You never see him.
He just hides all day.
But that is Plisskin.
He's a total bad ass,
always trying to escape
and shit.
But breaking out
is impossible.
Breaking in is insane.
That is Peter North Parker,
you know, 'cause he's a spider,
man, he's just so big and all.
And this is Claws Meine.
Let me show you something.
Check this out.
That is love at first sting,
right there.
Yoohoo! Johnathan!
He is obsessed
with the ocean.
If you had a shark in there,
he would never leave.
- Johnathan, you like music?
- Hmm?
- You like music?
- Mm-hmm.
Check this out.
Some dude in Austin gave this
to me for a bag of weed--
Uh, weed killer.
Said it was an import.
You like this?
I don't like it.
I love it!
Well, it's yours.
Take it.
- Can I listen to it first?
- Of course! All you want.
You wanna go outside
for a sec?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay. Hey, Johnathan,
make yourself at home.
All of it?
All of it.
Shit. I only have
a week's worth left.
All I got's
a couple days' worth.
What about his regular meds?
I told you about
the complications he has.
He just responds better
to the hydro
than he does with
the pharmaceutical crap.
The only guy I know is Lonny.
He only sells a quarter pound.
I can't afford that much.
We can go in half.
I can't afford that either.
Maybe I could
sell some shit.
Ratshot owes me some.
Oh, it's too bad
we live in Texas.
If we were on the coast,
hydro would be doctor's orders.
Yeah.
Man, you ever think about
leaving Texas?
I don't know, man.
I like it here.
In Texas, you may have shit,
but you'll always have
your dignity.
Here, you can throw your head in
a toilet bowl, lick it clean,
that'll at least make you
the baddest son of a bitch
in the room.
How do you figure that?
the Alamo.
Which reminds me, you wanna see
my dad's most prized possession?
I don't know.
What is it?
I'll be right back.
My old man never let me
listen to Ozzy Osbourne
because he pissed
on the Alamo.
You'd think Ozzy pissed
on his mother's grave,
he's so serious about it.
Check this out.
What is it?
That is an actual musket ball
from the Alamo.
Seriously?
Hell no!
It's an old fishing weight
I hammered down.
I told him it was pried
from Colonel Travis's bedroom.
He's so proud of that, you'd
think it was Bowie's own blade.
I just don't have the balls
to break his heart,
tell him the truth now.
That's really awful, Curtis.
Aw, the old bastard's happy.
That's all that matters.
I wonder how many times
I've been lied to by a man
just to make me happy.
Well, he'd be a fool.
Shit.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm--
I'm sorry.
No, that's-- I mean--
No, it's fine.
Uh...
No. I should probably
go check on...
check on Johnathan
anyway, huh?
Shit.
Johnathan...
- What?
- What are you doing?
I'm looking for Neptune,
but I can't find him.
I'm telling you
he's the shyest pet.
You'll never find
that lazy water bastard.
Johnathan, let's go.
Guess what I did today?
It was a baby,
but it was the real thing.
The mom's still out there.
Sorry you couldn't be there,
but Grandpa says a hunter
takes a shot once he has him.
We have to celebrate
with jellybeans.
Jellybeans!
Mmm, good.
Nothing like those old ones.
- Hey.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Looking for something to eat.
Well, go play, and I'll
make something to eat.
Johnathan! No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Hey, you can't use
the bathroom anymore.
Why?
Just don't, please.
If you gotta go,
go out back like Dad.
If you gotta go number two,
then just go behind the shed.
Look, I'm serious, okay?
Go play, and I'll make us
some oatmeal. Go on.
Did you put any sugar in it?
We're out of sugar,
thank you very much.
You got any jellybeans left?
Yeah.
All right,
put those in there.
Gross.
Why can't we go to Grandpa's?
Because I told you not to.
I don't want no more.
Can I play a song now?
After we finish
your scales, okay?
All right, D-minor.
- Hi.
- She made me pull over
to look at the parakeets.
No, that's fine.
They make great pets.
No, she won't be getting one.
I would have to take care of it.
Oh.
Hey, Julie.
No, I couldn't open
the attachment.
They're pretty!
I want one!
You don't take care of
your puppy or the turtle.
The puppy is ugly
and poops on the floor.
Turtles are stupid.
I want a parakeet!
Which one do you like,
sweetie?
- No, Kimmie, let's go.
- I want a blue one.
I got yellow ones.
I don't want
a stupid yellow one!
- I want a blue one!
- Hold on one second.
Kimmie's about to throw
a hurricane.
I don't have
any blue ones here,
but I just live
right up the street.
We could go get
a couple there.
She has a blue one at home!
Pick one of these
if you want one, and let's go.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it right now! No!
Stop it! No!
Why do your eyes do this?
I have nystagmus
and glaucoma.
Eww.
Want some jellybeans?
Sure.
Hey, Mama,
you want a jellybean?
No, thank you.
Hey, why'd you take
my jellybeans?
Come on, Kim!
Okay.
Uh, Kim?
You'll have to excuse the place.
It's a bit of disaster
since my husband's been on tour.
Oh, really?
My little brother
is in Afghanistan.
Oh, no, my husband's
a musician.
Oh, cool.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me,
I have to take this.
Hey, Julie, hey.
No, I haven't.
No, hey, shut up,
shut up, shut up.
You'll never believe
where I am right now.
This is Captain Johnathan
and first mate Kim
looking for any sea monsters
in the area.
I don't wanna be a first mate.
I wanna be a mermaid.
Why a mermaid? Mermaids are
boring. They don't fight.
I don't care.
I wanna be a mermaid.
Then get in.
If you wanna be a mermaid,
you have to get in the ocean.
I'm not getting in there.
Watch out!
- Why?
- Sea snake!
Man the harpoon!
Kim!
It's just an old spring.
- No, it's a sea serpent.
- Don't be stupid.
A pretty bluebird.
- Thank you.
- Mom, get it away from me!
- Here, piggy, piggy, piggy!
- Get it away from me!
We have to go.
Be careful. Watch your step.
Get in the car.
- We gotta go.
- Okay.
- We'll get our own ride back.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, that's fine.
We'll walk.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Hey, Grandma!
Well, hey, there, little rascal.
Where you been?
You wanna help me
fix my garden?
- No.
- Why not?
'Cause Mom says that
I couldn't come into your house
or your yard.
Why'd she say that?
I don't know, but can I have
a drink from the hose?
Of course.
But don't tell Mom.
Why?
'Cause our water
got turned off today.
Well, sure, of course.
Okay.
"Hello, Jo.
Well, here I am.
Better late than never,
I guess.
I hope.
I started to write you
a thousand times,
but the words
just never seemed to fit.
This morning I woke up
in a motel room in Memphis
to the sight of
one regal little cockroach
perched on my pillow,
just staring at me.
And before I knew it,
all I could think about
was Galveston,
that night we spent together,
that morning we woke to find
an entire army of cockroaches
closing in on
last night's dinner.
Our very first taste
of freedom.
Everything was
so simple then,
so clear.
It was the one time I knew
exactly what I wanted.
I just wanted you.
I miss you, Jo.
I do. I know this
has been hard on you,
but things really seem
to be picking up out here.
The shows are getting better,
and I finally have a little
money to send your way.
I wish I was sending more.
How's Wee Wee
and the Wonder Boy?
I hope he understands.
I used to see the world
like he does.
Now there's a question
for everything.
I can't seem to hold
onto anything.
I wish I could just go back
to that motel in Galveston,
where it made sense.
I don't know why I can't.
Maybe I'm broken.
Maybe I could fix it.
But for now on,
I'll just keep searching.
Searching for you."
No shit.
- That's it?
- I got this too.
- Dang.
- I know.
- Not bad.
Hmm. Man, it won't scan.
Something wrong with it?
I don't know.
It says you won 200 bucks.
Hey, Leon, can you
take a look at this?
God darn it!
I told you to move that bucket.
We all gonna be millionaires?
I don't know.
I think the scanner's busted.
- You gambling, honey?
No, this is a Tennessee Lotto.
Oh.
So you guys
can't cash this here?
Sorry, JoLynn.
It's only good in Tennessee.
Come on, Johnathan.
I'd drive to Tennessee
for 200 bucks.
Johnathan!
Please come take your medicine
and brush your teeth.
- Okay. Guess what.
- What?
I was just reading that
a lobster doesn't have a brain.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
And its kidneys
are in its forehead,
and its teeth
are in its stomach.
Please chew
with your mouth closed.
So if you're ever facing
a giant lobster,
I'll bash it in its forehead
to kill it.
I am a lucky, lucky woman.
- Okay, go to bed, please.
-          - Oh--
Please forgive me for being
a bad wife and mother.
I know I ain't good at
giving my child what he needs.
I promise you...
I promise you
I'll be better.
I can't do this on my own.
- Hi.
- Are you Johnathan?
- Yeah. Who are you?
I'm Gale.
Can I talk to you?
I just wanna ask you
a few questions.
I'm friends with your grandma.
Okay.
So where's your mama?
Asleep.
Have you had breakfast?
No, but she'll probably
make oatmeal when she gets up.
You don't like
oatmeal, do you?
No.
I heard that
you have a pet pig.
Yeah, Wee Wee.
And I heard that Wee Wee
sleeps in your bedroom.
Sometimes, but Mama
don't like her in the house.
She doesn't? Hmm.
Well, can I see your bedroom?
Okay.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Gale with Social Services.
Step away from her,
Johnathan.
I'd advise you
to put down the gun, ma'am.
What are you doing
in my house?
I'm just doing my job.
Now, there's no reason
to be upset.
Do you have a warrant?
No, not yet.
Then get the hell
out of my house!
I'd advise that you comply
with our investigation.
Well, I'd advise you to
stay the hell off my property.
Okay, but if you
don't cooperate,
I come back with a court order
and an officer to escort me.
Let's talk about this.
You stay the hell away
from my son.
I don't want you to ever talk
to that woman again. Ever.
Since the little
boy's dad was away,
the mama leviathan
sent sea monsters
to attack his home.
The crab monster came first.
And then came the big fat one
with a thousand eyes.
No matter how many sea monsters
the mama leviathan would bring,
he will always protect
his mother.
- Yes?
- I'm looking for Mark.
He's out back working.
Hey, stranger.
Hi.
Something wrong?
Why'd you call CPS on me?
What are you talking about?
I'd expect that from her,
but not from you.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, we had a fight about it.
Yeah, well,
they came to the house.
Well, I'm sorry, JoLynn.
This is not my doing.
This is her thing.
I happen to think
you're a pretty good mother.
She's just trying to do
what she thinks is right.
Now, I'm in no position
to judge anybody,
but the way
you and David live,
that is not the way
we raised him.
Let me show you something.
Can you see those medals
right there?
Now, those are my most cherished
personal possessions,
and here they sit
in this dirty garage
because they don't go well
with her knickknacks.
Sometimes in life you got
to choose your battles.
Now, her little
ceramic trinkets
may mean more to her
than those do,
but those do not mean
more to me than she does.
I'm sorry. That's...
That's the most pathetic thing
I've ever heard.
Come on.
Don't make fun of me.
No, I mean she's luckier
than hell to have you.
Yeah, she is.
Hey, uh...
do you ever think
you could love somebody else?
Now, why would you
ask me that?
I mean, do you feel like you
love her 'cause she's the one?
Or did you decide long before
she threw you out in the shed?
Frankly I don't see what the
hell difference it makes anyway
'cause it's not like
I'm going anywhere.
Sweetie, sometimes in life
you get to choose your family
and sometimes you don't.
But that doesn't make them
any less family.
I mean, like you.
To me, you are my daughter.
You always have been,
and you always will be.
And that's
just the way that is...
'cause I love you.
No matter what you
may decide to do.
I owe you more
than I could ever repay.
No, you don't owe me anything.
For once,
I'm offering you something.
I'm listening.
A freezer full of meat.
Will you, uh...
Will you meet me back
at the generator at 9:00?
And don't tell Johnathan.
I'll be there.
The only true weapon
for a sea warrior is a trident!
- Hey.
- Like Poseidon.
What?
Come sit down with me.
Come here.
- You having fun?
- Yeah.
Good.
Hey, you wanna go
on a trip with me?
Where will we go?
Wherever we want.
Can we go to the ocean?
Yeah, we can try.
When will we go?
Tomorrow.
But you gotta
promise me something.
What?
You can't tell anybody.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Promise?
- I promise.
Okay.
It's just gonna be me and you.
What about Wee Wee?
We'll have to ask Grandpa
to take care of her.
Okay.
Okay, go on.
Once there was
a little boy,
and him and his mom and his pig
went out to the ocean,
and he's trying to protect
his mom from the leviathan
'cause he killed
her little baby,
the leviathan's baby.
Sharky piggy, piggy,
piggy, piggy!
Come on.
And the leviathan
is a giant old octopus
that could stand on land.
Real sea monster.
So the little boy
and Wee Wee the Shark Piggy
went to go fight
this leviathan.
Wee Wee, no!
After 5 miles of swimming,
digestive systems growling
for hunger and food,
this long arm came up
and scooped up Wee Wee.
Luckily it didn't eat her
before I could save her.
He said it was worth it
for saving his mom and his pig.
- Johnathan!
- What happened?
You knocked yourself out.
Why did you jump
out of the boat?
I don't know.
My eyes hurt.
Oh, God, not now.
Okay.
Curtis!
Hey, what's up?
You okay?
Look. Can we come in?
We need your help.
Oh, shit. Yeah, yeah.
You sure you want to make
a nine-year-old take vapors?
I have to.
If we don't relieve
the pressure,
the damage is permanent, so...
I'm not gonna let him go blind.
All right, listen,
I want you to open your mouth,
and I'm gonna blow air
into your mouth, okay?
Okay.
It might make you cough
a little bit,
but I want you to hold it in
as long as you can.
Can you do that for me?
Hold it.
- It tickles.
- I know it tastes funny,
but that's 'cause
it's medicine, okay?
You did a good job.
Now we're gonna do it
one more time for me, okay?
So that phone's gotta be worth
at least a couple hundred bucks.
And then the scratch-off
is as good as cash.
Where'd you
get this phone at?
Don't matter.
Look, I need this for him.
Okay. I'll do it...
for you.
For Johnathan.
It's a nice phone.
Yeah.
Hey, Lonny! Hey, man.
Hey, it's Curtis, yeah.
Yeah, hey, could you maybe
come by my place
and bring that real cute
kewpie doll that I like so much?
No, the Q.P. doll.
The real nice one.
Buddy, I need
a quarter pound of hydro.
The best you got.
All right, all right.
All right, thanks.
Bye, buddy.
He's gonna call back in 10.
If we gotta go somewhere,
you're driving.
I can't, Curtis.
Johnathan's inside.
- I'm not leaving him.
- He's passed out cold.
If he wakes up,
he'll be fine by himself.
No, man, if something happens,
I'll lose him.
If something happens,
I got two DWIs already.
If I get caught driving again,
hmm, uh-uh, no way.
No way. I am way too pretty
for prison.
No, I'm not driving, Curtis.
I can't.
At least you get to drive
a balls-to-the-wall classic.
This is a 300 effin' Z, baby.
170 horsepower,
rear wheel drive, V6.
Man, this car costs $30,000
when it was brand-new.
Yeah, in like 1982.
Hey, 1986, man.
Yeah, well,
what's it worth now?
Who cares?
It's got T-tops.
Man, they don't even
make those anymore..
And that rear window
is louvered.
- That is some posh shit.
- Mm-hmm.
That's like having
French blinds on your car.
Mm-hmm.
There he is.
I'll be right back.
How you doing, Lonny?
Shit, man,
I've had better days.
Hey, man, push me
on this thing, will you?
- What?
- Yeah!
I used to love this thing
when I was a kid. Push me.
Okay.
Hey, not so fast.
Hey, do I look like
a screaming schoolgirl?
Aaah!
Now hop on.
How long has it been since
you've been on one of these?
Been awhile.
I hate these damn things.
I'm sorry, Lonny. I can't stay
and play in the park all day.
Seriously, I...
Seriously,
I think I'm gonna vomit.
Can we just--
Can we just do this?
It's all there.
There's a point
in a man's life
when he yearns to enjoy
a place like this.
Is everything all right?
See you around.
Sorry, Curtis.
Sometimes you gotta
throw a dog a bone
or else he'll
come after yours.
Oh, my God.
Hey!
Mom!
Johnathan!
Can you hear me?
Go to the window!
Open the window.
Come on, get your stuff.
We gotta go..
- Why?
- Do it, please.
Where's Curtis?
He had to go help some people.
- What are you looking for?
- It don't matter.
Hot dogs!
Grab your hot dogs!
Get your mustard and relish.
Get your fixings here.
Sorry, Curtis.
Come on, let's go.
- Are you gonna answer it, Mama?
- No, just pedal faster.
- Go get your clothes, okay?
- Why?
Just do it!
Is that you?
Yeah, it's me.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
- I'm-- I'm real--
- No.
Listen, I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Don't say anything.
I don't know
if they're listening.
But if you bastards are,
I want you to know
what you don't find
was never there.
I got to go now.
I don't know if they
can trace this, but...
don't worry about me.
They don't know who you are.
I just--
I just called to say
that you and...
and your special someone
are safe.
I would never do anything
to hurt you.
Thank you so much, Curtis.
I can never repay you.
Thank you.
No.
I got to go.
Bye, girl.
Bye.
- Let's make some noise.
- How?
A lot of noise.
Let's put on a concert.
- Like Dad?
- No. We'll wear makeup.
Eww. Makeup?
Yeah. Boys wear makeup too.
On stage.
- Why?
- So girls can see 'em.
But I don't want girls
to see me.
So their mamas can see them.
Close your eyes.
Shake your head and go crazy!
Yeah!
Hey, I gotta go check
on the generator!
- Okay!
- Keep the concert going!
Okay!
Go crazy! Whoo!
Come on.
- Good girl.
Yeah, come on.
Come on. I know.
I know, honey. I know.
Mark, you can't do this.
Will you put that away?
Get on in there.
That a girl, that a girl.
I'm sorry, girl.
I'm sorry.
Do it, JoLynn.
- Johnathan!
- Grandpa!
- What?
Get your ass back up here!
Come on! Stay away from
the generator. It's dangerous.
Was that Grandpa?
No. It's none of your business.
Come on.
Don't do that to my arm.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Grandpa had to take Wee Wee,
so let's go inside.
- Can you feel that?
- Mm-hmm.
Does it feel good?
You gotta push harder.
That's just like I do.
Oh, yeah, that feels good.
Oh, yeah, that's the stuff.
- You got cute little feet.
- Thank you.
They're stinky,
but they're cute.
They're coming to get you.
Yeah, monsters.
Raah!
This little piggy monster
went to the stinky fish market.
said no.
This little piggy
had some ham.
This little piggy had none.
Aww!
This little piggy went,
"Wee wee wee wee wee wee wee!"
all the way home.
What'd I say, Mama?
What's wrong?
Mama, what's wrong?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Everything's
gonna be okay, Mama.
gonna be all right.
Promise.
- You promise?
- I promise.
You okay?
Yeah.
Come here, baby.
Come lie down with Mama.
Come on.
Johnathan!
- Morning, Captain.
- Morning.
- You hungry?
- Mm-hmm.
Shall we say a prayer?
God is great, God is good.
Thanks for the food, Jesus.
- Amen.
Eat all your medicine.
- Is it good?
- Mm-hmm.
- You ready?
- Ready.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Mm-hmm.
Why don't we just
let the parakeets go?
They'll die if we do that.
It's better this way.
Wait, hold up.
"Jo...
I found the bottom.
And it's in the same place
it's always been.
I'm sorry
I put you through this.
I thought this was
what I wanted.
But I want my family.
I need my family.
I'm coming home.
And if you let me, I'll make
this up to you and Johnathan.
I promise.
If you get this before I do,
I should be
just around the corner.
So we'll see
who gets there faster,
me or my words.
I love you. David."
Hey, if I give you a dollar,
would you put a stamp
and throw that
in the mail for me?
I got it.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Johnathan, are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
What tickets
do you have available
that will get us to the beach?
- One way or round trip?
- One way, please.
Okay.
Well, Miami...
for an adult and a child
would be $367.50,
and for San Diego,
it would be $409.50.
Okay. You got
anything cheaper?
Well, there's always
Galveston.
How much?
Galveston would be $90.25.
Perfect.
You know, I'm gonna help you.
I got the quarter.
Once there was a little boy,
and he got a little piglet once
he was only five years old.
One, two, three.
Once he was nine or so,
him and his mom and his pig
went out to the ocean
'cause he loves the sea.
And him and Sharky Piggy
went to go find
the little boy's dad.
He was lost in the ocean.
But instead they ran into
the mama leviathan.
In anger, the leviathan
tried to kill us,
and he had to fight
to the death.
And I kept on stabbing it
and stabbing it
and stabbing it.
Stupid octopus.
They lived happily ever after
with eating octopus every day.