You and your whore mother.
Might be a bit more appreciative.
Without me you'd both
be out in the streets.
Now be a good girl and make nice.
Come on.
Now you're gonna get it.
What are you doing?
Hey take it easy buddy.
Your full name?
A-N-N-A.
Spell your last name?
N-I-X.
He came into my room and
he started touching me.
He never touched her
inappropriately
I swear.
I didn't mean to kill him.
I was an accident. I didn't mean to kill
him. I just tried to push him off me.
The defendant, Anna Nix is here
by sentenced to 4 to 9 years
in a maximum security juvenile
correctional facility.
Let's go! Move your ass.
Hurry up! We are not getting paid
to wait for you to take your time.
Get on my yellow line!
Side by side!
- Hurry up!
- Come on princess!
Go!
Line up! Heals on the curb.
Last 3.
Ok open your mouth.
Ah.
Alright. Turn around. Drop trou!
Come on! Let's go!
Fast fast fast!
Alright spread'em.
Cough.
Alright.
We're good!
Here it comes!
Alright that's it.
Alright ladies!
Take a towel.
Take your orange.
Side by side!
Hurry it up! Move it Move it!
Welcome to your new home.
My name is Frank.
I'm the warden.
You do exactly what I say! Or you
do exactly what my staff say!
How are we doing everybody?
Are we doing good?
Have a good day.
Let's go! Move out!
Face to the left!
Let's move out!
This is you.
What's your name?
Genie.
You don't talk much.
Do you Genie?
How long you been in here?
5 years 7 months 22 days.
Fuck.
OK LIGHTS OUT!
Let's go!
Lights out!
Bedtime sweetie. Come on.
Let's go. Move your ass.
Lock it up.
Hey.
Don't mind them.
They're just curious.
I'm Kody.
What's your name?
Anna.
Where you from?
Rancho.
I thought I smelled smoked ham.
You got an edge.
It's on the inside.
Didn't see one single tear yet.
Most first cry day one.
I don't want any trouble.
No cuts. No marks.
Who the hell you fall from?
Oh you're one of those?
You must have fucked up big time.
Just trying to be your friend.
I know you think there's juts a
bunch of little girls in here.
But some of these
bitches are monsters.
You're real cute.
Cute don't last long around here.
Frank. Brown.
Can get real nasty.
You know what I mean?
Gotta pick a side.
In here, things are different.
Get the fuck outta here.
Nice to meet you Anna.
Hello again.
Sit down. I'm not playing.
That's better.
What I'm offering you is,
Friendship and Protection. Trust me,
you need us more then we need you.
You see that girl over there?
In case you haven't noticed, a lot
of people have been looking at you.
Ok, I appreciate what you're doing
but I just wanna be left alone.
Before you walk away
and disrespect me,..
know that there is a consequence
for everything around here.
Hey!
She fell. She's clumsy.
Learn how to walk.
Bitch!
This is called a blind spot.
Means you can't see anything.
Body shots.
Means no visible marks.
Never ever disrespect me in
front of my people again.
Ya dig?
One last thing, you say
anything you're dead.
Think about it.
You mean to tell me
you saw nothing.
It was dark.
You sure?
Yes.
Lift up please.
Good news is nothing is broken.
Bad news is that you have
one hell of a bone bruise.
It's gonna hurt for a while.
You new here?
You do drugs?
No.
You a trouble maker?
Just asking to see how
you're gonna fair here.
You have an attitude you're gonna get
into trouble, that much I know for sure.
You don't know me.
No but I know what
it's like in here.
They maybe you can tell me how to
get everyone to leave me alone.
I wish I could.
It's a nasty place.
The people are cruel.
It's prison sweetie.
If you get into real trouble again,
you can always talk to Frank.
20 minutes on and
20 minutes off, OK?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
She's all yours.
Hi.
What are you doing in here?
I'd like to talk to
you for a minute.
Have a seat.
What can I do for you?
I'd like to be on my own.
I heard about that incident.
That was-that was horrible.
I really wish you would've gotten
a good look at those assailants.
It was dark.
Anna, right? Anna Nix?
Solitary is a room about
maybe, 1/4th this size.
And you're in there 23 hours a day.
You get 2 showers a week.
Believe me, you don't want lock up.
Let me get your file
really quick, hold on.
Anna I'm gonna say something.
We do the very best that we can...
To protect you.
But we've got 214 of the nastiest meanest
girls in the whole state of California.
This becomes very very difficult.
I did look at your file. You, this
is so interesting about you...
You are pretty much a model student. I mean
you made straight A's and B's in school.
You play Cello.
I gotta tell you something.
Every year we have a talent show here.
Alright, so you're not interested
in that. I can see that.
Ok I'm gonna tell you something.
If you help me Anna, I'll help you.
I'll tell you the way this works.
Doesn't mean much about
the girls out there.
They're so mean.
But I have the power
to protect you.
And I'll do that for you.
How?
It just sort of like, you know...
Just take care of me.
Ok.
That's all. We're done.
You can go now.
Good luck out there.
Did he come on to you?
I saw you go into his office.
Everyone here is perverted.
Fuck you.
I'm sorry.
Is that Kody got to you?
Been here since I was 12.
Use to run with her.
What happened?
You'll see.
She doesn't mess with you anymore?
She did.
I served 5 years in this place.
One more year and I'm getting out.
Time.
Time's passing as we speak.
All the girls in here are so ugly.
You...
Stop it.
What's the matter?
I think you're pretty.
Ok a noun. A noun is a
person, place or thing.
A good way to remember is "A noun
is a clown, he made me frown".
I've been expecting you.
Grab a seat.
Can you read?
Yes.
Good.
Follow along on page 24.
Alright, where was I?
Oh yeah, who can tell me
what an adjective does?
What good bitch?
I said what's really good?
What's your problem?
I don't fucking like you.
That's the problem.
I'ma cut you. I'ma cut
you up so fucking good.
Walk off.
What the fuck off.
Whack ass bitch.
You ok?
This shit's gotta stop.
I have no choice.
What are you doing?
You got something to say chica?
I want to speak to Kody.
She don't want to talk to you.
I said I want to talk to Kody.
This isn't fall back bitch before
I smack the shit out of you.
Get her Jo!
Shut you face!
Stop!
Play nice.
You doing what I
think you're doing?
Yeah.
So you realize you can't
make it on your own?
Don't trust that bitch.
It's cool.
You sure about that?
Pretty sure.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
If you didn't do what you did,
I wouldn't respect you.
Let's take a walk.
Anna Lynn Nix.
Involuntary manslaughter.
You shoved you stepfather
out of a window.
I have my sources.
I didn't shove him. I pushed him.
He was on top of me, drunk.
Bastard was molesting you huh?
It's ok. Most of the girls in
here have been raped or molested.
I was. I'm not ashamed to say it.
I messes you up huh?
It fucks you up completely.
Look, you want to run with me,
you gotta prove yourself.
Lunch count! Line up!
Talk later.
Come with us.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Wow.
How did you get all this shit?
Let's just say, you do them favors...
sometimes they return the gesture.
Have a drink.
This is Bella, tory, switch, Jo.
Not bad huh.
Now, as much as I would like to welcome
you, It's just not the way it works.
I saw that bitch fucking with you.
You're gonna walk up there and
you're gonna clock her in the head.
And we're gonna
record it with this.
That way if you try to bring us
down, we got out asses covered.
What's the matter? Shook?
What's good bitch?
Remove your clothes inmate.
Get in there.
Alright sir.
Thank you.
Did you have fun?
That was only 47 hours.
Can you imagine what 2
whole weeks would be like?
They tell me that you're
with the low riders now.
The low riders.
You know how I know that?
I have 119 cameras around here.
I can see everything,
every time everywhere.
If I didn't like you...
I could put you in
there for 2 weeks.
They would have left you alone.
They really would have.
But you didn't take my deal.
You should uh,
consider yourself lucky.
I'll tell you what, you don't
want to go back to solitary...
Then whatcha gonna do...
You're gonna give me the
best blow job you've given.
Either that or what I'ma do is lock
you up 23 hours a day for a month.
That's gonna be bad. I mean you get outta
you're not gonna even know your name.
Ok?
Ok.
God stop twitching.
Be happy. This is a celebration.
Don't worry, when they new
shipment of new girls comes in...
He's gonna forget all about you.
All done.
Badass, right?
You better like it.
That shit is art yo.
Give us a minute.
Shut the door.
Relax.
You're in now. It's official.
Damn girl.
You drank the whole thing.
I told you I don't do that shit.
Don't be a pussy.
It's not a needle.
It's when you start shooting up,
that's when you become a zombie.
I can't.
I wouldn't give it to you, if I
didn't think you could handle it.
What are you giggling about?
Last month I was in my room,
playing with my...
Playing with you what?
Your pussy?
No.
I was playing with my cello.
You know how to play the cello?
Yeah. My grandma taught me.
That's the only thing what would ease my
mind, we he was doing that stuff to me.
I would close my eyes
and think of the music.
You have the most beautiful smile.
You should smile more.
I'm usually not into girls but,
You...
You're special.
If anybody try to hurt you.
They'd have to go through me first.
Lights out!
Don't look at me like that.
I fuck who I want to fuck, Bitch!
What the hell is going on in here!
Nothing.
0822 this is not your cell.
Get out!
Do me a favor Ma'am.
Sign in for me please.
You told me that
next week you're gonna get me out!
I'm gonna bail you out!
Just hang fucking tight! Alright!
Hey! Visitation is over!
Keep you fucking mouth shut!
- Keep your fucking mouth shut!
- I'ma fuck you up! I'ma fuck you up!
How are you?
Talk to me.
What do you want me to say?
You tell me.
You really think I did it, do you?
I didn't come here
to talk about that.
He was a good man.
He took care of us.
You call that a good man?
He did everything in
the world for you.
You're fucking delusional.
You're fucking crazy...
Hey!
He treated you like you
were his own daughter!
He cooked! He fixed things!
He fucked me every single day since I was
a little girl and you knew all about it!
You knew all about it!
Hey!
Oh my god! I can't believe
you're doing this?
If you don't want the visitation
to end, keep-the-volume-down.
You deserve to be in here.
Yeah.
Just leave me alone.
Don't ever come back here.
You wouldn't be here if she
wasn't with that perv.
She picked him. Not you.
The way I see it, you did the world
a favor by taking his ass out.
Hey she's got a knife.
Get the fuck off of me!
Ok ladies! Ok!
- Break it off! Break if off!
- Stop!
Get up! Get up! Get over there!
- What's going on?
- Bitch get out of my fucking nuts!
Oh is that right!
Yeah.
You told me that last week.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah I'm busy right now. I'm busy
right now; I'll call you back later!
Ok. Bye bye.
Ok.
Now the department of corrections
have stop by here and have told me,
That inmate 0822 which is of course you,
has a large number of infractions...
She was going to stab me.
I can see on the monitor, it
looked like you attacked her 1st.
She had a knife.
Ok she had a weapon.
She didn't have a weapon.
I mean it, it really
doesn't matter does it?
Because I put her away fro 2 weeks.
Now, but you!...
What?
What do you mean what?
Don't "what?" me.
You know exactly what
I'm talking about.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You know that shit will kill you.
But you like it.
So why don't you take a little hit.
Take a hit. You know you
like that stuff. You like it.
There you go.
Now here's the way this deal works.
You take care of me now. And this
little incident that you did.
It's gonna go nowhere
near your record.
So stand up.
Go ahead and stand up.
There you go. Ok.
Turn around.
Mmhmm.
Good.
Now pull your pants down.
Mmhmm.
And... bend over.
There you go.
This is fun.
This is going to be fun.
Alright.
Ok. Here we go.
Just one second here.
Gotta be safe now a days, You know?
Ok.
Alright. There we go.
Damn.
Shut up!
No yelling!
What the fuck are you reading?
Don't talk to me when you're high.
I'm not high.
What are you reading?
Don't.
Why do you care?
Don't start that with me.
Fuck you!
Don't ever talk to me again.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
What happen?
I bit my lip.
Hmm. Is that right 0822?
Yeah.
Come on let's go.
Yeh. Come on in you guys.
Come on in.
Thank you.
Come here.
Come here. I want you to
sit in the captain's seat.
Come on.
Come on it'll be fun.
You do that. I'm gonna
finish up really quick.
Ok. You know Anna...
I'm kinda getting tired
seeing you come in here.
Then send me home.
Well that's not
really gonna happen.
So you rape me?
Whoa Whoa Whoa.
See that's a different word.
Rape.
You know the thing about Rape, It's if
you really wanna know what Rape is...
I can send you up, there's a
place just up-Just up the road,
A little piece. And I send you up there,
they got some big ol' mama girls up there.
This is kiddy prison. This is the
equivalent to Disneyland right here.
Pack me a bowl now.
What the hell is the
matter with you?
Can't believe you ask
me that question.
You gotta learn how to control your rage.
You're got gonna make it in here.
Keep this up, you're going to
have to buy your own shit.
You got any money?
Can't keep floating you.
You're not a fish anymore.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm not cut out for this place.
Stop it.
Ok?
I care about you.
Nobody cares about me.
I do.
I just want to be left alone.
Fine.
Get out. Take your stuff and go.
You're such a little kid Anna.
Fuck you!
Get the fuck out!
You ungrateful little bitch!
Hey girl.
Leave me alone.
What the hell do you want?
Get out of here.
Please.
I said get out of here!
Fuck!
Fucking idiot.
I don't do first timers.
Are you sure about this?
Fuck.
You're so stupid.
Go, Keep a look out.
No veins girl.
Fuck you. You a total idiot?
You're gonna fuck up your life?
I can handle myself.
Obviously you can't.
Stop talking to me like
a dumb fucking kid.
You are a dumb fucking kid.
Fuck you!
I will blind you bitch.
Don't fuck with me.
Done.
You're out.
You're on your own.
Raise the bitch up.
What? You though I wasn't
gonna catch up to you?
Who in the fuck do you think I am?
Cracker bitches like you amuse me.
Come in here all hard and shit.
3 weeks later you crying
home to your mama.
Breathe girl.
Breathe.
That's right. Keep it up.
Take care now.
Breath in.
And out.
You got a death wish?
I hate to see you like this.
Let's go easy.
Crazy. Crazy world baby.
What are your thoughts on suicide?
Mmh.
I tried to kill myself twice.
My only advice is, If you mess up
they through you in the psych ward.
Those fuckers are crazy.
You whore.
You killed me for it.
You asked for it.
You're gonna die in jail.
What the fuck is this shit?
Just do me.
Please.
Chill.
I feel sick.
There's a drug counselor I
think you should talk to.
She's good.
She helped me.
You?
Al long time ago.
Yeah well figures.
You know what?
I don't care what happens to you.
Do as many drugs as want.
They only bring withdrawal.
I hope you fucking die bitch.
What the fuck are you
doing over here bitch?
You hear me?
Aah!
Sobered up I see.
How you feeling?
If I let you sleep in your
bed will you be a good girl?
Come on.
That's withdrawal for you.
I gotta talk to you.
No you don't.
Shootin' up?
What are you? Retarded?
Half those bitches go AIDS.
You should get tested.
Leave me alone.
This yours?
I'm talking to you,
is this your book?
I didn't write it.
Getting smart?
Hey!
Fuck you!
You little junkie bitch.
Hey stop it.
Either you're my friend or my enemy.
What is it?
Neither.
Making some bad decisions girl.
From now on, I'm just gonna
keep to myself if I can.
Just stay in here.
Your breathe smells like puke.
You're gonna be like
this for a few days.
I can't.
You can.
Come on.
Don't. Stop.
I'm so sick. Gotta get some.
Get away from her.
I'm taking you. I care too
much to see you like this.
Girl, you come with me
one way or another.
This is strike 3.
You don't want that.
Girl you disrespect me like this. I swear
to god I'm gonna fucking kill you.
This is your last god damn chance.
Come with me or I'm gonna
bet you down girl.
Get off me!
You get any closer and
I'm gonna kill myself.
You don't know what it's like!
I need you to remove that object
from your throat and calm down 0822.
Now!
Get off of me.
0822.
My name is Anna!
Alright, calm the fuck down, Anna.
Anna just calm down.
I can make this easy for you.
I know what it's like
to work with you.
Awe well then, would you like one day.
Would you like one month?
I don't care anymore.
Everybody stay down!
Stay down!
Some body let me out of here!
Let me out of here!
Somebody!
Please!
Let me out!
Tray.
You want to fuck me?
You can look.
Stop talking. Shut up!
Faggot.
Tray!
Take the Tray.
Shit.
Shit!
Medic.
My name is Dr. Han.
Where am I?
Suicide watch.
You do remember what happened, no?
I was in there for a while.
How do you feel now?
I'm tired.
Are you aware of the
severity of your actions.
You do recall
attempting suicide, no?
Yes.
So you do want to end your life?
No. I just wanted out.
Out?
Out of that room.
I swear to you,
I didn't want to kill myself.
I just lost my mind.
How do you feel?
Like shit.
Withdrawal will do that.
If I take these of you will you
do something you'll regret?
No.
Let me ask you something...
Why would you give up a free
scholarship to Pacific Conservatory?
You do right, you could be
out of here in 2-3 years.
Been here 3 years.
See girls throw their
lives everyday.
Why don't you worry about yourself?
Trust me, It's the first
thing on my mind.
Please shut up.
Are you ok?
Hey are you ok?
Help! Help! Someone come here!
Help!
Somebody help!
She's having a seizure.
Her airwave is obstructed,
get Dr. Jacobs.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Would you like to talk to somebody?
I wanna see my mom.
How are you?
They're taking the house.
Mom, just listen to me.
He's dead.
He can't hurt us anymore.
I'm the one that deserves
to be in here. Not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so so sorry.
You have a gift.
You have such a talent.
And when you get out of here,
cause you will.
I want you to go to
that conservatory.
I'll go with you.
How do you know they
still want me there?
I'll go with you. I promise.
I promise.
I'll talk to the lawyer.
I'll talk to the judge.
And I'll tell him the truth.
Relax!
Hey.
The warden what's to see you.
You're doing better I hear.
I feel better.
You see this?
19 years of corrections.
I've been bit. Scratched.
Kicked.
Nobody has left a mark.
Not permanent one.
But you have.
I'll always remember you.
I'm sorry.
You're lucky I like you.
I was just about ready
to ship you off.
That was drugs.
Are you ready to go into Gen.
Pop.?
No.
You can't say anything
in front of my fiancé.
I'll do what it takes. I give you
my body. Whatever you want.
Just please keep them away from me.
Alright.
Anna, I have mentioned this to
you a couple times before...
But it's really important to me. Because
I think it's important for you too.
Dead huh?
We'll see about that.
Yeah.
How'd you do that?
Gotta be tough.
What do you want me to say?
You're the nicest person in here.
If I was nice.
I wouldn't be in here.
Why are you in here?
I don't talk about it.
Look at that skinny bitch.
Look who it is.
What up bitch?
Put the mop down.
Go ahead.
What I do?
Just come with me.
What's going on?
Come on in.
Sorry the room is all dusty.
We um,
don't really use it anymore.
Ever since the digital age.
What do you think?
I had it restrung for you and,
Polished and nice and everything.
So what I want you to do, I want you
to practice. I want you to get good.
For the talent show.
I want you to be really ready.
Come on.
Play it.
Right now?
Yeah.
Come on.
Get her. Get her.
What's good bitch!
No you did not.
That's the most disrespectful
shit I have ever seen.
Oh I ain't gonna kill you. But this
time I'm not afraid to leave a mark.
Don't worry about that
shit with Frank so much.
You're not that pretty anymore.
Which hand is the
cello playing hand?
I heard you are going to
grace us at the talent show.
Or is it the left one?
Fuck her up.
Did Kody do this?
Yes.
She'll be punished.
If it means anything, I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Off limits.
Give us a minute please.
Frank?
Yeah.
It's bad.
Who's gonna believe me?
I believe you.
Nobody ever believed me.
My own mother never believed me.
My sister's husband
works for the governor.
If I can get to him we can bring the
bastard down before he ever finds out.
You would do that for me?
Not just for you.
Keep your fucking mouth shut!
You ok?
Have a good day. I love you.
Ok, bye bye.
Hi Jane, how you doing?
Is this because of you?
Lord honey, what happened to you?
Did you do something to Anna Nix?
Anna? Listen Anna...
I'm telling you about Anna. And
here's something about her, ok?
She's a troubled little girl and
we're working our butts off
to get her life all cleaned up.
You know that?
Right?
She told me some things about you.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh Jane I'm so sorry about your eye.
I really am. Hope it gets better.
And probably take some Advil.
I will really help. Ok?
Thank you. Thanks for
telling me everything.
Yeah. Yeah Jane?
Uh huh. Yeah.
Let's go ahead and finish her off.
Security!
Oh my god.
Come on. Come on.
Anna, do you know why
I called you in here?
No.
Because I think you
know who killed Jane.
I don't.
My gut feeling...
It's the same person who
did that to your face.
Why would she do that?
Cut the crap.
If you haven't noticed she's crazy.
Rumor has it that you're next.
Anna, good luck at the talent show.
I'm really looking forward
to watching you play.
♪ Rapping ♪
Give it up to killa Kal
and the K block crew.
Ya ya that was ill. Up next I got
some classy shit for your ass.
Anna Nix on the cello.
Yeah you heard me right.
The mother fucking cello.
So put your hands together
and make some NOISE!
Anna Nix.
Is that good princess?
That was amazing.
My who twelve years of doing this,
I've never heard or seen
anything quite like that.
No no no no no no.
I want you to keep that.
Keep it. It's yours.
You've done me right.
You know...
When I heard you playing tonight,
When I looked up
there and I saw you,
So you deserve a chance.
You deserve a REAL chance.
So what I've done,
I've schedules a parole
hearing for you.
Really?
Mmhmm. Next month.
Now take it off.
That's good. Mmhmm.
Oh.
All of it.
Yeah.
Oooh yeah.
Lay down.
There we go.
You know you could look like
you're enjoying it a little bit.
There we go.
I got a parole hearing.
Next week.
I wouldn't be so quick
to trust Frank.
He likes to pump people
up then crash them.
I got a deal with him.
Well what does he have
to gain if you're gone?
What's up?
Hey! Keep moving. Keep moving.
Have fun Cinderella.
Keep mopping.
Talking shit bitch! Talking shit!
Huh?
Letter up.
Parole hearing. September 13th.
What up bitch?
Huh what! What up bitch!
Hey!
What up?
Either kill me or help me.
Help you do what?
Bring down Frank.
Shut the fuck up.
I should fucking stab you
in the throat right now.
How?
Have a seat.
You ready?
Yeah.
On. Off.
It's really easy.
You sure you want to do this?
I got no choice.
I missed you.
What?
You fucking idiot.
God damn you bitch!
So you nervous?
A little.
What do you think my
recommendation should be?
We had a deal.
You're right.
I'm totally fucking with you.
So this is our last one, so I
really want to enjoy this.
So let's make it... slow.
Come here.
You're next.
Come on.
0822?
Anna Nix? Sentenced for 4 years
for involuntary manslaughter.
Served 1 year 3 months.
How are you today Ms. Nix?
I'm just really grateful for
the opportunity to be here.
Tell us why you feel like
you should be released?
I feel like I am
100% rehabilitated.
Do you feel remorse
for your actions?
Yes.
I feel terrible that it happened.
I'm really sorry.
I was young and stupid.
From the review of your file it looks like you
have had numerous infractions in your intake here.
Care to explain?
Those infractions were mainly due to
trying to adjust to life in here.
I'm truly sorry for everything that
happened and I have since matured.
Warden.
Anna Nix is a special girl
with a wonderful talent.
She's an amazing Cello player.
She was gracious enough
to perform for us.
It was one of the most amazing
displays of talent...
I've ever seen and I
really really mean that.
And as much as I would like to say
that Anna Nix is a model inmate,
Unfortunately she has a real
problem with authority.
I don't think it's just her necessary
acting out. I just think it's a matter of
circumstance. Perhaps it would be better
if she remain in here for a while longer
before she goes to the outside.
Wow.
In light of the warden's
recommendations,
and your numerous infractions
here, I have no choice but deny
you parole at this moment.
Wait!
What?
Before you lock me away again.
I would like you to see what your
trusted does behind closed doors.
What is this?
Let me take a look at this.
What the hell is that?
Let me see that.
I can take a look at this-
- Don't move! Don't move.
- Let me see it, Let me see.
What the hell is this?
Officer get her out of here.
You have a lot of explaining to do.
That is obviously a staged performance.
Can you not see that?
It is not a staged performance.
Officer, please detain this man!
Knock it off ladies!
Knock it off!
If I was you I would get too happy.
You still go me.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Well this whole place is messed up.
Did you see that video?
That was some messed up stuff.
Well we need to get internal
affairs involved on this.
Ms. Nix.
What you did today
was very very brave.
And on behalf of the state of
California, We apologize.
We promise you a full on
investigation will take place,
and justice will be served.
In light of today's events,
We grant you parole today.
You're free.
Come on. Let's go.
Thank you.
Good luck.
I'm sorry about the
ways things turned out.
I'm sorry too.
See you in the outside?
Don't come back.