EVERYTHING TO LOSE
Welcome to Bickleton, New Jersey.
Bickleton occupies less than 7km ²,
but is home
for more than 26,000 people.
We have the typical Main Street,
Lions Club
and reputable schools,
of the nursery. 12 years.
But the great attraction of Bickleton
is the proximity of the city.
In 35 minutes I can go
of my living room
Times Square,
depending on traffic.
. I have lived here all my life.
Fuck you, clown!
part of the furniture I already do
this community.
My name is Adam  Harris
and this was my life.
My grandfather served in U.S.S. Missouri
in World War II.
He told me stories
whenever we visited.
Stories of pain and triumph
and leaving the country proud.
it means to be a hero.
. sometimes start to cry. .
. My father, John Harris, .
. was in Vietnam. .
. never told stories. .
. I .
. finished high school among the best .
11 percent of my class. .
. could have stayed between 10 percent, .
but I failed physical education. .
. party finalists, TJ Buck .
said something that did not. .
Man, this city produces losers.
. worked in a grocery store. .
. I and my friends .
Mandavi in ??town. .
.We knew  malta
snooker hall, .
. the video store and the local bar. .
had everything he needed. .
. was all free, thanks to .
exchange of foodstuffs. .
. As we lived at home, income, and .
laundry were also free. .
. Life was beautiful, since each .
do their part. .
. The only type of school .
we thought could go away .
. Chico was the fornix. .
. Chico fornicate fornicate. .
. That's what he did. .
No longer did anything. .
. Chico fornicate fucked all .
the cute girls from school. All .
. Under normal conditions, .
have the will to kill, .
. but Chico was cool, .
knew the place. .
. Chico told us when and where .
would fuck .
. and it was always in front .
an open window, .
. so we could see. .
. After high school, Chico would .
to California to make movies, .
. and fornicating with models. If anyone .
in the city was able, he was. .
Pay attention, guys.
Unfortunately, the hearing is over ..
. But after ten unsuccessful auditions, .
. Chico returned to work .
Burgers  in Bickleton. .
. my other friends started .
to have full time jobs. .
. I do not. I was accepted at a school .
in New York. .
. What I wanted was to meet girls. .
I already have a drink
and she will pay the next round.
. When not apparent, .
had to go to plan B. .
Were you drinking?
A bit.
This is it, dear.
You know you want to come
for me, Adam.
., without more, .
was hooked. .
Another 10 seconds.
Campus security!
Open the door!
Hope you money
for bail.
. Well, did not. .
. She went to jail .
and I was expelled from university. .
. Okay. .
. was again with my friends, .
to live the dream in Jersey. .
- Don, you will come or not?
- How's the water?
- Wet. Come in, geek.
- Okay.
- I know Chico fornicate?
- No. What have you been doing this chrome?
- Now it does nothing. He killed himself.
- Chico's dead?
He was caught by a train.
They say it was an accident.
How? The train was his home
and picked it up?
Everyone knows that the trains
spend all hours. Think!
I saw him at a party a few weeks ago.
He said that his life
was in chaos.
Fuck it, we are still
all alive, right?
As we did not catch him
with trains.
To us.
- At undercooked hamburger.
- And to smoke weed.
Gentlemen, to pornography.
To a group of normal types,
fighting the good fight,
they do not give up
nor allow themselves to fall.
We have seen our dose
Scene sanded,
but we have come this far.
- It's true.
Malta, the better that this is impossible.
To our boys.
- Who is in my pool?
- Shit! Let's go!
- Bring the beer!
- It's my grill? Pirem from here!
Come here!
You know the problem?
Too many people believe
in certain institutions
unconditionally.
As the university.
Do not say it is not good,
but it is not unconditionally good.
Walking in college means nothing,
if you do not know why there stilts.
Everyone says that you have
to go to college
because the system does
brainwashing people.
However, the price of tuition
rises every year.
It is big business
that perpetuates itself.
- Do you know what the saddest part?
- What is it?
Have customers
to advertise for them.
"You have to go to university."
Fuck you!
You're the stupid type
smartest I know.
. That's what I wanted .
No, not really. .
. But it could be worse. .
- How are you, Adam?
- Hello, Mrs. Primrose.
.- What would you like today?
- How about a muffin  . blueberry?
Sounds good.
Thanks.
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Have a nice day.
Adam! Call an ambulance
quickly, the old lady got hit!
Ambulance calls soon!
. 112. .
I'm in Ami's Bagels,
196, Main Street.
Send an ambulance,
a lady was hit.
Forget it.
Has no head.
You gotta see this.
. I worked for the Israelis. .
. That beast was Uri, .
the younger brother of my boss. .
. Working with Uri .
was plotted. .
I was in a bar last night
where some girls were dancing.
They were so beautiful.
They had breasts the size of babies.
. Uri was very arrogant. .
.Just wanted to know  women .
and money. .
. He did anything for them. .
Hundred dollars to go to bed
with the next customer.
Go away, Uri.
.Hundred dollars as the next customer
asks  bagel . with poppy seeds.
Hundred dollars to kill you
before the end of turn.
Fuck you!
I am Israeli, I kill you!
Stop eating the egg salad.
Ami is losing money with you.
Fuck you, I have to see
it is good.
I think I see a rat.
.Hello,  sexy .
. was absurd, .
went through life eating. .
. was like an anaconda, .
ate twice my weight .
. and not put on weight a pound. .
Uri was intrigued. .
. started to make bets. .
.$ 65 for all  bagels .
meal and two of corn.
- $ 110 for whole wheat.
- How long?
Two hours, no butter
and without cream cheese.
As a ham for 70.
No, the ham is too expensive,
Ami was killing me.
. It was like .
a catalog price on his head. .
A pack of butter,
$ 43,
six shell eggs
$ 55.
. not always involve food. .
$ 120 for a 60cm cord
or a handful
packing material.
- And if you drink this oil?
- Still die, man.
The salary of a week.
. The only out was to bet .
a cabbage to eat it bite. .
. Pay attention. .
In the Army Way.
Paid, asshole.
What? You bet I ate,
I have not eaten, so I'm not paid.
A bet does not work like that!
In Israel it is so!
. was then that the good times .
over. .
She was without a head.
You know how many times I saw it
in Israel?
- Shit!
- What?
Look at the tires.
It's her brain.
My ..
.. thousand dollars in cash.
. The accident haunted me. .
. I had to go to the funeral. .
IN MEMORY OF
GRACE PRIMROSE
- Do not let us help you.
- Yes.
Why must bad things happen
to good people?
. I was fascinated. .
.The knowledge was  .
stored in this piece .
. What can know about someone .
from a piece of brain .
. Brain is equal to many questions. .
Adam, egg salad makes more now!
.How : "Why have happened .
bad things to good people? ".
What client so stupid!
Perhaps this makes you smarter.
Have a nice day.
- What are you doing?
- He is stupid, needs brains.
- Are you crazy? He could get sick!
- I do not know him at all.
And Grace Primrose?
You're disrespecting the memory
and her whole life, you idiot!
I go after it.
What will you tell her?
Woe to you?
Cut tomatoes in Israel
who messes with us!
Come here!
Step aside!
Uri! Uri!
Look what you did to the store!
What are you doing?
This crazy stole the brain
an old lady!
Ami, he pointed me a knife.
Poisoned food from a customer!
Sorry folks.
The cookies are on the house.
Let's talk in my office.
Now!
. Uri was Ami's brother, ie, .
I would be fired and ready. .
. But Uri was illegal in this country. .
. therefore a phone call .
on the attack with a knife .
. and goodbye, America, .
hello, the Israeli army. .
.We have combined a beautiful  compensation. .
. could have no job, .
but would not starve to death, .
. my mother did not raise no fool. .
. Unless you ask .
to my mother. .
How to get fired
a grocery store?
- Any idiot does that job.
- Look who brought the ham!
Do not pay bills with ham,
your asshole!
John, come here!
What happened to you?
Were you among the top 11 percent
in your class!
Can I pay bills with it?
Where you think you going?
No, this is not your room.
Me and your father talked and let you
live here without pagares income
You're not helping.
So it's over.
- So now I have to pay rent?
- No, you have to leave home.
Your room will be
a sewing room.
I'm fired and you expel me?
No, you'd already cast.
The dismissal only happened at a bad time.
- Do not believe it!
- Woe to you?
And I have to believe
I created my only son
to be an unemployed 25-year
living at home
and is expelled from college
for soliciting a prostitute.
But thou knowest not sew!
My God!
Whiskey.
Thanks, Luke.
Listen, do you think I can sleep
in your house?
Sorry, but I have a girlfriend
new and like to fornicate
the entire house.
That would ruin our style.
Fornicate new girlfriend ..
What a clown!
. When I left the bar was drunk .
and angry ..
. .. with my mom, .
with Israel, .
. but mostly .
myself. .
. I did not deserve anything. .
. not fought in any war. .
.It was just a failed  useless. .
. I only wanted things from. .
. was so angry and drunk, .
. I decided to beat .
the next person you see. .
. Indeed, the next man you saw. .
. battery never a girl. .
. But the next guy was dead. .
- At the bottom of the block.
- What street?
Will you tell us?
Congratulations, kid.
You're a hero.
. His name was Richard Pope .
but his nickname was "Hands." .
. few years older than me, .
the "Hands" broke all records .
. reception and led our team .
football to successive championships. .
. He should have gone away. .
. But the same hands .
who caught 284 passes, .
. were used to attack .
seven women. .
. A portrait robot was placed .
in the city, .
. I had never noticed. .
. had just breaking .
his seventh victim, .
. Mona Huxley .
when I showed up. .
. As in all small land, .
the news spread quickly. .
. My mother was so proud .
that made me go home. .
. Until we won a free dinner .
in "Red Lobster" in Paramus. .
I always knew you were a good person.
- How are you?
- Hello!
. People would go to look .
to me in a different way. .
. imagined my life .
as a superhero, .
. always be sought. .
- Let's take a good picture of it.
- There he is!
Make some noise out here!
. I understand the secret identity, .
but why have a job? .
. you like so much of journalism .
. not imagine a superhero .
in need of money. .
Damn Taxes!
. The least people could .
do was help you, .
. by saving lives .
and doing good deeds. .
. Apparently, there was a reward .
the capture of Richard Pope. .
. But that was not part .
more rewarding. .
- Hello
I am the mother of Adam.
This is my husband, John.
- Hello, John, Bob Huxley.
- Your daughter is very brave.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Carlson heard of Frankie?
He was working at Sizzler ..
- Not Sizzler, Steak and Ale is.
- Does it matter?
Anyway, was closed
and were clean.
Two types knocking at the door
and ask to go to the bathroom.
Frankie let them enter
and lean on him a gun to his head.
Frankie forced to open the safe and
put us in the fridge.
- Were there girls?
- Man, could have died frozen.
- Well done, went into the fridge!
- What were you doing in relation to the gun?
Did I say what I should do it.
Spim, lay your hand to me,
as if you were targeting me. Come on!
What you have to do is grab
this hand, twisting it
and using the elbow as well.
- Okay.
Caught in the gun
and you give him on the face.
Okay, my! Stop!
My God!
You got the dog on?
If they bite me,
bite up to you.
- The dog is outside.
- Don 't be clever with me.
- You said you were coming for two hours.
- There've been selling lollipops, asshole.
. Everyone knew Vic. .
. was when we were freshmen veteran. .
drug trafficker professional. .
. "Watch my bike, .
have to go poo. .
.What the hell they put
those gyros, . Greek?
.Never ask a gyro  . there, man.
Vic, do not get faster
if they came by car?
I do not want to teach
manage my business.
He had learned to drive, make sure
and enter the system. I do not want that.
Whats there to drink?
I'm dry.
We have beer.
I do not drink while working.
Anything else?
. Diet soda .
The sweetener does not cause cancer?
Your curtains do not match.
No girls?
This is some Greek orgy?
We're just playing cards.
Where did you get this?
The brook?
Get you a cheap filter.
Just the same herb, Vic, thank you.
Okay. Gotta go.
120 are in the bag
Greek and still owes me 75.
Don owes me 40
by phone cards.
- Come on, man, I forgot ..
- So now we are one.
The total is 235.
But it is by 235.
- He is right, are 235.
- I am good at math.
Come on, do the sharing.
Great.
It was you that you got
Richie Pope?
Good, "Hands" was a creep.
I know some stories.
. A tragic end for .
Samantha Cohen of five years, .
. abducted from her home .
for more than two weeks. .
. His body was found .
in the forest, .
. near West Milford, New Jersey. .
.'s very sad. However, .
there is good news. .
. Women in the city of Pickleton .
sighed with relief .
. with the arrest of this man, .
Richard Pope. .
. Pope is the prime suspect .
a series of egregious violations, .
. that began two years ago. .
He looks like a cockroach.
The problem is that when there
an infestation of cockroaches,
a crush and there are a hundred more
hidden in the shadows.
What this city needs
is an exterminator.
. The more I thought about it, .
did I realize more. .
.Was this . .
.He had discovered  finally .
my vocation in life. .
I'm in trouble?
I know.
- Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon, may I help you?
I want to join the police force,
I decided to be police.
Wait just a moment, okay?
Where can I get the uniform?
My size is S.
Thinks it can
Police make it?
You must go to school,
in academia
and then can become police.
No offense, Agent Pavone, but ..
.. I know that the police of this city
to go for a joyride
between Burger King and McDonald's.
I can do it.
You are arming themselves in funny?
Not for the first time in my life
know what I want, I'm ready.
I just told you.
First go to school
and then go to the gym.
Bob, can you get here?
. I was a hero, .
but did not look like that. .
. was fat where it should be thin and .
skinny on other sites. .
. Fuck it. .
. things would change. .
. decided I had to live up .
of my image, I was a hero. .
. It was going to conduct myself as such. .
. I began to wake up .
increasingly early age, .
. though he had to do it. .
. ate a dozen eggs, bacon, .
sausages, frozen waffles. .
. Then spent the rest of the day .
to turn everything into muscle, .
. with an intensive training regimen. .
. pushups, push-ups, .
abdominal lifts weights. .
. To gain strength, .
started jogging. .
.Three miles , .
after eight. .
No sleep at work!
. I found myself touring the city .
late at night. .
. limit myself to look. .
knew there were things happening. .
. But it was impossible to find them. .
Hello Mona is?
No.
Okay.
Can tell you ..
Forget it. Thanks.
You got that monster, the Pope.
Mona came out with a friend.
Okay ..
Thanks.
You should have killed that bastard.
Father?
Can you teach me to fight?
Even a strong man has
their limitations.
Go to the phone.
It is Mona.
An important meeting?
It is not important.
Not a date.
- Have fun.
- Thanks.
Hello
Sorry for having to bring the car.
My mother had to go to work.
No problem.
Where are we going?
- With the phone is bigger the tip.
- Thanks.
How is it, boy?
Where have you been? Do not have time
to call me, fool?
I always have time
to call you fool.
Greek, this is Mona.
Mona, this is George the Greek.
- How are you?
- Well, thank you.
- Have you come to Greece?
- No, only work in the restaurant.
- How many? Two?
- Yes.
Come on.
Here you are.
- I was happy to connect.
- My dad said you spent there.
And passed.
I know I did not think
he was lying.
Well, of course.
Tell me about yourself.
Okay. I have 25 years e. .
.. I was born here, grew up here, e. .
I measure 1.80m, but sometimes I say
I measure 1.77 m.
Okay.
Want to know the dishes of the day?
It's a lie, no dishes of the day.
What do you want?
.- Do me a favor, do not ask  gyros .
- Okay.
- Why not ask for me?
We want two hamburgers
with cheese and baked potato
with cream sauce
and extra butter.
Cream of broccoli
toasted bread with extra ..
And for the girl,
a tuna sandwich.
You got it.
Are you a social worker?
I am taking a master's degree at Brown.
I came to the funeral of my Aunt Grace.
My condolences for your aunt.
Thank you.
She went to my grocery store.
It seemed like a good person.
Are you okay?
Question to my children
in 20 years.
Father
The mother says that you want to talk to me.
I want to show you something.
We started the night patrols
on April 69.
There was nobody
to take care of us.
Fuck it. Invent.
We take care of each other.
But the jungle was the hole
more dark and scary
I've never seen.
Sometimes we spent weeks
without seeing a bastard of a chino.
But we always knew
they were there.
Everywhere.
Nowhere.
.It's a radio scanner  .
The police use the 477.16 channel.
I thought it might help you, son.
How is it, man?
What is this?
It's for my new job ..
Security.
Really? You must tell us
where you work,
for us to go plunder the site.
You know ..
Spim ..
Where you found the smartest
of our group.
E. .
Well .
This is difficult to explain, but ..
.. 've been having some ideas.
What kind of ideas?
Say ..
.. I look around me
and feel that someone should do something.
Compared to what?
Compared .. things.
In the city.
I do not know, man.
've Been having some crazy ideas.
You have always been weird, man.
Shit, I love this song.
I'll turn up the volume.
You're great, man.
I was talking with Don
He meets a kind
who knows of a party in Lodi.
There must be women. Will you?
I will not go to parties.
I have plans.
. Central to 508, .
respond to the call. .
. Grocery Stephanie, .
425 Main Street, in Vernon. .
Good evening, officer.
- Can I help with anything?
- Stand back, please.
It's just a criminal or is there more?
Thanks,
but we have everything under control.
Go to the store or go home.
. The first suspect is arrested. .
. The second suspect is still .
free. .
.-  The suspect is a black man ..
- Come here!
824, need support.
Not in this car.
Are you kidding or what?
Hands behind your back.
They arrested me for starting the car?
No, hold up
for being an asshole.
Is that a crime?
What is the police code for this?
And to be tattooed on their forehead?
Can you give us a few seconds;
please?
Thanks.
I think he can not
deal with the stress of this job.
- I on the other side ..
- Stop! Shut up.
I see what you are
going, Adam.
You helped us to hold
a very dangerous predator.
And you became excited.
I understand that.
But that does not make you
a professional law.
That's what makes.
So give me one of those.
It is dangerous and illegal to walk around
chasing criminals.
I am willing to forget this
If you promise
do not you put the laps
in the affairs of the police.
I appreciate what you're doing,
but the city is small.
We do the trick.
- Can I go?
- Yes, you can go.
- What the ..?
- Damn!
What are you doing here?
We are your friends, remember?
Let the house of Don Get dressed.
The car is on, you have 5 minutes.
You can not refuse.
Coming with us.
Anda.
Shit! How is it, guys?
Where have you been, bro?
I've been there.
I know, do not you walk with us,
but you walk around.
- I do not want to know of your friends?
- You started without me?
What the hell are you doing?
Adam told me about a club
in Jersey City ..
How do I look?
.You okay,
taking that shirt  gay .
.- What about the shirt?
- It's the shirt more  gay . I've seen.
.The two types is less  fornicate gay .
this shirt!
Guilt is the mother of Don,
it was she who bought ma.
- We went to school or what?
- Yes, taking the cocaine.
Who you got it? The Vic?
Someone told me?
Look, it's the "G Squad"!
Nice shirt, Greek. Bet
that engages many guys with that
They brought their wallets, their pussies?
No.
No, I'll go crazy.
- No!
- Do not!
Try it.
Vic, you get yourself a bit?
Sure.
Try before you buy.
- I do not want.
- This is it.
- Come on, man! You do lose.
- Pressure from friends ..
Do not be a woman
what is your?
Do not touch it. If you can not
to fornicate, do not want.
Good thing you never do.
.What's your excuse,  cowboy .?
Be a man.
Walk to train.
For the Paralympic Games?
No, just kidding.
It is obvious that you exercise.
How much lift?
110? 130 pounds?
Just trying to help you, dude.
Do not be ashamed, we are only
two men talking about bench press.
.Thus, get you steroids.
Andro, The Clear. .
Get you depressed,
if you have fear of injecting.
You like porn?
I know you love to hit one.
He's laughing.
I got sick shit bro.
I have a Cuban
to nurse a zebra.
What?
I'm kidding, it's a horse
painted zebra.
What is yours, mine?
That is $ 80.
Calm down.
He is cool, Vic.
Fuck you, do not tell me
to relax.
It is I who decide who is cool.
Come on, Vic, was an accident.
.- So are you, papa gyros  . of shit!
- Calm down!
Shut up, motherfucker!
- Vic, we're friends.
- Fuck, this is business.
Pay me $ 80 now!
Now!
Not having to go ask
at your mothers.
Tell her that spilled
cocaine throughout.
Now!
Okay. My God, Vic,
speaks softly.
Shit!
Don 't be clever with me.
My God!
- Where you going?
- Let him go.
. My father was right, .
this city is full of cockroaches. .
. But Vic was more than a cockroach, .
. he was a cancer. .
. consume this city. .
. He went from Manhattan to Brooklyn, .
returned to the Bronx. .
. stretch of line. .
. would pick the 7 to Queens .
or J to Bed Stuy and Brownsville. .
.The worst neighborhoods  .
to remember me. .
. Night after night, .
this became my routine. .
Sir, sir!
I think you missed
your stop.
Die, motherfucker!
You have to be prepared
for anything.
Got your mail here.
Not finished your story.
Why you out of school?
Apparently they have
something called "rules."
- I think I broke them.
- Hellion.
- Have you ever thought you reapply?
- No.
I was not done for the university.
Not everyone can be doctors,
lawyers, social workers.
Some people have to do
the dirty work.
This is a total coward.
I wish I could stay in school.
- How so?
- I'll stop for a few semesters.
My father ..
My dad needs me at home.
And he was able to ask you this?
He is my father.
Do not want to deal with it,
but I have to do.
My God, how old are you?
.How long does it take to put
a wonton . on a plate?
Let me help you.
Yeah, right. There should be laws
against people like you.
First Law, out of my way!
Second law, learn English. Say:
"The Vic makes my nipples
Yellow hard. "Can you?
What made you decide to go
the funeral of my aunt?
I was the last person
with whom she spoke.
What did she say?
She said ..
"Thank you, Adam."
You were there when my aunt died
and two days later you got
the guy who attacked me.
It's a great coincidence, is not it?
Yes, maybe I should give chance.
No, I think that was
destined to happen.
Be right back.
- Where you going?
- Search for the duck sauce.
- Sorry, I need sauce.
- Take, dear, they do more.
What? She is with you?
- Hello, my name is Vic.
- I'm Mona.
Are you?
You're going to the movies?
It's just that I have everything on DVD,
with good quality.
- Good. Thanks.
- Whatever.
- I go to the bathroom.
- It's back there, baby, on the left.
Mona .. Look at that.
It is good to "mona"?
Fuck that this is a chick raped?
Uncle Vic never experienced before.
It recreates the situation?
Well ..
Anyway, I would not put her
where Richard Pope has been.
Nutty bastard.
- Eight dollars? Keep the change.
- Enjoy.
See you, dude.
What a freak!
My God!
Thank you.
- Thanks for dinner.
- It was a pleasure. Thanks for the ride.
My mother needed the car
to go bowling.
Are you 25 years, get a car.
That guy knocked on your door!
Forget it, it was just a touch.
Look, hit the car of my friend
with the door.
We're sorry.
What are you doing?
Save it.
Have you paid the dinner,
not have to pay for petrol.
Ten dollars from 95 normal, please.
Do not fill the tank
with better gasoline.
Adam, what are you doing?
Why?
Has the dirty windshield.
Lazy shit.
They are 36.18 dollars.
- As was said?
- 36.18.
How much?
38.18, has a hearing problem?
No. You have a hearing problem,
clown?
Shit, are you!
Spim, this is Mona.
Mona, this is Spim.
- Never seen you.
- We were at the Chinese Buffet.
What a fine!
I'm still waiting for the 36.18.
Are you charging me gasoline?
This is a bomb,
where people buy gasoline.
You see those prices?
Is the price of gasoline.
Do not talk to me
as if three years.
Okay, I speak as if you had
36.18, as it is you owe.
This is because the other night?
It is because of several things.
You're out, Adam. Do not work,
you have nothing to offer,
why should I risk being fired
only to help you?
What I gain from this?
We have no money.
So you can not leave out of here.
- How much do you owe?
- 36.18.
$ 36 and 18 cents.
He filled the tank?
Sorry that happened.
Borrowed money.
Want to go with dessert?
I am very tired.
You can catch a ride with your mother?
Yes, of course.
See you there.
Great.
. Don, can you confirm a price .
box 2 .
- Here's your change. Thanks.
- Thanks.
CASE CLOSED
Hello, Greek. Want a ride?
- Yes.
- Come on.
Thanks, man. Next time
that you come here, dinner is free.
Agreed.
Do not exit properly out of his pocket.
We no longer know where I live?
You should have turned left.
You know what makes a good cop?
Resources.
You have many resources.
Did you know that TJ Buck works
the Directorate General for Traffic?
Good for him.
Where are we going?
With that then I'm off, is not it?
What do you think said Spim
I'm out.
Adam, what the hell are you doing?
My work.
Hello, how are you?
I'm fine. I know you?
- Hello!
- Hello
Your friends want a drink?
We're not friends. Her husband
hit the car from my friend.
- And then freaked out.
- Really?
Are the police or what?
I'm like a cop.
Okay ..
I'm busy.
Back to the car Mom
and go away,
before they get hurt.
I think not.
Do not you think?
- Maybe I can help.
- His tattoos do not scare me.
You bastard!
I'll call the police!
This is what happens when
it is a beast in my town.
You know what, Adam?
I walk.
Tell them, Greek.
Tell others.
I have a function.
I'm not out.
The Greek was the cry of the city.
He had other and they decided
if they wanted to be part of the solution
or part of the problem.
God knows Bickleton
had enough problems.
Hydroponics,
just want organic.
I do not want anything that has to do
with the pharmaceutical industry.
Adam!
Telephone!
Thanks for coming with me.
Okay.
Do not want to return for trial.
The idea of ??returning to see his face
makes me sick.
Do not worry,
I'll be there with you.
Sometimes I do not believe
that this happened to me.
You know?
It seems so distant and vague,
who could swear
it was just a dream.
A dream ..
.. very realistic.
And then I become the victim.
I'll always be that girl.
Is not that what people
think of you.
Not people like you.
My wallet!
Thief! Get him!
Someone who grabs!
Put the wallet.
It's okay.
I'm a good Samaritan.
Have you got your wallet.
. There are casualties in all wars. .
. war my grandfather, .
. the war my father .
and now, .
. in my war. .
VIGILANTE THE METRO
THIEF KILLS
We have a great country.
Even know how to treat
their heroes.
Gather round.
Seriously, take two more steps.
Why do you look for it?
I have what you want.
Are you afraid that you hurt?
If you wanted to, were already hurt.
I'm here every day.
Okay?
Why do you want to go there?
Because it is less
300 m of school
going to jail five years, Bronco.
Come here.
They need?
- Two bags of grass.
- They are $ 20. It's simple.
Toma.
Go away.
It looks good.
Yes, it is good.
Chaval disappears.
There she is. Hello, dear.
Here, let me see.
I love the equipment.
Take a spin.
Show me that ass.
- You use this for me tonight?
- You know me.
You'll not be able to ride more.
- Are you good?
- How is it, dude?
I thought you wanted to be
with someone your own age for once.
Yes .
Kids, pirem up.
Go do your homework.
Stay in school.
Not owe me money.
No, do not owe you anything.
I'm not asking,
I'm saying.
Not owe me, which is bad for me.
Everyone has a price and a vice.
What do you need? I have detectors
radar, mobile phones ..
Do not smoke weed?
Smoked.
But I never bought it.
Are these?
Well ..
I heard that you like prostitutes.
I know a brothel in Jersey City.
I can get you there.
No thanks.
Okay.
We need to talk.
Yes .
I want you to miss the traffic.
Dude, I'll just stop when you can
herb buy at the supermarket.
I'm serious.
Traffic is not cool,
especially with these kids.
I think that would be of interest to stop.
You know who was my father?
It was the bookies.
He had a client very stupid.
The kind with some 30,000 lost
Betting stupidest ever made.
Nobody told him to bet,
not much to bet,
but how well it was stupid,
continued to bet.
And instead of paying, as a man,
shot my father in the chest nine times.
I saw my father die in the street,
in front of my house.
This also is not right.
These people to fuck off.
And fuck you are you.
I was not going to town ..
.. if this type.
. No problem, no need .
back to town. .
He had unfinished business
here.
Adam, how's it going?
Your friends are there.
Have you made peace?
Where's Vic?
I do not know.
He walks around.
Are you all right?
Question to my children
in 20 years.
Your turn, I have nothing.
I have nothing.
Give me.
Look into it. Shit!
What the hell!
What a nice party!
Come on, guys,
we are friends since childhood.
- I need your help.
- Would you believe that you need help.
See, this is what I have
been doing,
- This clown are you?
- I told you, he passed up!
We should think this is cool?
Listen, I know you like
Vic's,
but it is bad wave,
sells drugs to kids.
He is ruining our city.
Let's take him out tonight.
Okay, I get it.
It was, to do the same.
Useless crap.
Vic!
Who is calling me?
Come outside with me.
- What did you say, dude?
- Come with me out there.
Sorry, honey,
only go out with women.
Are you scared?
Yes, I am afraid to kill you
and spend the rest of his life in jail.
- Clown.
- A chicken shit!
What did you say?
You heard right.
Its a chicken shit!
Okay, let's go.
In my house there.
Go outside.
- Want to bet money?
- This has nothing to do with money.
You want to fight for the title?
Tae kwon do, three years.
Purple Belt.
I was in the best 11 percent.
Back up. Back up.
Get back, damn it!
My God!
.Let's do it,  hippie .
Anda.
Attacks, attacks.
There, there, enough!
Enough! Enough already!
Enough.
They go indoors
or disappear from here.
I'm not kidding, seriously.
Come on.
I spent all this time to ask:
"Why bad things happen
to good people? "
Because we have left.
Idiot!
Shut up!
What are you talking about?
You have mental problems.
What?
You saved the world, hero?
I tell you one thing,
not saved anything.
You think I'm a bad person?
I provide a service.
Let me tell you something,
this city needs me.
Your father needs me.
Then you are out, kid.
Want to save someone?
Save thyself.
Clown!
He's crazy.
He loved this city
was in Kansas,
to be able to see a tornado
that takes everything ahead.
Why?
Not everything is bad.
Tell me something good.
I do not even know.
I could tell you some stories.
Trust me.
You inspire me, Adam.
The way you live the life
one day at a time.
You play with the hand that you leave.
Never get complaints.
Seedlings things about you
you do not like.
You leave behind
This does not take control.
You're stronger than you think.
Stronger than me.
And you're right.
I can not let what happened
control my life.
I was a victim, but ..
.. I'm more than that.
The other day I was thinking,
while writing in my journal,
what people are like plants.
Sometimes catching too much sun,
or too much shade,
or too much rain.
Then they are plucked,
cut
footsteps.
But therein must appear
a gardener.
To fix things.
Even in the worst circumstances
something good can come.
You also inspire me.
Since our first night together.
What is this?
I decided to return to university.
That's great, Adam.
I am very happy for you.
I know you need a flyer.
It will be the biggest party
the university's history.
Sorry, today I'm going to New Jersey.
You'll see family
or girlfriend?
The trial of rape
a friend of mine starts tomorrow.
Next time.
See you soon.
Wait.
Sorry.
I love you, honey.
Daddy loves you very much.
You are my precious angel.
Now you are safe.
. Why bad things happen .
to good people? .
. And when they happen, who will be there .
to correct .
I'll be there. .