HAVE FUN!
Thank you.
Thanks very much and…
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have a friend here tonight…
…who like me, she’s a long way from home.
And if it’s okay with you…
I was wondering if you’d like her
to play one of her songs.
Is that okay? Yeah?
Gretta, will you come up here please.
Chờ tôi một chút.
Just give me a moment.
I think it’d be a really good idea
if you’d come up here…
and sing one of your songs.
I think it’d be a really fucking bad idea.
Gretta, come on. This is New York.
No.
You want to hear it, right?
You’re gonna be amazing.
Hi.
This is a new song
so it might be kind of rough.
It’s for anyone
who’s ever been alone in the city.
♪ SO YOU FIND YOURSELF AT THE SUBWAY. ♪
♪ WITH YOUR WORLD IN A BAG BY YOUR SIDE. ♪
♪ AND ALL AT ONCE, IT SEEMED LIKE A GOOD WAY. ♪
♪ YOU REALIZE, IT’S THE END OF THE LIFE… ♪
♪ FOR WHAT IT’S WORTH. ♪
♪ HERE COMES THE TRAIN UPON THE TRACK. ♪
♪ THERE GOES THE PAIN. IT CUTS TO BLACK. ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY FOR THE LAST ACT ♪
♪ TO TAKE A STEP? ♪
♪ YOU CAN’T TAKE BACK. ♪
♪ DID SHE LOVE YOU? ♪
♪ DID SHE TAKE YOU DOWN? ♪
♪ WAS SHE ON HER KNEES, ♪
♪ WHEN SHE KISSED YOUR CROWN? ♪
♪ TELL ME WHAT YOU FOUND. ♪
♪ SO YOU FIND YOURSELF AT THE SUBWAY. ♪
♪ WITH YOUR WORLD IN A BAG BY YOUR SIDE. ♪
See?
earlier that day…
It’s seven AM. Good Morning, New York…
and welcome to the second hour of Potsy
and Andy in the morning!
Hey Potsy, did you read about the dog?
The Korean restaurant thing?
Oh, I certainly did.
Did you hear about that, Katie?
Fresh prospects, let’s hear it.
What do you got for me?
No, no.
Who’s next on this delightful journey?
No, no, no. No, man.
You can’t! No! You can’t!
It’s shit. It’s shit!
Get fucking out of my car.
Give me anything. A song. A hook.
Anything I can work with..
I’m not asking for much.
That’s something. That’s good.
Until you started to sing!
Where’s mom?
Where’s my daughter?
What do you mean?
Your mom has a deadline.
She asked me to watch you today.
Let’s go.
So where do you want to go?
The Museum of Natural History?
You want to go to the park
and get some ice cream, or what?
Why would I want to do that? I’m not a kid.
What’s that smell?
Oh, that’s gasoline.
I was filling up the car with gasoline…
and I spilled a little on my pant leg.
That isn’t alcohol.
I think I’ve got a meeting here.
You want to wait here
or you want to come with me.
You think you have a meeting?
Do you or not?
Let’s see.
This is fun, right?
When we came into this neighborhood in ’92…
there was nobody here.
It was like a war-zone.
Hookers. Crack.
Now it’s totally gentrified.
I know, Dad.
I’ve had the tour.
Okay, we’re going to go up here.
Just be quiet.
I think it’s a great way
to generate revenue for the company.
Was there bad traffic?
No, traffic was actually pretty good.
I was just passing by.
We were just closing up
about the audio commentary piece.
Yeah, shit idea.
It was a shit idea then.
Still a shit idea. It didn’t age well.
We appreciate your candor.
We had a different view of it here though.
Musicians for the most part
are pretty much…
monosyllabic teenagers
who really don’t have much to say…
and that’s the good ones, right?
So what are we doing here?
The music industry is fine.
It’s always going to be fine.
We always have been fine.
Maybe the kids are right.
Maybe music should be free anyway.
That’s an alarming thing to hear…
the head of a record company say.
What? The truth?
Thanks so much Karen. Let’s talk more.
Yeah, of course.
Great meeting you.
I’m glad we got it all figured out.
The band doing audio commentary
on their own music...
Is so fucking lame, Saul, and you know it.
Ten years ago, man,
you would have shit on that idea.
It’s something. It’s an idea.
It’s something that helps keep the lights on.
It’s something.
We need vision, not gimmicks.
That’s us.
I’ve been following you, Mr. Mulligan.
Down a track on every long shot…
you’ve been bringing in here
for the last five years.
And which one of them has come in.
Which one?
Dan.
See you later, brother Saul.
We need to talk, man.
Come back here.
Don’t you walk away from me.
You can’t do this shit, man.
You can’t pull this shit, dude.
You can’t pull this shit.
Don’t do this here.
I’m going to do it right fucking here.
All right, then let’s do it then!
Let’s go! Cause they know.
These people know...
that they are sitting behind those desks...
because I started
an independent record label.
Above that bar, Saul.
And we changed the way
things are going to be done, man.
Nurture and foster.
Things change. Times change.
People gotta change with them, Dan.
It’s not working.
You gotta go.
I don’t have time for this.
I’ve got my own shit going on, all right?
I’m taking my client list.
I’m out of here, man.
I am fucking out of here.
What are you talking about?
They signed to us.
Don’t bother her.
Jerry McGuire.
Dad, let’s go.
I’m taking my art then. That’s it.
I’m taking the art.
It’s my art. I paid for it.
I bought it. I picked it out.
I got it.
No you don’t.
Okay. Leave it there.
I’m coming back for that.
It’s mine.
All of that’s mine.
Come on, baby.
You want another one?
Ah, I do but I won’t. I mustn’t. I can’t.
How could he fire me
when I set the whole fucking thing up?
Did you?
Don’t you know anything about your father?
Yeah.
I do.
I know what mom says.
What does mom say?
She says you’re a pathetic loser.
She says that affectionately.
What about you?
What do you think?
I don’t really know you
Two years is a long time
in the life of a teenager.
Where’d you learn to talk like that?
My psychiatrist.
Psychiatrist. You have a psychiatrist now.
I do. Mom thought it’d be a good idea.
I was acting strange.
There’s nothing strange about you.
You’re 15-years-old.
You don’t need a fucking psychiatrist.
Believe me, I know.
I know you better than anybody.
Yeah, you sure do, dad.
How old did you say I was?
Did I say you were 15?
I meant you were 14.
Did I say 15?
You got money to pay for these beers?
I’m a kid. I don’t have any money on me!
What happened to your pocket money?
Well, I spent that on condoms.
What? No, no, no, no, no.
Too much information.
You ready?
For what?
That was fun, right? Don’t smile.
It was fun, dad.
Yeah. You had a good time.
We haven’t run like that
since we were little. That was good.
This your daddy.
I’m glad you’re here cause
I was just going to the car...
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
I’m sorry, my bad. Have a great day.
I could have taken that guy.
He still had to make a scene.
Do me a favor, all right?
Don’t tell your mom I lost my job today.
Listen to me.
Thanks for a really normal day, dad.
What?
Hello, everyone.
- Hi
How’s work?
Fine.
You look hungry.
Her teachers are really worried about her.
No girls like her at school.
She is distant.
And the only people
who want to hang out with her...
are older boys who want to fuck her.
Oh really?
And you find that a big surprise...
seeing how you let her
walk out of the house looking like...
like Jodie Foster from “Taxi Driver”?
She dresses the way she wants to.
And any daughter who dresses like that
only wants one thing.
A pimp?
No, Dan. Think about it.
A daddy.
That is fucking bullshit.
She needs some guidance for fucking sake.
Well, guide her. Guide her.
You waltz in here like a fucking clown.
You tell me how to raise my kid.
The kid that you pick up once a month...
and decide you have a fucking conscience about
You know what?
Thirty seconds after you’re gone...
we’ll have totally forgotten
you were ever here.
Thank you.
I thought there was no hope.
I thought there were no answers.
And then I found God.
God may not always be on our time
But he’s on time.
We’re never alone.
Sir?
Go, have a talk with God.
Right, Man. Okay.
I’m gonna have a little talk with God,
all right?
Thank you.
What if he doesn’t answer?
Attention. Due to a signal malfunction
at Jay Street...
the next uptown train
will arrive in 20 minutes.
Give me a bourbon. Hurry up.
What kind of bourbon you want?
I don’t care.
and I was wondering
if it’d be okay if she sang a song.
Is that okay? Yeah? Gretta,
would you come up here please?
Hi.
So, this is a new song
so it might be kind of rough.
It’s for anyone
who’s ever been alone in the city.
♪ SO YOU FIND YOURSELF AT THE SUBWAY ♪
♪ WITH YOUR WORLD IN A BAG BY YOUR SIDE. ♪
♪ AND ALL AT ONCE, IT SEEMED LIKE A GOOD WAY. ♪
♪ YOU REALIZE, IT’S THE END OF THE LINE. ♪
♪ FOR WHAT IT’S WORTH. ♪
♪ HERE COMES THE TRAIN ON THE TRACK ♪
♪ THERE GOES THE PAIN. ♪
♪ IT CUTS TO BLACK. ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY FOR THE LAST ACT ♪
♪ TO TAKE A STEP? ♪
♪ YOU CAN’T TAKE BACK. ♪
♪ TAKING ALL THE PUNCHES YOU COULD TAKE. ♪
♪ TOOK ‘EM ALL, RIGHT ON THE CHIN. ♪
♪ AND NOW THE CAMEL’S BACK IS BREAKING. ♪
♪ AGAIN. ♪
♪ AGAIN, FOR WHAT IT’S WORTH. ♪
♪ HERE COMES THE TRAIN UPON THE TRACK. ♪
♪ AND THERE GOES THE PAIN. ♪
♪ IT CUTS TO BLACK. ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY FOR THE LAST ACT ♪
♪ TO TAKE A STEP ♪
♪ YOU CAN’T TAKE BACK. ♪
♪ DID SHE LOVE YOU? ♪
♪ DID SHE TAKE YOU DOWN? ♪
♪ WAS SHE ON HER KNEES ♪
♪ WHEN SHE KISSED YOUR CROWN? ♪
♪ TELL ME WHAT YOU FOUND. ♪
♪ HERE COMES THE RAIN, SO HOLD YOUR HAT. ♪
♪ AND DON’T PRAY TO GOD ♪
♪ CAUSE HE WON’T TALK BACK. ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY FOR THE LAST ACT ♪
♪ TO TAKE A STEP? ♪
♪ YOU CAN’T TAKE BACK. ♪
♪ BACK. BACK. ♪
♪ SO YOU FIND YOURSELF AT THE SUBWAY. ♪
♪ WITH YOUR WORLD IN A BAG BY YOUR SIDE. ♪
Bravo!
I’m in.
What?
I want to make records with you.
I want to produce you.
I want to sign you.
We’re meant to work together.
Sorry, didn’t you just see
what happened up there?
Yeah, what?
Are you feeling sorry for yourself?
No, I like my music. I mean who cares
if they don’t get it, right?
You just need to work
on your performance a little bit.
I’m not a performer.
I just write songs from time to time.
And are those songs as good as that one?
Are you really an A and R man?
You just look more like a homeless man.
I’ve been out celebrating all week.
And I just signed a band
and we got carried away.
That’s some song you’ve got there.
I promise you it could be a big hit.
Plus you’re beautiful.
Sorry, what does beauty
got to do with anything?
Jesus, you’re tricky aren’t you?
No, I actually just think that
music is about ears not eyes.
And I’m not Judy Garland just off
a Greyhound bus...
looking for stardom, but really, thank you.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
SO BEFORE YOU GO...
ENJOY MY SHOW.
Okay here’s the truth.
I couldn’t have signed you if I wanted to.
Okay.
I didn’t come from a signing tonight.
I haven’t signed anybody in seven years.
My label has completely lost all faith in me.
So why did you give me your card?
Force of habit.
If I look homeless
it’s because I practically am.
I left my home about a year or so ago.
I’m sleeping on a shitty mattress
in some shitty apartment.
And I wasn’t celebrating tonight.
I was drinking my ass off standing on
a subway platform...
ready to kill myself.
And then I heard your song.
Want to get a beer?
Sure.
Yeah, come on.
“Dan Mulligan. Born 1966”
“Headed A&R department at Island Records
for two years.”
“Left to co-found
indie label Distressed Records...
with Harvard classmate, Saul Byron.”
So, you own Distressed Records?
I sold all my interest
due to emotional difficulties.
What emotional difficulties?
I was too emotional. Read on.
“Very active on the hip-hop scene
in New York in the early 90s...
the pair were responsible for discovering...
numerous break-through artists.
on two Grammys as producer.”
“Lives in New York with wife...
music journalist Miriam Hart,
and their daughter.”
What happened to the Grammys?
I pawned them.
You pawned them?
How much did you get for them?
A hundred and twenty five
for the both of them.
Which got me wasted one weekend
a couple months ago.
Were you drunk when you heard my song?
Absolutely, babe.
That’s when the magic happens.
What magic?
I hear things.
You hear things?
Arrangements.
ou need to be drunk for that sort of thing.
You must have been drunk tonight...
because nobody else heard anything.
No, your song’s good. It’s you.
Standing up there like a tomboy.
I don’t mean to be offensive...
but don’t you think that looks a little passé?
Really?
Seriously. We get you a look.
And a killer video.
And you’ll go straight to the top.
I’m thinking Nora Jones.
Singersongwriter thing...
at a piano. Or the Cardigans.
Back in the day
when they first came to America.
Maybe even Debra Harry.
A male band behind you. -- What?
You find that amusing?
No, I’m sorry.
Something went down the wrong way.
No, you were saying?
Me with a cardigan on? Nora Jones?
Babe, who the fuck do you think you are?
What? You gonna stand up on a stage
with a beat-up guitar...
and you think you’re
the new Carole-fucking-King?
No. I just think that an A&R man
telling an artist...
how they should dress
or come across is total bullshit.
People don’t want that.
They want authenticity.
Okay, babe. Authenticity.
Give me the name of one artist...
that you think passes
your authenticity test.
Dylan.
Dylan. That is the most cultivated artist
you could have thought of.
His hair. His sunglasses.
He changes his look every decade.
Randy Newman.
I fucking love Randy Newman.
Okay, you got me on that.
Listen to me.
I am not saying that you can’t be...
a real bona fide motherfucker
in this business.
But you got to do whatever it takes...
and get people in to see your shows...
where the music can start
to do its real work.
Oh my God. What were we even talking about?
You can’t sign me.
And I don’t want to be signed.
That’s right. What’s not to like?
Come on, let’s get out of here.
Ah, shit. You’re gonna.
have to get these beers, though.
It was really nice to meet you.
Where you going?
To sleep. I have a plane to catch tomorrow.
Where?
- Home.
- Why?
Because I’m sick of this city
and I want to go back to Uni.
Oh, come on. No one comes to New York...
and just leaves
without something terrible happening.
What happened to you?
Come on. You can share with me.
I’m no stranger to misery.
Just come to my label
and let me play your demo to my partner.
If it doesn’t work out...
I will personally pay
to change your ticket.
What’s one more day in New York,
for crying out loud?
You’re just probably gonna go home
and mope around anyway.
All right.
I’m gonna go home and think about it.
And, I’ll call you either way tomorrow.
Okay?
Good answer.
-It was very nice to meet you.
- Yes, pleasure.
Pleasure’s mine.
You’ve got my number, right?
Yeah.
-Hi, Dave?
-Yes
Hi, I’m Jill.
I work in hospitality with the label.
Right this way. Thank you, Marco.
Nice to meet you.
I think you’re really gonna like
the apartment.
It’s very high end.
I’m sorry. You’re Dave Kohl.
Yes.
Yeah. I told you guys!
We saw your film the other day.
I so love your songs in it.
Thank you. This is Gretta, my girlfriend.
She writes songs too.
Oh, would you mind taking our photograph?
That’d be so awesome.
Just that button right there.
Yeah, it’s a good one.
You’re gonna have to get used to that,
I’m afraid.
This movie is selling out all over town.
It’s pretty crazy.
- Unbelievable.
- Oh no, it’s real.
All right, here we are.
We hope you like.
Your fridge in here is stocked with food.
There are two sets of keys
on the table in there.
This is your driver’s number
and my cell phone number.
I’ll leave that here.
You’re due at the label later
this afternoon to meet everyone.
And then we’ll take a tour
around the studio.
So, probably want to catch up
on your sleep before then.
I’ll leave you to it. Okay?
Pleased to meet you, Gretta.
This place is a shithole.
Biggest fridge I’ve ever seen.
Oh my God. Come here.
- Hey. Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Should I have come over in a week or two...
and let you settle in first
and get used to everything?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I don’t know
if I could do this without you.
It’s kind of scary.
Am I a wimp for saying that?
Hey, there he is.
Big Dave. What’s up, kid?
Good to see you. Gretta?
Come on in, guys.
Put Dave at the head of the table.
All right. I like it.
You guys meet everyone?
Hi, everybody.
My assistant, Mim. The beautiful Mim.
This is Mildred from Marketing.
Billy there is Social Media
The rest of the gang,
you’ll meet. Spend time with.
So, Gretta you’re gonna play guitar
on a track or two, I hope.
Oh yeah, sure. If Dave wants.
Yeah.
Gretta and I have been writing together
for a couple years now.
Even before the film came along.
So, I would love for us to try
a couple of her songs.
Did you write on the film with him?
No, no.
That’s the sound we’re after is
from the movie, right? Dave?
Of course.
- Oui? Si?
- Yes. Yes!
- Capice?
- Yes
Gretta’s very much apart
of the inspiration behind everything.
She’s not just my girlfriend.
We’re partners almost.
I just wanted to include her.
Just to be completely clear.
I’m just tagging along on this.
I’m really happy to be here.
And happy to accompany Dave
on a couple of tracks.
How sweet is this girl? I love that.
How great are these guys? I love them.
Yeah, I’m going on tour with the band.
“Rolling Stone.”
Yeah. Thank you so much.
It was great talking to you. Thanks.
What’s that?
That’s matcha tea.
Matcha tea?
It’s got like four million antioxidants in it.
Oh my God, it tastes like piss.
I like it.
The samurais used to drink it
before they went into battle.
You’re not a samurai. You’re a songwriter.
Well, I’m kind of like a samurai.
Are you?
I’m gonna give these to the guys.
Oh, hey. We gotta go to LA
for a week on Monday.
We’re going to LA?
No. Sorry.
It’s just with some of the label guys.
They have an office out there.
They want me to meet
this video director guy.
But, in the meantime, I’d really like you
to listen to this. So, yes?
Yes, I’m sorry. I’ll deliver coffee.
Hey guys, can we do this again, please?
Take two. And rolling.
♪ IS EVERYTHING JUST RIGHT? ♪
♪ DON’T WANT YOU THINKING’ ♪
♪ THAT I’M IN A HURRY. ♪
♪ I WANT TO STAY YOUR FRIEND ♪
♪ BUT I HAD THIS VISION ♪
♪ AND IT’S GOT ME WORRIED. ♪
♪ CAUSE EVERYONE WANTS SOMEONE. ♪
♪ THAT’S ONE CLICHÉ THAT’S TRUE. ♪
♪ THE SAD TRUTH’S I WANT NO ONE... ♪
♪ UNLESS THAT SOMEONE’S YOU. ♪
♪ AND LOOKS LIKE YOU. FEELS LIKE YOU. ♪
♪ SMILES LIKE YOU. ♪
♪ I WANT SOMEONE JUST LIKE YOU. ♪
♪ THROUGH AND THROUGH OR I’M FOREVER BLUE. ♪
♪ CAUSE THERE’S NO ONE ELSE LIKE... ♪
Thank you.
Look at you!
He has the studio for three months.
And then we go on tour.
So I think we’re staying for six?
This is unbelievable.
You’re total rock stars.
Which studio is he working with?
Electric Lady?
Oh fuck off.
It’s really cool, isn’t it?
Are you serious?
So this is me.
Oh, this is lovely.
Yeah, it’s like that old joke.
You put the key in the door,
you break a window.
My God, look at all this stuff.
Yeah a lot of the studios are upgrading.
So practically giving stuff away.
I can record an album here soon.
Well, that’d be cool.
Look at you, you’ve got CDs.
Yeah. I just phased out all my cassettes.
Sit down.
How retro of you.
I have whiskey. Or water.
Whiskey, please!
Of course you will.
Look what you’ve got.
People are going crazy for that here.
When I play a show and the people know...
I went to college in Bristol...
the first thing they ask is
if I know your boyfriend.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I’m becoming “Dave Kohl’s girlfriend”
back home.
I’m like, “Hello, we used to be a team.
What happened?”
Oh, you know what they say.
Get your songs in a movie.
So, this is me. This is where I’ve been
for God knows how long.
I love it.
Do you?
Did you see the bed?
I made that bed. That bed is mine.
That’s very impressive.
How’d you get up there?
I vault.
You vault? With a pole?
No, no pole. I do it in one straight...
one straight luge.
Unless I’m drunk. In which case.
It’s off on a dismount.
It’s the back I like.
It’s like he’s holding a guitar.
But he wants you to think it’s his penis.
He’s saying, “Look, it’s a guitar.
But it’s not.
This is the actual size of my penis.”
Why, no?
I am gonna shoot this
because you have to play that...
exactly the way you just played it.
Okay, you play the guitar.
Because I can’t do that
when that thing’s on.
It’s in G.
- I know G.
- I don’t like that.
It doesn’t matter. And you know what?
You have to get over this.
This is an exercise.
Yes. Ready?
Slower.
♪ PLEASE, DON’T SEE. ♪
♪ JUST A GIRL CAUGHT UP
IN DREAMS AND FANTASIES. ♪
♪ PLEASE SEE ME. ♪
♪ REACHING OUT FOR SOMEONE I CAN SEE. ♪
♪ TAKE MY HAND. ♪
♪ LET’S SEE WHERE WE WAKE UP TOMORROW. ♪
♪ BEST LAID PLANS. ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I’M JUST A ONE- NIGHT-STAND. ♪
♪ I’LL BE DAMNED. ♪
♪ CUPID’S DEMANDING BACK HIS ARROWS. ♪
♪ SO LET’S GET DRUNK ON OUR TEARS. ♪
♪ AND GOD, TELL US THE REASON... ♪
♪ YOUTH IS WASTED ON THE YOUNG. ♪
♪ IT’S HUNTING SEASON, ♪
♪ AND THIS LAMB IS ON THE RUN. ♪
♪ WE’RE SEARCHING FOR MEANING. ♪
♪ BUT ALL WE ARE... LOST STARS. ♪
♪ TRYING TO LIGHT UP THE DARK ♪
Done.
What’d you think?
What do I think?
I think I’m angry. I think I’m mad at you
because it’s so good...
that I hate you a little bit.
And is it… is it It’s about me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Really?
Yeah. What’s it called?
I don’t know...
Lost Stars?
You like it?
I don’t like it. I think it’s… I love it.
And I think it’s incredible.
And is it… is it It’s about me.
Or, it’s not about
your other boyfriend, right?
I don’t know if it’s about you
but it’s definitely for you.
I’ll take it.
It is actually your Christmas present...
cause I can’t afford
to buy you another one...
so Happy Christmas.
This is the only Christmas present I want.
Happy Christmas.
Thank you very much.
I love you.
Turn it off. Turn it off.
I missed you.
What did you do?
Nothing, really.
I just kind of hung around here.
And I went to some botanical gardens.
It was very lovely.
It was good.
I wrote a new song.
- Did you?
- Yeah.
I was inspired in LA. Want to hear it?
Wow. Yeah.
- Would you be interested in that?
- I would be very interested.
I’ve got it right here.
How exciting.
♪ I DON’T KNOW IF I’M THE FOOL ♪
♪ WHO’S GETTING THIS ALL WRONG. ♪
♪ AND THAT’S THE DREAM ♪
♪ TO SING THE PERFECT GIRL ♪
♪ THE PERFECT SONG. ♪
♪ ALL I KNOW IS I CAN’T KEEP ON ♪
♪ WEARING THIS DISGUISE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE THAT SEES ♪
♪ WORTH REAL IN MY EYES. ♪
♪ YOU TAKE ME TO ANOTHER SPACE AND TIME. ♪
♪ YOU TAKE ME TO A HIGHER PLACE. ♪
♪ SO I’M ABOUT TO GET OUT OF THE RACE. ♪
♪ I DON’T MIND. ♪
♪ YOU OUGHT TO KNOW THAT EVERY... ♪
♪ THERE’S NOTHING IF I DON’T HAVE YOU. ♪
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You’re like a fucking mind reader.
Who is it for?
Mim.
Mim from the label, Mim?
Mim who we met one month ago. Mim?
Yeah.
Was she in LA with you?
I don’t know what to say.
It just happened.
Maybe it’ll go away.
Maybe it’ll fade. I
I have to see it through.
Do you want to put your head
on this end or this end?
Do you want a tea?
I don’t remember if you take sugar or...
I’m gonna wing it. I’ll wing it.
Please won’t you come out with me tonight?
I’m gonna play some songs down
at this open mic night.
Why don’t you come with me?
Cause I hate your fucking songs.
I think we both know that isn’t true.
Sorry, I didn’t... No, I love your songs.
I’m paying fucking horrendous right now...
which is exactly why I need to go home.
That’s exactly
why you need to come with me.
Come on. I insist.
Pick that up & come with me.
You’re coming. I’m not leaving you here.
Come back,
I’ll find your fucking head in the oven.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
I have a friend here tonight.
And if it’s okay with you,
I was wondering...
if you’d like her to come up here
and play one of her songs.
Is that okay? Yeah?
Gretta would you come up here please.
Hello.
Hey.
Were you serious last night
about signing me?
Who is this?
Really?
I’m joking. Yeah, I was serious.
I have all my suits here.
Would you get me a nice suit
and make me look nice, princess.
I heard a song last night
and I’m telling you...
it’s exactly what that shit ass
record label needs right now.
You can’t just barge in here.
You can’t come in here like this.
Why?
Because that’s our arrangement.
What you got somebody here?
That’s not the point.
We have an arrangement.
Hello!
Stop that.
Stray man! Any stray man!
Don’t worry about me.
It’s just her husband taking a shower
You can continue fucking my wife.
That’s not funny.
Hey, I’m sorry.
If I did, you’d be the first I’d tell.
So you’re not.
Get you a shirt and a...
No razor.
You want to come in?
You want to sexy time?
No.
Ready?
So where are we going mister A and R man?
We’re going to my partner
to play him your music.
You got your demo?
No.
You don’t have a demo?
Do you have My Space or Facebook?
My Space? No, I don’t.
I told you.
I write songs from time to time.
Well, what do you write them for?
What do you mean what for? For my pleasure.
For my cat.
Oh, really? Does he like them?
She. Yes, she seems to.
How do you know?
Because she purrs.
Maybe she’s booing.
No, she purrs at Leonard Cohen too.
She has very good taste.
Maybe she’s fucking with you.
Can we stop talking about cats now?
Okay.
Fuck it. Let’s do this
the old-fashioned way.
♪ SO FIND YOURSELF AT THE SUBWAY. ♪
♪ WITH YOUR WORLD IN A BAG BY YOUR SIDE. ♪
Thank you, Gretta. Thanks for coming in.
I’m just going to take a moment
to talk with Dan for a minute.
Thank you.
I’m not into it.
It’s a little undercooked for me.
She seems to have kind of
an attitude problem and...
What are you looking for man?
You want some little teenaged pop star....
whose mom’s been raising
since two years old for stardom.
No, that’s not what I’m looking for,
but if you know someone...
Just give me the money to make the demo.
I’ll take her into the studio.
Get a hot shit producer.
Get a couple of session musicians,
dial the thing out...
and then you can hear what I’m hearing.
And then you can tell me to fuck myself.
People send us their demos.
It’s not the other way around.
We don’t make demos.
We’re prospectors man. We’re investors.
We’re digging for gold.
Make a tape and we’ll get back to you.
That’s the best I can do right now, bro.
So, I’ve been thinking.
Why do we even need
to rent a fucking studio?
Because you need a desk,
a live room and sound proofing.
Laptop. Pro Tools.
A couple of dynamic mics.
And the city is our fucking live room.
You mean record outside?
- That’s right.
- Like where?
Everywhere.
Fuck him.
We don’t need a demo.
Let’s record an album.
Every song we do in a different location.
All over New York City.
And we do it through the summer.
And it becomes this tribute to
this beautiful, God damn crazy...
fractured mess of a city. New York.
Okay.
Under the bridge on the lower east side.
Top of the Empire State building.
On rowing boats in the lake
in Central Park.
Chinatown.
Cathedral of Saint John the Divine
In the subway. Fucking Harlem. Everywhere.
So what happens if it starts raining.
Whatever happens, we record it.
If we get arrested?
Keep rolling! It’ll be beautiful.
You like it?
What do you think? It’s good.
Will you produce it?
Me?
Yeah.
I haven’t produced in a long time.
We’ll get somebody young to produce it.
No, but I want you to do it.
Why?
Because I do.
I give you strings,
but we definitely need piano.
Then with the guitars underneath.
Got it. I love it.
- Done.
The world’s first Jag mobile recording studio.
It’s done.
It’s bloody genius it is.
Where do you want to go?
We need musicians.
Terminally, miserably bored musicians.
After that I think...
then you bring in the violin and cello.
First cello then violin.
When we get into that lead guitar thing...
I want it to become
a whole different kind of sound.
This is Malcolm.
Malcolm is a child prodigy.
He’s been playing violin
since he was five years old.
I technically started when I was four.
Four.
And this is his older sister, Rachel.
She’s at the Manhattan School of Music
on a full scholarship.
Top of her class cellist.
That’s amazing.
So here’s the deal.
I can’t afford to pay you up front.
So I want to offer you
a legitimate back end deal.
Sound good?
Yeah, as long as it’s not fucking Vivaldi.
It’s not fucking Vivaldi.
It’s great. No, no, no. It’s great.
Definitely need piano.
Like fill in the guitar underneath.
You got it. I love it.
Steve, beautiful.
Zach. What’s going on?
I quit.
Good luck girls.
Keep in touch.
When we get into that lead guitar thing.
I want it to become just
a whole different kind of sound.
I want it to be punk meets pop.
And have some fun.
Ah, he’s home.
Dano, what’s up, man?
Troublegum, my brother.
My troubles are over.
What say you give me some love, man
This is it! Gangsta paradise.
I’m glad to see you.
Thanks to you.
Give me a hug. I don’t know you
That’s Gretta.
Great singer and songwriter.
Let’s get another one.
Where have you been?
It’s been two or years.
I don’t appreciate this shit.
Been on the down low a little bit.
Doing this. Doing that.
Waiting for the next move.
Anticipating the next groove.
I know you got
a lot of shit to prove. Right?
Been on the underground,
looking for that new sound.
We aint fucking around.
Cause if it ain’t right then it’s wrong.
And the road is long,
and you’re only as strong
as your next move.
You feel that?
That’s pretty much it.
Damn. That was like
some paranormal activity.
You know me.
I’m just so happy to see you, man
Yo! Fat Jimmy did you get that down.
Yeah, I got it.
Cause that was exceptionally good.
Hold my hand, baby. Come on.
How can I help you, brother?
An outdoor album! That’s fucking crazy.
I wish I could have thought of that.
What do you want me to do?
I need musicians.
I need a base player and a drummer.
I got plenty of musicians.
The problem is we can’t pay them.
Fuck it. I’ll pay them.
Why?
What do you mean “why?” For him.
Of course.
Come on. Get your sexy self in the pool.
I will kill you.
She’s English. She’s a little uptight.
Good luck on the album, Gretta.
Thank you.
Everything you see around here.
This crib. These cars.
They’re because of him.
I don’t ever forget that.
I get it.
No, no, no.
You can’t know.
A guy like that falls on his luck
for a couple of years.
People lose sight of who he is.
And they don’t treat him with the respect.
He deserves.
Anything he’s saying is bullshit.
Anything you need, okay?
I love you, man. Thank you.
I like her.
Are you serious? Are you listening to this?
We’re gonna use it. It’s gonna be genius.
You’re a genius. I don’t have any fear.
You don’t hear what I hear.
You’re gonna make it real. I love it.
Got it?
- Those kids are gonna be all over this track.
- What do you mean?
Take this.
Little children. Yo! Yo! Yo!
Let me see this for a second.
I’m shooting a song down here...
and I need you guys to be quiet
for five minutes.
No way, man.
I’ll pay you.
- How much?
- A buck each.
Hey, you’re funny. Five dollars.
Five bucks for all of you guys.
Okay. Two bucks ! Two bucks each.
No!
All right. Five bucks each.
Bring us five bucks and five lollipops.
One for each of us.
Throw in a box of cigarettes and lighter.
I’ll give you one cigarette for each of you
to smoke and you share it.
And I’ll give you a pack of matches.
All right?
Yes.
Can you sing?
♪ WHEN YOU WERE ASLEEP AND I WAS OUT WALKING. ♪
♪ THE VOICES STARTED TO SPEAK. ♪
♪ AND THEY WOULDN’T STOP TALKING. ♪
♪ THERE WERE SIGNS ALL AROUND. ♪
♪ IT REALLY GOT MY MIND RACING. ♪
♪ YOU WERE RIGHT ALL ALONG. ♪
♪ SOMETHING’S GOTTA CHANGE ♪
♪ HOLD ON. ♪
♪ HOLD ON. THEY’RE NOT FOR ME. ♪
♪ CAUSE EVERYTHING’S COMING UP ROSES. ♪
♪ ROSES. ♪
♪ NOW WE’RE BACK ON THE STREET. ♪
♪ FOR A SONG THAT’S WORTH SINGING... ♪
♪ THE BLOODY NOSE OF DEFEAT. ♪
♪ WHY ARE YOUR VICTORY BELLS RINGING? ♪
♪ OH LIFE’S TURNED AROUND. ♪
♪ FOR THIS THING YOU KEEP CHASING. ♪
♪ YOU WERE RIGHT ALL ALONG. ♪
♪ BUT IT’S ME WHO’S GOT TO CHANGE. ♪
♪ HOLD ON. ♪
♪ HOLD ON. THEY’RE NOT FOR ME. ♪
♪ CAUSE EVERYTHING’S COMING UP ROSES. ♪
♪ HOLD ON, HOLD ON. ♪
Yes! Yes! That was it.
Yes! It’s gonna work!.
Oh my God! Is that the Empire State?
Yeah, right here.
Get up here. Get that.
It’s really good.
It’s great.
The wind’s good, right?
It’s not too loud. It’s good
And we can look into people’s windows
which is always fun.
You want to come with me to get Violet.
Is that okay?
Yeah. Come on.
My brother. There you go.
Thank you very much.
That’s her.
This is Gretta. She’s the song writer
I was telling you about.
My daughter, Violet.
How are you doing?
So who was the cute guy?
The one in the blue shirt.
Greg. You noticed him?
Sure. Who wouldn’t? He’s gorgeous.
He’s totally out of our league.
He’s out of your league?
He didn’t look out of your league.
Ignore him.
How can you get someone to notice
you’re ignoring them...
if they’re ignoring you?
He’s not ignoring you. You’re beautiful.
He knows you’re there.
He’s just hedging his bets.
You have to be sure
that you actually like him.
That he’s not just the guy in school
to be seen with.
No, I do really like him.
Well, then, you have to find a way
to get him to ask you out.
Yes, but how?
Well, for starters, stop dressing
like you’re totally easy!
I thought this was sort of sexy.
It’s American Apparel.
It is sort of sexy. It’s very, very sexy.
But it doesn’t leave much
to the imagination. You know?
I guess.
You want to go shopping.
I do.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay, good.
We’re going shopping.
- Thank you.
Good luck with the rest of your album.
It sounds cool.
Thank you.
You have your key?
Yep.
Hey you should come sing on a track?
I can’t sing.
I can play like a bit of guitar.
Can you? We’re doing one on Thursday.
It will be really simple.
You should come and play.
Can I dad?
I need to contemplate that.
What are you doing? That ain’t cool.
I don’t know if she can play guitar
well enough to play on a track.
I don’t won’t to embarrass her.
What if she can’t play?
Look, it’s going to be easy. Let her do it.
Yeah?
Hey, babe.
Where’s Violet?
Violet?
I was wondering...
You think it would be cool if she came...
and played guitar on a song
I’m recording on Thursday?
She’s terrible on guitar.
She’s not bad.
I think she’ll be okay.
When will she...?
Five o’clock. Will you bring her?
It’s up to you.
I’ll text you the address.
Why don’t you come to?
No way.
Come on. Just come. It’ll be fun.
I want you to come.
I’ll think about it.
- I’ll come, maybe.
- Thank you.
You know it was nice to see you
and Violet today.
It must be hard not seeing her more.
Yeah it’s...
So why don’t you?
She obviously really needs
her father around.
What are you
the fucking Social Services now?
No. I mean I’m just saying...
It must have been fairly tense
for you to leave.
Especially seeing as how much
she obviously wants you around.
I’m gonna split.
I’ll see you tomorrow morning.
Fuck, man.
Dan?
Hey, look. I’m sorry.
I’m sorry.
What do you want from me?
What game are you playing?
What does that mean?
I just...
What?
I saw how sweet she was today...
and I just felt sorry
for you being away from that.
That is such a crock of shit .
You were back there judging me.
You think that I left that relationship...
because I’m some sort of selfish,
depressed prick.
Which I am, by the way.
No. I don’t think you’re a selfish,
depressed prick.
I think you’ve let your troubles get in
the way of your entire life.
Oh, babe. You’re really showing
your age right now.
You have no idea what happens
between two people...
after 18 years of marriage.
And because you’re willing
to hang around for some asshole...
after he totally betrayed you,
that’s your business.
Oh no. I’m sorry. You’re right.
I put a lot of time and effort
into that relationship. And no!
I’m not walking away just because of
a bump in the road!
Bump in the road?
I left that relationship cause
I was having a nervous breakdown.
And she was out there
fucking some other guy...
planning how she was gonna start
a whole new life with him...
when I was here taking care of my kid!
You have no fucking clue
what you’re talking about!
You know nothing!
She goes a year up to work on a junket.
And she ends up meeting
and falling in love with this singer.
Bang. Boom. Thunder, lightning. Fireworks.
The whole bit.
And the arrangement was that
they were gonna come back...
and tell their partners that
they had fallen in love...
and they’re gonna spend
the rest of their lives together.
And so I go to the airport
to pick her up...
and she just comes out with it first off.
Whole story.
Then next day her bags are all packed...
and we’re telling Violet
what’s going to happen.
So what did happen?
He choked. He got on the airplane.
Went back to his life.
Turned his phone off
and she never heard from him again.
I move into another bedroom.
She’s waiting around for a phone call
that never comes.
And I turn into a...
I lose my shit a little bit.
So sorry.
No.
Maybe people in the music industry don’t...
just don’t make good life partners.
Or fathers.
Yeah. It certainly looks that way.
I didn’t mean about the father’s bit.
You make a very good father.
Yeah, right.
Maybe just not a good partner.
What is that?
This? That’s a splitter.
For two headphones go into one input.
It’s actually from my first date
with Miriam.
It is?
Where’d you meet?
We walked all over the city,
listening to her CD player.
I don’t think we said
more than two words...
to each other the whole night.
That was New Year’s Eve
and we were married two months later.
That’s lovely.
What kind of music you got on your phone?
I’m not giving you access
to my music library. I’m really not.
There’s a lot of embarrassing,
very guilty pleasures in there.
Mine too.
You can tell a lot about a person
by what’s on their playlist.
I know you can. That’s what’s worrying me.
So are we gonna do this?
Okay. Let’s do it
This is a really good choice!
Oh yeah.
Genius. Perfect. Right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh no! I forgot the words!
Okay! Okay, we’ve got to dance.
What?
We’ve got to dance!
- Okay, we’ve got to dance.
- We’ve gotta dance!
This way.
I’m quite frightened cause
you might find this cheesy...
but it is one of my favorite songs
from one of my favorite films.
Are you ready?
It’s good, right?
That’s what I love about music.
What?
One of the most banal scenes
is suddenly invested...
with so much meaning.
All these banalities.
They’re suddenly turned into these...
these beautiful, effervescent pearls.
From music.
I’ve gotta say,
as I’ve gotten older these pearls...
are just becoming
increasingly more and more rare to me.
More string than pearls?
You’ve got to travel over a lot
more string to get to the pearls.
This moment is a pearl, Gretta.
It sort of is, isn’t it?
All of this has been a pearl.
Hey guys!
Hi.
Hello Steve.
Come on and check it out.
Your boyfriend just won a Music Gong.
No way.
You won’t believe it.
He’s done something to his face.
Wow. Thank you so much.
I’m a bit taken aback by this.
This is incredible.
It just proves that a guy from nowhere...
can actually make it
if he follows his dreams.
I’ve been practicing this speech...
into a shampoo bottle
in the shower my entire life.
Gosh. Thank you.
Nice beard, you fucking loser.
What dreams?
We never had those dreams.
I don’t remember those dreams.
How do you know?
Because, I know him.
Maybe they were private dreams.
Maybe he just never told you about them.
Who was I living
with for the last five years?
Baby, you’ve been living with a rock star.
Only he didn’t know it.
It didn’t matter.
But now that he does,
I’ve gotta tell you...
these people get married to it.
They fall in love with the music.
They fall in love with the lights.
They fall in love with the road.
The chicks. All that shit.
And no matter how hard he tries...
he’s never gonna be able
to make a woman happy.
See you in the morning.
See you.
He just looks a dick.
Why would he do that?
I don’t know. Well why would anyone?
I’ll tell you why he did it.
Cause he wants to look like
the guy who doesn’t realize it.
“Oh! I’ve grown a beard!”
“I was so busy,
lost inside myself writing music...
I didn’t realize
I’d grown a beard the size of my neck.”
I’m gonna sound quite cheesy over it.
I loved him like a fool.
I don’t think that’s cheesy.
I think that sounds like a phenomenal song.
Does it?
It sounds like a song
and I think it sounds like a song...
that you should write right now.
You should write it down.
Write it down.
Write it down, cause you’re in the zone.
Say, “I’m in the zone.”
I’m in the zone.
Don’t say it like
you’re those posh English girls.
Say it like someone in New York.
Say, “I’m in the fucking zone.”
- Say, “I’m in the fucking zone."
- I’m in the fucking zone.
I’ve gotta write a song.
And I don’t give a shit.”
I’m gonna write a song.
No, actually shut up.
All right. I’m shushing. I’m shushing.
Dialing.
All right, here we go.
Speaker.
Hey, this is Dave Kohl.
I am probably busy doing something awesome...
so leave me a message...
and I probably won’t be able
to get back to you. At all. Ever.
♪ WE TAKE A CHANCE FROM TIME TO TIME... ♪
♪ AND PUT OUR NECKS OUT ON THE LINE. ♪
♪ AND YOU HAVE BROKEN EVERY PROMISE... ♪
♪ THAT WE MADE ♪
♪ AND I HAVE LOVED YOU ANYWAY. ♪
♪ TOOK A FINE TIME TO LEAVE ME ♪
♪ HANGING OUT TO DRY. ♪
♪ UNDERSTAND NOW I’M GRIEVING... ♪
♪ SO DON’T YOU WASTE MY TIME. ♪
♪ CAUSE YOU HAVE TAKEN... ♪
♪ ALL THE WIND OUT FROM MY SAILS ♪
♪ AND I HAVE LOVED YOU JUST THE SAME. ♪
♪ WE FINALLY FIND THIS, THEN YOU’RE GONE ♪
♪ BEEN CHASING RAINBOWS ALL ALONG. ♪
♪ AND YOU HAVE CURSED ME ♪
♪ WHEN THERE’S NO ONE LEFT TO BLAME ♪
♪ AND I HAVE LOVED YOU JUST THE SAME. ♪
♪ AND YOU HAVE BROKEN ♪
♪ EVERY SINGLE FUCKING RULE ♪
♪ AND I HAVE LOVED YOU LIKE A FOOL. ♪
One more?
Hey!
Everybody! This is Miriam.
This is Gretta.
This is my daughter Violet.
Miriam. Thank you.
It’s not too high is it?
It’s not too high for a bass. Exactly.
No one should play bass
unless it’s this high.
You want me to set
your amp or are you good?
Hold up. Hold up. Hold up.
Rachel. At the top,
come in a little more gradually.
Bad Jimmy!
Yo, what’s up?
Come on, man.
All right. I got you.
The police ain’t gonna get you up here.
Let’s hear that bass.
I got you, baby. I got you.
Wait a minute. Do you play bass?
You were out of tune. You are flat.
Because I read on the internet
that you used to play bass.
If we can get Violet
doing some guitar on this?
This should be a family affair.
I’m a producer
cause I don’t play bass, baby.
Yes you are! You gotta do it.
You gotta do it!
All right! All right!
Come in whenever you want. You can wait.
Just keep it simple.
I don’t know if I’m gonna play.
Whatever.
If you feel like it you do it. Okay?
It’s totally cool.
But don’t feel like you have to overdo it…
or prove anything to anybody.
These guys are all, serious...
"Dave Kohl
Voicemail & Missed Call"
Guys? Sorry. Can we take five?
All right. Let’s take five.
Five, not ten.
Hey. I’m back in New York for a gig.
I got your singing message.
I have to see you.
Call me. Please call me.
♪ OH MAYBE YOU DON’T HAVE TO KILL SO KIND, ♪
♪ PRETEND TO EASE MY MIND, ♪
♪ WHEN BABY YOU WON’T. ♪
♪ OH SUGAR, YOU DON’T HAVE TO BE SO SWEET ♪
♪ I KNOW WHO YOU’RE GOING TO MEET ♪
♪ DON’T SAY THAT I DON’T. ♪
♪ SO MAYBE I WON’T LET YOUR MEMORY HAUNT ME ♪
♪ I’LL BE SLEEPWALKING WITH THE LONELY ♪
♪ IF YOU’RE TAKING ME HOME. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF I’M BACK ON MY OWN ♪
♪ GIVING BACK A HEART THAT’S ON LOAN ♪
♪ JUST TELL ME IF YOU WANNA GO HOME. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF YOU WANNA GO HOME. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF I’M BACK ON MY OWN. ♪
♪ GIVING BACK A HEART THAT’S ALONE. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF YOU WANNA GO HOME. ♪
♪ IF YOU’RE TAKING ME HOME. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF I’M BACK ON MY OWN. ♪
♪ GIVING BACK A HEART THAT’S ON LOAN. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF YOU WANNA GO, ♪
♪ WANNA GO, WANNA GO, ♪
♪ CAUSE I’M JUST NOT SURE ♪
♪ HOW TO GET BACK THERE. ♪
♪ "AND I JUST CAN’T BEAR ♪
♪ IF YOU’RE NOT THERE." ♪
♪ IF YOU’RE TAKING ME HOME. ♪
♪ TELL ME IF I’M BACK ON MY OWN. ♪
♪ GIVING BACK A HEART THAT’S ON LOAN. ♪
♪ JUST TELL ME IF YOU WANNA GO HOME. ♪
Turn down that fucking music!
Give us three more minutes!
Oh my God! Oh, Violet!
And now the police! Come on, let’s go.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Thank you. We should have a toast.
Right now.
To your album?
To our album.
Really?
Don’t get too excited.
I’m just trying it out.
Should we toast to that?
Goddamn. How do people drink that?
We’re going to play a game.
I’m going to play a song
that is impossible to not dance to.
I defy you not to dance to this song.
This is good.
You know you want to. You know you want to!
Oh, you know you want to. You do.
Oh! There it is! There it is!
I’m gonna give them a ride home.
- Good night.
Thank you for everything.
No, thank you for everything.
OK asshole, let’s meet.
So how was touring?
Touring was amazing. Grueling. Punishing.
Inspiring.
Did you find yourself?
I don’t know.
Well, you certainly found a beard anyway.
Look at that thing.
- It’s intense.
- It’s big.
Did Mim go with you? On tour?
You just wanna go straight into this then?
- Yeah.
Are you the happiest couple ever?
Or did you...
break up after a month
and she came back to New York on a bus.
It was a train actually.
I’m sorry. I’m being a bitch.
No.
You’re entitled.
So, what’ve you been up to?
HOLD ON.
HOLD ON. THEY’RE NOT FALLING…
God... It’s amazing, Gretta.
Really?
Totally. Ambient sound. The city.
And that’s it? No over-dubs? Nothing?
No, no, no. It’s just the way you hear it.
God, it’s so great.
And they’re really offering you a deal.
Well, I don’t know.
He has to play it to his partner first.
So, we’ll see.
I cannot believe
what he’s done with your songs.
I know. He’s amazing.
You should get him to do your record.
Ah, it’s too late.
I just finished mastering the record in LA.
Yeah, I recorded in various studios
on the road.
Wow. So what’s it called?
“On the Road.”
So it’s kind of like Kerouac.
Yeah.
Yeah it is.
That’s actually a terrible album name.
No.
It worked for him.
No. It’s bad.
I know that you now it’s bad.
No. I’m... I’m…
Would you like to go hear it?
I would love to hear it.
♪ BUT ARE WE ALL LOST STARS ♪
♪ TRYING TO LIGHT UP THE DARK. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I SAW YOU OUT THERE CRYING. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU CALL MY NAME. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU OUT THERE CRYING. ♪
♪ OH, JUST THE SAME. ♪
All right.
What do you think?
I think I need to listen to it again.
No.
No, I want your immediate reaction.
My immediate reaction?
Okay.
I think that you’ve lost the songs
in the production.
Okay, take ”Lost Stars.”
I wrote it as a ballad.
And it sounds like a piece of stadium pop.
Yeah but, I wanted to turn it into a hit.
Why?
Why? What kind of question is that?
You’re the writer.
You get sole writing credit on it, Gretta.
This is huge for you.
Yeah, but you weren’t supposed
to lose the song in it. It’s…
It’s delicate.
I really…
I think you should get it remixed.
Yeah but, everyone loves it
when we do it. It’s amazing.
You have to come see it live.
The reaction to it.
The energy in the room just changes.
Why are you so worried
about what other people think?
It’s our song.
It is, but… Isn’t that what music is about?
Sharing it with people.
No, not that song, Dave.
Okay. Then… Who do we get to remix this?
Mim. Maybe you should get Mim to remix it.
Really? So this is obviously not anything
about the album.
You think?
Don’t become this music biz couple,
you know?
Arguing about our… our albums.
The funny thing about all this...
is that I would throw that fucking record
into the ocean...
if we could just continue
this conversation right now.
This is what I want to talk about. Okay?
And if I could somehow say something
or do anything...
that would undo what I did to us…
Just tell me what it is. Help me.
Would you?
Would you throw it in the ocean?
Would you want me to?
No.
No, I think...
I think everything’s changed.
And I’m…
I’m just finding it a big hard to adjust.
I know.
It makes sense. But we’re just gonna
have to find a way to...
get through this.
Get through this together.
When did you realize that?
When you sang to me on my voicemail.
And I realized that nobody on Earth
in their right mind...
would ever do anything remotely like that.
And that killed me. That crushed me.
You completely won me over.
You know I wasn’t actually trying
to win you over.
I was trying to tell you to “fuck off.”
And I had.
And now, you’ve come back and…
And you’ve opened the whole thing up again.
And I think actually,
I think I’m gonna have to go.
Take that.
I’m gonna go cause it’s all a bit much.
I hear you.
Take your time. I’m not going anywhere.
What? Are you gonna stay on the bench?
Yes. I’m gonna stay...
I’m gonna live on this bench.
Come to The Gramercy. On Saturday. Please.
Just hear the song.
I want you to see
how everyone’s just falling in love...
with what you created...
Please don’t play it like that.
Okay.
Well, look at you. A vision of pure class.
There’s my daughter.
No way.
Is this it?
There you are.
Yeah.
You look great.
Look how cool you are.
Can I keep this? Show all my friends?
That’s what it’s for, babe.
Look at you.
Hilarious.
Why is that hilarious?
I just had no idea you were that talented.
I just didn’t know.
You’re a real guitar player.
You got some talent. Seriously.
What? Do you want me to start a band now?
Yeah! Let’s start a band.
Let’s start a band.
Why not? I’ll record you. I’ll produce you.
I like this idea.
Do you?
Yeah.
You all motivated now?
It’s a family business.
It’s like the Jackson Five.
There you go.
The Mulligan Three.
You coming in?
No. I’m going to go play that for Saul
and see if we can get a deal.
Good luck. Let me know how it goes.
I love you.
I know you do.
Come on. Yeah… So pretty.
Bye!
Thanks for coming in guys.
This is fantastic.
You’ve got a great record.
I missed it on the first listen.
But I don’t want to miss it again.
We’re very glad that you like it.
Well, I reached out
to some of my studio connects in LA
and I was thinking we could get
the first track placed in a film.
Write a film.
There’s also pilot season right now.
Yeah man, we’re not interested in
any of that stuff.
Okay, so then…
What are you interested in?
What are we doing here?
Well, I think Dan needs his job back.
Yeah, sure. What? Take my office.
I don’t care.
Okay. I guess I want to know,
how does this work?
We put the album out. We sell it for…?
Let’s say an album
costs ten dollars a unit.
The artist gets a dollar.
It’s the same in publishing.
It’s a buck for a book.
Oh, I’m just thinking
for this specifically.
I have to get my head around it.
The album doesn’t have
any overhead because we did it.
And then, distribution…
It’s not gonna go in stores.
It’s gonna go online.
And publicity would be…
What? Word of mouth?
So, I think what I’m wondering is...
why do you get nine out of ten
of my dollars?
Gretta, you’re a very smart young woman.
And you’re a determined artist.
You have a wonderful project here.
And with the right team behind you
to push you and guide you...
Maybe hire a hot-shot producer
to remix a couple tracks.
You could have a hit record
and a very long career.
But you know, ultimately that’s up to you.
Ah, you had them. You wound him up.
I know.
It’s amazing
when you’re not actually that interested...
you always win the hand.
Yeah. That’s never really worked out
that well for me.
I found it worked very well.
You’re gonna get a deal.
That asshole is gonna give you a deal.
You might have to compromise a little bit.
Never.
Of course.
Hey, we should do a bunch of these.
What do you mean?
Do you like the European Series?
I like that.
The Paris Tapes. The Prague Sessions.
The Berlin Recordings.
We could go all over Europe by rail.
We could take the whole gang?
Rachel, Malcolm, Steve.
So…
Oh look. I guess I’ll see you in awhile.
Thank you.
Come to the show. Your name is on the list.
Please. Dave.
An Evening with Dave Kohl
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Guitar change.
This next song was actually given to me
by an amazing songwriter...
and an even more amazing woman.
So it’s a very special song.
We’re gonna do her arrangement of it.
So If she’s here… I’m not sure that she is.
I’d love for her to come up
and join us on this one.
There’s a guitar right there, so…
If you’re here, please join us.
It’s a really special song to me.
See your vision of this song through.
♪ PLEASE DON’T SEE ♪
♪ JUST A BOY CAUGHT UP
IN DREAMS AND FANTASY. ♪
♪ PLEASE SEE ME ♪
♪ REACHING OUT FOR SOMEONE I CAN SEE. ♪
♪ TAKE MY HAND.. ♪
♪ LET’S SEE WHERE WE WAKE UP TOMORROW. ♪
♪ BEST LAID PLANS, ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I’M JUST A ONE NIGHT STAND. ♪
♪ I’LL BE DAMNED. ♪
♪ CUPID’S DEMANDING BACK HIS ARROWS. ♪
♪ SO LET’S GET DRUNK ON OUR TEARS ♪
♪ AND GOD, TELL US THE REASON ♪
♪ YOUTH IS WASTED ON THE YOUNG. ♪
♪ IT’S HUNTING SEASON ♪
♪ AND THE LAMBS ARE ON THE RUN ♪
♪ SEARCHING FOR MEANING. ♪
♪ BUT ARE WE ALL LOST STARS ♪
♪ TRYING TO LIGHT UP THE DARK. ♪
♪ WHO ARE WE? ♪
♪ JUST A SPECK OF DUST WITHIN THE GALAXY. ♪
♪ WHO IS ME? ♪
♪ WHEN OUR CAREFUL TURNS INTO REALITY. ♪
♪ DON’T YOU DARE LET OUR BEST MEMORIES ♪
♪ BRING YOU SORROW. ♪
♪ YESTERDAY I SAW A LION KISS A DEER. ♪
♪ TURN THE PAGE ♪
♪ MAYBE WE’LL FIND A BRAND NEW ENDING. ♪
♪ WHERE WE’RE DANCING IN OUR TEARS ♪
♪ AND GOD TELL US THE REASON ♪
♪ YOUTH IS WASTED ON THE YOUNG. ♪
♪ IT’S HUNTING SEASON ♪
♪ AND THE LAMBS ARE ON THE RUN ♪
♪ SEARCHING FOR MEANING. ♪
♪ BUT ARE WE ALL LOST STARS ♪
♪ TRYING TO LIGHT UP THE DARK. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I SAW YOU OUT THERE CRYING. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU CALL MY NAME. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU OUT THERE CRYING. ♪
♪ OH, JUST THE SAME. ♪
♪ GOD AND GIVE US THE REASON ♪
♪ YOUTH IS WASTED ON THE YOUNG. ♪
♪ IT’S HUNTING SEASON ♪
♪ AND THIS LAMB IS ON THE RUN ♪
♪ SEARCHING FOR MEANING. ♪
♪ BUT ARE WE ALL LOST STARS ♪
♪ JUST TRYING TO LIGHT... LIGHT UP THIS DARK ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I SAW YOU OUT THERE CRYING. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU CALL MY NAME. ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU OUT THERE CRYING. ♪
♪ OH, BUT ARE WE ALL LOST STARS ♪
♪ TRYING TO LIGHT UP THE DARK. ♪
Hey.
Where are you going?
Home.
What’s on your mind?
I don’t want your label
to release my album.
Fine.
Fine? Really?
No, because I thought that
you’d be really upset.
No, it’s your album.
So, what do you want to do with it then?
There it is.
That’s the whole album for a dollar.
A buck for a book.
The whole thing. Now, once
this goes out, that’s it. They’re gone.
Yeah.
Are you sure you want to do this?
How about two bucks?
Such a capitalist. No, a buck is fair.
And then we’ll split it evenly
between everyone…
Malcolm and Rachel – everyone! Come on!
Once I press this, that’s it.
I’m going to war with my whole business.
Gretta James – The Great Outdoors
That’s so exciting.
What are you doing?
Calling reinforcements.
Check it out.
I got Troublegum to tweet out the album.
How many followers does he have?
Apparently the entire world.
Just about every living human being.
Mr. Mulligan.
Good morning.
News for you on the inter webs.
Shit!
You didn’t know nothing about this?
- No.
- No?
How many did she sell?
Ten thousand. Today.
Troublegum tweeted about it.
If Troublegum helped her out,
it’s because he liked her.
They’re artists.
You didn’t know nothing about this?
Nothing.
Kind of funny though.
Is it really?
It’s pretty funny, man.
Boo-boo, you know how to pick them.
It’s kind of good.
Sure is. Kind of uppity
Clean out your locker.
See you later.