I can't believe we
gotta do this shit, man.
This thing's been in the
ground three fuckin' months.
- You know what it's gonna smell like?
- Yeah, I know.
Stop bitching and let's just
get this thing outta here.
I remember about 10 years
ago, I had to do the same shit.
I almost died from
the fucking stench.
Oh, God.
Here.
All right. Let's do this.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(ANIMAL HOWLING)
Oh, fuck. I'm gonna
break my neck out here.
- Hey, Danny. How much further?
- Not far... just keep walking.
- What the fuck?
- What is that?
Do you think some kind of animal
or something could have did this?
How the fuck is an animal
gonna dig a hole like that?
Louie, gimme that
flashlight. Carmine.
- What?
- Come here.
Go down and see if
there is anything there.
- Cock.
- Thank you.
Louie, help me out. I'm
not a fucking kangaroo.
(THUD)
There ain't nothing down here.
And I don't smell nothing neither.
Really, Carmine? You don't
smell a rat down there?
(GUNS COCK)
- Big "V" sends his regards.
- Louie! Louie, Louie, Louie!
(DANNY) Let's bury the rat and
just get the fuck outta here.
I don't even know
where the fuck we are.
Why'd we have to come all
the way out here to do this?
We've been burying pricks
like this out here for years.
If these woods could only
talk, we'd all be in the can.
(DISTANT SCREAM)
(METAL CLANKS)
(SCREAMING)
Who's over there?
(GROWLING)
- Danny, look out!
- (GUN CLICKING)
(SCREAMING) Danny, no!
(KNIFE SLICING)
(SCREAMING)
(DANNY GRUNTS)
(SOBBING)
(DANNY SHOUTING)
(KNIFE UNSHEATHS)
(LOUIE GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(KNIFE CLANKING)
(KNIFE SLICING)
That is so pretty,
you're gonna look so hot.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Pull it down, you don't wanna
give away the milk for free.
It'll get so much
lighter with the sun.
You have such a
nice butt, like J.Lo.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Right here. (LAUGHING)
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
(PHONE RINGING)
(RINGING CONTINUES)
- Can somebody pick up the phone?
- Why don't you answer the phone, bitch?
Don't you dare call her bitch.
I'll shove this curling iron right
up your fat fucking ass, bitch.
I'll get the phone.
A Touch of Class, Teresa speaking.
Hold on... Ricardo.
It's for you. He says
that his name is Monty.
Ugh.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Excuse me. Who do you think
you are, calling me at work?
Oh, no, and don't ever call me
again! Yech!  Ay, Dios mio.
- I like this outfit...
- Who's Monty?
Oh, some pig I met online last night.
We were chatting for just 10 minutes
and he expects me to drive
to his place at 1:00 a.m.
I said, "No, you can't
just pick up the phone
"and send for me in the middle of the night.
What do you think I am, Pizza Slut?"
(LAUGHTER)
Mira, I have a picture of the slob.
- Ugh.
- Is it the full Monty?
Yeah, that's the pig.
(LAUGHTER)
He's cute. Should have called
me last night. I deliver.
Listen, honey, unless
your pizza has pepperoni,
don't even bother
heating up your oven.
(LAUGHING)
Come on, Dina. I want
to beat the traffic.
All done. Let me
just get my things.
Where the hell are you two going?
Down the shore for a girls'
weekend of sun and sin.
(LAUGHTER)
Maybe the two of
youse can either drown
or get eaten by a shark and
make it a holiday for all of us.
Heh, or who knows? Maybe we'll find a
beached whale and name her Christy.
Oh, sounds like fun. And while
you're looking for Mr. Right,
Dina can sample all
the Mr. Right Nows.
(LAUGHTER)
You said it, not me.
- Whatever.
- I'm out of here.
I just kidding...
you know you fabulous.
- You look so pretty. You look so good.
- I tell her that every time.
It's like a shelf up here.
They just hold up.
I don't know how she does it.
- I made it!
- Hey!
- Mwah!
- Oh, you're not working today, Gigi.
- You got that right.
Oh, chica, you too? Wait, am
I the only girl not going?
- Next time, we'll invite you, I promise.
- What am I gonna do this weekend?
- Aww.
- I don't know.
Maybe you should ask Monty.
You get out of here,
you... Good-bye.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello, Monty?
Yes, I'll taste your chorizo.
(HORN HONKS)
Come on!
(POUNDING HORN)
Come on, Gigi, let's go!
All right, Dina, she's
coming, she's coming.
Come on, Gigi, we want
to beat the traffic.
Okay, Seaside
Heights, here we come!
Michael, what are you doing here?
I was just driving by, and I saw your
mother drop you off. Where you going?
Not that it's any of your business, but I'm
going down the shore to see the girls.
Well, I might be there too. So
maybe we should all hook up.
That is so not happening, Michael.
I just don't want you going down the
shore with a car full of single girls.
Would you rather I go in
a car full of single guys?
Don't be stupid, Gigi, you know you're
still my girl. Show me a little love.
It's not happening, Michael! Now, go
do something with Tony and Fat Angelo,
- and I'll call you on Monday.
- So it's like that?
- Yeah, Michael, it's exactly like that!
- (DINA) Yeah, it's like that.
- Dina!
- (DINA) What... he's a dick.
- Hey, fuck you, Dina!
Yeah, fuck all youse! You're gonna regret
this day, Gigi. Remember I said that.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Means drop dead!
(DINA) Fuck off, Michael!
- What the fuck, Gigi?
- I don't know.
I don't know what the
fuck I'm doing anymore.
I mean, one minute, I think
I love him, and then the next,
I wanna knock his fucking head
off and throw it in the river.
- Like right now?
- Yes, I think so.
But he really is sweet,
though, don't youse think?
- So are you single or what?
- Yeah, right now, I am.
You don't see no fucking
ring on my finger, do you?
No, but if you really
think that there's a chance
for you and Michael, don't go hooking
up with every guy in New Jersey
just to prove to
yourself you're single.
- (HORN BLARES)
- Fuck you, Dina!
No, no, no, no,
no... I'm with Gigi.
Until you're married, you
do whatever the hell you want
with whoever the hell you want,
whenever the hell you want,
'cause guess what, Teresa?
Life's just too fuckin' short.
Okay... next topic. When are the
girls meeting us down in Seaside?
Uh, Joanne said that she, Candi, and
Val left Brooklyn almost an hour ago,
and that Val's cousin Rosemarie
can't make it till tomorrow night.
So in other words, they could
have stopped for hot dogs.
Or they're banging three
guidos at a turnpike rest stop.
- (LAUGHTER)
- Eww.
(HORN HONKS)
Oh, my God, speak of
the fucking devil.
(ALL WHOOPING)
- Almost fucking killed us.
- Oh, my God.
You should have seen the old man's face
at the toll booth. He was so funny, ha!
- Put your tops back on and follow us.
- Yeah, Jersey Shore!
(ALL WHOOPING)
(CHEERING)
(HORN HONKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Are you sure this is
the right house, Dina?
Yeah, I'm fuckin' sure.
Come on.
Hello? What do you think
you're doing here?
(LATIN ACCENT)
Excuse me? This is our rental.
- What are you doing here?
- Nice try, chonga.
This is our house, so get the hell out.
Take your little rat dog with you.
Who are you calling chonga, bruja?
Don't be scared, Pico.
I won't let her eat you.
I'm calling all of youse chonga. And
I'm calling the owner right now.
You no have to call, okay? He lives right
there, and I just gave him our check.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
We'll see about that. Girls.
(KNOCKING)
(COUGHING)
Well... Hello there, ladies.
I'm Ronnie... what
can I do you for?
Yeah, Ronnie, we spoke
on the phone a month ago
to confirm our reservation for
the house this weekend.
Oh, yeah! Your friend just gave
me a check, so we're cool.
- Romero, right?
- No... Romano.
Dina Romano, you idiot.
Romano. You're not all together?
Uh, give me a minute. Don't
go away... hold on, just wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Here it is. You're Romano.
They're Romero.
♪ Romano, Romero, Romano ♪
You're two different parties.
That explains everything.
Fine... so can you get those
chongas out of our house,
so we can finally
shower and unpack?
I'm afraid I can't do that,
and here's why. You see,
I already gave them the keys, and
then now they take over the house.
That's the law. See, the house
is not mine, it's theirs.
I know it's a little peculiar, but
it's how they do it in Jersey.
Now that every house and hotel are
booked, where are we supposed to go?
Nice going, Ronnie. You
managed to fuck us all.
Hold on... hold on, hold on. Why don't
you guys just stay here with me?
Excuse me?
(SIGHS)
Look, I can find ways of keeping
you girls reasonably...
- entertained.
- (ALL) Ugh!
I'll take that as a no. Or
I'll take it as a maybe.
Their loss. Okay,
pot, it's you and me.
That bitch think she's better than me
just because she has fake tits. Huh!
I don't speak Mexican or Puerto Rican, but
I know they definitely talking about us.
Fuckin' nightmare.
Hold on a second.
I'll be right back.
If that chonga gives me one more look,
I swear, I'm gonna fuck her up.
Who would believe that someone
could screw something up so bad?
- Are you trying to say this is my fault?
- Well, whose fault is it?
(DOG WHIMPERS)
Oh, my God, your little fucking rat
dog just pissed on my fucking leg!
Thanks for telling me. I gotta go
now and disinfect his pee pee.
Oh, my God, you're the best!
Thank you! Thank you!
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
Uh-huh.
Ugh!
- Everybody back in the car.
- Where are we going?
- My Uncle Vito's house.
- Where's that?
About 15 miles west of here.
Do any of youse have a napkin?
Follow us.
Whoo!
Kiss my ass, chonga!
Gnaw on some meat?
Do they even know where we're
going, or are we just lost?
I'll tell you right now, we're
going straight back to Brooklyn
if she thinks we're staying at a
fucking campsite all weekend.
(NEWSCASTER)
Your news for Ocean County.
Human remains were found today in the
Pine Barrens section of New Jersey.
According to detectives, the victims were
alleged members of the Rubino crime family.
Details of how this will affect the upcoming
trial of Big "V" Rubino, coming up.
- Wow.
- (DINA) This ain't no campsite.
Where the hell are we?
We're right at the edge of the
Pine Barrens, that's where we are.
So where's this Uncle Vito?
He's at his home in Staten Island.
If he tries leaving the house,
his ankle bracelet beeps, the cops
come, and he could be put in jail.
So he's under house arrest?
I mean, what did he do?
You know, he's an entrepreneur.
But because he's Italian,
they keep harassing him for every
single thing he does. It's this way.
Oh, wow.
Here we are.
(TERESA)
You can put your stuff down here.
Wow, look at all this stuff.
This has all the Belgian whistles.
You know, Teresa,
I know your uncle,
and I can't ever see him
buying a house like this.
- It was willed to him.
- Willed to him... by who?
Some guy in the entertainment industry
that he used to do business with.
- What happened to him?
- Uh, no one really knows.
But since my uncle has
business in New York and Philly,
he kept this place because it's
located right in the middle.
What about the people
that live around here?
My uncle says they're not really friendly,
unless they're trying to sell you things.
Well, obviously,
they would be jealous,
seeing how they live, and
then seeing all of this.
It's pretty awesome... the only thing
we're missing now is a Jacuzzi.
Hey, even better.
Swimming pool!
(ALL SHRIEK)
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God.
- Awesome!
- (SQUEALING)
Perfect.
(WOMEN SQUEALING)
- Oh, my God.
- (ALL SQUEAL)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Oh, my God.
Not too bad, right?
Wow, you guys, we could
totally go swimming later.
You guys can go.
(CANDI) It's kind of dirty. Should
we call someone to clean it?
Uh, no. I just have to clean the leaves off
with the skimmer and change the filter.
(ALL SHRIEK)
Ew!
- Where did that come from?
- He had to come from the lake.
- (FROG CROAKING)
- Ohh.
Eww!
What lake?
Um, I think it's... that way.
Come on, I'll show you.
Come on, little guy.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
This is not a good idea.
Be free, little guy.
(SCREAMING)
- Saved your life.
- That's not funny!
Teresa can't swim! She has a serious
fear of water, you stupid bitch!
Fuck you, Dina. If you didn't
fuck up the beach house,
we wouldn't be here right
now. I'm sorry, Teresa.
It's okay. Let's just go back
to the house and unpack.
(GASPING)
- You okay?
- Yeah... I'm okay.
Okay, so there's plenty of
rooms. I'll room with Dina.
Gigi with Joanne, and Valerie
and Candi can share a room.
- Uh-uh, I'm not rooming with Candi.
- Why not?
- 'Cause she farts in her sleep.
- I do not.
Yeah, you do.
Okay, I'll stay with Candi, and
Dina can stay with Valerie.
I'll just have to keep
my window open all night.
(LAUGHTER) Knock it off.
Where's my cousin gonna sleep?
Uh, if she shows up,
she can have the couch.
- Good? Fine.
- All right, let's go.
- Whoo!
- Good.
- Come on, my little stinker.
- Oh, stop it.
Uhh! This freaking bag is so...
heavy!
Just be careful. They already
started renovating downstairs.
(BAG THUDDING DOWN
STAIRS, GLASS SHATTERING)
Sorry, Teresa. Was that expensive?
You're not going to unpack?
Ugh, I'm so fucking
tired, I'll do it later.
What's that?
What do you think it is?
I know what it is, but really?
Did you actually think you would
need that thing down the shore...
I mean, you might as well
bring sand to the beach.
Well, I don't leave home
without it, and don't touch it.
Yeah, 'cause I'm just dying
to touch that skuzzy thing.
(SCREAMS)
My name is Edgar.
Would you like to try
some of my sausages?
No, thank you, Edgar.
- Yeah, none of us eat meat.
- Yeah, we're all veterinarians.
All you girls look so pretty
and shiny. Are you all sisters?
I never had sisters. I have
a brother... he's a asshole.
No, we're not sisters, but, um,
it was nice meeting you, Edgar.
So instead of watching hot-looking guys
with washboard stomachs on the beach,
we're gonna hang out with Edgar, the
300-pound axe murderer, instead.
Just because he's big, sloppy, and weird
doesn't make him an axe murderer.
So what are we doing
tonight? I'm getting bored.
I'm not driving all the way back to
the shore in that traffic again.
Fine, Teresa, what do
we do around here?
Well, forget about going to a bar or a
club. Those things don't exist around here.
Mm, there was that sign down the
road for that Jersey Devil tour.
(LAUGHING)
Are you kidding me? Walking around in the
woods, listening to stupid ghost stories.
Well, we can either do
that or stay here all night
while Edgar leers at
us through the windows.
Who knows, maybe
we'll meet some hot guys.
(FLIES BUZZING)
Well... Good evening, ladies.
Would you like to take the,
uh, Jersey Devil tour?
How much for the six of us?
Uh... $7.50 apiece.
Screw that... we want a discount.
Uh, $50 for the six of us.
Fine.
All right, soon as all
your group is here,
we'll have Junior take
you on your tour.
Is it scary?
Scares the tar outta me.
- Great, let's fucking go then.
- Okay, let's go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(NIGHT BIRD CALLING)
Okay, I hope we're all keeping our
eyes open for the Jersey Devil.
What can you tell us about the... creepy
people living in the Pine Barrens,
like cannibals, called Pineys?
(JUNIOR) Well, there are
people that live around here.
Yeah, we heard there are a few dozen Piney
families who are all inbred, illiterate,
and very hostile towards outsiders,
living just about a mile down the road.
Now that's creepy.
- Hey, Junior?
- Mm-hmm?
- Where do you live?
- 'Bout a mile down the road.
Now, believe it or not, the
Jersey Devil was the 13th child
of a woman named Deborah Leeds who
emigrated from London, England
here to the New Jersey
Pine Barrens in the 1700s.
Moving here from London and all,
was she able to learn English?
That's a pretty good question. I'll
have to get back to you on that.
But anyway, during a very
difficult and painful labor,
Mrs. Leeds invoked the devil.
(GASPS)
And when the baby was born,
it immediately grew into
a full-grown winged devil!
(SNARLING AND GROWLING)
And then escaped from the house
out into these Pine Barrens.
Ohh!
- Who keeps hitting my ass?
- No touching.
Ugh... that's disgusting.
There are have been hundreds of Devil
sightings throughout the years.
I think these girls like us.
(ALL CHUCKLING EXCITEDLY)
There are six of
them and three of us,
so you know what that means?
Oh, my God.
This could be the greatest
night of our lives!
Shh... let's try
to keep them scared,
so that they cling on to
us for safety, and then...
- Back to the RV!
- Exactly!
(ALL GIGGLING)
This is gonna be so amazing!
(JUNIOR) ...one in 1909
by Councilman Wheaton,
who heard flapping wings outside
his bedroom window one night,
and then the next morning,
found large, cloven footprints...
in the snow.
Hi. Uh, m-my name is Henry.
Uh, what's yours?
- Joanne.
- Oh, nice to meet you.
Um, are you girls headed
to the Sci-Fi Expo in DC?
Uh, if so, we could
all go together.
- Are you serious?
- Sure, uh...
We even have a DVD
player, a microwave,
and a queen-sized bed.
(JOANNE)
Val, wait until you hear this.
Cool!
I think she's going to get all
her friends to come along also.
(GASPS)
- Try to keep them scared.
- Okay, okay.
Hundreds of people have
heard the Jersey Devil
rampaging through the
woods while shrieking.
(SHRIEKS AND GROWLS)
(ROARING AND GROWLING)
Or making blood-curdling cries.
(HOWLS AND BLABBERS)
Some call it the Leeds Devil.
Some call it the Wozzle Bug.
And others call it the
Hoodle-Doodle Bird.
Either way, no one comes
out here alone at night.
Oh, God, I'm really feeling scared.
I want to get out of here.
What are you worried about?
I feel like we're being watched, and
I'm starting to freak out a little.
Yeah, you guys, I wanna go back.
Why don't you girls give us
your... your email addresses
so we can put it on our phones now?
Sure...
Uh, it's getalife...
- Getalife...
- at...
yougottabefuckingkiddingme.com.
What's with the mixed messages?
I don't know. But it seems like every
girl we meet has the same problem.
(MAN) Help!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Oh, damn!
Oh, my God, somebody
give me their belt!
- I gotta make a tourniquet!
- Oh, my God! Oh!
(GROWLING AND BLABBERING)
(WOMEN SHRIEKING)
(BLABBERING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Welcome to the country, girls.
You kidding me? We're getting
the fuck outta here!
That was so uncalled
for! Let me go!
Come on, don't be
upset. It was all in fun.
F-U-N, fun.
No, it's stupidity.
S-T-U... pidity!
(TERESA) Are you okay, Val?
I want to get outta here.
I don't like being scared.
Let's go.
(MAN BLABBERING)
Hey, later, girls.
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah, that's fucking great, man.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Argh...
Hey, you ready, Gigi?
No... you guys go ahead. Mike's
gonna come pick me up later.
I really need to see him
tonight. I'm sorry.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- Okay, I'll see you tonight.
- Bye.
(DINA) She's ditching us for
that loser again, isn't she?
She seems to love him, so
let her do what she wants.
I don't buy that... I think Michael
just knows how to manipulate Gigi.
He turns her into, like,
his little mental prisoner.
Yeah, kind of like Stockholder
Syndrome or something.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, bitches, you
want some pound cake?
- Oh, yeah, I'll take some.
- I can't even look at that.
(PING, ENGINE STARTS)
- Are you dieting, Val?
- I'm going to.
I just took five laxatives last night to
help get my stomach down for the weekend.
- Oh, my God.
- That really isn't good for you, you know.
Ugh, well, I don't wanna look like a
stuffed sausage all weekend either.
- Sure you don't want some?
- No.
- You're just gonna shit it out anyway.
- No...
I wanna have a six
pack for the yum yums.
- Yum yums.
- Yum yum yums!
It's hot as fucking here.
Daddy!
Wow, a jellyfish!
Don't touch that.
You could get stung
very badly by it.
- Ouchie.
- Yeah, ouchie.
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Ohh!
Oh, my God! That took me
all morning to build!
Well, build it somewhere else. The
thing just made me drop the ball.
Are you kidding me? You have
the entire beach to play on!
Because the people is over there,
and if we play over there,
no one's gonna be able
to see us right there.
So why don't you pick up
all your sand and move it?
Over there! You feeling me?
And take your faggot-ass
pail and shovel with you.
(SPLAT)
(HIGH-PITCHED LAUGH)
Oww...
Ouchie.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
- What you looking at?
- (LAUGHTER)
There's no fucking parking.
Well, if you didn't make us late, we
would have been here two hours ago.
Fuck you, Joanne.
- Can you both please stop it now?
- Stay the fuck outta this, Valerie.
- Yeah, shut the fuck up, Valerie.
- Don't tell her to shut the fuck up.
- Who the fuck are you?
- Bunch of pains in the asses.
All right, guys, calm down.
We're already here.
Ah, there's a space.
Give me the handicapped pass in the
glove compartment, just in case.
- We're not disabled.
- Just limp a little when you walk out.
- Ready?
- Whoo!
Here we are.
(CRUNCH) Whoo!
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
I was dying for one
of these corndogs.
- Me too.
- Me three.
- Hey, what about your diet?
- I don't wanna starve to death.
Why don't we set up over here?
No... I see where we should go.
Yo, throw the ball!
Hyuh! Freddy, you asshole!
- Ooh la la!
- Let's go, girls! Come on!
(LAUGHING)
(GIGI) Let me out!
Uhh!
Gigi, get over here! I'm
not done with you yet!
Well, I'm done with you, Michael, and
if you know what's good for you,
get your ass off
Teresa's uncle's property.
Gigi... you little bitch, get over here!
You know what, I'm done with you!
Stop following me, Michael!
(SCREAMS)
I have to tell you, Tre...
Despite the mix-up with the house, I think
this is gonna be a really good weekend.
(SHRIEKING)
No, please, please! Help me!
No, stop, please!
Stop, let me go! Please!
And if not for you, we would've had to have
turned back yesterday and miss all of this.
No, no, no!
(GASPING AND GRUNTING)
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
We're all in the same boat.
(GRUNTING)
- That didn't take long.
- No, it didn't.
Impressive, I have to say.
We gotta step up our game.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LAUGHING) Ah, ow!
God.
Teresa and Dina... This is...
Tony, Joey, Gino,
Vinnie, and Freddy.
- (TERESA) Hi.
- Hi...
Oh, wow.
- What is that?
- It's a mime.
A what?
(WOMAN) What is he doing?
Why is he wearing that?
- Dude, there's no window there.
- He's just pretendin', Tony!
- Ohh...
- (WOMAN) He is cute.
I don't get it, either.
Oh! Aww...
(WOMAN) Now he's hitting on her.
Now get the fuck outta here, Bozo.
(LAUGHTER)
- He's doing you, Gino!
- Gino, that's you.
You gonna take that, Gino?
(LAUGHING) Yo...
Yeah, keep going. Really?
Yeah.
(ALL GROAN)
- One punch!
- Good night, motherfucker!
- Now get the fuck outta here...
- Asshole!
Before I throws you a real beatin'!
Whoo!
- Who's going in the water with me?
- I am, let's go!
- Yo, Gino, go out for a pass.
- Hey, wanna catch some crabs?
(LAUGHING)
Hey, we're going to the Barnacle
Club later if you guys wanna come.
There's something so relaxing,
you know, and elegant
about the beach. You
know what I mean?
- I just love the fresh air.
- Mmm.
Those guys were kinda
hot, don't you think?
- They were definitely hot for you.
- Ooh, yum, yum, yum.
- (FARTS) Oh, my God!
- What?
- Oh, I have to go!
- Go where?
Uh, the laxatives are kicking in.
I have to go to the bathroom right now!
Oh, my God, oh, quick, run up to
the boardwalk and find a restroom!
Aah! Aah! Get out of the way!
- What?
- (VAL) I gotta go!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh... my... God.
(SCREAMING)
(WATER BUBBLING)
Ohh.
- Eww...
- Ohh.
Look, Daddy, sea shells.
(TERESA) Come on, Valerie. We've
gotta get ready for tonight!
- Hey, you got any more corndogs?
- (SQUISH)
Poopy.
All right, we got dollar Jersey Devil
shots for the next two minutes,
so go to the bar and get you some!
- Here's to the king.
- What king?
- Fuc-king!
Oh. (HIGH-PITCHED LAUGH)
So, fellas, who's gonna
pay for all these drinks?
- He is.
- You are.
- I'm paying for the cab.
- I always pay for the cab!
- No, you pay for the drinks.
- Hey, you watch yourself there.
You gotta be faster than that to stay in
the ring with the Staten Island Stallion.
Man, you got it all wrong.
If you weren't my boy,
you wouldn't even make it to the ring.
Pa-pow! End of story, motherfucker.
- Who's next?
- Bullshit!
- You never popped nothing.
- How the fuck do you know?
'Cause I've known you since we were 12,
and you have such a big fucking mouth
that half of Staten Island
would have known about it.
There would have been billboards
along the highway saying,
"Gino Digideo whacked some
dude. Paid for by Gino Digideo."
- (LAUGHTER)
- I like it. I like it.
Yeah, let's do some more shots, buddy.
Let's get some more... which ones?
(ALL) Ohh!
- What the fuck?
- I'll tell you what the fuck.
That's for drugging and raping my friend
Tammy last week, you fucking dirty scumbag.
Yo, I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Yes, you do, and two other people saw
you drop a fucking pill in her drink.
Yo, that bitch was DTF, so get the fuck
outta my face before I smack your mouth.
I bet you would, you
fucking dirty scumbag.
- Get the fuck out of here, you slut.
- You can't do that in here, come on.
- You're out.
- Get off of me!
- Bye-bye, you little twat.
- Peace!
Works every time.
Yo, bro, we gotta get another
bottle of that shit.
All right, my guy's coming in
next week. I'll get a shitload.
- Hello.
- How you doing?
If I was you, I'd
be stalking me too.
Oh... well, let's have a couple more
drinks and see who's stalking who.
- After you.
- Thank you.
Right now, I'm just working on my
demo, trying to get signed to a label,
- you know what I'm saying?
- (LAUGHING) Get a label.
What the fuck are you
laughing at, Dominic?
(CHUCKLES)
Look at you, kid. Who we kidding?
You can't sing, you can't rap.
You can't even play a
goddamn instrument.
How the hell is a record
company gonna sign you?
'Cause I'm that fucking down! Besides,
what the fuck do you know about records?
You're just a part-time
manager at a nightclub.
If I need the urinals or some
shit cleaned, I'll give you a call.
(ALL LAUGHING)
- You don't know who the hell I am.
- That's the point.
We don't know who the fuck you
are, and nobody else does either.
(LAUGHING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
I'll be back.
So, I was just down in the ladies' room,
and it's, like, totally empty down there.
Like, two people could totally have
sex and no one would know, but...
that... that would be wrong, right?
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, no.
Yo, yo, yo, for the first
time in over two decades,
give it up for the one, the
only, Jersey's own Italian Ice!
Hey yo!
New Jersey, make some
motherfucking noise!
Come on! Kick it, DJ!
(SCRATCHING)
♪ Let's roll ♪
♪ We're about to get nice ♪
♪ With the one, the only ♪
♪ No phony, Italian Ice ♪
What the fuck is Italian Ice?
♪ I got more fans
than the Mona Lisa ♪
♪ When the ladies see
me, they all scream nice ♪
♪ Everybody wants
some Italian Ice ♪
"Italian Ice. Born
Dominic DiLallo in 1966.
Had a minor regional hit
in 1991 called 'Melt.'"
♪ Melt, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Melt all over my face, yeah ♪
"But he's best known for
his unsuccessful lawsuit
against Vanilla Ice for
stealing his career."
♪ Melt all over my face, yeah ♪
Hey, Freddy, that's
you in 20 years.
(LAUGHTER)
- "Ha ha ha ha"... screw you!
- ♪ Melt all over my face, yeah ♪
♪ I'm Italian Ice ♪
♪ Yo, DJ, get nice ♪
I've got such bad butt cringe,
I think my ass is gonna crack in half.
(LAUGHTER)
New Jersey, Italian
Ice is back! Yeah!
Suck my balls, Vanilla Ice.
Stupid douche.
(SIREN BLARING)
What the fuck are
you looking at, bitch?
(ALL SHRIEK)
(MAN) Oh, yeah!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
(MEN) Ohh!
(MEN CHEERING)
Security to the
dance floor, please.
(ALL CHEERING)
Shit!
(GLASS SHATTERS)
No, no, no. No!
No, no, no, no, no!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS)
- Hey...
- Get the fuck off of me!
- Hey, all right!
- Fuck the police!
Fuck the police!
- (OVERLAPPING ARGUING)
- Hey, come on, come on.
Hey, youse is all suspended from the
club for the rest of the summer.
But they started it!
- Yeah, but you threw your drink at her.
- It spilled!
- Ah, get the fuck outta here.
- Motherfucker!
We can't go out like this, so
let's just go back to the house.
- Hey.
- Fuck it.
- Hey, where youse goin'?
- Back to our house... you coming?
- Yeah, we're going. Yeah, we're going.
- Just follow us.
Come on.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Let's have some fun now!
How many times have you been
banned from this club before?
- Ah, I've been banned, like, three times.
- Three times... no way!
(CLATTER)
Shh! Shh...
Shh.
(WHISPERING)
What the hell was that?
- (WHISPERING) Someone's in the house.
- What?
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Who the hell are you?
I'm Rosemarie! Val's cousin.
- Rosemarie!
- Valerie, there you are!
Everyone, this is
Rosemarie, my cousin.
I texted her the address this
morning. I forgot to tell you.
Thanks. Uh, how did
you get in here?
The sliding glass door was unlocked, so
I just came in and made me some dinner.
Oh, God, was I starving.
By the way...
you're gonna need some more Super
Fudge ice cream and beef jerky.
(LAUGHING)
Yo, this place is fuckin' hooked!
A little out of the
way, but hooked.
What happened to Gigi? She should
have been back here by now.
Maybe Rosemarie ate her.
(LAUGHTER)
Watch it, that's my cousin.
- Where do you keep the liquor?
- Screw that, where's the food?
I'll nuke some fried chicken.
- (DINA) He's hungry.
- Yes!
"Fat Camp Massacre!" This is
supposed to be the best movie ever!
(JOEY) Oh, yeah, yeah, put it on.
- Hey, I want a leg!
- I want breast!
- I just want a piece of ass!
- Aah! (LAUGHING)
(MACHINE CLICKING)
Ooh... Oh, yeah...
(LAUGHTER)
(BED SPRINGS SQUEAKING)
(GRUNTING)
(WHISPERING) Roger.
(SNORING)
Roger. Roger!
Roger! I smell pizza.
(SIGHS) I told you already. Stop thinking
about food, and go back to sleep, Keith.
If they catch you eating at night one
more time, they're gonna kick you out.
I don't care about that. I smell pizza,
I'm starving... I'm gonna find it.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(MUNCHING LOUDLY)
Cupcake!
(GASPS)
Ohh, I finally found you, cupcake.
(MUNCHING) Mmm...
Now where's that fucking
pizza? I'm starving!
Pizza!
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my leg!
I wouldn't mind being stuck in a bear trap
alone in the woods if it was with you.
Ooh, who needs a bear trap when
I have handcuffs in my bedroom,
- you sexy little ape, you?
- You little freak!
- Uh-huh.
- Uhh!
- (GROWLS)
- (SHRIEKS)
(SQUEALING AND LAUGHING)
Oh, my God!
(LAUGHING)
- Bye! Whoo!
- Later, boys.
(BOY SCREAMING)
Who are you?
I'm Cupcake the Clown. And
you just ate my cupcake.
So now it's time to cut a few
calories the old-fashioned way!
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)
Get me outta here, Mister.
Come on, get me outta here!
(CHUCKLES)
Certainly.
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)
I'd smack that clown so fucking
hard, he'd be begging me to stop.
Where are you taking
me, you big ape?
- To the bedroom.
- We just passed it. Put me down!
(CHUCKLING)
So... do you have a girlfriend?
No, sweet tits. I don't
get burned like that.
So why don't you do me a favor...
go into that bedroom.
I'm going to the shower
and rinse off, okay?
(GIGGLES)
The Electro Beam 300? Classic!
(BUZZ)
(BEEP)
(GRUNTING)
Ba ba!
(GRUNTING RHYTHMICALLY)
(GRUNTS)
Yeah.
(WATER RUNNING)
(CLINK)
(GIGGLING) You little freak.
(CLANKING)
Oh, no. I'm a prisoner.
Please, don't hurt me.
(MUFFLED PROTESTS)
(MUFFLED) What?
(ELECTRONIC TONE RISING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(KNIFE SLICING)
(CHAINSAW BUZZING, BOY SCREAMING)
I just wanted a slice!
- Yo, get that fat piece of shit!
- Yeah, cry like a little bitch, fat boy.
(WHIMPERING)
(THUD)
(SIZZLING)
(GRUNTING)
(WATER TRICKLING)
(BOY SCREAMING ON TV)
I can't take this shit.
Who wants to take a swim?
Me. (GIGGLES)
Let's go.
(SCREAMING)
(THUD)
(BEAR TRAP SNAPS)
(GASPING)
Ha ha ha! Prepare to die!
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)
(ALL) Ohh!
Damn...
(BOY SCREAMING ON TV)
(DOOR SLIDES OPEN)
Wait for me!
I could totally see you as
becoming a lawyer. You know why?
You got eyes just like the
guy from "Law and Order."
Yeah, so maybe that's
what I should do...
becoming a backstabbing lawyer
and make a lot of money.
- (GIGGLES)
- What about you?
I could be your secretary. I got lots
of really sexy dresses and nice boobs,
and I'm really good
at answering the phone.
Val, Dina. Come over here so I can show
you the new pictures of Mr. Wiggles.
- Mr. Wiggles!
- Ohh...
You sit tight there.
- Who the fuck is Mr. Wiggles?
- Rosemarie's pet ferret! Wanna see it?
- Aww!
- Isn't he sweet?
This is me and Mr.
Wiggles in the shower.
Aww!
Dude, what the fuck is wrong
with these fucking girls?
I love that one!
I'm not fucking putting
up with this shit no more.
See, he's got a
personality like a person.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Where do you two
think you're going?
I'm taking my secretary...
to the boardroom.
He wants me to take dick-tation.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Oh, shut up.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Get lost. We're trying
to have a conversation.
- Freddy, come here.
- What?
I don't know, I got a math question I'm
trying to figure out. Just get over here.
What do you want?
Look, Tony wants to get with Dina.
I wanna get with Teresa, and you
wanna get with Valerie, right?
Yeah.
Well, there's four of them,
and there's three of us.
So you know what that means?
No one is gonna get with anyone until we
figure out a way to extract the grenade.
Make it three on three.
Hey, girls, girls, you guys...
you guys want a doughnut?
No, the doughnuts are for
you, honey. We get it...
you like to eat fuckin'
doughnuts all the time.
No fucking way. I'm not taking one for the
team for the fifth fucking time in a row.
- Oh, come on, Freddy.
- We got a better idea.
Just start talking to
her as if you like her,
and pretend you're interested
in what she says, right?
Ask her to take you to the store,
like you gotta go get something.
Yeah, use my car. Now, when you
get a few miles down the road,
just open the door, let
her out, and drive away.
Yeah, but then when she finds her way
back, they're all gonna hate us.
So? We'll be done.
Yeah... Tony will be smashing Dina,
I'll be hooking up with Teresa,
and Valerie, she'll be all yours.
(HIGH-PITCHED LAUGH)
Youse are good.
- Go get 'em.
- Watch this.
(ROSEMARIE) What are you
guys talking about over there?
Tony just wanted to find
out the square route of 37,
so I figured I'd help
him out, you know?
(ROSEMARIE) Oh, okay.
- You must be good with numbers.
- Well...
I know a perfect 10 when I see one.
Ohh.... You're so sweet.
I never got to tell you about
my ferret, Mr. Wiggles.
Oh, yeah, I'm so interested.
Please, tell me.
Well, every Christmas, I dress
him up in a ballerina costume.
Wow. Jeez.
What?
Oh, nothing, I just wish I had a cigarette
when we talked about Mr. Wiggles.
We could drive into town
to get a pack, if you want.
Yeah, that's a great idea!
Then we could smoke cigarettes and
talk about Mr. Wiggles all night!
Let's go!
Oh, you nasty little bitch.
Oh... oh.
Oh, fuck yeah.
(CLINK)
(SCREAMS)
Aah!
(SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMING)
(CRUNCH)
(GIGGLING)
- I have a hamster named Buzzy that...
- Oh, wow, that's fucking amazing.
He knows how to swim.
Hey, what's up?
Nothing, just, uh,
catching up on some emails.
That's cool. So, uh...
- you get good reception out here?
- Yeah, it's not too bad.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah...
So, um...
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Nothing, I'm just
hanging out, you know?
- It's all good, sweetheart.
- It's, uh...
- You're gonna have fun, come on.
- Yeah, I'm having a good time.
Just relax.
- I'm pretty relaxed.
- Just relax.
- What the fuck?!
- What the hell was that?
What the fuck?! What, you
don't wanna be with me?
No, why would you think
I'd wanna be with you?
'Cause every other bitch in New
Jersey would kill to wife me up!
Wife... really?
'Cause if I was married to you, I'd put
poison in your orange juice every morning!
Yeah, well, if I was married to
you, I'd drink it, you fuckin' bitch!
(DOOR SLAMS)
Dick.
So, uh, is Buzzy a boy
or a girl hamster?
(COWS MOOING)
(ROSEMARIE)
So how much longer to the store?
Couldn't be much further.
Oh, my God, you see that?
See what?
Looked like a little puppy
dog... it crossed the road.
- A puppy dog?
- Yeah, it looked like it was lost!
Stop the car!
I think it ran into the cow pasture! Oh,
God, I hope the cows don't eat him!
Oh, my God!
(COW MOOING)
(HIGH-PITCHED LAUGH)
Freddy! Freddy, you asshole!
(FREDDY LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(COW MOOING)
(WOMAN ON TV) There's so many
hot gorilla juiceheads in here...
Hey, where's Rosemarie?
(FREDDY) Uh, she saw an all-night buffet and
decided to go back for a midnight snack.
(LAUGHING)
What?
Mmm. Where's my shot?
- Hey, wingman!
- Oh, yeah!
(CHUCKLING)
Huh?
Ah!
(ALL GROAN)
- Vinnie, you fucking asshole!
- What?
Fuck all of youse. I need a smoke.
(CLATTER)
Yo, hey, come back here, you pussy!
What'd you have, two bowls
of stupid this morning?
(BUZZING, ZAP)
Oh, that was a good one.
- Yo, that was dope.
- Eww.
Why do they keep flying into it
when they see their friends
exploding all over the place?
Just mindless life forms following the
light aimlessly into the darkness.
(FREDDY HUMMING)
Mm?
(FOOTSTEPS CRUNCHING)
(DOOR CREAKS FAINTLY)
Hey, anybody home in here?
(HIGH-PITCHED LAUGH)
- Hey, where'd Freddy go?
- He had a hissy fit and took off.
Oh, he's got my fucking keys!
You just gonna leave
me here? Screw him.
- (VINNIE) Ah, quiet, bitch.
- (SCOFFS) Screw you.
Hey, Freddy!
- What's he doing?
- Dropping dead, I hope.
Hey, I'm starving.
What do we got to eat?
I got some hot dogs in the fridge.
Hot dogs? I'm all over that shit.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Hey, Freddy, you fucking
dickhead! Where are you?
(MAN SCREAMING)
Freddy?
Where the fuck are you?
(FREDDY) Vinnie!
If he's fucking with me, I'm
gonna throw him a beatin'.
Freddy?
(SIGHS)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
So, yeah, I do, like, about
1,000 push-ups every day.
Really?
I need to eat now.
Good... get the barbecue going
while I get the other stuff ready.
All right.
(CHAIN CLINKING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(CREAKING)
(FRANTIC GRUNTING)
Mm!
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GASPING)
(SANDER GRINDING)
(MOANING)
(WHIMPERING) No...
(SCREAMING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(CLATTERING)
(SCREAMS)
(MOANS)
Kill me.
Please kill me.
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
- (THWACK)
- (SCREAMING AND MOANING)
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
I thought I heard
something outside.
It's probably just the
guys horsing around.
(SCREAMS AND MOANS)
There it is again.
Why don't you see if they
want anything to eat?
(DINA) Yeah, Val, I'm starving.
All right. I'll be right back.
(SIGHS)
Mmm.
Told you I was hungry.
(CREAKING)
(CHOPPING AND SQUISHING)
(VAL) Freddy?
Vinnie.
Freddy?
Stop horsing around.
Vinnie?
Freddy?
Freddy!
Hey, how many dogs am I
supposed to be making out there?
- (DINA) We don't know yet.
- Where the hell is Valerie?
So, Dina, whose house
is this anyway?
- It's Teresa's Uncle Vito's house.
- And who's Uncle Vito?
Vito Rubino.
Teresa's uncle is Big "V" Rubino?
- Isn't he in jail?
- He's under house arrest...
but I wouldn't bet on too many
witnesses testifying against him.
That's it. I gotta go find where these
meatballs are. I'll be right back.
Hurry up.
(SIGHS)
Yo, Freddy, Vinnie! Teresa's
uncle is Big "V" Rubino.
We gotta get the fuck outta here!
Hey, you dickheads in there?
What the fuck?
(THWACK)
(THUD)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(SCRAPING)
I'm gonna go and straighten
things up around the pool.
- You want a hand?
- No, I got it, um...
could you clean things up around here and
see when everyone would like to eat?
I bet they'll be
dying to eat by now.
(MUFFLED CRIES FROM VAL)
(SCREAMING)
(VAL MOANING)
Shit!
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(TONY GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRINDING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(GROANING, ROPE SQUEAKING)
(SIGHS)
Bunch of pigs.
Ugh.
(SCREAMING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
You guys want something to eat?
(SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKS)
Dina! Dina!
(BOTH SHRIEKING)
(SOBBING) Dina!
Joey and Joanne! They're dead.
- So is Gigi!
- What about Candi and Gino?
I don't know... I don't know. They
have to still be in their room.
- Oh, my God.
- (SOBBING)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
- What's going on?
- (WHISPERS) I don't know.
Wait...
Gino!
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
Dina!
Dina, open the door! Dina, help me!
Tony!
(LABORED BREATHING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Help me.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- Oh, my God, what's going on?
- I don't know... call 9-1-1.
(PHONE SPEED-DIALING)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
Uncle Vito? Uncle Vito, pick up!
Yeah, somebody's trying to kill us!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Quick, open the door!
(SCREAMS)
Ohh!
Dina, it's stuck! Oh, my God.
- Run!
- Oh, my God.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Come on... come on,
get up! Get up... run!
Let's get out of here!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Oh, my God!
(VIBRATOR BUZZING)
(GRUNTS)
- Oh, God.
- Oh, holy shit.
Oh, God.
- Where are the fucking keys?
- Come on!
(BOTH SHRIEKING)
(FOOTSTEPS CRUNCHING)
Come on!
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Let us in!
(CRYING) It's locked! Come on!
Come on.
Ohh!
(CLUNK)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Shit!
- Where's the fucking light switch?
- I don't know. I got it!
(CLICK)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Go, go, go! Go!
(GASPS)
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
(BOTH SHRIEKING)
Come on, come on!
- (DINA) Valerie!
- (SCREAMING) Valerie!
My God!
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERING)
- Where the fuck can we go?
- We can't use the cars...
- and he'll catch us in the woods.
- If we can get to the rowboat...
we can take it to the middle of the
lake, where he can't reach us.
You know I can't swim!
If I fall in, I'll drown!
Jesus Christ, Teresa,
he's gonna kill us!
(SCREAMING)
Who are you?
Edgar?
Troy, my name is.
- Why?!
- It's a Jersey thing.
(KNIFE SLICES)
Dina, look out!
(SHRIEKING)
(SOBBING) Dina!
(SCREAMING)
(SQUISH)
(GROANING)
(THUD)
(SIREN WAILING)
Police!
(SOBBING)
What's wrong? Tell me what's wrong!
Everybody's dead!
Everybody? Is there anybody else?
- In the house.
- All right, stay here.
Backup and the ambulance
are on the way.
Stay right here. Dennis, come on.
(WAILING)
(SIREN)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
I'm Officer Davis. Do you need
any kind of medical assistance?
Okay. Go check inside!
Okay, I need you to tell
me everything that happened.
- I need to see Dina!
- No, no, no.
You can't go in there. You
need to stay out here with me.
I'll take care of this one. Check
the rest of the barn for me.
Okay.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER OUTSIDE)
He's got a pulse! Help
me get the gurney.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Help me!
(GUNSHOT)
Fuck! Oh, fuck.
- What the fuck happened?
- Man, I was nervous.
- (RADIO) Gordon to Davis.
- Hold on.
(STATIC)
- Davis, go.
- How do I explain this?
- I have an 11-71.
- Shit.
I think you should get
over here right now.
I'm on my way. Okay...
I need you to stay in this
spot, okay? I'll be right back.
Plant this in his hands. We'll just
say it was self-defense, all right?
All right, cool. Good
looking out, man.
Dex, look at this. How am
I supposed to say that?
Some weird shit going on here, man.
(CRYING)
(SOBBING)
(SIREN, INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
This can't be the guy.
Wasn't this guy missing an eye?
(CHAIN CLINKING)
(SCREAMING)
Get over here right now.
Take that, motherfucker!
(HOWLING)
(SIZZLING)
(SCREAMING)
(KNIFE CLINKS)
Come back here, you bitch!
I'll gut ya like a pig!
(BRANCH SNAPS)
(PANTING)
I'll turn your insides
into sausage!
(GASPING)
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
No!
No! (WHIMPERING)
(SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMING)
Please!
Get over here right now.
(SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOTS)
Uncle Vito!
(BEEPING)
(SOBBING)
He was gonna kill me, just like
he killed Dina and everyone else.
- Everything's gonna be all right.
- How did you get here so fast?
When Edgar called, we
knew something was wrong.
Edgar?
Last week, two of my guys went missing
down here, and when you called,
said you were coming down for the weekend,
I asked Edgar to keep an eye on you.
He left me this message
an hour before you called.
(BEEP)
Mr. V., my brother's lost
his fuckin' mind today.
Turned our barn into a
fuckin' slaughterhouse.
(TROY)
Give me the phone, you big idiot.
(EDGAR) Troy, no!
(CLATTER ON MESSAGE)
(BEEP)
Oh, my God.
Promise me I'll never have
to see this place again.
- (SOBBING) Please.
- I promise, Princess.
Never again. Never again!
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(REEL CRANKING)
It's so beautiful out here, and
I love all this nature, but...
don't you miss your beach
house down by the shore?
What beach house? After the
storm, there was nothing left.
So I took the insurance money,
and I bought all of this.
No way. You own all of this?
- This must have cost you a fortune.
- A fortune?
A fortune? The little mobster who used
to own it was so anxious to sell it,
he practically gave it away. So I wound up
spending pennies to buy a fully renovated,
cool-as-balls home with a lake!
Tell me I'm not the
luckiest guy in the world.
That's why I like you, Ronnie.
'Cause you're smart
and you're classy.
(GIGGLING)
Ohh... life is good.
(BUBBLING)
(SCREAMS)
(ROARS)
Oh, my God! That's a huge gun!
And it's always fully loaded.
Here, little puppy.
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
Come here, little puppy.
Don't let the cows eat you.
(COW MOOING)