( MUSIC PLAYING )
YOUNG GIRL:  I read in
the "Little Big Book of Birds"
that ravens were once
the most colorful birds.
But they were vain and mean
and never recognized
their beauty.
They were too busy
being unkind to each other
so they were stripped
of all their colors
and turned black.
They are considered so evil
that their favorite food
is said to be
the flesh of a dead man.
But ravens really like
to be together, like family.
Let me introduce you
to my ravens.
( PHONE RINGING )
What's up, man?
Look, it'll just be
a couple of days.
They're good people.
You got nothing
to worry about, all right?
C'mon, Mom, let's go.
MOTHER: You know what?
You go ahead.
I just want
a minute alone, okay?
Fine, grump.
Hello, ladies.
Hi.
( MUMBLES ) ...Dad.
Can we go swimming?
We'll go in a little bit.
JOEY: Why?
'Cause I want to talk
to your Mom.
Promise?
I promise.
Okay.
See you at the dock.
ELLIS:
How was the flight?
Not bad,
a little bumpy.
Yeah?
Glad you're here.
Me too.
( VOICES CHATTERING )
Wendy, hey.
Oh my God.
Come here, group hug,
group hug.
WENDY:  Here you go.
Yeah? Nice.
Oh my God,
this is Saturn.
She's my life partner
for now.
We had to put
the finishing touches
on the art car
for Burning Man,
so we just worked
all night,
hopped in the vangina
and, boom, here we are.
All right, well,
if you need anything, just ask.
Yeah, I will.
You're a Virgo,
aren't you?
Triple.
That is so sexy.
( SIGHING )
The truth
is always beautiful.
Mm-hm.
Thanks, all right.
MAN:  There they are.
Good times.
Come here.
You blinked.
No, I didn't.
You did.
Now go get your victorious
bio-Dad a drink.
( RACING )
Pink fever dry martini
standing up with
a lemon twist
( INDISTINCT )
two olives?
Atta boy.
ELLIS:
Sounds good.
Why don't you get
your provider-Dad
one of those as well?
Ohh, come here.
Show Emma where you keep
the Chardonnay, okay?
ELLIS:  Let's grab a round of
small ball this weekend, yeah?
What's a small ball?
Golf, darling.
It's very, very dull.
Saul.
Ellis.
( SIGHING )
WENDY:
Here's your room.
Oh, this is very nice.
We've never stayed
on this floor before.
Oh, really?
I didn't realize that.
Yeah, we stay in the room
by the kitchen,
the maid's quarters.
( SIGHING )
What? I'm not saying anything
underneath what I'm saying.
I'm simply stating a fact.
Well, Joey's really
excited to see you.
All she can talk about
is you.
She's a smart kid.
Try and spend
some time with her.
It'll mean so much.
WENDY:
You know Jay's coming.
He's supposed to be here
for dinner
but he's bringing a guest.
I guess he needed a ride.
You know Jay.
At least
he has a new girlfriend.
He seems rather happy.
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
The drink always goes
on the right side.
This is the incorrect side
or the left side.
Put it on the right side.
I think I'm
going to make a toast.
Ellis and I
want to thank you so much
for coming to our home
and celebrating with us.
We really appreciate
you making the commitment
every summer to come to
our annual 4th of July party.
Tradition is important
and you mean the world to us.
So cheers, to us
and to years to come.
Years to come.
EVERYONE: Cheers.
( CHATTER )
So how's work, Big Guy?
SAUL:
It's fantastic.
When everyone in Hollywood
is bitching about the recession,
I haven't felt
a goddamned thing.
My new book
hasn't even come out yet
and I've already sold
the movie rights.
Wow.
Yes, not caving to
commercialism is a real feat
for you, isn't it,
darling?
And you don't
seem to be bothered
by the lifestyle
its afforded you.
Honey, can you get
some more wine?
Yeah, sure.
Joey, could you
bring us a bottle
of the '63 Chateau Lafleur,
please?
We're out.
We have the 2009 Twin Oaks.
That's fine. Why don't you bring
us two of those?
JOEY:
We have one.
HAL: I was told I'd get
everything I desire,
and you guys are kind of
dropping the ball on this one.
Desire is everything.
When it fades, life ends.
That's why I don't have sex.
Not like you guys do.
I fuck only to elevate
to a higher spiritual plane.
The mantra of Tantra.
Orgasm is a waste of energy.
HAL:
Hah!
Anyway, Hal, let's hear
what have you been up to
in your crazy world?
Well, got certified
as a life coach.
Certified.
What exactly is that,
a life coach?
HAL:
Life is a game, Emma.
You weren't born a starter.
None of us
were born a starter.
I mean, take Wendy here,
for example,
I mean, humble beginnings,
to say the least.
There was a time at Berkeley
when she wouldn't be caught dead
hanging out
with you people.
But now, she's on
the varsity squad.
That's my job.
I get you guys
off the bench.
What's keeping you from
taking it to the next level?
What are you afraid of?
What truth
are you hiding from?
When the student is ready,
the master will appear.
JOEY:
Uncle Jay!
Jay!
Ellis.
Good to see you, my dude.
ELLIS:  It's good to see you,
my dude.
Everybody,
this is my buddy, Chad.
Hi, Chad.
EMMA:
Hello, Chad.
ELLIS:  Why don't you come
take a seat.
It's okay?
ELLIS: It's okay.
WENDY:  Hi, Jay bird.
JAY:  Hey sister.
WENDY:  Glad you made it.
So I'm headed into
the back country tomorrow.
I met this cute hippy chick.
We're gonna let our
animal instincts run wild.
Chad's gonna let me use
his truck off road.
Is it cool if he stays here
for a few days?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
SAUL:
The more the merrier.
JAY:  Cool.
Chad makes films.
What kind of films?
Nature films.
What are they about?
Nature.
Well, you know what
Thoreau said about nature.
It has no morality,
only what mankind
imposes upon it.
You're Saul King?
Yes.
I've read four books
in my life
and three of them
were yours.
What was the other one?
JAY:
"The Little Big Book of Birds."
I memorized it.
It's about birds.
"A Covey of Coots"
was funny
but I thought it was
gonna be about birds.
It's a metaphor.
JAY:  I especially liked
"A Cast of Hawks"
but it wasn't
about birds either.
It was strange, you know,
you really could have said
something interesting.
Where do you get the ideas
for your books?
I think of them.
Can I interview you?
About your books.
Maybe later.
What time?
I don't know.
Okay. Can I--
I'm so sorry,
can I sleep now?
My room's at the top
of the hall, to the left.
Do you want some dessert?
No thank you.
Okay.
JOEY:
Goodnight.
Hey, a nightcap?
Yeah, something like that.
God, you look beautiful.
You really think so?
Absolutely.
No. No, Saul.
( LAUGHING )
What's wrong?
No. I can't.
You know, it's funny
'cause I don't remember
you ever writing
the entire time
we were together.
I don't even remember
you reading a book.
It's like you left me
and changed into somebody else.
Look, I'm by myself
all the time.
Writing is a God-awful
existence.
You should be grateful
you blocked my creative voice.
It would have been hell
to live with.
CHAD:
Wendy?
Yes, Chad?
I'm ready for my dessert now.
Sure.
Sure, Chad.
( NOISE FROM OUTSIDE )
ELLIS:
What is it, honey?
I think it's Chad.
ELLIS:
Chad!
Please, come back.
Chad, come back.
Okay, come on.
It's an antique.
It was not made
to get wet, Chad.
HAL:
Let's do this.
SATURN:  The truth is
always beautiful.
HAL:
What's going on?
Dad, can you watch me swim?
I can't.
JAY:  What's Chad
doing out there?
He can't even swim.
Hey, pal,
bring it on in, will ya?
It's time to go.
Okay, see you
on Independence Day.
May the 4th be with you.
Hah.
( LAUGHING )
JOEY:
There is a kind of hawk
that spends most of its time
in the air.
People think
that they're hunters,
just riding the wind,
looking for prey,
but they're really quiet
and gentle,
even secretive.
They just like
to travel alone.
( JAZZ PLAYING )
¶ That deed there's a big
Change in your life ¶
¶ Why you don't treat me-- ¶
MAN:
I can't work like this.
The food sucks.
The facility's insufficient.
You promised me a cabin
and you stick me
in this shithole.
Last time this piano
was tuned
like he didn't have
a hole in his head.
Hey, you've been paid
handsomely for a job
many others would fall
on their goddamn knees for.
What the hell
is the holdup?
I'm stuck, Saul.
You're stuck.
Let me help you out.
I'm blocked.
What do you mean
you're blocked?
It's something
that writers get.
I got nothing.
I'm blank.
Done with and washed up,
the muse is gone.
What the hell happened?
It just doesn't go away.
It does
if you've banished it.
Well, invite it back.
I can't.
I quit drinking.
What the hell kind
of self-destructive
behavior is that?
I mean, who the hell quits
drinking in the last chapter?
Maybe I do, Saul.
Or maybe I'm just
better than you
at making shit up, hm?
Write your own
fucking books.
( TURNS MUSIC LOUDER )
What are you doing?
You said
I could interview you,
about your books.
No, I didn't.
I said "maybe."
But I meant "no."
CHAD:
Saul?
You have to ask someone
if you're gonna make
a documentary about them.
Yes.
MAN:
Hey, Saul.
( GLASS SMASHING )
CHAD:
Saul?
HAL:  One.
CHAD:  Saul?
HAL:  Two.
One, two, three, four.
( UKULELE PLAYING )
Yeah.
All right.
Here we go.
We go, one, two,
three and four.
That's perfect.
Step high.
Chins up.
Here we go.
Again, we go high,
high, low and low.
And one last time.
Make it count.
Leave 'em wanting more.
Yes!
You guys were awesome.
JOEY:  Hey, Chad,
this is Olivia.
Hi, Olivia.
OLIVIA:  Hi, Chad.
Joey, I'm gonna go
get my bathing suit.
Bye-bye.
Will you take us swimming?
I can't swim.
You really don't swim?
No.
Just seems wrong.
C'mon, Chad,
live a little.
It's just water.
Please?
CHAD:  Okay,
but not too far, okay?
Whoa.
Is that a real gun?
Yeah, it's real.
Why do you have it?
I always carry a gun.
Can I hold it?
Chad's going swimming
with us.
Awesome.
C'mon, c'mon.
( WAVES OVERLAPPING )
( LAUGHING )
Can we stop, please?
I want to stop.
( LAUGHING )
I want to stop, please.
Can we stop?
No.
Stop.
Stop, please, stop!
Stop!
WENDY:  Joey, Joey,
what's going on?
Huh?
OLIVIA:  We were just swimming
and he started freaking out.
He hurt me.
He hurt you?
How did he hurt you?
JOEY:  He didn't mean to.
We scared him.
I was scared.
All right,
you know what?
That's enough
swimming for today.
Joey.
But Mom.
No, you're done,
you're done.
Honey...
( MUMBLES )
SAUL: He lurks.
He's always lurking.
Who knows what's going on
in that mind of his?
He started filming me today.
Yes, well,
he's filming everybody, Saul.
Yes, but he's making
a documentary about me,
his favorite writer.
I think he's some sort of
a lunatic fan.
Where did Jay
meet this guy?
I don't know,
but I just--
I don't fully trust him
with the kids.
Okay. Well, then,
he's got to go.
Okay.
Look at us, co-parenting.
So who's gonna tell him?
I'll tell him.
Hey, Chad.
I've upset you.
WENDY:  No.
It's just that it's not
gonna work out.
The truth is
we weren't expecting
another person
this weekend.
I understand.
Do you?
Yes.
I appreciate that.
You've all been
really nice to me.
I wish I could pay it back.
Bye, Chad.
Where's Chad going?
He had to leave, honey.
JOEY:
But why?
Well, people
are like gardens.
Gardens and flowers
want to blossom
but weeds overpower
everything
and flowers learn
to tolerate weeds
but if they can't,
the weeds need to be pulled
to save the garden.
Who decides
what's a weed?
Joey, just don't make
any sudden movements.
Not coming with?
No, thank you.
Just gonna take a walk.
I'll walk with you.
Yeah, sure,
if it's all right with Hal.
SATURN:
I didn't have a family
so it's really lovely
to see one with so much love.
ELLIS:  Why didn't you
have a family?
Oh, my dad died
when I was young
and my mom took off
on her Saturn return
and I've been on my own
since I was 14.
14, that's young.
No, no, no, no.
It was perfect.
To be free at that age,
not having to repress
all that sexual energy,
I can't imagine having lived
any differently.
I definitely learned
a thing or two.
I can imagine you did.
You need to fuck
my yoni puja.
Wow.
Wow, that's flattering.
I appreciate it.
But I love my wife.
That's okay.
I do too.
I would love to please
both of you.
Okay, Saturn,
I need you to stop.
This entire conversation
is making me very uncomfortable.
I haven't felt like this
since my father died.
( CAMERA CLICKING )
Chad?
There's a tribe
of tit warblers
nesting
in that juniper tree.
SATURN: Where?
I don't see them.
CHAD:  They're more easily
heard than seen.
I have gifts.
ELLIS:  Look who I found,
everybody.
It's Chad.
He brought gifts.
Awesome.
Gifts? Why?
For being so kind to me.
To pay it back.
Chad, you didn't
have to do that.
Yes, Wendy, I did.
Ellis, this is for you
because Wendy loved flowers.
Oh, beautiful.
I thank you, Chad,
for your floral support.
And Saul?
Yeah?
CHAD:  Saul?
Saul?
Yeah?
Saul, this is for you.
( LAUGHING )
EMMA:  Oh, very interesting
choice, Chad.
I like it.
Oh! Ah,
I have something for you.
So you brought him back?
ELLIS:
He's harmless.
CHAD:
For our lemonade stand.
JOEY:
Perfect.
Why are you
standing so awkwardly?
I'll go stand over there.
JOEY:
No, I didn't mean that.
I meant, are you feeling
uncomfortable?
Yeah.
Most of the time.
All the time, actually.
JOEY:
Why?
It's how I feel.
Take a seat, Chad.
If we're going to be
best friends,
we have to tell
each other a secret,
a secret we've never
told anyone else.
I have to tell you
a secret?
I left school
when I was your age.
I preferred watching birds.
But I have
an even bigger secret.
Really?
I chose you as my friend
because you're perfect.
Or just I'm amazing.
You are amazing.
What amazing things
do you think I'm going to do?
No, if I tell you
you'll think I'm silly.
Please tell me.
I think you're gonna
make people smile.
That's important, you know?
And I'm pretty sure
you're gonna cure cancer
and end hate too,
so you've got a big life
in front of you.
Cool, you're right.
CHAD:
Your turn.
Everyone lies to me.
Why?
'Cause they think the truth
will hurt me more.
You have to promise
not to lie to me, okay?
Promise.
So I'm raising equity
for a new startup.
We're in our very first
round of financing.
I thought it might be something
you'd be interested in.
Okay, what's the company?
It's not so much
of a company per se
as it is seed money.
Investing in the daily cog
of my life.
What you'd be investing in
is my expertise.
Your expertise?
You're a trust fund kid, Ellis.
I wouldn't know your expertise
if you put a handgun to my head.
Anyway, a high percentage
of these startups fail
and there's always the risk
of losing your friend's money
and the friendship.
I'm just asking
for a little bit of help.
Look, Ellis,
the last thing that I want
is for these family reunions
to turn more into
what the startup is doing
than about catching up
with friends and family.
I just don't think
I'm the right guy.
Yup.
Yup, well, your loss.
( BUZZING )
Agh! Bees, bees!
Beeeeeeees!
Did he call?
No.
He's such an asshole.
We were supposed to play
the small ball tonight.
Hey, at least
we have each other.
Right?
( BRAKES SQUEALING )
I got attacked by a whole
goddamned swarm of bees.
It's this fucking shirt.
Jesus, it's like they think
they can smell nectar on me
or something.
CHAD:
Bees can sense fear.
( GASPING )
Sorry. Sorry.
He did this on purpose.
Did what on purpose?
Give me a shirt
that was meant to kill me.
( LAUGHING )
That's ridiculous.
Is it?
Jay's coming back tomorrow.
Let's just let it go
for now, okay?
Oh, that feels good.
You're very pretty.
Thanks.
C'mon.
No.
I'm not in the mood.
Then how about
just doing it for me?
I don't want to.
Come on, Wendy.
Ellis, I don't want to.
Are you still
in love with him?
With who?
Saul.
Saul, Wendy.
No. Why?
Did he say something to you?
No.
No, he didn't say anything.
I could see it
with my own eyes.
Look, maybe
I'm the small person here
but this whole being friends
with the ex-husband thing,
it's weird.
I have a child with him.
I mean, what do you
want me to do?
I want to feel like
you love me the most.
I don't want to talk
about this right now, okay?
We have a full house
of guests.
What more can I do?
WENDY:
Ellis.
What--
what more can I do?
Ellis.
Huh?
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Look--
How much rejection
am I supposed to take?
( CAMERA CLICKING )
CHAD:  What's the best nap
you've ever taken?
When I was little,
I used to pretend to be asleep
so I could hear
my mom and dad talk about me.
They would say,
"That one's a goner"
and then my dad would pick me up
and carry me to bed.
Yeah?
How about you?
I haven't really
fallen asleep in a long time.
CHAD:
Hey, buddy.
Do you think
a kitty hurt it?
Baby birds fall or--
and sometimes they get
pushed from their nest.
Why?
CHAD:
To learn to fly.
That's mean.
No, it's normal.
And if it's feathered,
it's a fledgling
and has left the nest
on its own.
Then you leave it
where you found it.
If it's unfeathered,
then you look for a nest.
And if you find it,
you can bring it home.
Chad!
Wait for me.
You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
Joey, I want you
to come down right now.
I want you to come down
on solid ground right now.
Why do you care?
I'm gonna count to 10.
You mean 3.
I mean 10!
One.
Joey, don't make me come up,
up there, after you.
I want you to get down
from there right now.
Okay, fine,
I'll come up there.
I can climb a tree.
I don't know why anybody
would ever want to climb
a goddamn tree
and bring a little child up.
Let's all climb a tree,
let's climb trees
and free the birds
and because then,
everything's good
and our wives aren't
emotionally distant.
Goddamn it!
Don't look at me.
Look at me.
Joey.
Joey, baby, help me up.
This is how people
ride it out, huh, please?
See you later, sadly.
JOEY:  I read that frightened
birds will freeze in place,
hoping that they won't be
seen or heard
when they're scared
or in trouble.
But some birds fly alone.
They're the ones
that fly the highest.
And they can see the most.
They can fly so high,
that they vanish into thin air,
like a dream.
( UKULELE PLAYING )
Do you know
where I go every day
when I say
I'm leaving for work?
I actually go
to the driving range
which is ironic considering
that my golf game is for shit.
Just like the rest of my life.
And then if I'm really,
really motivated,
I'll come home
and I'll jerk off.
That is the sum total
of my day.
Sounds pretty good
to me, bro.
No, man, you've kind of
got to have your shit together
to smoke this.
Sorry.
You know, we live life
like it's supposed to be
a certain way and,
when that doesn't happen,
we think
that life is wrong.
But you're in control, bro.
I mean, your hands
are on the steering wheel.
You crash your car into a tree,
you don't blame the tree.
You could have it all.
Like me.
What are you
talking about, Hal?
You're not doing anything
with your life.
Yeah, but that's the point,
man.
That's my choice.
That's what makes me happy
and, fuck you,
because I'm right here
right now,
which is more
than you can say.
( SIGHING )
You create what you want
to create for yourself, bro.
You just got to keep it real.
So what is it you want?
Saul wants to have a baby.
Really?
You're surprised.
WENDY:  I thought he didn't
even like children.
He barely even looks at Joey.
Well, I don't think
liking children
has anything to do with it.
I think he just wants to have
something of his own,
something that he made.
He's made up this story
about himself
and now he's convinced himself
that it's true.
Are you pregnant?
No.
Why, do I look fat?
No, I just thought
since you said
Saul wanted to have a baby.
Wendy, I am not just a vessel
for that man's needs.
You know, my body is not here
merely just to deliver a child.
I told him to get
his own uterus.
Or have it with someone else.
And you know Saul, tell him
he can't have something and--
He tricked me.
What did you do?
I--
The love is lost.
And when it's all gone,
it's surprising
how freeing it is.
Just not a care.
SALESWOMAN:
What can I help you with?
I have an anniversary
coming up next week.
It's my tenth, big one.
And I'm honestly not sure
if my marriage
is gonna make it 'til then
unless I do something big.
Anything to do with the--
Oh, the bee stings?
No, that's just shit luck.
Okay.
( LAUGHING ) Tell me
a little bit about your wife.
What does she like?
Okay.
You know what?
Why don't you just show me
the most expensive
ring you have?
SALESWOMAN:
Okay.
That would be
this right here.
This is a 6.5 carat GIA
certified cushion-cut diamond.
It's very pretty.
How much is that one?
It's $250,000.
You know what?
Could you maybe
show me something
a little less expensive?
Okay.
That's pretty.
It's smaller,
it's definitely smaller
but a woman would
like that, wouldn't she?
I would.
JOEY:  Ravens usually nest
together for life,
but sometimes they visit
with other ravens.
Maybe this is because
they like shiny things
and will even steal them
from other birds' nests.
Anyways, that's what
"The Little Big Book" says.
But I think they're looking
for something that's missing
and they don't know
what it is.
And they don't know
where to find it.
( PLAYING THE PIANO )
What did you tell him?
I told him I quit.
You quit?
Oh my God.
You are amazing.
Will, you did it.
We're free.
( PLAYING THE PIANO )
Not exactly.
What does that mean?
It started out slow
and it's just gotten real fast.
What does that mean?
I told him
I quit drinking.
I definitely told him that.
Oh, shit.
Oh!
So he doesn't know.
I look at him
and I'm paralyzed with dread.
Yeah, he has that effect.
So what did you tell him?
I definitely told him
he's not the boss of me.
I'm sorry, Emma.
I'm just tired and just
really tired of all of it.
You're not gonna
say anything?
It's not easy for me,
either, you know?
Just a couple of phonies,
aren't we?
WOMAN: ( ON RADIO ) We're here
today with Saul King
a former Wall Street
Whiz Kid
who was the first
American author
to hit the number one spot
with his debut
since F. Scott Fitzgerald.
Mr. King's work
has been described
as a strange mix
of the mythic,
the slightly implausible and--
( MUSIC PLAYING )
( CAR HORN )
( BANGING ON WINDOW )
TERRI: Thank you, Mr. King,
for joining us today.
MR. KING: Terri, it's nice
to be here.
Thanks so much
for coming along to my house,
I really appreciate it.
TERRI:
It's wonderful to be here.
So, Mr. King, tell me,
where do you find
your inspiration?
MR. KING: Terri, a story is like
a beautiful woman.
For me, writing
is like making love.
Agh.
Aghh!
TERRI:  Wonderful. Do you--
Do you find yourself
writing wherever you are
in the world?
Do you have a certain place
where you to write?
( MUSIC DROWNS OUT
INTERVIEW )
Woo!
Oh, I mean, could this be
more beautiful?
Actually...
yes, it can.
What is that?
( MUSIC PLAYING )
This shit's
not working at all.
( SHOUTS )
( GARBLED NOISE )
What are you talking about?
I love you so much
and I get it,
I understand fear,
you know?
I walk into the tiger's mouth
every fucking day.
I got a lot of things
that terrify me, you know?
Spiders and big-ass fucking
malicious hairy predators
and, you know, I'm scared of--
Saturn scares me.
Really scares me.
( GUN FIRING )
SATURN:  Dad?
What the fuck
am I doing?
( GUN FIRING )
( GARBLED NOISE )
You betrayed the cause.
We were gonna
change the world.
Oh yeah.
I like money, you know?
Everybody likes money.
I like money.
But do you really need
all this shit?
( JUKEBOX PLAYING )
Hey.
Why did you bring him?
WENDY: Because he's
our house guest, Ellis.
Can't just leave him
at the house by himself.
ELLIS: What are you
gonna put on, Chad?
Phil Collins?
( "GODDAMN LONELY LOVE" BY
DRIVE-BY TRUCKERS PLAYING )
¶ I got green and I got blues ¶
¶ And every day
There's a little less ¶
¶ Difference between the two ¶
¶ I belly up and disappear ¶
¶ Well I ain't
Really drowning ¶
¶ 'Cause I see the beach
From here ¶
¶ And I could take
A Greyhound home ¶
¶ But when I got there
It'd be gone ¶
¶ Along with everything
A home is made up of ¶
¶ So I'll take two of
What you're having ¶
¶ And I'll take all of
What you've got ¶
¶ To kill this goddamn lonely
Goddamn lonely love ¶
You never gave me a gift.
ELLIS:
Honey, that's enough.
¶ Sister listen to what
Your daddy says ¶
¶ Don't be ashamed of things
That hide behind your dress ¶
Wendy, stop it!
¶ Belly up
And arch your back ¶
( GLASS SMASHING )
You two--
CHAD: Get off me.
Get off me!
ELLIS: Don't fuck with my wife.
¶ And you could
Come to me by plane ¶
¶ But that wouldn't
Be the same ¶
¶ As that old motel room
In Texarkana was ¶
¶ So I'll take two
Of what... ¶
I don't want
to be touched.
Wendy.
You're drunk.
Go home.
¶ Goddamn lonely
Goddamn lonely love ¶
¶ Stop me if you've
Heard this one before ¶
¶ A man walks into a bar ¶
¶ And leaves before his ashes
Hit the floor ¶
You asleep?
Yeah.
Did you finish?
Do you want to read it?
EMMA:  No.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
I love you, Will.
I love me, too.
The fireworks
have started.
They're so loud.
Are you okay?
No.
No, I'm not.
Sit with me.
My dad
always wanted a boy.
That's why he named me Joey.
I disappointed my dad
by being a girl
and my mom by being
too much like my dad.
I think that's why
my dad left,
'cause when he looks at me,
he sees himself.
It's all my fault.
Hey, you're just a kid.
How could it be your fault?
I know my family will never
be together again.
But I still hope.
Is that crazy?
No.
No, I don't think it is.
( FIREWORKS EXPLODING )
JOEY: ( NARRATING )
Ravens are territorial
and like digging up
against other birds,
especially when they're
near their nests.
Anyways, that's what
"The Little Big Book" says
but I think
the book is wrong.
They're just bullies.
They're the ones
that are scared.
It's so beautiful.
Yeah.
Morning.
WENDY:  Good morning.
Is there a Mr. Saul King
staying here?
Mr. King was involved
in a hostile incident
with a taxi yesterday.
Mr. King, you need
to come with me.
Thanks for
picking me up.
You're welcome.
I want a divorce, Saul.
Jesus Christ, Emma.
Do we have to do this shit
tonight again?
It's been a hard enough day.
I swear to God every time
you get three drinks in you,
you want to get
a goddamned divorce.
No, I'm completely sober.
I've never felt this clear.
I've been unfaithful.
So there's that.
You're unbelievable.
Don't tell me you're
fucking someone else
and expect me to fall out
of my goddamned chair, okay?
Your delicate sensibilities
can go fuck themselves.
You have no soul.
You're a fraud
and, you know,
I permitted myself to be
swallowed up by you for years
and, you know,
now I just feel like
I'm coming out of this
long, slow, dream.
Don't you think this is
a little bit dramatic?
EMMA:
Don't speak for me.
For once, just don't
fucking speak for me!
There you go.
Every time you try to win
an argument,
you've got to scream.
I know about your lie.
Which one?
How's the writing
going, Saul?
You repulse me.
I just don't love you
anymore, Saul.
I don't love you either
and I never have.
Thank you.
You okay?
No.
My wife just left me.
What are you gonna do?
In my bedroom?
Yes. I'll just use it,
just for a moment, okay?
Come here.
Mother of my only daughter,
I need to fuck you so bad.
I don't mean to be pushy
but I think if I could
just fuck you once more,
I mean,
completely fuck you,
that everything in my life
would be okay.
No!
Saul.
No.
SAUL: What?
Goddammit.
Don't fucking
walk away from me.
Don't talk to me like that.
I'm not your wife anymore.
I have my own problems.
I don't need any of yours.
What are you doing?
What is it you want?
I'm dying here, Wendy.
I need you.
You don't need me.
You're just trying
to get your dick back
because you lost someone
you care about.
Why can't you just admit
that you care about her,
that you actually
feel something?
And why don't you just admit
that there's no difference
between fucking
someone for $10
and fucking them
for $10 million?
This is a whore's house,
Wendy.
Fuck you!
Get out of my house.
Daddy.
Daddy, can I show you
something?
I made it for you.
Hey.
How do you like it?
Well, let's hope
it doesn't rain.
Yeah, I built it myself.
Well, the seats
are comfortable.
Honey, I have to go.
Wait, I made you something.
Thanks.
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
Wait.
Can I ask you a favor?
Go ahead.
Can you at least pretend
to be interested in me?
What are you talking about?
Of course
I'm interested in you.
No, you're not.
And that's okay.
Just thought we could be honest
about our relationship.
I don't want to feel
like a fake.
Are you calling
your father a fake?
Kind of.
Come here.
You blinked.
Are you fucking my wife?
Yes.
How'd you know?
A woman like that
doesn't leave you
unless she's climbing
up the food chain.
Thanks.
SAUL:
You didn't finish.
No.
I am too tired to hit you.
I'm choosing the life
that I want to live, Saul.
Not haunting hotel rooms,
anonymous to the world.
I have a story
and it will be heard.
What is this?
WILL:
It's your masterpiece.
It's a list of crimes
starting with fraud,
ending with assault.
It might be the best story
you've ever told.
It's yours, at least.
What do you want?
A clear conscience.
That sounds expensive.
Hm.
Truth must always
come first.
It's the only thing
we never had.
Shit.
Hey provider dad.
Are you coming to the 4th of
July party with us?
Well, that sounds fun
but why don't you guys
go ahead?
What do you mean?
It's the 4th of July.
Cotton candies,
candy apples, clowns.
Why don't you guys
go on without me?
I'll catch up
with you later.
What are you doing?
I want you to have this.
If you ever have
any questions about anything,
all the answers
are in there.
( CAR HORN HONKS )
Chad.
How's it going, bro?
Did you have a good time?
Yeah. Everyone was
very kind to me.
I want to go home now, though.
Hm.
What do you say
we just roll here
with the primates
a little while longer?
Then we're out of here,
easy-peasy.
WENDY:  Jay.
JAY:  Hey.
WENDY:  Oh my gosh,
you must be starving, huh?
Happy fourth.
¶ Walk away ¶
¶ Walk away real slow ¶
¶ Don't hold your head so ¶
¶ Don't hold your head so low ¶
¶ I was a stone ¶
¶ I was a stone to throw ¶
Chad.
Yes, Saul.
I'd like to have
a word with you.
You're all gussied up.
Thank you.
I had it made
for a funeral.
Oh.
Can I get you anything?
No, thank you.
Are you working?
SAUL:
I wanted to ask you
if you'd be willing
to read my new book?
But there's a catch.
You'd be the first.
How does that sound?
I'd like that, Saul.
Is it about birds?
You tell me.
( MUSIC PLAYING )
SAUL:
Did you finish?
Yes.
He's too good
for this world and
he lives but he doesn't.
He needs to die
so that he can live forever.
Anything else?
I don't like
what it's called.
SAUL:
Any suggestions?
"Give Up the Ghost."
You're not gonna go
run off some place, are you?
No.
That's good.
( MUSIC PLAYING )
SATURN:
Fuck you!
C'mon, baby.
Yeah.
C'mon.
It's not-- I'm not there.
I'm sorry.
You can do this, right?
I know.
Come on. Come on!
Fuck me please.
Are you getting too old, huh?
Can't get it up?
Can't get it up, old man?
Come on!
I need this.
What is wrong with you?
Stop it.
Fuck you.
Hi, Chad.
You like to watch?
Watch.
With your own eyes.
( SIGHING )
Touch me.
Touch me, Chad!
( SIGHING )
( GROANING )
You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
Chad!
Oh my God,
he's got a gun.
He's got a gun.
Chad has a fucking gun.
( SCREAMING )
Get away from him.
Leave him alone!
Get away.
Put that down!
He's got a condition,
all right?
His nerves get fried.
She probably freaked him out
and he overloaded.
He's a fucking pervert.
He's jacking off
in my yard.
WENDY: Stop it, you're crazy.
Bullshit.
Jay, stop it!
Jay, stop it, Ellis.
You want to just
fucking hit me, huh?
You fucking hit me?
Ha-ha.
WENDY: Don't, don't.
Ellis, stop it,
you're so crazy.
Let's take a walk, Chad.
ELLIS:
Everybody's happy.
Some fucking vacation
this was.
Ellis, what the hell
are you doing?
You're scaring the shit
out of me.
We're broke.
We got to sell the house.
We got to sell all of it
'cause I blew it,
on jewelry and private schools
and antique canoes.
I blew it all.
It's gone.
This is just an illusion.
It doesn't even exist
anymore.
Finally!
No shit.
Do you think
I'm fucking stupid?
That I didn't know?
Excuse me for giving you
everything you ever wanted.
I went broke trying
to make you happy.
Do you think any of this shit
makes me happy?
Do you?
Do I look happy?
I'm lost, Ellis.
I am lost in
all this bullshit,
in this whole life
we built together.
I don't even know
who the fuck I am anymore.
Joey!
ELLIS: He's got our daughter.
WENDY: Joey.
ELLIS:  Joey!
WENDY: Joey!
ELLIS:  Joey, stop.
WENDY:  Get back here.
ELLIS: Joey, stop.
WENDY: Come back,
what are you doing?
ELLIS: Chad!
( SHOUTING TO
COME BACK )
JOEY:  Get away.
Get away from me!
Don't touch me.
Let me go.
Chad!
No, no, no!
Don't leave me.
Chad, please.
JOEY: ( NARRATING )
I had a dream.
I was as light as a bird,
a spirit flying
through the air,
and I could see
my home and my family.
But then I woke up.
And I was on the ground.
When you step out
of a dream,
things are never
what they seem.
What you thought was real,
wasn't real at all.
Nothing is
as bright or clear
but the dream
is always there.
And it gives you hope
that one day it will return
and, if you're lucky,
you'll see
your friend again.
It's so beautiful.
Yeah.
JOEY:
Some birds fly alone.
They're the ones
that fly the highest,
can see the most.
They can fly so high,
that they vanish into thin air,
like a dream.
Don't worry, Mom.
All the answers
are in here.
¶ I'll see you
In my dreams ¶
¶ And we'll dance
With you holding me ¶
¶ But I know your heart'll
Never be mine ¶
¶ Moon shines bright
In the sky ¶
¶ And I see the light
In your eyes ¶
¶ But I know your heart
Will never be mine ¶
¶ I know we're never
To be oh dear ¶
¶ I fear my heart
Is lost to you ¶
¶ My dear sweet
How madly I fell for thee ¶
¶ Now I fear my heart
Is lost to you ¶
¶ Your heart stole me away ¶
¶ And I dreamed
Of you every day ¶
¶ But I know your heart
Will never be mine ¶
¶ So I'll say my fare thee
Well as my tears fall ¶
¶ How sadly they tell
How your heart ¶
¶ Will never be mine ¶
¶ I know we're never to be
Oh dear ¶
¶ I fear my heart
Is lost to you ¶
¶ My dear sweet how madly
I fell for thee ¶
¶ Now I fear my heart
Is lost to you ¶
¶ Yes I fear my heart