"Financial Times"
was a small two-piece thing -
That humans may cause
bunch of extinction.
The story was buried in page six.
This is how people take care of the problem.
Not at all.
Check your cell phone.
The signal is interfered with here.
How you doing, Louie?
-How Many cameras do you have?
Pöydällänikö?
-No, But stick to you.
Less than seven, more than two.
I make an order: one hat camera,
two buttonhole camera -
Sports bras,
one bottle camera, tactical shirt.
Now it describes.
Make sure that the buckles are correct.
Booking is
10 minutes.
We are sitting at the table
Is the recording site?
-There is.
Shrimps.
How do I know much about sushi?
He brought me here last year.
-You Have an exotic flavor.
Subscribe oath, when you're ready.
Just the point. Minutes.
Here comes the whale.
Yep. Three return.
Bingo!
The trend of the restaurant owners and chef
-
May be charged with
tarjoiltuaan endangered animals.
Case revealed the filmmakers took
stuck.
Gobi Desert, Mongolia
We make the road by yourself.
The skull is big.
I did a "National Geographic"
four extinction story.
I went to beautiful places.
Dinosaurs was
eye can see.
It happened a long time ago.
What if that happens currently,
and we do not notice it?
In Nature extinction die
one in a million species each year.
Over the next few decades -
We drive species extinct
one thousand times normal speed.
It is difficult to estimate exactly how many species we lose
.
Hundred years -
We may lose
50 percent of all species.
I remember thinking,
that this is the world's the biggest thing.
When we lived in the time of dinosaurs,
but we can do something about it.
Blue whale is the largest animal the earth,
larger than any dinosaur.
Sinivalaatkin
are in danger of extinction.
It swam towards!
-Look!
Blue Whales were asked
brink of extinction.
Remaining was about two per cent of capital.
Now, they reduce the frequency of ship traffic.
Go! It swims about you right.
I hope that when people see the blue whale
beauty -
They can be saved.
Blue Whale song is
animal kovaäänisintä.
People do not hear it,
because it is too shallow for us.
We look at the world with their own senses
and we think we are seeing it all.
But there is a secret world.
I want people to see it.
When we left the ship,
fisherman came to his interpreter -
And asked for a $ 500 finder's fee
finds on the buoy -
Which must be returned to the United States.
I glanced at the buoy.
Return address points at the Chris Clark, Cornell
bioakustinen laboratory.
A familiar man!
Chris had created new ways of record
whales for 30 years.
He testified that the whales hear
each other across the oceans.
Finding the buoy was the
I had found a bottle of mail.
We built recording systems,
we dropped them into the sea -
And record and without interruption.
Whales, dolphins -
, And any day in the sea.
The first time I knew that the nearby
singing blue whale -
This song screen,
but I heard it.
What to do? The song must be speeded up.
Niskavillat rise up even more.
Pretty damn great!
When we listen to the sounds of
from all over the globe...
Whether
frozen Arctic Ocean -
Or the Central African jungle -
Whole world sing.
Clicks on,
screech, whistle, jyskettä.
We only stopped to listen.
Cornell bioakustisen laboratory
animal sound storage is the largest in the world.
Votes have been collected since the 1930s.
It's like a museum. On the walls could be
bird skins or beetles.
Stock is the sounds of the world's biggest
animals votes -
Smallest insect sounds.
This is
male oun singing Kauailta.
Out mate for life. The male
singing duets with their partner.
This singing male.
It does not respond.
The male continues.
In the last of its kind in the male singing
females, which never comes.
The male is all alone.
Now the noise has stopped.
Collection short lifetime,
a period of about 70 years -
Many recorded
species are extinct.
Sound Inventory is living proof -
Extinction fierce pace.
In the history has been made
five major extinction:
Ordovikikaudella,
Devonian -
Permikaudella  -
Trias and / Jurassic.
Chalk / Tertiary destroyed
killed the dinosaurs.
The deep perception of time
is very difficult.
Earth's history
comprising 4.6 billion years.
If the Earth's history
seal least 24 hours -
When a person comes into the picture?
Was only a few seconds before midnight.
We are a new entrant.
We are currently anthropocene,
a new era.
Antropos means
people's time.
People leave their mark on
impact on the future of the fossil record.
65 million years ago an asteroid hit
-
And caused the dinosaur extinction.
September the sixth extinction
is easy to name.
Mankind has a new asteroid.
This is a turning point,
whereby it is either too late -
Or popular movement gets started.
We knew
the Hump restaurant sold whale meat.
At issue is something isompaakin.
We heard about the Obama administration
negotiating with the Japanese -
Commercial whaling
initiation of a review.
If we could prove -
The endangered whales served in the US Coast -
Negotiations would end short.
12 November 2010
Four days after ravintolaratsian
Animal rights organizations intervened
-
But the restaurant did not close its doors.
There were Ady Gil,
which I had not heard before.
He brought kamansa in front of the restaurant,
and guests saw them.
What are you doing?
Es my mind.
Yesterday there was 200 people
demonstrating.
I thought that someone must continue to exert pressure
.
Ady screens and projections
sees Oscar and Golden Globe Award Gala.
He parked the Ferrari
minivan next.
The owner came out to ask how long the
Ady will continue.
He held me hippinä,
which would continue a day or two.
I said I will continue to
months or even years.
"How long will you survive my presence?"
Restaurant closed its doors
10 days later.
It was a great moment.
All the others had gone home.
One man held the spotlight.
There are thousands of people -
Who will do everything to save the species.
They go to the Earth's darkest,
to insecure corners.
In the past decade has died
more than 800 environmental activists.
They make tough ropes
and are not well-known names.
Shawn Heinrichs. Colorado Boulder
is so inside the country as can be.
I heard that pretty neighbor
live in an ocean activist -
Who gave up work
technology in the enterprise -
Order to save endangered species.
Shawn doing pioneering work.
Isla Mujeres was the east coast of Mexico
's largest shark fishing island.
From there, set off at least
20 shark fishing platform on a daily basis.
Shawn help the island was
haituristien top destination.
Now the former hainpyytäjät
earn much more -
By taking tourists to swim with the whale sharks.
Simple economics.
Shawn's partner is often
investigative photojournalist Paul Hilton.
They end up always
dangerous situations.
Paul is a photo journalist. He, too,
focus on endangered species.
He has a great work.
Paul and Shawn are trying to catch
the endangered species selling rinkejä.
Making it a place in the package.
Shawn is a great eager.
He speaks gigs always too much
and I have to restrain him.
Americanism shine through.
A couple is a joy in many situations.
I may forget to describe something -
No one Watch my back.
, Paul and Shawn has a habit of
onto the camera around your neck.
Many imagine that the camera needs to look describing
-
But it's a video camera,
which describes all the time.
What a lot of these!
Are these jaws?
Jaws...
Do not overdo it.
How did you find the place? -Facebookin,
Colleagues and friends to help.
In walks a negligently.
How long were you there?
- 10 - 15 minutes.
Picture Then all of this in that time.
Are we soon be there?
-It's In the next block.
I did not know the illegal wildlife trade
to be so open.
Every second shop
was endangered animals.
Not only shark fins
but all possible endangered.
When the demand for shark fin soup in China rose
-
Daily asked
estimated 250,000 sharks due to the fin.
Hai may be the best type of
to describe the situation of the oceans.
Haiti from the period before the dinosaurs.
They have survived
four Holocaust.
Stocks of sharks has declined 90 per cent
in my generation.
I followed in Indonesia evänpyytäjiä,
which were transferred from the camp to the other.
One morning
shallow coral reefs reflected something.
The sight was horrible.
Beautiful ruosteviiksihai,
which the fins were cut off.
It tried to swim but could not.
It was heartbreaking.
This is a fact which no one realizing.
Behind, about 200 meters away,
is the biggest evänkäsittelylaitos.
I called one type.
Can we get inside the factory?
-I Have contact.
Shawn has an interpreter.
He has covered work in China
decades.
First, he took us to a place,
which they reached for the first time.
It was like a Hong Kong
supermarket endangered species.
Me and Paul have done a lot of work
get to the factory.
We have received
only our feet in the door.
Hello! Why are you still here?
I told the filming!
The staff pushing us out of
and threatened to call the cops.
Hands, Machete...
We were kicked out.
According
I took a couple of colleagues Hump-raid.
Heather Rally
makes us a cover job.
Charles Hambleton
lead to mask my mission.
We came up with the cover story. We put ourselves
kulinaristimatkalla.
We are looking for exotic products.
We are gourmets study visit.
We take pictures of food.
With buttonhole camera
may have to rat trap in China.
If you come up against the authorities,
tear off all the equipment.
Let's go in!
What business
you are practicing marine living?
We base our company,
which sells seafood. -As?
We Conversely, sold tuna,
marlin and swordfish.
They want to see something exciting.
Aasialaisturistit are a big target group, more than 50 per cent.
Should we leave?
-Tulkaa Only. I will present locations.
A great entrance.
Should go to the toilet. Thanks.
Hain Begging is difficult.
If it is successful,
shark each part can be sold.
We do not throw away
a single piece of meat.
Many ekoihmiset
realize our right.
They think that we fin
and leave the shark to sink into the pain.
That's not true.
This video has been made by ekoihmisten.
This is the worm.
It is very expensive.
Price per kilogram is $ 44800.
Of $ 44800,
but it is the wholesale price.
They believe that it improves
cancer.
The Chinese have a lot of beliefs.
We ended up with another
hongkongilaisvarastoon.
Evia were guaranteed 10 - 20000.
The plant was one of the largest in the world.
It was insanely big.
I have not seen anything like it.
Jesus...
The world is a crazy place.
I remember diving trip to the Galapagos
northernmost islands.
Darwin and Wolf islands are,
where Darwin was not the case.
It is a place BC,
before human arrival.
A huge whale shark swam up to me,
and followed by dolphins.
It was a film camera time.
The screen was filled with animals.
Dolphin circled in front of the whale shark, the tuna was caught
-
Brought it to me, shook it
and swallowed its tail above.
It was a moment when I wished that
36-exposure roll of 37 images.
It was magical.
Underwater photographer,
or photojournalists -
Document the time and place -
Which is not in the future may not exist.
The clock is ticking.
When I described the "National Geographic"
for the first time in 1960, -
I took seven or eight squares
6 x 6 Ektachrome film.
Connector them together, and I made my first
color panoramic photo of reefs.
When I returned to the scene in 1989,
beautiful reef was gone.
Often contribute to the extinction of the human toimet-
Such as the destruction of the habitat
or overfishing.
Then there is global climate change.
It is, therefore, the human direct actions -
And indirect actions
climate change in the form.
The oceans regulate the climate.
The oceans are the boss.
Now, the oceans are slow to change.
It is a threat to the modern era.
Environmental Change
to promote joukkosukupuuttoa.
We are changing the environment in such a manner exactly
-
That can trigger a disaster.
Joukkosukupuuttoja has occurred
five. The reasons are varied.
All have been
one thing in common:
A huge increase in the amount of carbon dioxide.
Current carbon dioxide spike
is the largest in history.
We burn fossil fuels -
Which has accumulated hundreds of millions of years.
Translate geological history
direction of travel of a blazing pace.
Gulf of Mexico oil accident year
about 4.9 million barrels of oil.
It is a quarter of the quantity of oil,
which the USA is used on a daily basis.
Gulf of Mexico accident was US
of history's worst environmental disaster.
It is nothing alongside the devastation
that we achieve every day.
I have the worst culprit.
Shooting is the worst,
things you can do to the environment.
We estimate two years of filming
carbon footprint.
Horrified it,
how much energy consuming job.
We are making our lives even better
ourselves thinking -
But we do it at the expense of the future.
The problem can be solved in many ways.
We living what we fast enough?
Homma has gone out of control.
The chemical composition of the seas
becomes frighteningly fast.
When we
carbon dioxide into the atmosphere, it stays there.
One-third or even half of
is absorbed by the oceans.
Carbon dioxide forms carbonic acid with water.
Sea acidified year by year.
If you want to know what it causes,
drop the shell etikkalasiin.
Numerous species can -
Simply dissolve in the human acidifying the sea.
Northwest Pacific Ocean
Mass Death has already begun in the seas.
It is well under way.
Are those maggots?
Those brown stains.
We collect annually
7 to 10 billion osterintoukkaa.
Send them to breeders
northwestern Pacific Ocean.
I remember the day when all
toukkamme were bottom of the tanks.
Six billion larvae
died in one day.
Washington and Oregon represent
deep seawater flowing breeding -
And oysters
unable to increase its bark.
The shell dissolves more quickly than
grow.
It seems kind of crazy to think
that the sea can be so sour.
It seems the future Threat
and current problems.
Change in the rate of Mer -
And the change it causes food chain
-
Is dramatic and takes place
in our lifetime.
Some foods are no longer available -
And we may need to eat
even jellyfish.
It will be a new trend.
It sounds funny that
diet change would save the planet -
But if people undertake now
vegetarians, the change would be enormous.
Contribute to the extinction of most is
destroying habitats -
Or we will apply
in order to get food.
What's more, we use
meat, milk and eggs -
Generates increased
carbon dioxide and methane emissions.
Livestock and all ruminants
produce methane -
Hay and other food digestion
-product.
Contractions push the gas out of the abdomen.
The gas passes through here.
-And We collect the bag.
How long will the bag is collected gas?
-just Two hours.
Methane impact on climate change
is a 22-fold -
Compared to carbon dioxide, so
even a small amount of methane affected.
Cow to fill a 200-liter garbage bags
methane every day.
One cow is not a problem, but they must
1.5 billion.
Very inefficient food production.
75 percent of cropland is
is used to feed livestock.
Land cleared for livestock pastures,
for the food and transporting.
Cattle
cause more greenhouse gases -
As the transport sector in total.
There is one problem is not another bigger.
The same is like asking -
Whether global warming worse
as ocean acidification -
Or large fish fishing
worse than the pollution of the sea.
It would be silly
solve only one problem.
Contact to solve all of them.
Illegal animal market
Guangzhou, China
Rodents.
Home Cats.
That's still alive.
The doors will be closed.
Lights go out.
Frightening. We do not welcome.
The Board of Directors closed the
animal markets in southern China in 2002.
Trade began to visit
secretly in the early hours. Horrible thing.
Square closed.
-Animals Hidden.
Oh my God!
This market changed seats twice
within a year.
They know it to be wrong.
What is dangerous and illegal,
it syrjempään activity is hidden.
I'll show you one thing, Louie.
Bags must
ten giant manta rays.
Ray gets one chick
every couple of years.
A few years ago
streets began to appear stingrays -
Areas, which were sold before the sharks.
Stingrays can not make shark fin soup
-
And their meat is tangy tasting.
Why heavy stingrays
being dragged countries?
I did not believe my eyes,
when I saw a long line of big stingrays.
I was wondering what it is about. Thus,
How to Skates and rays cut from the gills.
Gills is removed.
Where do they leave?
It turned out that it was a folk medicine
South China coastal city -
More than 50 years ago.
The drug was somewhat lost,
but after the outbreak of SARS -
Someone came up with,
that sharks are running out.
What else can we offer?
Administration published
years ago in a book -
Chinese medicine
use of animals.
It was told how to skate
gills can be treated diseases.
Gills ended
Chinese shops -
With the sale of medicines
or dried seafood.
Gills were believed to improve blood circulation
, treating bruises and vammat-
Healing and cancer.
Deviated folklore.
I'll never forget the first
my encounter with the skate.
I sat in the water, the ray
suddenly swam over me.
It disappeared on their way.
I was left gasping for breath.
Some time ago we were in Bali.
The end of the last dive -
Rays swim beneath and missed
place five meters.
I wonder why it did not move.
In the body fluttered fishing line.
I swam over to it and switch to the line
above the hook.
I swam to the surface.
It did not go off
but remained below me.
I went back over to its
and stretched out my hand toward the hook.
I took off the hook slowly
of its upper jaw.
That's it.
I thought it would leave on their way.
It circled beneath my feet.
I returned once more to join
and I put my hand next to a wound site.
I patted it like to speak,
that there is nothing to worry about.
I put my head next to the eye.
Its eyes moved back and forth.
It knew that I was trying to help.
People often ask,
what one person can do.
What if you could see how
shark fin soup is done?
If you could see how 70 million sharks are killed because of
soup each year?
Would you eat the soup yet?
I gave the footage in Indonesia
what I saw the shark Wild mother -
To protect sharks in China.
More than a billion people saw the film.
Of them, 80 percent said
vacating shark fin soup -
Or reduce the eating
a minimum.
When buying stops, the killing can end
.
Still portraying this image of power.
It made a difference.
Need to take care of future generations
's in our genes.
If we find the right bus -
Reach people in an instant.
We will change them.
The human eye sees a small strip
electromagnetic spectrum.
Like home would be a grand piano,
but hear only one note.
The human eye does not see carbon dioxide.
Carbon dioxide and methane absorb infrared
certain wavelengths.
This camera has a color filter -
Which allow us to see from the nose and mouth
future carbon dioxide.
We have two cameras.
One camera sees the same as the eye.
Another what fossiilipolttoaine-
companies do not want people to see.
Carbon World.
Horrific but beautiful.
Turn left.
Dial to the left? Slowly.
About all we do
cause carbon dioxide emissions.
Houses the heating and air conditioning -
Passage of airplanes, trains and cars.
All produce huge amounts of carbon dioxide.
You can not see.
Secret world Seeing
seemed like a magic trick disclosure.
Magic trick that will kill the planet.
Like a big parade's trash.
-Save.
What are doing?
-I show. Translate from evidence.
The camera shoots carbon dioxide.
Government commissioned or your own project?
-My Science project.
Our generation is the last
a hand to twist the throttle lever.
atmosphere so much carbon dioxide and methane
-
The baby boomers generation
may well be -
The most important mammal generation
Earth's history.
During Antroposeenin everything changes.
Earth's geology,
chemical composition of the oceans.
Antropos means that the country
ball's fate is in our own hands.
When you take a drop of ocean water
and looks at it under a microscope -
It contains a huge amount of
beauty, pienoisarkkitehtuuria -
A view I will never tire of.
Boris Worm published important
controversial writings -
Reduction in phytoplankton.
When I speak of plankton, I call on the first
pull twice persons.
The second breath
comes from the sea.
Phytoplankton produce half of the oxygen we breathe
.
Man sea change in many ways -
Fishing on climate change and acidification.
No part of the sea is not left
from human activities.
Satellite images and research data on the basis of
-
Worm fell that we have completed
lose 40% of the phytoplankton -
During the last 50 years.
It is mainly the result of climate change.
It's a big thing,
which involves a lot of controversy.
If the plankton will be reduced so dramatically as we believe -
It is a big deal.
Our lives are dependent on the oceans
breathe.
Animals were able to live on land only after
-
The marine plankton was produced by
enough oxygen for them to live on.
Imagine that
the big environmental issues are important.
But if we lose the small things,
all else fails.
We have a fabulous tangle with
all of which are connected to each other.
If you remove one small part of
even plankton -
Whole tangle of collapse.
Like to listen to the symphony -
Where the orchestra is removed
player at a time.
Even the sounds of the past.
And then it's gone.
Most of the world is fighting for the preservation of the species
-
, And he will destroy
, at least 600 individuals a year.
That's treatment.
Paul found a man,
who smuggle endangered sharks.
Basking shark and whale sharks
.
We can get to rub shops
omega 3 oils.
What should I know about fish oil?
-We Want to ensure the quality.
Ask for samples. -I Am angry
and pushy. You calming.
We are from Brooklyn by hand.
-You Decide on the place itself.
Haiöljystä made
omega 3 products, -
But these sharks are threatened with extinction -
And are protected by
China and elsewhere.
CITES is the only law,
that protects endangered species.
Meeting decides
Trade in Endangered Species.
The menu is only a few hundred animals.
It is partly explained by the fact that the
people who päättävät-
Selling living animals.
... A new decision-making body,
which is developing the system -
International trade in ivory
to start after the break.
The economy has been in the doldrums
and interested people few and far between.
Mr. Sawyer is interested.
He said that the basking shark oil
is the highest quality.
Will we, the small sample?
Recently I received a small amount.
-I My people not tested it.
I am using their own lab.
Vien Louie aside for the moment.
Asked with just a...
Replace button Up button closed.
Microphone and tape are displayed.
Oh, Jesus...
Did he see it?
-I do not know.
After all, five years, say,
that fished all whale sharks?
In this area is the future,
that's for sure.
Now we sell
ten metric tons to Italy every year.
Shark Meat.
Smuggle shark meat
out of the country.
I can show you.
One hundred percent whale sharks.
We went to look at the processing plant.
Flooring was a whale shark fragments.
We started to describe.
We published a global press release.
Story captured the National Geographic,
Time, BBC, all possible media.
Chinese administration takes a lot of work
for the benefit of endangered species.
Ivory burned -
Official banquets
does not offer shark fin soup.
Things are going in the right direction.
I hope that they will go to stop the action
Mr. Lee.
Pahaltahan it seems, but the
end of the tunnel may be light.
People change. The direction is the right one.
Do not be so depressed.
If things change a little bit
our lifetime, this is worth.
It is easy to point an accusing finger at China
.
It destroys the earth, contaminates
and kill the species from extinction.
Equally, the West makes the splendor of the work -
Damage the environment and destroy endangered species.
China is experiencing similar growing pains
as we aikoinamme.
Our growing pains
time on Earth was one billion people.
Now China alone has 1.3 billion people.
We've driven many species to the brink of
and the destruction of the environment.
We can not afford
repeat the same mistakes -
Because soon there is nothing left.
The container has
rare amphibians.
More than half of amphibian species could disappear over the
next 20 years.
Frog species reside 7000.
All of them are endangered.
PhotoArk is my business to describe
all living species in captivity.
It is one man's desperate
attempt to get people to forward.
There it is.
Our final Ecnomiohyla rabborum -lehtisammakko.
The fungus killed them in Panama.
It is the last of its kind.
As a result, the species will become extinct.
You lift the chin a little bit?
Well done.
This is a great moment.
Many animals get my help, nation-wide visibility
before the extinction.
This is their last opportunity.
I hope that PhotoArk work
only as an archive of lost animals.
I hope that people will be attracted
and fall in love with these animals.
Turtle species is only 330 - 340.
Half of them are endangered.
If the Earth's temperature rises even slightly
-
Them are threatened with extinction.
This is a last resort.
Keeping
endangered animals in captivity.
Such an animal or wildlife in general -
Can compare the world's finest works of art.
It outperforms by Picasso, Matisse and Warhol
even the best works.
Life wants to flourish.
DNA wants to continue.
We have to be part of it.
Why would we want to destroy the thing, which
evolution took billions of years?
Trees fall into the lake -
Because the permafrost is melting.
Earth's Arctic regions
below the lakes and oceans -
Massive amounts of frozen methane.
It has been there for millions of years.
This is bubbling in the lake
a lot of methane.
Bubbles can be set on fire.
The pupils are aware of the destruction,
that killed the dinosaurs.
Paleontologists investigating
permikauden destruction.
It is the worst of earth's history, destroyed,
which destroyed almost all life.
It's called a big death.
The meteor caused the Cretaceous-destruction -
But what killed
land and sea animals permikaudella?
Now begins, it seems that the culprit was
methane.
The Arctic region is warming up. Methane
has been under the ice for millions of years.
It's starting to emerge.
When the process starts,
the effect is uncontrolled.
Unmanaged climate change,
which can not be stopped.
Methane problem can only control
reducing carbon dioxide emissions.
They warm the Arctic
and release methane.
Oil companies like ice melting
opportunity to drill more holes.
We do not realize, that the
under the ice lurking threat.
Rapid climate change
was even before humanity arise.
They did not go for millions of years
but three to four years.
Payment of the Mortgage will take longer.
Children's college will take longer.
What if the temperature rises
about three degrees in three years?
As a result, the oceans will die.
When the oceans begin to die, the Earth
can not conduct business as usual.
When that happens, all life dies.
This is a mass.
Indonesia is one of the most remote island.
It is located at the point where the sea
becomes narrow canals.
Whales, dolphins and all kinds of
animals pass down the aisle.
End of the island is
village called Lama Kera.
In the world there is no other seats -
Which killed as many stingrays
than that in one village.
Rauskuongelma had to solve
skull's seat.
Manta rays.
The package is 20 - 40.
The package costs about $ 20.
One gets a pair of skates package.
Gills get 500 - $ 600.
There's gills.
Cartilage is sent to China,
where they are crushed pills.
Glyseriinisulfaattitabletteja view of joint pain.
We met the master.
Fishermen believe that the coming
prohibit rauskunkalastuksen.
If you came Lamakeraan
animal protection matters -
Community hopes that you offer
alternative solutions.
Rauskunkalastus is the main source of income,
which we pay for our children's education.
We can not engage in agriculture.
We can not grow anything.
They did not take us
warmly received.
We had talked ourselves
fishing vessel.
Ask them how they got the skate.
After a couple of hours trip
reflected on the surface of the black character.
The blood colored the water.
Ray was fighting killed
hours.
I watched it and wondered
I can not watch.
He hit the skate blade to the brain.
Its soul disappeared before my eyes
and its body went limp.
Come on, Paul. There is nothing to panic.
When we returned to the village,
drove past us many boats.
Boats surrounded the rauskuparven,
villagers who had come to the field.
They began to beat off the gills.
Merchants offered to them
diesel engines -
And to the sales chain in China -
And the village developed into a powerful business enterprise.
Manta rays disappear in a few years.
They know that the rays are reduced.
They tajuaisivat without us,
that change is needed.
What their children are doing?
There's nothing left.
A touch of magic will disappear.
Without these species in the world is empty.
200 years from now -
Sounding out people this period -
And are wondering how to
this time people-
Gave their
magnificent animals disappear.
I or anyone else is in vain to save
unspoiled places -
If people are not taught to be better stewards
-
Than we have been.
If we lose hope,
hope is lost.
Without hope, people will sink into apathy.
Things that are worth fighting
is still a lot.
Chinese River Dolphin was disappearing
twenty years ago.
They had left a few hundred.
I thought that someone is doing something to save eläimet-
Who had both of its kind
sect that last.
Surely someone, somewhere, to save them!
It is mandatory that they do not die out.
Now they are gone. They died
extinct in my lifetime.
Always think that someone else
to save endangered species.
Protected Kissimmee Prairie region
This field is one of the last places,
where you can see heinäsirkkusen.
Sing in males is
from year to year less.
We now
sirkkusta about 20 years.
Before the 150, now 20.
Finding Sirkkunen more difficult.
Did you hear?
-That Is heinäsirkkunen.
Zoos spoken
phasing out.
When a species is no longer viable
captivity -
It will be removed in stages.
Let it sink into extinction.
There it is.
-Kiinni Stayed.
Elephants, pandas and rhinos
will not be deleted.
But how do people get excited
small, brown bird?
Sirkkuskuvani ended
"Audubon" action.
When the US Fish and Wildlife agency
saw it -
Heinäsirkkusen
a $ 30,000 annual grant -
Rose this year to 1.3 million.
Money is carrying out research
and try to turn the stem growth.
For me, photography is not intended to
not only to introduce some beauty.
It is a weapon.
How do you think the Ady Gil got the time
one of the projector.
I wonder how us to extend the pattern.
When we see a dream,
we stay within certain limits.
In the dream, there are different worlds.
Early photographs were round,
as televisions.
Media wanted more out of
and it was decided to make a box.
Box determines our way of thinking.
I have always increased the instrument
million parts.
It has become something else.
Grand Mosque United Arab Emirates
Sydney Opera House
Travis has made projections
the world's most famous buildings.
My dream is to get the "National Geographic
'photographers pictures -
And to bring their message to
a completely different order of magnitude.
The whale could swim in the bypass
And jump to the next building.
Haiti on Wall Street
is a great idea.
What do you say?
-Onnistuu.
Cities and non-residential buildings
cause 80% of greenhouse gases.
Tony Malkin owns all know,
the Empire State Building.
He has made it ecological.
Building in was considered outdated.
Renewed the 650 window,
switched to LED lights valoiksi -
Renew the heating and cooling systems.
Saving EUR 4.4 million per year.
The benefit is the best incentive
eco-friendliness.
I would like to project into the woods.
Full rakennusko?
-Yes.
We can also draw projectors
moving cars.
Travis drew a picture of the car,
which the projector paid.
Plan opened up entirely new opportunities.
Environmental Activists
may not be the only ones -
Who want to get rid of
fossil fuels.
All need to be involved.
I heard on behalf of the environment speaking
racing car drivers.
The sport not traditionally
transmitted to the environment.
He proves the claim to be false.
When I ask the PR firms
to look for sponsors for myself -
And I did not want to advertise
fossil fuels, oil -
Coal, meat, animal testing
factors, furs, leather -
I considered to be wondering.
Leilani Münter overtook five cars
During the one and a half lap.
I have been told -
The correct environmentalist
devout would compete in cycling.
When my species is not interested
75 million viewers.
Tesla factory in Fremont, California
Elon Musk rebuild
rockets used -
Who visit space stations.
She is America's largest
solar cells installer -
And he built the world's best
ranked car that is fully electric car.
Leilani felt Elon Musks.
The ongoing trial is silly -
How much carbon dioxide
marine atmosphere lasts.
In order to get future -
That does not end up environmental disaster
and economic collapse -
As can be seen, if we do not give up on oil -
Need for electric vehicles.
Hereby order the car to pull.
-Otamme Against it.
Obscura Workshop
Oakland, California
It's fast.
What about when the weight is 47 pounds?
The focal length is huge.
Image was really far.
It can zoom
even 300 meters away.
Hundreds of meters away?
-Yes.
How far these projecting?
-1600 Meters.
I build you
three times louder machine.
Suddenly a great sound.
Do you not hear it?
We were inspired by plankton and cuttlefish -
Communication using light or maastoutumiskeinona
.
We used loistevalomaalia.
We can take over to a mobile projector you
, buildings, streets.
We projected carbon dioxide emissions in real time.
That is legal,
until you press this button.
Is it because legal.
-All Ready, boss.
When we export our natural town -
Inspire hope that people
rescue the animals.
Bangkok, Thailand
A number of species in need of protection.
Most people do not end up in the protection list.
After four years of campaigning -
Brought the giant manta rays
CITES on the agenda in 2013.
I'll show you the video of our work.
Hope and inspiration are reportedly
doing for money and policy.
We live in a visual world.
The figures show a lot of strength.
The room may be to talk to
fifteen different languages -
But everyone understands
a photo message.
"Protection sipped the soup."
That's the hongkongilaiskatto.
Go to the next initiative -
Who would take second annex
paholaisrauskulajit according to the listing.
The EU supports the initiative of
giant manta rays inclusion.
Also, South Africa supports the initiative.
China does not support the initiative.
Copy that. Let's get moving.
Is the seat belt catch?
-There is.
Turn right.
Run forward.
Good.
Why are you up with the car?
-Car On the roof is really light.
What image do you suggest?
-Otamme Images in industrial areas.
Why?
-Heijastukset Seem nätimmiltä.
Can we describe the smoke you?
-There Will not smoke.
But what?
Vapor.
Can we describe the höyryänne?
-Ette.
People have to understand that this generation
have to save the animals.
We can not leave the task
future generations.
We have to do it.
Matter there is no consensus.
Can I get results displayed?
The only way to bring about change
Lamakeran such as the remoteness of the village -
Is to offer alternatives.
When CITES lifted mantas
protection list -
Indonesia banned the rauskunpyytämisen
all over the country.
Stingrays can not even hurt.
It can get a year in prison.
The Act provides new opportunities.
This is our theater.
The projector is here where electricity?
Conservation
small world events, opening doors -
Often lead to breakthroughs.
Does it work? It is seen as soon as possible.
I am a fisherman.
If we continue with the current style,
rays will soon no longer exist.
They may even become extinct.
We do not want to happen.
Requests for skates and rays should be limited to
-
So that future generations would know what the rays look like.
Lama Kera!
We need our village!
We want them to see
rays in a new light.
They are far more valuable alive.
Changing the fishing culture
turismikulttuuriksi -
Feel scary thought.
We show them success stories elsewhere.
The poor places,
which were to flourish.
The film makes the effect of
children and they are the future mentors.
We care about the message that they choose.
THIS IS A Antropos,
"THE AGE HUMAN"
We make a difference.
Dying extinction of species
is increasing -
So we need more and more
such undaunted souls.
People have to understand
that the fight is worth.
As a result of the small choices can be a world in which we all want.
UN headquarters in New York
THE WORLD SINGING...
BUT WE ARE NOT LISTENING
Japan was a pastor,
whose words remained in my mind:
"It is better to light one candle than curse the darkness
."
Many people said that the game is lost.
Why is good reason to make the effort?
But as one candle
counts.
Another candle ignited
may find you -
And the way
movements originate.
The task sounds impossible,
but if you start with one thing -
Movement gets started.
If we do not buy endangered species products
made, they can not sell.
Campaign against shark fins in China
decreased demand for the fins of 70%.
Deny the endangered
MADE OF ANIMAL PRODUCTS -
IN THE US AND ABROAD
One  meat free and juustoton day
week for a year in the USA -
Correspond 7600000 The car
elimination of you.
EAT MORE VEGETABLES!
CARBON DIOXIDE spike is
HIGHER THAN EVER
Home solar panels
saving fuel -
Driving a car around the side of the Earth
every year.
USE ELECTRICITY USE SOLAR POWER
Investing in renewable energy
can turn the state economy to rise.
Germany gets 30% of its electricity from renewable energy
.
By 2050
figure is 80%.
VOTE ecological values
START ONE MATTER
Find your own story.
Translation: Anitra Paukkula
www.btistudios.fi