DANA:
It began in earnest, several years ago.
A project of such scope,
such unparalleled magnitude,
it dwarfed everything that had come before.
It was located inside a vacant old house,
in rural DeKalb County, Illinois.
The perfect cover for a classified
government experiment.
Or so we thought.
...Washington security code transmission.
Outfitted with all the latest
in motion-detection
and surveillance equipment,
the house was a virtual prison
for Dr. Arden Westmont,  the
bio-engineer in charge of the project.
A brilliant scientist,
he was chosen not only  for his
impressive genetics experience,
but also his ability  to work alone,
in an isolated  environment.
His methods, though somewhat radical,
proved quite effective.
Perhaps too effective.
A United States Defense Department
operation,
the Carnivore-3 project,
fell under the jurisdiction
of the Defense Intelligence
Agency's bio-weapons division,
a little known segment
of our great bureaucracy,
dedicated to finding
bigger, better,
and more heinous ways
to kill people.
Westmont's creation, a hybrid species
that would revolutionize
the state of warfare as we know it,
was his greatest achievement to date,
raising more than  a few eyebrows
at the Pentagon.
The Carnivore, or Carnie,
as it had come to be known...
Hey...
...exceeded all of our expectations.
It understood language.
Had developed a mutating healing system
that rivaled anything in nature,
and except for what  we thought was a minor
pheromone imbalance,
it seemed  quite controllable.
That, however, was all about to change.
WESTMONT: Okay,
Burroughs, you shit!
(GRUNTS) Take that.
That'll teach you to keep me
cooped up in this stinking old house.
Genetic lab in the middle
of nowhere.
Here, suck on this, honey.
Uh! Love it.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
What are you so feisty
about tonight, huh?
You like that
leg of lamb I got you?
(CARNIE GRUNTING)
Yeah, I'll get you
some pretzels next time.
I paid some really good
government money for that.
Your pheromone level's
a little high.
Hmm.
You need to get laid, big time.
That'll help you distinguish the
difference between fear and arousal.
Hell, what am I talking about?
I'm the one who needs to get laid.
He wouldn't know a good piece of ass
if he ate it.
(SCOFFS)
Christ!
He probably would eat it.
Goddamn savage.
Okay, Carnie,
I've got a shot for you.
We've really got to get this
pheromone situation under control,
before you're  gonna be of any use to
the Defense Department.
(BEEPING)
Okay, Carnie, come on out here.
Come here. Come on.
Carnie, give me your arm.
Carnie, quit playing games.
We've really got to do this.
Come on, bring
your arm here. Okay.
Carnie, will you give me your arm?
Come on.
Good. Good.
God damn it, Carnie.
Come here.
Carnie.
(GROWLING)
(GROWLS)
(GROANS)
Oh, that's just bloody great.
God!
Shit!
Oh, you really make my day, Carnie.
Oh, shit!
Carnie, you've really done it now.
Oh.
Oh, God!
Oh, shit!
(GRUNTING)
Oh, the bureau's not gonna like this.
(GROANS)
(CARNIE GRUNTING)
DANA:
And so began  what would become
the worst day of my life.
The creature had escaped.
It was loose in the house.
And while Dr. Westmont lay
dead in the lab,
it remained business as usual
for those of us back in Washington.
I need not remind anyone
but these proceedings carry a code Alpha,
top secret security classification.
Then we'll start with an MJ-12 update
from General Stalwart.
General?
Thank you, sir.
There's nothing unusual to report from
the Majestic-12 group.
Project Aquarius is proceeding normally.
We're continuing the selective
education program
with the EVE's help and guidance.
And all our covert operations
are on target.
What about this continued dissent among
your ranks, General?
Pardon me, sir, but if you're referring
to Agents Falcon, Condor,
or any of the others who are trying
to go public
with certain classified information,
may I remind you that during
their involvement in this operation,
they were not part of my ranks.
With all due respect, sir,
I do not feel they're
my responsibility or concern.
I believe that the DIA itself
should handle this problem.
General Stalwart, neither I  nor the
DIA have the time nor the patience
to babysit a bunch
of yellow-bellied agents
intent on destroying everything
we've worked for here.
The army is responsible for
the security of this operation.
I expect you to secure it.
Do what you have to do
to discredit the dissidents.
Silence them if need be.
Yes, sir.
Anything else, General?
No, sir.
Thank you, General Stalwart.
Now, let's move to the CV-3 summary
from Project Commander,
Dana Anderson, Fire Weapons division.
Dana?
Thank you, Director Burroughs.
Well, as of Dr. Westmont's report
at 2300 hours, last evening,
everything regarding the
Carnivore-3 project is proceeding
right on schedule.
Dr. Westmont is very close
to communication with the beast.
He also feels that it could in fact
be trained
for whatever purpose the
Defense Department deems necessary.
There still have been
no breaches of security?
No, sir.
The cover story of the house
being vacant has helped.
In fact, some of the locals
even think the place is haunted.
(ROCK SONG PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(TURNS OFF ENGINE)
SCOTT'S MOM:
Scott, honey, is that you?
Yeah, Mom, I'm home.
How was your workout?
Fine, thanks.  I'll be
up in my room if you need me.
Okay.
(HUMMING)
(ROCK MUSIC BLARING)
(LOWERS VOLUME)
Hi, Mrs. Kyle. Is Marc there?
Thank you.
Hey, man.  What's up?
Hey, did you talk
to your girlfriend?
Yeah.
Oh, is her sister coming with?
Cool.
So you still want to take them up
to the old house?
Sure. We can get in.
Don't worry.
Yeah, I'll have my brother
pick us up some beers.
Hey, a little liquor and a good skirt
will put any woman horizontal.
Especially when she's with me.
(CHUCKLES)
Right.
Okay, how about I
pick you up about 7:30
and then we'll get the girls
about 8:00?
Cool. All right, man.
I'll talk to you then.
Bye.
Yes!
Say that again!
When Dr. Westmont didn't report in
at his usual time,
I got concerned.
You know how prompt he is.
-Right.
So then I grabbed a tape from the
closed circuit recording yesterday...
You're not gonna believe
what's on there.
Are you sure that Westmont's dead?
Westmont is dead
and the creature's loose.
All right.
Get on the phone to Security.
I'm gonna have to go down there
and check it out.
And have Gary fire up
those video tapes,
because I wanna look at them
before I go.
Right away, Dana.
This is
a classified communication for
DIA Director Burroughs.
His ears only.
Codename "Mercury."
Reporting a CV-3 biohazard.
Status yellow.  Emergency.
(CARNIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREECHES)
WESTMONT ON TAPE:
Oh, shit!
All surveillance systems seem
to be online at the house.
Computer's shut down the lab diagnostics
in the environmental system.
But everything else is operational.
Okay.
WESTMONT: Oh, the bureau's
not gonna like this.
(GROANING)
That's enough.
So. Your opinion.
Is it still in the house?
My guess would be yeah.
If it went upstairs and it can't
handle sunlight,
it's probably trying
to get back into the lab.
Back to a familiar environment.
(SCREECHING)
Miss Anderson, the limo's on its way.
I'll be right there, Carol.
-Okay.
Thanks, Gary.
No problem.
Hey...
Good luck.
-Thanks.
(SCREECHING)
(BANGING)
Gary, I want those tapes of the
Carnivore lab accident last night
filed under a Delta Code, Class-B.
Mine and the President's eyes only.
Understand?
Excuse me, sir, but Delta Code?
Isn't that not to be used except...
Just do it, Mister!
Do it now!
Yes, sir.
Who did you send with Anderson?
Liddy and North, sir.
Good.
Hey, Liddy, can you believe
she fell asleep?
Yeah, she seems like the type.
I wonder if we should even
wake her up before we get
to the air base.
And just leave her.
Hmm.  We could leave her.
Pain in the ass.
Bitch.
I don't like her.
I don't like her either.
We could always shove
her right into traffic.
Don't fucking tempt me.
NORTH: You believe all that
tranquilizer gun crap?
LIDDY: That's bullshit.
I didn't modify my own weapon
to have her tell me I can't use it.
Christ!
This.
Piece of work.
I redesigned the bolt action
for a more effective blow back.
Tightened the recoil spring,
replaced the firing pin.
One of my own designs.
Adjusted the trigger bridge. Plus,
feel the weight of that baby.
Huh? Huh?
Damn!
-Huh?
Sweet, isn't it?
Gives me a hard on.
I customized the load distribution
and rebalanced the body.
I put my own stacks.
Hell, I even fabricated the clips.
Cut back on excess reloads.
And I'll be damned
if I'm gonna let some
bureaucratic bitch run my ass.
Little piece of shit tranquilizer gun.
Fuck. When I walk into that house
I'm shooting the first thing
that moves.
Bitch thinks we're going
on a fucking safari.
I heard all that.
Damn!
I say we leave her.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
MARC:
Well, are you gonna knock
on the door or what?
SCOTT: I'm not gonna knock.
It's your girlfriend's house.
You knock.
Chicken shit.
How do I look?
You look great, man.
But your shoe's untied.
Hey, knock it off, man.
Hi.
Hi, babe.
Hi. You guys remember
my sister Bobbi.
Bobbi, this is Scott.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Hi.
So, you ready?
Let's go.
So, what's this big secret
about where you guys
are taking us?
You'll see.
It's not going to be
someplace scary, is it?
'Cause I hate scary places.
No, don't worry about it.
You'll love it.
Come on.
Hey, man, did your brother
get beverage?
Yeah, I got it in the back.
Cool!
You guys got beer?
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Can we have some now?
Can't you wait till we're away from
the house, Dee?
Mom and Dad are probably watching.
Good idea.
Okay, fine.
This is gonna be great.
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
MARC: Whoo!
(ROCK MUSIC BLARING ON CAR STEREO)
Yeah!
Whoo!
After all that, I certainly hope
you hit something.
Your sister looks dead to me.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(TURNS OFF MUSIC)
Aren't you afraid we'll get caught
with all this beer?
Oh, Bobbi, don't be such a dweeb.
We do this all the time.
Yeah, it's no biggie.
So, you guys gonna tell us now
where you're taking us?
We are going where
no man has gone before.
What? Outer space?
Yeah. Scotty,
beam me up another beer.
(SHUSHING)
No! We are going to the house
of the rising penis!
DEE: Marc!
-SCOTT: Oh, Marc!
Don't tell me we're going
to the old Romero house.
Okay. I won't.
(LAUGHING)
Marc, is that really
where we're going?
Yeah.
Oh, cool!  God, I've always wanted
to check that place out.
Yeah, I know. That's why I suggested it.
I told you guys I hate scary places.
Come on, Bobbi, it's gonna be fun.
Yeah, what's to be afraid of?
It's just an old house.
Just an old haunted house.
Ooo!
I heard the old man
still lives there.
That's a bunch of shit.
Old man Romero died years ago.
Yeah. But they say that his spirit
still walks the house at night.
Guarding the house from intruders.
People have claimed to see
the lights going on and off,
weird screams coming from the basement.
Like someone being tortured.
Hey, there's talk of a wild creature
that lives in the place.
It eats people. Ah!
(ALL LAUGHING)
It's not funny, guys.
Oh, come on, sis.  Just lighten up.
At least try to
have a good time, okay?
(MOUTHING)
DANA:
We flew in to Chicago
on a government charter,
then picked up a car for the
remainder of  the trip to the house.
Naturally, the plane  was delayed.
We were two hours  behind schedule,
and I hadn't peed
since somewhere over Ohio.
Listen, guys. You think we could find
a place to pull over?
I have got to use the ladies room.
Sorry, ma'am. No time for that.
Well, then, maybe you've
got a colostomy bag
I can pee into.
Here you are, ma'am.
You can't be serious.
Yes, ma'am.
-Yes, ma'am.
Would you prefer a bedpan, ma'am?
(LOUD BANGING)
(BEEPING)
(ROCK MUSIC BLARING)
Why are we stopping here?
The house is right there,
past all the trees.
You mean we have to walk
through there?
Oh, Bobbi, come on.
MARC: Let's go.
Come on.
SCOTT: Okay.
Do you need help?
Hey, Marc, you wanna
give me a hand with some of the
stuff in the back?
Sure.
Uh, this is weird out here.
Yeah, you better watch out for
all those clowns
with machetes roaming around.
Clowns with machetes?
Or guys wearing hockey masks.
SCOTT: Get back here.
Great.
Hey, Dee.
-What?
Think fast.
What's this?
What's it look like?
A sleeping bag?
You got it.
You mean you guys are planning on
spending the night up here?
Well, if that's the plan,
you can count me out.
No way.
Oh, come on, babe.
It will be really romantic.
Mmm. We'll see.
Look, if you don't want to stay
you don't have to.
Let me take the stuff in
and I can drive you back home.
No, that's okay.
I don't want to ruin it for everyone.
But I'm not spending the night here.
Okay.
Well, we'll just take the stuff in,
in case we get cold, huh?
Yeah, right.
SCOTT: Come on, you animals. Let's go.
Yeah. Hey, you got the flashlight?
Yeah. Here.
You can have the bigger one.
-Thanks.
It'll be a nice
change of pace for you.
Oh. Comedy.
Yeah, well, Dee ain't complaining.
Are you, babe?
-No.
Not yet.
(CHUCKLES)
I thought you knew
where this place was.
I did know where it was.
I just don't know where it is.
Wait. Seriously.
Check it out.
Stay close.
SCOTT:
Would you flash on all those bats?
BOBBI: Bats?
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
I'm not kidding.
(LAUGHS)
We got some great rigs here.
You guys are just sick.
Hey, what the hell was that?
Um, it was the wind.
Yeah, it was the wind.
Yeah, it was just the wind.
DEE:  This place is creepy.
BOBBI: Yeah.
Look, it's just the wind.
It's just an old house.
Are we gonna stay out here and
look at this beautiful
structure all night,
or are we gonna go inside?
Well, you go first then.
Okay, I will.
After you.
(LAUGHS)
Come on.  Get goin'.  Get goin'.
(CREAKING OPEN)
Hey, this isn't that bad.
Oh, man, I don't know,
check this out.
Somebody really blasted this door.
No joke.
It's disgusting.
Sure could use a woman's touch.
Oh, I could use a woman's touch.
Huh?  What was that, Scott?
Nothing.
Hey, a fireplace!
I wonder if it works.
A fireplace?
See? I told you guys somebody
lived here.
Now, can we go before we get caught?
Chill out, Bobbi.  Nobody lives here.
(SIGHS) Dee, you're such a delight.
(GASPS)
You asshole!
You almost gave me a heart attack,
you son of a bitch.
Don't you ever do that again.
Payback.
It's a bitch, isn't it?
Hey, this looks like a good place
to hang out. What do you think?
Yeah, it looks cool.
Yeah, it's really nice.
Hey.
Look at this.
What's this?
Oh, it's a book!
I'm telling you, guys,
somebody lives here.
Look, kids come from school like
to come up here all the time.
Somebody probably just left it here.
I've never heard of anybody actually
coming inside this place.
Most people I know are too chicken.
Don't you think if somebody lived here,
they'd have chased us out by now?
Well, maybe they went out and
haven't come home yet.
Give me a break, Bobbi.
Where do you want it, Scott?
We really shouldn't be
eating this stuff.
There's so much cholesterol
and not to mention all the other...
Hey, will you knock it off with
all this health crap, Mr. Jack LaLanne?
That is the only food joint around
for miles.
Thought you might be a little concerned
about your health.
And we're police officers...
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
All right.
You're not here to think, mister.
You just drive.
Let me do the thinking.
WOMAN:
Sheriff Holt, come in please.
This is Sheriff Holt.
I hate to disturb  your dinner, Sheriff,
but we got another call for trespassers
at the old Romero house.
Another one?
Those damn kids never learn, do they?
No, sir.
Hey, any idea who keeps
calling these in?
No, sir.
It sounded like the same person
who calls every time  some kid
steps foot on property.
But I still can't figure out
who it might be.
Yeah. Well, me neither.
(LAUGHING)
"Me neither."
Oh, well. I guess we'll go over there
as soon as we finish eating.
Roger, Sheriff. Out.
Are we gonna roll on that call now?
What if it's serious?
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Twice a month this happens.
Like clockwork.
Bunch of kids nose around,
trying to scare their girlfriends.
They all think it's a spook house.
Hell, if I had a dollar
for every drunken, horny teenager
I chased away from that place,
I'd be a very rich man.
Hey, look. Here comes a car.
Oh, good observation, Einstein.
I might've thought it was a plane,
or maybe a UFO.
I mean, maybe he's speeding.
Go ahead.
I know you're gonna ask me.
Turn on the radar.
I got this one.
-No problem.
Five bucks says he's doing the limit.
You're on.
This one's going at least 70.
Okay.  Here he comes.
Get a bead on them, cowboy.
Oh, oh, oh!
Got 'em. Got 'em.
Oh, oh!  We got 'em.
Oh, look at that! Oh!
Shit.
How the hell did that happen?
(LAUGHS)
You kill me, you know that?
(LAUGHING)
Oh, it was real close though.
Come on, cough it up.
You're such a stupid shit.
How long till we arrive?
ETA roughly 73 minutes, ma'am.
Damn!
Excuse me, ma'am?
Can't you drive any faster?
Exceeding the posted speed limit
might bring unwanted attention
to this vehicle, ma'am.
Code-11
security precaution.
I'm sure you understand.
Oh, brother!
MARC: So when the guy gets out
of the car.
Being a nice guy, he goes around to
her side of the car
to open her door.
But when he gets there,
his eyes bulge!
He tells the girl to stay in the car.
Because there, on the door handle,
is a shiny, bloody metal hook.
(GROANS) Oh!
You see, this Hookman was right there
at the car, ready to open the door
when the guy took off out
of lover's lane.
BOBBI:  This is creepy.
Yeah, a real nice story.
SCOTT: Even weirder part
is when they went to
call the police
and the police finally got there,
the hook was gone.
Oh, great.  So this Hookman is still
roaming around someplace?
So they say.
I don't believe it.
Well, I do.
Look at all the crazies
out there these days.
I won't be surprised if
some lunatic with a hook
was running around killing people.
BOBBI: Can we talk
about something else?
Hey, I've got an idea.
SCOTT:
Oh, first one this year!
Way to go, bro.
No, man!
I was gonna say, why don't we, like,
check this place out.
You wanna do some exploring?
Yeah.
-Yeah, that sounds good.
What do you say?
No, you guys go ahead.
I'll just stay down here.
And do what, sis? Talk to the rats?
(LAUGHS)
You're gonna stay down here
all alone?
Okay.
What do you say?
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
BOBBI:
It's not my idea of fun.
Why do you want to go somewhere
where we don't even know
if it's safe or not.
(CARNIE GRUNTING)
(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Ding! Ding!
Second floor.
Lingerie to the right.
Pearls to the left.
Do you know that men think about sex
a thousand times a day?
What has that got to do with me?
I can't believe it!
Were you guys just gonna
leave me down there?
Yes.
-Yes.
That is so rude to just leave me
down there all by myself.
I can't believe that you will
not shut up.
One minute, Bobbi. Just one minute
without you whining, okay?
Hey, you guys.
Let's go check this out over here.
Let's go in.
MARC: This looks like the master bedroom.
SCOTT: No shit, Sherlock.
Hey, what do you say we come back up here
a little later, huh?
Maybe.
Be a good boy.
There's nothing in here but a bed, man.
Let's keep going.
What did you expect to find
up here, needle dick?  A Ferrari?
Oh, very funny.
You know, you're a regular
comedian, Marc.
(SLAMS DOOR)
I thought it was funny.
God!
(YELLING)
The Hookman strikes.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, you guys can't even
take a little joke.
Needle dick was funny though, huh?
My God, look at the ceiling.
Hmm. Wonder what
fell through there.
Don't go under there, something
might fall on you.
Hey, I wonder what's behind
door number two over here.
Let's go find out.
-Let's go.
Looks like this leads to the attic.
Let's check it out.
Uh, it's probably all
dirty cobwebs and shit.
What's the matter, Marc?
Getting cold feet?
Who, me?  Hell no!
(STUTTERING) But what if
the Hookman's up there?
I'm the Hookman!
Get going.
You're a creep.
It's just a joke.
(MARC SNIFFS)
I smell rotting flesh.
SCOTT: Smells like the school gym to me.
What would you do if there really was
a Hookman?
MARC: (CHUCKLES)
I'd beat his ass.
Running.
(LAUGHING)
DEE: Oh, God!
Two studs we have with us.
BOBBI: I just want to go home.
MARC:
She just wants to go home.
DEE:
Quit whining, Bobbi. Jeez!
(DOOR CREAKING)
Okay.  It looks safe.
Come on.
Stay close.
SCOTT: Hey, Marc.
Hey, Marc.
What?
Looks like your bedroom.
-Real funny.
Hey!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, this is gross.
DEE: You okay, Bobbi?
You good?
You think so?
I think so.
DEE: Oh, cobwebs.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
God! Now I'm even afraid
of my own refection.
SCOTT:
You sure you're okay?
Yes, I'll be fine.
Okay.
MARC:  Hey, look at this.
This thing is ancient.
Must be worth a fortune.
Yeah, there's probably a lot
of antiques around here.
I'm surprised nobody's
looted this place.
I bet you those stories
about nobody ever setting foot
in this place are true.
If they are, we just cashed in
on a goldmine.
Don't tell me you guys are gonna
steal this stuff.
Why not?  It's not like it belongs
to anybody anymore.
She's right. If it did,
somebody would've claimed it by now.
I'll tell you what.
We'll come back up here later
and put some of this stuff
in our sleeping bags.
Fine with me.
Hey, what do you say
we go back down
and check out
the rest of this place?
Yeah.
Who knows what we might find.
That scares me.
Mmm!
Would you come on!
Yes.
BOBBI: God!
This is crazy.
(YELLS PLAYFULLY)
DANA:  Well, thank you, God.
Now that you two boys had
to stop anyway,
I'm going over to those bushes
to relieve myself.
Meanwhile,
why don't you change the tire?
Please do something with this.
(SCOFFS)
Hey, y'all need some help over there?
Situation is under control.
Officer.
They're wearing sunglasses, Kyle.
I know. It looks like
they're either drug dealers
or government types.
Or Halloween's come early this year.
Well, from the looks of the car,
I'd say government.
A drug dealer wouldn't be caught dead
in a car like that.
You know, moon bathing is prohibited
after midnight.
(LAUGHS)
The moon...bathing.
Okay. Guess there's not a lot of moon
left anyway, huh?
Okay.
It's enough of that.  Let's go.
I don't know, Marty.
They look pretty suspicious to me.
Don't you think
we should check them out?
We have children to apprehend.
Come on, Dick Tracy.
Come on.
Let's go.
Drive.
Let's roll on out.
(LAUGHING)
Excuse me.  What are you doing?
Why haven't you changed the tire?
Well, ma'am,
we've been trained in survival skills.
Unfortunately, those skills
regard survival
after destruction of a vehicle.
Not repairs or tire changing.
You mean to tell me that neither
of you men have ever changed a tire?
BOTH: No, ma'am.
Oh, great.
Okay, boys, time
for a training exercise.
Let's roll those sleeves up
and pop that trunk open.
I can only hope that
our efficient government
has provided this car
with a jack and a spare.
Otherwise, one of you two
is carrying me to our destination.
Yes, ma'am.
Wanna do some exploring of our own?
I'd love to.
Hey, you guys.
We're gonna do a little look around
by ourselves, okay?
Yeah, no problem.
-What?
I mean, Bobbi and I can keep ourselves
occupied, right?
Don't get any ideas.
-I wasn't getting any ideas.
How can you leave me alone
with this guy?
You have to be such a stick in the mud.
Live a little.
Besides, Scott's harmless.
-Yeah, that's right.
Come on.
-Dee.
Later.
Hey, you guys have a good time.
Don't let the Hookman get you.
I can't believe she just did that.
She's always thinking
with her crotch.
Well, uh...
Why don't we just take advantage of this.
I mean, check out
the rest of the house.
Don't worry,
I won't do anything you won't let me do.
Okay?
-I know.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
I'm sorry for being such a bitch,
it's just that Dee
really pisses me off sometimes.
You mean, all the time?
Yes, all the time.
Well, let's...
Let's just go take a walk.
What do you say?
All right.
-All right?
Guess it can't hurt.
-You wanna lead?
No.
-Okay.
Oh, they really disappeared fast.
Where did they go?
(CARNIE GRUNTING)
This place is a maze.
I think we're gonna lose
Marc and Dee up here.
You know, Bobbi,
now that we're alone,
I wanted to tell you something...
(FOOTSTEPS THUMPING)
Marc and I were talking...
-(SHUSHING) Listen.
(GRUNTING)
I think they're trying to scare us.
Oh, is this another Marc practical joke?
You know, I'm really not into this.
Come out, come out.
Can we just go downstairs?
We might as well.  We'll probably just
get lost up here anyhow.
Have a good time, you guys.
(CARNIE GRUNTING)
You want a...
You want a beer?
Sure.
Hey!
What's the matter?
Those guys took all the beer.
I can't believe they did that.
Oh, look, here's one of the empties.
Oh, gross.
What now?
What is that?
God, that's sick.
Probably, Marc's idea of a joke.
Oh, very funny.
He's just a scream and a half.
Ugh!
How'd he do that?
I don't know.
I don't know!
(GROWLS)
Marc.
-What?
Look out, Marc.
What?
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God, Marc!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, my God.
(SCREAMING)
(DEE SCREAMING)
What's that?
Come on.
-Dee?
Come on, come on.
Is that Dee?
Quit stalling, come on.
Dee!
-(GASPS) Oh, God!
We got to get out of here.
We got to get out of here now.
What happened?
It's Marc...
We got to get out of here.
All right, all right.
All right, all right,
just take her downstairs.
I'll check the room.
-We got to go.
Calm down.
Just take her downstairs.
You'll be all right.  Calm down.
-You don't understand.
Take her downstairs, okay?
We got to get out of here.
(CHUCKLES)
All right, Marc.
I don't know what you did,
but you got Dee scared.
What the hell did you do?
Come on, where are you?
What are you doing here?
Come on, it's not funny, Marc.
Man, you've got me scared.
What the hell are you doing
over here?
(GASPS) Oh, my God.
Bobbi, Dee!
Get the hell out of here!
I'm right behind you.
Go! Go, go, go, go!
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
(SHOUTS)
Come on.
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS) Shit!
Oh, my God.
What the hell is going on here?
Thank God, you're here,
you've gotta help us.
Something happened upstairs.
Oh, yeah, yeah, hold on.
Sure it did?
There's this thing upstairs,
it killed my boyfriend.
There's a thing up there, Kyle.
Killed her boyfriend.
(FOOTSTEPS THUMPING)
We gotta go.
All right, no, no, no, no, hold on.
Now wait.
All right, we'll take care
of things in here, okay.
You just stay right here, all right?
(CARNIE GROWLING)
It's got Scott up in there now.
All right, now, okay, okay.
Please.
-All right, all right.
Come on.
Come on, now.
Marty, why don't I stay down here
and watch the girls,
you go upstairs and check it out.
-Hurry!
You want me to go?
Come on.  Do something.
You go look around
and I'll stay here.
All right.
All right, now shut up,
shut up!
We wanna get out of here.
Oh, yeah.  I bet you do.
You know, I'm sick
of this bullshit.
(WHIMPERING)
Be careful.
MARTY: Will you go? Go.
Go.
-I wanna get out of here.
MARTY:
Oh, will you be quiet.
Oh, please.
Why do you do this to me?
I don't wanna be in here.
Shut up.
Shut up!
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTS)
(CARNIE PANTING)
(PANTING)
(CREAKING)
Holy shit.
(COUGHS)
(WHIMPERING)
Okay.
You want to run this by me again?
KYLE OVER RADIO:
Marty,  are you there?
Oh.
Hello?
Get the kids out of the house now
and call for some backup.
MARTY:
Backup for what?
Will you just do it?
I got a homicide up here.
It's real nasty, okay.
Do it now.
Kyle, what the hell
are you talking about?
Man, it looks like a fucking wolf
ripped this guy apart, all right?
Just get the kids  out of here.
Just do it.
Okay, I'm getting the girls out,
all right?
Oh, listen, Kyle,
there's still another
kid up there, okay.
Get him, all right?
I'll be right there.
Listen, don't do anything stupid
All right, just... Just hurry up, okay.
All right, I'll be right there.
Let's go. Hey!
Hey, you come back here!
(PANTING) God.
(SHOUTS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
(GROANING)
Sending these back
for you, motherfucker.
(SHRIEKING)
Freeze!
We gotta get out of here!
What's going on?
(STUTTERING)
What the fuck is going on?
Please settle down!
We've got to kill him.
Look out!
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
Try and calm down.
I'm just going there for a little while
to look around,
I'll be right back.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(GUN FIRING)
Kyle, come in.
Kyle?
Shit.
Kyle!
Shit. Shit.
DANA:
We finally arrived at the house
to find my worst fear  realized.
Police on the scene.
I should have  called in sick
this morning.
(GROWLING)
(GROANING)
Oh, God.
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
No!
(STUTTERING)
Wait, what's the matter?
What the hell is going on?
It's got your partner,
now it's after me.
You move, you die.
Who the hell are you people?
Dana Anderson,
Department of Defense Intelligence.
Thank you for your help, Officer.
We'll take things from here.
Excuse me, miss, but...
I got a possible double homicide here
with my partner
probably killed by some crazy animal
running around loose...
I don't have time
to spar with you, Officer.
This area has been superseded
by the Unites States Government
and is now under quarantine.
I'm instructing you to leave
this area immediately.
Are you nuts?
I'm only the goddamn Sheriff here.
This is my jurisdiction, lady.
You can't have...
-Not anymore, Holt, it's mine.
And if you do not leave
this area immediately,
I will...
-Didn't you hear the lady, asshole?
This area is now subject
to military law.
Liddy, what are you doing?
Yeah, I'm a cop.
You are now considered a civilian
obstructing the security
of this operation.
No civilian witnesses,
wouldn't that be nice and tidy?
Huh? Huh?
-Liddy, that's enough.
Now let him go.
Let him go!
Oh, I love this shit.
What the hell is this bullshit?
You can't do that to a cop.
Asshole.
Who the hell
you think you are,
you son of a bitch?
Hey! You watch your mouth.
There's a lady present.
Goddamn crazy, aren't you?
He's fucking crazy.
Officer, I suggest you leave
before this man does something irrational,
and take the boy with you.
If anything happens
to my partner in there,
I'm holding you all personally
responsible, you shit.
I outta call every state cop
within 100-mile radius of this place.
In 20 minutes, this place
will be fucking swarming with police.
I mean, God damn it.
You're gonna have a lot of fucking
explaining to do,
you shits!
Goddamn defense.
Come on, let's get you and the girls
out of here.
I ain't done now, you shits!
I'll be after the whole
goddamn cavalry.
I'll find out what's going on
in that house. And... Shit!
Yeah, sure.
Liddy, what is the matter with you?
You could get us court-martialed for
this kind of behavior.
Just doing my job!
Oh, job, my ass.
-Ma'am...
All this macho bullshit.
I've had about enough of you.
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
You, see to it that civilians are moved
to a safe distance away.
Then secure this point out here.
Liddy and I are going in.
Much too dangerous for a woman, ma'am.
I suggest Liddy and I search
the place first.
Look, I'm your superior here
and I am telling you
to secure this point out here.
I told you before,
I don't want the Carnivore blown to bits
by some trigger-happy
gorillas like yourselves.
Now, let's go!
Oh, and that means you, too, Rambo.
Tranquilizer shots only.
Put away that damned Uzi.
Oh, and this is a real authorized
entranceway.
I suppose you want me
to show the general public
the secret access to the lab.
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(SHOUTS)
Jesus.
Come on, big guy, let's go check
the lab out.
(BEEPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Here's something you don't see every day.
Quiet. They might still be back here.
I thought this thing
was sensitive to bright lights.
Photo-sensitive.
Anything above 3,200 degrees on
the Kelvin scale
could blind him.
(CHUCKLES)
Can we be more technical?
Like the sun, for instance?
Yeah.
The computer keeps all the lights
balanced with dichroic sensors.
Di what?
Come on.
All right.
Edward Scissorhands
he's not, huh?
Go check the containment,
I'm calling it in.
In there?
Yes, in there.
I don't wanna go in there.
Ah!
That is awful.
(COUGHING)
DANA:
Yes, this is Agent Anderson,
CV-3 Project Commander.
Log and copy the
following information.
I'm reporting a classified perimeter,
positive biohazard.
Request that a containment team be
dispatched immediately.
This is the status
for red emergency team.
Ugh!
I have one confirmed DIA casualty.
Possibly two...
It's kinda cool.
(DANA TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Is that clear?
Bitch.
Better not sneak up on me again.
(COUGHING)
Ugh!
Area's clear.
Except for Einstein in there
stinking up the place.
All right.
He must be hiding upstairs somewhere,
let's go.
How'd it get through the funky fireplace?
The floor is
pressure-sensitive.
We were trying to keep people
from getting in here,
not leaving.
I knew that.
Look.
Oh.
It's cold.
Means it's probably been here a while.
Great.
(YELLING)
Little too much on the entrance, huh?
Hey, looks like your boy
got a little hungry.
Oh, my God.
Going in. Cover me.
I think he's dead.
We're gonna split up.
You check around here, I'm going this way.
I wouldn't advise that, ma'am.
You're my responsibility at this time
and I just don't think
it's a good idea.
You know, Liddy,
I still don't like your attitude.
We can cover a lot more area
if we split up.
Move.
Oh.
And tranquilizers, don't forget.
(MIMICKING)
And tranquilizers,
don't forget.
Tranquilizers, my ass.
That motherfucker's mine.
(RASPY BREATHING)
(CREAKING)
(CHIMING)
(SIGHS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
Fucker.
(DIALING)
Yes, sir. Agent Liddy here, sir.
No, this is a secure line.
Yes, sir.
Operation Boomerang is now in progress.
Three minutes to extermination.
Good work, Liddy.
But remember, she must die
by the creature's hands.
No fuck-ups.
I want a full report when it's over.
Yes, sir.  You can count on me.
(GROWLS)
Enemy.
No, no.
(CHOKING)
Poison.
Kill.
I wouldn't kill you.
(GROWLING)
(GROANS)
(COUGHING)
Dana.
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
Yeah.
(RASPY BREATHING)
Shit.
She's still alive.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLS)
(SHOUTS)
(SHRIEKING)
Oh, Liddy, you asshole!
What do you think you're doing?
Ignorant.
(GRUNTS)
(SHRIEKING)
(GROANING)
You son of a bitch!
I wouldn't advise that, ma'am.
You just shut the fuck up!
I'm so...
Sorry.
Liddy enemy?
Yeah.
Liddy's your enemy.
(GRUNTS)
Don't you say a goddamn word.
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yeah.
I heard gunshots.
What's the status, ma'am?
Oh, ask Robocop there.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Just like shooting squirrels back home.
What did I say about
using live ammunition,
huh?
Didn't I tell you
tranquilizer shots only?
Are you deaf and dumb?
Do you realize what you've done?
You have just destroyed
one of the greatest
scientific discoveries of this century.
I'm gonna see to it that the Defense
Intelligence Agency
hangs you up by your balls, mister.
That thing was a menace. Your life
was in danger, I did what was necessary.
That creature was no menace.
Didn't you read my report?
It only killed when it was threatened.
Then how do you explain the boy
killed in the bedroom?
Pheromones, Liddy.
The creature was
very receptive to
pheromonal excretions.
Huh?
I thought you said
you were briefed.
Well, if you had read my report,
you would know that every mammal,
including humans,
excrete pheromones when they're in
an agitated state.
Fear or sexual arousal emit
the most concentrated form
of pheromones.
The boy was either
upstairs afraid
or fooling around
with his girlfriend.
So he was killed
because he was horny.
No. It was receptive
to the scent of sexual arousal
which is the same scent as fear.
That's why the Defense Department
was so interested.
Dr. Westmont's final tests
were trying to tell the creature
the difference between the two.
Obviously, he failed.
Look, the thing actually spoke to me.
It had some intelligence,
unlike you.
And that is going in my report.
Along with your flagrant disregard
for a direct order.
Why don't you two go begin
the removal process?
The containment team
will be here any minute.
Removal process?
That's not our job!
That's an order, Liddy!
Come on.
(INAUDIBLE)
NORTH: So how come it didn't kill her?
LIDDY: How the fuck should I know?
What are you gonna tell Burroughs?
I don't know.
I'm half tempted
to just off the bitch myself.
Careful, man,
you'll blow our cover.
Yeah, yeah.
In there.
Man.
You really messed this place up!
Shit happens.
What is this?
Good shootin',
you blew him right out of his skin.
Man, don't even fuck with me.
I'm in like no mood
to deal with this.
I'm not. Take a look for yourself.
There's nothing here but a pile of meat
in a puddle.
Where the hell's the rest of him?
I told you...
Man, we're dead.
(GUN COCKING)
Boss man's not gonna like this.
We're fucking dead.
DANA:Though I'd seen
Liddy's rampage firsthand
and thought I felt  the life drain out
of the Carnivore,
somehow I knew it had survived
and this nightmare wasn't over.
It would never be over.
Carol, we've got a problem.
CARNIE: Liddy, enemy.