Are you having fun?
Yes.
You know,
you wrote this song for her.
You sure.
There is something romantic.
"Baby, I wrote this song
if fucking"
Because you've never played that for me.
I had not finished bunny.
Wanted it to be super good.
- Did you like?
- Si.
- Yes?
All right.
- And... find this.
- Si.
're So sweet.
Where did you get that?
I do not know, I think I
found in the grass.
We're leaving.
Yes.
Bunny, honey, where are you?
My God. Sweetie
Baby, you're so bad.
I know.
God.
No, no, God.
Thou soul stays with me.
FIELDS OF THE DEAD
fucking hate  Lions.
This is a shock.
Trent
could not have found a research site.
Yeah, where is that is this place?
Is an abandoned farm that
university purchased 10 years ago.
In fact, they got it very cheap.
- Yes? .
- Yes
Well, probably
there is a reason for that.
Was it the killer boyfriend, a slaughter of Indians
,
not forget the fucking death cult.
Someone must have spent some time on the Internet
last night.
Yeah, well I had time to look
things more interesting than that.
What, boobs and vaginas?
In the account. All right.
Hey guys, need to start behaving
.
You were the ones who pointed
for research.
Yes
because it is mandatory for graduation.
Coercion?
And you who are, pre-lawyer?
Yeah, well mom fawning
playing for you, Trent.
- All right.
- Burned.
Look, going to be a difficult journey know.
But we can also have fun.
We do our research,
our work during the day...
and had a fun night.
Do not let it bother you,
affection. It will be a good week.
Thank you.
The best week!
God, this weighs.
That's a gay bag.
Thank you.
Well, my bag.
Ashley!
Cheryl, are you ready for the filets
store?
Here. Thank you.
Want to help me with this please?
Thanks for the help, these things always get
problems.
No problem.
Also, this should come
my share of the rent.
I'm sorry, your rent?
Yes, roommate.
I do not think so.
Moreover, do not you want a room with Ashley
?
Ashley is not the kind of woman he wanted
to cohabit.
Would you want a room with Ashley?
No, decidedly not.
Well, I think that settles it.
Actually
Linda and I share the store.
Well, that is fine,
I do not mind sharing.
- Shop, Cheryl.
- Si.
God, do not imagine things.
's Actually quite logical when you think about it.
I mean, Trent and
Randy, obviously. Linda and me.
Obvious.
Josh and you.
Course.
Ashley
has his own shop so... we are complete.
Yes, I guess that covers it.
Yes.
So much so, no!
I have three days to take her to bed.
Hey, knucklehead,
what the fuck do I do with this?
Sit up.
Is not funny.
All this corn was infected by this disease
earlier this year.
Yes, you can see there.
Let the barn. Gather and prepare all
,
we go early in the morning.
Early?
Very early.
Remember, I'm useless before seven.
Useless opposed to... porcelain.
Hey, no shower.
No shower out here.
All right. Well, I have to shower
at least once daily.
Seriously, we're one week.
I know,
a week without a shower, that's disgusting.
We are there.
It's okay. Good luck with that.
Go find a shower. All right.
So
I'm not interrupting anything here, right?
No.
is a little cloudy in here, yes?
I care little, but do not let Trent
see this.
I say, he acts quite great,
trying to be okay with you ..
But this is her thesis project.
Yes this is fucked
is capable of killing someone.
So what touches me something?
That's disgusting.
It's not so bad.
What am I going to do?
I have to be clean.
You know, I have a plan B.
brought a hose, we can connect
to drain beside the barn,
take it to the barn, be
clean water. Privacy will also.
Will frost.
The put from morning, the sun's heat
,
but have to shower in forty seconds.
Forty seconds warm water, you can handle that?
- Forty seconds to shower?
- Yes, a shower actually.
You're an idiot?
Well, do you like that, wood?
Hi brother.
Does this still work?
This is an amazing machine.
- Well, now we have wood
tonight. - Yes
Lamp fuck, fuck..
Trent.
- God, Jones, you scared me.
- I've been looking everywhere.
Thought you returned to camp without me.
What ?, no.
I came here to find you, I
I'm looking at you.
Yeah, well, they are seven, and that's what makes
as 45 minutes.
So, what time is
camp?
In an hour or less.
Then we have time.
A little, yes.
Let's use that time.
Yes, we can... make snow cones
or something...
Steven would kill me if he saw me eating this.
Yes, I would be scared that you're neglecting
.
Because you arm is as big as my alita
You. know that he is training to be a boxer
, right?
Is in very good shape.
It's just that I also
is in good shape.
So this is how it will be,
five of us doing it all alone...
while the two lovebirds do God knows what.
Well, I bet you can guess what they are doing
now.
Moron.
I'm just saying.
Do you really think you are doing
in the barn?
Is so dirty there.
God would never do without.
Even with Steve.
Well, technically, Trent is in.
What an idiot you are!
're Back.
Hello gang, how's it going?
Randy, shine.
Hello friend. Hello.
Did you leave the computer in the barn?
You know, you took
wood for the fire?
Do not know what that means.
Did you have sex with her?
Smell sex.
Dude, that's Cheryl is very good.
Well, I think she has
eyes for one person here.
So, good luck with that.
I tell you, I see this as an obstacle
...
but as an opportunity, my friend
.
Thought you chosen sex partner to you.
What?
Ashley.
Since I was there and I've tried.
STAY AWAY.
Respect.
All the time.
You beer, my love.
You. do they talk about?
None.
Linda has a great voice.
Would be a good American Idol.
Yes, I should audition.
Yes, it should.
Should tell.
I understand.
But if you're a fan of Linda Small.
Yes, it is so wide.
I'd love to see that.
Well, once again, going for an encore.
No, I think it done.
Before that Downhill Cartwright was established,
residents
had a relationship of tension with the natives.
So these group
traveling in the region to prevent attacks.
However, travel prints
passed...
from the holy land of the Indians.
Native Americans.
Multiculturalism. Amordácenme.
They were here first, idiot.
Anyone else, Ashley?
'll Take that as a yes.
Two days after Jack and Emma Cartwright disappeared...
their bodies were found in the forest,
mutilated, in
skinned skull.
Raleigh Cartwright formed the group immediately war...
to achieve his revenge.
Later that night
inhabitants massacred a tribe nearby.
Men, women, children.
No one survived.
That's the official story,
but according to Indian legend...
Trent, by God,
Native American legend.
Shut up, Ashley.
Several days later, the men of the tribe who were...
hunting discovered his slain brothers.
Y
cast a curse on those who were responsible.
Nenwey, the worst curse, the
despicable of all beings.
Good!
Wonderful piece of land to investigate, Trent.
Yes love, I'm a little scared.
Is a story of camping
I am trying to have fun with you.
Well, how does it end?
The curse did not allow the souls to rest
blah blah blah Fuck.
This story stinks.
The scared, guys.
Where's the beer, Alex?
The forgot.
Linda, Linda hears.
"Brothers, we must avenge our
."
"We have been cursed and my loved ones have been snatched
I"
"The fault is yours, unless the person is born
not man."
"You and Cheryl must not leave me."
Cheryl arise,
Trent wants to do the job today.
Come on, get up, Trent
wants to look fit.
- Hey, you're fine.
- Yes, I'm fine.
I did not sleep very well last night.
Did you drink too much? You look stunned.
I had a bad dream about that woman
Trent spoke.
My God, that was so stupid.
All here know that stupid story.
I know, do not be so heavy on that.
Do not worry, I will not tell anyone
how pathetic you are.
Come on.
- Very hot.
- I know, a lot.
Are you done?
Ashley know, because it
take the shovel for a while...
I have to write the report of the day.
I do not use the shovel.
Thank you.
The ladies do not use the shovel.
Son 13:20 Ashley
if you're listening,
that means 20 minutes after one.
Temperature: A hot as hell.
Humidity: Probably 80%
judging by what I'm sweaty.
I hate them, they make me puke.
You can not be adopted without
give you a little back.
Hey, are you, are you guys? Hello.
Hi.
Hello?
"August 16, 1843.
I am nearing the end of my pregnancy."
"I counted the months and
afraid that this child does not belong to Raleigh."
"Nine September, 1848.
Jack is five years old and"
"is less like Raleigh
and his real father."
"Raleigh
looks so shady and I think it is"
". Beginning to suspect the truth"
"Three May, 1853. I'm sure Raleigh
knows."
"Treat Jack
more like a servant than a son,"
". And cruelly punished"
"I do not think
miss this for so long,"
"because Jack is the spitting image of his father
."
"And the townspeople notice it."
"I fear for our lives, we must flee."
Hi gang. Preparing to leave.
And Josh?
Realising pleasure.
Not for twenty minutes, so
that we should go get it.
Josh! Hey, stop masturbating
, we gotta go.
Is not what I had in mind. No?
No. Sorry.
're An idiot.
I'll get it, I'll be right back.
HMT means talk to you later, SMS.
Yes, yes, yes.
What about Randy? Hello idiot.
Seriously.
That was funny.
Josh, Josh.
God, man
I was looking for.
Hey, I'm ten feet from you.
Hey friend. Hey.
Slight Literature?
Yes, I guess, this is so fucked up.
're Really into it,
we gotta go, we go.
Good job, even you Ashley.
Finished? Yes, we finished.
Thank God, I'm disgusting.
I'm taking a shower, do not follow me.
You heard her.
How drunk was
when I thought this would be a good idea?
'm An idiot. I was thinking about me.
I have to stop thinking with my... fret.
Forty seconds, you can.
God, because I do.
34, 33, 32, 31
Anyone there?
Alex, I'm going to hit.
What an idiot!
30, 29... 26...
Shit forty seconds.
"Which truth be told"
Hey, did you hear something? No.
Cheryl, Cheryl. What is that?
Do you hear that?
I can not. Can we see how they are?
You gotta be fucking me.
Just to see you are well.
Wake up idiot.
Cheryl, what the fuck...
What the hell is that?
Cute God what the hell?
There is something wrong with Cheryl, he is talking
with something or someone in your dream,
I do not know what's wrong. Wake her.
I tried, do not know what's wrong. I'll.
Cheryl for. What are they doing?
I do not know, it's crazy.
Cheryl. Trent, come here.
Do not know what the hell is wrong.
Store Saquémosla.
It's okay.
Could stop Christ.
Cheryl, are you okay?
Say something, are you okay? We scared.
What the hell was that?
Everyone back to his tent to sleep.
Cheryl, hello,
'll take the sample or what?
Sorry, I'm a little out of my element
today
'm sure Ashley would
best research partner.
Scared me so much last night. This is A4.
So the two talked me
makeover and to each other?
Yeah, that would be the best time to
...
know Posh Spice,
my new best friend.
Yes, that whole scene Linda Blair
you had last night, definitely perfect.
It was great. We talk about
subtle power of pink.
And the majesty of
the Cosmo quiz.
Was amazing.
Hey ladies, Any of you can help me with my
"Dec State", dictated...
No. Okay, no.
Day
two sample collection. 4. Site
clear sky. Normal temperature of 80
.
Signals bites everywhere... Shit!
Was just a bug. Randy and Trent:
status of the relationship: strong.
I still wonder if I'll be able to sleep with
Cheryl.
The prognosis is currently unknown.
Ashley,
you want to lay in the sun all day or...
Yes.
Okay.
Steve will take me to the wedding of her cousin
two weeks.
And I have to look tanned,
so leave me alone.
And I do not block the sun.
Guys, guys, I think I found something.
- Man, what the hell is that?
- I'm studying agronomy,
- I'm not the fucking Indiana Jones.
- Looks like a religious artifact.
I wonder if these were lands
burial of Native Americans.
Look, okay
look but make sure you back up where it belongs.
This land used to mean a lot, so I respetémoslo.
Idiot not snore.
My God. Damn.
Where this fucking idiot hid beer?
I have never been more sober in my life
. What the fuck is that?
Shit, shit.
Fuck!
Has anyone seen Cheryl?
It was
walk through the early morning.
- Alone?
- No, Josh was with her.
- Why Josh would be with her?
- I do not know.
Why two people escabullirían
in the woods alone? Randy? ¿Trent?
- So what, we look for?
- Maybe.
I hate to jump on the bandwagon of
perverts but Alex is right.
Call them and tell them that we found on the site
5.
We are going in 20
minutes with pants.
Great.
Be a good day. A good day.
Hey, it's me.
I do not know where you are, we're leaving.
Come to the site  5, is in your map.
Call me when you get this. All right.
In fact it is much better. Now I reach.
- You are right.
- Our ferocious leader is a fool.
- And you're no better.
- Look, he stressed.
Try to be great, to inspire,
but you can not perform under pressure.
Seriously, is like a
combination of five years of work.
Well, look, we advance what ifs
really work today...
So do not bother so much...
and then we can sneak to look for these lovebirds.
Do not think you're doing, right?
I do not know, a journey of research like this...
outside in the forest, does
strangers bed partners, uh, maybe?
We'll see.
Cheryl.
Cheryl, Cheryl!
I missed this morning.
Linda tried to call 4 times.
- Where were you?
- Here.
- And this morning?
- In the barn.
- With Josh?
- Yes.
- Where is Josh now?
- He said he was going to meet you
I felt bad, so I fell asleep here
.. Did you find it?
No. I'll have to report this to
Dr. Foy and the three are going to solve it.
I know, sorry,
was stupid.
're Absolutely right, it was.
"July 15: Day two of
sample collection."
"Son 13:20 Ashley
if you're listening,
that means 20 minutes after one o'clock."
"That's what she said."
"Soil samples look promising today
,
despite my best efforts...
things are progressing well."
"Why do not listen"
"Why do not you listen to me"
"Please, please listen,
I have little time."
This is stupid. "I'm trapped here
forgotten God
and we can not go."
"Please help, this
is our purpose."
"Your secrets must be disclosed."
"
Raleigh should be known for who he really was."
"Please help, can not stand this anymore
,
fear for our lives when he finds out."
"We must flee, no, you must flee."
"Do not have much time,
Alex, please listen to me."
Here is you water. Thank you.
Can I talk to you? Yes, please.
I do not remember what happened last night.
And no.
I do not remember anything until you found me today.
- What happened to Josh?
- I do not know, there was...
You know what, sure okay, sure.
Let's do dinner.
Why do not you go to the barn and looking at Alex?
"Please help can not stand this anymore
." I fear for our lives
when he hears "
- Alex
- Yes.
- Dinner is ready
-. Thanks.
Josh  Why not have your phone
Who does that?
probably thought it would not be covered here
What is it
This is a book that Josh was reading yesterday
.
was acting really weird with it What is
I do not know, at first I thought it was a
map...
treasure was in an expedition
or something...
but when I read
is the diary of a woman.
"I think Raleigh knows, I fear for our lives...
must flee."
- What was that, Alex?
- That phrase, I swear...
I heard my recorder
some random recording,
or something like that.
A voice, what the hell are you talking about?
- Let me hear.
- It's nothing, well,
rechecked and there was nothing.
But you heard a voice.
Thought it was a voice,
well, I'm not sure.
I'm exhausted.
I can not sleep with all this shit happens.
So this is your plan, Emma.
What?
Well, what are you supposed
do then sit here...
and wait to do again. No, seriously
guys, something is happening.
Josh is a big boy.
You know what, Josh is fine.
Is probably elsewhere,
I believe that conversation...
him, that
end up elsewhere.
Is now dusk,
be here anytime. It's okay.
Yet.
- It's getting late.
- Josh should be back.
Yes, what time will it be enough
late to start looking?
About a half hour ago.
Well, yes. They need to stop, this is
seriously screwed.
Josh is there in the woods alone...
and you're not going to find
because it is dark.
I'm tired.
Shit, I'm going to pee, you have one minute
twenty-five seconds...
to organize a search party.
That's it.
There is no spider,
there is a spider's nest.
There are three, then I do not pee.
The problem is
I am trying to do something good with my life,
not depend on others, and others
not disappoint me.
Sometimes you're a little anal
, ie, we can have fun.
But you understand that the fun has no place
...
in my career. I'm under a lot of pressure.
My mother has two doctorates,
my father in chemistry.
They are very intelligent people.
It is very frustrating when I'm
trying to do the same...
but I stopped a guy...
he wants to leave the forest alone for a while.
Shit.
My God.
Boys! Guys! Guys!
Is that Linda, what the hell is that?
- I think it's just a possum.
- We gotta get out of here.
True. We have to go back to camp...
Do not leave here, the
forest, middle of nowhere...
all must come with me.
Wait, we can not let Josh
here.
Fuck, I'll walk.
Fun.
You joined by four days of investigation.
Honestly, do you love me
suspend because I want to go first?
Someone did something terrible to Josh.
See this.
All should come with me. It's crazy.
You joined for 4 days research
.
Do not you go, I need to
all the people who showed...
to help me in my thesis. This is my life.
When Josh returns, and
make, I'm going to tear,
But you do not go, dammit.
- Hey, Linda.
- What?
God, look, I talked to Trent
and agree...
to give you credit,
for what you've done...
and let you go.
I can take back to Cartwright
Downhill.
And there is a bus station,
where I think you can get...
the 11:30 to town.
Do not have to do that.
Linda, you're scared,
nobody will blame you if you go.
I know I will not.
But I have drunk so much
I can take.
Do you want to go look for Cheryl?
No, I do not know.
No, I do not know what's going on.
I dunno.
Gotta get out of here.
- I have to go.
- Well.
- OK?
Let's get your things, good.
- Take care.
- I will.
Where is Cheryl?
Are you going to miss Trent
when you go to Chicago?
Yes
Me too.
Do you want me to wait while
buy the ticket?
I'm not fine, I'm a big girl,
despite my recent actions.
Seriously, do not be ashamed, either.
Were you scared, is not that great.
Afraid?
You did not see Cheryl in the store that night.
Did you see that skull?
Seriously, there is something horrible
is happening out there.
The girls are pretty scared, right?
Yes.
Sorry you had to see that.
Shit.
This is pretty fucked up.
Sorry.
You know, you can go to bed,
I'll just wait for Randy.
You sure?
Yes. Thank you.
- See you in a few days.
- Yes.
- Let me help you with your team.
- No, it's okay, I have it.
Well, I've been really awful
you.
The last days or since I met you.
I'm so sorry. Thank you for supporting me
tonight.
- Really appreciate it.
- For nothing.
Well, again, it seems that
will rain. Take care, Randy.
Yes, beware.
- Hi.
- Cheryl, what do you do?
I do not want to be alone, not after...
Yeah, well, I understand.
- Do not think I...
- No, no. Josh is fine.
I find in the morning.
Got to be kidding, shit.
Shit, by God, I see nothing.
What the fuck is that?
God. Shit, shit, shit.
Well, what was that?
Not let him do it.
I know what it hides.
Do not let them do it!
Randy
'm just worried about you.
You should be back.
Looks like a storm is coming, hurry up please
. Bye Bye.
- Come there's Josh.
- Damn, I'm going to kill you.
Josh! Seriously stop playing.
Cheryl.
Yeah Well..
Cheryl, this is a bit unexpected
but good.
Yes.
Ash.
Run.
Trent!
Do I...?
Do you understand now?
The story has,
the truth be told.
Subtitles translated by ricardorfm
and corrected by japezoa.
: Www.SubAdictos.Net:..