"Apartment For Rent
Furnished Spacious Loft $ 700"
MANAGER
Here you go.
Well, the furniture's not new
but it's in pretty good shape.
And it's just been steamed today.
- It's beautiful!
- Yes it is.
The morning sun can be pretty intense,
especially if you're a night owl like me.
No, no, I'm a morning person.
Best light for painting.
You an artist?
Well that's what I'm here to find out.
Well, then this place
is perfect for you.
Quiet building...
Nice neighborhood...
A fairly nice neighborhood...
considering the area.
Besides,
you got me.
Right next door.
Yeah...
So...
The bathroom is over
here behind the stairs.
And the bedroom is
right upstairs in the loft.
Is this the only closet?
Yeah, I'm afraid it is.
This... used to be a real wood
burning fire place here...
but now it just operates on gas.
You know...
no fuss no muss, huh?
I'll take it!
Great!
When would you like to move in?
Next week?
That soon?
Okay well, you can sign the lease
now and Elaine can sign it tonight.
- Elaine?
- My wife.
She's the one that
actually owns the building.
And I guess should warn you...
She's a bit... eccentric.
- What do you mean?
- Oh!  She's harmless...
It's just that she still
thinks that it's 1969.
You still want to move in?
I... yeah!
Well then.  Welcome, neighbor.
What's your name?
Paige Benedict.
Paige... well, I'm
Jonas Lowrey.
If you need anything, you
call me... day or night.
I think I'll be fine.
Thanks.
Oolaa...
You're the new girl in unit "C" right?
Yeah, and you must be Jonah's wife.
How did you know that?
Lucky guess.
Elaine Lowrey.
Paige Benedict.
And this is  Doo.
Far out!
He likes you.
Oh boy!
I named him after the song...
The song?
You know?  Me and you
and a dog named "Doo".
Well, I think the song is
"Me, you and a dog named Boo".
What...?
No...
Who name their dog "Boo".
That's a a stupid name.
Isn't it, baby?
Yes it is.
Wow, that looks like it weighs a ton.
Yeah.  Feels like it too.
What are you standing here
rapping with me for?
Get it inside before
it breaks your back.
Good idea!
Thanks.
Get a grip, Paige.
It's only a Ouija board.
Okay!
The phones all hooked up.
You got any cold beers in there?
No.
All I got is a coke.
Oh!  That's all you got.
Hello!
Anybody home?
YES
Hello?
Is there anybody there?
Is there somebody here?
Oh my God!
These things really work?
YES
Who are you?
S... U...
S...
A...
N...
Susan!
YES
Hi Susan,
I'm... I'm Paige.
Hello
What are you doing here?
P... R...
O...
M...
A promo ...?
A promotion!
You know about the promotion?
Am I going to get it?
Susan?
GOODBYE
Sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
Mitch, what are you doing here?
You forgot this.
I thought you might
need it for your CPA exam.
And really, Paige...
the question is...
What are you doing here?
I mean... look at this place,
it's a dump.
It's an artist loft...
And living here is going
to make you an artist...
I am an artist!
Why?
Because you did a couple of
drawings when you were a kid?
You know, if you really
wanted to paint, Paige,
you could have just set
your stuff up in the garage.
You didn't have to move out.
You don't understand...
Yeah, you're right, I don't understand.
Why don't you explain it to me?
I tried to...
You wouldn't listen.
Well, I'm all ears now.
Mitch... I...
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Can't do what?
Mitch, please!
Talk to me, Paige!
- I can't!
- Just talk to me, God dammit!
Excuse me.
Is everything alright in here?
Yes, everything's fine.
You know, man...
maybe you should go find yourself
some business or something...
because right now
you're in mine, okay?
Well...
Actually this is my business.
You see, my sister
owns the building...
And , I'm pretty
sure she has a policy
against her tenants being harassed.
So?
So.
You're not really going to
make me call the police, are you?
I am the police.
Are you still here?
25-O-5,
Right?
What?
Your badge number.
I just want to make
sure I had it right.
So, when you call your superiors
so I can tell 'em...
what great work you're doing
for public relations down here!
Thanks.
- Russell Upton.
- Paige Benedict.
You must have a whole hell
a lot of unpaid parking fines...
No... he's my ex-boyfriend.
MENTONE & SONS
ACCOUNTING FIRM
Carla?
Wait.
Hold on a second.
Have you seen my books
for the Eden account?
I left them on Henry's desk
last night but he can't find them.
Why are you asking me?
Well I... am...
you were the last one in there.
George, I'll call you back.
Okay.
What are you accusing me of?
Nothing...
I. .. I just... um
Well you know...
we're both up for this
CPA position, and I...
Listen to me, Paige...
Do you really think I
need steal your work
in order to beat you
out of this promotion?
No!
I don't... know...
I guess not.
Then why don't you go and
look for it somewhere else?
Oolaa!
Have you met any of
the other tenants yet?
No... not yet.
What about the guys behind you?
You haven't heard any strange noises?
Oh, what do you mean?
Well.
They claim they're just roommates,
but I have my doubts.
Not that I would
say anything though
because like I don't dig gossip.
Not like Wanda Esbell.
Who?
The writer in unit "B".
Never smiles.
Never sets foot out of her apartment.
Never has a pleasant thing
to say about anybody.
You know everyone in
this building, don't you?
I am the landlady.
Did you ever know anyone named Susan?
You mean Susan Sidney?
I. .. I don't know.
Or maybe ...
Did she use to live here?
Two years ago.
Why?
I found a Ouija board in the closet...
Hi, Paige!
- Get settle in okay?
- Oh yeah, thanks.
Oh, Christ!
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, it's okay.
Listen, I'm the handyman around here.
So if you ever need anything,
and I mean anything,
just let me know.
Ahhh... thanks.
You're making a fool
of yourself, Jonas.
Come on.
The shower drain is clogged again.
It's because you keep washing
your goddamn mud in there.
Well, I have to clean him, don't I?
Well, hose him off in the backyard.
He's a dog, for Christ sakes!
Shhh!  He's sensitive...
You know he doesn't
dig being called a D-O-G.
Come on, Doo,
Mommy and Daddy are going upstairs.
Elaine, you get way too
many drugs and weird stuff.
Russel!  Are you crazy?
You nearly scared me to death!
Yeah.
My death.
I'm... I'm... I'm
so sorry.
God I'm sorry...
Oh God, it must have hurt.
I don't know what came over me.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Yeah!
Kill me!
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to laugh.
Oh here, let me.
There.
How are you feeling now?
Better?
Oh, yeah, yeah!
I always welcome new
tenants by writhing around
in the dust and he's
groaning in agony.
I still can't believe I did that.
I'm usually not that aggressive.
What are you doing
down here, anyway?
Checking the boiler for leaks.
Shouldn't Jonas be doing that?
He is the handyman, isn't he?
I'm the handyman is more like it.
You've got a great
face, you know that?
I'm not coming on to you.
I'm a photographer.
Would you consider
posing for me some time?
I don't think so.
I'd be way too self-conscious.
Okay I don't to push it.
But ...
Here is my card.
In case you change your mind.
Did Susan Sidney pose for you?
- You knew Susan?
- Uh, Elaine mentioned her.
Figures.
There's 3 forms of mass
communication around here.
Telephone, telefax and tell-Elaine.
What was she like?
Susan I mean?
Smart, sexy,
totally independent.
And very tough.
She'd kicked me just like you did,
but she never would have apologized.
So what were you and Elaine
talking about her anyway?
I found a ouija board and
I think it might be hers.
Probably is.
She was really into
all that occult stuff.
And yes, she did pose for me.
I can't believe I'm doing this...
Susan!
Are you still here?
Susan?
Susan, is your last name Sidney?
YES
And, um...
this is your ouija board.
YES
What are you doing here?
A...
R...
T...
I...
S...
T...
Artist?
Are you an artist?
H...
E...
L...
P...
Help?
You need help?
Or you mean you're here to help me?
Susan?
Susan, what do you mean?
Whoa!
Who did that?
Susan, what are you doing?
What the hell...?
Susan!
Are you alright?
E...
D...
N...
Eden?
The Eden account?
You know where my books are?
C...
A...
R...
L...
A...
Carla?
That bitch!
EDEN COSMETICS FISCAL YEAR 1993
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
This is my office, my desk!
How dare you come in here like this.
- And you get out of here before...
- Shut the fuck up.
If you ever...
pull a stunt like this again,
you're going to need a calculator and
count all the teeth you'll be missing.
Hello!
Paige Benedict.
Paige!
It's Mitch.
Listen, I think we should talk.
Mitch, I'm at work.
Well, you wouldn't talk to
me in your apartment, so...
You weren't talking,
you were yelling...
and I'm not putting
up with it anymore.
Damn it, Paige!
Just listen to what I have...!
UPTON PHOTOGRAPHY
Russell Upton
Beautiful, Paige!
... Beautiful!
Now be sexy.
This is the sexiest I can...
Come on!
You're not even trying...
It has nothing to do with trying...
- I'm just not sexy.
- I don't believe it!
Here, lick your lips!
I said lick them, not swallow them.
I'm sorry.
I just feel silly...
That's because you're posing.
Try to be more natural.
Pretend I'm not here.
Oh!
Easier said than done.
Okay
Then, forget the camera.
Just talk.
- Tell me about yourself.
- What do you want to know?
- Whatever you want to tell me.
- Okay.
I'm an only child, born and
raised on a farm in Indiana.
My parents were very
old fashioned and very strict.
- I could have guessed that much.
- How come?
- You dress like Mary Poppins.
- I beg your pardon.
Perfect!
See, there's a natural pose...
Good enough for my
driver's license, I'm sure.
So how long you've
been interested in art?
Oh!  Guys lyings I can remember...
When the other little girls were playing
jump rope, I was doing charcoal sketches.
Then how did you end up an accountant?
Well, I wanted to go to Art School
and become a painter
but my father wanted me to go
to college and study business.
He said a career in art was too risky.
So we compromised.  I went to
college and studied business.
You always do what your father wants?
Until he died last year.
And then I decided to do what I want.
Move out here, and become a painter.
- So what happened?
- I met Mitch ...
and fell into the same doormat
relationship I had with my father.
And you eventually give up painting.
Well, that didn't take much.
I hadn't drawn anything in 4 years.
I don't ... sorry, it's like I have
writer's block or something.
And I'm not very good at confrontation.
At least not until today.
- What happened today?
- I don't know.
I guess I just got tired
of always playing it safe.
Is that what made you
change your mind about posing?
POLICE
CORONER
What happened?
It's Jonas.
He's had an accident.
What?
How?
The boiler.
I begged him to stop drinking...!
I begged him!
He must have been
drunk out of his mind.
She said it looked like he hit the
boiler room door with every tool he had.
Where is Doo?
Where is my dog?
I'm sure he's fine.  He's probably
in the apartment somewhere.
- Don't believe I knew!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Hello?
Paige?  It's Henry.
Are you coming in today?
You know...?  Um...
I'm really not feeling that good, Henry.
I think I'm getting
the flu or something.
Oh well, that explains it then.
I figured it had to be
something pretty serious
in order for you to
miss a day of work.
Oh, yeah!  You know.
I'm sorry I didn't call.
I slept right through my alarm.
No, no, no!
I understand.
- You just get well quick, okay?
- Yeah okay.  Thanks, I will.
Who is it?
Paige, it's me.
What do you want?
Well, I heard about the
accident here yesterday
and I wanted to make
sure that you are alright.
Can I come in, please?
Christ, you look like shit!
You came all the way over
here just to tell me that?
No.
I came over here because
I wanted to make sure
that you are alright.
I was worried.
You did this?
Yeah?  So?
Well, it's .. it's great!
Do you really think so?
Hell, yes I think so!
Paige, when you told
me you wanted to paint
I had absolutely no idea
that you were capable of...
I guess I wasn't
very supportive, was I?
Right...
Well, I should go.
I've got a watch.
Mitch!
Could you do me a favor?
Name it.
A woman named Susan Sidney.
She used to lived here about 2 years ago.
Could you find out how she died?
What for?
Okay.
Might take a couple of days.
Okay.  Thanks.
Ashes to ashes.
Dust to dust.
The Lord giveth and
the Lord taketh away.
Rest in peace, brother Jonas.
In the name of the Father, the
Son, and the Holy Ghost.  Amen.
- Thanks for coming.
- You're welcome.
Thanks for coming.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I'm glad you came.
- You look great.
- Thanks.
- I didn't see Elaine anywhere.
- She hasn't accepted it yet.
- I suppose it will take time.
- More than you know.
Our parents died in '69,
that's why she's stuck there.
Russel,  I'm sorry.
It was a long time ago.
I was just a kid.
Luckily we inherit a lot of property,
got us through the tough times.
Now if there's anything I
can do, you let me know.
Thanks.
Actually, she's better off without him.
I mean, he was a drunk and a cheat.
- Russel!
- What?
You gonna tell me he
never made a pass at you.
I suppose.
You suppose.
Trust me, he went
after anything in a skirt.
Poor Elaine !
She doesn't know.
How could she not know?
She lives in her own little world.
Reality very rarely intrudes.
Do you think Jonas had an
affair with Susan Sidney?
I know he did.
That's how she paid her rent.
And Elaine never knew?
I made sure she didn't.
And Jonas, he wasn't gonna tell her.
So how did she die?
- Who?
- Susan of course.
Susan's not dead.
She moved.
I made Jonas kick her out.
What?
Okay.
Who are you?
I know you're here.
Answer me, God damn it!
You're not Susan Sidney, are you?
YES.
Okay.
You are Susan...
How did you die?
M-U-R-D-E-R.
Murder?
You were murdered?
No...
I don't believe you.
Russel says Susan's still alive.
R-I-F-L-E   C-A-P-E.
Rifle Cape?
What's that suppose to mean?
Susan...
What does it mean?
Susan, I can't help you unless
you tell me what you want.
BYE.
- Hello?
- Paige.
Hey listen, I got
that info you wanted.
But there is no death certificate
on file for Susan Sidney anywhere.
Are you sure she's dead?
No.
Okay, I've got to run trace and see if
I can find out if she's moved and where.
And I should have the information
for you by tonight, okay?
Hello?
You still there?
Ehhh...  yeah.
I gotta go Mitch.
Okay.
That's it!
I'm through with you,
whoever you are!
This thing is going out
with tonight's garbage!
NO.
Are you sure you're alright?
Maybe we should call a doctor.
No. .. I'm fine.
I just fainted.
You did more than that...
You... You screamed like you
were having a bad acid flashback.
What’s going on, Paige?
When did you paint this?
What do you guys know
about Ouija boards?
Not much.
I mean supposedly
ghosts can spell out messages
with that pointer thing, right?
Do you believe that?
No.
I figure it's probably just
your own subconscious.
How about you?
Last week I would have said no.
It's only a game,
like checkers or chess.
But now I...
I believe it.
You do?
I'm not the only one, Russel...
Lots of people believe in spirits and
that you reach them with the Ouija board.
You can!
I mean I have!
I have been in contact with a
spirit since the day I moved in.
It claims to be Susan Sidney.
But Susan isn't dead.
Well, how do you know that?
I mean... you haven't seen
her in two years, right?
And so I've been painting again.
Susan helped me.
What are you talking about?
Susan was an exotic dancer.
- Susan wasn't an artist?
- A con artist maybe.
Halt...
There is only one way
to find out for sure.
Susan?
If you are Susan...
Are you here?
Susan?
Ladies, this is really weird.
- Hold it, Russel!
- I feel stupid.
Well, so did I at first.
That's Doo.
Susan must be close by.
Susan, is that you?
YES.
And you still claim
to be Susan Sidney?
YES.
Then you know these people with me.
Good.
They want to ask you some questions.
NO.
No?
Why not?
You are Susan Sidney, right?
U-P-T-O-W-N
Uptown?
Uptown...?
Susan, what's uptown.
You?
2-1-7   P-A-R-K-W-O-O-D
Wow!  217 Parkwood
It's an address.
Susan?
Is that where you murdered?
Come on, guys!
This is not Susan.
YES.
Then, what's your middle name?
When is your birthday?
Where are you from originally?
She's getting agitated...
Why?  Because she can't
answer the lightning round?
Or maybe she's just confused.
Oh, I am sure death
is very disorientating.
Shut up, Russell!
You're upsetting her.
Upsetting who?
This is not Susan.
That's it!
I don't think that's it all.
I'm splitting.
That was incredible!
Maybe you shouldn't
use this thing anymore.
There's a ...
map in the side table.
See if you can find
Parkwood Street.
You sure you want to do this?
Yeah ... I'm sure.
- Hello?
- Paige...
Listen here.  There is absolutely
no paper on this Susan Sidney at all.
Oh so, what does that mean?
Well, it means that when
she moved from there,
she never reestablish her new address,
not with the phone company, the
post office.  None of the utilities.
Oh, that's unusual isn't it?
Well ... not if she moved out of state.
She could have moved
in with somebody here,
who just has all the
utilities in his own name.
Mitch, what's a Rifle Cape?
I have no idea.
It's not part of a gun or something?
No.
Okay.
I can't find Parkwood Street anywhere.
What?
Mitch, do you know where
217 Parkwood Street is?
Never heard of it.
You must have, it's uptown somewhere.
No.
- Not unless...
- Unless what?
Are you sure you're not
talking about Park Woods?
Park Woods?
Right.  The Woods.
Outside the city limits,
near the Interstate...
Yes! Yes!
That must be it!
Thanks, Mitch.
I got to go.
What's up?
Are there any shovels in the basement?
WARNING!
NO TRESPASSING
You know, if I were to
list every stupid stunt
I've ever pulled in my entire life,
this would rate in the top two.
We don't even know
what we're looking for!
I think this is where
Susan was killed and buried.
Oh, man!  I have a
bad feeling about this...
So where do we start?
She said 217 Parkwoods.
That must mean something.
What do you think?  We gonna
find a sign that says 217,
the big "X" that marks the spot?
I don't know, Russell!
It's a mystery!
You don't want to
help me figure it out, fine.
But I've spent all my
entire life playing it safe.
I'm sick of it!
Now I need to do this.
Not just for Susan, but for me.
What was that?
It's footsteps.
- Someone else is here!
- Or something...
We are in the woods, Paige.
It could be a bear... or a cat.
Let's get the hell out of here.
What the hell are you two doing here?
Mitch...
Something's chasing us.
Alright, go to the
car, I'll check it out.
- No, don't go.
- Just do what I'm asking you to, ok?
Come on, Paige, let
him play Dirty Harry.
Who's there?
Here's your bogeyman.
Have you both completely
lost your minds?
Us?   You're the one
who just shot Rocky.
Hey listen, Chuckle Head.
Now is not the time for you
to impress me with your wit.
Do you understand?
Mitch...
No, Paige.
You don't even know this guy.
What are you doing out in the
middle of nowhere with him?
She invited me.  The question is,
what are you doing out here?
I was looking for Paige.
I was worried about her.
- Yeah?
- Yeah!
I wonder if wasn't you
chasing us back there.
What ?
Maybe you trying to scare...
Get her to move back in.
Your charm sure isn't gonna do it.
Stop it!
Both of you.
- You're very brave with that gun.
- Then you want me to get rid of it?
- Yeah!  Give it to me!
- Shut up!  Just shut the fuck up!
Come on.
I'm taking you home.
Are you asking me or telling me?
I'm asking you.
Please...
I'll call you tomorrow, okay?
What's happening to you, Paige?
What do you mean?
Now look at the way you're dressed...
- What about it?
- Baby, that's not you.
Same as the first time I've
ever heard you swear, ever.
Since when did you notice
anything I said ...?
Or wanted, or cared about?
I noticed...
I'm not an idiot, Paige.
I knew you were unhappy, I just ...
I don't know, I was
afraid to mention it to you
because I thought you would leave.
But I left you anyway.
Well, I didn't say it was a good plan.
It really hurt me when you left.
And you know how I get when I'm hurt.
I'm angry and nasty...
It doesn't mean that
I don't care about you.
I know.
I want you to move back in.
- I can't.
- Why not?
This Russell character, I
suppose he's the sensitive type.
- Knows exactly what you need?
- I don't even know exactly what I need.
PANPIPES
MAGICKAL MARKETPLACE
I know what you're thinking.
You've never seen
a Jewish occultist before.
Not to worry, I'm not orthodox.
First thing you gotta understand,
is that spirits are all
around us all... the time.
But they can't reach us
without some kind of help.
Like the Ouija board!
Correct!
When you use the Ouija...
you open the door...
and the spirits...
can step through.
So that's how she was
able to break my mirror?
Because we were using the Ouija.
Right!
No Ouija, no broken glass.
Couldn't that be dangerous?
Sure.
You get an evil spirit...
You could have furniture and
silverware flying all over the place.
This spirit of yours,
she was murdered.
Yes... How...?
How did you know that?
They all say that.
Being dead must be really dull.
Because they love to "talk" to us.
But they know we won't talk to them
if they're some boring
schmuck who died of old age.
So they say they were murdered.
I guess even in the spirit world,
sex and violence sells.
So what are you saying?
All spirits are liars.
To a degree, yeah.
- What's a a rifle cape?
- You got me.
It isn't some spiritual
term of some kind?
Not that I know of.
Are you sure she didn't misspell it?
- Is that possible?
- Are you kidding?
Spirits are terrible spellers.
Their communication skills in
general leave a lot to be desired.
Look...
assuming that all this stuff
isn't just a bunch of "mumbo jumbo".
How can we be sure this
spirit really is who it says it is?
You're not sure?
- Did you know her when she was alive?
- I did.
I got just the thing ... for you.
- What is it?
- An automatic writer.
You use it just like
a regular planchet.
You put it on a sketch pad
instead of a Ouija board.
And ... you stick
a pen ... in this hole.
Then this, Susan of yours will actually
have to write out her messages.
Well, what good is that?
If it's really her, it will be
her handwriting, not yours.
That's incredible!
When did they come up with this?
What's today?  The fifth.
About two thousand years ago.
They actually predate Ouija boards
been around since at least 540 BC.
Which makes them only slightly
older than my mother-in-law.
You got any other questions ...
Read this.
The Complete History Of
OUIJA
So, as soon as we get back, see if
find a sample of Susan's handwriting.
Can't wait to use this.
Maybe you should read the book first.
Find out what you're doing.
You read the book.
I know what I'm doing.
What's the big hurry?
Why can't you wait one lousy day?
- What for?
Paige, look at yourself.
You're obsessed with that Ouija board.
Russell, why do you even care?
You don't even believe in it.
No, I don't.
You were there, Russell.
You saw the pointer move
with your own eyes.
It was your subconscious,
or Elaine's or maybe even mine.
So who's subconscious
shattered the mirror?
I don't know.
But there's a logical
explanation somewhere.
Yes!
Susan Sidney is dead and
she wants me to find her body.
Promise me, you won't use the Ouija or
the writer till I read this book, okay?
Okay, Mom, I promise.
CAR  FILE
FIRE  PLACE
Hello?
Paige, it's Mitch.
Listen, I think I found
your friend Susan Sidney.
You're kidding?
Where?
Well, it seems a couple
of years ago, Parks Woods
was going to be
developed into tract homes.
The plans fell through but not before
they subdivided the land into lots.
And one of the lots is number 217.
Mitch, that's great!
Yeah... Well, I'm going to
head up to it right now.
- Okay yeah.  I'll meet you there.
- No!
Listen.  It's police business.
If there is a body out there
you're out of it, as of now.
You got it?
- Wait, I was the one who...
- No!
No "buts", Paige.
And I mean it, okay?
Okay, but you call me as
soon as you find something.
I will.
Goodbye.
Susan?
Susan are you here?
Susan...?
Susan, I have good news.
Mitch found your body.
He's driving out there right now.
Stop.
Stop?
Isn't that what you want?
Susan!
What do you want?
Paige...
Paige!
Snap out of it!
What happened?
You had to use it, didn't you!
You just couldn't wait.
Please, no lectures.
- Still feeling a little faint?
- It's nothing.
No, it's not.
I've been reading this book on Ouija's
and it scared the hell out of me.
Do you know what
they used to be called?
Before this century...?
"Witch boards".
Yeah.
Witches used them to contact demons.
Remember when I said
you were obsessed.
Well, I was right.
According to this book,
when you use the Ouija alone
like you've been doing, you're very
susceptible to the spirit you contact.
At first they'll be
helpful and friendly
so it can get you to use
the board over and over.
And each time you do, he gets
stronger and you get weaker.
Soon you're so weak, you have to
use it whether you want to or not.
What are you telling me?
I'm a Ouija junkie?
It's no joke, Paige!
It's called "progressive
entrapment" and it gets worse.
After you're addicted,
the spirit changes.
He starts to threaten
and terrorize you
breaking down your
resistance like brainwashing.
So eventually it can possess you.
Why would Susan want to possess me?
It's not Susan!
Yes, it is!
Look...
She lost this when she was killed.
This could be anybody's.
It's Susan's!
Oh, yeah?
Here, take a look at this.
What is it?
Susan's lease agreement.
Compare the "S"s in her
signature to the "S" in STOP.
It doesn't match!
No!  It doesn't!
Well, then who the fuck is it?
It doesn't matter who it is!
Well, what it is, you have
to stop using the Ouija
and the automatic writer right now!
Russel, I'm not falling
into progressive entrapment.
Oh, no?  Here...
Let me read you some of the symptoms.
Fainting spells, aggression,
excessive use of profanity,
overtly sexual,
provocative behaviour.
Sound like anyone you know?
Russell, what am I going to do?
I'm glad you asked.
Here, take these and toss
them into the dumpster.
- Should I take the earring too?
- No!  All on to it.
Good night, Paige.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Hello?
Hi Paige?  I'm Officer Rogers.
I hope you remember me...
I remember you.
Mitch's friend, right?
Right.
Mitch has been in an accident.
What?
Where?
Ah, in the County Hospital.
Yeah... yeah...
Thanks.  Okay.
- Russel?
- Elaine!
- Something wrong?
- You tell me.
What do you mean?
You forged that lease
agreement you showed to Paige.
What are you talking about?
I found the real one.
Look.
The "S"s all match perfectly.
It really is Susan's spirit, isn't it?
I think so.
And I think she
caused Jonas's accident.
Elaine!
Wait!
All right you bitch!
I know you're not Susan.
So what the hell do you want from me?
I know you're here!
What do you want from me?
Answer me, God damn it!
What do you want?
Russel, I don't want
to talk about it ...
Just leave me alone!
Go home!
Come on!
Official Mitchell!
What are you doing out of bed?
Going checking out.
But Dr. Gillano hasn't released you.
Russel?
Russel!
Russel...?
Paige!
Listen.
We need to go back Park Woods.
I know where Susan is buried
and I know how she died.
The only thing I don't know
is why she said the
woods were uptown
when they were actually
up by the interstate.
I thought you were going
to stop using the Ouija.
I don't think I can.
You were right.  I've fallen
into progressive entrapment.
God damn it!
Why don't you just leave it alone!
Russel.
What's the matter with you?
Why are you so angry?
Oh my God!
She wasn't saying "uptown".
She misspelt Upton.
You said you inherited property.
Park Woods?
You murdered Susan!
Paige!
Stay away from me!
Let me explain...
Paige...
Open the door, and let me
tell you what happened!
Susan!
Susan, I need your help!
No!
Don't use the Ouija!
Paige!
Susan, please!
Hold it!
I got you!
Scumbag...
Drop the pick axe.
We have to stop her.
Like you stop Susan Sidney?
I didn't kill Susan!
Elaine did!
She must have found out
about her affair with Jonas.
Yeah, right.
You just helped her hide
the body, didn't you?
No!  That was Jonas!
I didn't know anything about it!
I really thought Susan moved.
I'm sure you did.
Paige!  Come on out here, babe.
Everything's under control!
Listen to me...
Susan came back for revenge...
To kill Jonas and Elaine.
But now I think she wants more.
She wants her life back!
And she's going to possess
Paige unless we stop her.
What ...?
Possess Paige?
What the hell are you
talking about, man?
Paige!
Who the hell are you?
Official Mitchell...
So nice of you to drop by.
What's with the gun, Russel?
Aren't you happy to see me.
You can't kill me...
I'm already dead.
Look, Russell...
I have nothing against you.
After all, Elaine was
the one who killed me.
Just let me walk out of here...
and we'll call it even.
I can't.
I can't do that.
You don't have a choice.
You shoot me, you shoot Paige.
And it would be a
shame to put a hole
in such a nice body
when I just got it.
It is a nice body, isn't it?
Not as nice as mine,
but then I was a dancer.
You were a bitch!
And you still are.
But you wanted me
anyways, didn't you?
And you wanted Paige...
Put the gun down, Russell!
And you can have us
both at the same time.
Come on, Russell!
It's not everyday you get
a chance to fuck a ghost.
Stay back!
I mean it...
Let her go ... Susan!
She's innocent...
Nobody's innocent!
And I want my life back!
Paige!
Evening, officer Mitchell...
Where is she?
You tell me where
she is, where's Paige.
Tell me where she is,
you little bitch!
Where is she?
Right here, officer Mitchell...
Mitch...
Help me, please!
Paige...?
Seven years bad luck!
Please!
Whoever you are...
Let Paige go...
Actually, I'm doing her a favor...
She was always afraid of life.
Now she doesn't have
to be afraid anymore.
Paige!
Don't!
You can fight her!
I know you can stop her!
I know you can!...
You fight her, Paige!
You fight her!
That's it!
Fight her!
Don't tell me you're having
second thoughts about moving.
No.
Now that found Susan's body has
finally been found and laid to rest...
I'm ready to move on with my life.
And I'm definitely going to
go to art school this time ...
and nothing is going to stop me.
So, can I call you
once you're settled in?
I'll be insulted if you didn't.
You should know by now,
I'm not so easy to get rid off.
Who says I want to get rid of you?
Chuck, you and Linda
finally have that baby, huh?
Yeah.
A boy.  Named him Brandon.
Yeah alright Chip.
- Hey!  Look at this!
- What?
Well, it looks like one of those...
You know, the pointer
things, to a Ouija board.
Oh man, those things
give me the creeps.
Look, this one's got a pen in it.
Huh, you can actually write with it.
Mike, come on!
Put it back!
We got to go.
You don't think these
things really work, do you?
YES.