As Baltimore's race
for mayor heats up,
former Homicide lieutenant,
Al Giardello, is s cheduled
for a press conference
this morning,
at the Inner Harbor.
He'll be joined by current mayor
Kurt Schmoke.
The joint appearance
signals an important
endors ement for Giardello.
How does it feel
to be the favorite
the last week
of the campaign?
It ain't over
till it's over.
The polls show you
12 points ahead
of your opponent,
Robert Gessner.
The fat lady
has already taken
her curtain call,
don't you think?
One thing I've learned working
with Homicide unit.
Never assume anything.
Give me a $1.00?
A $1.50?
Just a measly $1.50!
Your recent statement,
that if elected,
you'd push
to legalize drugs.
Do you think
this is the issue
that has set your campaign
apart from your rival's?
I know what drugs have done
to this city.
Educate. Don't legislate.
That's all for now.
Everybody,
take three steps back.
We want Al! We want Al!
We want Al!
Meldrick, I will partner
with you any time,
any place, when
it comes to a crime.
But I'm not investing
in your bar.
Come on, Falsone,
you can s ee for yours elf
that ''The Waterfront'' is
a moneymaking proposition, man.
It's a cash cow.
Veritable green machine.
Yeah? So why you so anxious
to cut me a slice.
'Cause my other so called
partners are way too silent.
Munch is up in New York
looking for fame and glory.
And Bayliss has taken
a semi-permanent
leave of his senses.
So you need someone
to do all the work.
Hey, all I'm asking,
Falsone,
is just to give it
a couple of minutes
of your very, very
valuable time.
Just examine
the concept.
That's all
I'm saying.
Yo, officer.
Gentlemen.
Mike Giardello. As I live
and as I breathe.
I heard you traded the Bureau
for a beat.
Working on my detective
shield.
I love a man in uniform.
Check you out.
Your pop's out there,
stumping for mayor,
and you're back here having
yourself a little yard sale.
Oh, it's been
a real media circus.
Every time I open the door
it's like candid camera.
Hey.
Alan Funt was a great American,
okay, and I took his passing
very, very personally.
So what we got here?
Local dealer. Shot in the head.
Been dead about a day.
Does our deadhead
have a name?
Jos eph Hardwick.
AKA Yin-Yang.
Yin-Yang?
Looks like he ''yinged''
when he should have ''yanged.''
Hey, Mike.
Yeah?
Dispatch just radioed.
They you downtown pronto.
What's up?
Your father.
He's been shot.
The question remains:
Is it possible to find
a rule of thumb
to look outside the realm
of religion
and its absolute values?
The answer is no.
All people,
in the community,
even those
without formal religion,
formal absolute values,
formal spirituality...
always construct
their own.
Class dismissed.
Mayoral candidate
Al Giardello
was making a campaign
appearance early this morning
when he was shot
by an unidentified assailant.
Giardello was rushed here
to Church Hillman hospital,
where he is now undergoing
emergency surgery.
His condition is listed
as critical.
Here is his son,
Officer Michael Giardello,
perhaps we'll be able
to get a word with him.
Officer Giardello!
I have nothing
to say.
- Officer Giardello!
- Look, I don't know anything.
Well, tell me this,
how do you feel?
How do you think I feel?
Get out of my face!
Officer Giardello...
understandably distraught about
this tragic turn of events.
How's my father?
He was shot
in the abdomen.
Maybe more than once.
Is he gonna make it?
He just went
into surgery.
As soon as there's any news,
you'll be the first to know.
- I promise you.
- Soon.
No. No.
Maybe we should go
to the hospital.
Hey! G wouldn't want us
keeping vigil.
He'd want us out there
in the black
looking for the ebola
that did this.
What about
Joseph ''Yin-Yang'' Hardwick?
Who?
Our day-old,
dead drug dealer.
Aw, he'll keep.
Oh, look who's back
from oblivion.
Hey. You guys...
you find the shooter?
Naw. We were waiting
on you.
Oh, well,
I'm here to help.
Sabbatical's over?
Yeah, for now.
That's weird,
ain't it?
What's that?
He just packs up
his desk,
doesn't say nothing to nobody,
just splits.
I had things
to think about.
Issues.
That's the thing
about you Bayliss.
See, you always
did have...
''issues.''
You gonna stand here
yapping?
Step back.
Any comment?
Frank.
All right, some of you
came to homicide
after Al Giardello left.
Some of you worked
alongside him.
Like Kay Howard,
now on the Fugitive squad.
Tim Bayliss, been on a
leave of absence.
Frank Pembleton,
retired a couple years ago.
You're the almighty, Pembleton.
We've all heard
the stories.
Can we get on
with this?
Yep. Okay.
We got a homeless man,
won't give us his name,
he grabbed Giardello
just before the shooting.
We swabbed his hands
for gunpowder residue.
He's clean.
As soon as uniforms
bring him up,
I'm gonna interview him,
find out what he saw.
We talked to everybody
at the rally,
and all thevendors,
and we brought in
a few witness es
for further questioning.
And this event was covered
by the press, right?
We're way ahead
of you, Frank.
We've requested video footage
from the local news stations.
Stivers and Ballard, I need you
to collect those cassettes.
Sure, Lieutenant.
Lots of witnesses,
what about suspects?
G's campaign for mayor knocked
some noses out of joint.
Made him a few enemies.
Coupled with the ones
he already had.
I'm up.
All right.
Howard, Bayliss.
I want you researching
G's past.
Get me everything on anybody
he ever tangled with.
How far back?
To his rookie days,
if you need to.
Pembleton, Lewis,
Falsone.
Make me a list
of people
that he's pissed off
on the campaign trail.
A list?
Well, I didn't come here
to make lists.
Frank. Just like
old times.
Okay, we meet back
in an hour.
Yeah, I love you too.
I caught a bullet
on a job myself, you know.
Bullet in the brain.
Stanley Bolander.
Used to work for your dad.
Thanks for coming.
I had to, didn't I?
Your dad,
when I was shot...
He was...
what's the word?
''Tenacious.''
Yeah, he is that.
Not like he sent me flowers
or anything like that, no.
But he was
a pit bull.
He wouldn't let go until they
caught the bastard who did it.
Mikey!
Nonna!
This is so terrible!
This is terrible!
Come on.
What's a new?
There ain't nothing.
They tell me nothing.
Hey, here's one of G's
from '82 that looks promising.
Very blue.
You never told me the squad
room was this blue.
Sure I did.
Yeah, but not
this shade.
No, huh?
This is excessively blue.
Azure.
Cobalt.
Cerulean.
Except the board.
All these open cases.
Too much red.
Hurts my eyes.
I'm seeing spots.
What?
Nothing.
No, something.
No.
Well, what's this, Ryland.
Is this one
of your open-- Hmm.
No, no, no, no.
That stone cold sucker
is mine, Frank.
Luke Ryland snuffed two women
live on the Internet.
And Baltimore being Balto-less,
he got off on a technicality.
Next day they found him,
curbside, laying there.
.44 slug in the back
of his head.
- You got a suspect?
- Not anyone.
Nuh-uh.
Whoever did the deed,
knew how to execute
an execution.
And this, sordid little tale
makes you jumpy, because--
No, no, Frank.
Doesn't make me jumpy.
Oh, come on.
You're jumpy. I know you.
No. You know something,
you don't know me.
Things change, Frank.
People...
they change.
Kid's still in the interview room
with the homeless guy, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
Taking way
too much time.
Yeah.
You got a name.
I know you do.
Give me a dollar.
You know, I got
a hundred eyeballs
saw you assault
Al Giardello.
Now you saw who shot him,
didn't you?
Didn't you?
I want a dollar. I gotta get
something to eat.
Come on!
Just a, measly little dollar?
That so much to ask?
You know what?
I am really losing
my patience with you.
You know, I was gonna give you
a number two beating.
But you have worked
and worked.
And you have earned yourself
a number one.
Now I am gonna beat
your balls
until you tell me
what I wanna know.
This does not reflect
my command.
I thought you were in charge
here, Lt. Gharty.
You better go help
your man.
Damn!
This is gonna cost you,
buddy.
This is gonna cost you.
You okay, mister?
See him come at me? Huh?
See how he came at me?
Whoa!
Shit!
All right, sit down.
- Sit down. Sit down.
- Why, you big --
Come on, sit down.
What are you two
doing in here?
What's this?
Hey, hey, hey,
I'm in the middle
of something here.
A dollar.
You asked
for a dollar?
Yeah, I asked
for a dollar.
I heard you.
I know you guys
are legends, but, uh...
This is
my interview.
Shut up.
What?
Excuse me?
I said:
Shut the hell up.
Me out?
Yeah, grab a coffee.
This ain't right.
Grab me one, too.
Milk, two sugars.
Well, he's a feisty little guy,
isn't he?
I'll be right in there
if you need me.
Tell me
what's going on!
I'm really sorry,
sir, but
I don't know
what's going on.
Well, then find me someone
who does!
Hey, Mike, Mike.
It's been hours.
I can't get any real information
from anybody.
The hospital has got
to cover its ass
just like everybody else.
And you want to know
something else?
The minute that he's out
of surgery,
I'm sure they'll be telling you
exactly what they did
and handing you
an itemized bill.
Yeah.
Oh, look, they're replaying
that little clip
of you pushing Helen Lucaitis
ass over tea kettle.
Great.
You made
the national news.
Al would be proud.
You know, I can't believe you
were my father's boss.
For awhile.
But, I was also his equal.
And his underling.
Guess you might say I know
all sides of the man.
Yeah, wish I did.
I used to be FBI Liaison
with the department.
Took the job to be closer
to him.
Make amends.
Maybe put to rest some anger
and resentment
we have
for each other.
But that didn't happen?
If anything, working together
made things worse.
You pimped us.
Oh, man.
He gave everything
you told him
to the Independent Counsel's
office.
Well, how was I
to know?
We were always stepping
on each other's toes.
So, I quit.
Started over
as a Balto uniform.
Bottom of the totem pole.
I don't know if any of it
made any difference to my dad.
If he even noticed.
You wouldn't hurt
anybody.
Would you?
No.
You wouldn't hurt anybody
because it's not in you?
Al Giardello wouldn't hurt
anybody either.
It's not in him.
You and he, you got
a lot in common.
That's why I asked him
for a dollar.
I knew he'd understand.
What's your...
your name?
You ain't got an address,
what do you need a name for?
Post office
can't find me.
Why should it matter
if I have a name.
Well, we don't need
to know your name.
What we need to know is if you
saw who hurt Al Giardello?
You got a dollar?
A dollar?
I'm jonesin'
for a Hershey bar.
I just gave you
a dollar.
I'm asking him.
What did you see
at the Inner Harbor today?
I'm a fiend
for chocolate.
Didn't I just give you
a dollar?
Didn't I?
Yeah.
So now you gonna play me
for the fool?
If I give you a dollar, will you
tell us what you saw today?
I'm the fool,
right?
I gave you a dollar,
and now, what, huh?
No, no, no, no.
Put that away.
I'm here out of concern
for a good person.
Somebody who means
a lot to me.
Means a lot
to this city.
And what, now you think
this is some kind of deal
where you gonna...
use my concern to mooch money?
'Cause... you think
that you're the key to the puzzle?
You're holding all the vital info,
so yeah, screw me.
And screw him!
And screw Al Giardello.
Hmm?
Do you think
you mean anything?
To anybody?
Anything to this city?
No.
But I'm here.
I'm extending you
my kindness.
I give you what you want,
out of goodwill.
And it's not about the money.
It's not about a dollar.
'Cause if you ask me for ten,
I'll give you ten.
Ask for a hundred,
you got it!
I'm respecting you.
But you're gonna
sit there...
and piss on me.
I'm gonna send you
to hell, mister.
''I ain't got a name,'' so feel
sorry for my mooching ass.
I'm jonesin' for a Hershey bar.
The guy that I see
is in his late 40s--
or early 50s, maybe.
- Jonesin' for that Hershey bar!
- Of the Negro persuasion.
The guy is black.
Uh-huh, what's he look like?
How tall is he?
He is...
nearly as tall as me.
Got gray sidewalls.
His hair, you know.
Sideburns.
And he's got a gun.
One of them black guns,
that go pop-pop-pop.
An automatic.
I don't know.
Okay, so he shoots
this gun, pop-pop-pop.
What happens then?
Where does he go?
He just disappears. He gets
swallowed up in the crowd.
I got scared.
I was just trying
to get out of there.
And then the cops
grabbed me up.
Oh.
Can I have
that other dollar now?
Giardello is still
in surgery at this hour.
Meanwhile, police have
intensified their investigation,
interviewing literally hundreds
of witnesses.
We'll have more
after this.
And we're out.
I'd like to give you
the tape, but I can't.
Okay, well then
we'll get a subpoena.
No, you don't understand,
I can't.
There was some kind
of technical glitch
- with our camera.
- Glitch?
All I got is stuff leading up
to the gunshots,
then the camera dies.
We're the only station
in town
that didn't have footage
of the actual shooting.
And believe me,
I'm not happy,
losing out on the biggest
news story of the year.
I'm crying
big crocodile tears.
Give us what you've got.
Okay, we're back
in 10.
So you're living
in St. Michael's now, huh?
Yeah.
Play a little golf.
Practice the cello.
Hey, retirement agrees with you.
You got that healthy pink glow.
That's high blood
pressure.
I'm on a zero sodium diet.
Zero as in none.
As in I can't even go down
to the ocean.
Take in the sea breeze.
You know how bland life is
without salt?
I was under the impression
that you were still in Balto.
No.
That you refuse
to answer my calls
out of some
misdirected spite.
I have never
mis-whatevered my spite.
I got married again.
What, number four?
Yeah. In two weeks,
I'm getting divorced.
Jeez, John!
I like this.
This is great.
You and I, we're prowling
the streets of Baltimore again.
I have never prowled the streets
of anywhere with you, all right?
Don't start agitating
me much.
- Come on...
- What's the status...
Step back,
step back.
Stop it there.
What are you
looking at, Stan?
Uh, well, you see this guy
right here?
He's right on the edge
of the stage.
His body language.
Doesn't look right.
I can't see anything.
We're looking
for a gun.
At this angle, you can't even
see his hands.
Well, what we need
is to enhance the tape.
Yeah, send a copy
to the state police lab.
Lieutenant!
We--
Captain.
My, my, my,
look at this.
Sgt. Howard, Frank Pembleton,
Munch, Bayliss.
Even the big man.
All the old boys and girls
gathered again.
Everybody
pals y-walsy.
You interrupt one
of my detectives
in the course of interviewing
a witness?
I was giving him
some relief.
Relief, my ass.
You just wanted to show him
who's boss, that's your game.
Sir--
But now I'm gonna show you
who's boss.
I order you to apologize
to Detective Hall.
Apologize?
Bobby.
Go ahead.
I... apologize.
Yeah, no problem.
Now what the hell are
all of you doing in here?
We came to help.
This is your call?
What are you,
desperate?
No, for G we come
on our own.
Truly noble.
Get your ass in gear,
Gharty.
I want this Giardello shooting
down today.
That's what we all want,
Gaffney.
This is police business.
You're not a cop anymore,
is that right, Frank?
That's correct.
Then get lost.
Okay. Sure.
Fine.
Me too, then.
No, no, Bolander.
You can stay.
That's the beauty of power.
It's arbitrary.
I have a press conference
at 2:00.
I better have some startling new
revelations to tell the media.
Somebody open
a window.
That won't do any good,
that's ''Eau de Gaffney.''
Lingers for days.
- Frank?
- Uh, don't worry about it.
If we... if we get anywhere,
I'll keep you posted.
Fine, fine.
Give me a ring.
Frank!
Wait, wait, wait.
You're just
gonna leave?
Yes. And you're coming
with me.
Where?
If the bosses won't let us
investigate,
we'll do our own.
- Unofficially.
- A citizen's brigade.
Okay, let's start
with the crime scene.
Excuse me, excuse me,
excuse me.
We got 15 different descriptions
of a possible shooter
from 25 different
witnesses.
Some say he's black,
some say white.
Some say he's in his 20s,
others in his 60s.
Yeah, well, they all agree that
the shooter is a man, right?
Well, actually, a few of them
think that maybe he's a woman.
Yeah, I say it's
a conspiracy.
Oh, Munch.
This guy that G's running against,
what's his name, Gessner.
He sees that he's going
to get his ass kicked.
So he decides
to take action.
So he hires an assassin, like in
the ''Manchurian Candidate.''
What did I say
about agitating, Munch?
I'm gonna check out the widow
of Raymond Desassy.
What, the guy G shot?
G shot someone?
Yeah, a couple,
three years ago.
Kevin Lugo,
big shock radio personality.
I remember, he got whacked
in the Mt. Washington parking lot.
Yeah, we get a tip Raymond
Desassy is the murderer,
Gand I go to his house,
Desassy draws a weapon,
G shoots him dead.
Turns out our tip was from
Raymond Desassy's best friend.
Called it in
as a practical joke.
Desassy's wife was pretty bitter
about the whole thing.
Okay, Howard.
Mrs. Desassy it is.
Hey, you need backup?
Sure.
Stivers, Ballard,
take the video tapes
to the state lab
and study every frame.
Lewis, stop by the courthouse,
grab Sheppard,
and go talk
to Carl Miller.
Carl Miller?
The pride
of the Aryan Nation.
Yeah, he's been beating
the drums,
trying to start a race war
over G's drug policy.
If you're volunteering,
how about calling on John Komen?
Whatever you need,
Lieutenant.
Who's John Komen?
Uh, there was a mass suicide
of the African Revival Movement.
Yeah, I saw it
on the news.
Yeah, QRT storms the place,
finds 16 bodies. Poisoned.
A real Jonestown.
Not like the other one,
where the CIA and the military
whacked those people.
Komen's taken over as the head
honcho of the movement.
So, we talk to him.
You know, I say
a Black Nationalist
and two whiter shades
of pale detectives
don't exactly interface,
you catch my drift?
You know, if you got
a problem with it, Munch,
make it easy on yourself.
There's an Amtrak back
to the Big Apple every hour.
Stan, you know where the African
Revival Movement building is?
If it's in Balto,
I can find it.
What do you want me
to do, L.T.?
Check the 800 Tip line.
Okay, we got 48 hours
to catch this guy.
Anything longer than that,
and you know what hits the fan.
All right?
We're a team.
Let's go.
Let's catch this bastard.
Could have handled
this better, Stuey.
Are you coming,
Detective Munch?
Yeah, yeah,
but I'm driving.
You know I like to drive,
as long as you don't smoke
with the windows closed.
- We're gonna smoke.
- What you know--
- I've got a cigar this big.
- Oh, man. Here we go again.
Mrs. Giardello, any word
on his condition?
- Uh, excuse me, do you mind?
- No, no.
Hey!
Hey, you! Leave her alone!
Leave her alone!
What are you doing
here, anyway?
Leave her the hell alone!
We're just doing
our job, okay?
That's no excuse.
Pressure's 90 over 60.
Heart rate's up to 120.
That's the second one.
Big sucker.
Let me see
the X-ray.
Suction, please.
Hmm, we need to clean up
these rib slivers.
So, how was that
for you, Frank?
Being back
in that squad room?
Strange.
So many things
have changed.
Well, the color of the doors
and the floors, maybe.
But, the room's the same,
the work's the same.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess
that will never be different.
What bothered me the most was
not seeing G there, you know?
Having him charging out of his
office like a water buffalo.
As a matter of fact,
the last conversation
we ever had
was over your hospital bed.
After you took
the bullet for me.
My partner's down!
My partner's been shot!
Somebody!
But really it wasn't him
I was angry at.
It was the whole,
you know...
bloody business.
Yeah.
I haven't spoken to him
since that day.
And now,
here it is,
I may never get the chance
to speak to him again.
Well, Frank, why don't we just
stop by the hospital now, huh?
He's in surgery.
Besides, I can do more
for the man...
out here
on the street.
He didn't hate you,
Frank.
And he knows you didn't
hate him.
But I handed him
my badge.
He hated that.
You're not upset by the shooting
of Al Giardello?
Upset? Yes.
But not surprised.
There's a long tradition
in this country
of shooting black men
who speak the truth.
We got a witness who says that
the would-be assassin was black.
A black assassin?
How convenient.
The white man
can always find
a race traitor
to do his dirty work.
There are those who blame
Al Giardello for what happened
in this building
three years ago.
There's some say
he's responsible
for those 16 suicides.
Do you think
I would want revenge?
Well, maybe some
of your followers--
Which you see where?
This movement was destroyed
that day.
So this morning,
at about 8:15--
Was I at the Inner Harbor?
No.
Anybody who can vouch
for your whereabouts?
I was here.
Okay, what about somebody
to back you up, then--
Yes.
They'll tell you that I was
at my desk. Working.
Working?
Said you had
no following.
I'm going to be interviewed
this week on the radio.
''The Mark Steiner Show.''
Steiner? I like him.
And I'm going to tell the world
that Al Giardello
was set up by the white banking
establishment to run for mayor.
Then shot by them.
The bank shot Giardello?
Giardello gets popular,
he gets shot, he dies.
The city riots.
The city goes up in flames.
The smokes clears.
The banks come in and rebuild
the neighborhoods.
Shoving all the poor blacks
out to the collar counties.
The banks and the developers
want all that land near the harbor.
It's worth hundreds
of millions.
The banks, huh?
If you think about it, the scary
part is, it makes sense.
The banks, the multinationals,
the real estate lobby.
That's big money,
Stan.
Think about it.
When you gonna let me
re-open my cart?
I mean, I'm dying here,
I'm losing a whole day's receipts.
I told you and them other
detectives 99 times already
I didn't nothing.
And I told you a hundred times
you are lying.
Why would I lie?
Because you're afraid.
Me? No I'm not afraid
of nobody.
Yeah you are,
you're frightened.
You're frightened of the guy
who shot Al Giardello.
You're afraid that if he finds
out you I D'd him,
he'll come back,
shoot you too.
Listen, if you know anything,
you should tell us.
We'll protect you.
Yeah, how?
Look, this thing goes to trial,
I've got to testify.
The gunman gets off,
I'm dead.
No thanks.
Look, I got no reason to die
for this goon Giardello.
Goon?
Well, legalizing drugs?
Come on,
that's insane!
Listen, listen, if you don't
tell us what you know,
that gunman is free and he
is running the streets.
If he hits his mark next time,
if he kills someone,
that's on you.
Yeah, well, guess what.
I can carry that.
Okay, thanks
for your time.
Uh, hi,
I'm J. H. Brodie.
I used to work with
your dad at Homicide.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry. I was at D.C.
at a film festival
and I heard
about the lieutenant.
How's he doing?
I brought him
this giraffe.
Yeah, I can't get anybody
to tell me anything.
I thought the ER doctors
were supposed to be
so caring and compassionate
and all that crapola.
Yeah, as far as I can tell,
nobody gives a tinker's damn.
Do you think Al Giardello will
benefit from a sympathy factor?
Will this put you even further
behind in the polls?
Well, the polls be damned,
Donna, a man's life is at stake.
Now, Al Giardello
and I may disagree
on certain fundamental
issues.
But when a tragedy
like this occurs,
it is essential that we put
these differences aside.
No, I'm not here today
as a candidate for mayor.
I'm here today as a concerned
citizen and as a friend.
- Sir. Sir.
- Now excuse me.
My dad hates
this guy's guts.
How you holding up?
I'm all right.
Good man.
Huh.
I have to admit,
white supremacists,
I was thinking something
a little more south Baltimore.
Yeah. Trailer park...
broken down row house,
major appliance on the front stoop.
Exactly. Not so--
Quaint?
Yeah, a little more, you know?
White trash.
You said it, not me.
Sure we got
the right address?
Sure I'm sure.
You ever know me not to have
the right address?
Don't answer that.
Can I help you
with something?
And the very identity
of this country
as a white, Christian nation
is in jeopardy.
Aw, Jerry, I couldn't agree
with you more.
But in the words
of Thomas Jefferson,
and Timothy Mc Veigh once wore
this on a t-shirt,
''The tree of liberty must be
watered frequently
with the blood of patriots,
and tyrants.''
Ladies and gentlemen,
stay with us.
It looks like I'm about
to interview
two of Baltimore City's Finest.
When Al Giardello took a bullet,
I admit, I thought,
''Well, there's some damn
justice.''
Where were you this morning,
Mrs. Desassy?
Me? Right here.
Making love to my bottle
of gin.
You always start drinking
early in the morning?
Nah.
No?
I don't start early 'cause
I don't stop the night before.
Maybe you should get
some help.
Maybe you should shove
this bottle
where the sun
don't shine.
You got anybody that can vouch for
your whereabouts this morning?
My next door neighbor,
she was over here.
Mooching a toot.
We may need you
for further questioning.
Hey, Ray and me, we was all
each other had in the world.
You cops killed him.
I hope that Giardello dies
and goes straight to hell.
Only wish I had shot
the bastard.
Have a good day.
Where were you
around 8:15 this morning?
When Giardello got shot?
Yeah.
On the air.
And when the good news
came out,
across the Jewish controlled
mainstream media,
we popped a bottle of genuine
American sparkling wine
and shared
the glad tidings
with our listeners
across the country.
Across the country?
Well, we reach most of our
followers by the Internet.
You can verify that you were
in the studio
at the time
of the shooting.
I'll play you
the tapes.
Don't bother.
You could fake that.
You could be on the air
and nowhere near this dump.
Then I'll make you a list
of people who were in and out
of the studio all morning
and saw me in the flesh.
Yeah.
Here's some paper.
Here's a pen.
Knock yourself out.
Oh, I do wish we were
on the air right now.
So I could describe you all
for the benefit of my audience.
Why is that?
Well, we talk all the time
on my program about mud people.
You familiar with
the term?
Yeah, I am.
It's one of our favorite
topics.
Along with the evils
of race mixing.
Just look at the two
of you.
Prime examples of both.
You gotta admit, they've come
a long way from the Grand Kleagle,
''Birth of a Nation,''
cross burning days.
Yep, good old boys have
definitely traded in
their bedsheets
for Web sites.
Assuming these check out,
Miller's not G's shooter.
He could have got somebody else
to pull the trigger for him.
Or he might have
incited it.
The shooter ends up being
one of his regular listeners,
maybe we can
tie Miller in.
Yeah, I'd love to tie him
into something.
How many Black nationalist
groups are there in Baltimore?
Many. Sheppard and Lewis
still checking the Aryan angle?
Yeah. Baltimore.
City of brotherly love.
That's Philadelphia.
Call me crazy,
but don't you think
we should be switching
with Sheppard and Lewis?
I mean, what's Gharty thinking,
anyway?
John?
Billy Lou.
I heard you were in town.
Why didn't you come
to see me?
Billy Lou, this is my
old partner, Stan Bolander.
Pleased to meet you.
I guess you have to eat
your words
about never coming back
to Charm City.
When did I say that?
Maybe I need
a cup of coffee.
And telling everybody I ran off
with one of your colleagues.
Well, New York Cops,
they'll believe anything.
Who did you have in mind?
Stuart?
Stivers.
In your dreams.
Maybe I'll see you later.
You see, I got a lot
of work to do.
You know where
to find me.
Is that the fourth
ex-Mrs. Munch?
Yeah. You think maybe I'm not
cut out for the domestic life.
Okay.
Guys like you and me.
Work is where we shine.
Work.
Excuse me.
You in the right OR?
This is OR 5,
here, doctor.
Security!
There's been a shooting
in OR 5.
Security! Security!
He's been shot!
We got a code red! We need a
code red here!
Code red! Code red!
In a bizarre development,
shots were fired inside the hospital.
As you can see, QRT teams
have been called in.
They are to do a room by room
search of the building.
Police are now moving everyone
out of the hospital.
Clear!
Move around.
Don, get in here.
Get in here!
Clear!
It's not clear at this point...
whether this incident is connected
with the shooting this morning
of mayoral candidate
Al Giardello.
Ready? And up.
We've got
90 over 60 still. Okay.
Heart rate's at 130.
Clear!
You saw this dealer
at the rally this morning.
Yeah, man. Easy Eddie Moe.
I know him all too well.
Used to cop from him
when I was in the game.
Back in the day,
before I got clean.
Why would he be at a rally
for Giardello?
That's what I'm saying.
To take him down, maybe.
Drug dealers are so flipped out
by the idea
of Giardello being mayor,
man, they're registering to vote.
So where can we find
this Mr. Moe?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
baby, whoa... whoa.
You might want to talk
to Bernie Weeks
at the Shiny Foil Lounge.
Eddie used to work for him.
Bernie Weeks...
Wasn't he that dealer
we busted by mistake?
We were looking
for Manuel Rendero!
Right.
He wasn't our shooter,
but he had 50 kilos of coke
in the trunk of his car.
Yeah. And now he's back
on the street already.
Right.
How could something
like this happen?
We had officers posted
on every floor.
How did the shooter get in?
If I were paranoid,
I'd say someone
in the department was involved.
I'm gonna forget
you said that.
Has QRT s earched
the whole building?
Yes. We'll catch him.
It's only a matter of time.
- Hey, Mike.
- How's my father?
Another surgeon is working on him.
He didn't miss a beat.
And the one who's shot?
Second surgical team's
cutting into him now.
Are we positive the two
shootings are related?
What are you talking about?
Of course they're related.
Maybe Dr. Williams
has enemies.
The shooter was after
my father.
We won't know for until we can
get in there and investigate.
Right now our Crime Scene
is still in OR.
Colonel Barnfather!
- He's not in there.
- Damn!
He must have escaped when
everybody was rushing out.
Let's get everybody
back inside.
Always--
Always wondered myself why they
just didn't do what he said.
Kick the bottom out of the market
by making the stuff legal.
Put me out of business
like that.
So, you're happy
Giardello got shot?
No, I didn't say all that.
It could backfire,
the... what you call it?
Sympathy vote.
You know what our next
question is, don't you?
- Do I got a alibi?
- Yeah.
Maybe I should just call
my attorney.
Whoa! You don't need
to lawyer up yet.
Come on,
this is still friendly.
You lawyer up, we gotta put you
in the system.
Waste of time
for all of us.
You Homicide, right?
You know anybody in Narcotics?
Yes, absolutely.
You got any juice
with Steve Fletcher?
I could talk to him, yeah.
'Cause if you could get that
bastard off my back.
I mean, he's camped out
on my front stoop.
My oldest daughter
thinks he's gonna kill me.
Just bust in the front door,
and grease me in my own bed.
The stress is just
aggravating her ass.
I'll speak to him.
I ain't do Giardello.
Well, how about
your crew?
Them neither.
Wait, wait, wait.
We got an eyewitness, says that
Easy Eddie was at the rally.
He don't work
for me no more.
He was spending too much time
running his mouth about Giardello
and not enough time
bringing me the cash money.
Soon as it happened,
everybody thought
the shooter
had to be Easy Eddie.
Okay.
Okay, so we'll
give this to Gharty.
And if this Easy Eddie Moe
is the shooter...
then he's in the wind.
You and I are never gonna
be able to find him.
Not on our own.
I could really use
a cup of coffee.
Oh, y eah, good,
I'll be buying.
No, no, I can't.
Because of the stroke.
You know, for a minute,
I forgot.
For a minute there, it s eemed
like time hadn't even gone by.
For a minute, it was
eight years ago.
You know, Frank,
I never...
never told you
how much I...
enjoyed having you
as a partner.
You know,
how much I loved--
working with you.
You think maybe
a cop shot G?
- What?
- A cop.
Why would a cop, one of us,
want to shoot G?
I'm not talking
about one of us.
I'm talking about a cop
with attitudes,
with prejudices,
a redneck cop.
Well, God knows there's plenty
of those around.
A Gaffney! A guy who'll put in
the time, walk the beat,
he sees Giardello
making a reach for power,
decides to...
change history.
Yeah, yeah, that's a real
interesting idea, Frank.
- Cops as killers.
- Happens.
Kellerman plugged
Luther Mahoney.
Still thinks some boy in blue
finished off, uh...
- Gordon Pratt.
- Yeah, me, too.
Hey, you know,
saying you're right--
saying that some law enforcement
officer shot Giardello--
How do we find him?
Where do we start?
I don't know.
Needle in a haystack.
Let's go see how Ballard
and Stivers are doing
with that videotape.
You know why
I left Homicide?
Why?
Because I could...
not... hear...
one more...
confession.
I got sick of hearing people
confess to me.
Like some Jesuit.
I'd sit there in the box,
listening to some guy
not only admit to...
having just
killed someone,
but cop to all the other crap
in his life
that over the course
of his life had...
led him...
to that point.
You would have made
a great Jesuit, Frank.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee...
I'm not gonna sugarcoat
reality for you.
Internal damage,
substantial.
Your father was shot twice
in the abdomen.
One bullet pierced
his right kidney and colon.
The other missed the vital organs
but pulverized a rib.
He's looking at several
more operations
to fully repair the colon
and remove the damaged kidney.
And the risk of peritonitis
remains high.
Recovery is gonna take
some time,
but I think the long term
prognosis is good.
He's a very strong man.
His general health is excellent.
When do you think
I can talk to him?
- I don't know.
- Well, that's refreshing.
A doctor who doesn't
know everything.
- You're welcome.
- Hey, I'm not thanking you.
I have been here all day
worried to death.
I have big problems
with the way this place is run.
I'm two under par on the 15th
green with a four foot gimme,
about to go to three under
when I get beeped.
I drop my club-- I don't even
take the shot.
I got here-- OR is a war zone.
Kosovo on ice.
You'd rather we held your hand,
or saved your father's life?
Putz.
The gun, the gun.
Where the hell is the gun?
Right there.
Pull it up.
- This guy?
- No, that guy.
You want to see what
he's holding in his hands?
Yeah, do your voodoo.
Okay, see, he's holding
something in his right hand.
Anything?
Maybe. Look, he's definitely
holding something.
- No, that's a tapere corder.
- A microcassette recorder.
Well, you guys
got anything?
A drug dealer with a grudge.
We passed that on to Gharty.
How far into these tapes
are you?
- About halfway.
- You mind if we sit in?
- Not a problem.
- Please.
- Let's go!
- Huh? What?
I'm buying you
breakfast.
What are you doing?
Get back in bed.
I feel fine.
Never felt better.
You've been shot twice.
You shouldn't be out of bed.
I feel fine.
Let's go down to Jimmy's
and get some scrapple.
Get some funnel cakes,
with frim-fram sauce,
chufafa on the side.
What?
Nat King Cole was a merry old soul.
A merry old soul was he.
Wait, wait, Pop. Are you sure
you should be doing this?
My cholesterol is down.
I'll risk it!
I don't mean having breakfast
at Jimmy's.
I mean checking yourself
out of the hospital.
Don't ask, don't tell.
I won't if you won't.
Pop, you know you're not
making any sense.
Why don't you lay back down
and let me call a nurse?
Sh-hh! Last one out
is a rotten egg.
Mike?
Hello, Dr. Bristol.
Do you know
Julianna Cox?
She was my predecessor's
chief medical examiner.
Hi. I'm really sorry
to hear about your dad.
Thank you.
We've been talking to his doctor
and getting the full story.
His prognosis
sounds promising.
Knowing G the way I do,
I'm sure he's gonna pull through.
Excuse me.
I gotta take a walk.
Hey, Mike? I'm gonna take
your grandmother home.
She's exhausted.
Oh, thanks, Megan.
Get some rest.
Speaking of rest,
you could use some.
- Grab some nap time.
- I'm too fired up to sleep.
- Will you call me later?
- Yeah.
Mike.
They told me downstairs
your dad's out of surgery.
Yeah, yeah,
he's in ICU .
You hear anything from Homicide?
They catch the shooter?
- I've been so caught up here.
- I'm sure they're all over it.
I wanna go down there
in a little while anyway.
I have an idea I want
to tell Gharty about.
I could go with you.
I know I'm not a cop anymore.
And there's a lot of people
who would be just as happy
never to see my mug again,
but G was always good to me.
And fair.
Yeah, sure.
Come on.
Brodie!
Hey, hey, I just filmed
a triple bypass operation.
It was awesome, man.
Do you guys know that this is
the very hospital
where Edgar Allan Poe
died of rabies?
News to me. I guess
they must have remodeled.
We're gonna head down
to headquarters for a while.
If my dad comes to,
would you beep me?
Sure.
That kidney is definitely
history.
It is amazing
how effectively
they treat gunshot
traumas nowadays.
Even 10 years ago, these bad boys
would have been fatal.
The upside
of automatic weapons.
They've expanded the boundaries
of medical science.
Talk about
your silver lining.
Wish I knew what caliber.
What's your best guess?
- It's odd.
- What?
I'm just not used to seeing
a body still breathing.
So judging from the damage,
the internal damage,
the assassin was how far away
when he fired, would you say?
15 feet, max.
Maybe as much as 25?
No, no, the injuries
are much too severe for that.
Much too severe
for that distance.
I would love to get in there,
and have a good look around.
- Not that I want him...
- No, no, of course not.
- I know what you mean, though.
- I'm sure you do.
When I first moved back
to Baltimore,
there were a series
of murders in Little Italy.
- Your cousin, right?
- Mario.
Mario?
It's Al.
Oh...
Oh, man...
Now eventually we caught
and we convicted
the two children of one
of Mario's enemies.
- Carlo Rolletta.
- Yeah, I remember.
Maybe another member
of Rolletta's family
is responsible
for Dad's shooting.
- It's possible.
- Put one of your guys on it.
- I ought to put you on it.
- Me?
Yeah. You know the people
in that neighborhood,
they'll talk to you.
Oh, yeah.
Just casual conversation
between me
and some old friends.
You wanna talk
to me now?
Talk! Talk!
I'll talk!
You tell me!
Tell me what I wanna know!
- All right.
- No, he knows!
Mike!
Mike, enough.
Enough.
One of the things
your father taught me
was how to recognize
a dead end.
- Dead end?
- Uh-huh.
And this is a dead end.
Michael?
Dad?
Yeah?
They get the guy
who shot me?
No, not yet.
But everybody is working
every side of the equation.
Including Bayliss
and Pembleton.
Pembleton?
That doesn't smell like
hospital food to me.
Nonna brought me
some gnocchi.
But the doctor won't let me
eat any of it.
Mangia.
Grazie, but I wish
I had known.
I had just finished whipping down
some bad Chinese takeout.
Michael, because you became
a policeman,
doesn't mean you have
to eat like a dog.
Yeah, well,
you've always said that.
When I went to Rome...
We would sit down,
and have a two hour lunch...
with three full courses,
and a good wine.
That's why the Romans
never get anything done.
But they knew
how to live.
That's important, Michael.
I hear you.
To know how to live...
in the little time
that we have.
Okay.
No more bad takeout.
Promise me.
I promise.
Bene.
Okay.
That was Falsone.
That day-old dead drug dealer,
Yin-Yang Hardwick?
What, that K.C. and Lewis
picked up this morning?
Yes. The lab boys did
a comparison of the slugs
out of G and our
dead dealer. Same gun.
We have a witness
that places a dealer
named Easy Eddie Moe
at the scene.
And another dealer that says
that Eddie had it in for G.
- Maybe Easy Eddie shot Yin-Yang.
- Yeah, maybe he did.
Let's you and me meet Falsone,
see if we can help him out.
Maybe there's a connection between
Easy Eddie, Yin-Yang and G.
Fine by me. I can't look
at these tapes another second.
Okay,
back it up for me.
I was looking
out of my kitchen window
and I saw the man,
clear as day.
Well-dressed.
Good-looking.
Walked up the alley
to that boy, that Yin-Yang.
Spoke to him for a moment,
I figured he was buying drugs.
Then the well-dressed man
took out his gun
and shot that boy dead away.
- What did he look like?
- Who? Which one?
The well-dressed man.
40 or so. Gray at the temples.
Beard. Glasses.
- Distinguished.
- Black?
Oh, yes.
Blacker than you or me.
Sound like Easy Eddie
to you?
Not much.
You watch these tapes
of G getting shot,
over and over, frame
by frame, in slo mo,
the act itself stops
being shocking.
That's the problem
with the job.
Things stop shocking you.
You know that murderer,
Luke Ryland?
The one you said
made me jumpy.
Those women that he killed,
those murders,
they still shocked me.
They angered me.
Good-- whoa!
What's that? Go back.
Wow, you see that?
Wow!
That's pop-pop-pop...
followed by a puff of white smoke--
Pow! Right here.
Just a wisp.
- Right...
- Where?
Okay, hold on.
Go forward.
- I still don't see it.
- Okay, give it to me bigger.
Okay.
Daniels,
cameraman.
See that?
Well, it could be,
I just didn't see a gun.
I mean, where's
the gun?
I don't know...
Boom.
But if this smoke
is coming from a gun,
then it's right next
to the Y.A.T. cameraman.
Pow!
You hear that?
You're saying the shooter
was the cameraman from WYAT?
Maybe, maybe.
Now this is tape
from channel 11.
See that, see that puff
of white smoke?
Yeah, I see it.
That's with
the pop-pop-pop.
Not just showing him
with the gun?
No, no, of all the tape
that we looked through,
there's no gun visible
from any angle.
You feel there's
something to this?
Could be.
Yeah. Frank and me,
we'll go suss it out.
Yeah, well, Bayliss,
you go, but,
Pembleton, um...
I think you should
back off right now.
Right now?
It's not my decision.
You saw, I had my lunch
handed to me
for letting you take over
that homeless guy.
When Bayliss called in the tip
on Easy Eddie Moe,
I knew you guys
were working out there.
I didn't say squat.
But this is...
It's not like I ever had
a lot of respect for you, okay?
But what are you doing?
Putting up with this nonsense
from Gaffney.
I had to get off
the street.
I could smell it.
I wasn't gonna last.
I live with Gaffney
and the rest of the brass
because that's what
this job is.
I'm just a stooge.
I know that.
But it's better
than being out there.
Al Giardello had nothing
but respect for you.
He stood up for you.
For the rest of his men.
Covered our asses and didn't
give a crap about Gaffney
or anybody else because it was
all about putting down the cases.
So take a cue from G.
See, you're heading
a detective squad...
and they're
looking to you.
Give them something...
or else walk
the hell away.
All right, all right,
wait, wait, wait. Hold.
Go over to YAT and find out
who this guy is.
That was spoken
like a champ.
A true murder police.
Kiss my ass.
The guy you're looking for,
his name's Eric Thomas James.
Okay, is he still
on the job?
He was down at the hospital,
but he's off now.
We'll need
his home address.
You have any idea what he thinks
about Al Giardello?
I don't have a clue.
I never heard him talk politics.
I don't know anything
about the man at all.
He's a freelancer.
Works weekends, evenings.
He comes and goes.
What can I tell you?
He's a cameraman.
He's removed.
He sits behind his lens
and observes people.
Cameramen. They're a little ''hinky,''
if you know what I mean.
Mr. James?
Eric Thomas James?
Yes.
Detective Bayliss,
Baltimore Homicide.
This is my partner.
Frank Pembleton.
I suppose you better
come in, yeah.
I've got some coffee here.
Would you like some coffee?
- No, thank you.
- I'll take a cup. Sure.
I know it's late,
but I don't sleep much.
Well, neither do I.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I've been expecting you.
Why is that?
See this?
It's my boy's room.
Any weapons in the house,
Mr. James?
- I don't have a gun.
- Well, just having a check.
Were you at the Inner Harbor
this morning, Mr. James?
- And at the hospital?
- I was working.
But I'm going
to show you something, okay?
It's my boy.
It's my son, Tommy.
You know...?
No, look.
He's got it all.
He's got smarts...
and he's good looking,
and he's got
girlfriends, and...
He's gonna make his mark.
He's gonna leave his imprint
on the world.
He's just got
his license, and...
me and the wife,
we're gonna,
get a hold of a used car,
you know, for college.
And where is
Mrs. James?
Who knows?
She left.
I don't know,
a couple weeks ago, she just...
left.
Buffalo.
No, Buffalo.
- Her sister.
- Sit down.
But I haven't called her,
she hasn't...
I don't have the energy.
You haven't asked, but...
Yes...
I shot that man
this morning. Giardello.
Mr. James, we're going to have
to advise you of your rights.
My rights?
I have the right to have things
as they were three months ago.
I play by the rules.
I pay my taxes.
I cut my lawn.
I mean, that's what you're
supposed to do, right?
So, I don't deserve
to have my son die.
Your son is dead?
Yes.
Well, I'm sorry.
Why?
No one should have
a child that dies.
Maybe you should tell that
to all those bigshots.
You know,
want to legalize drugs,
give everybody the right
to get high on whatever they want.
Okay, okay.
You've admitted shooting
Al Giardello?
Yes, I shot him.
I wanted to kill him.
But, hey, why should I expect
to be a sharpshooter?
And why should I expect my son,
go all the way into Baltimore,
buy his dope...
and OD...
right on the street.
And his friends-- why?
Why did they leave him?
Why did they leave him
on the street?
They just left him
there to die.
Three months ago
to the day.
This is how he left
his room, you see?
I'm sorry
about the doctor, okay?
I never meant that.
And...
I meant to shoot the drug dealer
who sold my Tommy the drugs.
And that man, Giardello, because
he was trying to legalize drugs.
That's what
I'm trying to stop.
I'll shoot whoever
says it's okay.
I'm just trying to save
all those innocent kids.
I understand...
Yeah.
You know what, I don't have
any cuffs on me, Frank.
You don't need them.
Hey, hey.
He had the gun
attached to the camera,
which is why
no one saw it.
And it's right here
that...
he keeps the camera rolling
after he shoots G.
Although he neglected
to turn the cassette in to YAT.
We show this tape in court,
Eric Thomas James is done.
We got two counts
of attempted murder:
Giardello and Dr. Williams.
30 years each.
Not to mention
the spare change he'll pick up
for killing the drug dealer.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I'll need you both
to testify.
Yeah, yeah,
we'll be there.
I know
how James feels.
You gotta stop those
that are gonna hurt the innocent.
James is a lunatic.
He's certifiable.
His son gets killed.
He's gotta do something.
Hey, say, uh...
Say one of your kids
gets hooked on drugs.
- One of my kids what?
- Gets hooked.
- They wouldn't.
- Just say that they did.
They're not going to.
It's not gonna happen.
Case closed.
You have no sympathy for James,
for what he's going through?
James is trying to lay
the blame on G,
because in his heart of hearts
he knows that he's responsible
for what happens
to his kid.
I appreciate
how he feels.
You can appreciate it
all you want to, Tim,
but there's a line
between right and wrong.
Yeah, well, you're the expert
on that, Frank.
Nothing lumpy about you.
You know all.
The city looks clean
tonight.
We can't all be you,
Frank.
Think I'm gonna take my wife
out to dinner in the harbor.
Sometimes you can lose
your bearings.
Sometimes, the line
isn't so clear.
Of course the line
is clear.
There's good,
there's evil.
You never shot anyone,
did you?
- No.
And you never would?
I never had to.
I've been lucky.
Yeah.
The righteous cop.
Line's always been
clear to you.
Not always.
Time for one more
confession, Frank.
Defendant is set free.
Confession?
I killed a man.
I'm not in the mood,
all right?
Luke Ryland.
Be seeing you,
detectives.
Who?
I shot the bastard
dead.
Good.
''Go to jail.
Go directly to jail.
Do not pass Go--''
I'm not kidding, Frank.
I killed him.
Come on, Tim.
You couldn't kill anybody.
Frank, he got off
on a technicality.
Defendant is set free.
The bastard had to die
before he went out
and he murdered
another innocent woman.
Don't screw with me.
You killed this, whoever?
Luke Ryland.
Internal cleared you?
Frank...
I'm saying that I hunted
the bastard down,
and when I found him,
I blew his brains out.
I executed him
in cold blood.
And I'm saying, Internal
rules this as a good shooting?
No, no.
Internal doesn't know crap
about me killing Ryland.
You're standing here
telling me you killed somebody?
Yes.
In self defense?
No.
You're standing there
with your weapon,
and it went off,
and you don't remember how.
Frank--
Guns go off accidentally.
Happens all the time.
It was no accident.
No, I'm saying
this is an accident.
For you to shoot somebody?
It's gotta be a mistake.
No, no, no.
It's no mistake.
- No accident.
- Tim...!
- Frank, you're a good cop.
- I'm not a cop anymore.
No, you're always
gonna be a cop.
No, I'm a teacher.
I teach. Civilians.
No-- I murdered
this son of a bitch,
because he was
a predator, Frank.
He preyed on women.
What?
Why are you doing this?
I put the gun right up
to the mother's brain
and I pulled the trigger.
Shut up!
Just shut up!
You put this on me.
You son of a bitch.
In here, I know
that I did right.
But for here...
So you waited till I came back,
so you could...
unload this...?
Unburden yourself?
- What's supposed to happen now?
- You tell me.
I'm not bringing you in.
No, huh?
I'm not a cop.
It's not official.
Really? What are you
going to do, not say a word?
Gonna keep my little secret
to yourself?
Son of a bitch!
You son of a bitch!
You murdered him.
I executed him, Frank.
Who was the primary?
- Lewis.
- You talk to him?
No. I came to you first.
Who else would I tell, Frank?
But did you talk to Lewis?
About this case? No.
So nobody suspects
you're the shooter?
No...
no, man...
Suspect me?
Good ol' Tim Bayliss,
the Zen detective?
Huh.
So, you...
you'll take me in.
I'm gonna take you in.
Are you wild?
No.
You'll take me in, Frank.
Did I take...
a bullet for you?
No, no.
Cut it out.
- Did I take a bullet for you?
- I'm not taking you in--
Did I take a bullet for you?
I take a bullet for you,
and you take a bullet for me.
Now that is
square business, Frank.
This is not
taking a bullet for you.
This is you wanting me to toss
your ass in the junkpile.
You're confessing to a murder.
Do you understand that?
You want someone else
should take me in?
Someone else should bust me.
Is that what you want?
- No.
- Then it has to be you.
No, no, no.
Frank, listen.
Listen to me.
I've thought about eating my gun,
and I'm gonna eat that gun--
right now-- if you don't
do the right thing for me, Frank!
For right here!
I have no other...
no other option, Frank.
Please...?
You thought about putting
a gun to yourself?
Yeah.
You'd be saving my life.
I don't know for how long.
For now.
At least you would.
I believe that you did not mean
to do this killing.
You believe
what you want to believe.
That's okay.
So we're gonna
turn around...
right now...
and we're gonna go
back inside...
okay?
Never put off
the inevitable, Frank.
It's gotta be
what it's gotta be.
Son of a bitch.
Frank...
If you absolve me...
Absolve you?
I can't.
Can't?
That's remarkable,
I mean...
'cause I was certain
that you could.
I think maybe...
Mary and I are going
to stay home tonight.
Have dinner
with the kids.
Thank you.
I would like to make
a toast, actually.
To Al Giardello...
too badass to die.
And to Bayliss
and Pembleton.
Where are Bayliss
and Pembleton?
Oh, come on, do you really
expect to see
the notoriously antisocial
Frank Pembleton here?
- What about Bayliss?
- Who knows?
Yeah, really,
who does know?
What's up with that
Bayliss anyway?
Is he pitching,
or is he catching?
Who cares?
Hey, hey,
I'm making a toast.
It's bad luck
not to finish the toast.
Says who?
Says me.
So, to Bayliss
and Pembleton,
who doggedly pursued
the case,
despite interference
from the bosses,
and brought the shooter
to justice.
And to new friends.
And old friends.
To pathological friends.
Hey, you know, Lewis,
I really love this joint.
Maybe I will be
your partner.
You serious, man?
I'll sell you my third
in a New York minute.
Not so fast.
We're still married.
I own half
of your third.
Hey, hey, Tony!
Tony! Tony! Tony!
I was at the hospital.
So what's the latest?
He died.
Lieutenant Giardello died.
That's not funny, son.
Wasn't meant to be funny.
Doctor said it was
some kind of aneurysm.
It was fast.
And there was no pain.
No pain, huh?
That's what the doctor said.
Hello,
I'm Frank Pembleton.
Mike Giardello.
I heard about G.
I'm sorry.
Thanks...
for catching the man
that killed my father.
I'm good at catching
the bad guys.
Caught me a couple tonight.
Lot of people worked in this
squad room over the years.
Lot of them have died.
Beau Felton got killed
in the line of duty.
Steve Crosetti
committed suicide.
To this day,
nobody knows why.
Do you miss it?
Homicide?
I don't know.
It's not like you could
escape it, you know?
Death is every day.
Death goes on...
and on and on and on...
And that's because
life...
goes on, and on.
Tina?
Hey, hey, hey.
G.
Felton?
We've been waiting for you.
- Crosetti.
- Have a seat.
Okay.
Jack of spades
for Mr. Beau Felton.
A 10 of diamonds
for my esteemed lieutenant.
And a whole lot of nothing
for the little Italian salami brain.
- What are we playing?
- Five card stud.
Who's the fourth chair for?
We don't know yet.
But they'll be here
sooner or later.
Anybody I know?
Maybe.
It's not like
it's written in stone.
It's not preordained,
or anything, Lieutenant.
I suddenly got worried.
My son.
He's a cop.
I thought maybe--
I wouldn't worry,
Lieutenant.
Life is short.
And once you're dead...
you're a long time dead,
if you know what I mean.
Your son?
Michael.
- He's a good kid?
- Yes.
You taught him well?
I tried my best.
- I wish--
- G...
no regrets, huh?
You know what the best thing
about this place is?
All the worries and cares
that you had in life...
They don't matter anymore.
''Rest in peace''...
means what it says.
Lieutenant, do you want
a cup of coffee?
Coffee.
Coffee would be good.
- Do you have any espresso?
- No espresso.
Where do you think
you are, heaven? Sit!
- $20 to you, G.
- I'm in.
Okay, we got one more card
coming up here.
We have another card there.
Who am I to need you
when I'm down?
And where are you,
when I need you around?
Your life
is not your own
Who am I?