- Hi.
- Pluto.
- Jellyfish.
Did you find the place okay?
Yeah.
Good.
You look better than I thought.
Really?
Yeah.
Your emails are just so depressing.
My emails were depressing?
Yeah.
Well, looks like the rain stopped.
It should be a nice, sunny day.
I don't like the sun.
Yeah, me neither.
You've brought your computer.
- That's good.
- Yeah.
- Let me just take that.
- What do you want it for?
I just wanna be able
to get rid of the evidence.
I don't... I don't want
any record of our correspondence.
I don't want everyone
getting all depressed
over me being...
you know, me being dead.
Tell me about it.
Wanna go?
Okay.
- I fucking hate Messiah.
- Well...
- I hope he dies.
- Me too.
He's, like, one of those saviors,
you know.
He's trying to...
trying to save the world,
stop everyone
from hurting themselves
or committing suicide.
I hate those people.
He should just
mind his own business.
There are people who want to be saved
by people like him though...
people who leave
all these comments,
people like Nursery.
Nursery.
She's pretty, huh?
Yeah, she's pretty.
Who do you like on that site?
I like you.
Who do you hate?
Needle and Grimalkin.
They're both me.
Are you schizophrenic?
Maybe.
I get that a lot.
There's a little store up here.
I'm gonna stop,
grab a couple of things.
It's the last one for a while, so...
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
10% off next time.
Thanks.
Have a nice day.
Here.
Sorry, I...
I bought a bunch of stuff.
Oh, that's...
that's okay.
We'll just have a party.
I'm sure that
that $10 wasn't enough.
It's fine.
I added my own money.
I don't mind giving you some more.
I guess I don't need it anymore.
Right?
Right.
Let's go.
So...
have you thought about
how we're gonna die?
Yeah. I mean, some.
Some, I guess.
How about you?
I don't want it to hurt too much.
I'm kind of scared of guns.
I don't wanna jump off
something high either.
I mean,
I'm sure it feels great
when you're falling,
but it probably hurts when you land.
I definitely don't want
my head smashed in.
I mean,
can you imagine
if at that last moment?
You're like, "Damn, my face,"
and that was your last thought?
That'd be the worst.
So you don't want it to be messy.
I'd say so.
What about you?
I just want it to be over.
This is the worst muffin
I've ever had in my life.
I can't just end it
like this.
There's a Thai place up the road.
Were you holding out on me?
No, I wasn't holding out on you.
I just...
I didn't think you'd be hungry.
I can't just...
end it with a shitty old muffin.
This is it.
So we should probably
just get it to go, right?
What?
I just...
I don't want anyone to see us.
No, let's eat in.
I don't think that's a good idea.
You're being paranoid
No one's gonna be looking at us.
- Let's eat in.
- No. Listen.
Yes, I just... I really don't want
anyone to see us, okay?
Is that okay?
When we die,
none of it's gonna matter anyway.
Look, I just...
you know what? I don't even know why
we're going in here in the first place.
I think we should
just be going. I think...
I don't want anyone to see us.
I just wanna go.
- Takeout... take...
- I just want... I just wanna go.
Takeout will be fine.
What do you want?
Come on.
I'm not going in.
I don't want anyone to see us.
I'm gonna go in.
I wanna eat in.
Well, you know what? Then why
don't you just jump off a bridge?
I got this for you.
He wanted to come with us.
You don't wanna stop, do you?
Dying?
I just...
I wanted my last day to be perfect.
But this sucks.
I failed.
No, you didn't fail.
You didn't fail.
Mm.
It's not so bad.
Try it.
It's a car accident.
I have an idea.
You wanna give it a shot?
What?
I have an idea.
What if we drained our blood?
You mean like slit our wrists?
- No.
- I don't want a bloodbath.
No, no, no.
It's not like that.
We just use a syringe?
And you just drain the blood
out of yourself.
It's a really quick
and easy way to die.
I don't love pain.
Don't worry.
There won't be any pain.
You know, there's actually
a warehouse just up here.
I think we could...
we could probably do it there.
What do you think?
I mean, either way.
Just an idea.
Cops.
Must be an accident.
The horses have escaped.
And don't worry.
It doesn't hurt.
Apparently it's totally painless.
When I was young,
I wanted to be Cinderella.
A prince would come
with a glass slipper
and slip it on my feet
and take me away.
Mickey Mouse was actually a rabbit.
- Bullshit.
- It's true.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Here.
You should take these.
Sleeping pills.
Oh, it's okay.
I brought my own.
No, these are the ones though
that you really wanna take.
Okay.
I'll get you some water.
- Here.
- What about you?
Yeah, I... I'm just gonna...
I'll drain your blood.
And once that's finished,
I'll finish myself off.
It's 'cause I know
how to use the instruments.
It's just easier that way, I guess.
Okay.
I'll get set up.
You mind if I go pee?
I'm just gonna go over here.
Okay.
I'm gonna take
your boots off, okay?
You ready?
Okay.
This is an old shipyard, yeah?
Yeah.
I guess there's no way
to properly lock this place up.
Sure, but, you know,
you can get in anywhere, so...
Right.
How long would you say it's been
since this freezer's been moved?
Uh, I don't remember.
Maybe two years.
Stop. Stop.
So...
have you ever been
jealous of a butterfly?
Sure, you guys are young.
You're very young,
so you don't think about it,
but in general human beings...
we live;
we grow up; we die.
That's it.
But what if,
when we got older,
we could form
a chrysalis?
Burst out of it, you know.
All of a sudden we've got wings.
We're flying around.
We can stay up all night,
eat whatever we want,
have all the sex we want.
Sounds like a good life, right?
Butterfly is better.
You're right, Brian.
That's a good answer.
So today we're talking
about the mechanism behind molting,
so essentially why animals molt.
- Holy shit.
- What the f...?
What are you doing?
Ma'am, is everything okay?
What's your name?
Who is she?
Her name's Helga.
Her son's a high school teacher.
Where's he?
I guess he would be
working right now.
So you're a high school teacher?
Uh, yeah.
A biology teacher.
All right, thanks, Scott.
We'll take it from here.
Look, sir, what have you been
doing with this woman?
- Are you imprisoning her?
- Imprisoning her?
No, no, no. I'm just making sure she
can't get out of her room, that's it.
That's what imprisoning is,
Mr. Williams.
You're holding her against her will.
And what's with those balloons?
She has Alzheimer's.
My mother's a wanderer.
She could get into trouble.
She could hurt herself.
I'm sorry, but that doesn't justify
keeping her bound all day.
So what would you
suggest I do?
I mean, stay home
with her all day? Quit my job?
- I don't understand.
- No.
Just... would you try it on?
Try it on.
I'll show you how it works.
That's why I built her this...
so I could take care of her.
All right? Here, come here.
Just take your jacket off.
And there.
Huh.
Yeah, right?
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
It's kind of a...
it's not bad actually.
You see how easy it is...
I mean,
your knees and your hips?
The toilet over here...
here, try sitting down on this.
Come on.
It's very easy
on her hips and her back.
Uh-huh.
- Huh. Fascinating.
- Yeah.
She can't get up?
She can't leave the room?
No. Here, just try the door.
Go on,
try to get outside the door.
I dare you.
Wow.
Look, I gotta hand it to you.
You should probably
apply for a patent.
So what do you do
on your days off?
Me? Uh, nothing.
I just, you know,
take care of my mother.
Well, you gotta...
you gotta take her out
every now and then, you know?
Take her...
I don't know,
take her fishing or something.
Fishing?
Yeah. I like fishing.
How about you?
No, not... not really.
Well...
I know a great spot.
How about next Sunday?
Do you wanna go?
It's the perfect time of year.
I'll... I'll call you.
You don't mind, do you?
I'll call you.
Thanks for your time.
I think she likes you.
Who?
My sister.
Oh.
Lucy.
Lucy? Laura.
Yeah, sorry. Laura.
How about you?
What does she do?
She's a student...
police academy.
Whoa.
Are you okay?
I've been taking care of her
ever since my dad married her mom.
She...
she had kind
of a rough childhood. I just...
I want her to be happy,
that's all.
Like I said, I just...
I don't know
if that's a good fit.
It seems like a lot
of responsibility to me.
I had a good feeling about you
when I met you.
Call it a gut instinct.
And my gut's usually right.
Kind of goes with
the job, you know?
I'm telling you, when it comes
to judging character,
I am second to none.
I like your mom.
Hi, Simon.
I got out of class early,
so I came by.
I left a message
on your cellphone.
Did you get it?
How did you get
my cellphone number?
Abbot gave it to me.
- Is that a problem?
- Oh, uh, no.
No, it's... it's fine.
Can you take this?
It's kind of heavy.
You're hungry, right?
I'm gonna make you some pasta.
How's your
Um...
Hi, Mommy.
Do you remember me?
- Oh.
- No.
She doesn't like to be touched.
You have a lovely home.
Well, I hope you're hungry.
I'm sorry, Mommy.
Did I scare you?
I work with DNA research
at the university.
And we're looking for a connection
between genetics and suicide.
And if we can find that connection,
if we can find that suicide gene,
then we think that
we can probably prevent
a lot of suicides.
We can save a lot of lives.
But it's very very hard
to find blood from people
who have killed themselves,
from suicide victims like...
I know this is
a very strange request,
but if you do wanna die,
you could give me your blood
and you could help out
a lot of people?
Who are in the exact same
position that you're in,
a very similar situation.
You could save a lot of lives.
Look at me.
Wouldn't that be a nice legacy?
Wouldn't that be an amazing thing
to leave behind?
So... so...
so you want my blood?
Fine. I don't need it
anymore if it's...
what do you need me to do?
My car is just down here
if you wanna...
This is not the way to go.
This is... this is not
the way to go.
Let's just...
let's go this way, okay?
Okay.
Jack the Ripper, Albert Fish,
Ed Gein, Jeffrey Dahmer,
Richard Ramirez,
Andrei Chikatilo,
the Zodiac killer
and Ted Bundy.
Which one of those is a vampire?
Jeffrey Dahmer.
Jeffrey Dahmer
is my fucking hero,
but that's just because
he was the ultimate pervert.
The truth of the matter is
is that everyone I just mentioned
is just a plain old serial killer.
So what is a vampire?
Someone who loves blood.
Someone who loves blood
is a vampire.
Renfield, Eclipse,
this is Blood Baron.
Nice to meet you. Eclipse.
Blood Baron,
you've been missed here, sir.
Renfield.
Let's get you a glass of wine.
Shitty vampire sushi party.
What do you think of these?
Like 'em?
They're certainly functional.
I mean,
if you were interested
in biting someone's jugular,
that would be
the instrument to use, I suppose.
I've been reading all of your posts...
quite radical.
And sexy.
If all of you could take your drinks
and please join me in the living room,
I have something
that I'd like to share with you.
If you guys wanna grab
some chairs from the kitchen.
Just throw them up front here.
Oh, except for there.
Renfield, Blood Baron,
could you guys actually
flip the couch around, please,
so it's pointed towards the screen?
Bram Stoker,
a real estate agent,
pays a little visit
to Count Dracula's mansion.
Now upon arriving
he stumbles across his private diaries.
Dracula finds out
that Bram has stolen his diaries
and begins to search for him.
Hey hey, could you just stop
spoiling the film, okay?
It's a silent film.
I have to explain it.
- And how long is this again?
- It's two hours.
- Two hours?
- Two hours.
All right, so Bram Stoker
steals Count Dracula's diary
and writes a book about it.
Dracula finds out and follows him
back to England.
That's basically where
we'll pick up, here.
Blood Barry.
Blood Barry,
are you all right?
Are you okay?
Sleepy?
I found this.
Is this yours?
Is that yours?
I know about her.
Thanks for hanging out with me.
Franny Pierce.
Marcia Lizinski.
Saw it all on the news.
Are you the one they call
the Blood Stealer
or the Vampire on some sites?
You know how careless that is...
leaving something like that
on your cellphone?
Do you wanna get caught?
Hey, guys,
we got the Vampire up here.
He's right here.
Don't think about killing me.
I'm not snitching on you.
I love you.
I'm your friend.
You can trust me.
You know how cool it is
for me right now,
being face to face
with the Vampire himself?
I knew there was
something different about you...
from the moment I met you.
Let's go for a drive.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Is this yours?
- Huh?
- Is this yours?
Oh, yeah.
Just a little hobby of mine.
I'm sorry, a hobby?
Yeah.
You can drive, here.
Try it out.
Let's try her, right here.
Try her?
Kill her.
I wanna see you in action.
It'll be fun.
Hi. 1921 Adam, please.
Sorry, he's in training.
You're his first passenger.
A cabbie never forgets his first
'til the day he dies.
What's your name, if I may?
My name?
Michaela.
That's a beautiful name.
Take a left up here.
Fuck, did you just see that plane
go down? Did you see that?
I swear to God,
I just fucking saw it.
I'm sorry, do you want
to make a quick stop?
We need to... your fare's on us.
Is that okay?
Yeah, sure, I guess.
All right.
Hello.
Yeah, I'm calling to report
a plane crash.
Where is that?
Is that over...
is that Andrews Bay?
Yeah, somewhere over
Andrews Bay somewhere.
Me? I'm a cab driver.
Yes, I'm with a passenger
right now.
They... they want us to stay put
until the police can come here.
- Is that gonna be a problem for you?
- No, no, no, that's fine.
Thank you.
Okay. All right.
15 minutes?
Okay, just please hurry.
So where did you say it crashed?
Watch out for the dog shit
there, sweetie.
No! No!
Stop it!
This isn't the hard part,
holding her down at first.
- Get off me!
- That's why I go to judo every week.
I won't kill her just yet.
It's better alive, right?
Three minutes of asphyxiation?
Seem to do the trick.
Hypoxia, panic impedes
her ability to think.
But then again, it didn't seem like
she had much thought
up here before.
Am I right?
Where are you going, sweetheart?
Oh. Hi. Hi.
You want some?
That's rape.
Nothing more, nothing less,
just rape.
What?
You're a sorry sorry son of a bitch,
you fucking maniac.
We both are.
Is there...
Is there more than I know of?
How many have you taken so far?
I... I can help.
What are you gonna do
with the body?
- Well, I don't...
- What are you gonna do with the body?
I don't gamble like you.
I play it safe.
I will take her home.
Her bones...
I just crush them up
and spread them in the ocean.
The flesh I just put in a pot
with cayenne pepper,
boil it and make a nice...
Pull over.
- Pull over the car. Pull it over.
- I'm not gonna kill...
- Pull over!
- Okay.
Did you have too much
to drink tonight?
Are you all right?
All right, everyone,
these are the biology exams.
Uh, we should get started
in a few minutes.
Please put your binders away.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
Good luck.
Dave, eyes on your paper, please.
Hi. You're home.
What are you doing in here?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- This one's different.
What are you doing in here?
What are you trying to do?
Detach it.
- Take it off?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
What are you...
What are you doing here?
The building manager let me in.
- How did you get in here?
- He let me in.
Oh, wow, she just
starts moving around
as soon as she's free, huh?
Yeah.
So he... I'm sorry,
the building manager let you in?
Yeah, sorry. Do you have
extra keys to your apartment?
Can I have one?
Uh, no.
I only have one key.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's pretty risky.
I mean, what would
you do if you lost it?
I probably have five
or six copies of my own keys,
and when I leave the house
I bring at least two of them with me.
Listen to me. You need to call
before you come over here, okay?
- I mean...
- I did.
We could be busy.
We could be doing some...
I did call.
You didn't pick up.
- I didn't?
- No.
You should probably
check your messages more often.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Um,
and by the way, can...
Can you stay out
of my room? Um...
- Sure.
- This should be off-limits.
I'll remember that next time.
Hey, Mina,
what are you doing?
Mina, come down
from there, okay?
Going
Mina.
Do you really want to die?
Let me ask you something, Mina.
Do you know yourself?
You who decides to kill yourself...
but do you really know
who you are?
Do you know that self?
I mean, there are
60 trillion cells inside of you.
Do you know that?
I mean, how often
do you think about that?
Mina.
I don't.
Yes, you do.
You think about them all the time.
You just don't think about it
in the right way. I mean...
If your body is
an apartment complex,
those 60 trillion cells
are your... your tenants.
They need ventilation, right?
So you breathe.
They need nourishment,
so you eat.
When they seek renewal,
they nudge you with a little bit of a...
sexual urge.
What you do is what they need.
You have five senses, Mina:
Sight, smell, sound, taste...
and touch.
But what is their purpose?
To see the world outside.
To see everything,
to feel everything,
to taste everything,
to touch everything.
But they're completely useless
when it comes to seeing
what's inside of you.
Right?
When you're eating something,
at what point
do you not feel it anymore?
About here?
I mean, there's a party
going on inside of you,
but you're not invited.
The only time they nudge you again
is when it's time
to get rid of the garbage.
But don't fool yourself.
They need you.
They need you
to see the outside world,
like a submarine crew.
You're their sonar.
That is your function.
You need to feed them.
Everyone forgets
they're just a slave to them.
You're just a slave.
And you start thinking about yourself.
And you start thinking
about your death
and not theirs.
And it's not fair,
because they're the ones living,
not you.
You may be dead already.
Now I really want to kill myself.
Oh no.
Well...
now that's exactly
the opposite of what I want.
All I'm saying, Mina...
all I'm saying
is you
don't have to die.
Okay?
Thank you, Mr. Williams.
Let's get you home.
You're sure you're not gonna do
anything crazy on your own, right?
Sorry.
I was just... kidding.
I just wanted you to look at me.
Really?
Good night.
Bye.
12 times now I have tried
to kill myself already,
and God just won't let me die.
It's like I'm testing myself...
how much can I keep believing in Him?
How much can He keep forgiving me?
Maybe
I'm just testing Him.
But then one day I realized
that God doesn't ever die,
that He's incapable of dying.
So how can He know
the first thing about death?
That's like asking a newborn baby
about how to live life.
His existence has
nothing to do with death.
He has nothing to do with death.
Okay.
Can you please bring your computer?
I don't want any record
of our communication.
Or I could just delete those.
No. No, the police
can still retrieve it.
After I'm dead,
I don't want anyone knowing
that it was me.
Get in.
Oh. No, I brought my own car.
I was planning on taking it.
We're going in this.
Just get in the back.
Lapis Lazuli.
Mandala.
I'm Gargoyle.
Hi.
- I'm Gallows.
- Hi.
You thought you were going to be
the only one, didn't you?
Yeah, I guess I did.
Sorry.
Couldn't choose just one.
I'm... I'm Ladybird.
Do you want some coffee?
We have coffee.
Of if you're...?
I made sandwiches.
I mean, do you want...
want a sandwich?
Here you go.
Done deal.
Ladies and gentlemen, shall we?
Have you heard about the Vampire?
Supposedly
targeting people like us
who wanna die.
That's the guy who killed that woman
by draining her blood, right?
What was her name?
Rumor says it was Jellyfish.
Who's Jellyfish?
Well, she was a regular
member on Side by Cide.
After that incident
there hasn't been
a single post of hers,
so people think it was her.
She stops posting on a suicide site...
naturally you'd figure
she killed herself.
Either way it means Jellyfish
has left this world.
Vampires are real?
This is it.
Nice place, huh?
So let's hear your ideas.
For what?
Our suicide method.
I brought a gun.
Someone shoot me.
That'd be murder. We want
to commit suicide, not murder someone.
I brought some charcoal.
It's clean and painless.
You pass out first,
and be dead before you know it.
Sounds good to me.
I just need everyone's hand
sealing the entire body of the car.
Charcoal is fine
and all,
but I can do you
one better.
What the hell is that?
It's like carbon monoxide,
except you don't need fire.
You just mix these liquids...
real easy.
It will be painless,
like going to sleep.
It's a kit I bought online.
What kind of liquids?
It's like, you know... kind of like
bleach, detergent, stuff you can get...
- Let me see that.
- Hey, fuckface,
who the hell cares what it is?
I will tell you one thing though:
it's 100% fat-free, motherfucker.
Oh fuck.
There's your sandwiches.
Are... are they dead?
What are you gonna do?
Me? Uh...
What about... what about you?
Do you still want to die?
Uh...
what about you?
Do you want...
do you want to die?
Do you want to die?
I'm not sure.
Well, if you're going to die, I'm leaving.
What are you going to do?
If you're going to die,
I'm going to leave, okay?
- Okay.
- And by the way,
if you don't want to die,
I'm still leaving.
They're... they're dead?
I've got to find out where we are.
If I can find out where we are,
I can find our way out of here.
Okay?
- Okay, well...
- Here, look.
- Well, if we take the...
- No, look, here.
- Here, look.
- ...the van.
It's 10 miles that way.
Oh. Well...
well, what do we do
about the bodies?
- Listen to me.
- Yeah?
Fuck the bodies. We're gonna
pretend like we were never here
and we're gonna walk
10 miles that way, okay?
- We're gonna walk?
- We're gonna walk.
We're gonna leave the van
and we're gonna walk.
- That's impossible.
- It's not impossible.
You've never walked 10 miles before?
You can walk 10 miles.
Let's go, come on.
Come on.
- Okay.
- Ladybird, right?
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
There you go.
There you go. Nice.
Can we...
can we take a little break?
- What?
- Just... my...
Yeah.
Ow.
Oh, these boots aren't
cut out for this terrain.
- There's something on my leg.
- What?
Oh my God.
- What's the matter?
- Can you...?
What... what... what is that?
It's a leech.
What do I do?
Do you have a...
like lighter or salt?
Or pepper also works.
I've got... I've got salt.
Let me see. Let me see.
Come here. All right.
Eww. Eww. Eww. Eww.
Eww.
Oh sh...
Their saliva has enzymes in it
that stops the blood from clotting,
so that's not gonna stop bleeding
for, like, three hours.
What do I... what do I do?
You've gotta suck... suck it out.
Oh, um...
would you mind?
There. Oh.
I swallowed it.
Are you a vampire?
Oh boy.
You've got another one.
What?
Eww.
It's a big one.
This is a little bit embarrassing.
Are...
are you the Vampire?
Are you the Vampire?
We should keep walking.
Wait. Wait.
You've got one too.
On your... look.
I can... I can... it's my turn.
It's okay.
It's really okay.
No, no, no.
Yeah, come on.
Why do you have that bag?
What's in it?
A laptop.
Isn't that Lapis's laptop?
Yeah. She wanted me to delete
the evidence of our conversations.
If everyone was supposed to die,
then who would've
destroyed the evidence?
Did you even plan to die?
I'm the Vampire.
I'm...
Bullshit.
Do you want my blood?
No. If I wanted it,
I would've asked you for it already.
You can have it if you want it.
I won't tell anyone...
anything.
I promise.
Find me when you're ready.
I think I should call him again.
No. No.
He's fine, right? I don't know
why teachers work so late.
And they don't get paid enough,
do they? It's so sad.
It's so sad that they don't
get paid what they should.
Do you think he likes me?
Twice for yes, once for no.
That was yes.
What are you doing in here?
Did you sleep in here all night?
What are you doing?
You know, if you don't...
if you don't like me,
you should just say so.
What?
Otherwise, what's the point
of me doing all this for you?
Stop.
Do you like someone else?
I...
- Do you?
- Yes.
- You do?
- Yeah, I like someone else.
- And you're still with me?
- Listen, Lucy...
Who the hell is Lucy?
Laura.
I meant to say Laura.
I mean, I said "Lucy"...
Go to hell!
How about we go to my place?
Maybe...
maybe you can kill me there.
I want to die in my home.
It's the only place I fit.
Hmm.
Well,
I just think it's too risky.
Because after you die,
it's gonna be hard to get
your body into the car
without someone seeing me.
You won't have to move my body.
I bought a fridge.
So this is my apartment.
Well, it's kind of a basement.
There are no windows.
But it was really cheap, so yeah.
How much?
$50.
$50?
- Yeah.
- Wow. Wow.
She's a beauty.
Will it work?
Yeah , it's perfect.
That's Josh.
Unfortunately, his...
his father couldn't admit
that the boy was his, so...
so I found a new man.
Eric.
He was actually...
he was a really good person.
He was sweet
and kind.
And he always wanted a peaceful,
happy family.
But Josh never took to him,
so Eric started
beating Josh every day.
But I couldn't...
I couldn't stop him.
Um...
I was...
I was more scared
that Eric would leave us, and...
I should have let him leave us.
Eric ended up killing Josh.
Eric's in j-jail?
Yeah.
Maybe he was too young
to have kids.
No.
He was 40.
How old are you?
I'm 28 years old.
You're so young.
Do you know how long before you die?
What do you mean?
Vampires live a long time.
Do you know when you'll die?
I've never died before.
I don't know.
Wake up.
Oh boy.
What are you gonna do
with them after you're gone?
I'll let them go.
You know,
the crows will get them.
You know what?
I'll find a place for them.
Oh, will you?
Yeah.
The sky.
Blood...
makes up 8% of your body.
That means if you weigh 100 lbs
you've got eight lbs
of blood inside of you.
That's about a gallon.
To lose a third of that is lethal.
Each one of these bottles
has a quart.
So if you lose two of these bottles...
it would kill you.
Four would be pretty much
all the blood that you have.
Really?
Yeah.
I thought...
I thought the blood made up
80% of your body.
No. You're thinking
about water.
Your body's made up
of about 70% water.
This is
all the blood you have.
Not much.
And yet without it you're dead.
Blood...
blood is life itself.
It's kind of beautiful.
I guess I'm giving you my life.
Exactly.
Simon Williams.
Laura King.
"Jellyfish."
It's a terrible book.
You should be helping her.
Why aren't you helping her?
That's the normal thing to do,
is to help somebody when they're...
Simon.
That's enough.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mommy.
I'm sorry.
Did I startle you?
Say, would you happen to know
Simon's computer password?
What's in here?
What is in here?
Are you sad?
Is it because I don't
come around here anymore?
I know. It's too bad.
Simon is such a jerk.
He's such a jerk.
He has a girlfriend now, right?
What's she like?
Has she been here before?
What's wrong?
Are you trying to remember?
It's okay.
Come on, you can do it!
Don't worry about it.
Don't think so hard,
'cause your veins might explode.
I'll figure this out on my own.
Bingo.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't do it.
I'm sure you're disappointed.
This is the second time
I've failed to die.
If you don't mind,
how about I live for you?
You could drink my blood
whenever you wanted,
however much you wanted.
But...
you have to promise me
no more killing...
that I'd be the only one.
Can I drink from your neck?
I've never drunk like that before.
Do whatever you want.
My blood is your blood.
Mandala...
I'm Ingrid Bell.
I'm Simon Williams.
It's nice to meet you,
Simon Williams.
It's nice to meet you too.
Hello.
Excuse me, can I help you?
Uh, I'm here for Mina.
Oh, you're the teacher.
Yes, come with me.
Okay.
Is everything okay?
Well, no, it's not okay.
We've got her in intensive care.
- I see.
- She had quite a night last night.
We almost lost her.
She's a bit pale.
She's been through a lot.
She's in a state of shock
from the blood loss.
It wasn't fatal.
That said, her condition's
far from stable.
She's a Japanese exchange student.
She's in my biology class.
Yeah, her host parents
from her home stay
are on the East Coast
this weekend.
You know,
she had to call 911 herself.
Makes you wonder
if she really wanted to die.
Well, maybe she just got scared
at the last minute
and changed her mind.
We found your phone number
in her phone's call history.
It looks like she tried calling you
over and over again.
- Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Is there anything I can do, Miss Ray?
Well, she's lost a lot of blood.
Do you know what your blood type is?
Mine?
Uh, yeah.
She needs blood.
Maybe you can help us.
I don't know
what my blood type is, so...
Well, let's find out, shall we?
Come on, it's just very simple.
Okay.
Now just one little prick.
- You'll barely feel it.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Ow.
All right,
I just need a drop.
Here.
All right, yes,
sometimes it's better if you don't look.
- Yeah, I don't want to look at it.
- There you go.
Okay, gotcha.
Okay, congratulations.
You're O-positive.
It means you can help her.
- Oh.
- Here.
You know, I know that she is
really gonna appreciate this.
Okay.
Yeah, let's just...
swing yourself around. Good.
- And lay down.
- Okay.
All right, now...
You don't look like needles
are your favorite thing, huh?
No.
Oh God.
All right,
now make a fist for me.
I am.
Let's see.
That looks pretty good.
All right.
Simon!
Stop.
Stop. I...
Stop. I can't...
I can't see anything. It's...
everything is dark.
I can't see.
I'm anemic.
I gave too much blood.
Your high school teacher stopped by
and donated this blood for you.
Is he here?
No, he left already.
But he said he'd stop by tomorrow
and check on you.
Just rest.
- Hmm.
- So this is it.
A balloon.
Yeah.
I'm sorry
it's a bit of a mess in here.
It's okay.
- I'll get you something to sit on.
- Okay. Okay.
Here.
So I can take pictures with this.
Or I...
I can do your...
do your video also.
Okay.
I brought you an apple.
I used to dance.
What kind of dancing?
Ballet dancing.
Belly dancing?
No, not belly dancing.
Ballet dancing. Ballet.
It's weird to dance on a refrigerator.
- On a freezer.
- A freezer. A freezer.
Okay.
Hmm.
Why do people walk?
Walk?
Yeah, why do they walk?
When I was little, I used to...
I used to think that people walked
'cause they liked the sound
that their footsteps made
and that all the people
on the street were walking
'cause they liked the sound.
- Huh.
- Hmm.
I'd put, like,
pebbles in...
pebbles in my shoes
so they made more noise
when I walked.
One day my teacher told me...
it was like I was walking funny,
so she made me take them out.
I hated school.
Me too.
I'll tell you what...
you can walk however you want.
- Okay?
- I know.
- Okay.
- Here.
Okay.
Hi, everyone.
My name...
my name is Maria Lucas.
I'm 25.
And I'd be turning
26 next month
if I weren't about to die.
But I'm... I'm done.
I never figured out how to enjoy...
enjoy life.
It just really...
it's always seemed
so strange to me,
didn't make sense.
But in my next life
I want to be human again.
Hades is helping me to die.
He's... he's behind
the camera right now.
I wonder if I'll see you in heaven.
We met on a website called...
called Side by Cide...
and decided that we were
gonna die together, so...
I'm gonna go first.
Don't take too long, okay?
Okay.
Do you ever die in your own dream?
I've never died in my own dream.
Is it even possible...
to die in your own dream?
If this were my dream,
I would never die.
What if this isn't your dream?
Hmm?
What if it's mine?
Is this your dream?