>> SO YOU HAVE TO SPRAY IT DOWN
REAL GOOD, SEE?
ALL OVER.
HERE.
YOU TRY.
[ BOTTLE SPRAYING ]
NO, UH...
NOT TOO MUCH.
SO, HOW DO YOU LIKE IT?
>> WELL, IT'S PRETTY EASY, AS I
FIGURED.
>> OH, SO THAT'S WHY YOU WANT
THE JOB HERE.
>> YEAH, AND IT'S ON MY WAY HOME
FROM SCHOOL.
>> OH.
WICKENHAVEN HIGH?
>> YEAH.
SO, SHOULD I FILL OUT AN
APPLICATION TODAY WITH YOU?
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY.
WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN A, UH...
FAMILY-OPERATED BUSINESS.
>> OH.
>> BUT THERE MAY BE A POSITION
OPENING UP SHORTLY.
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE IT A LITTLE
MORE ELBOW GREASE, AND I'LL --
I'LL RUN THE IDEA BY THE REAL
BOSS -- MY WIFE.
[ BOTTLE SPRAYING ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
A LOVELY LITTLE HIGH-SCHOOLER'S
HERE.
SEEKS EMPLOYMENT.
>> AND?
>> I'M CONSIDERING HER.
A PRETTY YOUNG FACE BEHIND THE
COUNTER'S WHAT WE NEED.
>> [ SIGHS ]
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO HIRE
STRANGERS.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I MEAN, YOU COULD USE SOMEONE,
MAYBE, BUT NOT AS AN EMPLOYEE.
IS SHE FROM OUT OF TOWN?
>> IT WOULDN'T MATTER.
WE COULD JUST KEEP HER IN THE
DARK.
>> I SAID NO.
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE A SOFT
SPOT FOR THE CUTE ONES?
>> BUT SHE COULD BE A MAGNET TO
PULL IN THE OTHER CUTE ONES.
I'M CERTAINLY NOT DRAWING
THEM IN.
THERE'S SOMETHING TO BE SAID FOR
YOUNG, INNOCENT FLESH.
>> OKAY, IT LOOKS LIKE I'M GONNA
HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF THIS ONE,
JUST TO GET YOU TO SHUT UP ABOUT
HER.
>> DAMN IT, JOAN!
WE COULD AT LEAST OFFER HER A
FREE TAN FIRST!
[ SIGHS ]
WE REALLY NEED TO FIND A BETTER
METHOD.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> PLEASE, LINDSAY?
YOU TOLD ME TWO DAYS AGO THAT
YOU'D COME.
>> NO. I REFUSE TO BE THE THIRD
WHEEL SLEEPING UNDER THE SAME
ROOF AS YOUR SISTER.
SHE ALWAYS FLIRTS WITH ME, AND
IT'S REALLY AWKWARD.
AND SO IS HER NEW HAIR COLOR.
>> SHE KNOWS YOU'LL NEVER SWING
THAT WAY.
CAN YOU PLEASE STILL JUST COME?
I MEAN, IT'S REALLY MEAN A LOT
TO ME RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M SURE IT'D MEAN A LOT MORE
TO HER.
WHY ARE YOU ACTING SAD AND ALL?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THIS GUY.
>> YEAH, BUT, I MEAN, HE'S STILL
FAMILY.
>> JUST DO THE FAMILY THING
WITHOUT ME AND BRING ME BACK
SOMETHING COOL.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT KIND
OF STUFF HE HAS.
AND I TOLD MY SISTER THAT I'D
BRING HER BACK SOMETHING REALLY
NICE.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, I'LL PROBABLY
JUST GO AND BUY HER SOMETHING
BECAUSE HE'S NOT GONNA HAVE
ANYTHING GIRLY.
>> WHY?
WASN'T HE YOUR GAY UNCLE?
>> THAT'S JUST FAMILY GOSSIP.
AND EVERYONE JUST ASSUMED HE WAS
GAY BECAUSE HE NEVER GOT
MARRIED AND HE NEVER HAD A
GIRLFRIEND -- THAT ANYBODY
KNEW OF.
>> SO, HE DIED A VIRGIN?
>> APPARENTLY.
>> CAN THEY TELL THAT FROM AN
AUTOPSY?
>> EW.
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT REMINDS ME -- MY DAD IS
MAKING ME PICK UP HIS ASHES
TOMORROW WHEN WE GET THERE.
>> EW.
WHAT'S THAT GOT TO DO WITH YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS NOBODY ELSE REALLY
CARES.
HELLO?
>> HI.
>> OH, HI.
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> YES. I'M HERE TO PICK UP AN
URN.
>> SURE.
SARA.
>> [ GRUMBLES ]
WHAT IS IT, GREG?
I WAS RESTING MY EYES.
>> SOMEONE'S PICKING UP.
>> MM. SURNAME?
>> UH, NUNEZ -- ARLO NUNEZ.
>> CHECK THE BOOK.
IT'S IN CRATE 43.
NO FUNERAL, NO MEMORIAL.
IT'S IN THE LOT.
>> CERTAINLY.
>> IT'LL BE ONE MOMENT.
>> UM, SO, DO I GIVE YOU THIS?
>> OH, NO, DEAR, IT'S BEEN TAKEN
CARE OF.
>> OKAY.
UM, SO, WHERE'S THE MAIN PART OF
WICKHAVEN?
>> IT'S WICKENHAVEN, AND YOU'RE
STANDIN' IN THE HEART OF IT.
[ COUGHS ]
THIS STRING O' STORES HERE, IT'S
BASICALLY OUR SHOPPIN' DISTRICT.
RUMOR HAS IT WE'RE GONNA GET AN
OLD NAVY AT THE END OF THE
WINTER.
>> SO, WHAT AROUND HERE WOULD BE
THE BEST PLACE TO GET SOMEBODY A
GIFT?
>> A GIFT?
>> YEAH, LIKE A SOUVENIR OR
SOMETHING -- SOMETHING CUTE AND
UNIQUE FROM THIS TOWN THAT YOU
CAN GET AT, LIKE, ANY OTHER
RANDOM PLACE.
>> MM. SOMETHING UNIQUE, YOU
SAY?
I SUGGEST VIRGIN LEATHERS ACROSS
THE STREET.
YOU CAN GET ONE THERE.
>> ONE WHAT?
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT.
>> OH, THE MAKER OF HIGH-END
DESIGNER PURSES.
BASICALLY WHY ANY FOLKS COME TO
THIS OL' GHOST TOWN.
>> HERE.
>> OH. THANK YOU.
>> SO, YOU'VE BEEN TELLING HER
ABOUT VIRGIN LEATHERS?
>> YES. THE BEST HANDMADE
HANDBAGS AND ZIPPER WORK YOU CAN
EVER FIND.
>> IT'S RIGHT ACROSS THE STREET,
RIGHT THERE.
>> I HIGHLY RECOMMEND YOU GO
TAKE A LOOKSEE, DEAR.
>> GO ASK TO HOLD ONE AND FEEL
IT.
>> THE TEXTURE JUST CAN'T BE
BEAT.
>> MNH-MNH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, IF MY SISTER
ISN'T BACK FROM GETTING GAS,
I'LL -- I'LL GO CHECK IT OUT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
>> BYE.
>> IS -- IS THAT THE
"TEENAGE WITCH" GIRL?
>> IT SURE IS.
HOLDING, WHAT I BELIEVE, WAS HER
FIFTH CUSTOMIZED PURCHASE.
>> HMM.
>> THAT ONE DID TURN OUT
INCREDIBLY NICE.
WE CATER TO MANY CELEBRITIES.
>> ARE YOU, LIKE, THE DESIGNER
OR SOMETHING?
>> GUILTY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
YOU ARE, LIKE, SO POPULAR, AND I
CAN DEFINITELY SEE WHY.
>> WELL, IT SHOULD BE VERY
FAMILIAR.
YOU LOOK LIKE A GIRL WHO KEEPS
UP WITH THE LATEST TRENDS.
I'M SURPRISED YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
OF US BY NOW.
WE SELL MOSTLY CUSTOM COUTURE.
OUR PRODUCT IS IN HIGH DEMAND.
>> I MEAN, I DEFINITELY WANT
ONE.
I JUST -- I DON'T EVER SEE
MYSELF BUYING LEATHER 'CAUSE I'M
A VEGETARIAN.
ARE THESE MADE OUT OF BABY COW?
>> OH, HEAVENS, NO.
NOW, THIS ONE IS BABY LLAMA.
AND UP THERE, WE HAVE BABY
OSTRICH.
THE BABIES ARE THE SOFTEST.
FAR LESS EXPENSIVE THAN SLINK.
>> SLINK?
>> THE UNBORN FETUS.
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
THESE ARE PROBABLY WAY OUT OF MY
PRICE RANGE.
>> OH, DARLING, I CAN GIVE YOU
25% OFF, BUT NO MORE THAN THAT.
LOOK AT THE EXQUISITE DETAIL ON
THAT ONE.
THAT TAKES 80 HOURS OF CUSTOM
STITCHING, MOSTLY BY HAND.
YOU    MUHAVE ONE.
>> WELL, I MEAN, IT WOULD BE
KIND OF CUTE FOR MY LITTLE
SISTER, BUT I JUST DON'T SEE HER
HAVING ANYTHING THAT'S NICE AT
HER AGE BECAUSE, I MEAN, SHE'S
ONLY 8.
>> BUT THAT'S THE PERFECT AGE
FOR A DESIGNER PURSE.
>> ARE YOU SURE THIS IS IT?
>> YES.
>> I DEFINITELY DO NOT REMEMBER
THIS PLACE.
>> KAYLA, HOW COULD YOU?
YOU WERE JUST A BABY LAST TIME
WE VISITED.
WOW.
>> WOW. THIS IS AMAZING.
>> PLACE IS HUGE.
>> HE SURE HAD AN INTERESTING
TASTE IN FURNITURE, I MUST SAY.
>> NO ONE TOLD ME HE WAS RICH.
WHAT GOOD IS THERE IN EVEN
SELLING IT?
>> WELL, WE CAN ALWAYS LEAVE IT
FOR THE REST OF THE FAMILY.
>> NO ONE'S GONNA COME ALL THE
WAY OUT HERE TO THE STICKS.
>> JAMIE MIGHT.
>> YEAH, HE'S KIND OF WEIRD.
NICE.
[ CLATTERING ]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THAT WAS WEIRD.
>> SOMEONE'S DEFINITELY HERE,
AND THEY'RE UPSTAIRS.
>> WHO COULD IT BE?
>> YOU MUST BE ARLO'S FRIENDS.
>> OH. HI.
I'M COURTNEY AND THIS IS KAYLA.
WE'RE XAVIER'S DAUGHTERS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I REMEMBER YOU.
I CHANGED YOUR DIAPER ONCE OR
TWICE.
I'M YOUR AUNT -- AUNT MAY.
>> OH.
IT'S AUNT MAY. HI.
>> WELL, IT'S NICE TO FINALLY
MEET YOU.
>> MY, KAYLA, ALL GROWN UP.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU SINCE YOU
WERE AN INFANT.
SO I ASSUME YOU ARE HERE FOR THE
SAME REASON I AM.
>> YEAH.
>> ATTEMPTING THE DAUNTING TASK
OF WEEDING THROUGH MY POOR
BROTHER'S STUFF.
>> YEAH, WE WERE HOPING TO GET
SOME STUFF FOR OUR DAD, SOME
THINGS HE THINKS ARE IMPORTANT.
>> OH, PLEASE, TAKE WHATEVER
YOU LIKE.
ALL I WANT FOR MYSELF HERE IS
RIGHT HERE IN THIS SHOE BOX.
WELL, DON'T LET ME TALK YOUR
EARS OFF.
MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME.
THERE'S PLENTY OF GUEST ROOMS TO
CHOOSE FROM AND LOTS OF GOODIES
TO SORT THROUGH.
THAT ARLO, HE WAS SUCH A PACK
RAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANKS.
>> TAKE CARE.
>> WHAT THE HELL, KAYLA?
DAD SAID WE'D HAVE THE HOUSE ALL
TO OURSELVES.
NOW WE HAVE TO SHARE IT WITH
SOME LONG-LOST AUNT.
>> COURTNEY, DON'T BE SELFISH.
FOR ALL WE KNOW, THEY COULD HAVE
BEEN REALLY CLOSE.
AND I DON'T KNOW.
SHE SEEMS KIND OF COOL.
WE SHOULD GET TO KNOW HER.
>> ARE YOU FORGETTING THAT THIS
IS OUR VACATION?
AND HOW AM I GONNA GET HIGH IF
SHE'S AROUND?
>> PHONE'S FOR YOU.
>> HELLO?
>> HEY, IT'S KAYLA.
>> HEY.
>> JUST GOT SETTLED IN HERE.
>> HOW IS IT?
>> IT'S BORING.
YOU SHOULD'VE COME.
>> HOW'S YOUR ROOM?
>> THIS ONE'S GIRLISH, BUT THE
OTHER ONES ARE TOTALLY GOTHIC.
SO, I BOUGHT HAILEY THE CUTEST
DESIGNER PURSE.
>> REALLY?
>> HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF
VIRGIN LEATHERS?
>> UM, YEAH.
YOU GOT A KNOCKOFF, THEN.
>> NO, IT'S A REAL ONE.
WELL, IT BETTER BE.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
THOSE THINGS ARE LIKE $4,000, AT
LEAST.
>> WELL, THE ONE I GOT WAS LIKE
400 BUCKS.
IT WAS FROM THE MAIN STORE OR
WHATEVER.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
I MEAN, ALL THE IT GIRLS HAVE
VIRGIN LEATHERS -- BRITNEY,
CHRISTINA...
>> YEAH, AND SHE ALSO GAVE ME A
FREE PASS FOR A TAN IN THE SAME
SHOPPING CENTER.
>> GREAT. NOW YOU'LL MAKE ME
LOOK EVEN MORE PALE.
HEY. DO YOU THINK YOU COULD GET
ME ONE?
YOU STILL OWE ME FOR WHEN MY
PARENTS PAID FOR THAT CRUISE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY CAN'T JUST KEEP
CHARGING STUFF ON THIS CARD.
>> JUST MAX SOMETHING OUT
ALREADY.
WHO CARES?
BESIDES, THAT'S WAY BELOW FACE
VALUE.
SO, WHAT'S IT LIKE?
IT'S A SMALL ONE WITH --
IT'S KIND OF RETRO-LOOKING, AND
THERE'S A SMALL ROSE ON IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET ME CALL YOU BACK.
I'M GONNA LOOK FOR IT.
>> LOVE YOU, BITCH.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
>> COURTNEY.
>> WHAT?
>> HAVE YOU SEEN HAILEY'S PURSE?
>> NO.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
I THOUGHT I BROUGHT IT IN.
I JUST -- I CAN'T FIND IT
ANYWHERE.
>> PROBABLY LEFT IT IN THE CAR.
>> PROBABLY.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN GO OUT AND
CHECK FOR ME?
>> [ SCOFFS ]
KAYLA, PLEASE.
I'M ALREADY PISSED THERE'S NO
DIAL-UP.
>> IT'S JUST, LIKE, IT'S DARK
OUTSIDE, AND...
I THINK THE CAR IS LOCKED.
AND YOU HAVE THE KEYS.
>> NO, IT'S UNLOCKED.
>> UGH! FINE.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
[ MUFFLED GUITAR PLAYING ]
>> YEAH.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
I SAID YEAH.
[ SIGHS ]
>> COURTNEY.
>> OH, HEY.
>> I WASN'T SURE IF YOU'D EATEN,
SO I MADE YOU A SPECIAL
CASSEROLE.
>> MMM. IT'S GOOD.
>> I'M SO GLAD YOU ENJOY IT.
IT IS SO SPECIAL.
>> WHAT'S SO SPECIAL ABOUT IT?
>> I FOUND IT IN THE FREEZER, SO
THAT MEANS IT WAS THE LAST MEAL
ARLO PREPARED BEFORE HE DIED.
>> [ GAGS ]
UNCLE ARLO WAS COOKING FOR
HIMSELF?
I THOUGHT HE WAS BEDRIDDEN.
>> BEDRIDDEN?
COURTNEY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
UNCLE ARLO WAS --
>> HEY, IT WASN'T IN THE CAR.
OH. SORRY FOR INTERRUPTING.
>> OH, PLEASE, SIT.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I MIGHT AS WELL SET THE RECORD
STRAIGHT FOR THE BOTH OF YOU.
SOME OF THE FAMILY ACCEPTS THE
FACT THAT UNCLE ARLO WENT
NATURALLY.
IT'S EASIER ON THE SPIRIT.
BUT THAT'S JUST NOT THE CASE.
THE TRUTH IS, ARLO WENT MISSING
AND WAS MOST LIKELY MURDERED.
>> WHAT?
WAIT. MURDERED?
>> THERE WASN'T ANY PROOF, SO WE
JUST AGREED THAT IT WAS BEST FOR
THE REST OF THE FAMILY NOT TO
DISCERN ANY DETAILS.
>> I MEAN, WHAT HAPPENED?
DOES OUR DAD KNOW?
>> I'M SURE HE WAS TOLD THE
EASIER VERSION.
>> I HAVE TO CALL HIM.
>> NO NEED, NO NEED.
I THINK IT'S BEST FOR HIM IF WE
JUST KEEP IT ON THE HUSH-HUSH.
FOR NOW. OKAY?
>> WHAT?
>> I JUST THOUGHT I COULD SHARE.
IT'S WHAT MY MEDICATION TENDS TO
MAKE ME DO.
PROMISE YOU WON'T DISCOURAGE
HIM.
LET'S BE GROWN UP ABOUT THIS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOUR
FATHER EVERYTHING.
>> I MEAN, WHAT HAPPENED?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT
HAPPENED?
>> I'M NOT ONE TO SAY.
HE JUST WENT MISSING AFTER
GETTING A SECOND JOB AT THE
BLACK STALLION.
>> IS ANYONE DOING ANYTHING?
ARE THEY LOOKING FOR HIM?
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S A REAL SHOCK FOR ALL OF US.
I'M SO SORRY FOR GETTING YOU
GUYS WORKED UP.
I HOPE IT WON'T KEEP YOU FROM
SLEEPING.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN THE HALL IF
YOU NEED ANYTHING, OKAY?
NIGHT-NIGHT.
>> OKAY. NOW I'M REALLY STARTING
TO FREAK OUT.
>> NOW YOU STILL WANT TO STAY?
>> I MEAN, DAD MUST HAVE KNOWN.
>> NO. I'M CALLING HIM.
HE WOULD'VE TOLD US.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M NOT GONNA KEEP A SECRET
FROM DAD.
I'M JUST NOT.
>> WELL, WHAT IF HE'S BEEN
KEEPING IT A SECRET FROM US?
>> I THINK THAT IT'S TIME TO
SMOKE ONE.
YOU IN ON THIS?
>> NO, I'M GOOD.
I DON'T LIKE YOUR STUFF.
I GOT MY OWN.
>> SUIT YOURSELF.
[ BLENDER MOTOR WHIRRING ]
>> OH! WELL, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> CARROT JUICE?
>> UM...
NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I HEARD THAT MAKES YOUR SKIN
ORANGE.
>> TRUE.
WHY YOU WORRIED ABOUT SKIN AT
YOUR AGE?
THAT FAKE TANNER WILL MAKE IT
TWICE AS ORANGE.
>> I DON'T USE THAT.
>> OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE NATURALLY DARK.
>> WELL, I STILL LIKE TO
MAINTAIN AN EVEN TONE.
I'M ACTUALLY THINKING ABOUT
GOING TO THE TANNING SALON
TODAY. MAYBE.
>> WHAT FUN!
WELL, YOU WON'T FIND ANY FOOD IN
THIS HOUSE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> I'M ACTUALLY LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING FOR THIS HEADACHE.
>> OH, YOU POOR THING.
LOOK IN MY PURSE.
I DON'T GO ANYWHERE WITHOUT IT.
>> THAT'S...
>> SORRY IT'S GENERIC.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>> OF COURSE.
ANYTIME, SWEETIE.
>> COURTNEY!
COURTNEY, WAKE UP.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> AUNT MAY TOOK MY PURSE.
SHE TOTALLY TOOK IT AND MOVED
ALL HER CRAP INTO IT.
>> HAILEY'S PURSE?
>> YES.
ARE YOU LISTENING TO A THING I'M
SAYING?
I MEAN -- OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SLEEPY.
>> SHOULD I SAY SOMETHING?
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> WHAT SHOULD I SAY?
"UH, THAT'S MY PURSE YOU'RE
USING"?
>> YES, THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'D
EXPECT YOU TO SAY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK BEHIND MY
BACK, YOU KNOW.
WE'RE ALL FAMILY.
LAST NIGHT, I OPENED UP TO YOU
TWO AND WAS HONEST ABOUT ARLO.
>> I'M JUST CONFUSED.
>> I SAW THE PURSE LYING THERE,
ASSUMED IT WAS ONE OF ARLO'S
THINGS, THOUGHT IT WAS UP FOR
GRABS, SO I CLAIMED IT.
MY MISTAKE.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT I GOT
THAT FOR MY LITTLE SISTER.
>> YOU BOUGHT IT HERE, IN
WICKENHAVEN?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I'LL GO CLEAN IT OUT
FOR YOU, AND IF MY MAKEUP HAS
STAINED IT, I'LL GET YOU A NEW
ONE.
>> WELL, IT WAS EXPENSIVE.
>> SO SORRY FOR THE
MISUNDERSTANDING.
I WOULD LOVE FOR YOU TO SHOW ME
WHERE THE STORE WAS.
I'D LIKE TO HAVE ONE FOR MYSELF
TO BRING HOME.
>> WHEN ARE YOU GOING HOME?
>> THURSDAY, MOST LIKELY, BUT I
WAS HOPING WE COULD ALL SPEND
SOME FAMILY TIME TOGETHER.
WHO KNOWS WHEN WE'LL HAVE
ANOTHER CHANCE TO DO SO?
>> WELL, THAT LITTLE SHOPPING
CENTER SEEMS TO BE THE ONLY
PLACE TO GO.
>> OH, YES.
WEREN'T YOU TRYING TO GO
TANNING?
>> YEAH, AND I GUESS I CAN TAKE
YOU NEXT DOOR.
THAT'S WHERE THE SHOP IS.
>> PERFECT.
I CAN PICK ONE OUT FOR MYSELF,
JUST AS CUTE, WHILE YOU GET A
NICE, LONG TAN.
A DATE WITH MY NIECE -- WHAT
FUN.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> HELLO?
TANNING.
YEAH, BUT I DIDN'T TAN ENOUGH,
SO I CAME BACK, AND I'M DOING
TWICE THE MAX THIS TIME.
YEAH, HE TOLD ME HE CHANGED
THE BULBS, BUT I DON'T BELIEVE
HIM, SO I'M USING A DIFFERENT
BED.
I ALSO BOUGHT BRONZER.
'CAUSE I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
SAMPLE LAST TIME BROKE ME OUT.
I PROBABLY JUST CAN'T USE
TINGLERS.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, LET ME FINISH
UP HERE, AND IF I HAVE TIME,
THEN I'LL STOP BY.
OKAY, BYE.
AAH!
>> [ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
>> WELL, HELLO. WELCOME.
>> HI.
>> YOU'VE COME TO DO AWAY WITH
THAT PALE SKIN?
>> UM, I ACTUALLY HAVE A FREE
PASS, SO I THOUGHT MAYBE I'D
JUST GIVE IT A TRY.
>> FIRST TIME?
>> YEAH.
>> SAVE IT FOR NEXT TIME.
FIRST TAN'S FREE.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
>> JUST, UH, SIGN THE
HIGHLIGHTED AREAS.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
DO YOU NEED ANY LOTIONS OR
EYEWEAR, MISS, UH...
NUNEZ?
>> I'M SET, THANKS.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU HAVE MINUTES LEFT.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THE NAME'S ALREADY IN THE
SYSTEM.
>> ARLO NUNEZ?
>> YES, AND HIS UNLIMITED
PACKAGE DOESN'T RUN OUT UNTIL
THE END OF THE MONTH.
>> WELL, HE'S NOT AROUND
ANYMORE, SO...
>> WELL, UH...
SINCE YOU'RE RELATED TO HIM AND
I'M SUCH A NICE GUY, I'LL LET
YOU USE HIS PLAN.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
>> ROOM 6.
IT'S MY BEST BED.
>> THANKS.
>> K-A-Y-L-A.
KAYLA.
[ GIGGLING ]
OH, PRECIOUS...
KAYLA.
TIGHT...
OH, PRECIOUS...
LITTLE.
TIGHT...
[ SIGHS ]
LITTLE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS.
[ SIGHS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS.
KAYLA...
[ LAUGHING ]
I'M WATCHING YOU.
[ CHUCKLES ]
UGH.
OH.
>> WAS 15 MINUTES LONG ENOUGH?
>> ALMOST TOO LONG.
THAT BED GETS REALLY HOT.
>> JUST THINK OF IT AS YOUR
PRIVATE OASIS.
>> WOW. OKAY. UH...
WELL, THANK YOU.
>> ARE YOU COMING BACK TOMORROW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT MIGHT BE TOO SOON.
>> I'D LIKE TO SPACE IT OUT,
MAYBE SEE HOW MY SKIN FEELS.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU AFRAID YOUR SKIN WILL
TURN TO LEATHER?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
THANK YOU.
>> [ GIGGLING ]
[ GUITAR PLAYING ]
[ Ringing ]
>> HELLO?
>> COURTNEY, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA CALL ONCE YOU ARRIVED.
>> YEAH, SORRY.
YEAH, WE'RE FINE.
>> HOW'S THE SLEEPING
ARRANGEMENTS?
>> GOOD. THIS HOUSE IS HUGE.
I DIDN'T THINK HE WAS THIS RICH.
>> WELL, COURTNEY, "WEALTHY" IS
THE PROPER TERM.
DID YOU FIND MY PRIZED CLUBS?
>> NOT YET.
THERE'S LIKE A MILLION PILES OF
CRAP TO GO THROUGH.
>> WELL, HE PROBABLY KEPT
EVERYTHING I LOANED HIM.
WHAT ABOUT MY APRON AND MATCHING
OVEN-MITT SET?
>> I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW, DAD.
>> YOU FIND ANYTHING YOURSELF
WORTH KEEPING?
>> NOT REALLY.
STILL LOOKING, THOUGH.
>> MM. HOW'S KAYLA?
IS SHE RIGHT THERE WITH YOU?
>> NO. SHE'S OUT SHOPPING WITH
AUNT MAY.
>> AUNT MAY?
>> YEP.
SHE WAS HERE WHEN WE GOT HERE
LAST NIGHT, UNFORTUNATELY.
>> WHAT?
MAY?
MAY...MAY...
>> I THINK SHE PROBABLY PICKED
EVERYTHING GOOD HERSELF.
>> COURTNEY --
>> I KNOW. IT SUCKS, BECAUSE
SOMEBODY CAN'T GET THE WHOLE
ENTIRE HOUSE TO OURSELVES.
WHY DO YOU THINK WE CAME ALL THE
WAY OUT HERE?
FIRST DIBS -- WHAT HAPPENED TO
THAT?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE AN AUNT MAY.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
GRANDPA COULD'VE HAD A FLING.
>> I'M CERTAIN.
>> YEAH. I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I'M COMING HOME.
YOU CAN DIG THROUGH YOUR
BROTHER'S GAY TOYS ALL NIGHT
LONG IF YOU WANT TO YOURSELF.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
ATTITUDE.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US WHAT
REALLY HAPPENED TO HIM?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> [ COUGHS ]
THIS CRAZY LADY SAID THAT HE
WENT MISSING AND HE WAS PROBABLY
MURDERED.
>> WHAT?
I WANT YOU AND KAYLA TO STAY PUT
AND MAKE SURE THIS AUNT MAY
CHARACTER DOESN'T LEAVE.
I'M COMING OUT THERE TONIGHT TO
GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
>> WHAT ABOUT HAILEY?
>> HAILEY WILL HAVE TO COME.
>> FINE.
I MEAN, SHE PROBABLY IS REALLY
JUST CRAZY, JUST LIKE MOM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH VENTING ABOUT MOM.
EVERY TIME YOU GET INTO ONE OF
YOUR MOODS...
>> ENJOY THE LONG-ASS DRIVE.
>> GOODBYE, COURTNEY.
I'LL SEE YOU IN A COUPLE OF
HOURS.
>> BYE.
>> EXACTLY.
I HAD SO MUCH FUN.
>> HI, COURTNEY!
>> HEY.
>> WE HAD A LOVELY TIME.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AUNT MAY GOT THE CUTEST
LITTLE PURSE.
I'M KIND OF HOPING SHE'LL TRADE
ME FOR THE ONE I GOT HAILEY.
>> OH, WE'LL SEE.
>> WHAT LITTLE NEAT THINGS YOU
FIND?
>> OH, NOTHING.
THERE'S NOT MUCH HERE WORTH
KEEPING.
>> OH, COURTNEY, YOU MUST BE
HUNGRY.
I'LL HAVE MY FAMOUS PUMPKIN PIE
READY IN 40 MINUTES.
>> MMM.
>> I GOT TO TALK TO YOU.
>> WHAT?
>> COME ON.
>> I'M COMING.
>> JUST GET IN THE ROOM.
>> WHAT?
>> KAYLA...
>> WHOA.
>> ...I TALKED TO DAD.
WE HAVE NO AUNT MAYs IN THE
FAMILY.
>> HE'S SO CLUELESS.
>> NO, NO, SERIOUSLY.
SERIOUSLY, I DON'T KNOW WHO THE
HELL THIS BITCH IS, BUT SHE'S
NOT ANY -- SHE'S NOT OUR AUNT.
SHE'S NOT AN AUNT OF OURS AT
ALL -- AT ALL.
>> WELL, THEN WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO?
>> DAD'S COMING DOWN HERE.
>> RIGHT NOW?
>> YEAH, HE'S DRIVING DOWN RIGHT
NOW.
>> OH, GOSH.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> FOUND IT -- ALL THIS STUFF.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH, TONS OF IT.
>> OH, GROSS.
I GUESS THAT PROVES HE WAS GAY
AND PROBABLY DID WORK AT A GAY
BAR.
>> THE BLACK STALLION.
I FOUND PAY STUBS IN THE DRAWER.
>> I GUESS THAT PROVES AUNT MAY
DOES KNOW MORE THAN WE DO.
>> STOP CALLING HER AUNT MAY.
JUST "MAY" OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
DAD WILL STRAIGHTEN IT OUT WHEN
HE GETS HERE.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T GONNA
SMOKE IN HERE, BY THE WAY.
CAN YOU SMELL IT?
>> DUDE.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
>> COURTNEY, KAYLA.
>> WHAT?
>> WHAT IS GOING ON IN THERE?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THANK YOU.
>> WELL, DO YOU BOTH LIKE
GREEN-BEAN CASSEROLE?
>> NO. WE'RE FINE, THANKS.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
>> ALL RIGHT. WELL, THERE WILL
BE A PLACE SET FOR BOTH OF YOU
AT THE DINING-ROOM TABLE IF
EITHER OF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> HELLO?
HELLO?
COME ON, SWEETIE.
SEE IF ANYONE'S HOME.
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> THAT'S THE SAME QUESTION I
WAS GONNA ASK YOU.
OH. YOU MUST BE AUNT MAY.
>> WHO'S ASKING?
>> XAVIER NUNEZ.
THIS IS MY BROTHER'S HOUSE.
>> OH, YOU'RE XAVIER.
WISH WE MET SOONER.
GUESS YOU COULDN'T MAKE IT TO
ANY OF THOSE FAMILY REUNIONS.
>> WHAT FAMILY REUNIONS?
>> MAYBE YOU WEREN'T INVITED,
AND I CAN SEE WHY.
>> IT'S FUNNY HOW NO ONE EVER
TOLD ME ABOUT YOU.
>> YOUR FATHER LEFT MY MOTHER
FOR YOUR MOTHER.
>> WHAT?!
YEAH, YOU TRY AND EXPLAIN THAT.
COURTNEY, KAYLA.
>> HAILEY!
>> KAYLA!
>> LONG DRIVE, EH?
>> YEAH, IT WAS.
TAKE HER UPSTAIRS, WILL YOU?
>> OKAY. COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> SEE YOU, HAILEY.
>> WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT TO
TAKE OVER MY BROTHER'S HOUSE?
>> WELL, ASIDE FROM THE FACT
THAT I'M HIS HALF-SISTER, I WAS
HIS CLOSEST FRIEND.
>> WHY THE HELL DIDN'T HE EVER
MENTION YOU?
>> HE WAS AFRAID TO CALL YOU.
>> HE CALLED.
>> HE SAID HE COULDN'T OPEN UP
TO YOU.
YOU SHUNNED HIM FOR HIS SAME-SEX
ATTRACTION.
>> I NEVER WANTED TO KNOW HIS
BUSINESS.
>> YEAH, I PICTURED YOU AS A
SELFISH BROTHER.
YOU WEREN'T EVEN HERE TO WATCH
HIM DIE.
>> YEAH. AND YOU WERE?
>> WHO DO YOU THINK FED HIM AND
CARED FOR HIM IN HIS FINAL DAYS?
I WAS ALL HE HAD.
>> YOU TOLD COURTNEY AND KAYLA
THAT ARLO WAS MURDERED?
>> OH, PLEASE.
THAT'S ABSURD.
I'VE BEEN NOTHING BUT CARING AND
WELCOMING.
I'VE -- I'VE EVEN FED THEM.
DID YOU WANT THEM TO SHOW UP TO
A COLD, DARK HOUSE?
HOW CRUEL?
>> WHY ARE YOU TELLING MY KIDS
LIES?
AND WHAT ALL HAVE YOU TAKEN FROM
HERE?
>> SOME PEOPLE CARE MORE ABOUT
OUR BROTHER'S MATERIAL THINGS.
>> SHE KEPT A SHOE BOX.
SHE KEPT A SHOE BOX AND ALL OF
HIS FAVORITE THINGS.
SHE SAID IT WAS ALL SHE WANTED
TO KEEP.
>> WHERE'S THE SHOE BOX?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I KNOW WHERE IT IS. COME ON.
>> WHERE'S THE SHOE BOX?
>> COURTNEY, SHOW ME WHERE
>> I KNOW WHERE IT IS. COME ON.
IT IS.
>> COURTNEY, SHOW ME WHERE
>> COME ON, DAD.
IT IS.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
>> COME ON, DAD.
READY FOR THIS?
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
>> JUST WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
>> MATCHBOOKS.
>> AND HUNDREDS OF THEM FROM
EVERY STATE.
>> THIS IS WHAT YOU WANTED MOST?
>> ARLO HAS BEEN COLLECTING THEM
SINCE HE WAS A CHILD.
I THOUGHT I WOULD PRESERVE THEM.
IT WAS HIS ONLY HOBBY.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
EVERY TIME DAD WOULD BUY
CIGARETTES, HE'D PICK UP AN
EXTRA SET FOR ARLO'S COLLECTION.
>> WELL, A CIGARETTE SOUNDS
WONDERFUL RIGHT NOW.
SO, ARE WE DONE WITH THESE RUDE
FIRST IMPRESSIONS?
>> YES.
>> GUESS SO.
>> I THINK WE'VE HAD ENOUGH
CONFUSION FOR ONE NIGHT.
DON'T YOU THINK SO, COURTNEY?
>> YEAH, WHATEVER.
OKAY.
>> I THINK YOU OWE AUNT MAY AN
APOLOGY.
>> NO, I'M GOOD.
EXCUSE ME.
>> IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S GOING THROUGH A PHASE.
BUT I'M GONNA GO HAVE THAT
CIGARETTE.
[ Dialing ]
[ Ringing ]
>> TANISTRY.
>> DALE, YOU'RE GONNA HATE THIS.
>> WHAT IS IT, MAY?
>> THEIR FATHER'S HERE.
THEY MUST HAVE TALKED ABOUT ME.
>> WELL, WHAT DID YOU TELL HIM?
>> I STUCK TO MY GUNS, AND HE
ACTUALLY BOUGHT IT.
>> I DOUBT THAT.
>> NO, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN ME.
I REALLY WON HIM OVER.
IT WAS PATHETIC.
>> YEAH, YOU ALWAYS WERE THE
LITTLE ACTOR OF THE FAMILY.
>> THE ONE GIRL HASN'T BEEN A
PROBLEM.
IT'S THAT BRAT, COURTNEY,
GETTING HER FATHER ALL HEATED.
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN THIS
GENEROUS.
WE WAITED TOO LONG.
>> WELL, HOW OLD'S THIS ONE?
>> EARLY 20s, ATHLETIC, MINIMAL
FRECKLES.
>> SHE SOUNDS PRIME.
I COULD USE THE RESOURCES.
>> YOU SHOULD TURN HER INSIDE
OUT FROM HER ASSHOLE.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
I'LL BE AT THE STABLE IN AN
HOUR.
>> NO.
WAIT TILL EVERYONE'S ASLEEP.
>> WELL, YOU CAN'T PICK THEM ALL
UP.
>> THEN WE'LL JUST WORRY ABOUT
COURTNEY TONIGHT.
I'LL CALL YOU WHEN SHE'S READY.
>> SO YOU DON'T MIND DOING HER?
>> NO.
IT'LL BE A PLEASURE.
[ BEEPS ]
[ SPITS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
>> KAYLA, IT'S DAD.
>> HEY, DAD.
>> HEY, GIRLS.
>> HI, DADDY.
>> HEY. THANKS FOR WATCHING HER.
>> YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
WE'RE GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> EVERYTHING'S FINE NOW.
YOU KIDS JUST LET YOUR
IMAGINATION RUN AWAY FROM YOU.
WE SHOULD ALL BE THANKFUL FOR
THE LONG-LOST FAMILY MEMBER.
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
IT'S JUST, LIKE --
IT'S SO RANDOM, YOU KNOW?
>> I KNOW.
IT'S ALL SO SUDDEN -- MOM
LEAVING, UNCLE ARLO GETTING ILL
AND PASSING.
>> YEAH.
I'M SO SORRY.
I MEAN, THIS MUST BE THE HARDEST
ON YOU.
>> THANKS, KAYLA.
I'M GONNA BE RIGHT NEXT DOOR
GETTING READY FOR BED.
YOU GET HUNGRY, YOU GOT SOME
CRACKERS IN YOUR KNAPSACK, OKAY?
AND DON'T LET HER STAY UP ALL
NIGHT.
>> SHE'LL BE FINE.
THERE'S PLENTY OF ROOM ON THIS
BED.
>> OKAY. THANKS, KAYLA.
I'M RIGHT NEXT DOOR IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING, OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
LOVE YOU, DAD.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> LOVE YOU, GIRLS. BYE.
YOU KNOW, COURTNEY'S PRETTY
UPSET.
I'D JUST LET HER BE.
SHE'LL FEEL BETTER AFTER A NIGHT
OF UNDISTURBED SLEEP.
>> YEAH, SHE'S JUST BEING HER
USUAL SELF.
>> GRUMPY?
>> REALLY?
>> SO, IS AUNT MAY GONNA BE
STAYING?
>> HAD A GOOD LONG TALK WITH
HER.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE THAT'S BEEN
CARING FOR UNCLE ARLO, AND FOR
THAT, I'M GRATEFUL.
SHE'LL BE STAYING OUT OF OUR
HAIR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I JUST DON'T WANT HER TO, LIKE,
BOTHER ME.
>> KAYLA, THERE'S A LOT OF
PEOPLE LIKE THAT ALL THROUGH
LIFE.
YOU JUST HAVE TO NOT LET THEM
GET UNDER YOUR SKIN SO EASILY.
NIGHT, GIRLS.
>> NIGHT, DADDY.
>> PERFECT SKIN.
YOU'RE GONNA BE MY BEST
COMMISSION.
>> [ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> OH, I JUST -- I GOT A STRANGE
FEELING.
>> MAYBE IT WAS JUST A
NIGHTMARE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
>> [ LAUGHING ]
>> MORNING, SWEETIE.
>> HEY, DAD.
>> HAILEY NOT UP YET?
>> NO, SHE'S STILL SLEEPING.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> SOMEONE REALLY NEEDS TO DO
SOME GROCERY SHOPPING AROUND
HERE IF WE ARE GONNA STAY HERE
ANY LONGER.
>> I THINK YOU'RE GONNA WANT TO
STAY AROUND.
I'VE GOT SOME GREAT NEWS THAT I
THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE GLAD TO
HEAR.
>> WHAT?
>> AUNT MAY'S GONE.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> LUGGAGE AND ALL.
MUST HAVE LEFT THIS MORNING.
>> WE MUST HAVE REALLY MADE HER
FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE, THEN.
>> I KNOW.
I WAS WONDERING.
MAYBE WE WERE A BIT TOO FORWARD.
>> I THINK COURTNEY WAS THE
HARSH ONE.
DOES SHE KNOW SHE'S GONE YET?
>> NO, COURTNEY'S STILL
SLEEPING, TOO.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, CAN I TELL
HER?
>> YEAH. AND YOU CAN ALSO TELL
HER THERE'S NO EXCUSE FOR DRAMA.
WANT A PLEASANT REST OF THE
WEEKEND WHILE I SORT THIS PLACE
OUT.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
WELL, I THINK I'M GONNA GO GET
DRESSED AND THEN PROBABLY GET
SOME FOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT. HERE.
>> OH.
PICK UP SOME GROCERIES.
YOU KNOW WHAT COURTNEY LIKES.
>> YEAH.
OH.
THIS IS WHAT I GOT HAILEY.
>> NICE.
ON MY CREDIT CARD?
>> MAYBE.
>> BYE, SWEETIE.
>> BYE.
>> WELL, HELLO.
YOU'RE BACK SO SOON.
>> YEAH, I THINK MY SKIN CAN
HANDLE IT.
>> WE'LL SEE.
SO YOU'RE HAPPY WITH THE BED YOU
USED LAST TIME?
>> YEAH, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
JUST MAYBE NOT AS LONG THIS
TIME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S READY WHEN YOU ARE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THIS LOTION JUST CAME IN --
NAVAJO MIST.
IT'S EXPENSIVE, BUT I THINK
YOU'LL LIKE IT.
I'LL LET YOU GIVE IT A TRY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> JUST LATHER ON A GOOD AMOUNT
BEFORE STARTING.
>> OKAY.
>> LOOKS LIKE MY SHOW'S ABOUT
READY TO BEGIN.
SHE'S BACK.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'RE SO LUCKY TO
HAVE A WIFE LIKE ME WHO PUTS UP
WITH THIS.
>> SHUT UP.
SHE'S RUBBING ON THE
GLUTARALDEHYDE.
>> COURTNEY, YOU ALIVE?
I FOUND A RECORD FROM ARLO'S
BAND IN THE '80s.
PRETTY NEAT.
ARLO NUNEZ, BASS GUITAR.
COME ON, COURTNEY.
ENOUGH BEAUTY SLEEP.
DON'T YOU WANT TO HEAR THIS?
>> WELL, IT'S OUR LUCKY DAY.
NO MESS.
WHY CAN'T THEY JUST ALL EAT THE
CANDY?
>> YEAH, YOU ACT LIKE IT'S YOUR
IDEA.
>> COULDN'T BE ANY EASIER.
THEY JUST WALTZ RIGHT INTO THE
WEB.
IT'S TEMPTING.
I HAVE JUST HAD THE MOST
WONDERFUL IDEA.
>> OH, THAT'S GREAT.
I'D LOVE TO HEAR IT.
LATER.
I HAVE TO GET BACK TO THE STORE.
>> THE GIRL'S SAID AND DONE
WITH.
>> ALREADY?
>> DALE'S TAKING HER OUT TO THE
STABLE BEFORE SHE STARTS TO
YELLOW.
AND YOU'VE GOT TO GET BACK TO
THE HOUSE AND TAKE CARE OF THE
FATHER.
>> AND HOW DO YOU SUPPOSE I DO
THAT?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO DO IT BEFORE HE
GETS CONCERNED.
>> [ SIGHS ]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
COULD'VE DONE IT LAST NIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT HIM PUTTING UP A FIGHT.
MIGHT BREAK A NAIL.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
JUST SNEAK UP BEHIND HIM.
YOU'RE GOOD AT THAT KIND OF
STUFF.
NOW, I'VE GOT TO CLOSE UP HERE
AND GET BACK OVER TO THE SALON.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE LITTLE GIRL?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT WHAT TO
DO ABOUT THAT?
>> WELL, WHAT'S THERE TO FIGURE
OUT?
SKIN HER.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> AARON!
STRAIGHTEN HER OUT.
WHAT'S MICHELLE DOING HERE?
SHE'S BARELY PLIABLE.
LET'S TAKE HER BACK.
CAREFUL.
OKAY.
[ GRUNTS ]
AHH.
MORGAN.
YOU'RE FINISHED.
MMM.
AMBER.
SWEETHEART.
BRING HER ON DOWN FOR A DIP
LATER.
WHEN SHE'S DRY.
I SEE YOU'VE BEEN PRODUCTIVE.
>> T-T-TH--
THANK YOU, POP.
HAVEN'T SLEPT.
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
YOU TOLD ME.
>> YES, AARON.
WE MUST STRIP THEM IMMEDIATELY
AND GET THEIR HIDES INTO THE
FORMALDEHYDE BEFORE IT'S TOO
LATE.
>> T-T-THEY NOT ALL BE READY THE
SAME.
>> AH.
YOU'RE MATURING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO PAY
ATTENTION, ALWAYS.
WHY ARE YOU LOOKING AT HER LIKE
THAT?!
>> I DON'T KNOW!
>> THERE'S WORK TO BE DONE.
I HAVE TO GET BACK TO YOUR
MOTHER.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO HESITATE
PREPPING THE NEW ONE.
THEN YOU FINISH OFF MICHELLE
HERE.
SHE HAS NICE SKIN.
>> GOOD SKIN.
G-G-GOOD SKIN TODAY.
>> YOU MAKE BIG CUTS!
WE HAVE ENOUGH POCKETBOOKS.
>> THERE WON'T BE ENOUGH OF HER.
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
YOU CAN GET AT LEAST TWO BAGS
OUT OF HER!
YOU ALREADY KNOW THAT, UH...
THERE'S NO HAIR YOU HAVE TO
SHAVE OFF OF HER.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
GO MOP THE FLOOR.
I GOT WORK I GOT TO DO.
>> FINALLY.
MY PRIZED CLUB.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
MAY, YOU'RE BACK.
COME IN, COME IN.
I DON'T WANT TO LET THE
MOTHS IN.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING I FORGOT TO
TAKE CARE OF.
WE TURNED YOUR BROTHER INTO A
PURSE.
>> HUH?
I DON'T GET IT.
>> WELL, HE WAS OUR BEST
CUSTOMER.
HE HAD THE MOST OUTRAGEOUS
CUSTOM ORDERS -- THONGS, WHIPS,
JOCKSTRAPS -- YOU NAME IT.
SO, NATURALLY, WE ONLY THOUGHT,
AFTER TIME, WE FELT HE WAS MEANT
TO CONTINUE THE CYCLE.
HE HELPED MAKE UP THE BARGAIN
BIN.
>> MAY, YOU'RE UNWELL.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
AND IT WAS JUST SUCH A
COINCIDENCE WHEN YOUR DAUGHTER
CAME IN AND BOUGHT THE BAG HE
WAS MADE FROM.
ALTHOUGH I GUESS, IN A WAY, THAT
BRINGS THEM BACK TOGETHER,
DOESN'T IT?
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
>> BOY, DID HE LOVE LEATHER.
>> UNH!
[ SIGHS ]
>> FINALLY, YOU CAN CARRY WHAT
THE STARS DO.
>> AND WHAT IS SO GREAT ABOUT
THIS SPECIFIC BAG IS IT'S REALLY
SIMPLE, VERY POSH, AND IT STANDS
OUT FROM YOUR OTHER HANDBAGS.
>> IT IS THE BAG FOR ALL
SEASONS.
WITH ITS NEUTRAL BEIGE AND NUDE
TONES, IT'S THE NEW ADDITION TO
YOUR ACCESSORY COLLECTION.
>> GREAT FOR A SPECIAL NIGHT
OUT, GOOD FOR AN EVERYDAY GO-TO
BAG, AND BECAUSE ITS DESIGN IS
SO LIMITED --
>> YES, ONLY FIVE LEFT.
>> MAKES THE PERFECT GIFT FOR
YOURSELF OR SOMEONE SPECIAL.
>> FOR JUST FIVE EASY PAYMENTS
OF $999.99.
>> WHAT A STEAL.
AND FOR ALL THESE LUCKY CALLERS,
THEY'LL ALSO RECEIVE JOAN'S
PATENTED LEATHER OINTMENT CREAM
TO KEEP YOUR PURSE LOOKING
RADIANT FOR YEARS TO COME.
>> OPERATORS ARE STANDING BY.
NOW LET ME SHOW YOU A PAIR OF
DIAMOND EARRINGS THAT ARE, UM...
>> OH, SORRY.
JUST SO HARD TO PART WITH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> HEY, HAILEY.
>> HEY, I WAS WATCHING THAT.
>> YOUR DAD ASKED ME TO BABYSIT.
THERE'S ANOTHER GIRL YOUR AGE I
WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU TO.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> OKAY, I GUESS.
>> WHY YOU GIVING ME TROUBLE,
JOAN?!
>> [ SIGHS ]
DON'T START.
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
>> YEAH, FOR WHO?
FOR YOU?
>> DARLING -- [ GASPS ]
PLEASE.
>> I'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT TAKING
CARE OF BODIES!
SO WAS AARON!
THERE'S WORK TO BE DONE AROUND
HERE, AND YOU SURE AS HELL AIN'T
PULLING YOUR WEIGHT!
>> ME?
I'M THE ONE WHO RUNS BACK AND
FORTH BETWEEN BOTH STORES WHILE
YOU SIT HERE AND ALPHABETIZE
YOUR PERVERTED ARCHIVE OF VOYEUR
PORN!
>> DAMN IT! DON'T!
IF YOU WOULD JUST SHUT UP AND
LISTEN, I CAN EXPLAIN MY
BRILLIANT PLAN TO YOU --
THE EPIPHANY THAT I HAD!
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> TINY HANDS!
>> ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
>> DON'T YOU THINK WE SHOULD AT
LEAST CONSIDER IT?
IT'S A BLESSING IN DISGUISE.
HER NIMBLE FINGERS -- I SAY WE
TEACHER HER HOW TO DO THE
STITCHING AND RAISE HER AS OUR
OWN!
>> NO.
AND DON'T TRY TO PERSUADE ME.
>> REBEKAH WAS A BREEZE, AND
IT'S TIME TO START MY
UNDERGROUND ASSEMBLY LINE.
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, WE'LL BE
PRODUCING TWICE THE BAGS IN HALF
THE TIME!
>> DALE, THAT'S ABSURD.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME TO JUST ALL
OF A SUDDEN RAISE ANOTHER CHILD.
AARON WAS A PILL.
>> [ SNIFFING ]
>> AAH! OW!
[ CRYING ]
STOP!
AAH!
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
AAH!
[ FORMALDEHYDE SPLASHING ]
>> AAH!
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
>> UNH!
[ COUGHS ]
[ MOTOR WHIRRING ]
>> REBEKAH, I WANT YOU TO MEET
YOUR NEW PLAYMATE, HAILEY.
[ GASPS ]
LOOK WHAT A GOOD JOB YOU'RE
DOING.
YOU'RE GONNA GET ANOTHER TREAT.
AND IF YOU'RE A VERY GOOD LITTLE
GIRL, I WON'T HAVE TO PUT YOU
BACK IN THE PLAYPEN, SO TEACH
HAILEY HOW TO SEW, OKAY?
>> COME ON, COME ON!
DIE! DIE ON ME!
DIE!
DIE, WILL YOU?!
REACH FOR YOUR PEPPER SPRAY!
REACH FOR IT!
GO ON, REACH!
HERE! I'LL HELP YOU!
I'LL HELP YOU REACH FOR IT!
HOW'S THIS?!
HOW'S THAT, HUH?!
HOW'S THAT?!
[ LAUGHING ]
DIE!
D-I-I-I-I-I-IE!
[ LAUGHING ]
OH.
THERE'S NO ONE IN THERE.
[ LAUGHING ]
NOW YOU'LL REALLY BE AN OLD BAG.
>> YOU...
YOU KILLED HER?
>> OH, SHE EGGED ME ON!
AND DON'T ACT LIKE YOU LIKED
HER.
>> SHE WAS MY ONLY SISTER!
>> THERE AIN'T NO ROOM FOR
EMOTION IN THIS GAME!
NOW YOU'RE SENIOR DESIGNER.
MEANS YOU'LL MAKE QUITE A BIT
MORE THAN 11%.
>> YOU EXPECT ME TO TURN JOAN...
INTO ONE OF THESE?
>> UH, SUPERVISE.
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
OKAY, LOOK -- I'M WILLING TO
TRUST YOUR JUDGMENT.
YOU STARTED THIS COMPANY, SO WHY
SHOULD ANYONE ELSE'S OPINION
MATTER?
AND, YES...
I DID DESPISE HER.
>> EXACTLY!
SO, UH, YOU TOOK CARE OF THE
FATHER WITH NO TROUBLE?
>> YES.
I DIDN'T HAVE ANY SOLUTION TO
TREAT HIM.
>> DAMN IT!
IF YOU HAD ANY CONSIDERATION AT
ALL, YOU'D KEEP A FEW EXTRA
QUARTS OF FORMALDEHYDE IN YOUR
TRUCK AT ALL TIMES!
>> AND IF YOU HAD ANY
CONSIDERATION, YOU'D DICE UP HER
FACE SO AARON WON'T HAVE TO KNOW
HE'S SKINNED HIS OWN MOTHER.
>> YES, HE'S...GOT A SENSITIVE
SIDE THAT I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
RID HIM OF.
TAKE CARE OF THAT.
OH, POOR BABY.
[ LAUGHING ]
>> UGH.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> THIS IS MOLLY.
>> HOW LONG HAS SHE BEEN DEAD?
>> UH, IT'S A DOLL THAT I PLAY
WITH.
WHERE'S MY DADDY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHERE ARE WE?
>> THIS IS WHERE I HELP MOMMY
AND DADDY MAKE THE PURSES.
THIS IS MY OWN SEWING MACHINE,
BUT SOMETIMES I HAVE TO STITCH
IT WITH MY HANDS.
MOMMY AND DADDY SAYS THEIR HANDS
ARE TOO BIG TO DO STITCHING.
I WISH THEY'D LET ME KEEP THIS
PURSE ONCE IT'S DONE.
>> WHEN WILL IT BE DONE?
>> AS SOON AS DADDY BRINGS IN
MORE SKIN.
I'M TOO LITTLE TO TEAR IT OFF.
THAT'S MY BIG BROTHER'S JOB.
AND MY MOM AND AUNT MAY DESIGN
THE BAGS.
>> MY BIG SISTER GOT ME A PURSE.
IT'S PRETTY.
WHAT'S THE PLAYPEN?
>> IT'S THE HOLE IN THE WALL
WHERE THE SMELL'S COMING FROM.
>> [ MOANING PASSIONATELY ]
>> I'VE BEEN WAITING SO LONG FOR
THIS.
>> OH, YEAH!
>> SHOULD WE DO IT RIGHT HERE?
>> YES, YES! RIGHT NOW!
RIGHT NOW! YEAH!
>> OH, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
WAIT!
>> WHAT?! WHAT?!
>> CAN WE JUST GET RID OF HER
FIRST?
>> OH, COME ON!
>> NO. REALLY, IT'S KIND OF A
TURN-OFF.
>> COME ON!
OH, GET HER LEGS.
COME ON.
>> OH, YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOSH.
>> [ CRYING ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED, MADAM?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> THERE'S MURDERERS!
>> MURDERERS?
WHAT? MURDERERS? WHERE?
>> CALL THE POLICE NOW.
>> CALM DOWN.
I'M GONNA HELP YOU.
YES, DON'T WORRY.
SOMEONE WILL HELP YOU.
CALM DOWN.
WE'RE GONNA HELP YOU.
I'M GONNA HELP YOU, BITCH.
HELP YOU!
GONNA HELP YOU.
>> SO, YOU PUT THIS RIGHT HERE,
AND YOU MOVE THIS THERE.
AND THEN THERE.
AND THEN IT GOES LIKE THAT.
>> WHAT THE HELL, GREG?
YOU MEAN SHE WAS JUST WANDERING
AROUND THE INTERSTATE?
>> LOOKS LIKE SHE'D BEEN THROUGH
HELL.
>> WELL, I THOUGHT SHE WAS
FINISHED.
SHE MUST HAVE WOKEN UP, AND MY
ANIMAL OF A SON LET HER GET
AWAY.
WELL, I'M GLAD THAT YOU DIDN'T
LET HER GET AWAY.
>> IT'S A GOOD THING THEY DIDN'T
FIND HER.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE
INVOLVED.
BUT I COULDN'T LET THE FATE OF
WICKENHAVEN'S ECONOMY CRUMBLE
BECAUSE OF THIS STUPID GIRL!
>> I'LL JUST PRETEND THAT YOU
DIDN'T DO ME THE FAVOR.
SO I GUESS I'LL GO BACK TO
ARLO'S HOUSE WITH REBEKAH AND
WRAP UP DADDY.
WE'LL JUST STAY THE NIGHT THERE
IN CASE SOME OTHER FAMILY
MEMBERS SHOW UP.
YEAH. [ SNIFFS ]
>> BYE.
>> YEAH.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> IT'S BEEN SUCH A STRESSFUL
WEEK.
>> INVENTORY'S REALLY ADDING UP?
>> YEAH, IT JUST NEVER SEEMS TO
EXCEED THE DEMAND FOR OUR
PURSES.
>> JUST DON'T LET IT GET OUT OF
HAND.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN NOTICING
YOU GOT SOME CLOSE CALLS LATELY.
I FEAR IT'S GETTING TOO
MAINSTREAM.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S...
IT IS NOT EASY MAKING A LIVING
THAT ISN'T...HONEST.
>> WELL...
I'M NOT THE ONE TO SAY WHAT'S
HONEST OR NOT.
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT -- IF YOU
MADE THE TRANSITION OVER TO
NORMAL COW HIDE, DO YOU BELIEVE
THE CUSTOMERS ARE GONNA EVEN
NOTICE?
COME ON.
A FEW YEARS AGO, IT WAS JUST THE
BAGS BEHIND THE COUNTER.
THAT WAS SPECIAL.
BUT RIGHT NOW -- RIGHT NOW --
IT'S THE WHOLE DANG STORE.
AND ALL THE PUBLICITY -- MY
GOSH.
>> WELL, YOU REALLY SAVED THE
DAY, GREG.
HOW CAN WE EVER REPAY YOU?
>> WELL, UM...
IF YOU WANT TO RETURN THE FAVOR,
YOU KNOW, MY GIRLFRIEND'S
BIRTHDAY'S COMING UP NEXT MONTH,
AND I'M SURE SHE WOULD --
>> SAY NO MORE.
>> THANK YOU.
SHE ALWAYS WANTED ONE OF THOSE.
>> I'LL EVEN MAKE IT FROM THE
GIRL YOU JUST BROUGHT IN.
>> UGH!
DON'T EVEN TELL ME WHERE IT CAME
FROM.
I HAVE TO GO.
SARA'S WAITING IN THE CAR.
>> HI, MR. RAT.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
[ GIGGLES ]
WHAT'RE YOU DOING THERE?
DO YOU MISS YOUR FAMILY, TOO?
>> WHAT'S MY NEW FAVORITE NIECE
UP TO, HMM?
OH, I KNOW IT'S A LITTLE SCARY
HAVING TO ADJUST SO SUDDENLY AT
SUCH A YOUNG AGE.
YOU SEE, I RESCUED YOU.
YOUR FAMILY DECIDED TO LEAVE YOU
HERE FOR A LITTLE WHILE TO WORK
FOR US.
AND WE'LL LEARN TO LOVE YOU.
BUT IF YOU OBJECT...
THEN I'LL BE FORCED TO...
MAKE A WHIP, TAILORED FROM YOUR
SISTER'S SKIN, TO PUNISH YOU
EVERY DAY FOR THE REST OF YOUR
MISERABLE, ISOLATED EXISTENCE.
AND YOU'LL BE PUT IN THE PLAYPEN
AGAIN AND AGAIN.
BUT IF YOU BEHAVE, THEN YOU GET
TO EAT AND HAVE TREATS AND LOTS
OF OTHER GREAT STUFF.
I ACTUALLY BROUGHT YOU
SOMETHING.
IT BELONGED TO MY SISTER.
GET EXCITED, KID.
IT'S 6 KARATS.
PEOPLE KILL FOR THIS STUFF.
>> HAILEY.
HAILEY.
>> KAYLA!
KAYLA!
>> HAILEY, I FOUND A WAY OUT.
JUST PULL THE LATCH AND JUST
FOLLOW ME.
>> I CAN'T! I CAN'T!
>> JUST PULL THE LATCH DOWN
THERE.
I GOT IT!
>> COME ON, LET'S GO.
WE'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> WH-WHERE'S --
WHERE'S KAYLA'S TAPE?
OH, IT'S IN THE VCR. KAYLA.