Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
RECALL THE DOOR TO THE DEMON
There are two kinds of people on earth ...
those who believe in the spirit world ...
and those who do not.
The devil likes of both types.
SÃO MIGUEL
BLESSED DEATH
I've got something for you
tada!
I can't beleive we're doing this again
Come on, Sara, they're just cards, they're not going to bite you.
Come On.
OK. Good
OK. So the first card represents the past.
The tower
It looks like you had some stormy times recently.
You could say that.
Moving on to the present.
The Fool. Perfect.
That's the way I feel now.
No, this is a great card.
It represents new beginnings and exciting opportunities.
- I like that. - Alright.
But what about the future?
THE DEVIL
- My God- No no no no.
It is not "The Devil" is the god Dionysus.
He is the god of pleasure and abandon
It looks like we'll have a wild night ahead of us.
I've put all that behind me
Sara, the cards do not lie.
Your chariot awaits Ladies
Hey
Come On.
Nice wheels!
This'll put hair  on your tits
Joey, you know I do not drink anymore.
Some party this is going to be
Leave her alone.
What a nice car, Marcus.
I'm using the old hearse as a camera truck
It is one of the perks of the job
Do you really need all this equipment?
You want me to make you look beautiful, don't you?
You'd better
I will
We got together
Now and forever
You can not separate us If you try
The past behind us
Will remember
Why we fight to death
Until dead
To kick and knock down any wall
And we will be who will stand
We are one for all and all for one
We are standing
This is not my place
MORGUE - We thought it would be cool to film...
somewhere a little more edgy
- A morgue? - It's where I work.
It gives a nice tone for the film.
And it makes it a lot harder for you to fake anything.
Fine.
There should be plenty of spirits around here
And for the record, I never faked anything in my life.
Well you never had to with me
That's what you think.
Hold that. Thanks.
Hey, you want to help?
It's fine ...
Stop that.
You have a lot of security, for a bunch of corpses.
Keeps them fom escaping
What's the code?
Try 6-6-6.
You're kidding, right?
Mortician humour. Punch it in.
Welcome to the House of Death.
Where is everyone?
Dead.
- How funny. - Here was a hospital.
But the municipality constructed a new building at the end of the road ...
then just left over the morgue and funeral center.
- You're kidding, right? - I swear to God.
Why do not they close the place?
You know how much to die today?
It's a tremendous fortune.
We call this place the dump
We get al the unclaimed bodies...
junkies, homeless people, poor people; whoever.
This is where Marcus likes to do the creepy student movies
Staff's gone on weekends.
I can work and no one ever bothers me.
- Stop it, Marcus. - What it was?
Are you trying to look like a serial killer ...
but it is not working.
I'm just trying to get in the mood.
And he does not know why has no girlfriend.
Ok, Alright
Here we have the main entrance hall and the family waiting area
Come on, guys, get back on your mark
I put them for a reason. Come On!
- "Marks"? - Here no light.
I need you there, okay?
- That's right. - Yikes.
Here is good?
Right. They are ready?
How you feel? Because you' look fantastic. Ready?
Thank You.
We are here today with Eva Delgado ...
self-proclaimed Santeria priestess.
I never called myself a priestess.
What can you tell us about Santeria?
It is true that you practice animal sacrifice?
Marcus, give me the camera.
What, I'm the director. This equipment is my ...
- This camera is mine. - Have a camera does not make you director.
Kiss my ass
She can't Bro. She is a Christian crazy now.
She'll have to marry you first if there's
going to be any ass kissing
You're an A-hole.
A-hole? You can say that? This is not sin?
Not when it's true.
ooh! Vicious
Spicy Christian. Sure, zooms here. Come on, here.
Joey, do not tell me what to do.
Look, I'm giving you an opportunity to ...
a great documentary, okay?
You're giving me an opportunity to witness
more of your bullshit
Can you you get serious, porfavor?
I'm filming, say something smart, just once.
Okay.
We are here today because our friend, Eva ...
thinks she talks to ghosts.
I said "smart" Joey. "Smart"
Inteligente.
We are here today because our friend, Joey ...
afraid of things he does not understand.
Very scared.
Marcus is making his thesis documentary about me.
It's not about you. It's about our bet.
To prove that I am a real medium.
So our friend Joey here ...
will stop hassling me, once and for all
And what if you can't prove that you are for real?
As I promised, I dance on stage at all his shows next year.
In a bikini. - I never agreed to a bikini.
I'm just thinking of the fans.
This has just come into my head.
It was a sudden idea.
But if you're right, you do not have to worry about, right?
Right. Okay.
- Okay. - I agree with that ...
as long as you agree ...
that if I win, you'll quit your band ...
and join the church choir for one year.
I'd pay to see that.
Deal
This will be the best student film of all time
Come on let's go
Here we have the casket room where grieving families come ...
to select urns and caskets for their love ones
This is nice
Nice? This is a scam
You know how much they charge for a box like that?
$ 2,000.
On the low end, if you want mahogany, they are 15,000.
$ 15,000 for a box?
It's hard to say goodbye to family, Joey.
The burial ritual can be an important part of it.
They are not saying "goodbye" are saying "I'm sorry".
Are 15,000 ways to say "I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry I left you in that shitty nursing home
to die alone
You always look on the bright side of things, Joey.
That's why we love you.
- Thanks. - You are welcome.
I think the caskets are beautiful.
Be damned coffins. Where are the bodies?
Downstairs, in the embalming room.
Embalming room? Now we're talking
Are we allowed down ther?
He is a security guard. We can go anywhere, right?
Sure. Let's go
Come On.
Or or or.
Do you ever see any ghosts up here?
No, but the basement is haunted.
Perfect. Eva will have many people to talk to.
Got it.
There's a weird energy here.
We're in a morgue.
Not serious.
They have bodies that have been here for years.
How old?
I do not know. They are stacked up like side of beef in a freezer.
Um freezer?
Yeah. Want to check it out?
Let's go.
After you.
I've never seen a dead body before
Why this plastic on his face?
Dry skin so fast that they need ...
fill Ios moisturizer and wrap with plastic.
He looks fake. Like he's made of wax or something.
When you're gone you're gone. Nothing left but the carcase
Do not touch the clients
You almost scared me to death, Marcus.
Sorry, but we have rules here.
These things are covered in bacteria.
Thank You.
Okay, here we are.
Welcome to the embalming room, where they drain your blood ...
and pump you full of preservatives.
- It's cold here. - Yeah
Joey, do not do that.
My God.
Nice tits
I do not believe you dated him.
- It was the first year. - My God.
We all make mistakes
It's my animal magnetism. She could not help.
Of course, Joey, you were impossible to resist.
She still wants me.
I'll talk to her about it.
Dude, what's that, a sword?
It's a trocar, do not touch it.
They use to pierce the organs and drain fluids from the body.
That's disgusting.
So, boys, where are we doing the seance?
How about if we set up in the casket room?
Okay for you?
The lighting is better.
For me, no matter.
At least not have bodies up there.
FORMOL
These caskets really are beautiful
I understand why people pay so much to make their
loved ones look good
Me. When I'm gone I'm going to get burned
Nobody looks good dead
I just want a simple service
Simple but elegant, classic.
Not me
I want a giant pyramid, for my fans go idolize me.
They can send me messages and I can answer your prayers and such.
Of course you are
And will your music be on a loop?
For all eternity.
- I hope I'm dead by then. - Hey, that's harsh, right?
What's the one good song that Joey sings.
Oh, That's right, they all suck!
You are so out of my fan club.
Marcus, where's the bathroom?
The only one that is open, it is down stairs...
third door on the left, near the freezer.
- But take the camera. -  So you post me going to the bathroom?
- I don't think so. - You can turn ...
when in the bathroom, but we have to ...
document everything we do, right?
Ok
You need to work on your game, Marcus.
I liked it.
Smooth. Very smooth.
I'm Sarah and I'm going to the bathroom.
For some reason, Marcus think this is essential viewing.
What is this?
Gross!
- Babies. BABIES IN BOTTOM SHELF
My God!
Oh no.
Open the door!
Let me out of here!
Let me out! This is not funny!
Let me out!
Please.
Please, let me out of here!
There's something here!
There's something here with me! Please let me out!
It's not funny!
My God!
You should see your face!
- What? - This goes straight to my website.
- Was you? - It was perfect.
Wow, you know what? Good for you, I saw it coming ...
but I did not believe it.
You forgive me?
Go to hell
That's not very Christian.
I am old school. I don't turn the other cheek
You are an old-school psycho.
Hey! Stop that! Sara, stop it!
No. No!
She attacked me!
You know, you have no sense of humor.
- He locked me in the freezer. - What?
- It was a joke! - That's not funny!
You're an asshole, Joey.
You peel back a Christian, you always get a little crazy.
No. You need to apologize now, Joey.
I'm sorry
I'm sorry you lost your sense of humor.
What is your problem?
You, Eva.
- Me? - You and your mystical bullshit.
Sara and her crazy Christian cult
You are my problems.
Look, there is no God
There is no afterlife
There are no benevolent guiding spirits.
This is the drug that bosses feed the masses ...
to keep us confused and ignorant!
To distract us from the fact that 1% of the population ...
It is controlling 95% of the world's resources.
Here we go again.
Religion is the drug that ruined the world, no matter what.
Christianity.
Do you really think Jesus Christ is the only way to get to heaven?
And the poor kid in the Amazon that's never
heard of Jesus Christ?
Is he going to spend all  eternity burning in a firey pit of hell?
Does that sound like justice to you?
I don't  think so, and if ...
if that's what God thinks justice is, then God's an asshole.
That's enough, Joey.
What about the Muslims, then?
You blow yourself up. Kill a bunch of innocent men,
women and kids
And then, guess what.
He gets to spend all eternity with 72 horny virgins.
Does that make sense to anybody, except a psycho?
-You finished? - No, I'm not finished
This is the only life we've got. It;s right here, right now.
There is no heaven and no hell.
People are asleep at the wheel, and I'm going
to wake them the fuck up
It's a great speech, Joey, but you're wrong.
There are spirits trapped in this world.
Even you can not be arrogant enough to believe that ...
humans are the center of the universe.
No no no. Not humans, Me.
I am the center of my universe.
And I will prove to you ...
That you and all your religious mumbo-jumbo is full of shit
- We will see. - Yeah, we will
You know what? I do not want to talk about it.
Hey, it's okay, it is over.
Joey knows exactly how to piss me off
I feel like an idiot.
Joey can be an asshole. You know it.
Come on, ignore it. That's what I do.
To be honest, this whole seance thing is really freaking me out
It's no big deal
It's like picking up the phone and calling grandma
The only difference is ... she's passed on.
The Bible warns us not to commune with the spirits.
It also warns you not to eat shellfish
Come On.
I will not let anything bad happen to you.
I promise.
Let's get this over with.
Sara, Joey would like to tell you something.
Isn't that right, Joey?
Sara, I'm sorry about the freezer.
I did not mean to scare you.
OK, I did mean to scare you, but I didn't mean to freak you out.
Don't worry about it
Would it help if I gave you free tickets to my next show?
- Not really- Hey guys, my mikes are a little...
"prosumer-ingus", so keep your voices up, alright?
English, Marcus, we speak English here.
Don't touch the rum.
It is for the spirits.
When are you going to put on your sexy voodoo robe?
Santeria is not voodoo, retard.
Whatever. Are you going to get naked?
This is serious, Joey.
I'm all business, baby
What do we do next
Okay, before we get started, I need to lay out
some ground rules.
You do not need to believe in spirits ...
but I need you to be open to the possibility.
You have to set aside your prejudices.
Even you, Joey, otherwise we will not see anything.
Oh, your getting your excuses out early. I like that.
Are you finished?
OK, I promise. I promise that I will take seriously.
Good.
Iastly: Once we open the door to the spirit world ...
we can not break the circle until the door is closed.
OK?
Marcus, I think we're ready.
Guardians of the East, I call upon you to watch over our rights.
Powers of knowledge and wisdom, guided by air ...
we ask that you keep watch over us tonight within this circle.
Guardians of the South, I call upon you to watch
over our rights.
Powers of energy and will guided by fire ...
we ask that you keep watch over us tonight within this circle.
Guardians of the West, I call upon you to watch over our rights.
Powers of passion and emotion, guided by water ...
we ask that you keep watch over us tonight within this circle.
Guardians of the North, I call upon you to
watch over our rights.
Powers of endurance and strength, guided by earth ...
we ask that you keep watch over us tonight within this circle.
Let all those who enter the circle ...
do so in perfect love ... and perfect trust.
Close your eyes and bow your heads
Beloved Grandmother Maria ...
we bring you gifts from life into death.
Commune with us, Grandma, and move among us.
Beloved Grandmother Maria ...
we bring you gifts from life into death.
Commune with us, Grandma, and move among us.
There's something wrong.
What?
I can't do this.
You can not make the fucking magic happen in a morgue?
Come on
There's has a power here, a darkness.
How do you spell bullshit?
You're just trying to get out of our bet.
That's not it.
We are surrounded by bodies, the whole building ...
and you can not make your magic happen.
- Just admit thatyour full of shit. - Joey!
I usually get images in my head before my grandmother
comes to me
Faces or names. This is just dark.
All I see is darkness
That's fine
Just admit that you can't see through the dark mist ...
and let's go.
What?
- Nothing. - What did you say?
- Nothing. - I never said "dark mist".
Oh my God. You can see it too.
Stop it!  - That's why you're so afraid.
Of course, I should have known.
It's so obvious.
You are a chaneller
You see spirits, right? Hear Voices?
- Fuck you! - No - Don't, don't
Don't break the circle, Joey.
I think the darkness is drawn to your negative energy.
All your anger is acting as a beacon.
- We ned to close the door. - Whatever.
If you can't call up the dead, I win the bet.
I'm headlining the club this weekend.
Don't forget to to bring  your bikini.
No!
My God!
- Shit! Eva.
- Eva!
Eva! Can you hear me?
Eva.... Eva
Up, up.
I told you not break the circle.
You're bleeding.
Are you OK?
I think so.
You're the one I'm worried about.
What you mean?
Joey, can't hide from the truth.
We need to talk about what happened.
I'll tell you what happened.
You fell down and you passed out. I do it every weekend.
This does not change anything!
Are you OK?
Joey.
Joey!
What the fuck... Joey!
What the fuck
Joey!
Joey.
Dude, do you see dead people?
Dude, that is some nasty shit
I did the joints in embalming fluid.
- Maybe that has something to do with it. - You did what?
You say the gang kids do it all the time.
I told you it causes brain damage, you moron.
What the fuck are you doing?
Nothing.
- Jesus you've got blood running  down... - I said it's nothing.
Jesus man, I knew you'd cut up when we were kids, but ...
Shut up!
I do not want to talk about it.
When did you start cutting again, man?
This is the first time since my parents ...
What? When they sent you to rehab?
It wasn't a rehab clinic, Marcus.
What do you mean?
It was...
They sent me to a nut-house.
What?
It was a fucking loony bin.
Look, the doctors, they ...
They filled me with all this antipsychotic medicine...
until I couldn't hear them any more.
Hear who?
The voices that are in my head.
- Why didn't you tell me this? - Because I didn't want you to think ...
- I'm a freak. - I wouldn't think you're a freak, man.
I am cured okay? I am cured.
It was a miracle of modern medicine.
Sure, the drugs... they worked. Okay?
I haven't seen or heard shit since.
I told myself that I imagined the whole thing, you know?
I thought I was cured.
Are you OK?
I felt it
Like something cold was trying to crawl inside me
It's over now.
We should go.
No. You don't understand.
Joey left the door open.
He is a natural channel, but he has no control, no training.
We have to close the door.
I've never judged what you do, Eve, but this is scaring me.
Maybe it's wrong.
What?
Are you going to put down that joint so we can
talk about what happened?
-I don't think so. - Joey, you need to talk to me ...
about your gift.
It is ready to go again?
Or are you going to admit to everybody that you're a fake
so we can get out of here?
I'm not faking it, Joey.
You know the gift is real.
You know it, because you've got the gift too
I'm not a freak, alright?
"A freak"? Is that what you think I?
Do not put words in my mouth, Eva.
- It is OK to be scared. - I'm not fucking scared!
Yes you are. You are terrified. But that's OK
- I can help you. - I do not want your help.
You can't just run away from this Joey
You need to talk to me.
You know what your problem is, Eve?
You do not know when shut your Goddamn mouth.
- Joey. - Do you know why they burn witches?
It was the only way to make them shut up.
They drowned them too. That's how my grandmother died.
Killed by a bunch of ignorant ass-holes, just like you.
I should have known it ran in the family. Do you know what?
There's only one letter between witch and bitch.
And you're both, girl
- Joey, stop it! - It's fine.
I've got this.
- Okay. - Want a personal experience?
You want real proof?
- I'll give you proof. - Wait, you think that's a good idea?
I'll be fine, as long as no one breaks the connection.
Joey, you do not have to do this, man.
Bring it!
- Joey, this is not a good idea. - Sit down!
Let's go, Right now! I'm going to win your award, Marcus.
Fuck it. We're rolling
Close your eyes and bow your heads.
Spirit, we bring you gifts of life into death.
Commune with us and move among us.
Hello.
Cheap trick!
We humbly thank you for this evening's visitation.
all seek your guidance
- What is happening? - Do not break the circle.
That does not prove anything!
What's your name?
I - A - M - U
"I am unclean."
Lord, protect us. Lord, protect us.
Why are you here?
J
O
E
Y
My God!
What do you want to do , Joey?
I want to hear it speak
- Eva, make it stop! - Joey, call it off!
Joey, let me know when you've seen enough.
- Joey!
- Stop it, Joey!
Joey!
Joey?
[speaks foreign language]
Joey, what the fuck, man?
Stop!       Joey!
Joey, get off me!
Where were we?
Come on. Go, Go, Go
- What was that? - We gotta get out of here!
- Is not working! - Do it again!
It is broken!
Come On. Come On!
No no. Do Not!
It is not working.
My phone's dead. Shit!
Sara.
- Wer'e trapped! - Sara.
Sara, stop it!
You said it was safe, Eva. That no one would get hurt!
I know. But when Joey touched the eye ...
Marcus is dead!
He's dead and he's never coming back.
No! Fuck!
What happened to Joey?
I do not know.
But, somehow, we ihave summoned a malicious spirit.
A malicious spirit.
You mean a demon.
Look, whatever it is, it's powerful.
It's possessed Joey and trapped us in the building.
We have to find out what it wants.
You want to talk to it?
We have to help Io to pass to the next dimension.
You're crazy, you know? You lost your mind!
It is the only way to save Joey.
Joey 's gone, Eva.
That thing, that monster down there killed Marcus ...
and you want to go back there and talk to it?
I'm sorry, but I will not. I can not.
We have no choice.
When I knocked Joey unconscious ...
I trapped the spirit inside his body.
He's going to come around/ and when he does
it is not going to be prety
Please, Sara.
I need your help.
Fuck!
Hey!
Marcus!
Marcus, get me out of here!
What the fuck, Guys?
Why am I on the ground, Eva?
Joey, is that you?
No, it's the Easter Bunny!
Help me up.
- Are you going to untie me or what? - We can't.
Not yet.
- What do you mean you can't? - We have to make sure ...
that you're not going to attack us again.
What?
Where's Marcus?
- You don't remember? - Remember what?
Marcus get in here, I'm going to kick your ass!
- It sounds like Joey. - Of course it sounds like Joey!
I'm sitting here on the floor aren't I?
It's me. Joey Polito
The spirit can still be hiding inside.
Spirit?
Okay, let's go back
Does somebody want to tell me what's going on?
What's the Iast thing you remember, Joey?
I do not know. Look, my head's killing me right now, alright?
Answer the damn question, Joey.
We were using the spiritual board ...
and Eve did some trick with the eye.
I do not know, it all goes blurry, I don't know
You do not remember because you were possessed, Joey.
What the hell are you talking about?
You were possessed by an evil spirit.
A demon.
A demon?
Do you guys have any idea how crazy you sound?
I need to talk to the spirit inside your head, Joey.
You have to let me hypnotise you
So I can bark like a dog every single time you whistle?
I don't think so
You have to let her do it.
Where's Marcus?
Hypnosis does not work unless you give permission.
Pleae, Joey. We do not know what else to do.
You have to let Eva hynotise you.
Fuck! Where's Marcus?
He is dead.
What?
Okay, okay, this is a joke, right?
That's joke. You guys are all in on a joke, right
You got me.
I get it. You're all going to teach me a lesson for all the bullshit that...
Okay, fine
I've learned my lesson. Okay?
Untie me now. Enough is enough.
This isn't a joke, Joey.
Bullshit!
Where's Marcus?
Marcus?
Where is he, dammit?
What the hell is going on, Sara?
Sara, come on
Come on. Untie me, please.
Please.
Stay away from me.
What is that?
Marcus?
My God, Marcus. What is this? What happened?
- You attacked us. - Bullshit!
Marcus tried to stop you and you broke his neck.
Do Not! Marcus is my best friend! I would never do that!
We saw you, Joey.
We saw you break Marcus's neck
We have no reason to lie to you.
My God, You're serious
You are serious?
Joey...
Look, I know you would never do anything to hurt us.
But when you touched the eye of Isis ...
you allowed the spirit to enter your body.
So you're saying that this spirit or whatever ...
It's inside of me?
Yes
Well then get it the fuck out of me
Ok then you have to let me hypnotise you
Yeah, whatever. Let's get it done.
Okay ... good.
But can't do it here. It's not safe.
Come On.
What are you doing?
It is a bonding spell that my grandmother taught me.
Is this really necessary?
It's for our protection.
And yours.
Okay.
Are you ready?
I want you to stare ...
to this spot on my forehead, right here.
The more you focus on this spot ...
the more you feel your body relaxing.
You will notice that the sound of my voice ...
becomes more relaxing.
Now as you relax
you are going to go even twice as deep.
And you' are going to hear every word I say.
Five, four ...
three ... even deeper ...
two ... and one.
Now, you are completely asleep.
Can you hear me, Joey?
Tell me your name.
Joseph James Polito.
Good.
Your soul is your spirit and your body is your vessel.
Is there anyone else inside your body?
Yes
Do you know his name?
No, he won't tell me.
Is he your friend?
No
Do you want hime to leave your body?
- Yes - Okay.
It's okay.
I'm talking now to the spirit entity inside Joey's body.
You too are subject to my hypnosis ...
so you must answer my questions.
Can I talk to the spirit entity inside Joey's body?
You can not hypnotize me, little girl.
What's your name?
Names have power, Eva Delgado ...
you should know that.
My God!
And God will not help you, Sara.
Not after what you did.
What did you say?
You were not always a good little girl.
Were you Sara?
We know your little secret.
Do not listen to him, Sara.
He's just messing with you.
What do you want with Joey?
I want his body.
You are not welcome here.
You must leave him.
I think not.
I've been looking for a suitable vessel ... ...
for over two hundred years.
This body is so strong and so young.
I think I'll stay until he's all used up
I will not allow that.
You won't allow it?
Who do you think You Are?
How is my friend, Marcus?
He is with Jesus, asshole.
He's not with...Jesus.
He is with us.
I do not believe you.
If Marcus is in hell, you should know everything about him
, right?
Of course.
What's his brother's name?
Run! Get out of here now!
Joey?
He's still alive.
Outside.
Eve, where are you going?
Eva?
Joey tried to save us. You can't jst walk away.
I am not trained for this.
You better figure it out.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
I've never dealt with someone who was possessed.
We need a priest.
A priest?
We can not leave the building, how do we find a priest?
It's on you, Eva.
You summoned that demon into Joey and
you've got to drive it out
I can not.
- I might make it worse. - How? How could it be worse?
I might kill him!
Joey is dying, Eva.
He's dying.
You have to try something.
Please.
Okay. Okay.
There are specific prayers... incantations
If I had a prayer book, I could try.
Come On.
What are we looking for?
We need the King James Bible.
Sara, I'm not Christian.
When are you going to get it, Eva?
This is not some damn poltergeist we're dealing with ...
This is a demon.
Okay, you summoned a demon.
This is God versus the devil.
Good versus evil. You cant mess around
If you want Joey to survive this, you need the Bible.
Okay.
From what I remember ...
we need to make the demon so uncomfortable ...
that he choose to leave the physical flesh ...
rather than stay and endure the pain.
How do we do that?
Prayers, a cross and holy water.
Demons hate all three.
Okay
We have rosaries, we have prayer books.
We've got holy water.
We just need something to hold it.
Ive got just the thing. Here.
Okay ...
that's everythingl.
Are you ready?
Yeah. You?
What if we are not strong enough?
Then we pray for help.
Look at this:
"Finally, my brethren, be strong in the Lord and in
the power of his might
Put on the whole armor of God ...
that we may be able to stand against the wiles of the devil. "
The armor of God.
This is not a prayer, Eva, this is a call to battle.
This is going to be a fight
But it's a fight we can win
if you put all your faith in God.
Sara, my grandmother was killed by the Catholic Church.
I'm doing my best here.
I have something for you downstairs.
Come on.
There it is.
Sara, that was your mother's.
She would have wanted you to have it
Thank You.
That's weird.
What is it?
Holy water was right there.
What 's wrong?
Nothing.
My God! My hand!
My God!
Let me look at it! Let me look at it! - No no!
Eva, I'll have to pull it out.
- No, please! - These scalpels are infected.
We have to pull it out.
- Okay. - On three.
One two three.
We have to stop the bleeding!
Help me!
There's no disinfectant! - My God!
My God!
My God, help me! Please!
We ... We've got bleach.
That will have to do
Here.
My God! The scalpel was disgusting.
I can't even count how many infections I have.
The bleach will take care of most of it.
At least the bleeding stopped.
Yeah
How do you feel?
Angry.
Good.
I think this verse has got your name all over it.
Yea,  though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death ...
I will fear no evil, for Thou art with me ...
Thy staff and Thy rod they comfort me.
My favorite psalm.
Thou preparest a table for me in the presence of mine enemies ...
Thou anointest my head with oil; my cup runneth over.
Your cup is empty, Eva.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me ...
every days of my life ...
and I will dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
You have to believe for the words to have power, Eva.
Burn it.
Lord, stretch out your hand and look down on Joey.
Silence, witch.
God will not listen to your words.
You're not welcome here, demon!
It's time for you to move on!
Do not presume to tell me what to do, child!
I exorcise thee in the name of God, the Father Almighty ...
and in the name of Jesus Christ, His Son, our Lord and judge.
And in the power of the Holy Spirit ...
that thou depart from this creature of God ...
- Joseph Polito. - Amen!
God will not forgive you for what you've done, Sara.
You know I'm telling you the truth.
Keep going
We make this plea, devil, for your expulsion.
We make this plea, devil, for your destruction
You have no idea what you're doing, do you?
In the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Ghost.
Amen.
Your words have no power over me, Eva.
I used to fuck your grandmother in hell.
St. Michael the Archangel, we ask you to defend us
in this battle ...
against this world of evil.
The Holy Church venerates you as her true guardian
and protector.
The Holy Church burns witches like you, Eva.
Exodus 22:18..
Thou shall not suffer a witch to live!
Come back to us, Eve. You belong with us.
I'll make you a queen.
I used to rule for a thousand years before the Christian God.
And with you by my side, Eva, we will rule again.
Come back to me.
I'd rather die.
Your might get your wish
Eva, come on, this is not working.
Don't leave, Eva.
Come on, Eva.
We have to try something else.
Like what?
Like the power of Christ.
My God.
Whats happening?
It's the demon!
Oh no! Eva, get the door!
Okay.
My God! Sara! Sara!
My God!
My God, Sara!
Okay ...
You have to straighten the bone
What?
Take my foot, twist and pull it straight.
Sara, I don't know ... - Once it's straight ...
wrap it tight, use the gauze.
And find something to make a splint.
Hurry
Okay.
- It will work. - Okay
Okay
Now what?
If I pass out you have to keep going until you
get the splint on, okay?
Promise me?
I promise.
Okay.
Put your left hand under my heel.
Take your foot with your right hand.
You need to pull and twist, okay?
Okay
- Okay. - Are you ready?
Do it!
It's not working. - Use your hands. Use your hands!
Okay
- I can't do this!
I'm sorry!
Use your belt.
Wrap it around the bone and pull it tight.
Okay. Okay.
alright
Okay
Sara.
Hey, welcome back.
How are you doing?
I've been better.
Slowly.
Nice splint
I found you a walking stick
Thanks.
We're going to die, aren't we?
No
No, we're not
Not if you accept the power of Christ to fight this thing.
How do I do that?
Just open your heart and ask for forgiveness.
God will do the rest.
Sara...
I rejected the Christian God my whole life.
That does not matter.
He has already forgiven you.
All you have to do is ask.
Okay
Get the prayer book.
Pray with me.
Yeah
I believe in God the Father ...
Almighty, creator of heaven and earth.
And in Jesus Christ, His only Son, our Lord ...
which it was conceived by the Holy Spirit ...
born of the Virgin Mary ...
suffered under Pontius Pilate.
He was crucified, dead and buried ...
He descended to the dead.
He rose again the third day ...
He ascended into heaven ...
and is seated at the right hand of God the Father Almighty.
Whence shall come to judge the living and the dead.
I believe in the Holy Spirit, the holy Catholic Church ...
the communion of saints, the forgiveness of sins ...
the resurrection of the body and life everlasting.
Amen.
How is the foot, Sara?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Open the prayer book.
Oh, you're going to ignore me now, is that it?
In the name of Jesus Christ, we confidently undertake...
to repuls the attacks and deceits of the devil.
You're boring me.
May your mercy. Lord,  descend down upon us.
We five you from us ...
all unclean spirits ...
all satanic powers, all infernal invaders ...
all wicked legions.
Jesus will not answer your prayers, Sara, you know that.
Not after you have committed a mortal sin.
What did you say?
- Sara, keep reading. - Tell her, Sara.
Tell her about little Jude.
How do you know his name?
- Who is Jude? - Sar's bloody little bundle.
What?
Leave me alone!
Sara, who is Jude?
It's my baby!
That wasn't your fault.
You had a miscarriage.
Yeah, with a little help fom a coat hanger
Sarah was six months pregnant, he was still alive when ...
she squeezed him out, wasn't he?
They took him from me. They wouldn't tell me if he
was alive or dead!
You never told Joey, did you?
Joey never knew that he was a  Daddy.
Oh yes. That's right, Joey.
Joey was the father
Sara?
Joey was the father?
It was after you broke up.
It was a one-night stand. We were both wasted.
I tried to tell him, but he did not want to be a father.
How did you know, if you did not ask?
Where's Jude?
Didn't baby Jesus tell you?
Is he alive? Please, tell me.
Why don't you ask baby Jesus?
That's right, I forgot.
He does not answer the prayers of the damned.
No, He forgave me. I know he did.
I don't think so, because there's some things
you can't be forgiven for ...
and killing your baby is one of them.
No! I didn't know!
Baby Killer!
I told you it was just going to be you and me, Eva.
Oh, Eva!
Come back Eva!
Sara.
Sara, why didn't you tell me?
You could have tallked to me.
I was so ashamed after what I did with Joey.
After all ...
I'm a bad person.
I'm damned.
I'm going to hell.
No you are not.
Jude?
Sara.
Is that you, baby?
Mommy's got you.
Mommy's got you now.
It's you?
baby Killer!
I'm tired of this shit!
What? Where are you taking me?
Jesus forced that legion of demons into a herd of pigs, right?
That's right.
And then he drove the pigs off a cliff and drowned them
Yes. So what?
We're going to send this mother-fucker back to hell.
In the name of Jesus Christ, I command you to leave this body.
He has not suffered enough. yet
Burn him.
You have no power over me, mortal.
Again.
It is he who commands you.
He who flung you headlong from the heights of heaven ...
to the depths of hell.
It is he who commands you.
He who once stilled the sea, and the wind and the storm.
Again!
- We need more holy water. - Keep praying!
Tremble in fear, you enemy of the faith,
you foe of the human race ...
you begtter of death, you robber of life.
Corrupter of justice, you root of all evil and vice.
Seducer of men, betrayer of nations ...
instigator of envy, font of avarice ...
formentor of discord, author of pain and sorrow.
Do not despise my command because you know
me to be a great sinner.
It is God himself who commands you.
I adjure you, ancient serpent ...
By the judge of the living and the dead ...
by your Creator, by the Creator of the whole universe ...
by he who has the power to consign you to the depths of hell ...
Be gone from this temple of the Lord!
Are you kidding?
This is the best seat in the house.
I'm not going anywhere.
Liar.
You are trapped.
I bound you with my prayer.
I'm not trapped
I can leave anytime I want.
But where's the fun in that?
You see, if I don't give you any hope, you are not
going to struggle so much
And I do love to see you struggle
Prove it
You couldn't stay away, could you?
I command you in the name of ...
Are you ready to die, little christian?
Go to Hell
If Jesus can turn water into wine ...
imagine what I can do.
You have no power over me, demon.
Jesus protects those who love Him.
Sara.
Let's finish this.
The power of Christ ...
Help me!
God.
My God ...
I'm dying, Eva.
No! Please.
You have to let me go.
I'm going to see my baby.
You're not going anywhere.
Please.
Stay with me.
We will survive this, we'll be together.
Promise me one thing.
Anything.
Save him for me.
Sara.
Eva.
You know ...
I hate to be the kind of guy who says "I told you so."
But I did warn you that it would just come down
to you and me
Ready or not, Eva ...
here I come.
Please, Jesus, protect me.
Protect me in my hour of need.
Please.
He can't hear you!
But I can.
Shall we say mass?
Back off!
What do you think I am, a vampire?
I will kill you.
Not before I shove that cross up your ass.
Please.
Please do not kill me.
I'll do anything.
Anything?
It's been so long since I've had a willing mortal.
What?
Let's start with a little kiss.
A kiss?
Don't worry, I won't melt your pretty little face, I promise.
Okay
You stupid fucking whore!
I could make you a queen.
I could have given the world!
Now I'm going to rip off your head!
It is he who commands you.
He who flung you headlong from the heights of heaven ...
to the depths of hell.
The power of Christ compels you!
Leave this body and go to the rat!
Joey.
I'm sorry
Go to hell.
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0