- Baby, I put it right over there.
- No, you did not.
Baby, ifs right there.
You know I take care of you.
- Yeah.
- I give you everything.
I'm okay.
I can do this.
I'm not scared.
Ifs okay. I'm not scared.
I can do this.
I'm not scared.
I'm okay. I'm not scared.
I can do this.
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Where you going, baby?
I'm at 14811 Jefferson.
I want to go to...
77 Oak Ridge Road
in Saddle Ridge, New Jersey.
Yeah, New Jersey.
Have you seen my daughter?
What you do to your hair, sweetie?
Agnes, open HP-
I ain't got time for your crap!
I'm getting out of here.
What?
I said I'm out.
You ain't going nowhere,
you little bitch!
Open up!
You going to Jersey?
You got the money?
Yeah.
- Slut!
- Back off the car!
You slut! You useless slut!
You owe me!
- Back off the cab!
- You ain't going nowhere!
You're going to give me my money,
you little bitch!
Honey?
I'm sorry, okay?
Mommy loves you, okay?
Back off the car!
You're nothing
but a dumb, useless whore!
You'll be back! You hear me?
You need me!
Where's the money?
Show it to me now.
That's not enough.
Get out of my cab.
Get out of the cab!
- No!
- Get out of the cab right now!
Get out of here,
you little piece of trash!
Back away from the house!
Get down on the ground.
Down!
- Get off me!
- Easy!
This is a girl, not a boy.
All right, let's get her up.
What is this?
Do you know the people
that live here?
What's going on?
We're sorry to disturb you,
Mr. Fitzpatrick,
but we received a call
from your housekeeper.
- Who the hell is that?
- We don't know.
We found this on her.
She says she knows you.
- She said she knows me?
- That's what she said.
- Where was she?
- In the back, trying to break in.
She was trying
to break into the house?
That's right.
Did you pat her down?
Did she say anything?
She has nothing on her.
Nothing else. No ID.
- Inside, guys.
- A police car.
I know.
Let's just go in the house.
- But who is it?
- I don't know.
Show me.
Do you know her?
YES-.
Let her out.
Come on.
How old are you now? Fourteen?
Fifteen?
Sixteen.
It's a nice place.
You work
in real estate or something?
No. Wall Street.
Hows your mother, Agnes?
It's Apple,
remember?
You gave the name to me.
He re's what's up.
I need a place to stay
for a little bit.
That's why I'm here.
I ain't asking you to feel guilty
and stuff like that,
so let's not even go there.
I just need a place to stay
for a little bit.
I'll get a job.
I'll get my own place,
and then I'll be gone.
Here.
I knew I couldn't count on you.
Have a nice life.
Nice to finally meet you.
Wait. Where you going?
You just showed up.
The police said you tried
to break in.
I didn't try and break in.
They're lying.
Maybe there's something
we can work out.
I'm going to have a word
with my wife.
Were you in jail?
No, Dusty, she wasn't in jail.
Ifs just a misunderstanding.
We figured it out.
What kind of misunderstanding?
Alex, it's not a problem.
It's all better now.
Agnes, where are you from?
A lot of places.
And it's Apple, not Agnes.
You can call me Apple,
not Agnes.
I thought you said it was Agnes,
but Apple is a beautiful name.
Apple? That's a funny name.
And Alex is a boy's name.
No, it's not. Yours is stupid.
She smells,
and she's weird, Mom.
Why does she have to stay with us?
Tom?
All right, you guys,
time for bed.
Cece? Bath time.
Good night.
Honey, can you please wait?
I think now
would be a good time
for us to have a little talk together.
Why don't you stop calling me honey?
Hey, Apple.
You're in my house.
Look, we want to help you,
but we don't know how to.
We're going to have to get in touch
with your social worker
or someone assigned to your case
and let them know that you're here.
When I was eight,
I was taken away from my mother
when she was arrested for drugs.
I was dropped off
at a mental hospital,
where they kept me
in a steel room all by myself
because I didn't fit in
with the other kids.
From there, I was put
into another temporary shelter.
Apple.
Every few months, I'd be assigned
some new case worker,
and we'd start all over again-.
By the time I was twelve,
I was in my tenth foster home.
Seemed like good people
this time,
until the husband would come
into my room at night
and start touching me
and feeling all up on me.
I told my case worker,
and she got the police involved.
He told them
that I was making it all up,
because
that's what troubled kids do,
and they believed him.
I was too scared to even open up
my own mouth.
I ran away
and went to find my mother
and tried to stay
with her for a while.
Things got real bad,
and I had to go.
In all that time,
that letter was the only thing
I ever got from you,
I'm just asking you for a little time,
because I am done being passed off
as someone's case number.
I want out of the system!
So are you going to help me out
so I can get back on my feet?
Or do you and Joanna
still have to talk about it?
- You happy with this?
- Yeah.
You sleep all right?
You need some help there?
- No.
- You sure'?
Yeah, I'm fine just by myself.
Damn it!
Where you going?
Come here! Wait!
I'm talking to you!
Wait!
Where you going?
It was a stupid idea
for me to come here.
It's never going to work
between us!
Never!
So why don't you just turn around
and go back to your life.
And leave me and mine alone!
Where you going to go?
Look at you.
You don't even have your shoes on.
Who cares?
Here.
Come inside.
Are you pregnant?
What?
What are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
- She's just not feeling well.
Why don't you let her answer that?
She's not going to answer anything.
I'm going to ask you again.
Are you pregnant?
- I knew it.
- You knew what?
I don't know.
See? She doesn't know anything.
- I know.
- You don't know.
- Calm down, will you?
We are not having
this baby in our house.
What baby?
Where's the dad?
Is he in jail?
I don't know.
We only did it once-.
I need to talk
to you right now alone, please.
You want her in our life?
I don't know what you're thinking.
I will take care of it,
and we need to find...
I want her out!
Please, no-.
Come on, no.
We're here to check in.
Apple Bailey.
Thank you.
Hear that?
That's the heartbeat.
We almost done here?
Just a few more images.
Here you go. These are for you.
Good luck.
You see the woman I came in with?
Where have you been?
You're all wet.
Where you going?
Where were you'?
Wait!
Where did you disappear to?
I didn't disappear anywhere!
She left me there!
She left me!
Nobody left you anywhere! Stop!
I left you there?
You're a liar!
I waited for her.
She's trying to get in between us.
Do you see what I mean? A liar!
Cool it! Maybe you should
give us a minute... now!
Look at me.
Look at me!
Well, it's about time.
How are you feeling today?
Hungry'-
Shouldn't you be at work
or something?
I took the morning off.
I had a few things to do
with the construction,
and I wanted to check in with you.
I'm fine,
so I guess you can go.
You know...
today is an important day
for my firm,
and especially for me.
One of our biggest clients
asked to meet
with me personally to sign a deal.
Do you know why?
Mutual respect, trust,
and confidence.
This is what I've earned
from my peers.
Ifs taken me years to build this.
These are the same words
that I want to speak about with you.
Mutual respect,
such as I respect you,
you respect me.
That means
when I tell you something,
you stop ignoring me.
Trust, such as
when this conversation is over,
I'm going to leave here,
and I'm going to trust
that you are not going to get
into a street brawl with my wife.
And confidence.
These are the positive results
of our relationship
that can begin to happen
once the first two things
start to happen.
Joanna and I had
a long talk last night, and...
it's clear that you are not ready
to assume the responsibility
of motherhood.
Think about it.
You have no means of support
you have nowhere to live,
and you have no one
willing to help you except me.
It's time
that you turn the page on this.
Put it all behind you
so that you can move forward.
Just turn the page,
and before you know it,
you'll have forgotten
that it ever happened.
Just turn the page.
YES-.
And forget about it.
That's right.
Like you did with me.
Thank you, Cece.
I know that you must hate me,
and I just wanted
to say I'm sorry
about the misunderstandings.
No one's perfect, right?
How did your talk go
with your father?
Did he tell you?
Tell me what?
I made an appointment
for you tomorrow morning
at a clinic.
Wait, what?
You're not going to be able
to take care of this child by yourself.
We're not going to deal with this,
and if you don't cooperate,
we're going to have
no choice but to ask you to leave.
I don't want to do that.
Ifs not about what you want, honey,
unless you want to end up
just like your mother.
You don't have to worry
about anything.
I will be with you
to hold your hand.
Hi, Tom.
Not yet.
I'm sorry.
No cell phones, please.
I have to hang up.
Honey, I think I'm going
to wait in the waiting room.
Can you hurry up, please?
The doctor's on his way.
You got a man with you?
I'm okay.
I'm not scared.
Please, God.
Protect me.
Yo, Shorty.
Shorty, we got some business
we need to discuss.
Yo, Shorty,
let me holler at you.
You going to
make me come over there?
I said get in the car. Come on.
Don't you hear me?
I said get in the car.
We got some business to discuss.
Get your ass in the car.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm going to kill you,
you little bitch!
Rest easy.
You're in the security ward,
Newark City Hospital.
I'm Father Frank McCarthy,
chaplain here at the hospital.
Do I have your permission to be
in this room with you?
I'm not here about that.
Your baby's all right.
The doctors had this taken
when they found
the one in your shoe.
Can you try talking?
I don't need a priest.
God don't care about me.
Don't waste your time.
You're mistaken.
God is ever near
and with us always.
Last time I asked for his help,
he put me here.
He's a tough C.O. at times,
but maybe...
you're exactly
where you were meant to be.
“Lord, make me
an instrument of Thy peace;
"Where there's hatred,
let me sow lave;"
“Where there's injury, pardon;
"Where there's doubt, faith.“."
You still here?
This is still here,
I'm still here.
You were sleeping, so I didn't think
you'd mind if I used your john.
I found out that
the authorities will probably drop
all charges against you,
but they're
going to keep you here
until they can get
in touch with your family
or find you a temporary home.
I didn't ask you to talk
to anyone for me.
Why do you want to help me?
It's my job.
You're a priest.
If you were a good one,
you'd be at your own church
right now, not here.
This is my church.
And I'm
not just thinking about you.
What will happen
if you leave here by yourself?
Where will you go?
Here.
I want you to have this.
Being young and pregnant
is like being a pinwheel.
Whenever the weather changes,
you have no idea
what way your life is going to go.
The pinwheel is supposed
to bring good fortune.
Go ahead.
Blow it.
I did some research for you.
It led me to a special shelter
for teens
who want to have their babies,
like your baby.
Don't try and tell me this.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I've been in shelters and foster cares
my whole life.
I ain't going back to no shelter!
Don't make your child suffer
because you're suffering.
God put you here for a reason.
Leave! Now!
You talk about suffering!
Where was God
when I was getting abused
and suffering all these years, huh?
You can't help me!
You think you know me.
You don't know anything!
Now get out!
Leave!
Just press the nurse's station
on the phone
when you want me
to come and get you, okay?
Agnes, I was so worried
about you, baby.
What are you doing here?
Agnes, I'm Marie Abeanni,
your social worker.
I will be handling your discharge
when the time comes.
I had a long talk with your mother.
She's very concerned
about your well-being
and assured me
that this was an isolated incident,
that things at home
are okay between you and her.
Is this true?
I already told you we good.
Why you asking again?
Excuse me.
I need to talk with Agnes now
and hear it from her.
Agnes, look at me.
Your mother has custody,
so it is better
if we work this out together.
If you run away again,
we may have to place you
back in foster care.
Going home
is the best solution for you.
Your mother wants
to talk with you now
to settle your differences.
Do you think you can do this?
Yeah, whatever.
Good.
I'll be sitting right outside the room
if you have any other questions.
You got people asking
all types of questions,
coming around my place
looking around.
You crazy?
She said you carrying a baby?
And I got to hear
about it from a stranger.
That's nice. That's real nice.
Humiliate me like that!
What's wrong with you?
No, come on.
Why you think I'm here, huh?
State's going to take care of us.
You, me, and baby,
that makes three.
That means
when that baby comes out,
they're going to be paying us
more money.
We got another chance, all right?
We're going to be a real family now,
sweetie, for real.
Come on.
Look at you.
Taking me back.
You know,
I wasn't that much older than you.
Seventeen.
Don't look at me like that,
like you all high and mighty.
I didn't have no social worker
caring about me.
Nobody wanted me to have you!
Wait.
You think I always looked
like this, huh?
Like I born in the streets?
You don't know
what I wanted out of life.
You don't know who I was,
who I could have been.
You're so stuck up.
You think you're
so much better than me.
Like you're so different.
Baby, you are me.
You'll see.
When you're fighting for your baby,
and you're so young,
and you ain't got nobody
to take care of it,
you can't even
take care of yourself.
And all you want to do
is protect your baby.
That's all I wanted to do.
Hold my baby.
My little baby girl.
You don't know.
But I did.
I did everything that I could, Agnes.
I did.
And I messed up, okay?
That's right, I messed up.
And then when they took you
away from me,
that was the worst day of my life.
I hurt so much right here.
I just wanted
the pain to go away, baby.
I didn't want to feel nothing.
I didn't want to feel anything.
Look at me.
Look at me now.
I deserve a second chance.
A second chance.
Please, baby?
Please just give me
one more chance.
I don't know.
Baby, I'm your mother.
I just can't do this anymore.
- Just one more chance.
- I can't do this anymore.
Please, baby.
You got to let me go.
- You ready?
- Yeah. We're done here.
"But we will build"
"with hewn stones."
"“The sycamores"
"...as men rejoice
when they divide the spoil."
“For thou hast broken
the yoke of thy burden...“
Father?
I just wanted to...
to come here...
to tell you that...
I probably
shouldn't have yelled at you.
I mean, I know why I did.
I didn't think that...
that you would...
Are you apologizing to me?
Not really.
Seems like it to me.
Never apologize
for your true feelings.
Now that you're here,
grab a book.
Make yourself useful.
Page seventy-two.
We'll talk later.
Go on.
And?
"For I know the plans I have for you,"
"declares the Lord,"
"plans for your welfare
and not for evil,"
"to give you..."
"give you a future"
"and hope."
"Then you will call upon me,"
"and come and pray to me,"
"and I will hear you.“."
Father McCarthy.
Hi, I'm Afra,
one of the housemothers here.
Welcome to our shelter.
I'll let Kathy know you're here.
That's Kathy right there
with Mother Teresa.
And that's her in that one
at the White House
with Ronald Reagan.
Hello, Father. Good to see you.
Please bear with me.
We were having a little incident.
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything
worked out just fine.
Thank you for meeting
my friend, Apple.
Hello, Apple.
Kathy's the founder.
She started this shelter
twenty years ago,
taking young mothers
into her own home.
This is your home?
Well, ifs grown quite a bit.
Afra will give you a tour.
I'm going to wrap some things up,
and then you and I
will meet in the morning
and we'll have a chat
about the rules, okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
See you suddenly, Apple.
Hey, everybody, this is Apple-.
She's staying with us.
Her name is really Apple?
You will all get
to know her better later.
You'll be sharing a room
with Tawana.
And she'll show you to your room.
And I'll be on duty
if you need something.
Apple, huh'?
Goes well with caramel.
Carmel, caramel.
I'm just saying.
We just playing"!!-
She can't take a joke?
You can put your stuff in here.
I don't have any stuff.
Well, don't worry. You will.
Would you mind holding her
for a second?
Thanks.
Okay, Isaiah.
I hear you.
- What's your name?
- What the...?
- Where you from?
- Get that out of my face!
What is going on in here?
I like your PJ's.
Cassandra,
you missed curfew again tonight,
and you didn't tell anybody
where you were going.
I'm writing you up,
and it's not going
to be good for you.
Who is responsible for letting her
in here after curfew'!
Was it you, Apple?
I don't even know her.
She's crazy.
This is not going to look good
for your first night.
That's a really nice name.
We will deal with this tomorrow.
But you shouldn't call
people crazy around here.
I actually prefer Cassie.
It's five a.m.
I want everybody
back in their rooms now.
What happened
with you two last night?
Cassie, why were you late for curfew?
I went for a walk.
I got locked out.
I'm sorry? You got...
I went for a walk.
I got locked out.
It was nothing, really.
Good, because
I'm going to put you both
in the same room temporarily.
You're going to be roommates.
With her?
Why?
It'll to give you a chance
to work out your differences.
We have a twenty-four-hour rule
in this house.
Whenever two girls
are disputing,
they need to work it out
right away.
Do you have a problem with that?
Ifs exciting.
Good.
Cassie, would you
excuse us, please?
I have something
to talk to Apple about.
Apple, we have a serious problem.
Your mother will not give her consent
for you to be here.
I'm very sorry.
I tried everything I could.
How could you call her?
She will never let me go.
Not as long as welfare
keeps sending her money.
Why would you do this to me?
Because she threatened
to call the police
and charge us with kidnapping.
What do you have
against your mother?
Did she ever abuse you?
I don't want to talk about it.
You can tell me what it is.
I can't.
Then I can't help you.
As much as I like you
and care about you and your baby,
I won't go to jail for you.
Because you're a minor,
I need the support of the state
or consent from your family...
And I'm supposed to believe that'?
Stop talking and listen to me.
Or some legal reason
why you have to stay here.
You said you
was going to help me out.
You're a liar.
Apple, here you become a mother,
and that means
you take responsibility.
Don't cast your immaturity on me,
and then ask me to risk
everything,
including the future of this shelter,
on your foolishness.
Stop dancing with your demons!
Look at me.
Learn to cooperate.
Shine the light on the lock.
It won't open.
Get lotion.
This is like the shopping mall.
Shut up!
Check this out.
I don't think he's going to be able
to fit in that any time soon.
You calling my son fat?
You're a huge jerk.
Sh ll, 9 "Vs-".
Wow, Kathy needs
to clean up her office.
There's a lot in here.
- I know.
- Gosh.
Hurry up. Close the door.
Look. What's that?
Who's that?
Is that Kathy?
Let me see-.
No, ifs not.
Yeah, it's Kathy as a little girl.
Wow, she's nuke.
- She ain't all that, Jazzie.
- She's pretty.
She fight.
Don't open it. Who said that?
What is this?
Oh, wow.
"Carmel Nickerson.“."
What's that?
U N ice '3 ﬂ'
Yep.
“Destiny Morell.“
it's Princess.
Thank you.
“Danisha Dormer.“
Don't put my government out like that.
"Apple Bailey.“."
"Jasmine Colon.“."
It's Colon-n.
All right, check this.
This says "compulsive, anxiety,
and personality disorders."
What's “compulsive”?
It means you ask
too many questions.
What about you, Pink Friday?
Don't call me Pink Friday.
"Drugs, prostitution,
criminal record,"
"personality disorder."
"No family on record.“."
Prostitution?
Are you serious
with the prostitution?
Damn, girl.
You got a record!
“Rape victim, runaway.
“Family does not want her back.“
It's all right.
We're your family.
Ifs okay, Jazzie. We want you.
Mine says, "Mental
and physical abuse as a child."
"Chronic depression
and must overcome fear."
What the what?
No fear?
What about you, Apple?
It says,
"Severe physical abuse, runaway,"
“parental drug£alcohol abuse,
"multiple shelters and foster care,"
"aggressive behavior,"
"lack of trust.“."
Don't worry.
You can trust us, though.
Yeah, you're not aggressive.
That's what it says.
Hi. Can I help you?
- You must be Kathy, right?
- Yes.
I'm Agnes' mother.
Where is she? Agnes!
Oh, yes. Why don't you come in.
Where's my daughter at? Agnes?
I'm taking her home.
I missed you.
Yo, little Agnes?
Can I get you something
to eat or drink?
You must be very tired from the drive.
Nah.
We're leaving.
Grab your stuff. We're going.
I ain't going anywhere with you.
What?
Shut up, all right? You coming!
I'm just texting my associate
to have her things brought down.
Nah, you know what?
We don't need anything
from you, all right?
Come on.
No, no! I'm sorry.
NO! I cannot.
- You may not take her!
- What?
I am required by law
to report any abuse.
I'm sorry.
- Mind your own business!
- No, I'm sorry.
You don't come with me right now,
I'm calling DYFS,
and I'm putting you in a home!
You think for one second
they're going to let you keep that baby?
It's your choice-.
I have called the police.
If you don't want to be arrested,
you need to leave right...
- Nobody cares about us!
- I'm sorry.
You have to leave now.
Don't you know that?
I hate you.
Listen to me.
You need to leave.
You need to leave right now.
You don't even know what you did.
June?
Is that you?
What the hell is he doing here?
You have got to go.
Honey, you have got to go now.
I don't want to be around him.
Agnes, how could you
do that to me?
- I'm her mother!
- Stop.
I'm Tom.
Hi, Tom, I'm so sorry.
It'll have to be another time.
I made a mistake.
I'm so sorry.
It's not a good time.
- But I need to talk to Apple.
- I know you do.
I'm so sorry,
but it'll have to be another time.
- Can I help?
- No, we're good.
Another time, please.
- Can I just have a word...
- I'm so sorry.
Okay, honey.
Ifs okay now. Come on.
Let's go inside.
I've got you.
I don't know, but I know
I'm craving some red velvet cake.
How many more of these
do we have to do?
Kathy says
the more envelopes we send out,
the more donations we can get.
'So: M
'so: M.
It's going to be four black babies
and four white babies now.
Carmel, you can't count.
You forgot yourself.
Just s“ dum, dumdum.
And Tina and Jaz are Hispanic,
not white,
so that's another category.
Besides, you don't even know
what Apple's baby is.
For all you know,
it may be a caramel color like you.
Yet another category.
Okay, well, I tried.
My baby's father's black.
I bet he's fine.
See? I told you.
I bet you guys were getting it on.
Everybody grab a box
or something.
Take a box in.
Very good.
Can you get the door?
Need help?
I would like to call up
Kathy Defiore,
who many of us know,
to talk about her very special work
that she is doing.
Thank you, Father Marks.
Good morning, everybody.
Or should I say good afternoon?
- Good afternoon.
- I have been... thank you...
here eight or nine times
at Our Lady of Sorrows,
and I thought to myself,
"What can I say to you all"
"that I haven't said before?“."
Twenty years ago,
I was homeless.
And I'm not sure
I can really explain
what it was like
being without a home,
frightened and alone,
and all the while trying to hold
onto my dignity as a woman.
And then my life
began to turn around.
I found a job
and a home.
And then I had
the most wonderful inspiration.
I opened my home as a shelter
for teenage pregnant girls,
because, you see, I understand
that this may be
the only chance they have.
So please open your hearts;.
Take a look at your envelopes,
so that
we can give them shelter,
we can give them guidance,
we can give them an education.
So that we can give them a future.
Thank you, and God bless.
Thank you so much.
What a beautiful sermon.
Now you're not only a whore,
but you're a frickin' beggar too?
Let's see how much they give
an ugly beggar!
Give me a kiss!
Slop!
Get off me!
Why don't you come inside?
It is freezing out here.
You can come and help
with the decorations.
We're having a party.
A party for what?
Destiny went to the hospital
to have Leticia.
We're going to surprise her.
She's going to be back
in a few days.
Ifs going to be okay.
Aren't you sick of this?
Of what?
What? Being exploited?
The way we're marched
around here.
The way
we're told what to wear,
when to smile,
who to be nice to?
It all makes me sick.
I'm tired of it, aren't you?
We ain't got much of a choice.
I know I don't want anyone
feeling any pity for me
except for me.
Do you want me
to feel bad for you, Apple?
Because you know that
you're not the only girl around here
who never really had a mom.
Why can't she
just leave me alone?
I suffered my whole life
because of my mother,
and now that she's gone,
I suffer even more.
You hate her
for what she's done to you,
but deep down, you love her,
and that hurts you even more.
So what about it?
I'm getting my own place.
You should come with me.
Think about it.
And what about your baby?
My baby's all right.
Ain't nothing happening to my baby.
You sound like them.
I'm just saying that maybe...
Everything's set up
for after Christmas.
We're going
to go make our own money.
No more of this begging stuff.
Are you coming with me
or not, Apple?
My beautiful, healthy baby.
You're probably going to need
a little more than that.
Father McCarthy.
Thought I'd drop by
and see how you're managing.
I'm okay.
I heard about your mother.
I'm very sorry that happened.
She needs help.
But you have to think
about yourself now
and your child.
I caused all this.
It's my fault.
There's a saying in the Bible...
"All of us, like sheep,
have gone astray."
"Each of us has turned
to his own way.“."
And that's her way, not yours.
Look, I'm leaving here.
One of the girls found a place.
She wants me to come with her.
Does Kathy know about this?
No, she wouldn't understand.
Not until there's an empty bed to fill.
If you leave
the safety of the shelter,
you put yourself
and your child in jeopardy.
I got to go.
I'll pray for you.
Don't bother.
Why are you putting
a binky on the tree?
It looks stupid.
I kind of like it.
Yeah.
See that?
- I like it, too.
- Thank you.
Yeah, me, too.
We should
all put baby stuff on the tree.
I think that's a good idea.
Hey, Apple?
You want to add stuff to the tree?
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Watch out.
Good one, Apple!
Way to go!
All right, loves.
We're going to say
"Merry Christmas", okay?
Everybody ready?
One, two, three.
Merry Christmas!
Come on now.
What you trying to do?
The baby needs to turn over.
They can be very stubborn.
You hear that?
Wonder where she gets that,
or he gets that, huh?
There it goes.
What?
See the baby moving around?
Do you want to know
the sex of the baby?
Yeah.
You're having a girl.
What are you doing?
Get your stuff. Let's go.
She kicked me.
What?
We don't have time for this.
Let's go.
No, she kicked me.
Cassie, I'm not going.
Fine. Don't go.
Cassie, don't go.
If you leave,
I'll never see you again.
I know it.
Don't you get it, Apple?
I'm no good here.
Ifs time to go.
Good-bye, Apple.
Go ahead, loves.
What's the matter, honey?
Is he hungry?
Here's Dino, everybody.
Hi, girls.
Dino has generously donated
this very special meal for us.
Come on,
it's nothing for you girls.
He's letting us eat here for free?
That's nothing.
Enjoy it, girls.
Just enjoy it.
All right, everyone, let's eat.
- What is that?
- Salad... onions.
- This looks delicious.
- I don't want that.
Who needs a plate?
Passing down.
Ladies, I have
a special announcement to make.
In just a few weeks,
it's going to be
a unique anniversary for all of us.
It was twenty years ago
that I first opened my home
to start our shelter,
and it's because
of the courage of all of you
and all the young mothers
that we have survived.
And I would like to say
thank you to you.
And the way
I'm going to do that is
I'm planning an amazing trip
to the Jersey Shore
for all of us
to celebrate together.
Can we bring our babies?
Of course,
you can bring your babies.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
I think my water just broke.
There you are.
That-a-girl.
That's it.
Good, good, good.
Yes, there it is!
And relax.
Now we need you to relax-.
Keep your eyes closed, okay?
Ifs being contracted.
That's it. Now stop pushing.
Look down, look down.
Here's your baby.
My baby.
What's her name?
- Her name is Hope.
- That's beautiful.
It's Hope.
That's my baby.
You did it, sweetheart.
We'll take her right there.
Apple, your dad is
in the waiting room,
and he needs
to be part of this moment.
Can you do this?
He can come see the baby,
but I don't want to talk to him.
"I'm sorry it worked out this way."
"I never really meant
for this to happen."
"My name is Tom."
"I'm your father, but we'll
probably never know each other."
“L just found out
you're going to be a girl.
"June and I barely know each other."
"We just went out a few times."
“It's not like we planned this.
"You just happened."
"You showed up unexpectedly."
"I'm living at home
with my parents."
“I'm about to start college-.
"I can't disappoint them."
"I have no choice."
"June is stubborn."
"I can't talk to her."
“I'll never see her again,
“so I guess I'll never see you.
"That hurts."
"I would have liked
to be your father,"
“but I'm just not ready.
"I guess I'm hoping
that you may someday understand"
"and forgive me..."
"and that maybe"
"you would be apple of my eye."
"“Fm sorry. Tom."
Thanks so much for coming.
Apple.
Congratulations.
You look good, too.
Good feet.
Good foundation.
We got some presents for you.
And flowers.
And I spelled your name right.
Julian, go ahead
and say hi to Hope.
You go right ahead
and walk right over to them.
Julian, hi.
Play date.
Let's have a play date here.
I just love you guys.
Look at her stretch.
- She's out.
- Yeah.
I'm going to feed her
before she really passes out.
It's okay.
She's out like the light.
Want me to take that?
I'm going to go
to the restroom,
and you two can
have some quality time.
You want to hold her?
YES-.
Here.
Sweet little baby.
I never got to do this with you.
I didn't understand.
I'll take her.
There you go.
You know something?
She was born one day before I was.
Which reminds me.
We're having...
a little party tomorrow afternoon.
Joanna's put it together.
It's at the house, and...
if you're not doing anything,
we were hoping
that maybe you two would come by.
Come on.
I'll show you the new place-.
She's so cute.
It's a baby!
What do you think?
Nice?
Ifs all for you and for Hope.
- For us?
- Yes.
We want you to come
and live with us.
- Can I blow out...
- I want to!
One, two, three.
Is that how you cut the cake?
Who's going
to butter daddy's nose?
Who's got a napkin for me?
Keep it on there
as a midnight snack.
You're really leaving us?
What about the Jersey Shore
next week?
Yeah. We can't go without you.
It won't be the same.
It's real hard for me
to tell you guys how I feel.
Thank you guys
so much for caring
and being there for me.
You've all been
like sisters to me.
I'm never
really going to leave you guys.
Friends for life.
We're going to miss you.
See you suddenly.
Stop the car.
Tom, stop the car.
What's wrong?
Just the people there.
I mean, the girls
and the housemothers,
they make you feel like you're family.
Like you're loved.
Like you're worth something,
and you can achieve
a lot of things.
It's crazy how you can
go and live with strangers
and feel so much joy
and not feel
like you're any different.
And not feel unwanted.
And feeling
you can go places in your life
and succeed in life.
Apple
ifs okay.
It's all right.
Come here.
All right.
I understand.
I know I could be
your daughter someday,
but I just need some time.
Can you give me that?
Yep, I can do that.
Oh, my God! Apple!