Hey, Dad. Shit!
You owe me a pack of smokes.
Come on, it was one cigarette.
Punitive damages.
Here's a whole carton.
So?
Nothing.
How's your mother?
She's fine.
You could call her Mary
every once in a while.
Close that gap up a little bit.
Don't start on me.
Is Sherry okay?
She ain't been in.
Everything good with her?
A squabble. She's back home.
Oh, hey, Mark. Hi.
Well...
Mark? Yeah?
You still doing it?
No, I stopped.
Pop, they only give me an
hour for lunch, so I gotta...
I'll see you next time.
Hey, he's a vet, okay. What do you
say you keep an eye on him for me?
Oh, no, you don't have to.
Just take it. In case
he needs anything.
Hey, I got him, my man.
I got him.
I appreciate it.
Sports Facts.
Yeah, 54012, Princess Leia.
Go 54012.
I want Marshall for five dimes.
The line is down to 10.
I don't care if it's down to seven.
Marshall plus the points is a gift.
One play on this call? Yeah.
Yeah.
The Thundering Herd.
Go Marshall.
Please.
Me, I'd forget
the one with the scanner.
Everything you need is
on the net anyway.
Like you're actually going to check out
a library book and scan it, right?
Right.
You're gonna print, you know.
Maybe make the odd copies.
Doesn't hurt to have
the fax function.
Just the fax, ma'am.
You know what, I'm gonna
show you something.
Forget that other merch, okay?
It's their ticket to a pure profit stream,
overcharge you on the replacement cartridges.
This one is cheaper out the door, and
you can refill the ink yourself.
Thanks. Yeah.
We don't make
anything off that one.
Take a microscopic margin.
Okay.
Wait.
I want to get you my
employee discount.
20% is 20%, right?
Yeah.
¶ Way, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah
¶ My way, yeah, yeah,
¶ Way, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, my
yeah, yeah, yeah
¶ Which way, yeah, yeah,
¶ My way, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ¶
What the hell's
going on here, huh?
Yeah.
Sorry, Stan, we were just...
Goofing off
and costing me money.
You think I can't see that?
Well, not to put too fine a point on it,
but wouldn't it be Pete Coors' money?
If that truck isn't cross-checked
and rolling in five minutes,
you don't work here anymore.
Roger that.
And Juan Valdez is, you know,
up in the hills going,
"Don't sue me,
if you burn yourself."
Right?
But, you know, the thing that kills me is
that they invented a whole new business.
You know,
$3 for a cup of coffee.
I don't remember anybody saying,
"Hey, this coffee sure tastes great,
"but I'd rather say grande
and pay $3 for it."
You talk a lot.
But you're cute.
Got two more hang-ups today.
It's starting to give me the creeps.
I'm on it.
What are you doing there? Stuff.
Need help? I'm good. I got it.
Are you gonna tuck Hayden in?
Hey, buddy, what's up?
Good.
Doesn't sound like it.
Hey, uh...
I thought we were partners.
We are.
So, we share intel, right?
Right. Well?
Mommy's worried.
Of course,
she's worried. Mommies worry.
What do you mean,
Mommy's worried?
About the football games.
Well, Mommy's a fan.
Mommy doesn't care who wins
but she knows you do.
I won't be late.
I just keep getting better. You wouldn't
think it was possible, but there it is.
Did he foot fault? I don't
need to cheat with you clowns.
I don't know, gonna want
to check the video.
Oh, do I detect a hint
of athletic envy?
Of you? Not in this
lifetime, baby.
Face it. You guys cannot stand the
fact that there's finally a sport
that I'm better than you at.
Hold it. Darts is not a sport.
Of course it's a sport,
numbnuts, it's on ESPN.
So is poker, big deal.
Darts is an activity.
A game, at best.
A game, huh? How do you figure?
Simple, anything you can drink beer and get
better at, by definition isn't a sport.
Football, hockey,
baseball, sports.
Bowling, pool,
darts, activities.
What about golf? Activity.
Waste of time. It's a sport.
No. If they made them carry their
own bag and run to the ball, maybe.
But it's strictly a game.
Talking about
the Championship Bowl?
Yeah. Who do you like?
The dog, Marshall.
The underdog, really?
Yeah, whenever you don't know you
take the dog and the points.
No kidding. Absolutely.
There's four possible
outcomes in any contest.
Favorite wins a blowout.
Favorite wins in a squeaker.
Dog wins a blowout.
Dog wins in a squeaker.
Three out of four scenarios you win
if you take the dog and the points.
Spend any time
thinking about this?
Big game is Saturday, who do
we like, Texas or Marshall?
Texas is a walk. The game is
over by halftime I'd say...
Ah, I'd hate to agree with the Spider-Man,
but this one is a mismatch for the ages.
All right, Dibs, we haven't heard from you.
I don't like football.
You gotta pick, Dibs.
All right, if I have to, Texas. You
don't need to be a brain surgeon.
Goliath is gonna win
this one going away.
Anybody who picks
Marshall is nuts.
All right, it's unanimous.
Texas blows them out.
Those guys don't know anything.
Charlie starts building
prow ends for the pontoons,
when he discovers
another use...
Hey, babe. Hi.
Ta-da!
Very thoughtful.
You smell like smoke.
That's 'cause I'm smokin'!
Who is this jerkoff?
He's always on.
He fixes things.
I can fix stuff too, you know.
Yeah, I know you can, honey.
Do you have anything
needing repair, ma'am?
I'm all tuned up.
Thank you very much.
Maybe I should start
under the hood.
¶ Beer, beer, beer
Get your humble hydrate here
¶ Da, da Uh, uh, uh
¶ Uh, uh
¶ Beer, beer, beer
You know that's why I'm here
¶ Beer, beer, beer... ¶
Gentlemen, puts your hands
together for Tiffany!
New move?
If she's got another
concussion, she's fired.
Somebody clean that up.
Pick up the chairs.
Don't worry about her.
Get the chairs first.
Hey, Billy. Scarlet.
You work too hard. Says
the princess of the pole.
What is that supposed to mean?
Well, do you not fling yourself
through the air like a sexy gazelle?
How come you never let
me dance for you?
'Cause I'm married.
Married guys are my specialty.
I did one right thing in my life, Scarlet,
and the price, no snacks on the side.
Snack, my butt.
You'd never eat at home again.
Maybe so.
Suit yourself.
Swing by if you
change your mind.
See you next week, Scarlet.
Okay, when everyone's
quiet, we can do this.
Watch me win this raffle.
These tickets are mine.
Funny, if you're five.
Is it just tickets to the Championship
Bowl or do you get some parties too?
Yeah, there's a party in your
mouth and everybody's coming.
It's nice to have
so many first-graders here.
And the winner is...
Jason Klein.
Ugh!
Wow. I never win anything.
Have fun.
Thanks.
Wow, this is great.
Um, I want to thank...
You suck.
Florida? No.
Look, you're a nice enough guy and all, but that's it.
Go to Florida with you?
We were so good together at coffee. We
both like two sugars and a NutraSweet...
For Christ's sake, Jade, I've got
a full waiting room. Let's go.
Yes, Doctor.
Does anyone work here?
This is what I get for
having a latte with a loser.
So you gonna think about it?
I said no, are you deaf?
Take your tickets and your
NutraSweet and get out of here.
This is my job.
So you understand why I'm here.
Daddy had the Jets. That's right.
And the Jets lost.
I know.
And that wasn't the only one.
Daddy.
Hello, Mark.
What are you doing here?
How is it that this little man understands
so much more clearly than his deadbeat dad?
Hayden, get in the kitchen.
Now!
You've got some nerve.
Just doing my job.
Now pay up.
You come into my house. You scare my wife.
You touch my kid.
I'm not paying for that.
I go where I'm sent and I get what I'm sent for.
Now what do you have for me?
I'll show you what I got.
We can do this either way.
You got some balls.
True, but enough about me.
Mark. Not now.
You will come across. You
know I don't leave otherwise.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mark.
What? Your dad died.
Hmm.
Be seeing you.
(IF YOU WERE A BLUEBIRD.
Hey, Jason.
Hey. Hi. Come on in.
Thirty-seven years
I knew him. He was a good man.
112, high average, not bad.
Well he did love to bowl.
What the hell happened to you, kid? We all
expected you to be doing big things by now.
Was it the divorce?
Your old man always blamed himself
for knocking you off track...
Hey, thanks for coming, Mr. Dean.
It really means a lot.
Let's top you off there.
Is there any wine? For sure.
That's appropriate.
What?
Well you're the one who decided
to wear your ass as an outfit.
Whatever.
Yeah, I'm here to clean
out my dad's locker.
Sure, kid. Number 64.
Sorry to hear about your pop, kid.
Straight shooter.
Oh, Dad.
Hey, Sherry, what's this?
We're going to my mom's again.
Don't call for
a few days, okay?
No, of course it's not okay.
What are you doing?
Don't act surprised.
You did this.
Look,
I don't like the timing,
but you put us at risk.
He's my son.
I'm not going to keep
your son from you.
Bye, Daddy.
This was the last straw.
I'm just saying it takes time to lug five
pallets of empties down two flights.
No, McGriff,
you are not getting off early.
I need you back here at base.
Truck 18 is loaded ass-backwards,
all the longnecks are in front.
Get back here.
It's not my bad, Donnie.
I'm knocking off early today.
Big plans.
Jesus!
How did I get here?
Hiding out in my own house.
You remember, coming out of
high school, we were stars.
Well, you were.
You gotta be kidding me.
You were fast-tracked,
4.0 pre-law at Penn.
I had my football ride,
granted it was Division II.
How many guys even
get to play college ball?
Not many.
And not quarterback.
Yeah.
Hey, baby.
No way.
Aren't you Billy McGriff
of the McGriffters?
Oh, you guys were awesome.
I was there at Toad's Hole that night
that Joe Strummer jumped up on stage
and started cranking out
that song.
¶ Which way, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah
¶ My way, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ¶
Yeah, man, that was the one.
You had it going on.
You're such a fan. Shouldn't
I be banging your wife?
She's your wife?
Geez, I had no idea.
Give me a triple kamikaze,
with two beers back.
And whatever they're having.
So I'm guessing
you're off the wagon.
Of all the guys in the world,
she chooses that nitwit.
I mean, come on. You're gonna cheat,
pick somebody better than that.
Till death do us part, period.
Fact.
Well, I'd like to
make a suggestion.
What do you say to
a little adventure?
Shed some layers.
Fun, sun... Anyone?
Pass.
It'd be good to get away for a while.
Therapeutic.
I'm not running. I am.
Where are you thinking?
Into every rain,
a little sun must fall.
Championship Bowl,
how'd you get these?
The one and only OfficeMax
Christmas drawing extravaganza.
What do you know?
I got five...
I made a little bet.
You know, on Marshall.
You know, just so I can watch the
game and have a rooting interest.
What did you bet? Just a
friendly wager, you know.
Thundering Herd, 50 bones.
Hmm, these are tremendous.
Okay, don't get any ideas. I am
definitely sitting in one of those seats.
You'll be very comfortable in the car.
Game's better on the radio.
Yeah, you get Keith Jackson.
"As another lovely Florida day
drifts into the gloaming..."
Keith Jackson's on TV.
Sometimes he does the radio.
Or you get Marv Albert. Yes!
No. No, I'm no dummy.
Nobody said you were.
You may recall, I graduated
first in our class.
I remember. You put the
"dick" in valedictorian.
This game is on Saturday. If we're
going, we better get underway.
Pronto.
Cheers.
Florida.
I want to be clear on this. I get
to use one of those tickets.
I won them,
and I get to use one.
You two can figure out
who sits with me,
and we'll scalp another
single for whoever loses.
Why should you be automatic? It
was a random draw, was it not?
Yeah, come on. It's not
like you earned them.
Just let me get my guitar.
We got the radio. We got CDs.
There's always
room for live tunes.
No way I can stomach
1,000 miles of his light FM.
What happened to him, anyway?
Why did he go all
sensitive-acoustic?
I don't know. Maybe he can
play his way out of it.
These tunes
he's singing now, yuck.
It's like he's got
Music-heimer's or something.
He's trying to stretch.
Have a range.
Well, I like it
electric and loud.
Whatever was rock and roll
about him is long gone.
Museum gone.
I should've banged your
sister when I had the chance.
We are not gonna make Florida
on one case of beer.
I can tell you that right now.
Here we go.
27, 28, 29, and one is 30.
Give me a scratch ticket,
and make it a winner.
We're going to Florida.
$1.
Have you got any halva,
for the trip?
Halva? When in Rome.
This is Pennsylvania.
85 cents.
Hey, guys. I won.
5 bucks, it only cost
me a buck. I'm up 4.
That ought to cover a couple of tolls.
That a boy.
Give me six numbers.
Let me do it. I'm on a roll.
I'm seeing...
Quick pick.
Okay, that's a loser.
What do you got?
6, 11 and 56. June 11, 1956,
Joe Montana's birthday.
Pennsylvania boy and the greatest
quarterback in history for a little yin
and if you want to go ultimate yang,
we're going with the Boston Red Sox:
10, 25, 86, October 25, 1986.
Billy Buckner's grounder
Game 6, World Series.
You're thinking the whole
yin-yang package.
You're feeling me,
aren't you, Billy?
86 is too high.
It's gotta be 60 or less.
That's okay. We go 10,
25, and let's say... 57.
Heinz 57.
You just went from Joe
Montana to steak sauce.
Yeah. No, no, no. I like it.
Run it, Abdul.
My name is not Abdul.
(QUIT YOUR LOWDOWN WAYS.
What if we get a flat?
That's defeatist.
Come on, guys. Just let me hold
them till we get to Florida.
You can be shotgun.
I'm already shotgun.
And I'd like
to hold my tickets.
Relax, you will.
That's right. We are still waiting for the
food to show up for the Labor Day picnic.
That wasn't my fault.
But it was your responsibility.
That's great. Focus.
Shotgun is no joke.
Keep this map safe
and dry at all times.
And no snoozing. There is nothing
worse than shotgun sawing wood.
What about the radio? Doesn't
shotgun handle music?
We'll see how it goes.
You gotta earn those stripes.
Okay, ship's going down,  Titanic, whatever.
You got one life ring.
Who are you throwing it to,
your wife or your kid?
She won't like it,
but it's gotta be the kid.
Gotta be the kid.
Okay, I got one.
What would you rather lose,
your eyesight or your penis?
Is this my cock or your cock?
Here we go.
'Cause my cock,
that's one thing...
I'm not comfortable with that
kind of talk in the Fury.
My mother insisted on giving
me a bath till I was 12.
Scrubbed my ears, the whole deal.
Twelve?
That's sick, why did
you stand for it?
I didn't know any better. She
was the only mother around.
Drew the line
when pubes sprouted.
Okay, uncle.
No disrespect, but I always thought
your mother was a whack job.
Ditto. Hey, that's my mother.
You can't talk that way
about somebody's mother.
If I knew you a week less,
I'd have to hit you.
You brought her up. Yeah, we're
just trying to be supportive
like good friends are supposed to be.
Oh, thank you.
By the way, just let me hold the tickets.
I'm not comfortable with this setup.
I don't know. You two never
give me any responsibility.
Two words...
Labor Day party.
That was 14 years ago.
We suffered the whole day. Oh!
All right, I tell you what.
We'll go Switzerland.
What?
Switzerland, neutral spot.
Put them in the glove compartment.
We'll sort it out later.
Okay. So, we have
an understanding.
I get a say in who
ultimately gets to use these.
Agreed?
Oh, oh! Turn this up.
Dire Straits. Awesome.
Man, back in the day
these guys were the kings.
Hundred million albums,
you heard them everywhere.
You turn on the radio now, it's
all boy bands and Britney.
I'd throw one in her.
Nice of you. The point is,
they went from the top,
the very top, to nowhere or...
I don't know, back to some
castle in England.
They're not clipping
any coupons.
Yeah, or carrying
their own luggage.
Except for the bags
that are filled with cash.
I guess their time has passed.
It's scrudge. Skip it.
Wait a second.
- Turn it down. Scrudge.
- Scrunge?
No. Scrudge.
That song is not scrudge.
It's a change of mood.
The funkiest of scrudge.
What is scrudge?
Scrudge, a song
that follows a great song.
Doomed from the first time
you hear it on the CD.
We're talking about Dire Straits here.
They're incapable of scrudge.
Dead in the recording studio.
You see, every group knows immediately
when they got a great song.
And they don't want to burn a perfectly
decent one by putting it after that.
So they pick a shit
song for that slot.
You know, to fall on the
grenade, take one for the team.
A scrudge song.
Give me an example.
Okay. Do you remember the song
that followed, uh...  Freebird?
Um, no.
Exactly.
Brown Sugar? I don't know.
Born to Run?
Hey, back off Bruce.
Oh, so you can cap Knopfler
but Springsteen's off-limits?
Good Christ, She's the One.
Talk about scrudge.
- Stairway?
- Uh...
Where the Streets Have No Name?
Bullet the Blue Sky
is not scrudge. It's sonic.
Any reasonable debate, by
definition, means non-scrudge.
Flip it back to three.
Sing it, Jase!
I could do this all night!
Watch out! Jesus!
Oh! Watch the road!
I was out like a light.
Who farted?
My bad.
Oh, God, that's vile.
Grab it. The map!
It's a long way down.
Man, that would have hurt.
Watch where you're going.
Can't help it. It's the open road.
It gets me all fired up.
Always has.
Hey, you smoking now? Yep.
I never went on a road
trip with my parents.
Never.
We went to the Poconos, and my Aunt
Mickey's house in Long Island. Lindenhurst.
You missed out.
We went all the time.
From sea to shining sea.
Hey, your old man was a
road warrior, huh? Nah.
He just wanted to get there.
He wasn't a stop-and-smell-the-roses
kind of a guy.
I mean, me and Ma, we'd be
looking at something amazing and
he'd just be standing there, smoking
a heater, facing the highway.
And he'd click his fingers, "Let's
go." And we'd be on our way.
Man, they don't make
them like that anymore.
Billy, I'm bagged.
You take them.
I'm still shotgun,
right, Crime Dog?
But I handle the music.
Okay, fair enough.
(DRIVING WITH THE BRAKES ON.
Guess who?
Christ.
What am I doing?
Quality time, bro.
Beats a shrink.
No, not this.
I just always thought having
a kid would grow me up.
Instead, it's a bill, due
every day, every minute.
At least you got one.
I'm not griping.
I just thought it would
make a man out of me.
My dad always seemed like a man
and he had me when he was a kid.
Hey, want to order
some room service?
Room service?
What, in a dump like this?
Here we go, Chinese.
Alligators, cool.
Let's see. What goes
good with 42 beers?
Okay, wait. Let's get something
straight here, fellas.
I definitely get one
of these beds.
How do you figure? It was my
Championship Bowl tickets
that started this whole trip, so
eventually the perks have to kick in.
Nice try there, Billy.
But my chariot got us here, which
means bed number B comes my way.
Not from this angle.
Then you leave me no choice.
SmackDown. Oh, yeah.
WWF, this is going to be good.
You too, liver lips,
on your feet.
Both beds will be earned
out here on the mat.
Oh!
My balls! That's dirty, Mark.
What can I tell you?
Next battle.
Fine, let's go.
I give up!
You want it that bad,
you can have it.
Just like that, huh?
Just like that.
I'm tired and I don't care.
To the victor come his spoils.
Ugh!
Aw, it figures, I get
Heidi Fleiss' cot.
This is gross.
I guess you get
what you pay for.
See, never bet
against the Crime Dog.
Hey, guys, I'm
glad we're doing this.
Me too.
Ever notice if you scratch halfway
between your balls and your asshole
it smells like pussy?
No, it doesn't.
Get a little
closer to your bung.
Hmm?
I just wanted to say goodnight.
You guys are sick.
Excuse me, miss.
Yeah.
I ordered sunny-side up.
These are over easy.
Okay, I'll get them
to redo them.
Why do they always
foul up my order?
'Cause you always ask for
side orders and confuse them.
Why not just make it easy?
Order number three.
I don't like the way
everything gets hash browns.
Hash browns are a filler. I want eggs
and meat, period. Like the Duke.
John Wayne? I happen to know
John Wayne hated hash browns.
You're out of your mind.
When am I gonna learn?
Stick with the cereal.
You get your own little self-contained meal.
Nobody has had their mitts on it.
Special K, Frosted Flakes.
It's impossible to screw up.
I asked for dry.
Hey, Miss Allison, how are you?
Sher, sure hope you get
this message.
We're just down here in South Carolina,
making our way to the Championship Bowl.
I was thinking about you. We
stopped and got something to eat.
How's, uh...
How's Hayden doing?
God almighty,
I miss him so much.
Hey, Sher, I gotta tell you. I didn't like the
way that you decided to throw him in the,
in the car and split.
I know I screwed up and all.
But you can't just take
somebody's kid like that.
You're not perfect either,
for the record.
I mean, how many times did you come visit
my father when he was in the hospital?
The man's sick and you
can't pop in and see him once?
When your mother was sick I was like a
frickin' delivery service three times a week.
Just put the shoe on the other foot.
That's all I'm saying, you know.
It's a two-way street
and I know, I know...
Your, like, 11 hours
of labor and diapers
and I'm under a lot
of pressure too, okay?
I mean, you find a way to pay
the freight for three people,
start a college fund and somehow figure
out how to stay ahead of the various...
Bills, you may have.
So I frickin' gambled. So what?
I made a few picks. They didn't come in.
Nobody's perfect.
All I can tell you is
that I never quit on you.
I never quit on you,
you selfish...
I'm sorry. This is my mess.
Sorry, Sherry.
How's the wife?
Line was busy.
Awfully long busy signal.
Who are you, the time keeper?
I said the line was busy.
Just a concerned citizen.
Hey, Mark, want to get some fireworks for
old time's sake? It's legal in the South.
It's legal all the way up
the Delaware Water Gap.
You shouldn't know that. You
can get whatever you want
the minute you leave Jersey.
Sparklers, the mortars, floral shells,
reloadable black powder
rockets.
Anything you want.
I'm worried about you.
Look, Vanna White.
Vanna. I used to love her.
Me too. She's a babe.
I wonder if she ever
did that Chuck Woolery.
She did Chuck Woolery's  Love Connection.
Think she did?
No, might have taken
a run at Bob Barker though.
Down at the commissary. He's
been known to tap the help.
If the price was right.
Okay, quick quiz.
Dead or alive, Monty Hall?
Dead. Alive.
He's alive.
- Gene Rayburn?
- Dead.
Richard Dawson? Who?
The Hogan's Hero guy.
Or Family Feud.
The fat dude? Nah. You're
thinking Louie Anderson.
Dawson was the original.
Dead or alive?
He's gotta be dust or he'd still
be doing the show, right?
Look at us.
We're officially white trash.
Yeah, pretty much.
A Vanna museum.
My mother always said I'd
make it to the White House.
You know Vanna was on a soap for
like two months?  Edge of Night.
Some folks said she had a
shot as a serious actress.
Then she got the Wheel.
Add that to the list of
useless information.
How many people do you know have the first
100 episodes of Wheel of Fortune on VHS?
Might want to keep that
autobiographical tidbit to yourself.
I want to get them
transferred to DVD.
I just don't like the loss
of quality in the digitizing.
Billy, what are you doing?
Sniffing Vanna White's bush.
16, 17...
Is that 21? Yep,
21 rocket salute.
22, Vanna White.
To the greatest
letter turner of all time.
To the only letter
turner of all time.
Which makes her the greatest.
Oh, no.
What do we do?
I'm pretty sure we just
lit Vanna's house on fire.
Oh, shit!
Come on, guys. We gotta do something.
We gotta put it out.
This is a piece
of history here.
Cheers, Billy.
How could Vanna
not have a hose?
That wood's dry.
Yep.
Get a blanket. Check the Fury.
Get something.
I'd like to buy a vowel
and solve the puzzle.
You may.
"Smoldering rubble."
Remember when Vanna stopped
actually turning the letters?
She did? Yeah. Now she just touches them.
Special effect.
Out of the blue,
she just went electric.
Like Dylan. Way worse. I'm
dead-ended right there.
Uh-oh. Fire guys are rolling.
Okay, Medal of Honor
or Super Bowl MVP?
Medal of Honor.
Nobody is shooting at you
in the stadium. Fact.
Ooh, 3 o'clock.
Nice.
Anybody want a taco?
So the doctor says, "If this
is my rectal thermometer,
"what the hell did I do
with my pen?"
Is that funny?
I think it would be.
Yeah, definitely.
It would be if what?
If we weren't shroomed out of our tits.
Uh-huh, yes.
Absolutely.
Mushrooms?
It's a hallucinogenic.
I know what it is. Where
are you guys from?
Nashville.
Cool.
¶ Give me a job
Give me security
¶ Give me a chance to survive
¶ I'm just a poor soul
in the unemployment line
¶ I swear I'm barely alive
¶ My mother and father,
wife and my friends
¶ I've seen them
laugh in my face
¶ But I got the power
and I got the will
¶ I'm not a charity case
¶ I tell you long nights
¶ Impossible odds
¶ Keeping my eye
on the keyhole.
We have to go. Now.
¶ Well I'm gonna be
a blue collar man ¶
You shouldn't do that.
Ever.
Come on. Let's get going.
Now that's funny.
You're pathetic.
Nice ho tag.
What?
Ho tag?
Let me guess.
That tattoo is to remind your boyfriend
that your ass is not your face.
Jerk.
- Skank.
- Come on.
Geez.
And here I thought
Styx was bulletproof.
That was Styx? Oh.
I'm gonna take a leak.
Why don't we leave that
in the trunk for a while?
In the trunk? Yeah, you
can give it a rest.
I'll ride in the trunk
before that happens.
This baby is a work of art, worth at least 7 grand.
No way she's sleeping in the dark.
I'm not kidding. He just came up
from the field house and he says
half the basketball team just got
suspended by the NCAA. No way.
They got free clothes
from a store.
Some big booster was hooking them up
with all this swag, totally illegal.
They gonna miss
the game tonight?
Four starters and the Russian.
They're gonna get smoked.
Virginia is like
a 22-point underdog.
I bet you they'll cover the
spread tonight. No doubt.
This is the surest thing
in the history of sure things.
If you could just let me put
down $1,000 on Virginia, I'll...
I hate you.
All right, I need you
guys to concentrate here.
Do you know anyone who lives in
or near Atlantic City or Vegas
with access to
large sums of cash?
Not that I can think of.
You cannot be serious.
I haven't been more serious in my life.
Think harder.
You'll be doing them a favor.
All they gotta do
is walk into the casino, put down a
bet for me and I'll give 'em 50%.
I don't know anybody.
80%.
We just don't know.
An Indian casino, Foxwoods. You must
know somebody who lives in Connecticut.
Mark, calm down.
This is my lock.
This is my bulletproof, no two ways
about it, once in a lifetime lock.
It's like I can see
tomorrow's sports pages today
and word is gonna get out, it's
gonna spread like wildfire
and then they're gonna take this thing
right off the board. Now think!
We don't know anyone who can bet.
I am going to miss this!
Get a hold...
Mark, get a hold of yourself.
Come on!
Here, medicine.
What it that? Mushrooms,
the redhead dropped them.
I walked right into a taco stand.
I can't believe it would...
I thought it would be on a train.
A metro-liner rolling down to DC
for a Redskins game when a senator
comes in and sits next to me and
tells me he's gonna have the Secret
Service shove the guy into a dumpster.
Give me those. If I've gotta listen to
him, I've gotta be on the same planet.
Just don't let him
push you around.
Do you even know where
he's staying?
I got the seat locations
from Jason's mom.
Sure you want to do this?
Mom, he sounded terrible on the phone.
I need to go to him.
Here, Mommy, for luck.
I love you.
Can you see from back there?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Got chasers? A little bit.
You've done this before?
Not in a while.
I had a phase.
I tried most everything.
Gourmet reefer, crystal meth,
shrooms the odd Friday.
Crystal meth?
Nobody's paying much attention to me
so it's pretty easy to hide the buzz.
What if I just jumped?
Whoa, whoa.
Hey, don't screw around.
What would I be thinking when I hit?
You know, the last thing
going through my mind?
Your ass.
38 years old and I got squat.
You too, Billy.
Back there was
a stinking disaster.
You know, wasn't long ago
you were gigging clubs
and knocking chicks off
your dick with your guitar.
Ancient history, bro.
Dead and buried.
No, no. I used to love
watching you on stage.
You had the walk.
Then some Tuesday, you woke up a roll-over
pussy just taking shit from everybody.
Your wife, people at work.
Dog chases every car he sees.
First one he lets go...
It's not just me.
I mean, all three of us.
I don't know if it's bad
luck or age or laziness.
One day you realize you're
not going to be president.
You don't get it.
I mean no offense, fellas,
but I was gonna be president.
Or governor, CEO...
An astronaut.
I don't know. You know...
Somebody instead...
Mark, you got a kid.
Who collects a half million dollars if I
should happen to fall off this bridge.
Hey, that's crazy talk.
Yeah, well, I'm running out of illusions. And
I'm not going into the New Year a loser.
Wow, we got nothing
going for us.
We got beer left.
Hey, Billy.
You taking a pee or just
standing and touching yourself?
You know how it is,
once you break the seal.
Hey, where's the best place
you guys ever took a leak?
No such thing as a bad
leak as far as I'm concerned.
Agreed.
Grand Canyon.
Really?
Yep. Right over the friggin' edge.
A gust of wind,
I would have fallen a quarter-mile
and pancaked a pack mule.
I took a leak between
subway cars.
Elevated 7 train, rolling through
Queens on the way to Shea Stadium.
Fourth of July, doubleheader.
Nice.
You? Nancy Golotta's back.
Her back? I didn't want to.
She asked me.
She's dirty. Ya think?
You could've said no. Hold it.
You had sex with Nancy Golotta?
You demon!
The last girl I was with before my wife.
My wife...
Ha! Who's coming off?
Look at those stars!
Drink that on the horizon.
Twinkle, twinkle, Twinkie.
The trees in front of you
are 30 feet high, genius.
You can't see the horizon.
Come on, what's taking you...
Good Lord!
I'm blocked! What should I do?
Okay, I know what
to do. I know what to do.
Hold your balls, fetal
position. Play dead.
Play dead? No, that's bears!
Run, dumbass.
Come on, come on, come on!
- Easy...
- Cover my balls...
Whoa, hey, pull over.
How you feeling? We found a
carnival on shrooms, you tell me.
Hey.
Step off of that thing,
young man.
If you break that, somebody's
gonna have to fix it. Sorry.
No harm done,
just can't add work
when there's plenty
to do already.
I knew these things were rigged.
You can call me Melville.
Bill McGriff, Chalfont, PA.
Hour west of Philly,
I know it well.
Worked the northern circuit with
the Clyde Beatty outfit for years.
Hey, wait.
That's the circus, right?
The real circus, where you
smell the elephant dung.
Not like that tutti-frutti
French affair.
Cirque du Soleil?
Yeah, that'd be the one.
I'm Jason, and I love the circus.
Yeah, me too, Jason.
Till they forced me out.
Come on, boys,
have a drink with me.
Come on, guys.
Right behind you.
They forced you out?
Yes, they did.
Big cats.
Must've hurt.
A lion and a tiger
have a fight. Who wins?
Give you a hint. A female lion looks
enough like a female tiger that
the horny striped male thinks
he might take a shot at her.
King of the jungle doesn't like
the competition. Fight's on.
So the lion wins. He's got right on his side.
You see, a tiger
stands on three paws.
Swings with his fourth.
Lion gets up on his haunches,
fires back, two-hand volley.
Outgunned, tiger flips onto his back,
tries to fight up from the bottom.
Fatal mistake.
Is that what happened to you?
You got between
a lion and a tiger?
Nah, I rolled my pickup
shitfaced outside of Albany.
Can't drive a stick no more,
but I get by all right.
Hey, fella. St. Nicholas,
where you been?
Got some lungs on him. Yeah,
well he's got a lot to say.
St. Nicholas...
Like Santa Claus?
Come here, buddy. Hey.
Yeah, he brings me presents all year. Birds, mice...
Deader than yesterday.
A gift's a gift.
Pennyfeathers. I figure you
Pennsylvania boys are heading south.
- Florida, hmm?
- That's right.
Best damn bar in the state.
Pennyfeathers?
What you seek,
you may find there.
One arm, lives in
a dirty old trailer...
Didn't seem to bother him much.
Big talk, little cat, creepy bastard.
Deluded.
- Senile.
- We won!
We won, we won!
I don't believe it!
We're rich! Whoo! We won, we won!
I gotta tell 'em.
Jason, Jason, what...
Tell who? Come on.
We won! Did you take my
sports section, chief?
The answer to all our prayers.
Hand me the toilet roll,
will ya?
Oh, sure, Elmo.
You need to wipe up? Here.
Wipe up, Elmo. Use that.
Oh, that's stinky, Elmo.
Use this, that'll make you...
Get out of here!
What's the matter
with you, huh?
What the hell are you doing? Can
you say, "Mega Mad Millions"?
Can you say $26 million?
Million, as in
ma, ma, ma, million!
0, 6, 10, 11, 25, 56, 57.
God damn, he's right.
It's a match!
We won!
We won! We won!
We won! We won! We won!
I can't believe it.
Wait a minute.
There's a problem.
See, we split equal shares.
No problems at all!
Last week's newspaper.
Never thought my last
meal would be a corn dog.
I wonder if you can actually hear
your back snap when you hit.
Hey, I got an idea.
What if only you guys jump.
I tried to save you.
You know, I go back home,
say great things about you,
work your legacy.
You exist forever,
like dead heroes.
Heroes who offed themselves?
Oh, I know, I could write a
ballad about you guys. No.
Now you can jump last,
but then, of course,
you'll be bridge scrudge.
No way. We go, we go together.
All right then.
One.
Two.
Three.
Last time I was happy. Well, Mom
and Dad, I guess this is it.
I had a dog once. Wouldn't
poop till I looked away.
We had a picture of my wife
and my kid in the car.
It's going with me.
I just wanna say,
if we're gonna do this...
You're my best friend... Pal.
Thanks, buddy. That means a lot.
Ah, you don't give a fuck.
No sense going alone.
Here, I brought your wife too.
Speak up, dear. Ahhh!
Sweet Jesus, we killed him.
Help me, you idiots!
Come on, grab my wrists!
We got you!
I got you, I got you.
- Oh, my back!
- My balls!
Swim!
So much for that buzz.
Oh, shit.
A midget couldn't kill
himself off of that bridge.
Isn't this the part where the
hillbilly bangs me in the ass?
Oh, you guys wear me out.
You know what? I don't wanna be dead.
No way.
Me neither.
What if you could...
What if you could be dead
and not be dead?
Dead and... Huh?
Yeah.
No responsibilities.
No obligations.
And no debt.
You just get a fresh start.
Uh, I wanna get an order
of wings, to go, please.
Sure, hon, what size?
Medium bucket. I'd like
a big bucket, myself.
But I'm gonna make an
exception in your case.
That's a sweet little turd cutter
you got there. First-rate.
How would you like 'em?
Hot, baby, real hot.
Buddy...
Uh, not the spiciest, but you know...
Good. Be right back.
They got great wings here, huh?
Best goddamn wings
in the world.
Any place else,
I won't eat 'em.
They make 'em with
too much lard, no butter.
Makes me crap like I got a can
of snakes coming out of my ass.
That's good to know.
You like that? I'm not a
swordfish no sauce guy.
If it's on the menu,
I'm eatin' it.
That so? You bet
your ass, tough guy.
Mark? Yeah.
If I get married,
I want you to be my best man.
Sure, just let me know when
you meet somebody.
No, seriously.
Yeah, I know it's
not a time to bring it up, but
I've been thinking about it.
And I consider you to be
my best friend.
All right, buddy. I'm honored.
Ah, you don't give a fuck.
Anything else?
No, that's it. How about
a kiss for old Daddy-o?
No touching!
Mmm, still got
that new car smell.
You ought to be careful.
Sometimes they have boyfriends.
You're liable to get
yourself popped.
What the hell do
you know about it?
What? You heard me.
Look, there's two kinds of
guys in the world, right?
I mean, look at you. You've never
been in a scrap in your whole life,
have you? Am I right?
It's not a big deal. I mean,
a lot of guys missed it.
It starts in kindergarten.
You pretend that the bully didn't knock you down.
Then, in grade school, you pretend
they didn't take your lunch
money away from you.
You're always
duckin' and dodgin'.
You get to high school, you pretend you
didn't hear the teasing and the catcalls.
And all the time, you're
running from the danger.
You skip enough chances, before
you know it, you're 30, 35,
and you've never
been in a beef.
I guess you know everything.
Nah,
just a guy who's lookin' for
answers in a bottle.
Nope, not in that one.
So let me get this straight, you fake your
demise, your wife and kids get the money,
and you slip the bookie.
And the 27 G's I owe him.
And then what happens, you go into
the Loser Protection Program?
Give me the chum.
It's where you
were pissin', right?
Hey, hold on. Don't you think this is a little rash?
I mean, sure, you got problems,
big ones, but who doesn't? Sure
wish I'd paid more attention to
the Discovery Channel. I'd know
what these lizards like to eat.
Odds are it's not Hooters.
They're like sharks, they're opportunistic.
They'll eat whatever they can get.
Except chicken
wings, apparently.
The Discovery Channel
is awesome.
I remember watchin'
this one about panda bears.
Apparently panda bears have very low
libidos, so these poor Japanese bastards...
- Chinese.
- Huh?
Pandas are in China.
Chinese, Japanese, Charlie is Charlie.
The point is,
is that they spend all day showing 'em
movies of other pandas getting busy.
Panda porn.
Panda porn? That's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard of.
Till this.
So where you gonna go?
I dunno. Exile.
Where's that? In Mexico?
What about us? Are we ever
gonna see each other again?
Guess not.
Ever?
I don't see how.
Well that settles it.
We go, we go together.
- To exile.
- Exile.
All right, gentlemen,
we are officially in business.
Okay, here's the play.
I wind it up to 120 rpms.
Kick it back down into second,
lock her up in the gravel.
She stops in a power slide
10 feet shy of the swamp.
We push her in from there.
That's pretty fast.
We gotta make it look
like an accident, right?
You sure you can stop in time?
It's a Fury.
I can stop this baby on a dime.
I'm thinking we should
salvage some things.
Definitely get some cash
for these rims.
Sure, maybe there's
a swap meet Saturday.
This is the South, man.
Rims are like currency down here. They pass
'em down from generation to generation,
like heirlooms.
Mark... We should
yank the stereo too.
It's no Sanyo box, Blaupunkt.
Like Mercedes.
German gear keeps its value.
Wait a second.
For this to work,
the car has to go in as-is,
end of discussion.
Fine, I lose my car,
guitar gets wet too.
Leave her out of it. No way,
if Fury goes, guitar goes.
Why, 'cause you're a bad loser?
Well now, you show me a good loser,
and I'll show you a loser, loser.
It is only fair, we are supposed to be dead.
Think of the forensics.
Fine, she goes.
That's it?
- Good for you.
- Way to stick up for yourself.
Save some for the reptiles...
Please.
You know, I'm thinkin'? I should do it.
Do what?
I'm a professional driver. I drive for a living.
Give me the keys.
No way. There's only one
Joe who flies this bird.
Whoa.
Mark?
Where the hell is he?
He's gone.
Mark?
In the water!
Mark!
Did you see that power roll?
Off the hook.
All right, guys, if you don't mind,
we're in Wally Gator's swimming pool.
You see any?
You gotta look for their eyes.
I don't see any.
There!
He's got the chicken wings!
One, two, three.
Your sister's ass. What?
Tell me you got those tickets
out of the glove box.
Oh. There's two words...
Labor Day party. Sorry,
guys, I didn't think.
Damn right you didn't think.
I don't get it.
How do you manage to screw
up so many times in one day?
I get up early.
You know what this means?
Somebody's gotta go in.
I'll do it.
Pretty ballsy, huh?
Did you see that? Oh, no.
Hey, this is bad.
Wow!
Oh, man!
(LOOKING OUT THE WINDOW.
Just a few minutes to go, and Times
Square is coming to a boil...
I know what we need.
How about it? To, uh...
The afterlife.
The afterlife, that's good.
You know they say the way you
spend your New Year's Eve
is the way your
whole year's gonna go.
Really? Is that what
they say? Because I...
I feel great. Honest to God, I'm feeling
liberated, I'm feeling renewed.
Like Butch and Sundance. Butch and Sundance?
Didn't they get shot?
Yeah, but with their boots on. Come
on, let's go, I'm thirsty. Today.
It's stuck. Give me this.
Hey!
I wanna propose a toast.
New leaf, we got a clean slate.
I say we take advantage of it and
start living like philosophers.
No more mincin' words or dancin' around.
You see a thing, you name a thing.
What the hell are you
talking about?
Yeah, I'm gonna live
more true. More honest.
New me's gonna be a straight shooter.
Oh, okay then. Me too.
Straight shooter. Me too! You
gotta stop being a parrot, man.
You're always doin' that. You can't do that.
You just... You chime in,
you just agree with everybody right away.
All right, that's fair...
That's what I'm talking about.
Polly want a cracker?
Okay, now remember when you point that
finger, you got four pointed back at you.
Take Billy here,
he's the perfect example.
He backs down to everybody. He's got
more footprints on him than a treadmill.
All right, just give me some
bubbles. No therapy, please.
No therapy, just the truth.
You tell me right now. What is it gonna take
for you to finally stand up for yourself?
Thank you for that insightful
counsel, Dr. Freud.
Now what's it gonna take for you
to shut your know-it-all yap and
let me enjoy this outstanding beverage?
Pucker up and blow me.
I knew I should have killed myself alone.
Okay, guys, why don't we...
Wind it down a little bit, get some sleep.
We got a big game tomorrow.
Hey, Billy. Think that douche in the shitter
was the only one nailing your wife?
Okay, Captain Honest, you got something to say?
Finish the thought.
Let's just say there were other
passengers on that flight.
Fuck you. What are you saying?
You banged my wife?
Guys, why don't we just...
Shut up.
Did you bang my wife?
Tell me you're lying.
Or what, Billy?
Are you going to hit me? Tell me
you're lying, or tell me good-bye.
This is so wrong.
What the hell did you do...
All the women you could
get, why the hell...
Relax, I never
touched his wife.
Then why did you...
He's pathetic.
I'm trying to get him to stand up for himself.
I'm trying to help him.
You're a mess. Help yourself.
Oh, look, Dweezil, give me a break...
Yeah, I'm a clerk.
Sells whiteout
and envelopes, okay.
I can't get a girl, my mother's a bitch.
You got me, dead to rights.
And now that that's cleared up, why don't
you have a quick look at yourself.
You're the coolest guy
I ever met, hands down.
Could dunk a basketball flat-footed,
could talk a girl down to her Jockeys.
Make anybody think
his jokes are funny.
The man everybody wanted to be.
With all of that, you throw
your money away gambling,
you let your family slip through
your fingers, and now...
You run off the two best
friends you've ever had.
I'd ask why,
but then I'm kinda past caring.
Happy New Year.
(CHEATERS & NON-BELIEVERS.
Two sugars, no NutraSweet,
and that's the way
it's gonna be.
Hey!
Oops.
You stupid, little son of a bitch.
Sorry, sir.
Now get down here
and clean this up!
Hey, get down here
Whoo!
What are you doing, huh?
Good catch, buddy.
Ready? Down one, hike!
Kid's got hands.
And he's got heart.
Loves the game. Who's
he rootin' for tonight?
Ah, we don't have tickets. He just
loves to soak up the atmosphere.
Says he's gonna play
in this stadium someday.
I hope he gets to.
Yo, who's got tickets? I
need some tickets over here.
Who's selling? Who's selling?
Yo, need two!
Who's got two?
Oh, my God.
I'll give you $500 a piece,
right now.
$1,500, you gotta make a move.
Why don't you paint that thing?
It's earth tone, one of a kind.
Well, you better wear a
helmet, they'll write you.
I got a hard head.
We can't afford these.
Sure you can, they're on me.
Just leave me one when he comes
back and suits up some day.
Hey,
what's your name?
For the tickets someday.
Did you see that?
Nothing but cork.
Two triples and a bull.
This girl is unbelievable.
Talk to her.
Classic Tudor with a high finish.
You do that beautifully.
I like to think that it's Creole, tutored
by way of Lake Charles, Louisiana.
Hi, I'm Jason.
Janice.
May I have the honor
of a match?
I yield the lane to the challenger.
Hmm.
I accept the courtesy.
Tungsten Devastators with the
spinning Hammer Head flights.
Sweet!
They're not for everyone.
I could do some
damage with these.
Nice balance.
The R-182 shafts.
I'm thirsty.
Want a cold one?
Getting me a beer?
Can't find your seat? I'm looking for my
husband, he's supposed to be right here
in these seats.
Is his name Mark?
And now, America,
Miss Vanna White!
¶ Oh, say can you see
¶ By the dawn's
early light... ¶
The spectacular wreckage
of an ancient Plymouth Fury
was pulled from the swamp on
Country Road 61, near Beecham...
No sign of survivors...
I knew those guys.
Best friends I ever had.
Cold ones.
I'll take a beer.
Keep it.
Thanks.
Big cats. Melville.
Hey, more guitar. Up.
One, two, three!
One triple away.
Well struck, grasshopper.
Oh, well I've spent much time snatching
the pebble from the serpent's maw.
Hey, look at that guy over there. He's got
a hearing aid the size of a lawn mower
stuck to his head.
And he has it on high.
Oh, shit.
You again.
You know what it cost me
to detail that car?
It was an accident.
Uh-huh.
It looks like we're up next.
Well, uh...
Please go ahead, because
we were just messing around.
You can have it.
We want a match with you.
We accept. What do you
want to play for?
How about $10 cricket?
Cricket?
Do I look like I want to spend time with you?
All I want to do is take your money.
First bull's-eye, 50 bucks.
Okay, I'll lead off.
I'll call you when I need you.
Hey.
I got a score to settle with your
little comedian friend here.
I wanna see him shoot. Yeah,
shit or get off the pot.
Bet you 100 bucks he can hit
a dime on my forehead.
Are you nuts?
I've seen you shoot. It's like
throwing a rock in the ocean.
I'll take that bet. Oh, no, uh...
We're not doing this.
What's the matter,
chuckles? Chicken?
Pedro, where's the ice?
Jason...
I trust you.
Move.
No cheating. I don't need
to cheat, you clowns.
Lock and fire on it.
Good shot.
Pay the man his hundy.
Two out of three.
That's funny.
You know, there's three ways
that I can tell a jerkoff.
One, was O.J. guilty?
Two, Coke or Pepsi?
And I forgot the third one.
Bull's-eye.
- That went well.
- Leave him alone!
Zip it.
Okay, come on if you're comin'.
There's five of us
and one of you.
Two...
Of us. And I don't
like your chances.
We're gonna kill you guys.
Too late, we've already
been dead 11 hours.
Welcome back to the male species.
Nice to have you back.
What are you talking about? You think
I'm doing this because of you?
Fight!
Come on, bring it. Come, on.
Yeah? Billy!
Huh?
Hit him! Billy, hit him!
Go!
Come on...
Let go! Bastards!
Wow, I think it kicks ass.
Headin' out tonight.
As fast as you can.
Don't start with me.
Far be it for me...
You never stop, do you? Okay, come on, guys.
Enough already.
Come on, Billy, we got the motel room
for one more night. Let's just...
Go out on a good note. No.
I'm gonna get rolling north.
Back home.
All right.
I'm gonna go for a nightcap.
You wanna come?
No, I'm done. I'll go home.
Okay.
Hey, I was wondering...
What's it gonna take, huh?
I'll show you what
it's gonna take.
Mark! Hey, Mark! Me!
Congratulations, you win.
You're making me do something I thought
I'd never do, raise my hand to a friend!
Well, come on out! Dick!
You know not everybody has the same
definition about what it takes to make a man,
I mean, sometimes
it takes more guts to...
Maybe there'd be a little more
peace in the world if...
But not tonight.
You get your know-it-all, control freak,
make-your-friends-Mike-Tyson ass
out here now!
Let's do what we gotta do!
I am so sick and tired
of this macho bullshit!
Come on!
All right,
we'll do it in there.
He's testing every
time you give in. I know.
Try taking away a toy, and if
he doesn't stop, it's time out.
I know he's headstrong.
But you have to be firm.
Here you go, Jason.
I... I forgot the NutraSweet.
That's over.
I don't use it anymore.
Where's mine?
You were sleeping.
Weren't sleepin', I'd say.
It's like... It's like you took
a bullet that was meant for me.
I'm so sorry, Billy.
How's that?
Enough with the pillows.
Please.
I never touched Kate.
I would never do that.
But this is so wrong.
I'm in a whole 'nother
universe of wrong here.
And I gotta tell you, I gotta...
And you too, Jason...
I failed you guys
so completely.
I failed myself.
I have been a total
horse's ass, and
all you guys do is stick by me.
They used to think I was
so good under pressure.
And it turns out that I'm the
one who folds it every time.
Like a coward.
Never wanted anybody's help,
God forbid.
But I was wrong.
I need you.
I need you, Jason.
I need you to help me to stop
blaming everybody else for my...
Disappointments. And all I
can tell you is thank you.
Thank you for helping me
realize what's important.
Being one of you guys,
being a good husband to Sher.
And a good father to Hayden.
I am so sorry.
Hey.
Sherry, it's completely over.
I set up a payment schedule,
and it's done.
You two are
the center of my life.
Please give me a chance to prove
that I can change. Please.
You think she'll listen to me?
Yes, Daddy, I think she will.
Hey, get in here, you two.
Let's go.
Hey, Billy. Scarlet.
New bike, huh?
Yeah, makin' some changes.
Traded in 18 wheels for two.
Changes... Huh.
Got some miles on it.
Who doesn't?
Cold?
Take 'em.
What happened here?
It's a long story.
Get on.
I've got work.
Uh-uh. Your shift's over.
You mean it?
You bet I do.
(YOU CAN'T SEE THE STARS