Foxtrot 57 1 now entering third level.
- We've got one on the ground.
- OK.
You get her out, we'll take this guy.
One, two, three, lift!
Got it!
Steve, have you got it?
Yes.
Steve, you're dropping it!
l can't breathe!
l can't breathe! l can't breathe!
Hang on, Steve.
Hang on, l'm coming.
Take your mask off, Steve.
Take your mask off.
Just forget what it's for, Steve.
Come on!
You're dead! Yourteam's compromised.
Leave your casualties
and get your officers to the surface.
We need to speed things up.
Why is it taking so long?
The decontamination unit
was in the wrong place.
The suits are hard to work in. lt's taking longer
than anticipated to recoverthe casualties.
- How many casualties are you using?
- 60.
60? How many people work in these offices?
- Two orthree thousand.
- So it's not exactly realistic, then?
- lt's manageable, Minister.
- The press are waiting, Minister.
Thank you.
- l need some help here.
- We've got you, mate.
You'll be OK, mate.
That's it. Relax.
You'll be OK.
Let's get showered and out of these suits.
Turn around.
OK, good man.
Jenny, let's have a look at you.
Oh, shit.
- You're dead, too.
- What?
You've got a tear. Your suit's ripped.
Get out, Jenny.
These drills must send a positive message.
1,600 gas-tight suits, 7,000 modesty packs,
ten mobile mass decontamination units.
The Home Secretary
wants us to reassure the public.
Understood.
lt's always worth reminding Londoners
how resilient they are.
l'll put that in the report, will l?
- OK?
- This was supposed to be easy.
- l've got Steve on the way to A&E.
- Why?
Hyperventilation. We're meant
to wearthe suits for 20 minutes.
lt was 16 minutes before we got
into the car park, and Jen got a tear.
That's what this drill is for,
to iron out these problems.
Biscuits?
Minister, how do you respond
to accusations of scaremongering?
We live in difficult times
and must be prepared for every eventuality.
These drills will reassure the British people
that we are doing all we can
to protect them against terrorism,
and that London is as prepared
as it can be.
This is part of the government's commitment
to be honest about threats,
and to put as much information
in the public domain as we can.
An emergency services drill was held today
to test new anti-terrorism measures.
The new Minister for London,
Nicola Painswick, reassured Londoners
that the drill was not linked
to any specific threat.
West Yorkshire police confirmed
that three men were arrested yesterday
outside the US Air Force monitoring station
at Menwith Hill.
The men are being held
under the Anti-Terrorism Act.
Scotland Yard
declined to comment on whether...
lt's been a busy morning.
Two lrish nationals held at Dover.
A gun found in their car.
Officers are on their way.
US lntelligence have passed on six names
they want under surveillance.
The men arrested at Menwith Hill
have been confirmed as North African.
- Sir.
- Thank you.
The local police found notebooks
and video footage of the perimeter security.
We flagged up two addresses in London.
- What do we know?
- They could be GSPC.
Waiting for French and Algerian lntelligence
to get back. MOD want it low-key.
Fine. You're dealing with that one.
- lncident room is being set up.
- Good.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me. l'm looking for DS Drummer.
- Just overthere.
Thanks.
- DS Drummer? DC Habibullah.
- Great. l can give you five minutes.
Get up to speed on the briefing notes.
We assume the suspects are using false lDs.
They're North African, possibly Algerian.
They weren't acting alone,
so our job is to uncover cell members.
This is your desk here.
This is propaganda material, videos, letters,
recovered from a B&B in Leeds,
and the suspects' addresses in London.
Go through all that lot.
Most of it's in Arabic.
- What languages have you got?
- Urdu, Punjabi, Arabic.
Great. Normally,
l get stuck with a civilian translator.
l'll need you in interviews.
Help me understand what makes them tick.
- How would l know? l'm from Luton, Sarge.
- You're better qualified than l am, Detective.
- Mike, can l have a word?
- Yes. DC Habibullah, this is Dl Brook.
- Sir.
- Glad you're on board.
Get yourself settled.
l'm in A&E.
No, l'm fine. lt's Steve.
Can you pop down?
Hi.
Hello.
Thank you.
- How is he?
- He'll live.
The drill went well, then?
l'm finished in half an hour.
We could go home together.
Yeah.
Well, l'd better make sure
Steve gets back all right.
You know, if that had been for real,
two of my crew would be dead.
Deputy Assistant Commissioner lves,
you have stated that we must now expect
terrorists to use crude CBRN weapons
that could cause mass devastation to this city.
Could you explain what that means?
We're talking about such things
as a dirty bomb...
..which is low-grade radioactive material,
blown up by a conventional bomb.
Low-tech methods for contaminating
large numbers of people with deadly agents.
Thank you.
Minister, in a public statement,
you said, ''The government is committed
to being honest about threats,
''and putting information in the public domain.''
Yes, that is correct.
l have here a report from the Commons
Science and Technology Committee.
lt accuses the government
of being embedded in a culture of secrecy.
This seems to be
a direct contradiction to your statement.
The government rejects the criticism
that it is less open than it need be.
We have an active
public information campaign.
We've sent a booklet to every house...
Are you confident the information is adequate
to prepare the public for a terrorist attack?
Of course.
Obviously, there are times when disclosure
would not be in the public interest.
l'm sorry, but now l'm confused.
You're open and transparent,
except when it suits the government not to be.
Obviously, there has to be a balance
between truth and reassurance.
Are you saying it's acceptable
to lie to the public to reassure them?
What the public can be told,
and the need for secrecy...
Very interesting, but this report states,
''Lack of openness has resulted
in the public being ill-informed
''and insufficiently prepared for a chemical,
biological, or radiological attack.''
Deputy Assistant Commissioner,
as Head of the Anti-Terrorist Branch,
do you feel adequate measures
are in place to protect the public?
lmprovements have been made
across all emergency services,
but l'd warn against complacency.
A great deal of work needs to be done.
Thank you very much.
John.
That was public record.
And l'm not going on public record
to say we're fully prepared when we're not.
We've allocated ?330,000,000
on homeland security.
That's a huge commitment when the public
wants hospital beds.
What else do you expect us to do?
ln the States, they're spending 15 times
more per head. They don't think it's enough.
So all the work we're doing counts for nothing?
Don't confuse activity with achievement.
Out of 30,000 officers, the Met have 1,500
with protective suits and two days' training.
We'd struggle with a conventional attack.
- lf a CBRN weapon went off...
- lf it went off.
l've seen al-Qaeda's plans
forthese weapons.
We knew 90% of what the lRA
were up to and they got through.
With this lot, we're lucky if we know 20%.
lt's naive to hope it won't happen.
- How are you?
- Fine.
- OK, this is stamped, marked from lstanbul.
- Right.
- You all right?
- Something l ate.
Yeah? You want to leave that goulash alone.
Cheers. Got the other one?
The little one. That's it.
Cheers.
Come in, Mr Rashid.
You know, this is a very popular area.
There's a post office close by.
Also, the tubes are five minutes away.
Buses, and there's a market on Saturday.
Show me the cellar.
- We'll need all this cleared.
- lt'll cost you.
How much?
70 quid.
We have accommodation forthe bride's family.
This isn't the lRA.
With this lot, we don't know
who or where they are.
We have no inside informants
and they don't give warnings.
First thing to understand about lslamist
terrorist groups, there's no single cell.
Don't write it down, remember it.
The logistics cell. These boys
will be embedded in the target country.
They're likely to be British nationals,
so they'll stay low-key.
They won't associate with known extremists.
They may not even attend mosque.
Found the house.
They raise cash through petty crime
like credit card fraud.
They provide passports, safe houses,
equipment, et cetera.
They gather all the elements
that make an operation possible.
The three North Africans at Menwith Hill
recently entered the country underfalse lDs.
- So they won't be part of logistics cells.
- Correct, they're checking out the base.
The sole purpose of a reconnaissance cell
is to gather intelligence on intended targets.
They're closer to the planning of an attack,
and far more likely to be foreign nationals.
Neither the logistics nor the reconnaissance
cell would be your suicide bombers.
The attack cell.
These boys will be battle-hardened veterans.
Jihad nutters who fought
in Chechnya, Bosnia, Kashmir.
Nutters, Sarge?
Fanatics. However you want to describe them.
Almost certain to be foreign nationals,
brought in at the last stages.
And as we know, in any attack,
there's likely to be more than one attack cell.
Our problem is, none of this lot
will know who the other cells are,
or have detailed knowledge
about the overall operation.
But...
they all have links...
to one man.
The agent isn't the mastermind.
That person will be thousands of miles away
in Pakistan or Afghanistan.
The agent is the manager.
He puts the cells together
and executes the plan.
He'll be white-collar, well-travelled, educated,
and have lived in the West for several years.
He'll have multiple identities
and impeccable cover.
He could be a doctor, a lawyer,
a university professor.
The point is, he'll be invisible,
and skilled at hiding his tracks.
So far, all we have are three suspects,
a possible reconnaissance cell.
lf we're to get the rest of them,
we chase every person they've ever been
in contact with, here or abroad.
Follow every papertrail.
Anything that strikes you, however small,
let me know.
You don't listen to me.
- We need fags.
- Yeah.
Could l get 20 JPS, please?
And a Sim card for my mobile
and a pay-as-you-go top-up card, please.
What?
Oh, piss off!
Let's go.
How are you settling in?
l'm still trying to find my way around, but fine.
You had a grilling at the Select Committee.
The Chair got hung up
on the issue of public information.
- May l?
- Of course.
lt's easy to present it in black-and-white
if you're not making the decisions.
Maybe we're not doing enough
to train and prepare the public.
lf a CBRN attack happens,
we could end up with mass panic.
l've been in Whitehall 25 years.
There have been 80 terrorist attacks
on the mainland.
Why assume the public
will run around like headless chickens?
We're talking suicide bombers.
No warnings,
biological weapons, dirty bombs.
lf you start issuing gas masks
to everyone using the tubes,
you risk causing panic.
Al-Qaeda want us scared. lf you fuel
public anxiety, you play into their hands.
- l understand.
- Think of the implications.
Business withdrawing,
the tourist industry hit.
Local authorities
are using Madrid to demand extra funds.
We don't want kneejerk reactions
from the public.
Don't you take the CBRN threat seriously?
l'm saying it's a difficult balance.
Overreaction can be as dangerous
as underreaction.
As Minister of London, it's your responsibility
to reassure the public and business.
Everything is being done to make London
as prepared as it possibly can be.
lt's an issue that's easy to get
worked up about from the back benches.
Neverthat simple when you're minister.
This is the last one, anyway.
We've already checked it.
Sorry.
Mogul Prince Takeaway.
Speaking.
Yeah.
Will you be there after midnight?
Bye.
The train now arriving at platform 4
is the 17..50, Paris, Gare du Nord.
Please ensure you
do not leave your baggage unattended...
- Why am l getting calls from Customs?
- What?
They want to know why one of my officers
is inquiring about D&L Shipping.
lt's a name l came across
in the suspects' notebooks.
- l ran it through NClS database.
- l told you to let me know.
Sorry, you're right.
Did Customs tell you what their interest is?
They believe Turkish mafia
are using D&L as a smuggling drop.
Shit, it would be Customs.
Any chance they'll let us look
at their phone records and manifests?
- They're not gonna rush to share information.
- lt's only paperwork.
You must know someone
that owes you a favour.
l'll talk to Brook. l've run out of favours.
Have you everything you need?
For now.
We need a large lead sheet to make a hatch.
Just a precaution.
Come upstairs,
l'll introduce you properly to your brothers.
- Got any plans tonight?
- Why, have we heard from Customs?
You must be joking.
Come on, you can leave that.
That's yours.
Check he hasn't spiked it.
So, Sameena,
if they're not nutters, what's it all about?
- You're being serious?
- We can talk about football, if you like.
Do you mean blowing themselves up,
fundamentalism, what?
lf yourfamily's killed in front of you
in Chechnya, it might cross your mind.
But why would a third-generation Bradford kid
join al-Qaeda?
lt doesn't matter
if you're from Bradford or Saudi.
lf you're a Muslim,
you're a part of a widerfamily.
What happens in Chechnya,
Kashmir or Palestine is happening to you.
lt's a long way from that
to strapping explosives to yourself.
Yeah, but what these boys see
makes them angry.
Extremist groups exploit that anger.
They recruit men all overthe world,
get them into camps and focus that anger.
lt's brainwashing.
They hand them a Kalashnikov,
convince them it's their holy duty
to die in the defence of lslam.
When they ask forfive martyrs,
hundreds step forward.
How do you feel about that?
Pissed off.
These fanatics are just a tiny minority,
and people think we're all like that.
l take my faith seriously.
l care about the world, but you don't see me
strapping explosives to myself, do you?
- So that's why you joined the police?
- No, l wasn't clever enough to be a doctor.
Sameena?
Phone records and manifests from D&L
Shipping, courtesy of ourfriends at Customs.
Good hunting.
- Sameena, see you in the morning.
- Yeah.
Even before the terrible events in Madrid,
London's emergency services were
being prepared for a majorterrorist attack.
Under our New Dimensions initiative,
London Fire Brigade have been equipped
with extended-life breathing apparatus.
They have over 1,600 gas-tight suits
and new radiation dosimeters in all engines.
Senior officers are receiving
state-of-the-art training in Texas.
There are ten mobile mass decontamination
units established right across the capital.
The success of the recent drill
is a clear demonstration of how capable
London's emergency services are
in dealing with incidents
of major contamination.
Who's been telling herthis?
Of course, we can't afford to be complacent.
But London is now better prepared
than it has ever been.
Thank you very much.
Minister, this is Commander Paul Hardwick.
He's one of our gold commanders
in charge of GT control room.
- Commander.
- Pleased to meet you, Minister.
Minister, were you at the same drill l was?
- Sorry, you are...
- Murray Corrigan.
Watch Commander, London Fire Service.
That drill was a farce, wasn't it?
Have you ever worn a GT suit?
You can't work in them.
They're unwieldy. You boil.
What you're asking us to do
with this equipment is unreal.
We've had a lot of problems with our kit.
Clive Phelps, London Ambulance Service.
Half our suits were defective.
We sent them back.
The decon showers blew the heads off.
l appreciate your concerns.
That's why we drill.
That wasn't a drill, it was a PR stunt.
Controlled conditions, cadets as casualties.
- We're constantly reviewing our plans.
- Your plans.
l have never been consulted,
never been invited to any strategy meetings.
l haven't even seen your new procedures.
You'll appreciate we have to limit access
to plans in the interests of national security.
What a fucking great excuse
for incompetence!
- l'm sorry, Minister.
- l understand. Change can be unsettling.
With respect, my officers trained as firemen.
Now they're the frontline in your war on terror.
They're putting their lives at risk
and none of us know if your plans work.
Excuse me.
- We have the barrels.
- Around the back.
- What did he say?
- Take it round the back.
l used to really look forward to going to work.
They're perfectly happy to spend
billions on lraq, Ml5, a sexy new British FBl.
You'd think they could spend
a bit more on us.
The rumour is that the first officers in
are expendable.
Maybe that's why
they don't want to waste their money.
lf you really believe that,
perhaps you should get out.
Whatever you decide to do, l'll support you.
- What happened?
- Well, what have you heard?
Murray Corrigan, report
to the Station Commander's office now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
l'm expecting a call any minute
demanding l put you on charges.
l'll be a watch commander down, right?
We've already lost two senior officers
this year.
Bollocks. l'm resigning anyway.
Mobilise, mobilise. Foxtrot 57 1, Foxtrot 572.
Road traffic accident at thejunction
of Commercial Road and Cannon Street.
Three calls to a Leeds address,
nothing logged, local are looking into it.
Seven calls to a Kentish Town address.
Flagged, NCS already investigating,
we're talking to them.
One call to an address in Neasden,
the Mogul Prince Takeaway, logged.
A Muslim neighbour called the anti-terrorist
hotline about two men living above the shop.
lt might be something.
ln her statement,
she describes them as fanatics.
- Do we know who they are?
- We're checking.
l could send an officer over
to talk to her, get more details.
You go. She'll find it easy talking to you.
Thanks.
- Did you get the number?
- No.
You said that they were moving barrels.
Anything else makes you suspicious?
You described them as fanatics
to the hotline.
- l don't trust them.
- Something in the way they behave?
What did they say?
You understand?
We're rare.
But they are proud.
Rashid Dhar and lmran Nazir.
Both registered at 66A Craven Lane.
Both claiming benefits, both British nationals.
Neither has a record, nor has been associated
with extremist groups, as far as we know.
Check with provincial forces, see
if there is anything else. Any travel detail?
Both have multiple entry visas
for Pakistan and Saudi.
That doesn't necessarily mean anything.
Family trips, pilgrimage to Mecca. Half my
relatives would be suspects based on that.
You're the one asking for surveillance.
There's other leads we could be chasing.
Yes or no?
My instinct is that
the woman is right about them.
Fine.
He's got the wheel in his ribs,
and l'm saying,
''There's no other way to get you out.''
- Was he all right?
- He'll be fine.
Anyway, there he is, trapped in his car.
His phone's ringing. He starts looking for it.
He answers it and it's his girlfriend.
She's in a restaurant waiting for him.
They're supposed to be having lunch.
And he says, ''Love, l'm trapped in the car
and l've got firemen chopping me out of it.''
She doesn't believe him,
goes off on one, so he hands it to me.
She's furious.
l've never heard anything like it.
- What, with him for being late?
- No, for crashing the car. lt's her car.
- Did she calm down?
- Eventually.
Anyway, l saved him. l saved his relationship.
- l killed the car.
- My hero!
So you're not resigning, then?
Well, what else would l do?
Decorate the kitchen, fix the guttering.
Look, l'm sorry l was so down.
lt's OK, l understand.
l work forthe National Health.
- Hi.
- Welcome, my pleasure.
l hope you're well
and l hope yourfamily is well.
l'm sorry, l don't understand.
- l want you gone by Monday.
- Why Monday?
You've done your job well.
Unknown leaving.
Repeat, unknown leaving.
Stay with original target.
This is where he wipes his cup.
l'd say this stranger is his superior.
You saw the way he behaved
when Dhar stood.
- We got any DNA?
- Forensics has the cup.
What are the chances
of an lD from the photo?
lt's with Five and Six. lt could take
up to 48 hours before you hear back.
What do we know?
We found a reference for D&L
in one of the North African's notebooks.
A phone call was logged from D&L
to Mogul Prince Takeaway.
Dhar and Nazir both work there.
An eyewitness saw them
unloading barrels at night.
Customs believe D&L is used
by a lot of foreign outfits.
Are we just looking at
petty crooks smuggling lDs?
They're devout and disciplined. We've
identified extremist literature on their shelves.
They covertheirtracks.
This suggests that they've been trained.
- Have we found the North African logistic cell?
- No, l don't think so.
Why not?
These boys are Pakistani.
They operate through different networks.
So we could've stumbled upon a logistics cell
for a completely separate operation?
- Yes, sir.
- Shit.
We'll have a better idea
when we know who he is.
lf the lion was to come suddenly and go, ''Grrr'',
do you think the camel orthe lion
would be more stronger?
There is deepening concern
about the rising violence in lraq.
Faced with continued unrest
and a hostage crisis...
..some of the militant Shiite forces.
These canisters all contain
radioactive material in powderform.
These smaller ones contain alpha sources.
This you can handle safely.
lt's only dangerous if you get it on your skin
or you inhale it.
Breathe it in.
You must wearthese masks
when you work with it.
These larger ones contain gamma radiation.
This is much more dangerous.
ln this concentration, as soon as that lid
is open, you've got 60 seconds.
Afterthat,
it's going to make you very, very sick.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
The operation shouldn't take
more than four minutes.
- Sorry to drag you in.
- How long is this going to take?
There's a chance that radioactive material
has been smuggled in.
A body was found in Bulgaria last Tuesday.
He's been identified as Usman Selcuk,
a Turkish shipping agent
and a suspected smuggler.
He'd had a fatal dose of gamma radiation.
At least 50 different shipments left this man's
depot in Sofia one week priorto his death.
Destined for 17 countries, the UK among them.
Why are we worried?
lt may be a logistics cell
with links to the Turkish cartel.
His body was discovered five days ago.
Why are we hearing this now?
Five didn't considerthe intel a priority.
- Oh, God.
- All right, thank you.
Get me Dl Lane and DS Drummer.
Did you put the lids back on?
- The lids. Are they on?
- No.
Close the hatch!
Five have identified the man who met with
Rashid Dhar as Ahmed lbraham Abassi.
A Jordanian management consultant
studying at London University,
living in the UKwith his wife and child.
He's also lived in Cairo, Hamburg and Paris.
Now, his credentials seem legitimate but
we know he accepted passports from Dhar,
and that he wiped his fingerprints.
Do we know where he is?
A previous address. We're trying to get
a current one from the college.
We do have another problem.
Surveillance on Dhar and Nazir say
they're packing, possibly destroying evidence.
Shall we pick them up?
l'd preferto keep watching.
l'm confident they're not an attack cell.
Let's see where they take us.
How serious is the radiation threat?
We've no evidence
that radioactive material's been smuggled in.
Has anything come up
on radiation detectors in ports?
No, but there's been no intel.
They check ten-20% of the cargo.
Even if the Turk
was smuggling a gamma source,
there's no link to him and Nazir and Dhar.
lt could've gone to any number of clients.
643 incidents
of radiation trafficking in the last six years.
They're the ones we know about.
And we've no intel suggesting
a dirty bomb threat to the UK.
You've gone back to Five and Six?
Are they certain about that?
We're trawling all intelligence noise
just in case they missed something.
l'm not happy that Dhar and Nazir are packing.
Turn theirflat over.
And D&L Shipping.
l'll square it with Customs later.
Take CBRN teams and pick up Abassi,
before tomorrow if possible.
lf we spook him and lose him,
that's the risk l'll have to take.
Armed police!
He's got a gun! Police! Get down!
- Look at the light!
- Stay on your back!
- Stay lying down.
Give us your name!
lmran Nazir, l'm arresting you
underthe Terrorism Act.
Rashid Dhar, l'm arresting you
on suspicion of terrorist...
Hold on. l want a chat first.
Bag these separately, OK?
No sign of those barrels anywhere.
That's funny,
cos we know you picked them up.
What was in the barrels, Rashid?
Where are they now?
We know you only started packing yesterday.
Why the hurry?
What did Abassi tell you to do?
What the fuck was that?
Mobilise, mobilise. Foxtrot 57 1, Foxtrot 572.
Major incident.
Large explosion,
vicinity of Liverpool Street station.
That's pump engine
and pump ladder to investigate.
Foxtrot 57 1 responding.
We've lost all our people.
- What just happened, Paul?
- A large explosion, Liverpool Street.
lt could be gas, plane down or a bomb.
Still trying to contact City Police.
Got a visual,
north end of Bishopsgate, on two.
..probable incendiary device.
can Confirm ground zero is Liverpool Street.
Repeat, ground zero is Liverpool...
Shit!
Has anyone checked for contamination?
Foxtrot 57 1 to Control.
Mobile to incident.
ETA approximately two minutes.
Repeat, ETA two minutes.
Over.
Stop the engine, Ralph.
Keep moving, keep moving.
This way, this way.
Get your BA sets on now.
Foxtrot 57 1 to Control.
Dosimeters alarming.
Repeat, dosimeters alarming.
Radiation suspected, reading 26 millisieverts.
Holding position, over.
Foxtrot 57 1 from Control, recalled. Recalled.
Foxtrot 57 1 to Control,
we have suspected mass casualties.
We have serious fire hazards.
We need all services at site ASAP.
We have a major incident.
Repeat, major incident.
Control to Foxtrot 57 1,
pull out of site. Radioactive.
Repeat, all units recalled immediately.
Repeat.. recall. RVfollowing.
Foxtrot 57 1, status two received.
Back up!
Keep moving, everyone. Follow the engine.
We're being recalled.
We've got to get out of here.
Fire Control report several units approaching
the site are recording high levels of radiation.
Reports are from entry routes
surrounding incident.
North Bishopsgate, London Wall, Houndsditch,
corner of Threadneedle and Bishopsgate.
Get that helicopter back. Get the bomb squad,
find out what we're dealing with.
lf it's radiation in this bomb, how bad is it?
l need dirty bomb plans on all terminals.
l need safe sites for a marshalling area.
No more emergency vehicles
are to enterthe site.
Personnel already committed
are contaminated.
They must withdraw and stay put
till we know where to set up decon.
..definitely contaminated.
We got high levels of radiation on site.
Any officers reach ground zero?
Tom, get me fire, ambulance, military liaison.
lnform Number 10. See how long
it'll take government liaison to get here.
- They want to know where to withdraw to.
- Tell them, 400...
No, 500 metres
and tell them to stay put until further notice.
All units, withdraw to 500 metres.
We need potential target locations cordoned.
lf it's suicide bombers,
we have to expect secondary devices.
Sergeant, any way l can look at CCTVfootage
of Liverpool Street before the incident?
Hang on. We can't play that back here.
l can patch you through
to the surveillance suite at Woods Street.
- Jo.
- l'm onto it.
lt's line one, Bomb lncident Room.
Sir, ambulance want to know
what to do with casualties.
Take them to hospital,
they take contamination with them.
lf it's life or death, it's the ambulance call
but they must liaise with A&Es.
What about casualties at ground zero?
- We'll deal with that later.
- Yeah, go ahead.
Move along, please, move along.
Move away from the area!
- What's going on?
- Move back, please, just get back.
- Where to?
- Just get back now. Please, move away.
That way, sir, that way.
Keep moving, please.
Please, keep moving.
All fire ground personnel
returning from incident
must go through decontamination
before entering marshalling area.
Yeah? All right. Thanks, Dave.
- Name.
- Murray Corrigan.
- Corrigan. Rank?
- Watch Commander.
- Dosimeter reading?
- 43.
- 43, you're clean.
- OK?
- Any of you guys got a mobile that works?
- No.
No?
Keep moving, keep moving.
Move! Move it along.
God, are you all right? Let me help.
- No way.
- You have to leave your car.
No, the other way. Keep moving.
No one here has been able to confirm
that the bomb is radioactive.
But it's obvious here that there is fear
of some form of contamination.
Behind me, police are moving people
back from the area as quickly as they can.
We don't know if this is merely a precaution,
or whether the blast was, in fact,
some kind of dirty bomb.
ls this you, you bastard?
We've not been able to get closer
than 400 yards to the site of the blast.
What's even more alarming is that
emergency vehicles are being held back.
- Hold the line. Sir?
- Yes?
Liverpool Street are holding trains
outside the station.
- They want to know where to disembark.
- Tell them to hold.
No one can leave the area
without decontamination.
Tom, what's the weekday population
of the Square Mile?
Over 300,000.
But if you include the surrounding
residential areas, closerto a million.
Get back to me on that as soon as you can.
You're sure?
This lady needs a hospital.
- To the front.
- Can you help?
- You can't stay here. Move back.
- l've got seriously injured people.
The instructions are,
leave casualties you can't move.
Tell them that. We're not going anywhere
till we get some medical assistance.
Prat.
Come on. Come on, keep moving.
l've got an image outside Liverpool Street.
Sir?
Tell me what you see.
lt's a white Transit van.
Two people in the cab.
Can't see the registration.
Whoa! Shit!
What?
They were in the van when it went up, sir.
- Checking to see if l can get the number...
- White van. Suicide bomber.
Check for other suspect vehicles. Under
no circumstances must an officer approach.
Sir.
OK, officers on the streets...
l need a patch to surveillance units covering
Canary Wharf, lsle of Dogs, Tower Bridge.
- Repeat, Canary Wharf...
- ..parked white vans...
Confirmed, two people in the van.
Number plate
X-ray 334, X-ray Bravo Romeo.
..Parliament Square, Oxford Street,
central London, Westminster Bridge.
- X-ray 334, X-ray Bravo Romeo. Confirm.
- Correct.
Put this plate through the ring of steel camera.
lt'll give us the driver's face.
l've got something else.
They swapped drivers.
There were three people in the van.
- They switched drivers inside the ring of steel.
- Original drivergot out in Bishopsgate.
We know this man.
l'm sending you a photo.
Ahmed lbraham Abassi.
- l'll need an all-ports, he'll be using false lD.
- Get on to DS Drummer.
You can go if you want.
Where is Abassi?
What's he planning?
What's the next target?
Sarge, fire and ambulance need to know
where to send mass decon units.
We've got to establish hot and cold zones first.
Just give me a moment.
How can we do this? We're getting wildly
different readings from all overthe place.
Alan, what does it say in the procedure?
Fragmentation.
lt's vital to make
fragmentation distance assessment,
to allow for microclimate differentiation.
- What the fuck does that mean?
- Where's the Science Officer?
- Struggling to get in.
- Get him on the radio.
Get the Met Office.
Which way's the wind blowing?
Sir, Fire are getting reports
of casualties still trapped at ground zero.
lndia 99 to Control. We now have
secondary fires in surrounding buildings.
Maintaining safe distance. Over.
All units must await further instructions.
No vehicles...
So what's the plan?
Why are we just standing here?
We're on hold.
We've got suits and breathing apparatus,
we should be in there.
We still don't know what we're dealing with.
We're losing the golden hour.
There are people alive
and we've abandoned them.
We don't do that.
We can't give you an estimate
on the casualties.
We have no officers on the ground.
We'll give confirmation as soon as...
l can't reach Liz.
All the networks are down, mate.
l'm sure she'll be fine.
Let me stress right now that for someone
who was not caught in the blast,
who was away
from the site of the blast itself,
such a person is at very little risk to health,
certainly in the immediate...
Sir, Science Officer says they're getting
both alpha and gamma radiation readings.
No one should be deployed
without CBRN protection.
Understood.
People should cover their faces
with whatever they can.
They should cover any cuts and abrasions.
Sir, St Luke's and Mile End hospitals are
being overwhelmed by self-presenters.
The crowd is contaminated.
Hospitals requesting police to hold them back.
Tell them they'll have to wait.
- Can we spare the men?
- The inner cordon's a kilometre diameter.
So the outer cordon will need 1,000 officers.
- How many have you got with suits?
- 500. Mostly TSG.
Military liaison say they can mobilise
200 troops within the hour.
That's a last resort.
No soldiers on a civilian cordon.
The most important thing
for anyone inside the hot zone
is to be decontaminated before trying
to go home to their families.
Otherwise they risk taking
a radioactive contamination back to...
Contaminated people are getting out.
Suits or not, we have to contain this.
Listen up.
l want manned barriers at 2,000 metres.
Filter everyone in that area
into decon cordons. Try to hold those lines.
No one to cross
until mass decon is set up. Understood?
Sir.
They're afraid they might have been
contaminated and they want help.
l'll be far more useful down there.
They need to see a government face
on the front line.
Staff here are insisting
they can only treat serious casualties.
They're refusing entry to the
many minor injuries caused by flying glass.
- Someone has to reassure them.
- There's a lack of clear information.
- The press are already at the cordons.
- ..is fuelling anger.
- Thank you, Jonathan.
- Great.
We're receiving reports
confirming that all emergency vehicles
have been withdrawn
from what they're calling ground zero.
Confirm, van at Telecom Tower
has two people in cab.
Numberplate for Canary Wharf van
not registered.
Dead end, sir.
Reports of a third suspect van
parked with driver.
Between Abbey Orchard Street
and St Peter's Street.
- Between Abbey Orchard Street...
- Back of the DTl, Westminster.
Back of the DTl, Westminster.
Coming on screen now.
OK, can you tilt down?
Further.
Can you zoom in further?
- ls that the best we can get?
- Another camera?
Mr lves, we need you to make a statement.
- Another angle?
- That's the best they've got, sir.
l want SO19 in place,
with riflemen where possible.
Keep watching them,
but no one is to approach those vans.
lf they are bombers, the slightest thing
spooks them and they'll detonate.
Sir.
- What else have they got planned?
- Ma'am.
How many devices are there?
- How many devices are there?
- Sarge, tenancy agreement.
46 Churchill Avenue, Willesden Green,
three months paid in advance.
What's there, Rashid?
Take Phillips and whoever's still here
from SO19.
Come with me.
..live to Scotland Yard,
where we're expecting a statement
from the Deputy Assistant Commissioner
John lves...
Phillips, come with me, and you.
A large bomb hidden in a van was detonated
at 8am outside Liverpool Street station.
The bomb might have dispersed
small amounts of radioactive contamination,
which is why
every necessary precaution is being taken.
ln the meantime, we need the public
to stay calm and stay put.
lf you're already in your home,
stay in your home.
lf you're in your office, remain there.
All Londoners not in the vicinity
of the incident
should go in, stay in, and tune in.
There is no significant risk,
but it is vital that you are decontaminated
before you go home.
Mass decontamination units
are being set up.
No, they said we should stay inside.
lt was on the radio.
Everybody, stay behind the line!
Sir, mass decon units
have been dispatched to the cordons
at London Wall, Commercial Road,
London Bridge, Old Street.
Priority routes are filtering everyone
in the zone to these points.
Tom, how long are we going
to have to hold people there?
We've got ten mass decon units in London,
more en route.
Assuming fire and water
can get them running in half an hour,
they're supposed to do 200 people an hour.
How many people are we talking about?
100,000, 200,000. l don't know
how many people are still in there.
- Ten, twelve hours minimum.
- We'd better organise food and drink.
You can't. They mustn't put their hands
neartheir mouths.
No smoking, eating, drinking.
- They could ingest radiation.
- Has anyone told them?
- Haven't you?
- Sir.
We've got a major problem. Fires are
burning out of control at ground zero.
We've no idea how bad the situation is,
so officers must wear GTsuits.
Suits don't protect against gamma.
That's what the dosimeters are for.
We expect concentrated pockets
of gamma radiation close to the blast site.
- Officers must check meters every minute.
- What's the maximum dose?
Female officers can't risk exposure at all.
We can ask male officers
to take up to 100 millisieverts.
- Anything above that is at their own risk.
- How do we get men in on that timescale?
We could use engines that are already
contaminated to drive relays.
lt's gonna be hard getting close.
There's rubble everywhere.
They'll be lucky to last 20 minutes
in those suits.
They'll need to know the ground.
Your men have had half the maximum dose.
- So their reliefs better get in fast.
- How many men do we have now?
A couple of hundred we can ask to suit up.
Traffic is gridlocked.
The majority of the force
is struggling to get here.
lf you want it, you're first in.
You'd bettertalk to your crew.
Everybody get down!
Armed police! Armed police!
Armed police!
Man down!
Everyone should stay calm.
There is no significant risk to your health.
But it is vital that you are decontaminated
before you go home.
Pregnant women, children, any casualties,
should be brought to the front.
lt is in your best interests
to refrain from eating, drinking, smoking,
or placing your hands in your mouth
prior to decontamination.
- Minister, l'm your liaison officer.
- Bring me up to speed.
We estimate a crowd
of several thousand people behind the cordon,
in need of immediate decontamination.
We are setting up a decontamination unit.
lt'll be a couple of minutes
before we're ready to get the unit open,
and on its way to bring people through ASAP.
Confirmed. The house secured.
We have one casualty, one suspect dead.
Roger, understood. Ambulance en route,
medical team en route.
This man is hot. The whole house is hot!
We've got to get out. Clearthe house!
We've got to get out now. Clearthe house!
Clearthe house!
Murray, when your dosimeter gets to 100,
you come out. Do you understand?
Suiting up, preparing to go in, 12.
Corrigan.
Portley.
Ashwood.
McGee.
First unit en route to ground zero.
We need a decontamination team here
before anyone can check forensics.
Give me the radio.
Sir, this is DC Habibullah.
l'm looking at a rental agreement
for a white Transit van.
Registration:
Oscar Uniform 5-3 Sierra Foxtrot Foxtrot.
Yeah? No, that's not the van that detonated.
Sir, they've recovered documents
for a rented van.
White Ford Transit,
registration Oscar Uniform...
Oscar Uniform...
5-3 Sierra Foxtrot Foxtrot.
Not the Canary Wharf van.
Does anyone have a visual on suspect
vehicles at Westminster and Telecom Tower?
- Van one on the move.
- That's our van.
- Go, gol
- No clean shot, target obscured.
Take it.
Do not approach vehicle.
Our target's down.
Confirm target down, no movement.
Repeat, no movement.
Please wait patiently.
Mass decontamination has begun.
Everybody will go through
as soon as possible.
That's it. Wait yourturn.
Don't cross the line.
Please wait patiently.
Mass decontamination has begun.
Everybody will go through
as soon as is possible.
Your patience is appreciated.
Put a mask on, go outside.
Right, you're done. Step out. Next.
Step forward, please.
Close your eyes.
Turn around. Turn around.
Foxtrot 57 1, this is entry controller.
What's your status? Over.
We have severe casualties, civilians trapped.
We need heavy lifting gear.
Understood.
More units are en route.
What's your dosimeter reading?
Hang on.
250.
Repeat, 250.
You're over your limit.
You need to get yourcrew out now.
Negative, we can't pull out now.
We need more men.
Surely we need a decon unit here?
All units are committed, Minister.
- Can't we get more?
- We have more en route.
We're not sure when they'll get here.
Everyone in vehicles, please.
That's it. Everyone in the vehicles.
- Where do you want me?
- Where's the Prime Minister?
l'll take every question that you have.
We're getting some really high
radiation readings.
- How high?
- Very high.
Radiation has spread
east by north-east with the prevailing winds.
Alert Mile End hospitals
and all units in the area.
Be advised, radiation is spreading.
Do not let people leave hospital buildings.
Sarge, London Wall cordon reports
radiation readings of 50 millisieverts.
- They want to relocate mass decon.
- No, negative, hold position.
- On my coms, please.
- Transfer.
Extra manpower is on its way to assist.
Do not dismantle your decon
until you have backup.
You must hold that cordon line.
lf the perpetrators of this evil
think they can demoralise and intimidate us,
they are wrong.
Londoners have coped
with terrorist attacks many times before.
We are doing everything we can
to protect and inform people.
Sorry. l need to ask you to move.
Decon is being relocated. We need to move.
There will be a short delay while the mass
decontamination facility is resited.
Please stay calm. We will resume
decontamination as soon as possible.
Yourcooperation is essential.
There will be a short delay while
the mass decontamination unit is resited.
Please stay calm.
Minister, the radiation levels are rising,
you must leave.
Please, Minister.
Please remain calm.
Please stay calm.
lt's in your own interests to cooperate.
Decontamination will resume
as soon as possible.
Please remain calm.
Attention, all fire ground personnel.
High levels of radiation are suspected.
lmmediate withdrawal.
l repeat, immediate withdrawal.
Get us out of this!
Murray, this is Harper.
- Steve, check your air supply.
- OK.
Check your gauge.
- Foxtrot 57 1 to entry controller.
- All right, love. We'll get you out.
We're running out of air.
We've got to contain this.
We need more men.
Where are my reliefs?
Murray, this is Harper.
There's a delay.
Most of the area is having to relocate.
We're pulling back.
Will advise on new location.
You have to get out of there now.
Murray, are you receiving?
Murray, do you copy?
Situation understood.
Get out, Steve! Get out!
l've got it!
Are you ready forthis?
Ahmed lbraham Abassi,
also known as Nabil Kassem,
also known as Abu Hazan.
Born Hanif Abbash,
Amman, Jordan, June 17th, 197 1.
Pakistani lSl are holding your wife.
Your son Abdullah, as far as we know,
is in an orphanage.
Your son has no family to claim him.
Do you care what happens to him?
He's four years old.
You decided his fate.
You killed those people, not Allah.
Slaughtering innocent men, women and
children is not defending the brotherhood.
lt is a crime against lslam.
What happens now? The West retaliates.
Thousands more Muslims will die.
We expect your retaliation.
lt is what unites us and divides you.
Can you tell me where the lCU unit is?
Down there.
Follow the corridor, on your left.
Your husband has made good progress.
You need to understand
there will be long-term effects.
Murray should be able to come home
in the next couple of weeks.
We'll make regular appointments
but you should be alert
for any signs of melanoma,
tumours, skin lesions,
any unusual changes to the skin.
l'm afraid there may be problems
if you want to have children.
We have consultants here that you can talk to.
They'll explain the risks involved.
Do you understand?
The death toll as a direct result
of the bombing is confirmed at 375.
Medical experts warn that there could be
thousands of long-term cancer deaths
as a result of exposure to radiation.
The Atomic Energy Agency has announced
that three and a half square miles
of central and eastern London
may have to remain sealed off for 30 years.
Thousands of businesses
in the zone have been forced to close.
Millions of pensions, savings
and trust funds may never recover.
As London house prices plummet,
analysts warn the cost of the bombing
is impossible to calculate.
ln the hunt for the ringleaders
of the bomb attack,
British police have received
unprecedented cooperation
from all international intelligence services.
Later in the programme...
The Prime Minister
vowed the government will not rest
until all the terrorists who threaten
the civilised world are brought tojustice.