Subtitles  PT / BR:
Sphinx777 to Therebels.
"Oh, Osiris, the king departed
but that returns."
You fell asleep but awake.
You will die but rise again.
The vault is open, his tomb more
no longer sealed.
The gates of heaven are open "
text of the Pyramid of Unas, Egypt.
There long ago in the early stages of humanity
Sky came the visitors were called osiris
These gods gave us unimaginable gifts
samples that we still had not dreamed
Astronomy,
architecture, culture
But everything has a price.
The osiris wanted to own earth.
Pharaoh, the most powerful man
, and the sun god Ra
fought together against this threat.
When visitors were coming
to bring his people to Earth
became an opportunity like that will happen only
here 5000 years ago.
When the stars are aligned to one another
.
Pharaoh stole their lights
and subjugated the osiris...
And left them in a dungeon
maze on the bottom of your pyramid.
But some visitors still believed
and awaited his return.
The Princess Amanphur was one.
Flees with the child
He ​​is the last of the dynasty.
Give thanks to the gods.
The cult of Osiris
return to earth.
Exalt his journey to the next world.
She starts
rest in the glory of Ra.
Pharaoh knowing that placed the princess under
your pyramid. It was a portal built...
For when the stars were aligned again...
Visitors would welcome the
a legitimate descendant of the princess...
Pharaoh doubted the princess
was really dead.
He made a key
- The Key of Heaven.
Blocking the secrets that were there.
A guardian was created to protect the tomb.
He assured that no one talked about the secrets
Tomb
so that Osiris could never return.
If they returned was
his terrible revenge.
Fire could destroy the Earth for all
Men, women and children died
.
The osiris would be rewarded
becoming gods.
The stars are near
are again aligned.
But missing The Key of Heaven, and the lost royal descendants
for this day... UNTIL NOW.
Prisoners of the Sun
You're late. Traffic
filled again, huh?
I mean, it was terrible.
You are beautiful!
I'm dusty
depots so many hours that should be here, Mr. Adler...
- Where is he?
- Inside the tent.
Check this out...
Is... gorgeous!
You are amazing!
With all the risks...
7 days.
The builders of the pyramids did
an exact mirror of the heavens...
This image was created
5000 years ago...
Seven Days
only one configuration is complete again.
I asked Mendella
again yesterday evening. Nothing was found.
Tell him to expand
search warrants.
Money is nothing before that.
We're wasting time.
No one here plays.
I'm dealing with idiots...
Kids...
Take direction.
Here  Masterton.
No, I do not.
I want tomorrow
Not next week or next month. Tomorrow!
Masterton confirmed to date.
Exactly one week.
Input must be found.
I do not understand why
tomb has not been found.
He has to be here.
It is my intuition.
Increase  excavations.
Night Lights?
They come today. Unfortunately there's a storm coming
.
- This is great.
- Let's get?
You look tired, teacher.
Have you eaten?
Very hot.
- That's it... -
Not want to know how.
Why do people
museum are so damn boring?
They care for relics as if they were
watchdogs...
- Noted that. -
Do not look like a spaceship?
Could be a symbol of a flying god.
Egypt evolved so quickly.
As a human being could not.
The change was very fast today...
You won the award today.
There is something very strange going on here.
- Looking for something specific?
- The Key of Heaven.
Is very special.
Are you and I want it.
We do business?
Other
someone is ready to pay for it in abundance.
Tonight,
get a good buyer...
I am a very serious man.
And who are you?
Mr. Levitz, come with me.
I hope that has not been followed.
No one came near me.
You know the legend
Key of Heaven?
An Egyptian sect would have kept the
key guarded by priests...
Vanished in the mists of time, Mr.
Levitz.
It is said to be a link with
Princess Amanphur.
How do I know it is genuine?
How
I know you can pay this treasure?
Masterpiece carved.
Miraculously preserved.
Hitler sent archaeologists searching for him.
But remained hidden until now.
Test Results of Carbon 14
This willing to pay the price, Mr. Levitz
?
- What do you think? -
I'll be the first to see it.
Twice worth the money.
You will surely agree.
I was thinking of an exchange.
This stick is 1800.
You're kidding.
I'm not kidding.
I am a very serious man.
Mr Khalfani?
Oh, my God!
Masterton. - It seems that
looking for a key. - Levitz?
- It just changed hands. -
You are a murdering bastard.
Tell me where,
'll send the police after you.
Police
is already going to there in a minute.
He was killed with a cane.
Full of a certain fingerprint.
- Clear evidence, Professor.
- You bastard.
What do you want? Money?
Money? Would underestimate me.
I want a percentage.
- Otherwise, the police will have the
cane. - You will not get away with it.
What do we do?
Claire,
I need your advice.
You have to leave.
The storm is coming.
We've come on!
A huge storm is coming.
See for yourselves!
Everything has to be dismantled.
I will help you!
OK, let's go!
For the love of God!
Stay in the car.
Someone close to you died recently?
This is what I came to talk to you
.
The storm did not come about by chance.
The secret is revealed.
You will gain something.
A key.
Will complete its mission in the coming days.
Powerful Bird Sophus...
Floating in human blood...
Not be celebrated.
- The fire comes again.
- What is it, Claire?
Signs of Osiris rise up...
Osiris died...
- I need to know.
- Not!
What is it, Claire...
I need to know.
None. Only a bad view...
I'm leaving now.
You were a big help.
Of course, I told him.
He ​​is coming.
- What was it? - Professor
insists on seeing it.
Let's take a look then.
What is it? - What I can not believe supposedly
?
What you got for me?
Look what the storm revealed.
We thought we had lost the game.
I knew.
Old friend, can get
input for me?
My friend is already there.
Invite the rest of the team,
call Sarah, in London.
Tell him that his father
needs her.
Masterton! Professor
I would ask...
He has not slept in weeks.
Can the quest to wait until later?
He ​​needs a rest.
Dr. Adler! This pyramid is one Astronomical Observatory
devoted to celestial events
last 5000 years, repeated every event.
The next time will be at 12:37,
Thursday, the 12th of that month.
Three days from now, Dr. Adler.
I will be within the pyramid in three days!
Look at this. Translate
about what I could.
Party is destroyed,
some are missing.
Are you okay?
I am here to take you home.
- Need to prepare for tomorrow.
- Finished for today.
I'm not very well.
Maybe you should convince him to open
only in a few days...
Would be nice, but he did
astrological calculations.
He does not change his mind.
Okay then.
- Good evening.
Your customer came.
Have you seen the new pyramid?
It's amazing, is not it?
Do you want me to applaud me?
Want an enigmatic advice...
Should...
Marry an Egyptian beautiful.
People have a bad habit of disappearing.
- I protect my investments only.
- I wonder what's the investment?
Ici (here)...
Au revoir.
The Key of Heaven.
You can not enter the tomb without it.
I also studied the messages of the gods
the sun for many years...
- Tell your price. -
I do not need your money.
If the legend is true, this pyramid has untold riches...
- This is my job. -
I'm going with you like it or not.
Depots
more than 5000 years, written instructions.
- There is no place for you.
- Okay.
A walking stick with their fingerprints is the way to the station.
If I do not call
Apurilleni within three minutes...
- You get to say goodbye to the pyramid.
- You're bluffing.
Khalfani not think so.
The only camera you can
will visit Cairo is a cell.
Is not a nice place.
Take
Key to my office tomorrow and can go...
You get the key when we go
to the camera... together.
I consider myself dangerous,
suspend delivery.
Teacher?
Teacher!
Teacher.
- Come on.
- Do not worry.
Nothing to worry about.
- I'm fine.
- Is not.
Listen to Doug, there are 4
years in research with me.
- You need to go there. -
I have no experience.
- You underestimate yourself. -
Do you have the talent for this work.
Use your potential.
You will be able to interpret it.
- I'm calling it. - You
what happens tomorrow.
You know what
Masterton said the location of the Earth...
The pyramid is more than it seems.
Not only is the tomb of the princess.
Is only part of the puzzle.
Look.
Symbols refer to Osiris.
You have to go.
Do not worry... 'll survive.
I promise.
Would be better.
- I think you're Sarah?
- Yes
I am Ahmed, his father warned that
office is temporarily closed.
- And the rest of the team?
- Are there tonight.
Sarah...
- Was passed so long...
- You knew where I was.
've Been busy since the death of his mother.
I like to visit the tomb
before we start.
Welcome.
Mother, I'm here.
You used to sing it when I could not sleep.
Do you remember?
Princess Amanphur and his wonderful kingdom.
One day, the rain had turned into
fire.
Princess of innocent
not have to worry about anything.
You called me princess.
I loved.
Now I'll find out what happened to you
. I promise.
Hey, where the conference is being held
?
- Yes, I will check myself.
- Thanks
Dr. Adler...
I am Miss. Masterton I can not find
Teacher Mendella.
My father invited him to his house
. You can contact him?
Teacher tired.
Rest for a few hours.
Non flew here to
wait for their naps.
Be there in half an hour.
Dr. Adler.
- Hi ..
- I was being harsh.
I thought about apologizing for what
told me. Where is Dr. Mendella?
Can we talk? -
My father is waiting for me soon.
Professor is in the hospital.
His condition is critical.
He had a heart attack,
and asked me to come on their behalf.
With all due respect, Dr. Adler,
but you are not qualified.
Mendella worked with my father for many years.
It is unique in its field. You
resembles him in that?
He ​​does not think you should know.
Sarah, this is Adam.
He ​​works with us.
Came collaborate.
I've heard a lot about you.
And of course, his mother.
- Really? - Should I go to
the hotel to others.
- Who is he? -
I'll say it again.
- Found Mendella?
- He will not come.
He had a heart attack.
He ​​sent his assistant, Dr. Adler.
- Where is he?
- I think I pissed him off.
Does this man know anything?
He was beside Mendella
the last 4 years...
Mendella never had the assistance of fools.
This can destroy everything.
I was upset at being very cranky...
- Do not want to fight with you.
No doubt about it, Dr. Adler.
Can you come to the Sphinx Hotel bar?
I apologize for my rudeness.
I. ..
- I'll be there.
- Excellent.
The sky is beautiful today,
and you even look at me.
I am Professor Rohit Singh of India.
And you must be... - Doug Adler.
You're the expert in antiques.
Antiques is the future.
Mendella, Where is he?
The last part of the game
is located.
- Rohit.
- Teacher Masterton.
Welcome.
Everything is correct.
Not only Mendella who can not attend.
- Teacher Mendella... sorry...
- Where is he?
He had a heart attack.
Your ability to interpret the symbols
must have been a great help.
However his assistant, Dr. Adler
promised to do his task.
I'm sorry, but Mendella
is the best in its field.
For this you need a great
specialist.
We'll have to be satisfied with what we have.
Dr. Adler has worked with Professor
Mendella the last 4 years...
He is much more qualified than
a novice historian.
That's right.
Must be nice to take all the information in his head
.
Do you think too much data in a
head weigh?
The only credentials without
chi is you, Mr Levitz...
Can I be so brazen to ask
what you do on this journey?
The story of desecration
requires more than just knowledge.
The excavation of the tomb of Queen Victoria
was a desecration.
Depends on what you will do with it.
Friends, this expedition
needs us all.
Each of you.
Let's delve into history like never before.
I believe that what we find
can change history.
- A Toast to Egypt.
- Cheers.
- Is there anything wrong?
- Military.
Were not here yesterday...
Wonderful, is not it?
Shrouded in secrecy.
My father searched for life.
Told with your help.
I just now included .
My mother raised me alone.
- You chose the same profession.
- Searching for lost items.
Psychiatrists have much work with us.
Sahid is the representative of the Egyptian government.
He wants
confirm who did this puzzle back again.
Teacher tells of a miracle, though
get closer to becoming a disaster.
You would have more confidence in
old gods of Egypt.
This was to have convinced him.
Most reveleção that sandstorms brought
is a place of rest,
believe to be the tomb of Princess Amanphur.
When the rest of the world
lived in caves, it already existed.
When Christ was crucified it was covered with sand.
When Columbus sailed the seas
he was hiding and waiting.
Waiting for us.
Come to the tomb at dawn.
- Are you okay?
- Yes I'm fine.
Do you want some tea?
Here I am, and I do not even know how
is my own father.
This could be your chance.
He ​​called you here.
Not because I wanted to, but
because he needs me.
- I never liked him. - We can not choose our parents
, Sarah.
Simply find them.
Professor
is more my father than me...
Where is your mother?
Died ten years ago.
One night left of the pyramids.
His body was found the next morning.
Police said she was robbed and killed
.
You do not believe?
I do not know what to believe.
My mother was strong and intuitive.
Probably there was
but not allowed to be burglarized.
I think you are like him.
Thank you for your words.
I'm sorry.
I would like to be able to help her.
You helped hearing.
- Do not worry about me, okay?
- Okay.
Be careful with that.
There are exceptions.
Two soldiers, Major and
I'll go with you. Right?
Okay.
Anything else?
No one goes to the chamber and back alive.
Only the chosen of the gods
can do it.
He's right.
There is a single access.
Nothing like a good curse.
Can munch.
They violate  hieroglyphics.
Are you ready?
The entrance is sealed.
Is the only way to go.
This is enough.
Wasps.
Nests are new. Really.
Alright, let's go back.
Fall back.
Calm down.
Sarah...
- Do not move. -
I can not move.
Oh, my God!
We have to help him.
's Too late.
Clean Way!
Great.
Come on!
- I was hoping for traps.
- These are the ones.
Here is a set of containers for food
. - Come back.
I can understand.
Is precisely these places, traps.
I do not think that they will no longer function
.
Tombs were found with the skeletons of thieves.
They warn that criminals should leave.
Levitz, stop!
Levitz!
Do not move.
Stay right where you are.
Exactly.
Mr Levitz,
put the statue back.
- Stay where you are. - The camera is unfortunately
armed.
Mr Singh, take a look
the floor.
The stone floor is definitely
a surprise for us.
- There is a map of it.
- We have to leave.
How? What do you say?
We are stuck here!
- What do you mean?
- We're locked in here.
- You just have to find a way out.
- We are looking for the tomb.
And what is behind it.
Gather your courage.
We can do it over and over.
Claire knows, is not it?
- There are other options.
- I think I have one.
Suppose they believed in symmetry.
Two left.
Stop!
Take the weight of the stone.
Take the backpack.
- Rohit, the secret is on the rocks.
- Yes
- The right order would be from zero to ten?
- Yes!
The zero was invented much later.
Good observation.
Let's start with a...
Two right. A front
for two to the right.
A forward
two to the right.
- Good work, Mr. Rohit.
- Thank you.
forward and two to the right.
A forward two to the right.
Be careful, one by one slowly.
Thank you.
Another dead end.
- There is a passage. -
Must be locked from the inside.
- What did you say, Adler?
- No, he knows nothing.
- Will die if he's wrong.
- Shut up, Levitz.
- I go to the hallway.
- I'm going along with it.
Let's take a look.
Have you lost something?
These symbols, this place...
- You know the feeling?
- Déjà vu.
Happens to me all day since childhood.
- Some wanted to be here.
- Ask your friends this.
I'd really like to know.
What do you know about
Masterton and my mother?
- Everyone has skeletons in the closet.
- What do you mean?
Everything here will not compromise
pianos from his father.
And nothing will stop him.
Whatever the cost.
- What do you mean? -
I can not say anything more.
- Very strange. - It's a man.
Maybe worker.
For all that we
can not be ignored.
A classic example of this.
See how man is described.
The gods and pharaohs were mummified
because they believed knowing the secret of eternal life.
So we know the mummification process.
This is not common knowledge.
That came from somewhere else.
Look at this.
Some kind of device.
Find the same in Mexico and India.
How did they get there?
Sleeping up to agree.
The sleeper awakens.
The earth trembles underfoot.
- Claire? -
Floating on human blood.
Osiris rises.
Osiris was dead.
The path to the
current rulers and the gods will be opened.
What do you think?
I think there's a door here.
"I think"? I think... go fuck yourself!
Are our lives!
Come help.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Now starts happening.
Good work, Doctor.
Ancient Egyptians not spared
distances.
Be careful on the stairs.
How lovely!
The Amanphur Princess.
Masterton
spoke my mother was related to Osiris.
She had.
Apparently, more secrets.
And we're all in trouble.
Help everyone.
Get the coffin, let's go.
Princess  Amanphur,
finally her face!
Depots 5000 years.
Princess Amanphur...
Was the whore of the Pharaoh!
This is just smoke and mirrors,
mode not to reveal the tomb.
- This is a historic tomb! -
The History was written by kings.
- And by the gods.
- Mr Levitz.
The time has come. The key!
The Key of Heaven.
The key?
To Mendella this was the sacred Holy Grail.
We knew it was there.
Some thought it was a myth.
Hitler asked for it.
But eventually stopped in my hands.
We did not come here to get
gold or trinkets.
The true treasures are buried
with this shimmering facade below.
- Are you okay?
- I am.
There is something here .
will find us where ever we are.
Be careful.
- OK?
- OK.
The place is like a maze.
Do not "like a maze."
This is the maze.
A maze of traps.
Where is the treasure?
It is found in the deepest part of the labyrinth and
more dangerous.
A treasure trove of over 5,000 years forgotten.
The lost temple of Osiris.
- Just a myth.
- This does not look good.
I go first, you follow me and you
, Levitz, the last.
You already have enough problems.
Careful now.
Masterton! Stop this nonsense!
Levitz!
Were trapped inside.
- Doug! - Can you hear us?
Oh, my God!
I need all .
You're expendable!
Calm down, for now.
What we look for?
Symbols, hieroglyphs.
Something light inside.
Back  can not.
Returning the same way and look the other way.
Right here. Let's get going.
Hold.
Many times slaves were building trails.
Masterton.
We must continue down.
- What happened? -
He ​​fell and broke his neck.
- Can we go up? -
We do not know where we fall.
What is this?
Who's there?
Do what you must.
Come on.
Slowly now.
Grasp the handle.
- Beware.
- Do not worry.
Imagine that this is an elevator.
- Are you okay?
- Yes
- Doug!
- What happened?
The soldier...
Listen, Levitz, you
is a corrupt, evil character.
The Egyptian civilization is the beginning of a
of the biggest puzzles of history.
How suddenly started
bloom along the Nile.
Maybe its origin was elsewhere.
We are looking for an answer to this
.
I do not like this place.
"Sleepers, wake up."
"In human blood, floating."
- What is it?
- I do not know.
Came just try it?
As important as the key?
Want to play with me?
Who are you?
I'm just a canal...
The messages from the other side pass me by.
Something is wrong!
Very wrong!
- Doug, are you? -
What the hell are you doing?
Sorry.
Sought one way out.
Found a soldier.
He ​​had fallen.
You're still alive. This way.
- So many dead...
- Protected from light.
- What did they see?
- Are victims of the Sun
They are not people.
- What is it? -
I heard something.
- What was that?
- Mouse.
Do not get hysterical, Levitz.
It was just a mouse.
You're like a frightened child
college in the cemetery.
No wonder I'm nervous.
Some of us are dead, Levitz.
Could be you.
You bring bad luck.
She was attacked .
What is this?
What the hell?
You need to find the exit.
I am watching others.
You'll be fine. Go!
You! Follow me!
I found a portal front!
Come on!
Not!
Sahid is dead.
Is fascinating.
Fascinating? Sahid is dead,
Levitz almost too... how can?
You're not listening!
- Son of a bitch!
- Hear Me!
I wonder how Levitz has the key.
He ​​murdered Khalfani. A killer!
The murder weapon was in a police station.
With their fingerprints on it!
What creature was what is there?
What was it?
That... is...
The former guardian  inside the pyramid.
Protecting against intruders in the tomb.
But that will not stop me!
- I will not stop! - Will kill you
as did my mother?
Look.
Look!
Is not here.
And all these years
theories have been ridiculed.
See!
Doug. Find a way
I go.
Is the only way to get out of here alive
Sarah.
No one should look for the obvious.
This means Osiris.
Osiris rises.
Osiris was dead.
The name of the oldest form of a
name written with two characters.
The name is represented by a throne and an eye.
God opens the eyelids of the eye.
The wonderful bird, Sothis.
On the other  name is Sirius, the star of Ham
Sirius was a bright star that can be seen
in the sky when the pyramids were built
.
Here.
Doug, hurry up, please.
Sarah! Remember:
you are the key!
Come on!
Go through the door!
Adam!
This is some kind of ancient generator.
Come on, cowboy.
Not need you anymore.
No, Doug.
What are you doing?
The genetic code
Amanphur only exists intact in female offspring.
You are a direct descendant of Princess Amanphur
.
- We need your blood.
- Not!
I'm fine.
Rohit...
If your mother had agreed to
cooperate, he would be here now
witnessed this resurrection.
- "Refused to cooperate"?
- He was by my side
and to get involved with a new historical era.
But she refused.
Let the sleeping agree.
This knowledge has passed through countless generations.
- You can prevent this from happening.
- No, Rohit.
You are welcome back...
Stay with us.
E come from death to life.
In the end, the human race will
reach their full potential!
Look at the Suns!
Your blood will connect us all.
Too late!
Give me that.
This is over!
Oh, my God!
We're here.
You were very brave.
You saved my life, thank you.
No, thank you.
They are there... somewhere.
Hoping to return here.
Www.yifysubtitles.com