[Cheers and applause]
- Greg giraldo,
everyone.
[Cheers and applause]
- Thank you, Dave.
I don't know if you guys watch
a lot of hip-hop videos,
but, man, bitches
are the shit.
Bitches are so much better
than regular women.
They're always
in a good mood.
They just dance around
in their thongs
and their high-heel shoes,
and you get to smoke bongs
and play the Xbox
all day long.
They never seem to mind.
Bitches never complain.
They never tell you to take
your feet off the couch.
Or, "we gotta go see
my mother."
Bitches don't even
have mothers.
[Cheers and applause]
Greg giraldo, very simply,
was the real thing.
He had the respect
of real comedians.
- Nobody was as good as him
and yet lived
as hard as him
and delivered
consistently like him.
- One of the most
compelling things about Greg
was that there's
an honest soul
inside of everything
he did.
- The thing about his comedy
was just being so raw
and honest and real.
He just was such
a real guy.
- I was in a subway
the other day.
This guys screams
across the tracks,
screams across the tracks,
he goes,
"yo, Monica,
yo, Monica,
yo, you got aids, yo."
And I thought, wow,
that's how they tell you?
- He had this brain
that was completely
this, like, supercomputer
that just wouldn't shut off.
It helped him generate
all this stuff,
but it also tortured him.
- From the moment he got on
to the moment he got off,
he didn't take a breath,
and it was all funny.
- We need a whole new
energy source.
We need something else.
It's not gonna be conservation.
Let's face it, Americans
are not gonna conserve.
We're not gonna shift
to smaller cars.
We can't!
We have big, fat kids.
- He was also
the kind of comic
that you went,
"oh, son of a bitch."
It was right in front
of everybody's face.
He found it and I'm like,
"what am I, an idiot?"
- Gay marriage is fine
if you want
to make Jesus cry.
[Cheering]
I mean, if that's your thing.
You know what I mean?
- That's why we love him.
- There was
a darkness about him
that transcended beautifully
in his comedy.
- That's what made him funny.
Otherwise, you know,
you got Jim belushi
doing according to Jim,
you know?
- Everybody thinks of him,
you know, I think publicly
as kind of a roast comic.
Never in a million years
would I think of him as, like,
an insult comic or a thing.
He was a heady comic.
He was not the guy
in the club
that you thought
would die.
[Upbeat rock music]
♪
- That's what
you're calling it?
Give it up for Greg giraldo?
- Give it up for
Greg giraldo.
Greg giraldo!
- The concept of me
being interviewed
about Greg giraldo,
the great comedian
who is dead,
would be so hysterical to us.
- The west nile virus.
You know how they knew
it was coming back
to the New York area?
They found two birds
in whitestone, queens
that were infected
with the virus.
Who finds these birds?
I grew up in queens.
We used to find
dead birds all the time.
We didn't take them in
for autopsies, you know?
We picked 'em up and we threw
them at the gay kid.
That's what we did.
- The thing about,
you know, giraldo,
that he wasn't a dick.
- Greg giraldo.
- Oh, hi.
Yeah, this is where
they all stop shooting.
- When you walked into a room
and you saw Greg...
- Is everyone allowed
to come?
- You know you'd be
greeted with warmth.
- It's funny, I'm Italian.
He's from queens.
But we always used to do
this fake Italian greeting.
He'd go,
"hey [Imitating Italian]"
Some word that wasn't
even Italian.
We'd just, like,
hug each other.
But, uh, he was always
upbeat, you know?
- They don't get that comics
are dark, tortured souls,
that we don't need
to dance around for attention.
- Are you dark and tortured?
- He is.
Kid's twisted.
- They do say
that comedians are.
- He's like gitmo
in his head.
- Greg's comedy was just real,
you know what I mean?
There was no character.
There was no persona.
Everything he did,
like even in his roasts--
you know, his roasts
were so epic.
He just blew everybody
out of the water.
You're a vegetarian,
but you have no trouble
swallowing a moose [Bleep].
You liver is so shriveled,
black, and dead,
if you put your ear
to your side
you can hear it go, "what you
talking 'bout, Willis?"
What a night.
A couple of trolls,
a fairy, and a giant
all going after
a sunken-eyed little monster
whose obsessed with jewelry.
It's like
the lord of the rings.
- He kind of
let the audience know,
this is the bar.
This is how hard-core
this night is gonna be.
So either stay tuned or turn
off your TV now, you know?
- Nichelle Nichols,
farrah fawcett,
and Betty white.
I'll take women I would
masturbate to 30 years ago
for $1,000, Alex.
[Laughter and applause]
- He was one of those guys
that just went
bam, bam, bam, bam,
and just tears.
- Who would [Bleep] you?
You have the sex appeal
of a school bus fire.
You look like Nick nolte
[Bleep]ed a clydesdale.
Jon lovitz,
you [Bleep]ing gay weeble.
Come on, jon, there hasn't
been a more effeminate Jew
in the closet
since Anne Frank.
[Laughter]
- I think you can get to know
his personality at the roasts,
but the real Greg,
you know,
fans would get to know him
if they went to see him live.
- A lot of my friends,
you know, have a lot of money,
and they were calling me up,
you know,
"hey, did you lose a lot of
money in the stock market?
Did you get creamed?"
But I've had a lot
of personal problems
in the last few years,
so I don't have
any money at all.
So they're calling me up.
I'm like, "no.
"Actually I have exactly
the same amount of money now
as I did when all
this [Bleep] started."
Turns out investing all my
money in Tequila and strippers
wasn't such a bad policy
after all, you know?
[Cheering]
- He was such a life-force.
He was so animated,
so intelligent,
so present.
It's the way
he attacked a crowd.
- Now they have
these DVD screens,
and people are playing porn
driving around in these suvs
with porn playing
on their DVD.
What the hell kinda--what if
you get in an accident?
The whole car is totaled,
but the porn is still
blaring away on the sidewalk.
- Giraldo belonged
to the class of us
that were workers,
that sat and wrote and tried,
and he was always prepared.
- He was like
a [Bleep]ing miner.
You know, he was just--
excavate.
He would hit the joke
and then hit it again
and then hit it again,
and he'd find more
and more and more.
- I'm pissing in the sink
because my crazy wife
has locked herself
in our one bathroom,
and she won't come out
till I admit that I have
a drinking problem.
Well, it's gonna be
a long wait, buttercup,
so hang in there.
I'll always do stand-up.
My entire life is just trying
to fuel this stand-up monster,
you know, come up with ideas
and come up with things
to talk about.
I can't imagine not doing it.
But I also think
that once you stop,
then you really stop
for good.
This in-and-out thing,
is just, it's too painful
to regroup and restart,
and you gotta be in it
all the way.
- The story of giraldo for me
was he was just a great guy.
You know, I'd like to say,
oh, he was the guy of appetites.
Boy, you saw this coming.
It wasn't that way.
He was all of us.
- Greg's the oldest
of three of us.
Myself, I was
the second child,
and my sister Elizabeth
was the baby of the family.
My dad was from Colombia,
my mother from Spain.
Raised in queens, New York.
Typical middle class.
There wasn't anything
that would jump out at you
as being anything,
you know,
that led him into
some crazy world of comedy.
- You are you?
- Greg giraldo.
- Okay, how long
you been doing comedy?
- 35 years.
No, it'll be two years
in march.
- We both, I started
at the comedy cellar
in the same way.
And we were
just in the sort of,
as comics come
in sort of classes
in little five-year clusters
like locusts.
- Greg and I go back
to my first day in comedy.
I walk in
and the first person I saw
is skinny, young Greg
in the corner of the club
just sweating
like a nervous wreck.
He was like
a wet squirrel.
I mean, from that time
that we did that first show
you just knew
there was no way about it
we were comedians.
- I actually heard
somebody the other day,
he said, "these
illegal aliens come over
"and take American jobs.
They're taking away jobs
from Americans."
Really?
When's the last time you lost
a job to an illegal alien.
You want to deliver
you own Chinese food?
Is that a job you're
having trouble getting?
Do you want to ride your
shitty little bike
down Broadway in the rain?
I used to hang out
at the open mics
at, like, New York
comedy clubs and Gladys's
just for fun, you know?
- For fun?
- Yeah, just I would
hang out there.
It was a good time, a lot of
my buddies would hang out.
And I just thought, you know,
I could never be as good
as everybody there, but, uh...
[Laughs]
- I remember seeing him one time
in a suit and tie,
and I said,
"you look like a lawyer."
And he was a lawyer.
So, you know,
tip of the hat to me, huh?
- We were just miserable
as lawyers
and trying to figure out
how to get out.
I remember him saying,
"I gotta do something I like."
- During that time period,
stand-up comedy was a career
that did not have
a lot of openings.
So I used to joke around
that it was like
pursuing a career
in phonograph repairman.
- [Bleep]Ing Harvard lawyer.
It was just like a joke.
It's like saying,
"oh, there's that comedian.
He's also a brain surgeon."
- You were a lawyer?
- I went to Harvard preschool.
- Well, here's
a Harvard lawyer
who decided to do
what we do.
All of a sudden we're all
a little bit more fancy.
- I got arrested and spent
a night in jail in Virginia
for drinking a beer
on the sidewalk.
In New York I coulda been
drinking that beer
out of the hollowed-out skull
of something
I'd just decapitated.
I coulda been standing
on the hood of a cop car
mocking the officers
with it.
"Cheers, big ears!"
I coulda been doing funnels
out of this head's nostrils,
and there would have been
no problems at all,
unless I was
illegally parked.
You know, that--
[Laughter]
- I got busted
for inciting a riot
at this college gig.
I had no money
for a lawyer.
I was an opening act.
You know,
I didn't want a record.
He said, "yeah, I'll help you
get outta that.
That's no problem."
We each had our one good
suit and tie on,
and Greg, like,
worked circles
around some local judge.
And he got my inciting
a riot case dismissed.
And we were buddies
ever since then.
- It was a ridiculous thought
that I could possibly ever
work in a regular job.
I just thought, you know, I'd
taken the lsats and all that.
It went well, and going to law
school was fun enough I guess.
But then trying to be
a real working lawyer
was not an issue,
not an option.
I'm sitting here
about to perform
in front of
a giant audience
with my pants
electrical taped together.
So imagine the kind
of lawyer I would be.
I was on the subway
the other day.
I saw these homeless guys
singing a capella.
They were homeless and they were
singing a capella for money.
How'd those guys
even meet?
How do you bump into
other a capella enthusiasts
when you're out there
on the homeless trail?
You think they're just sitting
around the shelter one day.
"I need some crack."
♪ Me too, me three
oh!
- I can't ever remember,
like, looking back
remembering Greg
when he was new.
Even though he was new
when I saw him,
he was just always
an awesome comic.
- When you start out,
you do a lot of dick
and midget and [Bleep] jokes.
He was writing
topical stuff.
He had, like, you know,
dirty, filthy stuff
but really smart stuff.
I fought that.
I'm still doing the dick and
[Bleep] and midget stuff, okay?
- Hilary Clinton
is probably gonna get indicted
on whitewater charges.
And because Clinton's
still president,
he gets to decide whether
to pardon her or not.
He gets to decide whether
to pardon his own wife.
What an amazing relationship
bargaining chip that is.
You know,
if you get to decide
whether your wife
goes to prison or not,
who picks the movies then,
you know what I mean?
- The way you can really
judge comedians,
'cause you're not
gonna sit there
and watch everybody's
stupid act your whole life,
is going to the bathroom
just to pee.
Every time you walk
by the bathroom,
you hear whoever's
on stage.
And every time I walked
by hearing him,
you're like, wow,
that was a great bit.
Yeah, that's a great bit,
you know what I mean?
Then you stay for
an extra minute or two.
- We had both been doing it
for three, four years,
and all of a sudden
we were on sitcoms.
- I started in '92,
and then in '95
I did the Montreal
comedy festival.
There was an agent from L.A.
That kind of discovered me,
or whatever.
And it was kinda the days
when you could still
do that, you know?
If somebody saw you
and you were castable
and had a story, you know,
then you could just
go to Los Angeles
and, you know,
tell your stupid story,
and some executive
would give you money
and develop a shitty show
that would get cancelled
in three episodes.
- 8:30!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, what happened?
- Man, I don't know.
We had a couple of bottles
of champagne,
a few hours
of sexual gymnastics.
If I had
to put a name on it,
I'd say we got caught up
in pope fever.
I was [Bleep]ing awful in it.
I couldn't act.
I stood there like,
what am I doing here?
And I'd only done comedy
for about 2 1/2 years
when the show got on the air,
so I was ridiculous.
I was everything
that was wrong
with the nature
of entertainment at the time.
- And I think his lasted,
like, three weeks,
and mine lasted, like, six.
And then, you know,
then the next time I saw him,
you know, we were working, like,
in a Chinese restaurant,
going, "yeah, yeah,
this feels about right."
[Laughs]
- There's a fun competition
at a roast
where you wanna have that--
that best joke, you know.
And it's--it's good because
it keeps the bar high.
- Greg would go on first,
which obviously all the comics
are very jealous of
because he gets to just,
you know.
He'd say, "well, I have
to break the ice."
You know, "I have to break--
I gotta do my own warm-up.
I gotta break the ice."
He would crush the ice.
- What a teeny little pimp.
Man, being a pimp
ain't easy,
especially when you gotta
stand on phone books
to smack a bitch.
Kathy, you look like
Ronald McDonald
[bleep]Ed Lucille ball's corpse
then pushed it down
a flight of stairs.
Lisa actually has a lot in
common with that octomom.
She's never given birth,
but she has had 80 fingers
inside her
at the same time.
- Even, like,
the cable guy roast
is arguably one of
the funniest ten minutes
I think I've ever seen
anywhere ever.
And I mean, like,
out of anything.
It's just a [Bleep]ing tornado.
You're like the trojan army.
You're big, patriotic,
and you both [Bleep] inside
a giant horse.
You gravy-sweating
cousin [Bleep]er.
Larry [Bleep]ed his first
cousin when he was 16.
And his last one
about an hour ago.
- He would roast everything
about the person.
You know, and eventually,
like, his real feelings
could come through,
you could see, you know?
He stopped making jokes at
a certain point and he said...
- How the [Bleep]
are you so popular?
[Laughter]
Jesus [Bleep]ing Christ.
This one finally
broke my back.
- I think he really wanted Larry
the cable guy to answer him
in some way.
Bob saget, everybody.
Huh, Bob saget.
- Greg's the first person
out of the gate,
which is--
any good cockfight,
you send out
your best rooster.
And I'm just sitting there.
And when I say cockfight...
- Who gives a shit
about Bob saget?
Bob, you are a genital wart on
the [Bleep] of American culture.
- And I'm looking
like I'm happy.
But my posture's bad,
and I was not, like,
overjoyed.
And I was getting
mind raped.
And everything he said
was right.
- You are a vortex
of artistic compromise.
Charlie sheen watches you
and feels good about himself.
[Laughter]
- The stage manager yells,
"Joel wants you to sit up and
look like you're enjoying this."
- No, just you looked
a little uncomfortable.
- And I'm like, what?
See, that's what I have
to contribute.
It's not much.
You should cut to
Sarah silverman right now.
It'll be funny.
- You know,
a roast is something
where you can be brutal
because it's with love.
And it never occurs to me
that anyone might have
actually ill feelings
towards me,
which is I'm sure not true
but a great way to live.
- Courtney, what the hell
happened to you?
Your career dried up faster
than Sarah silverman's [Bleep]
Around guys who can't
help her in the business.
- We were in
the car together,
and he was talking about
doing the flavor flav roast.
And we just started
kinda riffing on it.
And I think that's when it
kind of occurred to him
that, like, oh, hey,
I think we could be good
at that together,
and the first joke
we kinda wrote was...
- Ice-t,
you [Bleep]ing fossil.
You're so old
the first thing you bought
with your record deal money
was your freedom.
[Laughter]
- And when ice-t threw his head
back and applauded
about that
particular joke,
I think everybody
kinda knew, like,
oh, this is okay.
- I've never roasted
an oily cadaver before.
You're like a turd with teeth.
Look at yourself.
I don't try so much
to be funny,
as I just try to make
people uncomfortable
and ideally raise a lot
of ugly truths.
And try not
to shit myself.
If I can get two outta three,
I feel pretty good
about that.
- We're a team.
We're a comedy duo.
We're a duo.
- Did you have fun?
- Oh, we're talking?
I'm posing for a [Bleep]ing--
I'm posing for a still shot
like a douche bag.
What am I,
a [Bleep]ing 90-year-old man?
Hey!
Hey, all right.
- The first time
I was on the roast,
I kind of, you know--
to me, my audience was Greg.
Like, if I can
make him laugh,
that's all that matters.
- I think those roasts really
did help focus him,
like, on, like,
on what he was good at,
which is just, like, cutting,
really, really funny
dirty-yet-clever jokes.
- This woman the other day,
she had glitter on her chest.
Glitter, and she catches me
glancing over.
And she's like...
You have shiny shit
on your tits.
Were you hoping
to divert attention?
That's not a great
strategy.
You know, why don't
you hire a marching band
to walk around you
with neon titty signs.
[Imitating band playing]
"What are you looking at?
What are you look--
I'm up here.
Look me in the eyes."
- The insomniac tour thing
was good
'cause I got to pick some of
the comics who were on it.
And one of them was Greg.
- This guy looks funny though.
- This guy is good.
- He actually looks funny.
- Thanks.
- I thought he was an undercover
cop in a '70s TV show,
but he's not.
And Greg really
did me a solid.
- After dinner, we go to
the make-your-own sundae bar,
and we make sundaes
for each other.
- Okay.
- Dane is sober,
but the rest of us, like,
we were hard-core drunk.
So, like, we definitely
coulda, like,
tore through that town.
- I was in
a restaurant recently.
The waitress says,
"hey, gang, did you leave
"any room for dessert?
Did you leave any room
for dessert?"
for dessert?
How gluttonous
a concept is that?
Is there any room left
in your fat [Bleep]ing body
cavity for more?
Did you leave any space?
Is there any physical way
we could cram more shit
in your fat, bloated face,
you fat [Bleep]?
Any chance at all?
Any space in your
distended esophagus?
We got dudes with plungers
that'll come out
and cram it
right in your head.
Any chance at all?
Won't that be neat, gang?
Won't that be a great way
to celebrate
your happy, Happy Birthday.
Happy, Happy Birthday.
[Laughter]
- When we did
the Vegas special,
it was a lot
of temptation.
But, you know, we were there
to do a job,
and I think we did it.
[Laughs]
- You rocked, and I'm not
just saying that.
- Hey, suck-up, I'm over here.
It was my show.
- No, you didn't do as well
as I expected.
You, on the other hand,
kind of blew.
- At one point
during his set,
the fire alarm
in the casino went off.
- These little [Bleep]ing
12-year-old girls
walking around with juicy--
[Alarm blares]
Holy shit.
Wait, are we supposed
to be concerned, anybody, or--
all the [Bleep]ing producers,
the people in the sound truck
have driven off.
It's just us
burning to death.
- That's kind of fun
to, like, deal with
for, like, a minute.
But if kept going off
throughout his set,
like over and over and over.
So it was amazing
how he handled it.
- How bad would that blow?
I quit drinking, I'm in Vegas
without drinking,
and then I die in a [Bleep]ing
fiery crash that day?
- As a guy
who did drink heavily,
I mean, I totally got it,
and I knew
what he was going through.
And few people know that,
like, he really did,
um, try to get sober.
I mean, he really did.
But I think
in his head that, like,
he was just too smart
for it all, you know?
He really just
was too smart for it.
- Say cheese!
- Oh, you got it.
Nice!
[Cheers and applause]
- He was--
I hate to use the word
given the circumstances
of what happened--
but he was reliable.
You know, watch him
on tough crowd, man.
Nobody came with more
prepared stuff than he did.
- If you could choose to be gay,
why wouldn't we all do it?
We would you put up
with the hassles
of trying to get a woman
to have sex with you
if you could just walk into
the steam room at the "y"?
- You knew you could
rely on him.
There would never be
nothing there, you know?
- Or maybe there's
a nonviolent way
to solve the whole
north Korea thing.
- Good thinking.
- There might be.
They're asking for--what?
- There's a nonviolent way
to solve a problem
with a country that we hate
that hates us
that's got weapons
pointed at us?
I don't think so.
- No, you're right.
Like, Russia, for example,
that big Russian war.
There are things that--
there are things that--
- with guys like Greg,
if you showed up not prepared,
you'd get your head
handed to you.
- This guy writes so many
jokes before the show
it's not even funny.
It's unbelievable.
He's got a pocketful of them.
- That's kinda what
we do here, Dennis.
I'm a comedy writer.
- It was Dennis leary
and Lenny Clarke.
- I'm not coming back!
- He was literally
attacking the king
with the king's general
to his left.
- I thought the whole idea
was just go out there
and sort of, you know,
spur-of-the-moment.
And he was like,
"yeah, you know,
but, you know, you wanna make
sure that you're funny."
And I was like,
"I'm not writing--
I didn't come here
to do homework."
You're the guy in school
that did all the homework
and then asked if there was any
more that needed to be done.
- Yeah, yeah.
That's a good point.
And if you had tried
a little comedy writing,
maybe your show would still
be on the air.
- Oh!
- I'm just saying.
- It was like
that great moment
when two guys
are about to fight
where they just both look
at each other
and neither one's like--
their eyes are just getting
opener and wider,
like, you know.
I thought they were just
gonna start fighting
in the middle of the show.
- Meanwhile the host,
Colin Quinn,
I mean, all he did
was actually
put his leg up
on the table
that was in between
me and Greg.
That was like--
what was that?
Like that was gonna
keep us separated
if we decided to go at
each other?
Ooh, Colin's knee
is in the way.
- This is a microcosm of why
war will never end right here.
'Cause we can't even
get along.
- No, no, no, [Bleep].
We're at war.
You and me, we're done.
It was a great moment
where I really, uh,
looked like a douche bag.
And I felt bad.
In Greg's defense,
he actually--
he was very prepared
for almost anything
that coulda happened.
- I think my on-stage
persona is punkish.
- People give him shit for not
having this huge career,
but comics were always like,
"oh, you know, comedy central
gives him everything."
- Here's your host,
Greg giraldo!
[Cheers and applause]
- Root of all evil.
He was, like,
automatically on the list
just to see if he really
was a Harvard lawyer.
If strip clubs are so bad,
why are they called
gentlemen's clubs?
- That's just another lie,
your honor.
Gentlemen's clubs.
There's no gentlemen in there.
You never hear things like,
"oh, I say, old man,
"have you seen the nipples
on the enchantress
in the rubber thong?"
- He was always on the side
that was gonna
probably lose.
Which is part of the reason
we put him there,
because he's the one
that would present the best
and the funniest argument.
- It's amazing
that we live in a time
where I use the same
machine to masturbate
that I use to teach
my kids to spell.
- He was a guy
we could count on
when we needed a great set
from somebody.
He was the guy
we always thought of
for particular shows
and pilots.
Like, we want to find a way
to get him on there
and give him a shot.
We sorta considered him
a part of the family.
- It's a comedy show
about sex.
It'll be great.
It's a topic everyone
can relate to.
And it won't be gratuitous
or low-brow humor.
I'm not talking about a bunch
of cheap sex jokes.
I'm talking about
a smart look
at the state of sexuality
in contemporary
American society.
Ah, [Bleep].
So what do you think?
- Whatever.
- People always talked about
that Greg had a ton of pilots
that didn't work.
And, I mean,
I think that's true
of a lot of really
talented people.
- As they say,
the cream rises to the top.
And just because
the things that he did
didn't necessarily
take off in the manner
that I think they could have
or should have,
it's not like he goes back
to the back of the line
as a talented performer.
- Comedians respect him.
Audiences respect him.
The work is all there.
It's digital.
It's on the Internet.
There are people
on other planets
watching him right now,
higher life-forms,
deciding whether or not
to invade
based on Greg's comedy.
And that endures,
you know?
Every once in a while
there's a celebrity
checks into the hospital
because she's exhausted.
You always hear
they went in the hospital
because they were exhausted.
How exhausted do you have
to be to go to the hospital?
I mean, I've been
pretty damn tired.
I just take
a little nappy-poo.
And I wake up,
and I'm like,
"wow, cancel
the ambulance, honey.
All better."
- You know, everybody
has, like, a hook.
You think, like,
people might have a hook
in what makes them memorable.
Like, with Greg, it was
always that he was smarter.
- These reality shows,
they're getting so extreme.
And they're all such copies
of everything else.
How 'bout the contender?
Everybody, ooh,
it's the contender.
That's a great show.
These shows
are [Bleep]ing soulless.
And by the way,
we already had a show
where we went around
looking for the best boxer.
It was called boxing.
I don't know
if you remember that show.
It was a really good show,
boxing.
- Yeah, there's too many
comedians out there
that are just smart.
Well, go be a scientist.
Smart and funny often means
not that funny.
And in Greg's case,
he was really [Bleep]ing funny.
And he happened
to be really smart.
- That whole thing of, like,
whether somebody's
smart or not smart,
you know, I'm not trying
to be a Professor here.
I'm trying
to make people laugh.
So that and also the fact
that I have mommy issues
I think is what drives me.
- He had all of the qualities
that a stand-up comedian
would want to have.
Intelligent, good-looking,
integrity.
He could have worked
off of his ethnicity.
Never did.
He never did.
- How dare you
not take the shortcut
and talk about your people
for an hour
every single night
of your life?
- Most people find out
that I'm hispanic,
they react the same way.
Like, "wow, man, you don't
seem hispanic."
They say it like
it's an enormous compliment.
"You don't seem hispanic.
Seriously, you look good.
Nice work."
- When a comic
deals with a heckler,
that's when you really see,
like, what they're made of.
- Let's talk about
Keith Richards then.
It's not really what
I had planned,
but why don't
you talk about it?
What exactly is the story?
- He snorted dad.
- Not so easy is it?
Now imagine trying to do that
with some [Bleep]ing drunk
screaming in your face.
- When it would get bad,
I would love to watch him
because he wouldn't
let them off the hook.
- Is that person sleeping?
There's a dude sleeping
dead center.
That is [Bleep] great.
- There was this guy
in the audience
who was asleep
during the special.
Like, he was, like,
passed out,
like in the third row.
And Greg just started
tearing into him.
This was at the taping
for his hour special.
- Doesn't strike you
as a weird choice
to fall asleep
in the third row
of my big TV taping?
I mean,
I'm all for sleeping.
I'm sure I'd be sleeping
watching you grow weed,
or whatever you do
for a living,
but I--I'm just
trying to wonder
why you would opt
for that.
You know what I mean?
- What's beautiful
about Greg
is unrelenting belligerence
to someone that deserves it.
[Laughs]
"Why you sleepin'?"
"Me don't know.
Me got up early."
- When you see a rerun
of one of Greg's specials
or one of his appearances
on the roast,
you forget he's gone.
You watch it, and you feel
like he's still around.
- Flavor flav!
[Cheers and applause]
- The flavor flav roast
was very special
because it was a year
where there was a lot
of racial humor
handled poorly.
- I'm not gonna say
anything about flav
that, uh, that hasn't
already been said
by, uh, Michael Richards.
- But the truth is,
racial humor like that,
when handled by professionals
in the right environment,
like the flavor flav roast
can be epic.
It can actually
bring people together.
I remember flavor flav
in that big throne
with that clock
and the smile,
and he was like a little boy
and it was his birthday.
You could not hurt
this guy's feelings.
He laughed so much,
you would have thought
he didn't even understand
English.
- You are one black
mother[Bleep]er.
You're like a skeleton
wrapped in electrical tape.
You look like idi amin
after a three-year crack binge
on the sun.
- He was funny, and...
Nobody questions funny.
You're not gonna get
a network call.
When things are working,
everyone shuts up.
Please welcome
the very funny Greg giraldo.
- People always wanna compare
their dogs to your kid.
You don't know what it's like
to have a kid
'cause you have a dog.
First of all,
nobody has a dog 'cause
they were too drunk to pull out.
All right?
That's the first thing.
- We had worked with Greg
through the late night show,
and he was just
the stand out.
I thought, "let's try and think
of something for Greg."
- I'm Colombian.
- Get a load of
the puerto rican
trying to pass himself off
as Colombian.
- What's the difference?
- A Colombian's a puerto rican
with a job.
- I love it--
the black guy
talking about jobs.
- Greg wanted to play
a stand-up comedian.
Which, of course, we were all,
you know, trepidatious about
because Seinfeld had so famously
played a stand-up comedian.
And comedy about comedy
is next to impossible.
- We finished the pilot
and, you know,
we were all so fired up.
You know,
it ultimately didn't go,
and I could tell that that
was another dagger for giraldo
'cause it was another show
and another opportunity
that should have happened,
and it didn't, you know?
Greg was one of those guys
that even when the doors close
and even when they said no
and even when he got another
rejection, he just kept going.
- Last comic standing!
- Greg judging
last comic standing,
I think was great for the show
because of his
universal respect.
- Uncle Mikey did heroin,
which feels like
you're naked in a pool
full of puppies...
- He was, I would say,
the Simon of the group.
- Mike, you're always funny.
Your jokes are always funny.
You're likable violent people.
- You know, he would...
Tell it like it is.
- From last comic standing,
wild card Greg giraldo.
- All season long I was like,
"we gotta get Greg.
We gotta get Greg,"
and it wasn't until
the final show
of the first season
that we finally got him on.
And he sits there with
Gwyneth paltrow
and Jerry Seinfeld
and just blows it open.
He was poised, he was funny.
He stole the show.
- You know, he's so happy.
His wife helps.
You're so happy.
Gwyneth--oh, look at us!
A rock star! [Mutters]
We're all happy!
All we do is just look
into each other's eyes
as we burn piles of money!
- He liked the rock and roll
aspects to comedy.
He would talk about comedy
like...Like he was
the rolling stones.
And I was like,
"I think we're like Bob Denver."
So when stories
would come back
and he was starting
to get mixed up
or whatever was happening,
I would always worry
about him for sure.
And then--boom.
Then it hits you.
I don't know.
You know...
There's not...There's not much
you can really say
in those moments.
- This homeless guy
asked me for money,
and I was about
to give it to him,
and then I thought,
"he's just gonna use it
on drugs or alcohol."
And then I thought, "that's
what I'm gonna use it on."
- He was struggling with
both, uh, you know,
addiction and--
and marriage, and, uh,
gave him plenty of material.
- Being married to a guy
would be great.
It would be great.
Could you imagine
saying something
and having the words you said
interpreted exactly
the way that you intended
your words to be interpreted?
"Remember what you said
ten years ago
"when you were driving the car
on the way to my mother's
house?"
"No."
"Oh, me neither! I'm a dude.
Shit, never mind.
[Bleep] It..."
- Greg had some anger,
particularly
in the past couple years.
Was saying stuff on stage
where I was like,
"wow, I can't believe...
He's saying that."
- "I hate you gotta go on the
road to get drunk all the time."
"Well, I hate going
on the road too, my love,
"but I'm just trying
to earn a goddamn living.
"And if getting drunk
is the only way
"I can anesthetize myself
enough
"to entertain a bunch of freaks
I have nothing in common with,
"I would have thought you,
"as the woman who supposedly
loved me for who I am,
would show me one [Bleep]ing
shred of compassion."
"I wouldn't have married you
if I knew you were gonna
"go on the road and get drunk
and work in night clubs.
I wouldn't have married
someone like that."
"Yes, you would have,
'cause that's how we met
in the first place, remember?"
- I mean, you could tell
he was being personal
with every bit.
That's what made him great
too, is like...
He'd be talking about
Tiger Woods,
but he's telling people
like this is about guys,
my frustration.
- 'Cause I was a loser nerdy
little golfer geek for years,
and now I have access
to all these women,
and it's very hard to just
turn that button off.
I mean, I really want
to have sex with them.
And it would mean nothing
to me.
I love you and I love
our family,
but occasionally I wanna
have sex with some women.
It would mean nothing!
And I know you don't understand,
'cause men and women
are different like that.
Like I don't understand
a lot of things about you.
how much you love shoes.
But if hundreds
of free pairs of shoes
showed up in your hotel room
every night,
I guarantee you'd keep a pair
every once in a while.
Thank you very much!
- There's no preparation
you can go through
to go from making a room
of 300 people laugh
and then going home.
- Well, everybody who drinks
eventually starts talking about
drinking.
I mean, I bought a house
off of it.
- One time I was trying
to get on a plane.
They wouldn't let me.
They said I was too drunk
to get on a plane--
too drunk to get on the plane.
Do you know how wasted
you have to be
for someone to say,
"sir, you're just too drunk
to sit in a seat."
- Every time he went
on a binge,
he would feel terrible
about it.
Greg was a kind,
good person.
So when he screwed up,
he felt bad about it for days,
maybe weeks.
He hated hurting his children.
He hated hurting his wife.
He hated disappointing
people.
But that addiction
just had him so--
so badly that
he couldn't let go of it.
- I do a lot of immoral
shit, believe me.
But I lie about it,
and I cover it up...
Because I'm a Christian
and...
I have the decency to create
a false sense of well-being
in my home.
- The other craziest,
insidious thing
about being an addict is
is that
you trick everybody
around you into thinking
that this is how it is
for now.
And then you'll give everybody
a little window
of, like, "see, look.
It gets better."
- He was--had these moments
where he was clean
for long spells,
and he was super-healthy
and he was eating great.
- You know, you sort of thought,
okay, he's gonna become
a pathological vegetarian.
Just talking about how "okra
really is a magical vegetable."
- So everybody kinda thinks
he'll pull through this,
you know, but...
The body is fragile.
Like there's only
so many times
that you can cheat that.
- If anything, if you were
gonna get the call,
you were gonna be like,
giraldo just went nuts
in a, you know,
a juicer store.
And you gotta bail him out
'cause he stole some radishes.
- The rules for being
a gentleman
used to be so specific
and nice, you know?
- Somebody texted me saying.
"I just read on the Facebook
that Greg giraldo overdosed."
- I found out from, uh,
a text from tom papa.
- I found out from...
Well, it was all--
it was from the club owner
where he was performing.
- I found out,
and I didn't believe it,
because it was on Twitter.
[Laughs]
- Nick swardson texted me
and he said,
"what's going on
with Greg giraldo?"
And I said,
"what are you talking about?"
And he said,
"he's in a coma."
- And I just remember
being mad,
like, "come on, man,
what are you doing?
You're too smart for this
stuff," and enough, you know?
I didn't realize
how serious it was.
- When I went to go visit him,
I knew...You know.
I knew it was happening.
- I got it,
like a text message...
Just said, "Greg died."
Like typical...Nowadays,
you know, text message.
- When a comic leaves,
especially somebody
like Greg,
to me it's more than losing--
[Ahem]
Just like a friend
or somebody I knew.
It's like a part of you
because you know...
You know
what they went through.
I mean, you just--
you know that world, you know?
It's a very unique...
It's a very unique existence.
And it's one
that you share together.
Losing Greg was really...
Really, really hard.
- You know, I have nothing
but heartbreaking, now,
you know, loving, adoring
respectful, um,
feelings for him.
But I--there's also,
there's like a part of me
that just is like...
"What the [Bleep]?"
- I really do miss his, uh,
you know,
just knowing that he's there
and that I can call him.
You know,
like I just saw something
that I really wanna
tell Greg.
He'll think
this is hilarious.
And you know
there's nobody there
on the other end
of the phone.
- Any young comics coming up,
that's where you should
try to get to...
To try to be that real
on stage
and have observations
so acute and so original--
that's what you should
strive to be.
- India and Pakistan
have nuclear weapons.
How did they get
nuclear weapons?
They're--they're--
those are dirt poor countries!
Their armies don't even have
matching uniforms,
for Christ's sake.
They go to war,
they gotta call each other up:
[Accent]
"Wear something tough-looking."
- My life is so much
harder now
than it was when I was younger.
I wanna be [Bleep] now
all the time, you know?
But I can't,
because now I'm an alcoholic,
and I can't drink at all
'cause when I do,
I end up snorting crystal meth
off a switchblade
in some after-hours bar
thinking,
[bleep] I'm gonna be late
for my flight in the morning.
Except it's like 2:00
in the afternoon,
and the flight
was six weeks ago.
You're like, "holy [Bleep],
how did that happen?"
- You can't try to, uh...
Dwell on the dark side
of Greg, because...
It wasn't why we loved him.
We loved him because
he was so generous
with his laughter
and his spirit and his mind
and the fact that he shared
his talent with us
and the fact that
he made us all look smarter
because he was this
cool Harvard lawyer
who decided to be a comedian
and then brought that
to the roasts.
And it was just like
a great mind and a great spirit
and...I just try
to think of him as...
The star that he is.
- Look at the things
we all believe.
Every religion's
got crazy stuff.
I'm catholic.
The virgin Mary.
We have a whole religion
based on a woman
who really stuck
to her story.
You know...
- He really elevated comedy,
and, uh, he made me proud
to be a comedian.
You know?
You look at Greg and, um...
And he made comedy
like a...
Admirable profession.
- I'm...Not sure I'm gonna
see anybody as good as Greg
in my go-round.
And that's depressing to me.
Like any comedian,
I've managed to make this
about me.
[Laughs]
This isn't about Greg.
This is about...How...
I don't get to book
Greg anymore.
- I hope he ends up, uh...
Known for more than being
just really great on roasts,
because that was really like
just in his pinkie.
- Right after he passed away
it was always like insult-comic
known for the roasts.
That just so minimizes
what he did.
- Anybody that knew his work,
the insult-comic
is the last thing
that would come out of
your mouth.
- He wasn't mean.
He just wasn't a mean guy.
He was, uh...He just really
had a good heart.
Really had a good heart.
- I don't know
if God cares or not.
I think there's some power
that's driving the universe,
but it laughs
when we [Bleep] up.
It laughs when you
walk into a glass wall
or, you know, every time
you're driving home,
trying to get to the bathroom
real fast
and you're almost there,
and you shit your pants
just a little bit.
Somebody's watching that.
And laughing.
- He was really going out there
like he was fighting
for his life.
There's part of you that's
being sucked into a hole,
and it's the fight
to get out of it
that, uh, is where
the comedy comes from.
There are people that...
They lose that fight.
- I don't know where
it all went off the rails.
I mean, I tried.
Drug addiction, alcoholism--
that probably didn't help.
But I think maybe
if I had just--
you know what I probably
should have done, really,
looking back on it?
I should have probably, uh,
committed to show business.
Because it's not show fun.
It's show business.
[Laughter]
[Nada surf's imaginary friends]
♪
- ♪ hey, I'm bewildered
and writing myself notes ♪
♪ that say
if you fake happiness ♪
♪ then no one knows
♪ convince yourself
♪ and then
you've got it made ♪
♪ there'll be
no black of night ♪
♪ they'll just be
turned out lights ♪
- I start walking
toward the Mike,
and some guy goes,
"you suck! You suck!"
So I just snapped,
and I walked over,
I picked up a beer bottle,
and I poured beer all over him.
And he goes, "I'll [Bleep]ing
kill you--I'm a trained killer,"
and he gets upall the [Bleep]
bouncer guys grabbed him.
Then I get offstage, and he
had come back and wrote a note.
"You've been one of my
favorite comedians for years.
"I was actually hoping
for you
"to use your articulate ability
to slam me.
"The beer thing was reminiscent
"of the last bar fight
I'd been in,
"and honestly,
I don't think
"you could handle me
in that arena.
After your show,
I'd be happy to buy you a beer."
So he gives his name
and his phone number.