Subtitles by jojimoreau
We're closed.
Closed!
"Saul Goodman and Associates".
I'll see if he's in.
Please, hold.
Skyler White, calling.
Skyler White on the line.
Hey.
What the hell does she want?
He's nowhere to be found?
I called his condo. I called every
number I have for him.
I'm sure he's fine.
You're sure?
As in... you know where he is.
I'm not the man's keeper,
but Walt's a big boy.
He'll turn up.
Mr.Goodman, clearly something
is going on here.
I mean, why would he leave
his car in my driveway?
People carpool to work, right.
It's good for the environment.
He carpools?
He carpools to his job
at a meth lab.
Your breaking up, there.
I didn't quite catch that last...
You're a chatty cathy, today.
Do you know anything?
Anything, at all.
Please, I am looking for some help, here.
Look, Walter is fine.
I guarantee that a hundred percent.
100%...
You gotta passport, right?
Sous-titre par jojimoreau