[Speaking
fantasy language]
Seriously, her pussy
is, like, falling out.
Someone needs
to feed that thing
Before
it eats her shorts.
[Speaking
fantasy language]
What are you faggots
talking about?
No. You must
be mistaken.
We're not gay.
You choads were checking
out my ass, weren't you?
I-I-i wasn't.
Well, at least
I'm not gay.
Fuck you.
Come on. Stick it
in the hole! Yeah!
I got one more.
Bring it.
Bring it, baby.
Push it. Push it.
Let me see you
stick it.
Oh, that's
such a bulge.
What is that,
like, 100 pounds?
No, it's 40.
Oh, okay, I got it.
Come on.
Bring it down.
I got one more.
Let's see that bicep
bulge, baby.
Here we go.
Here we go. This is it.
I wanna see your bulge.
It's a flex-off.
Oh, my God.
Yeah. You feel that?
Oh!
Oh, man,
I felt your bulge.
Oh, God. My sweater's
all nasty.
[Clears throat]
What's up?
Yeah, one English lit
435 paper.
The freudian interpretation
of the bell jar.
Yeah, put it...
Put it there.
The football team
thanks you
For keeping me
on the field.
Our pleasure.
Which is why I went
ahead and got you guys
A little token
of my gratitude.
Call it
something special
For being
so contingent.
Yeah.
Uh, consistent.
Yeah, whatever.
[Laughs]
You're gonna love this.
We can pledge
next semester?
[Both laugh]
Oh, please. [Laughs]
Oh, lower it down.
Lower it down.
Oh, use my shit, bro.
Oh, my God.
That's what bros
are for, bro.
You got
that much game?
Oh, yeah.
Man, you shave your...
Dude, yeah, man.
Chicks dig it.
Oh, Jesus,
that was good.
Oh, my.
Where was I?
You were about to give us
$300 for the homework.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway, I thought,
like, this time,
Something
instead of money.
No way, man.
We said 300.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up, Frodo
and frodette.
Oh, burn!
Oh, yeah!
Anyway, yeah,
so I made some calls
And, like,
I could get you guys
Into what
promises to be...
Wait for it...
The best party
of the decade
Tomorrow night.
We're listening.
No, thanks.
Yeah.
No.
Right. Well, maybe
you guys have heard
Of the Hollywood
fucking hills.
Anyway, yeah, my boy's
working the door,
And I can't go
because, uh,
Well, I'm fucking
both of your moms
In the ass.
Oh, burn!
Oh, it burns so good.
Jk, bro, jk.
I mean, this is
probably going to be
The most pussy
there's ever been
In one place guaranteed.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
no b.S., bra.
Thanks for the offer,
but we want the money.
The money?
Okay. All right.
Hey, it's your call.
I mean, I just thought
maybe you guys,
Like, actually
wanted to get laid
And go to a party
Before you graduate...
Or die.
Oh, double burn.
Twice.
Yeah, have fun
staying at home
With your whack pack
of super nerd shut-ins.
Oh!
Doing whatever, man.
All right.
I'll get the cash.
Wait!
An opportunity like this
Only comes
once in a lifetime.
You let him gyp us
out of $300.
How's that
an opportunity?
It's time we stopped
playing video games.
We need to get some tail
physically, not digitally.
We speak elvish, okay?
Nobody even wants to be
In the same time zone
as us,
Let alone
a Hollywood party.
I'm not going, man.
No way.
Dude, don't take
your blue balls out on me
Just because your girlfriend
locked her pussy up in fort knox
And gave the key to Jesus.
Shut up, dude.
No, I'm not going alone.
You're going.
Well, then
we're not going,
And we're out
three bills,
So that's great.
Fine. I'll go with the clan.
The clan?
Yeah, let's see.
Kwan barely
speaks English,
Marcus' condition
doesn't allow him
to talk to girls,
Doug's restraining order
Canvasses
all of Los Angeles.
I'm pretty sure that
includes the hills.
Look, I'm sick and tired
Of you moping around
all the time.
You need to get laid.
Whatever.
No, no.
Just because my grandma
Has a better sex drive
than your girlfriend
Doesn't give you an excuse
to be a cock.
Forget about
my relationship.
Look, you're either
going solo,
Or you're not going
at all.
And if you do
decide to go,
I'm gonna laugh
my ass off
When you get kicked out.
Speak of the devil
and she appears.
And in her mormon
undergarments, no less.
Shut the fuck up, man.
No, dude. It's time
to draw a line in the sand
Or move on.
Your virginity's
not getting any younger.
You gonna finally
have the talk?
I've been trying.
Hey!
Hello, ed.
Hey.
Loser.
Goodbye, ed.
[Speaking fantasy language]
Yeah.
So I was wondering.
Maybe we could go
to nona's tonight
And hang out with their
youth group for a while.
I don't know, Kim.
What do you
not know about?
I think just
maybe we should talk.
Okay. What's the matter?
The same thing
that's been the matter
For the past
three and a half years.
The sex thing again?
Look, I know
it's a broken record.
It's just, I have to...
I have to
lay down the law.
The law?
I don't wanna go through
college a virgin.
You know what?
Just go back
to your porn stars
and your hand lotion.
Leave Emily Addison
out of this.
Ross, just met me
at youth group tonight.
Arghhhh!
Okay.
Maybe after, we could do some
under the clothes touching?
If you're good.
All right.
See you later.
Fuck!
Hey, get to work.
I'm not paying you
4.99 a minute
Just to get
to know you better.
Hey, Doug,
fuck you, okay?
If you weren't
our webmaster.
You'd probably be working at
a drive-through somewhere.
Burger boy.
Hey, there is
nothing in the law
That says I cannot spend
money where I work.
Now suck titty.
Okay, ladies,
let's slay us a dragon.
Kwan, sign on.
Kwan-ho,
let's go.
Ed: Marcus?
Artemis at the ready.
Let's go.
Look, I know I helped
your ass-burgers
To get into character,
balakas,
But lay off the r.P.
Hey, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
You're pro.
You don't need me to
talk you through this.
Fucking Doug.
Seriously, after
the game, dude.
Look, my dick
needs attention.
Fat ass.
Oh, you wanna play?
I can do that.
Time for a raid.
Shit.
Take that, bitch!
[Girls laughing]
Marcus!
Hear me! Hear me!
Hear you? Aye.
Yeah!
Aah! Ha ha ha!
Douglas j.K.
That was hella funny.
Whoo! And I recorded
that shit, too.
Upload. That's gonna get
so many fucking views.
Fuck this! I'm gonna kick
your fat fucking ass.
Ladies, I just did
an epic raid.
Let's do this.
Is it beating fast
for you, Gina?
Oh, yes, it is.
Get out here, snack boy.
You're about to get
a long overdue ass-whupping.
Oh!
That fat ass
will jerk off forever.
Lick my dick.
Yes, lick kwan's penis,
you dick.
[Speaking
fantasy language]
No.
You know, he's like
your little brother
That, like, never
gets laid, you know?
Oh... Oh...
Hey, what the fuck?
You're on the clock.
Not cool.
You should never
intentionally wipe a raid.
I'm gonna
report you to buck.
I'm the best webmaster
That
the porndarosa's got.
You gotta
be nice to me.
By the way, funboy,
Buck said that you
better get current
on your bill
Or he's gonna
fire your ass.
The last time
buck fired someone,
He literally fired
a shot at them.
At their ass.
Log out.
Hey, guys?
Guys?
Guys? Look, I'm just
fucking around, guys.
Come on.
Porno's off. Let's go.
Guys?
Damn that shit.
Whoo!
Play it cool, guys.
[Speaking broken English]
What was I thinking?
We don't belong here.
Marcus, need
a drink, man?
What do I do
to get one?
Turn around.
Ask the waitress.
Waitress:
What can I get you?
You don't need
to get me anything,
I don't think.
Wait, maybe you do.
He'll have
a Jack and coke.
Maybe we should
split up.
We won't attract
as much attention.
Good idea.
The museum.
Come on.
I got enough data
stored in my spank bank
To jerk off
for the next four years.
Are you blind?
We gotta get out of here.
They know we're not
supposed to be here.
We're gonna get
our asses kicked.
I'm fucking one of these
chicks tonight. You watch.
Get it through
your head, ed.
No chicks
are gonna touch us.
[Footsteps]
She's not wearing
any underwear.
I know.
Oh. [Giggles]
Oh, God.
She's doing coke.
[Snorts]
What does she want?
Oh, shit.
You scared me.
How did you get in here?
Oh, I, uh...
[Laughs]
It's okay, darling.
Listen, you kind of
caught me white handed here,
So you know
what that means.
I'll give you
a little bump.
No, thanks. I...
Come on. It's good.
Wait a minute. Wait.
You're mellony Adams.
You were in
thunder run 3.
Holy shit.
[Laughs]
That piece of shit?
Oh, my God.
You killed my sister.
And now you have to...
[Together]
Face my wrath!
Best catch phrase
ever. Yeah!
God, what...
No, no, no, no.
Listen, you try to be
typecast at my age,
And you take every
fricking loathing line
And you try to make it
into this... Something.
Except... Except...
For these lines.
[Laughs]
Oh, man.
Whoo! Damn!
Whoo-hoo!
Try it.
It's really good.
Whoo!
It's so good,
It make you wanna move,
doesn't it? Whoo!
No, it hurts.
[Laughs]
Listen,
what's your name?
Ed.
Oh, yeah? Ed?
I know
we just met, ed,
But would you like
to drink
A little champagne
with me?
Whoo! Yeah!
You don't belong here,
asshole.
I beg your pardon?
He's talking to you,
poindexter.
Look, we're gonna
throw you the fuck out
Unless you do
something for us.
Like what?
Kind of hot
in here, though.
I think I'm overdressed.
Ed, could you help me
with that, please?
Oh, that's no problem.
No problem.
Here we go.
Wow, my friends are never
gonna believe I did this.
This is fucking insane.
Well, it's good
to get a little crazy
sometimes, darling.
Yeah. This may be
a little off subject,
But you haven't heard
of any of those
new cell phones
That have cameras
and record videos.
I don't know.
I must have one.
Oh, shut up and grab
my rocking tits.
That's what I call
a catch phrase.
Whoo!
Whoa!
Whoo! [Giggles]
This is gonna be fun.
See that sizzling hot
blonde chick over there?
The one next to
that huge mma looking
motherfucker.
Affirmative.
Here's what
you're gonna do.
You're gonna walk your
puny little ass over there,
And you're gonna
ask her,
Can I get
all up in that labe?
Labe? Are you referring
To that lady's
labia majora?
Hey, we call it labe
for short.
Kwan.
Oh, yes!
Yes, right there.
Oh! Oh, yes.
Holy shit, you better
be recording this.
What?
Nothing.
[Moaning]
Oh, yes, ed.
Teach my pussy.
Sex me, ed.
Sex-ed.
Teach my pussy.
Yeah!
* you know you gals,
you kind of sexy *
* don't let no man tell you
that you ain't nothing *
* they're trying
to abuse you *
* and make you feel like... *
* you can do way, way
better than that *
* you can do way, way... *
Oh, man, Ron's gonna
fuck that kid up.
No doubt.
Um... Hello. Hi.
Um, those gentlemen
over there
Are asking me
to ask you, um...
If I could
get up in your labe.
Excuse me?
If I could
get up in your labe.
But I think they were
referring to you labia majora
Or the fold of skin
on the outsides of your vagina
Encasing the vulva.
Oh, my fucking God.
Ron, did you hear
What he was just
telling me?
What's up, babe?
What?
Aah!
* from there, you can do
way, way better than that *
* you can do way, way
better than that *
Pshht.
What a dick.
Motherfucker!
Shit, is that mellony Adams?
Aah!
Oh, my God.
I fucked mellony Adams,
And I have proof.
Best night
of my fucking life.
Oh, my God. Wait until
Doug hears about this.
Roll up the window, man.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God. Marcus needs
to go to a hospital.
You okay?
Did I get to see
her labia?
[Speaking
broken English]
I deem the knockout
to be worth it.
Dudes, we hung out
with actual girls.
I'm glad you're okay.
He's okay.
He's okay. Whoo!
Best 300 bucks
we've ever spent.
Epic win!
Epic won.
* me and my wang *
* just hanging out
on the porch *
* drinking a beer *
* hand down my pants
and doing my thing *
* I'm drinking a beer
and playing with my wang *
* whoo hoo-hoo
hoo-hoo-hoo *
[Imitating guitar solo]
Oh, where the fuck
you guys go?
Oh, nowhere,
Except the most
epic party in history.
Bam! Go ahead.
Take a look.
Wait. Is that...
Is that...
Mm-hmm.
Mellony motherfucking Adams.
Maybe you've seen her before
in every movie ever made.
I hope you enjoyed
your masturbatory evening
In solitude, Douglas.
Okay, fuck you guys.
Why didn't you
invite me?
Next time
don't ruin our raid.
Maybe you'll get an invite.
Oh, I've gotta
go to sleep.
I think I have
a concussion,
And I'm extremely
inebriated.
Me, too.
Good night, dick.
All right,
you guys got me.
I'm a douchebag.
I'm sorry...
That you forgot
your fucking phone.
Oh!
You know,
it'd be a goddamn shame
If this video were
to somehow make its way
To the worldwide web.
Holy fucking shit. Did
last night really happen?
Yes, it really happened.
I boned mellony Adams?
Yep.
And kwan was there, too?
I'm trying to eat.
Yep. I got it all
on my phone.
Look, you guys can watch
it back a million times
if you want,
But it has to stay
between us, okay?
We can get into
a shitstorm of trouble
If anybody sees it.
Fuck that. I want
the world to know
what a stud I am.
I boned
mellony Adams.
It doesn't get any
non-gayer than that.
I'd rather bang
Halle Berry.
Britney! Britney!
Or eva Mendez.
Emily Addison.
You guys are just jealous
that I dabbled the dipstick
In some Hollywood
cream-sashine.
Okay, ed, come on.
Seriously.
Think about it, okay?
We only got into
that party
Because of
Delaney's buddy.
We weren't
really invited,
So technically
we can get arrested
for trespassing.
Not to mention, we kind of
filmed a sex tape
without consent,
So there's always that.
What good
is bonking a babe
If I can't tell anybody?
It's enough
that we know, right?
Oh, my God.
It is you. Sex-ed.
And you're kwan-zai.
Oh, and you poor baby.
Got your jaw broken
Without having
any of the fun.
Actually, it's just a contusion
of the zygomatic bone
With some secondary bruising
on the left mandible.
Whatever. [Laughs]
Well, we look forward
To seeing more of you
in action, stud.
Come on.
All: Fucking Doug!
Hey! Hey! Hey, dude.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey, you!
Hey, sweetie.
What the heck, Ross?
You don't answer
my texts now?
When? Oh, nona's.
Yeah, nona's
I waited there for two hours
Looking like a jerk.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it tonight.
I have study group.
I promise I'll
make it up to you
sometime, okay?
Num-num!
Bye.
Num-num.
Dude, no one
turns me away like that.
Dude.
You wanna
try it again?
Yeah, let's get back.
Oh, man, did you
moisturize this morning?
Yeah, every morning.
Of course I did.
[Moaning]
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Tickle, tickle, tickle.
Hold up. Hold up.
Doug, bend over so I can
burn your fucking balls.
Oh, hey! Hey, man!
She was about to stick
her whole foot
in her mouth.
You get on that
pornderosa site right now
And take down that video.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You post last night's
sexcapade
On a fucking porn site
you work for.
[Clapping]
You figure that all out
by yourself, Sherlock?
But once again,
you're only half right.
You see, a video
of that great quality
Deserves its own website
So that everyone can
see it in all its glory,
And I would hate
to deprive people
Of that now. [Laughs]
I'm gonna shove that mouse
right down your fucking piehole
If you don't
take it down right now.
I'm afraid you douchebags
are a little too late.
Check it out.
You're an overnight
celebrity, my friend.
Over three and a half
million hits
and counting.
Holy shit. Awesome!
No, not awesome.
Take it down!
Okay.
That's it.
Get rid of this.
No, no, no. I'm never
gonna get that kind
of pussy again.
Guys. Guys. Guys!
The God damn cat's
out of the bag.
This thing is viral.
[Knock on door]
Hey, must be some
of my fan club.
Answer it, Marcus.
Got to let them
come to me.
Like that, satchmo?
'Cause vinny here,
He can serve up sex
real quick.
All right, everybody
over here now.
Sit down. Come on.
Sit down!
Hmm.
I don't know, Danny.
Which one do you think
is the mastermind?
It sure as hell
ain't Jackie Robinson
over here.
Or jabba the hut.
Or wang chung.
Maybe...
Just maybe...
It's the little prick
who fucked my client
On the Internet.
Maybe...
Just maybe...
The prick didn't know
that fucking my client
Was like
you're fucking me!
You all right?
You sure?
Where are my manners?
Huh?
Was I raised
in the woods?
Mm-mmm.
No.
Well...
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Benny silva.
I'm a talent manager,
And my client
is mellony Adams.
You had sex with her
against her will,
Recorded it and put it
on the Internet.
It wasn't against her will.
She totally
wanted my rod.
No speaking out of turn.
Shut the fuck up!
I could have all of you
arrested for trespassing,
Making pornography against
the will of my client,
Defamation.
The list
goes on and on.
Hey, man, it was them.
I had nothing
to do with it.
I wasn't even there.
Come on, brother.
I had nothing
to do with it...
Shut up!
Then why was it uploaded
From your
fucking computer?
[Squeals]
Nobody likes a snitch.
And I sure as hell
don't want to see
A group of fine young
men like yourselves...
Going to jail.
So that's why
I'm offering you
Another option.
Whatever it is,
we'll take it. Anything.
You are going to pay me
a half a million dollars
In the next 30 days.
Or you're
going to end up
A bunch of pretty little
jailhouse bitches,
Dead in a ditch,
Or both.
[Urinating]
Accidents happen.
Oh, God,
we're so fucked.
It's not so bad.
I mean, half a million
sounds like a lot,
But there's five of us.
We could donate blood.
Or a kidney.
Black market kidneys
Sell for an average
of $20,000.
Unless you got
20 extra kidneys stashed away,
That ain't gonna work.
We could rob a bank.
Rob a bank
to not go to jail.
Yeah, that's brilliant.
Yeah, hey,
at least I'm coming up
with ideas here.
It's your great ideas
that got us into this
in the first place.
You could have
stayed at home
with your girlfriend
And not had sex again.
No, fuck you.
Fuck you.
No, fuck kwan.
Actually, I'm the one
getting screwed here.
I'm just saying.
Technically, I've sustained
the most serious injuries.
Shut up. Everyone
shut up please.
Damn, if we were chicks,
We could strip our way
to a half million
no problem.
I'd make extra 'cause I
wouldn't shave my bush.
What? It's a great way
to half a mil.
Why not just go all
the way and make a porn?
You could star in
hot and hairy volume 69.
That's it!
[Chuckles] 69.
You gonna grow a vagina?
No, dude,
We can't strip our way
to a half million,
But we can
screw our way to it.
We've just got to make
more sex tapes.
That's the complete
opposite
Of what
we should do.
Dude, dude,
all we have to do
Is find some willing
has-been celebrities
And convince them
to have sex on camera.
It's insane exposure.
All anyone's been
talking about all day
Is mellony Adams.
Just the pervs
on campus, man.
Not actually.
I mean, she's trending
pretty hard.
Top five searches
on the Internet.
Okay. Why can't they
just make their own tapes?
I mean, why
would they need us?
'Cause we've got
a proven track record.
Our video has...
17 million.
17 million hits.
Think about it.
Exposure.
I don't know.
Doug can set up
the websites.
We'll watch
the cash roll in.
I just...
You got
any better ideas?
I didn't think so.
Where can we find
a chick
That's desperate enough
To bang her way
back to fame?
I know of a venue
that will have
Several of those
female individuals
in attendance currently.
There's shelby Jones.
She played
a valkyrie berserker
On blood and breath
swords,
Seasons two
through five.
Dude, I'll totally
ragnarok her world.
Hi, Mrs. Jones.
I really like it
in episode 312
When you beheaded
the evil hydro
After drinking
the invincibility potion.
Thanks, kid.
So you want
an autograph or...
Oh, will you have
sexual intercourse
With my friend ed
and allow us to videotape it
So that we can make money
and pay off someone
who's blackmailing us?
Christ. You little shits
get weirder every year.
Sorry, sorry.
He's just joking.
He's just acting out a scene
in episode 478.
You know, when
the evil prince comes...
That's crazy.
There's no episode...
[Coughs] Shut up.
It'll be a tremendous
for your career.
Just let ed and I
do it, okay?
You got to find
the right chick,
One who's washed up.
Desperate, but still
kind of hot.
Someone with a bit
of a sexy background.
Forget it, man.
This isn't going to work.
Let's just
go pack for jail.
Bingo!
[Chuckles]
Jillian baines.
Lieutenant commander zolara
On orient five
seasons one through four.
Zolara was a completely
realistic android
With six times the intensity
of normal human strength
And telescopic vision.
She died saving
the starship hyperion
From a quantum singularity.
Fascinating.
I've heard about her.
The show's creators
killed her character off
After some nude photos
of her surfaced...
Which I still own,
by the way...
Plus she is a total drunk.
Never showed up
to the set on time.
Ahh... Yeah.
What are you doing?
Excuse me?
Look at all these
dried up old hags
Trying to cling
to the last bit of money
They can make for a job
they did 10 years ago.
But you...
You're in your prime.
You just need
the right opportunity.
Are you trying
to sell something?
Because I can
call security, all right?
You got to register
three weeks in advance
If you wanna be
a vendor here.
The only thing
I'm trying to sell you
Is a chance to
reinvigorate your career.
Do you have an Uncle
That's the head
of a studio or something?
Better. I'm the studio,
the agent,
And the costar.
You ever heard
of a little thing
called the Internet?
Are you retarded?
Like a fox.
Did you see
that little video
With mellony Adams?
Yeah. It's blowing up
everywhere.
It's on tmz,
entertainment tonight, extra.
Everybody's
talking about it.
I would kill
for that kind of coverage.
You don't have to kill.
I'm the guy
in that video.
You?
Me.
You know they're calling you
sex-ed on the blogs.
Oh, yeah.
So you're offering...
A refresher course.
Hmm.
All right, I'll fuck you.
[Chuckles]
But it's gonna take
a lot of liquid courage.
Show's over.
Aw, damn it. It's not
the right mount.
Tripod shots are 75%
steadier than handheld,
And that number
goes up to 350%
For shots zoomed in
more than four times.
Shut up.
Get the lube.
Ooh.
You know, if ed can't do
this whole thing by himself.
I can always jump in
and take over, you know.
Sorry, fat-ass.
This is a one-man show.
Just get
the website together, okay?
All right,
come on, guys.
She's gonna be here
any second. Let's go.
Hello.
So...
Who wants to fuck
the hottest robot
in this quadrant? Huh?
Huh? You?
Ooh.
Somebody's
ready to launch.
Over here.
Over here!
Oh, yes.
There's my stud.
So you gonna fuck me
like mellony?
Are you?
Hell, yeah.
Action!
I don't wanna film this.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
My mission is to
find out what happens
When you stick
your probe balls deep.
[Laughs]
Party time, space girl.
Yeah. Huh?
Okay.
[Laughs] Ooh,
robot on robot sex
Is hot and heavy.
Oh, yeah, baby. Ooh.
I was sent to study
The sexual
reproduction rituals
Of your species.
Huh? I'm
a fucking android.
I don't have a species.
Excuse me, but
technically speaking,
Androids
can build other androids
And therefore be
classified as a species.
Get out of the shot.
All right. All right.
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
I was about to insert
My hard disk
into your v-drive unit.
[Moaning]
Oh, God. [Chuckles]
Next mission, you're
gonna drill for oil
On the moon. [Laughs]
Negative. Negative.
Negative.
No, no. We are going
to stick to cave exploration
On this expedition.
Fine. Yeah,
give it to me.
[Moaning]
You've penetrated.
You've penetrated
my force field.
You're gonna have
to make a direct hit
To make me cum. Yeah.
Stay on target.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Ohh...
Oh, God. Look at
the size of that thing.
Kwan-zai!
[Splat]
Hey, Ross, it's Kim.
Uh, just calling
to say hello.
So where have you been,
silly goose?
I've just, you know, been
worried sick about you,
And, um... All right,
well, just call me
When you're not
too busy, I guess.
Bye.
Arghhhh!
Holy fucking shit.
Up to 17 million hits
in only three days.
Unbelievable.
Taking into account
the exponential nature
of these videos
With a minimal
coefficient of 16.3,
And now with two videos,
If you refresh the screen,
We should have
17,274,000 hits now.
That mans with
the advertising revenue
Growing at a rate
of 14.43 per 300k,
That we will be able to
come up with the money.
We just need to keep
producing videos.
We need to find
some new girls.
Where do we go
to find them?
Uh, guys.
I don't think that's
gonna be a problem.
[Laughs]
We need
to hang out more, Ross.
I feel like I haven't
seen you in forever.
Yeah, I know.
I've just been really busy
With studying, school,
and stuff, you know.
Yeah, well, you should
come to my study group.
I think it would really
help you concentrate.
Like, I really don't see
how you get anything done
Living in that house
with a bunch of losers.
Ross?
Have you heard
anything I just said?
Huh? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Studying.
We can do that sometime.
Yeah, look, I gotta
get back to work...
Uh, studying for work.
Okay.
I gotta go, okay?
Bye.
Yeah.
Uh, Ross?
Isn't it that way?
Yeah. [Laughs]
Guess so.
Thank you.
Okay, so who's
up to bat?
Former reality TV
personality Debbie Ballard.
She's the one
that ate that bull cock
To win a challenge.
Sorry, kwan. She's actually
got a special request.
Nope. Black.
Classic mud shark.
Marcus.
I can't.
Sure, you can.
It's easy.
In, out, in, out,
in, out.
I can't do it.
It's gonna be outside,
So it'll help you
with your claustrophobia.
We're actually going
for some better
production value.
Seriously,
I don't think I can.
You can
and you will.
Okay.
Good.
Better dust off
your cock, knave.
You're on deck.
No, not happening.
No way.
Yes way.
You know how much
money we'd make
If you lost
your cherry on camera?
Virgins are
big business, dude.
Like, I don't care.
Look, I don't mind
helping you guys out,
But I will never, ever
have sex on camera, okay?
Shut the fuck up, you two.
We're gonna be late
for Marcus' scene.
It's time to build
the course.
[Gulp]
[Whistle]
Challenger,
in order to win this,
You must up that bucket
with water.
That doesn't sound hard.
You have 30 seconds
While I shoot at you
with a paintball gun.
Go!
Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Oh, God!
Move it, you loser.
I'm coming.
Move it!
I'm coming. Oh, God.
I'm coming.
Come on!
Come on, you pussy!
Hey!
I'm coming.
Four!
One!
You did it!
[Panting]
Come claim your prize.
Okay.
Time to go head first.
Yeah!
Whoa.
That's it.
Munch away, brother.
Like mashed potatoes
and gravy.
Oh! Oh, yeah.
[Gasping]
I can't breathe.
My pussy's got
all the oxygen you need.
Actually, there's
only 6.8 ounces of oxygen
In the average vagina.
That would last
a man my size
About 12 uninterrupted
minutes theoretically.
Shut up!
Yeah! Yeah!
Aah! I'm gonna blow!
What?
I'm a squirter. Yeah!
[Splat]
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
My inhaler.
So is she.
[Groaning]
My inhaler!
Oh, my God.
That's that guy.
That's ed.
I heard he boned
raven Simone.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And tea-bagged Meg Ryan.
Fuck, yeah.
[Laughs]
I mean, you got to
make sure to moisturize.
It's the most
important thing.
Dude, I only use lotion
for when I masturbate.
Dude, you're not
even capitalizing
On what lotion can do.
I mean, dude,
check out my muscles.
Let me get some of that.
Get some.
Get on that.
Why would you even be
waiting on anything?
I mean, just do it.
Right?
So soft and...
Ed!
Ed, dude!
What's up, brah?
Come here.
Yeah, bring it in, ed.
Bring it in.
Yeah, what's...
Hey. Oh, dude,
You should come
by the house tonight.
Oh, man,
it's going to be a rager.
Oh, man, we're
gonna have kegs,
Drugs. [Laughs]
Sluts. Sluts.
Definitely sluts.
All right,
Who's the next contestant
on "fuck me famous"?
We're still getting a shit ton
of fucking emails.
I just got one
from a Liz Cooper.
Liz Cooper played
coach shearson
In seasons two and three
of hoops high.
Okay.
Uh, Katie Mayer.
Katie Mayer played
janey the secretary
On the first season
of Chicago sons.
Holy shit.
She just sent us a nice little
photo of herself here.
Look at that ass.
Marcus!
Ross?
Asperger.
Uh, Marcus?
You're acting
really weird today.
Did you
take your medicine?
What, nothin'.
Oh, hi.
Hey, babe,
what's going on?
Hi.
Uh, what's going
on here, Ross?
Oh,
just hangin' out.
Bein' dudes.
Looking at dirty porno
on the Internet.
[Laughter]
Jk, no we're not.
We're playing card games
and such.
[Laughs]
Oh, well, well.
What have we here?
Looks like our friend
Jillian bane
Just got a series regular gig
on the new CSI: Jersey.
She's going to be playing
A junkie hooker-
slash-police informant.
Huh. Wow.
She went from not working
for the past six years
To getting a series regular
gig on a big network show.
Wonder what
caused that, Ross.
What?
I wouldn't know.
I don't know.
Yeah, um...
Ross,
can I talk to you outside?
Of course.
Dick.
Hey, if I'm not
getting laid, nobody is.
So, uh,
what's going on?
You're not
answering my texts,
Your phone goes
straight to voicemail.
I mean, if I didn't
know any better,
It's like you're
trying to avoid me.
No. I'm not...
I don't know.
I've just been really
busy with, you know,
School and studying
and other stuff.
But, hey,
You know you're the most
important thing to me, right?
Right?
I'm sorry I've been
a bit distant lately.
Um, I was on the hill
just now and I saw ed,
And, you know,
palling around
With, um, Delaney mulroy
and, um...
Anyways, he gave me
a letter for you,
Told me
to give it to you.
Really?
Ed:
"Ross dog, sex ed here.
"I'm taking a little vacation
from fucking on camera.
"Me and Delaney
are going to slay
"Some sorority gash
all weekend.
"But the show must go on.
"We've only got
200k left to make.
"So make sure
to shoot a few videos.
"Man up, brah!
Sex ed, out."
Oh, fuck.
Hey,
watch your language.
Sorry.
Hey, I'm gonna skip
my third period psych class.
Do you want to
go grab a bite to eat?
Yes.
Fuck, yeah.
Me, too.
I'm starving.
Get some. Get some.
Yeah.
Come on, dawg.
Kill it.
I can do this.
I'm the game master.
I got this.
Oh, come on.
[All three talking]
Hi, guys.
Is now a good time?
Well, can't
you see that I am bus...
[Laughs]
Ahh.
Well...
Hi.
Ohh.
Isn't this special? Huh.
We got
the whole fucking band here.
Ross and the skid marks.
Now, you...
Got some
really big, hairy balls.
To keep taking advantage
Of those desperate girls
on videotape.
No, no, no,
Danny.
Uh, "Mr. silver."
Mr. silver, look, they...
They're contacting us,
okay?
We've got all these low-rent
actresses emailing us.
[Laughing] Now,
Mr. silver, he's lying,
Your majesty.
I saw Ross talk
to a girl. I did.
Jillian banes
at the comic convention.
I know. I know.
Now, that drunk bitch's
career ended years ago.
She was already dead
in the water.
Nobody was ever going to
cast her again in anything.
Not until
the whole world sees
Her getting her cyborg
bush plowed online.
It's kind of weird,
I know.
Mmm...
So that's
why you shit stains
Are going to keep making your
videos with my new clients.
[Laughing]
Oh, there's
no need to worry, fellas,
There's enough
to go around, okay?
Yes.
And the muff scuba diver,
You're going to
get another chance.
[Laughing]
Ichiro,
Get ready to get back
in the game, son.
And even your dungeon master's
high-cholesterol ass
Is getting
on the pussy treadmill.
What does that even mean?
Oh, yeah.
And your cameraman,
He'll have
to dip his wick, too.
That's a fucking promise.
The chat room trolls
Are suckers
for lily white virgins.
Ross?
Oh, now,
what do we have here?
Hi. Kim.
Mmm. I'm Ross'
old friend, Danny.
You're very,
very attractive.
Are you an actress?
No.
Have you done
any acting, uh...
Online?
Look, that's enough.
Oh, she's
more than enough.
I'd really love to
stay and chat a while,
But I must get going.
Kim, huh?
I'll be in touch.
You start tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Start what?
What? Uh...
What was that?
Uh, we don't
really know him.
He's just one
of Ed's friends.
He seems like
a real slime ball.
Okay, can we go eat now?
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Holy shit, man.
Was he for real?
He's trying to Jack us
for our fucking sex tapes.
With his own docket of
unemployed entertainers.
This could be bad.
Never thought
I'd say this, guys,
But I think
we need ed back.
Guys,
I peed my pants again.
She's here.
Who is it?
It's Meg lingbren,
The actress that
played Natalie Bernard
On the show sin city p.D.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that show.
Holy shit.
Oh, my God,
is it that showgirl?
Uh, no.
The hot detective?
No.
What?
Who is...
It's not the...
It's the chief.
How's it goin'?
So, which one of you boys
is gonna fuck me?
Answer, answer.
Ed, answer,
answer, answer.
[Frat boys chanting]
Ed! Ed! Ed! Ed!
[Cell phone ringing]
Ed! Ed! Ed! Ed! Ed!
Sex Ed's phone!
Ross: Ed!
No, no, no,
this is Delaney!
This is Delaney!
Sex Ed's busy pounding
some brew dogs!
Put him on the phone,
Delaney! It's important!
All right,
all right.
Shit!
There's only
one thing to do, guys.
What?
Put 'em up.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Oh! God damn it!
Okay, okay, okay.
One, two, three.
Motherfucker.
Yeah, okay.
One, two, three.
Yes.
Take all the time
you need, man.
It's okay.
It's all right.
[Somber music playing]
Son, it must be late there.
What's the matter?
They're with you always
in your heart.
Through
the most troubling times.
Kwan.
[Thud]
[Slow-motion shout]
[Shouts]
It's our biggest hit yet.
I guess people like seeing you
have giant knee-shooter jugs
Block out the sun.
This isn't cool, man.
I mean, look at kwan.
Now, we've gotta
call the cops.
Impossible. Marcus,
how much are we short?
$171,453.44.
We fucked our way
into the tunnel,
And now we
can see some light.
Yeah, whatever
you say, sex ed.
What's that
supposed to mean?
[Boing]
Wait. D-bag silver
just emailed us.
We got another client.
Who is it?
Oh, this
should be interesting.
Says here plushy fetish.
I got this.
Yeah, yeah totally.
Show us how it's done,
sex ed.
I will, virgin.
Fuck me, bucky!
Fuck me!
Yeah! Yeah,
dick me, bucky.
Dick me, dick me!
I'm gonna dick you!
Bucky, fuck me!
Oh, she's got
some serious issues.
She played
cheerleader Abby Collins
On lakeway heights
for six seasons.
After the show was canceled,
she played another cheerleader,
Darcy cummings, on thousand
palms for four seasons.
Yeah, I love it when
you talk dirty to me.
Talk dirty to me.
Okay, um...
You like bucky, bitch?
No!
No?
No, say it like bucky.
Say it like bucky.
[High-pitched voice]
You like bucky, bitch?
No, chirp
like a chipmunk!
Chirp, motherfucker!
Chirp!
[Chirping]
Yeah! Yeah!
[Laughing]
Dude.
[Both laugh]
Yeah!
Fuck me, bucky.
[Knock on door]
Fuck me! Yeah!
Yeah, dick me, bucky!
Dick me! Dick me!
[Gasps]
Ross, Kim's at the door.
Ross, Kim's at the door!
Cover for me.
What?
I'm not here.
No.
All right, get going.
Hey, guys.
Hi, Kimberly.
Where's, uh...
What happened to you?
Okay, whatever.
Where's Ross?
He's not here right now
in this room.
Not right now.
We'll tell him you
stopped by.
What are you wearing?
Black people clothes.
[Girl moaning]
What was that?
We are performing a live action
role playing exercise.
Yeah. [Chirping]
[Both chirping]
Okay, okay,
you guys have fun.
Tell Ross to call me.
Okay.
Bye.
Oh, God, I almost had
a fucking heart attack.
[Laughing]
Dude, brah!
Oh, man.
Way to pound it, sex ed.
Yeah.
What a freak.
And I think I almost
threw my back out, too.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, my God. Kim
almost busted us, man.
Oh, my God.
If she would've known
I was in here,
She'd have grabbed a knife
and killed us all.
She would have.
Hey, there,
chirpy chippers.
Where the hell do
you think you're going?
I wasn't done with you.
Sorry, babe.
This squirrel's busted
his last nut for the night.
You're a goddamn chipmunk,
not a squirrel.
Hey, babe!
Oh! I've missed you.
So you're here.
Give me a kiss, num nums.
How you doing?
So you're here.
Yeah.
Um, I was just...
I was coming back 'cause I
want to give you a note.
Well, I'm here now.
You can just
tell me what it says.
Well, no. I think you'd
really like what's in it.
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay.
[Laughs]
Oh. Oh, it...
Yeah.
Yeah?
You know,
I think it's about time.
Yeah?
Yeah, me... me, too.
Look really, me, too. I...
But not now.
Like, not here, I mean...
Maybe somewhere special...
Hey, Ross, you want
to be my sex chipmunk?
Oh, hi. I'm Mandy,
And I love girl-on-girl.
I don't know her.
Really? Kim!
What's her problem?
Atten hut!
Ten hut,
general Dougie, sir.
At ease, ladies.
Now drop and give me 69.
Oh, yes general Dougie,
sir.
Right after I examine
corporal Gina here
For any detonative
devices.
Corporal Gina,
Are you hiding any
illicit contraband?
No, sir! Ma'am.
[Laughs]
I think you have to be
court-martialed
For bad, bad,
bad behavior!
Oh, yeah. Let me pull
out my soldier.
[Laughs]
Aah!
Oh. Oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No other male soldiers
in this, all right?
Don't ask. Don't tell.
God damn it, Doug, I'm
cutting off your credit.
Buck.
Hi, sir.
God damn it.
You owe me $7,000 worth
of Jack-off time.
I'm not gonna extend
no more credit to you, boy.
Buck, I'm good for it.
Oh, I know you are.
In fact, I got a little
proposition for you.
Lexa, Gina...
[Laughs]
Get on out of here.
Aw!
Bye, Dougie.
I've seen your website.
I know what you're doing.
The one thing I don't
understand, though,
Is you work
for www.Pornderosa.Cum.
And your deal memo stipulates
that anything you do
In terms of content producing
Belongs to me
along with all assets.
What?
Yep. I want a piece
of the action.
Doug, I'm willing
to let all this slide
If you just partner with me
on a little side project.
I'm listening.
I wanna do a live,
pay-per-view, Internet fuck fest
With that young virgin, Ross.
One night, one hump,
$1 million.
Buck, I don't know
if he will.
He's a pussy.
He's scared
to fuck on camera.
Every single one
of your movies
Has over 25 million views.
If we can get that young,
sweet, virgin boy
To pop his cherry and sell
the live stream for $5.00 a pop,
That's
a whole bunch of clams.
I think
you can do the math.
Okay, buck, let me
get back to you on that.
Oh, and, buck?
Can you please put
lexa and Gina back on?
I mean I've
already gotten started.
I gotta finish up.
You fucking pervert!
Thanks, buck.
Now where
were we, ladies?
[Knock on door,
dialing cell phone]
Ed:
Open up, brah! Come on!
Go away!
[Line ringing]
You've gotta talk to me,
home slice.
You're always
the problem, ed.
You're talking crazy.
Just let me in.
[Cell phone rings]
Come on, man.
She was bound to find out
what you were doing.
[Bottle clanks in sink]
Yeah, but I wanted to explain
it to her myself, man,
When the time was right.
When's the time right
to tell your girlfriend
That you're
making porn videos
To pay off a psychopath?
You mean tell her that you
are making porn videos.
Look I may be the star,
But we're in this
together, brother.
No. No, you dragged me
into this shit.
Now she's gone.
Maybe
that's a good thing.
What?
Look, Kim's a nice girl.
Too nice.
She's held your cock
hostage for four years.
Maybe secretly you
wanted to get caught.
Now you're free.
Being free sucks.
You just gotta
give it a try.
No. I want her back.
You're too much
of a goddamn pussy!
I give up.
It's too much work.
You ever stop to think if I
wanted your help, ed? Huh?
You ever think that maybe some
of us are happy the way we are?
Some of us don't have
to go around showing off
Every single second
of our lives,
'Cause we don't
actually hate ourselves.
Fuck you.
You're jealous.
Jealous of what, ed?
Jealous of you fucking
drunk sleazebags
And chicks who
are borderline retarded?
Yes! Exactly.
God, dude, look at you.
I don't even know who
you are anymore, asshole.
Who are you calling
asshole, cock?
[Both whining]
[Squealing]
Unh!
Ow!
Oh! Aah! Aah!
Ow! You're a whore!
Aah! Unh!
Jerk!
I'm sorry.
All right, brother.
Let's see how well
you do without me.
Fuck you!
I'm done with all of you
for real this time!
What is the problem?
Oh, Ed's out for good.
So, yeah, we pretty much
have to come up
With the rest
of the cash on our own.
What are we short?
We need to generate $98,000
in the next four days.
So according
to my calculations,
We need to
make two more movies,
And that should
put us over the mark.
Okay, okay.
Uh, well, you're gonna
have to do it, Marcus.
'Cause kwan's...
I respectfully decline.
I did my part, and I'm
traumatized for life.
Trying to get the taste
of female ejaculate
Out of your mouth
Is like trying to get
skunk spray off clothing.
Brush it off, man.
Doesn't matter.
You're the only one.
Frankly, I believe
ed has a point.
You're the only qualified
person yet to contribute,
And now you're single.
And factoring in
your virginity,
Which increases
the coefficient by 4.2.
And if we carry over the 8,
then that's... whoa.
What does it say?
What does it mean?
According
to my calculations,
I believe that
if you were to perform,
We will only
need to make one movie.
That's impossible.
Oh! What about Doug?
Yeah, tell kwan to get
Our next starlet
on the phone.
Hey, wake up.
[Slap]
Ow. What...
Doug, you're up.
What?
You're up, man.
It's your turn to make a video.
We've got Anna Williams
for you.
Who?
Uh, that chick that fell
down a well 20 years ago.
You have
to have sex with her.
Me?
Yeah.
Oh, no. I'm, uh...
I'm all tapped out.
Dude, what?
No, you've been waiting
for this forever.
Come on, get up.
You've gotta
give me a warning,
Or I'm gonna take
care of myself first.
Besides, it's 3:00
in the afternoon.
Just get ed to do it.
I'll take care
of the next one.
Ed's not available.
Okay, you do it.
No.
[Sighs]
Okay, fine.
Oh, I got it.
Perfect.
Couple of these
will do the trick.
Pop 'em quick.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Isn't one enough of those?
Better safe than sorry.
Mmm!
I wonder how long it takes
for these things to kick in.
Oh!
All right, whatever.
Let's go.
All right.
Come on. Come on.
Oh!
I don't feel
too good, man.
My heart is
beating really fast.
You'll be fine.
The side effects
include diarrhea,
Flushing of the face,
heart palpitations,
Stroke and coma.
Like I said,
you'll be fine.
Go get her.
Go for it.
Hey, come on over here.
Hi.
Whoo!
[Groaning]
Mmm!
[Laughing]
Whoo!
[Laughing and coughing]
You okay?
I'm... I'm good.
Ahh.
Okay, good.
[Coughing]
You just relax.
Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Mmm!
Ooh! Do
you like what you see?
Ooh, yeah. Spank me.
Yeah.
What am
I supposed to do now?
Shit! Doug.
Doug, wake up.
Don't clap. Don't clap.
He's still functioning.
He's good. He's just passed out.
It says
we only have to worry
If his erection lasts
more than four hours.
Eww. Are you
sure he's not dead?
No, keep going.
Okay. Okay.
Should
I take his pants off?
Yeah, sure.
Take 'em down.
Get comfortable.
Come on, big boy.
Ooh!
All right. Looks
like we are uploaded.
[Woman moaning]
Fuck!
I can't believe it.
Why do I
always miss everything?
I can't believe you
let this woman fuck me
While I was in a coma.
Yeah, she's
going pretty wild here.
Ooh! Ooh, you like that?
You like that?
That might as well have been
a rock she was humping.
You didn't feel anything?
Anything at all?
No! God damn it!
Ohh!
Ooh!
I'm the first virgin
that's not a virgin.
Stop it.
It's true.
Now I know
what parents feel like
When they adopt kids.
Well, we're up to
3 million hits already
With Douglas's video.
It's good,
but not good enough.
Yeah, asshole.
Hey, at least
I got to have sex,
Even though
I don't remember.
You just got a face full.
We're totally fucked, guys.
We have no star.
I hate to say it,
But no one
can do it like ed.
We have three days
to come up with 80 grand
Or else
we go to prison,
Which means
we're fucked.
African-American men are
12 times more likely to die
In prison
than other ethnicities.
Think, think,
think, think.
There is one way.
Doug, you're not starring
in another video.
No. Porndarosa.Cum.
They want to do
a cross-promotion with us.
Why didn't you
fucking say something?
Will they pay us?
Yeah.
Not chump change, either.
We're talking one mil...
Hundred thousand dollars...
[Gasps]
If Ross agrees
to lose his virginity
On a live stream pay-per-view
at the porndarosa stages.
But I knew he was
too much of a pussy to do it,
So that's
why I didn't say nothin'.
Yeah, I mean...
Well...
Say we're
sorry to who, Danny?
Actually, yeah.
Yeah. Why don't
we just find her house,
And I'll beg for
forgiveness? I mean...
And we apologize
for recording ed
Slamming his penis
into her vagina
While she was intoxicated
Under a mix of narcotics
and alcohol.
I've got a better idea.
You guys stay here.
I'll apologize for us.
But just in case, uh...
Tell porndarosa yes.
What? Really?
It's our plan "b."
Danny's second option.
If Melanie doesn't
drop the charges, then...
Call porndarosa
and tell them to set it up.
[Doorbell buzzes]
Man, on intercom: Deliveries to
the service gate on the side.
No, I'm here
to see mellony Adams.
Is she expecting you?
No.
Then call her manager
and make an appointment.
I need to talk to her.
It's important.
Please step away
from the gate.
Security will be down shortly
to escort you off the property.
No, no, no.
No, no. Just, uh...
Just tell her
that I'm the guy
That put her
on the Internet.
[Gate buzzes]
Mellony: So...
Ross.
So, Ross, um...
What is it that you wanted
to talk to me about?
Um, uh, just, uh...
I just wanted
to see you and...
Wait.
Are you... are you
the one that I fucked?
What?
Are you the one that
I fucked from that video?
Okay, look, things are...
Things are a little fuzzy
from that night.
Don't really remember.
And I haven't really
gotten myself, you know,
Up to watch that
video, so...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no, no.
That was... that was ed.
It wasn't me.
Can I have a muffin?
Sure.
Yeah, um, so...
Can I have
an orange, too?
Yeah. No,
help yourself, darlin'.
Thank you.
Um, ed? Ed?
Oh, um, okay. So...
Well, you can tell ed...
That I said thank you
for me, please.
[Laughs]
Thank you?
He saved my life.
What? You're
not mad at us?
Oh, I was.
I definitely was.
But I also realized
that having sex with your...
Your friend ed
Was the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
Okay. You see,
I had hit rock bottom.
I needed to take a really long,
hard look at myself
And... And change.
But...
I'm 27 days clean.
[Laughs]
I know, it doesn't...
I know that doesn't
seem like much,
But I'm actually
really excited about it.
Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
But what
about the money?
Why are
you blackmailing us?
What?
Blackmailing you?
You know, the...
The half-million
Danny demanded
To not send us to jail
and, like, kill us?
He did what?
Yeah, he's gonna
send us all to jail
If we don't come up
with 80 grand
In the next two days.
Okay, no, no, no.
Danny is crazy.
Yeah, I know. Yeah.
And I'm sorry
if he hurt you.
So will you help us?
Look, I am... i am...
I am so flattered that you
came here to talk about this
And get it all out...
But I can't
help you, sweetie.
I can't go
back into that world.
I'm working on me.
I can't get involved.
I have to work on me.
That's what comes first.
But, um...
Please, I...
You got
some news, partner?
We're ready to do this.
Under one condition:
I am the producer
And I alone handle
all of the money.
I'll also need an unlimited
lifetime supply
Of live two-way Jack-off
access on porndarosa.Cum.
You drive
a hard bargain, partner.
But you got
yourself a deal.
Yes!
* gettin' porn money *
* gettin' porn and money *
Lifetime supply. Yeah.
Tickle, tickle!
Tickle, tickle.
I want to spank you.
Okay, come on, Ross.
Come on, Ross.
You got this.
Come on, come on.
One drink.
Take a little drink.
Blech!
Let's roll.
[Funk music playing]
Howdy, partners.
I'm buck Hollister,
president of...
What the heck?
Get the fuck outta here.
What are you...?
President of porndarosa.Cum.
I'd like to thank you all
for tuning in tonight
To watch
some hot fuck action
With one of the hottest
young cock stars in the biz.
Tonight, we got a special
treat.
We're ready for you.
Okay.
You ready? You excited?
You are going
to be waist deep
In some lady's vajayjay
in, like, 30 seconds.
Yeah.
I'm excited.
I'm excited for you.
Hey, I'd be out there
if I could,
But can't go back on set.
Oh, jerk off
once in the corner
And suddenly you're
public enemy number one.
All right. All right,
got it, Scotty.
All right. Thanks, man.
Fuckin' crazy, man.
Suck it up, suck it up,
suck it up.
Okay, you got this.
You got this.
We're gonna witness
America's favorite virgin,
Ross ganz,
Pop his cherry tonight
live on videotape!
[Chanting] I chi ooh LA
goo chi koopah!
What the hell
did he just say?
I don't, um...
Do you have to go potty?
I don't know.
Jeez.
Well, here he is... Ross.
Come here, boy.
Hey.
So let me get
this straight, partner.
You're a virgin?
Uh, yes. Yeah.
[Laughing] A virgin!
Whoo! Well, we're
pretty fucking classy
Here at porndarosa. Cum,
So what
we did is went out
And got
you an extra special
Little hussy to bang.
Are you ready to meet
your lucky starlet, stud?
Let's just
get this over with, man.
Right.
Well, you know
her from the magazines.
Let's all please welcome
miss Emily Addison!
Holy shit.
Hey, Ross.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Ohh!
Saddle up, cowboy!
Time for some fuckin'!
Yee-haw!
Whoa.
Uh...
[Whimpers]
Wait, wait, wait.
Aah!
Wait.
What?
You don't like me?
Yes. Yes, I do.
I just...
Holy shit, I do.
I-i-i don't know.
Get to it, kid!
You're gettin'
paid to fuck!
Shut up!
Fuck this!
My God, this is insane.
I can't.
I can't do this. I can't.
I... i... I can't
believe these words
Are actually coming
out of my mouth,
Considering I've probably
masturbated to you
Over 1,000 times.
I know everything about you.
Oh, my God.
You're awesome.
I, uh...
I even have
this little shrine
I made dedicated to you.
It took
some pretty huge...
Stuff. Shut up!
You know what?
The truth is
Me and my friends are
only making these tapes
Because we were threatened
By that Hollywood agent
Danny silver,
Who's a fucking
slimy cocksucker,
And I hope you're fucking
watching, motherfucker!
He threatened to beat us up
and have us arrested
And even kill us if we didn't
come up with 500 grand.
Well, here's your 500 grand
right here, motherfucker!
Come and get it,
'cause I quit!
You can beat me up.
I don't care.
Whatever, man.
All right?
Because we are
done working for you.
We're done!
You bitch!
And I'll have you know,
There's only one girl
I want to lose my virginity to.
My ex-girlfriend Kim.
And she wouldn't
be watching this,
Because she's
not that kind of girl.
Like all
you little perverts.
She's pure,
And I love that about her.
It's all this bullshit
that caused us to break up!
Fucking shit!
Hey, kwan.
Come here.
I'm not done with you.
Look, I know
you're watching, ed.
All right?
I just want to let you know
you're not a frat guy.
Come on, you're
a ninth level paladin
That's led the clan
on countless adventures.
Come on, dude.
If I had a fucking dollar
for every time you talked
About how much Delaney
was a cocksucker,
Man, I'd have, like,
between 84 and 130 dollars.
Hey, brah. I might've
said one or two things.
Seriously. Delaney
doesn't even like you, man.
He just hangs out with you
because you do his homework.
You know what, fuck this!
I hope you're watching, too,
Delaney.
Because I'm gonna tell
the Dean on your punk ass!
Get him off the fuckin' set!
He's blocking the action!
Time to take
out the garbage.
Recycle.
You can sit.
Ed!
[Speaking
fantasy language]
[Speaking fantasy language]
Unhand him, you ghouls,
at once!
Aah!
You guys are
killing my boner.
Marcus, wake up.
Yo, what the fuck happened?
Got knocked out
again, buddy.
You... you're black.
No shit, bitch.
Damn, who
the fuck served me?
Dude, all those blows
to your head
Somehow cured
your asperger's.
Boy, you really are a pussy.
You can't even get it up
for a million dollars.
You mean 100,000.
Doug made the deal
for a million.
He did?
You motherfucker!
You were gonna keep
900,000 for yourself?
Not really. I was just...
Come here!
I gonna get you!
That's some shit.
Now these motherfuckers up
in here better get ready
For an unholy beat-down
The likes of which
ain't nobody ever seen.
Gotcha
[Groans]
What you gonna do,
bitch?
[Groans]
The motherfucking buck
stops here.
[Smash]
God.
Whoa.
Hey, Danny.
You got a minute?
Can it wait?
Mmm...
I'm trying to do
some business over here.
Well, it's, um...
It's kind of important.
All right.
Make it quick.
Well, you're my manager,
and as an actor,
Us actors feel like
it's good to scratch
Our management's back
every once in while.
You know what I mean?
Uh-huh.
And as your best client,
I feel like
I kind of owe it to you.
And you know
how I roll, baby.
I'm kind of kinky.
Mellony, mellony.
Mmm.
What did I do
to deserve this?
Turn around.
[Both laughing]
Whoa! [Laughing]
[Moaning]
Stop it.
Look at this!
You see that?
That's called
a contract, baby.
[Muffled shouting]
A contract...
One of those
little bitty things
That you could never
get me, seven years.
In seven years,
You couldn't get me
one of those things.
And I just wanted you to
look at all those zeroes
That are going
to be all mine.
[Muffled] That's mine!
And none of yours!
Stop it!
[Groans]
Uh-huh.
Oh, and
guess what, Danny?
You're fired. Uh-huh.
You're fired,
and I never want to
Ever, ever,
ever see you ever again.
[Shouts]
Shut up!
Listen to me.
I should leave you
with a little something,
Though, shouldn't I?
I'm gonna give you
something before I leave
Just so you
remember me by, okay?
[Moans]
So you just stay there,
And I'm gonna give you
something to remember me.
It'll be real good, okay?
Stay down.
Fuck you!
You feel that! Uh-huh!
Yeah, it feels good,
right, baby?
Yeah!
Sorry I'm late for raid.
Who said
you were welcome?
Yo. What up, sexy?
Don't call me that anymore.
The guys kicked me
out of the frat
As soon as our videos
got taken down.
So what?
I figured I would bring you
this from the p.O. Box.
Ahem.
"Ed is the grossest guy
I've ever slept with,
"Rock bottom...
What was I thinking
fucking that guy?"
Yeah, I already
know all this stuff.
Skip to the end.
"This letter is to inform you
that Danny silver
"And all parties
have been arrested
"On extortion charges,
among other things.
"And to inform you that
the estate of mellony Adams
"Is dropping all charges.
All money you made
is yours to keep"?
Yep.
Holy shit. We get
to keep all that money?
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry I betrayed
the clan, brother.
I promise I will never be
in the wrong again.
[Speaking fantasy language]
Hey.
Um, I saw
your pay-per-view.
Look, I'm sorry.
Just kiss me.
Um, I think it's about time
I gave you a real kiss.
[Laughs]
[Both panting]
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry I made you
wait for so long.
Oh, I'm sorry for
pressuring you so much.