(WOMAN MOANING)
Oh, get it out of me!
Praise God, the fathers have arrived.
We are not too late?
The child comes now,
but where is Father Christopher?
He sent for us.
Our order is well-versed
in such matters as this.
How many children have you, my son?
12.
And you, have you brothers
and sisters yourself?
12 as well.
I am the youngest... the 13th.
In the New World,
the 13th child
of a 13th child will be born,
man and beast.
Where root first strikes earth
shall host their final struggle.
One shall rise triumphant.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Oh, get it out of me!
She's not ready to deliver this child!
She must wait!
It will not wait! (WHIMPERS)
In nomine Patris, et Filii,
et Spiritus Sancti.
Christus mansionem benedicat.
- Oh!
- What are you doing?
It is coming!
A blessing to contain the beast.
We cannot drive him out,
but we can trap him here.
She must not deliver the child.
Our preparations are incomplete.
WOMAN: But the child comes.
(SCREAMING)
Fathers! Fathers.
(SOBBING)
- Deliver it!
- Deliver us.
(SCREAMS)
Pater Noster. Adveniat regnum tuum.
Fiat voluntas tua,
sicut in caelo, et in terra...
How lovely is your dwelling place,
oh Lord, heavens...
(SNARLING)
(SNARLING AND SCRABBLING)
The beast is captured.
(BABY COOING AND CRYING)
WOMAN: They call themselves the Keepers,
these men who had held us
prisoners since birth.
Some sort of power
connects me to my brother.
As we grew older, it grew stronger.
We share a bond they can't understand,
and that scares them.
But it doesn't mean we deserve
what they have done to us,
what they continue to do to us.
As the years turn to decades,
turn to centuries.
They've tried to hide us from the world,
dismiss us as just one more legend,
but we're real, counting the days
until we can be free of our captors.
Over the years,
some have even tried to be our friends.
My brother and I, though...
we know better.
(MACHINE-GUN FIRE)
(ALARM WAILING)
All right, we do this by the book.
Confirm your targets.
I do not want us shooting at halos.
Come on!
Somebody tell me what's happening.
We were testing a new containment
when he broke free.
- Where is he right now?
- We don't know.
The first thing he did
was wreck the camera hub.
Check downstairs. You come with me.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
There!
Hey, hold your fire!
(ROARS)
Stop, stop firing! Reload!
Come out of there!
- Contact.
- (ROARS)
I'm getting reports of Melos
in the machine room.
The Jersey Devil is there.
Halo Tommy.
Host nation?
And he's not the Jersey Devil.
Zib is in her quarters?
No. She got out in the confusion.
All right, bring her in.
This is why nobody else treats
the captives as allies.
Just do it, all right?
With respect, if we let her,
she'll lead us right to the beast.
All right. Nobody is
to engage her until my signal.
Is that understood?
Where is she right now?
Right there.
Clear.
It's locked.
It shouldn't be.
MAN: Over there!
- MAN: Zib, you like that?
- (GASPS)
Listen to me, we have you surrounded,
the building surrounded.
It's over. Call off your brother. Now!
He's in here!
(ROARS)
(SCREAMS)
Zib, end this now,
and I won't have to hurt you.
Get her. Get her!
Call him off.
I'm trying,
but you're making him nervous.
I don't care. Call him off.
Let's go back to your room.
- (ROARS)
- (SCREAMS)
I said to call him off!
Call him off!
Stop.
Get him in the cage now! Go! Go!
She's an angel.
Can I put her in the cage
next to her brother now?
Not the time for this argument.
I've been telling you
to lock her up since I got here.
Advice I didn't want from
a team member I didn't ask for.
But got,
since your unit is a meat grinder.
I said not now.
You're right. Now isn't the time.
The time is before she killed
nearly half of your men.
- That wasn't me.
- No?
How about the two you nearly killed
in the east hallway?
You shouldn't have left them alive.
- I'm here to control my brother, right?
- Right.
Well, that's what I did.
And, look, your men got in the way, okay?
And I'm sorry they got hurt,
but I can't keep him calm
from inside a cage,
and there just wasn't enough time
to talk it through.
See, in the future,
you need to make time.
This works a lot better
if we're not fighting each other.
I know.
Hey, look.
She's your prisoner, not your friend.
(SIGHS) Can I borrow your knife?
What happened today?
She let him out.
She wouldn't do that.
You saw what she did today.
She saved my life.
After she put it in danger.
He's getting too strong here
for me to control.
That's what happened.
You need to find
a new place to hold him...
consecrated ground.
A souvenir.
What do you suggest?
You're the priest.
Valley Pennsylvania, the oldest
sacred ground on the East Coast,
and we have a presence there.
All right, set up the trucks.
We leave today.
Can you control your brother
until we get there?
The beast can't be controlled.
You get him to Pennsylvania.
I'll make sure you have a real life there.
I want to live off-complex.
You don't have to bargain with her.
I promise you I'll do what I can.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(BEAST SNARLING)
Why are you supporting this?
Because Valley's not 100 miles
from the Barrens.
Now?
Here, take this.
You'll need it when the time comes.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy Name...
(BEAST ROARS)
Don't touch me again.
I'll do whatever I want.
Why don't you take this off me,
and we'll see how brave you are.
The sweet rage of the impotent, huh?
I need to be close to talk to him.
Damon wants him calm,
I ride in the back with him.
DAMON: (ON TWO-WAY RADIO)
All right, everybody, listen up.
I know we're starting this
tired and grieving,
but I need everyone
at full for this trip.
So as long as we're careful
and we're alert,
everything should run smoothly,
but there's one rule
above all that we all must follow.
We know we're transporting.
We know how dangerous it is.
So if you notice something wrong,
you speak up.
We move out.
We don't stop, we don't try to fix it.
We move.
You know it'll be a long ride if you
just glare at me the whole time.
You know, I don't think
that you would be happy.
I mean, if I get to have a life,
it means you do too.
(CHUCKLES) You're not getting freedom.
We'll we get to Pennsylvania,
my brother will calm down, you'll see.
You'll be in a cage alongside him.
You know, you might want that,
but you're not in charge.
Be quiet.
What can I do to make you trust me?
Um... die.
Both of you.
MAN: (ON TWO-WAY RADIO)
We're running low up here.
Gonna stop for fuel.
Copy that.
Hey. Hey. Wake up.
We're gonna stop for gas.
Gonna stretch our legs.
Okay.
I'll just make sure he's calm.
- Let's go. Come on.
- Okay.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
Hey, you too.
No, I'll just stay here.
Oh, no, no, no, you're coming. Come on.
Come on!
Come on, you little animal.
Listen up... cash-only this trip.
I'm gonna go inside and pay.
Okay.
Zib, it's the last chance to stretch
your legs for a while, okay?
I'm gonna just stay here. You go ahead.
Really? (LAUGHS)
You wouldn't get far.
Whatever it is you're planning,
I'll stop it.
Now whatever pain you inflict,
I'm gonna be sure you feel it
a hundred times more, okay?
Tommy, come here! Come here!
Yes, sir?
Look at her.
Look at her and tell me what's wrong.
- She's doing something.
- No kidding.
Whatever.
Hey.
Her hand. She's hiding her hand.
Way to go.
Show me your hand, Zib. Show it to me.
Hey, dude, it's a gas station.
Come on.
Empty your pocket.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry. I am so sorry.
What?
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
- Damon.
- No, no, I don't think so. What?
We have to get out of here now.
Damon, now! We need to go now!
Go, go. Let's go.
Move out! Let's go!
Close that up! Let's get out of here!
DAMON: (ON TWO-WAY RADIO)
Everybody okay back there?
Yeah, Damon.
Knicks, put Zib on.
Okay.
Hey, Damon.
What happened back there?
I didn't see it in time.
You're supposed to be
keeping him under control.
There shouldn't have been
anything to see.
Yeah, well, I was distracted.
Knicks was harassing me about my hand.
Your hand?
Ask him.
All right. Don't let it happen again.
Why don't you tell Knicks
to let me do my job?
What is it?
I don't know. Could be a fuel pump.
(LOUD BANG)
DAMON: All right, everybody listen up.
We got engine troubles up here.
It's gonna take some time to fix it,
so I want everyone to get some rest.
Damn.
What's happening?
His wings are coming back.
Gas station.
The more chaos he causes,
the quicker he heals.
(ROARS)
He's testing the soul. He's only flesh.
Weaken the body, damage the flesh,
you weaken the beast.
There's no reason for this.
I'm sorry, Z,
we can't take a more chances.
Give me the key.
Frank, Corley...
give me a moment, then come in.
We can feel it, you know,
when you cut us.
This has to be done.
Please, Damon.
I can control him.
This is the cost of your freedom.
Zib, there's no other way.
You need to understand that.
Please don't make me do this.
I can't.
But you will.
MAN: Ready?
(BEAST SNARLS)
Now, Zib.
Now!
Stop.
(BEAST ROARING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Zib...
I need to know that...
I could have controlled him.
No, you couldn't.
And you didn't.
Just who I wanted to see.
I was hoping for a moment of your time.
DAMON: What do you wanna talk about?
KNICKS: Well, Damon, I want to talk
about a lot of things, all right?
If we're gonna do this,
you should come inside.
DAMON: Same as before,
my answer hasn't changed.
KNICKS: Beast or man, one shall fall.
DAMON: And one rise triumphant
where root first struck earth.
I know the prophesy
as well as you do, Knicks.
KNICKS: Then why don't we just end this?
Because I will not be a party to the beast
ascending to infinite power, that's why.
What about his death?
Will you be a party to that?
He killed two dozen of men yesterday,
and you hold the key to his destruction.
If he wins, mankind falls.
What if you're wrong?
PRIEST: He isn't.
You agree with him?
I've been doing this my entire life.
I know the scripture
better than any man alive.
And, yes.
I agree with Knicks.
More accurately, I agree with Tito.
So all of this,
all of this is your doing?
I'd hope you'd listen
to a unified front.
We have him contained and weakened.
We have our whole reliquary in our truck.
If there was ever a time
to do this, it's now.
And what if we're wrong?
For 300 years,
the Keepers have been keeping,
and if we don't kill him now,
what was it all for?
We give our lives to tread water.
But if you're wrong, Knicks...
Well, I will have done something.
I will, at the very least, have tried.
So I'll tell the men
about our change in destination.
Wait.
Let me tell Zib.
She's not gonna like this.
There's one last thing.
What's that?
She has to die, too.
She's not like her brother.
I know you believe that.
But she has a devil in her.
But she can be saved.
What was that?
What is it?
It's probably just a raccoon.
Or a halo if he's trying to distract us.
They just cut his wings off.
He's not strong enough to send a halo.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
Ssh, shh shh shh.
I'm here, brother. I'm here.
Friendly! Friendly! Hold your...
We're not done here.
Not by a long shot. Let's go. Let's go!
What's going on?!
Everybody stay calm! Stay calm!
Remember your training!
These are just halos!
It's okay, brother. I'm here now.
We've all dealt with him before!
Everybody just stay in control!
Come here, come here.
Guns down, everybody! Everybody!
Now we're better than this.
What you're seeing is not real!
It's a halo, okay?
You hear me? It's not real. It's a halo.
I'm sorry I hit you. It's all yours.
Tito, I wanna know
how he's gotten so strong.
Nothing to do...
I've heard just about enough from you,
do you understand me?!
She is a vital part of this mission!
You need to know that!
Yeah? Where's your most
trusted member right now?
- She's in her room.
- Sure about that?
Maybe the only thing keeping her
from freedom is my thumb.
You're shocking her right now?
No.
I'm teaching her...
a lesson!
Restrain the prisoner!
And it's not your unit anymore.
Give me the key.
Give me the key or I'll kill you.
Hand it to me.
Tito, I don't want her
in here again, all right?
It's just too dangerous.
Without her, the relics alone
won't be enough to control his halos.
The men will deal with it.
And it won't be long anyway.
We're gonna do this?
What?
Yeah, we're gonna do this. (LAUGHS)
Mike said the truck's ready.
We leave now, we get there by tonight.
I hope Tito's right.
What?
I hope Tito's right for all our sakes.
He is.
It isn't real. It isn't real.
What do you see?
Maybe talking about it will help.
You killing yourself.
That's pleasant.
Mmm.
I'm not.
Killing myself.
What do you see?
My sister.
We need a shift change in here, I think.
Definitely.
How much longer?
I don't think I can take this.
Let me check.
Knicks, how much longer to go?
We're in the Pine Barrens now.
Not much longer.
Almost home.
(HISSES)
Hear that?
Yeah.
Get them off me!
Greg, hold him down!
Corley, Corley, it's a halo!
It's a halo!
No!
(SCREAMING)
Emergency stop now!
Get them off me! Get them... no!
Right there. Put him down right there.
What's happening?!
Ma'am, I need towels, a lot of towels!
Please, thank you.
- In my bag, there's a sewing kit.
- Put the cell phone away.
- I need to close his wounds.
- Put that cell phone away!
I'm calling 911! This man needs help!
And he'll get it. We're fine.
He's not gonna make it.
We should just go.
WOMAN: Which one is Tito's bag?
I'll show you.
Do you want his bag or not?
Father.
Everybody just stay calm, relax.
No cell phones.
I don't believe they did this to me.
Knicks.
Hey, what are you doing?
They killed him!
Hey, come on. No, we didn't.
We're gonna go, okay?
We're gonna leave right now, okay?
I think you should wai... oh!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
- Get her in the truck.
- Here.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Ready!
- Hey!
- Come on!
Oh, come on. Come on.
Brace yourself.
WOMAN: Do something!
MAN: I'm trying!
Get down!
We gotta get out of here! Come on!
Back up. Come on, back up!
Oh, what the...
Hey, Tommy, what happened?
What happened? Go check.
There's a train coming, guys.
Back up. We gotta back up.
- I'm trying.
- You gotta back up!
- I can't.
- You gotta!
- Get us out of here.
- I can't, I can't, we're stuck!
Get us near the tracks.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
Get on the radio!
Get Knicks to move the truck!
- MAN: Move the truck!
- WOMAN: Move the truck!
- You have to move the...
- Get us nearer the tracks!
- Come on, move!
- Move the truck!
Tommy, where are you?!
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
Go get him.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Get in.
Zib?
No. Don't mind me. Just a hallucination.
- Do you guys see her?
- She's real!
All right then.
I can't see. I can't...
I can't see. I can't s...
In nomine Patris,
et Filii, et Spiritus Sancti.
In nomine Patris, et Filii,
et Spiritus Sancti.
Et Filii, et Spiritus Sancti.
In nomine Patris, et Filii,
et Spiritus Sancti.
(GUN CLICKING)
At last, brother, it is time.
Jers... Jersey devil.
- He's loose.
- What happened?
Zib, she got in.
Are you okay?
(MAN GROANING)
Hey!
What'd you do? What'd you do?
I let him go.
Okay. We gotta get moving.
Just gather up whatever
you can and let's go.
- We're making for the cabin.
- But we don't have the beast anymore.
He'll come.
If he wants the power,
that's where he has to go.
The prophecy.
It said his birth will be the site
of the final struggle.
Man or beast will rise triumphant, yeah.
- Are you sure we can still...
- I'll kill him, okay?
Let's go before he comes back,
all right?
Where are you?
We're not the first ones here.
(DEMONIC GROWL)
Oh, f...
Knicks, that's close enough!
- Damon.
- Don't do anything stupid.
Oh, okay. Hey, hey.
(WHISPERING)
You okay, Z?
Yeah.
"Z," huh? Your first thought is for her.
I've been in touch with Valley, Knicks.
Reinforcements are on their way.
I won't back down, Damon.
You don't have a choice.
Really? I don't?
Why can't you see, Damon?
Stop! Stop it!
Why can't you see? She's not human.
She's a freak, a demon, just like he is.
Say that again
without your cute little button.
How many of your men
has she killed, huh?
Will you let her kill you before you
see her for what she is, huh?
DAMON: Stop! Just let her go now!
Please help me, Damon.
Hey, Damon, by the way,
she let the beast loose.
- (SILENT)
- (BEAST ROARS)
Shut him down.
I can't. He's too powerful here.
I said shut him down.
- Shut him down!
- (SCREAMING)
- (BEAST ROARS)
- I see him!
Let us in! I can't control him!
(GUNSHOTS)
Hold fire! Hold your fire!
He'll kill everyone, Damon.
Everyone inside now! Move, move, move!
You see this, Knicks?
You see what I'm trying to stop?
Okay.
- I can kill him.
- You can kill him?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
That healing should have taken days.
In here, it took seconds.
He comes into this house,
his power grows, too.
How do you kill that?
- MAN: He's coming!
- (GUNFIRE)
Cover the windows, let's go!
We got relics.
Set them up.
Go!
Don't fire until you know it's real,
do you understand?
Please let them go.
300 years, Damon.
300 years your prisoner.
And we will be free.
In nomine Patris, et Filii,
et Spiritus Sancti, amen.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
In nomine Patris, et Filii,
et Spiritus Sancti, amen.
Guys?
You all right?
Contact! I see him, too!
Michael is down! Go, go!
Hey, she's telling him
everything we're doing.
- ZIB: He's powerful here.
- Everything we do.
He's stronger than I am.
I'm doing everything that I can, but I don't
even know if he's gonna respond.
- We can't trust her, you know...
- I know that!
I know that.
There.
All right, let's get back to work.
Windows secure?
Most of them.
The beast got the relics.
Damon, if we can fortify this cabin,
we can trap him.
DAMON: You saw what happened
when she came inside.
We can't risk giving him that power.
So we sit here until he attacks again.
Valley is sending reinforcements.
I already told you that.
ZIB: They won't get here in time.
And you assume that's gonna
get you what you want, huh?
How?
Then we'll be free of you
once and for all.
No, you won't.
We'll keep hunting you, trust me.
All those years.
All those years what, Damon?
All those years in your cage?
All those years bound and captive...
tortured at the whim of my jailer?
You were nice to me, fine.
You know what that's worth?
The kindness of a slaver is no kindness!
You are not a slave.
And you dictate where I live,
what I do, who I know.
You've kept me from my family,
and I serve
at the pleasure of the Keepers.
You look at me, you look at me, Damon,
and you tell me, how am I not a slave?
You're right.
You honestly still feel empathy
for this thing, don't you?
How do we move forward?
How do we go forward
DAMON: Help me.
Help me recapture your brother
and I will give you your freedom.
I'll get true freedom
when my brother kills you all.
No, you won't.
Even if you kill us,
the Keepers will never stop hunting you.
Give me your brother.
I will take that anklet off,
and you can walk away.
Are you being serious?
He comes into this cabin,
everything is lost.
And I would do anything,
anything to prevent that.
But you wouldn't
have to prevent it if...
she hadn't let him go.
I know, Knicks, but he's still out.
So now you're gonna put your...
your trust into this thing
that let him go already.
I don't trust her, Knicks.
We can't do this without her help.
What do you need me to do?
DAMON: We need to secure the cabin.
Without the reliquary and more ammunition,
we won't make it through the night.
But your brother took all the supplies
that Knicks brought with him,
so we need more.
I just happen to know of a truck
laden down with them nearby.
So you want me to help you
get back to the trailer?
Your brother is already wounded.
We just need you to keep him away from us
long enough to get there and get back.
- I'm coming with you.
- I wasn't planning on leaving you.
I'd rather not be here at half strength
if he attacks us again.
Well, the larger the group,
the harder it is for me to hide you.
Knicks, you bring Tommy.
I'm gonna bring Maya.
So we split our forces
into two groups on her word?
Do it or he'll find us and kill you all.
She's outnumbered,
and he's on her home-field.
Basic strategy 101...
divide and conquer.
If she's lying, we're all dead either way.
So it doesn't matter, does it?
I want her bound. Okay?
Me too.
- Do I get a say in this?
- No, you don't.
Make sure you should keep
that shock button close at hand.
You didn't have to tell me that.
(LAUGHS)
I am sorry, Damon.
I didn't wanna hurt you.
Just keep him off us, all right?
There's something
I need to know you understand.
We've held you for nearly 300 years,
and I get that you're angry.
The idea of righteous vengeance
would be a pretty appealing one.
That anger blinds you, Zib.
There's no good in your brother.
No love, no kindness, only pain.
Only what you put there.
Maybe. When the time comes,
I and all of mine will face our sins,
but right now, as I place my life
and the lives of mine in your hands,
you need to understand...
your brother can't give you what you want.
Well, I appreciate your concern.
I'm not concerned for you.
I just want you to understand
you can't win...
not like this.
Go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He's not here.
Good. Let's keep moving.
Let's go. Go.
Still nothing.
Let's go.
(ROARS)
Everyone in the trailer!
Everybody in the trailer now!
Go! Go, go!
Secure that door.
What happened here?
This is what we're fighting against.
He's making a profane space.
He's sick. That's what he is.
No.
He's making a place
of comfort for himself.
If we bless the room,
it weakens him, right?
Right now he's doing the opposite.
Zib.
Zib!
You lied to me.
I have to make physical contact
to connect with him if he's up in the air.
Why didn't you tell us that?
Don't you think
you should tell us that, huh?
I didn't know.
It never came up
while he was in your cage.
Wasn't in my cage.
Hey, this is your friend.
Let's just get the relics
and get out of here.
I couldn't agree more.
Couldn't have said it any better either.
Tommy, here.
DAMON: Knicks?
Knicks!
- Me?
- Yeah.
Come here.
What?
We have a chance here.
- Really? What do you mean?
- Look around you.
He's made a home here. He's made a den.
So he likes dens. He's a gentleman.
Where we have a confined space,
plenty of munitions,
and 300 gallons of diesel fuel
on the other side of that wall.
Damon, great.
But I'm not gonna stay here... and die.
- ZIB: Are you gonna blow up the truck?
- No.
I'm gonna blow up the truck
with the beast inside of it.
- Tommy, you have the C4?
- Yes.
Place it near the fuel tanks.
Make sure that explosion will reach them.
No, you said you were
just gonna recapture him.
He'll make it through the other side.
You and I both know that.
With any luck, we'll weaken him enough
that we can survive the night.
It'll be agony for him.
I know.
I'm sorry, Z, there's no other way.
Yes.
What is that?
It's what you kill a beast with.
I thought this was resolved, Knicks.
It's changed.
It's forged with a cross.
It's been quenched in the waters
of the River Jordan.
This...
is a sacred blade.
It's a piece of costume jewelry.
It doesn't matter what it is!
We're not gonna kill him.
You don't think it'll work?
- I don't care if it'll work, Knicks.
- I know it won't work.
- And you'd tell us if it would, of course.
- Try and kill him with it.
In order to do that,
we have to bring him inside the cabin,
which we are not doing.
Hey, okay, Damon...
hey, we're people, okay?
It's you and me, right?
Okay?
So let's just, you know, let's...
let's just test it, okay?
Let's just test it just to see
maybe... maybe I'm right.
I mean, she's right here.
We have the blood
of the beast amongst us.
Just let me kill her to test it.
I'm not testing anything, Knicks.
We have the relics.
Our only job is to secure the cabin
until reinforcements arrive
and we can safely recapture that beast.
Damon, she's the enemy.
Yet you continue to protect her.
- No.
- Yes, you do.
- No!
- I am not protecting her!
- You do protect her!
Over your own men, you do! Why?!
This stunt of yours...
this stunt of yours has gone long enough!
I will not indulge it any further.
Aren't you the guy, right,
that lost 20 of his men in two days?
Aren't you that guy?
Those men were my friends!
- What do we do?
- Just got to let them work it out.
That's enough, Knicks!
Stay down! That's enough!
Damon!
Stay outside.
You have to let him back in, Knicks.
I don't have to do anything.
You proved your point, Knicks.
Let me back in.
That's it, Damon.
Can't trust you anymore.
- (WINGS FLAPPING)
- Sorry.
You can stay inside and be quiet,
or you can go outside and be with him.
(CRASH)
(THUDDING)
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(SNARLING AND THUDDING)
Stop!
Good luck, Knicks.
I pray that you're right.
- No!
- (ROARING)
Let's move out.
(BEEP)
What now?
We wait.
For how long?
Not long.
I can't see those hands again,
I'm gonna kill you, okay?
Wait.
Now.
Yes! Yes!
Not so tough now, you stupid goat head!
Relax, we still gotta find him
and put him back in the box, all right?
(LAUGHS)
She's upset about her brother.
She's hysterical.
Hey.
You just don't get it, do you? (LAUGHS)
After all this time with him
and you still don't realize.
You watched him go into the trailer.
You watched it blow up,
But you forget one thing.
He...
makes... you...
see things.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
Run! Run!
(ROARS)
(BEAST ROARS)
(LAUGHS)
Come on! Open up! We're coming in hot!
Close the door.
What happened out there?
Well, we got the relics.
And a knife to kill the beast.
Damon and Maya?
Dead. It got ugly.
Without their sacrifice...
we wouldn't be alive.
I can kill the beast. I can prove it.
Tommy, go get the bedroom ready, okay?
This blade can harm him
and put to an end...
(BONES CRACK, KNICKS SCREAMS)
Get her.
Tommy, tie her up,
but not so tightly that she can't move.
Danny, come here. Push my arm back in.
Help me with my arm. Here, hard.
Harder!
Three people can't hold this cabin.
We'll stick to the plan.
Secure the room. Secure the room.
I don't understand it.
Understand what?
He could have killed us at any time
in the Pine Barrens, and he didn't.
He let you go.
Don't listen to her. Just ignore her.
She's just trying
to psyche you out, okay?
He let you go, Tommy,
because he wants you here
in his home when he kills you.
We're here, brother.
It's time.
(SPEAKING LATIN)
Find me, brother.
KNICKS: It's not real, Tommy.
It's not real. Come on.
Tommy, it isn't real.
I'm sorry.
We're close!
Let's finish the ritual.
- Let us finish this.
- Whatever you see, just keep going.
- Okay.
- I'm running out of time here.
(BOTH SPEAKING LATIN)
I'm in mother and father's room.
You came for me.
Knicks!
What did you do?
You poor, poor man.
You think you've won.
No, no, no, no, no.
You know what you have done?
Nothing.
279 years,
six months and 14 days
we have been prisoners of your Keepers.
I don't understand.
4,251 electric shocks.
I did everything right.
153,611 punctures,
stabs, and cuts.
You should be dead.
It's a shame you're not like us.
How I would love
to make you feel that one again.
The final struggle
between man and beast.
Oh, Knicks,
you can't retreat into madness yet.
We're just getting started.
Keep it together.
Man and beast,
and one shall rise triumphant.
Oh, you like what I did there, Knicks?
Huh?
"Keep it together"?
And you're a Keeper.
Man and beast.
(SNARLS)
I was wrong.
So very, very wrong.
(GROANS) I'm sorry.
I accept your apology.
The final struggle...
the struggle...
it isn't between...
humanity and the beast.
It is... between the children.
Don't worry.
You'll be free.
Between the man and the beast...
it has to be you, Zib.
You're the only one.
(GRUNTING)
They're all dead.
And we're home.
Tomorrow, when more come...
We'll kill them too.
And they will never enslave us...
or separate us ever again.
(ROARS)
What are you doing?
It's me.
Stop.
I'm your sister.
We're free now.
We don't have to fight anymore.
All those years...
everything we've suffered?
I'm your sister!
Your friend.
I love you.
Why are you doing this?
I love you, brother.
And I'm sorry.
(GRUNTS)
Be at peace, brother.
MAN: (ON TWO-WAY RADIO)
Come in, Damon. Damon, come in.
This is Dyer responding to your call.
Any surviving team members,
please respond.
MAN: In the New World,
the 13th child
of a 13th child will be born,
man and beast.
Where root first strikes earth
shall host their final struggle.
ZIB: One shall rise triumphant.