[SCREECH]
[ELECTRIC CRACKLING]
[TRAFFIC HONKING]
[POLICE SIREN]
[SCREECHING]
P.A. announcer:
THE TRAIN WILL BE STOPPING,
WATCH THE DOORS.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[SCREECH]
OW!
OH, DAMN IT.
OH.
[SPEAKING MIDDLE EASTERN
LANGUAGE]
NO, NO.
WAIT.
I HOPE YOU ENJOY SHOPPING.
OH, I ADORE SHOPPING.
VERSACE, PLEASE.
OH!
WHAT DID YOU THINK
WE WORE UNDERNEATH?
Susan: THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU MIGHT LIKE.
THIS IS OUR LATEST
HERE AT GARSONS--
FLAME OF THE FOREST
BY BOUVIER.
HMM.
NO.
OK. THERE'S MORE
THIS WAY.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF THE WHOLE STORE?
I'M THE OPERATIONS MANAGER.
I HANDLE EVERYTHING
FROM SECURITY ISSUES
TO PUBLIC RELATIONS.
MEANING YOU SPEND
YOUR TIME
BABY-SITTING
THE IDLE RICH.
EVERY CUSTOMER IS
IMPORTANT TO US
HERE AT GARSONS,
YOUR MAJESTY.
MM-HMM.
YOU'RE GOOD AT YOUR JOB,
MS. COSTELLO.
I WON'T MONOPOLIZE YOU
FOR TOO MUCH LONGER.
[SCREECH]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY,
MS. COSTELLO.
THANK YOU,
YOUR MAJESTY.
OUR FLOOR SHOPPER
WILL HELP YOU
PERSONALLY.
VERY GOOD.
ENJOY.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
HI. I'M SUSAN COSTELLO.
OH! ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
HOW'D YOU CUT IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST REACHED DOWN
TO GET MY CLOTHES.
CAN YOU SHOW ME WHERE?
IT WAS RIGHT OVER THERE.
OK.
[GASPS]
IT WAS A CARPET TACK.
BUT HOW CAN
THAT JUST CUT--
I'M SO SORRY. I'LL
HAVE MAINTENANCE
CHECK IT OUT
RIGHT AWAY.
LISTEN, YOU WERE
HAVING A FUN DAY.
WE DON'T WANT
TO SPOIL IT.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE
THAT OUTFIT HOME.
YOU MEAN FOR FREE?
YEAH! IT LOOKS
GREAT ON YOU.
[LAUGHS]
WOW.
THANK YOU.
SURE.
UM, YOU DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA NEED
A SHOT OR ANYTHING,
DO YOU?
WELL, IT'S NOT RUSTY,
BUT YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
HAVE YOUR DOCTOR
LOOK AT IT, OK?
OK.
FINE.
THANKS.
HEADING HOME, MS. PAGE?
HOW'D IT GO
WITH THE QUEEN?
DID YOU MAKE HER
FEEL COMFORTABLE?
OH, SHE MADE US
FEEL COMFORTABLE.
$12,000 WORTH
WITH THE DISCOUNT.
GOOD.
WHAT ABOUT THE GIRL
WITH THE FINGER?
OH, SHE'S FINE.
SHE LEFT HERE
A HAPPY CAMPER.
DID YOU GET
A RELEASE?
NO. I FELT THAT WOULD
PUT HER ON GUARD.
HER CUT DIDN'T
AMOUNT TO MUCH.
I DID TELL HER TO CHECK
WITH HER DOCTOR, THOUGH.
IT'S AN OPEN DOOR,
SUSAN.
WELL, I FELT NEGLIGENT
NOT TO AT LEAST SUGGEST IT.
JUST BE CAREFUL
YOUR COMPASSION
DOESN'T WORK
TO YOUR DISADVANTAGE.
OR MINE.
[COACH'S WHISTLE BLOWS]
COME ON, WARREN!
KEEP YOUR LEGS
TOGETHER!
REACH! REACH!
COME ON, AMY, GO!
GO.
GOOD JOB.
SEE YOU GUYS
NEXT WEEK.
REMEMBER
TO DO YOUR LAPS.
COME ON, AMY.
MOM, DO WE HAVE
TO DO BACKSTROKE?
YES. IT'S THE NEXT THING
WE'RE WORKING ON.
I HATE BEING LAST.
I KNOW. YOU WERE FIRST
IN FREESTYLE HEATS.
I GUESS.
I WANNA BE FIRST
IN EVERYTHING.
GEE, I WONDER
WHERE YOU GET THAT FROM?
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT THE BEST WAY
TO PRACTICE IS,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT?
PLAY TAG WITH YOUR MOM.
YOU'RE IT!
[GIGGLES]
AAH! WHOO!
[SCREECH]
Susan: WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IT'S A GREAT STORY
FOR THE 11:00 NEWS.
YEAH, THEY'LL BE
STANDING OUTSIDE GARSONS
THANKSGIVING NIGHT,
YOU INTERVIEW THE FIRST
SHOPPER IN LINE, AND--
CHEESY?! YOU KNOW WHAT?
FOX HAS ALREADY JUMPED
AT THIS STORY.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL MAKE
ARRANGEMENTS NEXT WEEK.
ALL RIGHT,
TALK TO YOU LATER.
AMY, MUFFINS
BEFORE DINNER?
HOW MANY HAVE
YOU EATEN?
JUST ONE.
WE HAD HALF A DOZEN.
NO, I THINK
MAYBE WE ONLY GOT 6.
VERY FUNNY.
DINNER'S ALMOST READY.
DO I HAVE TO SEND
DADDY AN E-MAIL?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO WRITE ABOUT.
WELL, TELL HIM
ABOUT THE MOVIE WE SAW.
YOU SAID YOU LIKED IT.
I GUESS.
AND SHOULD I TELL HIM
YOU SAID HI?
SURE.
ARE YOU EVER
GONNA BE FRIENDS AGAIN?
MAYBE SOMEDAY.
BUT NOT RIGHT NOW.
[SCREECH]
AAH!
WHAT?
[GASPS]
[SNIFF]
I DON'T SEE NO SIGNS.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP
YOUR WINDOWS SHUT,
YOU OUGHT TO BE FINE.
HEH HEH.
Susan: KARL?
IT WAS OUTSIDE
THE WINDOW.
PLEASE,
WILL YOU JUST
SET SOME TRAPS
TOMORROW?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU LIVE IN THE CITY,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE RATS.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
KARL.
TRAPS. TOMORROW.
Karl: TOMORROW.
Susan: OK?
TRAPS.
OK, I'LL PUT SOME OUT.
SURE THING. TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
Susan: DON'T WORRY, HONEY.
HE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
Amy: OH, MOM,
THAT RAT WAS SO NASTY!
[CHIRPING]
Karl: WHY
THE SCENTED STITCH?
ALWAYS COMPLAINING.
LADY, YOU GOTTA WAKE UP,
YOU KNOW, TO REALITY.
YOU JUST CAN'T,
UH, GO AROUND
KILLING INNOCENT
LITTLE ANIMALS, YOU KNOW?
WELL, SHE'D UNDERSTAND IF--
IF, YOU KNOW, SHE TOOK
A GOOD LOOK AROUND
TO SEE WHO, UM,
HER REAL NEIGHBORS ARE.
[DOG BARKS]
RIGHT.
WELL, COME ON NOW,
WOULDN'T SHE?
HUH?
NO, SHE WOULDN'T.
SHE'D HAVE TO LEARN
TO GET ALONG...
WITH EVERYBODY.
Woman on TV: PLEASE,
ANDRE, FOR MY SAKE.
MAYBE IT WILL WORK.
I BEG YOU!
NOW, DON'T BE SCARED,
ALL RIGHT?
I DID SAY I'D PUT OUT
A FEW TRAPS.
BUT I DIDN'T SAY NOTHING
ABOUT SETTING 'EM.
YOU SEE,
WHAT SHE DON'T UNDERSTAND
IS THAT EVERY LIVING THING
HAS ITS PLACE, OK?
LIKE YOU GUYS, OK?
YOU LIVE OVER THERE.
I LIVE OVER HERE.
WE WORKED THAT OUT
BETWEEN US.
IT DIDN'T BOTHER US.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO EXPLAIN
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
TO SOMEBODY LIKE HER?
[SCREECHES]
WHO ARE YOU?
HEY, I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU BEFORE.
YOU'RE A BIG FELLA.
WHAT ARE YOU,
WORKING OUT OR SOMETHING?
NO, DON'T BE SCARED.
COME HERE. COME HERE.
NOW, DON'T BE AFRAID.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
COME ON.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT, FELLA.
HERE YOU GO.
[CRUNCH]
AAH!
AAH, YOU LITTLE--
YOU GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
PIECE OF RAT SHIT!
PIECE OF SHIT!
THAT'S IT!
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?!
HUH? WHY'D YOU--
OK, LET'S--
OK, I SHOULDN'T HAVE--
I DIDN'T MEAN--
THAT WAS--
HE HAD RABIES
OR SOMETHING.
WHEW. GUYS,
I WOULD NEVER
DO THAT TO YOU.
PLEASE.
GUYS?
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I SWEAR, HEY--
I WOULD NEVER--
GUYS?
GUYS,
WHERE YOU GOING?
[SCREECHING]
AAH!
OH!
AAH! AAH!
AAH! NO!
Woman on TV: AAH!
OHH! AAH!
AAH!
HELLO?
THIS IS
SUSAN COSTELLO.
YES, PLEASE.
PUT HER THROUGH.
WHAT?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Nurse: I WILL.
Doctor: I WANT YOU
TO MONITOR T.B.C.
AND HER ELECTROLYTE
OUTPUT.
THANK YOU.
HI. IS SHE ALL RIGHT?
SHE CAME IN WITH
A MILD SEPTICEMIA.
IT'S STRANGE
FOR SOMEONE SO YOUNG
WITH NO DRUG
HISTORY.
SHE SAID
SHE CUT HER FINGER
AT YOUR STORE?
YEAH, IT WAS
ON A CARPET TACK.
4 HOURS
AFTER ADMISSION,
SHE'S GOT SEVERE
RESPIRATORY DIFFICULTIES,
THREATENING
RENAL FAILURE.
SHE'S VERY SICK.
IF SHE HADN'T COME IN,
SHE'D BE DEAD.
I'M 99% CERTAIN
IT'S WEIL'S DISEASE.
IS THAT SOME FORM
OF TETANUS OR--
NO.
FROM A CARPET TACK.
IT WAS A BITE WOUND.
I CAN'T SAY FOR SURE,
BUT I THINK
IT WAS A RAT.
Ms. Page: GARSONS
DOES NOT HAVE RATS.
NO OFFENSE, BUT WOULD YOU
SWEAR TO THAT IN COURT?
MY GOD, WAS THE GIRL'S
LAWYER THERE?
NO.
WHAT DID THE DOCTOR SAY?
WELL, SHE SAID
IT WAS A RAT BITE.
SHE'S ALMOST CERTAIN
THAT IT'S WEIL'S DISEASE.
LISTEN, IF GARSONS
GETS SUED
FOR A RAT BITE
AND IT GOES PUBLIC,
WHICH IT WOULD,
NOT ONLY CAN YOU KISS
YOUR JOB GOOD-BYE,
BUT SO CAN EVERYBODY
ELSE HERE, INCLUDING ME.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
KEEP YOUR EYE
ON THE GIRL.
MAKE SURE
SHE GETS WELL.
FIRE OUR SO-CALLED
EXTERMINATORS,
YANK THEIR NAMES
OUT OF THE ROLODEX,
AND SUE THEIR BUTTS
TO KINGDOM COME.
DISCRETELY, OF COURSE.
BRING IN NEW RAT PEOPLE,
COMPLETELY UNCONNECTED.
THE BEST IN TOWN.
I HATE RATS.
Man: HEY.
YOU CAN'T PARK THERE.
I'M LOOKING
FOR SUSAN COSTELLO.
SHE'S EXPECTING ME.
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
I'LL GO PAGE HER.
SHE'LL PROBABLY
GIVE YOU A CALL.
EXCUSE ME,
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU CAN HELP ME.
I'M LOOKING
FOR SUSAN COSTELLO.
DO YOU KNOW HER?
I'M SUSAN.
OH, HI.
HI.
I'M JACK CARVER.
OH, JACK CARVER
THE, UM, THE--
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU EXPECTING SOME GUY
IN A YELLOW T-SHIRT
WITH A BIG, BLACK RAT
ON THE BACK?
YEAH, SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I APPRECIATE THE DISCRETION.
ALL MY CLIENTS DO.
SO, UH,
SOMEBODY GOT BITTEN
IN A DRESSING ROOM?
Susan: NOT HOW
WE'RE PUTTING IT YET.
I SEE. HOW ARE
WE PUTTING IT?
WE'RE NOT, YET.
LOOK, MS. COSTELLO--
SUSAN.
SUSAN...
YOUR JOB AND MINE DON'T
MATCH UP ALL THAT WELL.
PEOPLE LIKE ME
GO AROUND FINDING THINGS
THAT THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT
SOMETIMES NEEDS TO KNOW ABOUT.
PEOPLE LIKE YOU
GO AROUND TRYING
TO GET PEOPLE LIKE ME
TO KEEP OUR MOUTHS SHUT.
MR. CARVER--
JACK.
JACK, IF YOU'RE SUGGESTING
THAT PEOPLE LIKE ME
WOULD COVER UP
SOMETHING LIKE THIS--
SOMETHING LIKE WHAT?
A RAT BITE?
I THOUGHT
WE WEREN'T GOING THERE.
WE'RE NOT.
WE'RE STANDING HERE
IN A COSMETIC DEPARTMENT
WASTING TIME.
OK, LET'S START OVER.
I'M JACK,
THE PERSON YOU CALLED,
AND I BELIEVE
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU NEED TO SHOW ME?
AFTER YOU.
IT HAPPENED IN HERE.
SHE WAS OVER--
HOW MANY BASEMENT LEVELS
UNDER THE STORE?
3 FLOORS INCLUDING
THE SUBWAY.
SEE, SHE WAS
OVER HERE AND--
3?
YEAH. SHE HAD
A PILE OF CLOTHES.
SHE SAID SHE REACHED
DOWN, AND--AND--
I GUESS
IT HAPPENED THEN.
I WAS THINKING
THAT MAYBE THE RAT
WENT UNDERNEATH
THE, UH--
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
I GOT A POSSIBLE
ENTRY POINT.
WHERE?
HERE.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME?
THAT TINY CRACK?
A HOLE THE SIZE
OF A WEDDING RING'S
BIG ENOUGH.
[SIGHS]
WE HAD A RAT OUTSIDE
OUR WINDOW LAST NIGHT.
Jack: HERE?
NO, AT HOME.
4 LEGS OR 2?
LET ME GUESS.
FIRST TIME YOU EVER
TOLD THAT JOKE?
IT'S AN OCCUPATIONAL HAZARD.
I'M SORRY.
I'LL TRY NOT
TO ANNOY YOU.
WHAT IS THAT?
FIBER OPTICS.
A LITTLE SOMETHING
I WHIPPED UP MYSELF.
IT COMES IN HANDY.
OH, BOY.
BAD NEWS.
LOTS OF CRITTERS.
COME HERE,
TAKE A LOOK.
YOU SEE WHERE THE WOOD
IS ALL SCRATCHED
AND CHOPPED UP?
MM-HMM.
THAT'S RATS.
THEY CHEW. THEY CHEW EVEN
WHEN THEY'RE NOT HUNGRY.
OTHERWISE THEIR TEETH GROW
SO LONG THEY CAN'T EAT.
THEY STARVE.
CONCRETE, METAL, WOOD.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
WE HAVE A RAT PROBLEM.
CERTAINLY NOT GIRAFFES.
Jack: LOOK AT THAT.
YOU SEE THAT?
OH, NO.
THE RAT PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN SANDBAGGING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, THEY CLEANED UP
THE RAT LITTER,
BUT THEY DIDN'T
CLEAN UP THE RATS.
IT HAPPENS.
COMPANIES GET
OVEREXTENDED.
THEY THINK
THEY'LL CATCH UP.
THEY NEVER DO.
TY? YEAH, LISTEN,
I'M DOWN AT GARSONS.
I NEED YOU HERE, MAN.
THE RODES ARE REAL BUSY.
YOU HEAR ME?
OK.
RODES?
SHORT FOR RODENTS.
YOU KNOW, CLIENTS SEEM
TO GET UPSET IF YOU GO,
"COME OVER HERE,
THE PLACE IS CRAWLING
WITH RATS!"
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SO, HOW DO YOU GET
RID OF THE RODES?
LOOK.
DEPENDS ON WHAT
WE'RE UP AGAINST.
HOW SOON DOES
THE STORE CLOSE?
2 HOURS.
GOOD NIGHT, LADIES.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
SURE YOU WANTS
LIGHTS OFF?
IT'S A WHOLE LOT BETTER
IN THE DARK.
SUSAN, THIS IS TY,
MY UP-AND-COMING APPRENTICE.
TY, SUSAN.
WHO YOU CALLING
"APPRENTICE"?
I'M THE GUY THAT DOES
ALL THE DIRTY WORK.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
OK.
[DIALING BEEPS]
ALL RIGHT,
LIGHTS OFF.
HERE WE GO.
Jack: LET'S SEE
WHAT WE CAN'T SEE.
IS THAT--
OH, THAT'S NOT--
WHERE OUR LITTLE FRIENDS
TOOK A BATHROOM BREAK?
THAT'S THE UGLY TRUTH.
SEE, RATS ARE
PERMANENTLY INCONTINENT.
SHOWS UP UNDER
THE ULTRAVIOLET LIGHT,
WHICH GIVES US
AN ACCURATE TRAFFIC PATTERN.
Ty: HMM.
CHECK THAT OUT.
Susan: OH, NO.
THERE'S MORE?
THAT'S NO BIG DEAL,
REALLY.
I MEAN, SOME OF OUR FINEST
RESTAURANTS ARE A LOT WORSE.
DISPERSAL PATTERNS
LIKE THESE,
THEY CAN BE CLEANED UP
OVERNIGHT.
OH, SO THAT'S GOOD.
Ty: NOT NECESSARILY.
WE JUST STARTED OUT.
COME ON.
Jack: WE GOT A LITTLE BIT
OF ACTION HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
UNBELIEVABLE.
[SCREECH]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Amy: THANKS FOR TAKING
ME, AUNT NYLA.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
NOW ARE YOU ACTUALLY
GONNA PRACTICE
OR WE JUST GONNA
LOOK AT GUYS?
NO. I HAVE TO PRACTICE
MY BACKSTROKE.
THEN WE'LL LOOK AT GUYS.
[GIGGLES]
OK, WELL,
THEN LET'S DO IT.
GIVE ME YOUR TOWEL.
READY?
OK, GO!
[GIGGLES]
[SCREECHES]
Jack: WELL,
GIVEN THE FACT
THAT THEY HAVEN'T
DESTROYED MUCH
AND THESE DISPERSAL
PATTERNS HERE...
AND HERE,
IT'S CLEAR THAT
YOUR LITTLE VISITORS
ARE RECENT.
NOW, THE GOOD NEWS
IS THAT THEY'RE
STILL CONTAINED.
WE CAN
ELIMINATE THEM,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO ACT IMMEDIATELY.
ALL RIGHT, I'M CONVINCED.
WHAT DO YOU RECOMMEND?
I RECOMMEND
YOU CLOSE THE STORE.
[SCOFFS] DO YOU KNOW
WHAT IT WOULD COST
TO CLOSE THE STORE
FOR ONE DAY,
MR. CARVER?
NOT TO MENTION
EXPLAINING IT
TO THE PRESS.
CAN'T WE JUST CORDON
OFF THE THIRD FLOOR
WHILE YOU WORK?
SURE. BUT I'M GONNA HAVE
TO FILE A REPORT
WITH THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT.
EVENTUALLY.
IT'S THE LAW.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[SQUEALS]
OK, GO PRACTICE.
[SCREECH]
AAH!
Amy: AAH!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[SCREAMING]
AMY!
AAH!
[SCREECH]
AMY!
Nyla: AMY!
HURRY UP, BABY!
LOOK OUT BEHIND YOU!
AMY, COME ON,
BABY, SWIM!
HURRY UP! COME ON!
AMY!
AMY, HURRY UP,
BABY! SWIM!
SWIM!
COME ON! YOU CAN DO IT!
AMY, COME ON!
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
GIVE IT HERE!
WELL, THESE BLUEPRINTS
ARE GREAT,
BUT I NEED SOMEBODY
WHO KNOWS
EVERY NOOK AND CRANNY
OF THE STORE.
MS. CO
FILLS THE BILL.
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
I MEAN SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS THE BASEMENTS,
THE SUBSTRUCTURE,
THAT SORT OF THING.
Page: I KNOW
WHAT YOU MEANT.
MY RECOMMENDATION
STILL STANDS.
IF MR. CARVER
ISN'T COMFORTABLE,
I CAN ARRANGE
FOR SOMEONE ELSE--
STOP IT.
YOU'RE THE BEST MAN
FOR THE JOB,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
HE'LL SEE THAT
SOON ENOUGH.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
EXCUSE ME.
HELLO?
IS SHE OK?!
WHAT--WHAT--
WAIT, WAIT, SLOW DOWN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN RATS?
Susan: I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
UM, MS. PAGE,
MY DAUGHTER NEEDS ME.
EXCUSE ME.
HARRY,
THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT
WANTS YOU
TO DRAIN THE POOL.
THAT'S GONNA TAKE
2 DAYS AT LEAST.
HI.
SHE SAID A RAT
TRIED TO SWIM IN HER MOUTH.
IT WAS SO SICK.
HI. WHAT'S
YOUR NAME?
AMY.
HI, AMY.
WHO ARE YOU?
MY NAME'S JACK.
THIS IS GARSONS'
NEW EXTERMINATOR, HONEY.
WHY WOULD RATS
BE IN A POOL?
WELL, THEY CAN SWIM,
JUST LIKE US.
THEY CAN
HOLD THEIR BREATH.
THEY SWIM
THE HUDSON RIVER
EVERY DAY.
THEY'RE COMMUTERS.
[GIGGLES]
AMY, WHY DON'T
YOU GO SIT OVER HERE
AND RELAX
FOR A SECOND?
YOU HAD
A CRAZY DAY, HUH?
SO, AMY, TELL ME--
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE POOL.
WHAT DID YOU SEE?
WELL, I WAS SWIMMING,
AND THEN THE RATS
JUST STARTED
COMING AFTER
ALL THE KIDS,
AND THEY CHASED US
OUT OF THE POOL.
THEY CHASED YOU
OUT OF THE POOL?
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
YES, AND THEY WERE
EVEN TRYING TO BITE US.
AND THE BIGGEST ONE
WAS AFTER ME.
YEAH, AND HOW BIG WAS IT?
HUGE.
WELL,
THAT'S ACTUALLY SMALL
FOR A NEW YORK CITY RAT,
YOU KNOW.
WELL, MAYBE IT
WAS MORE LIKE THIS.
BUT IT WAS REALLY UGLY,
AND IT WAS LIKE THE ONE
THAT WAS TRYING
TO GET IN THE WINDOW
THE OTHER DAY. REMEMBER?
YEAH.
AND IT HAD ITS TEETH
BARED AND EVERYTHING.
HMM.
THIS IS REALLY STRANGE.
IT IS?
MM-HMM.
CAN YOU
DO ME A FAVOR?
YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
AMY, THAT CLOSET'S
CLEAN AS A WHISTLE.
I MEAN, YOU COULD HAVE
A SLEEPOVER PARTY IN THERE,
IT'S SO CLEAN.
PROMISE?
PROMISE.
HEY, HONEY, YOU WANNA
TAKE A BREAK
AND GO WATCH A MOVIE?
YEAH.
OK.
GO PICK OUT WHATEVER
ONE YOU WANT.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
I PROMISE. REALLY.
GO AHEAD.
BE RIGHT THERE.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
IS THIS THE WINDOW?
IT WAS THIS ONE.
[GRUNTS]
OH, WELL, YOU GOT
A HOLE IN THE SCREEN HERE.
YOU EVER KEEP
THIS WINDOW OPEN?
SOMETIMES.
I MEAN, NOT SINCE--
OH, YOU'RE USING...
THE VENT.
YEAH.
EXCUSE ME.
OH, SURE.
AHEM.
YOU REALLY LIKE
YOUR JOB, DON'T YOU?
WELL, THE HUNT'S FUN.
IT'S NOT LIKE MY PREY
IS AN ENDANGERED SPECIES
OR ANYTHING.
RATS ARE TOUGH.
THEY CAN ADAPT
TO ALMOST ANY CONDITION,
CONTROL THEIR HEARTBEATS.
ONLY THE MOST EXPERIENCED
INDIAN YOGIS CAN DO THAT
OR COME EVEN CLOSE.
THEY'RE A WORTHY ADVERSARY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
NO, IT'S REALLY--
ALL RIGHT.
UM, DO YOU STORE CRUMBS
BEHIND YOUR RADIO?
[GASPS]
I KNEW THERE WAS
MORE MUFFINS.
MMM. YOU'VE GOT A RAT.
PROBABLY JUST ONE.
OH, WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
WAIT--WAIT A SECOND. WAIT.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
YOU GET RID OF THE RAT.
YOU DON'T REMOVE YOURSELF.
WE CAN'T LIVE WITH A RAT.
SUSAN,
WHERE YOU GONNA GO?
ANYWHERE YOU GO
IN THIS CITY,
YOU'RE NEVER MORE
THAN 5 FEET FROM A RAT.
ACTUALLY ABOUT 9
PER PERSON IN NEW YORK.
OK. WAY MORE INFORMATION
THAN I NEEDED.
LISTEN, CAN YOU JUST
FIND IT AND GET RID OF IT?
IF IT'S STILL HERE, I CAN.
DO IT.
[RAT SCREECHES]
[WHISTLES]
THANK YOU.
[REPORTERS TALKING]
I WANT TO MAKE
A BRIEF STATEMENT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE
UNFORTUNATELY,
I'M LATE FOR A MEETING,
SO YOUR QUESTIONS
WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
WHAT'S THE MEDIA
DOING HERE?
SOMETHING ABOUT RATS
IN SWIMMING POOLS?
I AM PLEASED TO REPORT
NO EVIDENCE
OF WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE
A VERMIN INFESTATION.
APPARENTLY, A PRANKSTER
THREW SEVERAL
DOMESTICATED RODENTS
INTO A SWIMMING POOL,
PANICKING SEVERAL SWIMMERS.
NO ONE WAS SERIOUSLY INJURED,
AND I'M TOLD
THE POLICE ARE CLOSING IN
ON A SUSPECT.
THANKS. THAT'S ALL FOR NOW.
THAT'S THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT
FOR YOU.
COME ON.
RAY.
JACK.
LOOKING
MIGHTY SHARP THERE.
RAY, THIS
IS SUSAN COSTELLO
FROM GARSONS.
SUSAN, RAY JARETH,
DEPUTY CHIEF INSPECTOR
FOR THE HEALTH
DEPARTMENT.
Susan: NICE TO MEET YOU.
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT?
I GOT AN EYEWITNESS
WITH A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT STORY.
COME ON, JACK.
WE NEED TO TALK.
JACK,
WHATEVER YOU HEARD,
COULD YOU TAKE IT
AND JUST PUT IT
ON THE SHELF
FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
COULD YOU DO THAT?
REMEMBER WHAT WE
USED TO SAY?
UH-UH.
ANYTHING GOES, LONG AS
IT DOESN'T HURT ANYBODY.
[CHUCKLES]
Both: OR COST US MONEY.
RAY, THE REC CENTER
HAS A RAT PROBLEM.
2 BLOCKS AWAY, GARSONS
I'VE GOT A FEELING
IT DOESN'T END THERE.
SO, YOU WANT TO TELL ME
HOW SITTING ON THIS
DOESN'T END UP
WITH SOMEONE GETTING HURT?
JACK, I'M NOT DOING
THE SITTING HERE.
THAT'S COMING
FROM HIGHER UP,
A LOT HIGHER.
I THINK THE CITY'S
TRYING TO BUY
A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
THERE'S
A BIG TRADE FAIR
GOING ON RIGHT NOW,
SOME KIND OF AWARDS
SHOW NEXT WEEK,
COUPLE OF MAJOR
CONVENTIONS.
YOU START HOLLERING
THE "R" WORD,
CLOSING PLACES DOWN?
UH-UH.
HEAVY PEOPLE
LOSE HEAVY BUCKS.
WE CAME HERE TO REPORT
A PROBLEM AT GARSONS.
I ASSUME YOU DON'T
WANT TO HEAR ABOUT THAT,
AT LEAST
FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
I WANT EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
THERE HAS BEEN
AN UNPRECEDENTED INCREASE
OF BITE REPORTS,
INFESTATIONS,
LOCALIZED HERE
IN MIDTOWN.
I'LL GIVE YOU COPIES
OF THE REPORTS.
SO, WHAT ABOUT
THIS WEIL'S DISEASE?
UNTIL A COUPLE
OF MONTHS AGO,
PEOPLE HAD BARELY
HEARD OF IT.
NOW IT'S SHOWING UP
AT HOSPITALS
ALL AROUND HERE.
AROUND HERE?
YOU MEAN MIDTOWN?
YEAH, PRETTY MUCH.
BITES AND SIGHTINGS
AT FAST-FOOD JOINTS,
APARTMENTS,
A LIBRARY, A BUS.
AND NOW THE MIDTOWN
REC CENTER
AND ONE MAJOR
DEPARTMENT STORE.
THIS IS BIG, RAY.
IT'S WEIRD, JACK,
THESE RATS.
THEY JUST
KEEP SHOWING UP,
KEEP COMING OUT
AT ODD TIMES, ANYTIME.
LIKE THEY'RE NOT
AFRAID ANYMORE.
YEAH.
THEY'D RATHER BITE
THAN RUN AWAY.
Susan: SO, YOU AND RAY
HAVE A HISTORY.
I USED TO WORK FOR HIM.
HE SOLD ME
THE BUSINESS.
I GUESS IT'S GOOD TO HAVE
THE CITY ON YOUR SIDE.
IT'S WORKED OUT WELL.
RAY, HE--HE WAS ALWAYS
MEANT TO BE A POLITICIAN,
BELIEVE ME.
HOW'RE WE DOING?
AH, THIS WHOLE FLOOR'LL
BE CLEARED OUT TONIGHT.
GOOD.
NOW, WHERE THE HELL
ARE THEY COMING FROM?
UH, I CHECKED
ALL THE OBVIOUS PLACES.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
ANOTHER MAJOR
PORT OF ENTRY HERE.
WHAT ABOUT
THE COOPS?
COOPS?
YEAH. IT'S
AN OLD STORE.
IT HAS FALSE
INTERIOR WALLS.
THEY USED
TO CALL THEM COFFINS.
SECURITY WOULD
HIDE BEHIND THEM
AND WATCH
FOR SHOPLIFTERS.
OH, AND THEN VIDEO
CAME ALONG--
THEY SEALED THEM UP.
COOPS.
[POUNDING]
WE'RE GOING EXPLORING.
OH, YEAH.
WE'VE GOT A RAT
PLAGROUND HERE.
Susan: I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU DO THIS.
BEATS 9 TO 5
AND FLUORESCENT LIGHTS.
I GUESS JACKIE BOY
NEVER TOLD YOU
HOW HE CAME
TO THE BIG APPLE
WITH A DRUM KIT
AND A DREAM, HUH?
THEN HE SETTLED
FOR THIS.
REALLY?
Jack: YEAH, WELL,
TY'S THE ONE BORN
FOR THIS BUSINESS.
HE USED TO MAKE
A DOLLAR A RAT
POPPING THEM
WITH HIS .22,
CLEARING BUILDING SITES
DOWN AT THE HUDSON.
WELL, I HAD TO PAY
FOR A VERY EXPENSIVE
COMIC BOOK HABIT.
Susan: THERE'S A LADDER
IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
Jack: YEAH? WHERE?
HERE.
RIGHT THROUGH THERE.
OH, YOU ARE THE BEST MAN
FOR THE JOB.
[GRUNTS]
Ty: THIS MUST BE
HOW THEY TRAVELED
BETWEEN FLOORS.
[GASPS]
UNH!
YOU OK?
YEAH. I'M OK.
OOF!
WATCH THIS RUNG
DOWN HERE.
NEED A HAND?
UM, NO. I'M--
NO, I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
I GOT YOU.
OK.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
WOW. IT CHEWED
RIGHT THROUGH THAT.
LOOK AT THAT.
ISN'T THAT SOMETHING?
YOU SEE RATS
EVERYWHERE,
DON'T YOU?
ONE OUT OF EVERY 4 FIRES
OF UNKNOWN ORIGIN--
CAUSED BY A RAT
CHEWING THROUGH
WHAT IT SHOULDN'T
BE CHEWING THROUGH.
THEY AREEVERYWHERE.
[SIGHS]
IS HE ALWAYS
THIS CHEERFUL?
THE WAY HE SEES IT,
THESE RATS WORK FOR HIM.
[CRASH]
WHAT?
IT MAY BE IN THERE.
SORRY.
[SIGHS]
Ty: IT'S BIG ENOUGH
FOR A WHOLE LOT OF RATS.
PLENTY OF DARK, WET
CORNERS FOR BREEDING.
ALL RIGHT,
SO, WHERE ARE THEY?
WELL, THAT'S THE BIG
QUESTION, ISN'T IT?
WE'VE REACHED
THE END OF THE LINE.
THEY'RE NOT HERE.
AAH! OK.
[TY LAUGHS]
FUNNY.
A 2-LEGGED RAT.
OH, HERE WE GO.
FANTASY
CHRISTMAS CANDLES?
ONE OF THE ESSENTIAL
RAT FOOD GROUPS.
LET'S GET THIS TO THE LAB.
IS THAT WHERE THEY LIVE?
NO, IT'S THEIR
PORT OF ENTRY.
WE'RE GOING IN.
OK.
Jack: WATCH YOUR HEAD.
BEEN THROUGH HERE,
ALL RIGHT.
Susan: I THINK WE'RE
OFF GARSONS' PROPERTY.
200 YEARS OF BUILDING...
BASEMENTS,
ACCESS TUNNELS, SUBWAYS.
WHO KNOWS
WHERE THIS LEADS?
[SUBWAY BRAKES SCREECHING]
[SCRATCHING]
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
IT'S GNAWING.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE.
[SCREECH]
[GNAWING AND SCREECHING]
Susan: I DON'T
LIKE THIS, JACK.
WHICH WAY DO WE GO?
THIS WAY. COME ON.
THEY'RE THIS WAY.
THEY'RE THAT WAY.
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE, MAN.
Susan: JACK,
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
LET'S GO BACK.
YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
WE GOT TO CRUISE.
WE'RE RIGHT ABOVE
THE SUBWAY!
YEAH, THIS IS MORE
THAN I SIGNED ON FOR.
YOU COMING OR WHAT?
THIS IS BAD. LET'S GO.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
COME ON.
I'M GOING BACK!
YEAH.
GODDAMN IT,
JACK, LET'S GO!
[SCREECHING]
Susan: UH--
WHAT DO WE DO?
LET'S JUST, UH...
WALK OUT OF HERE
NICE AND SLOWLY.
THAT'S IT.
WATCH--WATCH YOURSELF.
Jack: THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
WHOO!
WHAT ABOUT THE RATS
THAT WERE JUST
STANDING THERE
LOOKING AT US?
IS THAT NORMAL?
WELL, THAT'S A NEW ONE
ON ME. RAT-ITUDE.
SOON AS WE NUKE 'EM,
I'LL BE A LOT HAPPIER.
Jack: WHOA, WHOA,
CALM DOWN.
WE DON'T KNOW
IF WHAT WE SAW
IS PART OF SOMETHING
MUCH BIGGER.
YOU BETTER PRAY
THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
THE TUNNELS,
VENTWAYS, AND PIPES
ALL OVER THE CITY?
YEAH. WELL,
WE WERE CERTAINLY
OFF STORE PROPERTY.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO WORK
WITH RAY'S PEOPLE ON THIS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
HMM.
HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
UH, YEAH.
NO. NO,
I'M NOT ALL RIGHT.
HOW DO YOU
KILL THEM?
WELL,
WE SEAL THEM OFF,
AND THEN WE GAS 'EM.
BUT, YOU SEE, RATS,
THEY BUILD UP
AN IMMUNITY TO POISON
IN 2 GENERATIONS.
THAT'S EVERY 6 MONTHS.
SO, WE CONSTANTLY HAVE TO
CUSTOMIZE THE PESTICIDES.
DON'T YOU RUN OUT
OF COMBINATIONS?
THAT'S THE GAME WE PLAY.
OH.
SURE YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
HMM?
YEAH.
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OK.
SO, IT ALL COMES DOWN
TO A BIG HOLE IN THE WALL.
NO. IT'S MORE
COMPLICATED THAN THAT.
WHAT WE FOUND
INDICATES
A SUBSTANTIAL
RAT COLONY NEARBY.
CONFIRMING
WHAT WE SUSPECTED.
IT'S A CITY PROBLEM,
OR STATE.
THEY'LL HAVE TO CALL OUT
THE NATIONAL GUARD
OR WHOEVER
HANDLES THESE THINGS.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH
TO JUST CHASE THEM
OVER THE FENCE,
MS. PAGE, AND--
YOU TELL MR. CARVER
TO PATCH UP THE HOLE
IN HIS WALL,
SET HIS TRAPS,
AND GO HOME.
AND AS FOR YOU,
IT IS TIME FOR YOU
TO GET BACK
TO YOUR DAY JOB.
THAT FOR ME?
NOT UNLESS YOU LIKE
WOMEN'S LINGERIE.
[BOTH LAUGH]
NO, IT'S
FOR THE FIRST
AND HOPEFULLY ONLY
CASUALTY HERE
AT GARSONS, ANYWAY.
AH, THAT'S VERY
THOUGHTFUL OF YOU.
IT'S PART OF MY JOB.
I WOULD LIKE TO THINK
YOU'D DO IT ANYWAY.
JACK, UM,
THERE'S ANOTHER PART
OF MY JOB
I DON'T
NECESSARILY ENJOY,
BUT I HAVE TO DO IT.
GO AHEAD.
WELL, MS. PAGE
IS VERY PLEASED WITH
WHAT YOU'VE DISCOVERED.
IN FACT,
SHE'S SO PLEASED,
SHE FEELS
THERE'S NO NEED
TO PURSUE IT ANY FURTHER
THAN PATCHING THE WALL
AND SETTING SOME TRAPS.
SUSAN,
WE'VE GOT TO MOVE
ON THIS COLONY.
THE WOMAN CAN'T PRETEND
IT'S NOT OUT THERE.
WELL, THE WOMAN
CAN DO JUST ABOUT
ANYTHING SHE WANTS--
NOT WITH ME, SHE CAN'T.
WE DON'T PULL OUT
UNTIL I SAY SO.
WELL, SHE WON'T
AUTHORIZE PAYMENT.
OH, WELL, THEN
SHE'LL BE IN BREACH,
NOT TO MENTION
IN DEEP TROUBLE
WITH THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT.
WHICH DOESN'T CARE
RIGHT NOW, JACK.
I WAS WITH YOU.
OH, PLEASE, SUSAN.
YOU'RE NOT--
WHY ARE YOU
REACTING THIS WAY?
WELL, WHAT
DO YOU EXPECT--
YOU HAVE TO SEE
HER POINT.
SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO PAY FOR SOMETHING
THE AUTHORITIES
ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR.
EVEN IF HER STORE
IS THE CAUSE OF THE PROBLEM?
IF HER STORE
IS THE BREEDING GROUND
OR THE FOOD SOURCE?
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
I SUGGEST YOU HAVE
MS. PAGE GIVE ME A CALL.
I'LL TALK
SOME SENSE INTO HER.
TROUBLE IN PARADISE?
GARSONS IS TRYING
TO BAIL ON US.
[TIRES SCREECH]
THAT'S TYPICAL!
THE BIGGER THE NAME,
THE SMALLER
THE GAME, LADY!
HEY, LET'S TAKE A WALK.
COME ON, WE'LL DO
SOME OF RAY'S WORK.
I MEAN, HE'S IN NO HURRY
TO DO IT. RIGHT?
NO.
COME ON.
COME ON, TY.
[SIGHS]
[SCREECHES]
OHH.
[SIGHS]
[TEETH CHATTER]
[SQUEALS]
AAH!
[SQUEALING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[SQUEALS]
[SQUEAKS]
WE MUST HAVE COME
AT LEAST 2 BLOCKS NORTH.
OK, ABOUT HALFWAY
BETWEEN GARSONS
AND THE MIDTOWN
REC CENTER,
BUT THAT
WOULD BE, LIKE,
RIGHT ABOUT HERE,
RIGHT BELOW US.
WELL, WHAT'S DIFFERENT
ABOUT THIS STREET
THAN ANY OTHER STREET
IN NEW YORK?
NOTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL.
WE KNOW THOSE RATS
ARE DIFFERENT.
IT'S A ROGUE COLONY.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA
MAKE THAT LAB RUN,
SEE WHAT
THEY COME UP WITH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE.
UM, BLOOD SUGAR,
CALCIUM, AND MINERALS
ALL NORMAL.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
MUSCULAR DEVELOPMENT'S
EXAGGERATED,
AND THESE GUYS'
TESTOSTERONE LEVELS
ARE OFF THE CHARTS.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
DISEASE CARRIERS YET.
THAT'LL, UH, JUST
TAKE A LITTLE LONGER.
SO, THEY'RE
MORE AGGRESSIVE,
AND THEY HAVE THE MUSCLE
TO BACK IT UP.
YEP. WHAT
EVERY LITTLE RAT
WANTS TO GROW UP TO BE.
WHERE'D YOU, UH,
WHERE'D YOU FIND HIM?
MAN, THE RAT OLYMPICS.
WHERE ELSE?
YOU EVER SEE ANYTHING
LIKE THIS, ARTIE?
WELL, NOT
IN THE NATURAL WORLD.
WE DO GET SOME
PRETTY WEIRD SPECIMENS
THROUGH HERE, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, UH, LAB RATS.
SOME OF THE STUFF
THE DIFFERENT
TESTING FACILITIES
PUT THESE GUYS THROUGH,
IT'S REALLY NO SURPRISE
TO SEE YOUR
OCCASIONAL MUTATION.
YOU MIND IF I DO
A LITTLE SURFING?
OH, HEY, HELP YOURSELF.
OH!
SORRY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
IF SHE WAKES UP
AND NEEDS
ANYTHING AT ALL,
PLEASE
CALL ME. OK?
DONE. NOW, LISTEN,
I THINK YOU NEED
TO GET HOME
AND TAKE THE REST
OF THE DAY OFF.
OK?
ALL RIGHT. THANKS.
P.A. system:
DR. WILSON, ICU.
DR. WILSON.
HEY, THERE.
HEY.
HOW YOU DOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST GOT REALLY
SCARED. YOU KNOW?
WHAT IS IT
WITH YOU COSTELLO WOMEN
AND RATS, HUH?
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED TO HAVE
BETTER STORIES THAN ME.
YOU KNOW THAT. RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT. OK.
[SIGHS]
HOW'S SHE DOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S JUST NOT
GETTING BETTER.
SO, JACK, I,
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
OH, NO.
THAT'S NOT NECESSARY.
SUSAN, YOU'RE JUST
DOING YOUR JOB. RIGHT?
YEAH, BUT--
I'M SORRY. SOMETIMES
MY JOB GETS IN THE WAY.
YOU KNOW, USUALLY
I'M A REALLY GOOD
TEAM PLAYER,
AND THE STORE HAS ALWAYS
BEEN THE TEAM,
AND THEN--
OK. WHAT
I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
I WANT TO HELP YOU.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
EXCUSE ME.
JACK CARVER.
HEY, IT'S TY.
I'M AT ARTIE'S.
HE THINKS THESE THINGS
MIGHT BE ALTERED.
ALTERED? WHAT, LAB RATS?
Ty: EXACTLY.
NOW, I LOOKED ON-LINE
AT 3 TESTING LABS
IN MIDTOWN,
INCLUDING ONE ON--
POULSON STREET?
BINGO! 1444 POULSON,
TEKWORTH LABS.
4 BLOCKS SOUTH
OF GARSONS.
YOU'RE MY HERO, MAN.
HUH.
I'LL MEET YOU DOWN THERE.
LATER.
LISTEN, SUSAN,
I GOT TO GO DO
A LITTLE DETECTIVE WORK.
I WANT TO COME WITH YOU.
I DON'T THINK
YOU WANT TO COME--
I WANT TO COME WITH YOU.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
UNH!
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE A LAB.
TEST LABS
DON'T PUT UP SIGNS.
MAKES THEM
TOO MUCH OF A TARGET
FOR ANIMAL RIGHTS GROUPS.
DESERTED.
UNH!
WANTED TO GET IN,
RIGHT?
AFTER YOU.
UHH.
WERE YOU
A JUVENILE DELINQUENT?
NO. I JUST THINK
YOU'RE BRINGING
THIS OUT IN ME.
YOU STILL NEVER TOLD ME
HOW YOU CAME TO KNOW
EVERY NOOK AND CRANNY
AT GARSONS.
IT'S EASY WHEN
YOUR DAD'S A JANITOR.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
NOPE.
IT WAS THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST PLAYHOUSE.
THAT'S QUITE A PICTURE.
A LITTLE GIRL ALL ALONE
IN HER VERY OWN
DEPARTMENT STORE.
DIDN'T LAST.
DAD DIED WHEN I WAS 12.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
YOU WENT BACK.
WHEW!
OH, MY GOD.
THE SMELL.
ONE DEAD RAT'S
ALL IT TAKES.
[GASPS]
I'M SORRY.
I ONLY DO RATS.
[GASPS]
OHH.
Susan: ALL THESE
DEAD ANIMALS.
WHAT IS THIS?
FOOD.
OK, HERE WE GO.
NOTICE FROM THE HEALTH
DEPARTMENT TO VACATE.
THERE'S A WHOLE LIST
OF VIOLATIONS.
SO, WHAT, ONE DAY,
THESE PEOPLE
JUST LOCKED UP
AND WALKED OUT?
Susan: YEAH, BUT IF
THEY JUST WALKED OUT,
THERE'D STILL BE RATS
IN THE CAGES, RIGHT?
UNLESS WHATEVER
THEY WERE GIVING THE RATS
MADE THEM SO STRONG...
THEY BUSTED OUT
ON THEIR OWN.
Ty: AND HAD A FEAST
ON ALL THE OTHER
TEST ANIMALS.
Jack: SURE. THEY
HUNG OUT HERE, GOT FAT,
PROBABLY EVEN MUNCHED
ON THE OCCASIONAL
STRAY DOG OR CAT.
ACACIA FARNESIANA.
THAT'S A SCIENTIFIC
CLASSIFICATION,
BUT THAT'S NOT
AN ANIMAL.
PLANTS.
WHAT'S THAT?
Susan: WAIT A MINUTE.
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH
OF MATERIAL
ON THAT RIGHT HERE.
LOOK.
THEY MUST HAVE BEEN
TESTING THE MEDICINAL
PROPERTIES
OF THESE PLANTS
ON THE RATS.
NOW THEY'VE BEEN
OUT THERE MULTIPLYING
FOR HOW LONG?
THE LAB'S BEEN
CLOSED DOWN FOR 2 YEARS.
YOU START
WITH MAYBE 500.
A NEW LITTER
EVERY 6 WEEKS.
THAT'S MORE
THAN HALF A MILLION.
JESUS.
HEY!
TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS!
CHECK THIS OUT.
OH, MAN.
LOOKS LIKE THEY CHEWED
THEMSELVES A BACK DOOR.
Jack: MAYBE TO THAT
TUNNEL THEY'RE IN.
MAYBE TO A DEAD LINK.
Susan: A DEAD WHAT?
LINK. EMPTY SEWERS
LEFT BEHIND
WHEN AN AREA'S
REDEVELOPED.
THEY CAN BE
HALF A MILE LONG.
IT'S LOOSE.
READY? LIFT.
[BOTH GRUNT]
QUICK!
Ty: HMM.
THIS LITTLE RAT HIGHWAY
COULD LEAD ANYWHERE.
HEY!
[ECHOES]
[RATS SCREECH]
Jack: HERE'S GARSONS,
THE REC CENTER,
AND SUSAN'S APARTMENT.
AND THE INCIDENTS,
THE OTHER ONES,
ACCORDING TO REPORTS,
HERE, HERE,
HERE, AND HERE.
IT'S ALL MIDTOWN
WITHIN A 10-BLOCK RADIUS--
SOUTH OF 45th STREET,
ABOVE 25th STREET,
AND BROADWAY,
WEST TO 10th AVENUE.
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT ALL,
RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT WHERE
WE'RE STANDING,
TEKWORTH LABS.
SO, THIS IS YOUR
ROGUE COLONY THEORY?
IT MAKES SENSE.
NO WAY IN HELL
THESE LAB RATS
ARE DOING ALL THIS.
WHY DON'T YOU
GO IN THERE
AND LOOK
FOR YOURSELF?
THE DAMAGE THEY DID
IS UNBELIEVABLE.
RAY, LOOK,
YOU'VE GOT ACCESS
TO TOYS NOW
THAT I DON'T.
I NEED
A REMOTE CAMERA UNIT
SO I CAN GET DOWN THERE
AND FIND THEM.
I CANNOT HAVE MY PEOPLE
OFF WORKING FOR YOU
EVERY TIME YOU GET
SOME CRAZY IDEA.
LISTEN, WE COULD DO THIS
OURSELVES, QUIETLY,
NO COMMITTEES,
NO PANELS.
I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS WOULD MAKE
A GREAT STORY
FOR THE 11:00 NEWS.
SO WOULD THE TRUTH
ABOUT
THE REC CENTER.
THIS IS THE LAST TIME, JACK.
AND STAY OUT
OF THAT BUILDING
UNTIL MY CREW
GETS HERE TOMORROW.
Jack: YES, SIR.
[WHISPERING]
Those files.
We should get them.
I'm telling you,
he's gonna
take forev--
JACK.
GOT 'EM.
I CAN'T
TAKE YOU ANYWHERE.
MMM.
[LAUGHS]
HEY, NYLA.
HEY, YOU.
WILL YOU SHAMPOO MY HAIR
WHEN I GET TO THAT PART?
SURE, SWEETIE.
AND THE SPECIAL
SURPRISE RINSE?
YOU GOT IT.
THANKS.
EVERYTHING OK, TIGER?
YEAH.
OK.
[SPLASHING]
[SCREECHES]
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU KNOW, DINNER
IS NOT GONNA BE MUCH,
BUT YOU'RE MORE
THAN WELCOME TO JOIN US.
YOU SURE?
ABSOLUTELY.
I'D LOVE TO.
OK.
Amy: MAMA!
MOM!
WHAT?
THERE WAS A RAT
IN THE TOILET!
WHAT?
I LOOKED,
BUT I DIDN'T
SEE ANYTHING.
I SAW IT!
HE'S IN THERE!
[LAUGHS]
IT'S ALL CLEAR.
I CHECKED.
WILL YOU
STAY ALL NIGHT?
NO, HONEY. JACK CAN'T
STAY THE NIGHT.
BUT, MOM.
I WANT HIM TO.
PLEASE, MOM?
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
COME ON. I REALLY
WANT HIM TO. PLEASE?
I COULD
ON THE SOFA.
YEAH, HE COULD
STAY ON THE SOFA.
ARE YOU SURE?
I'M SO TIRED,
I COULD SLEEP ON
A COLD SIDEWALK.
THAT THING'S
SPEAKIN' TO ME.
YES!
ALL RIGHT.
Susan: HIT ME.
Jack: YOU DON'T
WANT ME TO DO THAT.
OK.
OH!
OF COURSE.
YOU NEVER HIT
ON A HARD 17.
BUT IT'S ME.
BUT IT'S YOU.
Jack: PFFT!
HA! OK, YOU OWE ME
244 YEARS
OF EXTERMINATING
SERVICE.
244 YEARS?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN
KEEPIN' TRACK.
OH, GOD. I STINK
AT THIS GAME WITH YOU.
NO, I'M JUST LUCKY.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE LUCKY.
I THINK THAT
YOU'RE EXCEPTIONAL.
YOU KNOW THAT?
I DON'T THINK OF MYSELF
AS EXCEPTIONAL.
HMM. YOU GOT THIS
WONDERFUL LITTLE GIRL.
YOU GOT THIS GREAT JOB
AND ALL THIS RESPONSIBILITY...
AND YOU'RE VERY CLEVER.
YOU KNOW THAT?
I MEAN, THE THING TODAY
WITH RAY, THAT WAS--
[LAUGHS]
I THINK I WAS JUST
INSPIRED BY YOU,
THE WAY YOU DON'T LET
ANYTHING DERAIL YOU.
[LAUGHS]
I THINK IT'S TIME
WE GET SOME REST.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Jack: YOU GUYS FROM
THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT
GET ALL THE GREAT TOYS,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT'S THE RANGE
ON THIS THING?
2 MILES, ACTUALLY.
OUR NEW SOFTWARE
WAS ADAPTED
FROM THE BOMB SQUAD'S
ROBOT,
SO IT'S PRETTY GOOD.
THAT POOL WAS SUCKY.
DEFINITELY WASN'T
OUR REC CENTER,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DIDN'T SEE ONE RAT
ANYWHERE, DID YOU?
GOOD POINT.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANNA DO NOW?
UH, WELL.
HONEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M FEELING GUILTY
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
JACK'S DOING HIS JOB TODAY
AND I'M NOT DOING MINE.
THEN YOU SHOULD
BE THERE.
YEAH?
MM-HMM.
THANKS.
MOM, DO YOU LIKE JACK?
YEAH. WE WORK TOGETHER.
I LIKE HIM, YEAH.
NO, I DON'T
MEAN LIKE THAT.
I MEAN DO YOU
LIKE HIM?
LIKE, DO YOU
REALLY LIKE HIM?
OH, DO I LIKE HIM?
MM-HMM.
WELL, I--
YEAH. I DO.
[GIGGLES]
GOOD,
'CAUSE I DO, TOO.
YOU DO?
SO, YOU WOULDN'T
FEEL WEIRD
IF THE 3 OF US
WENT AND DID
SOMETHING TOGETHER?
NO. JACK'S
TOTALLY COOL, MOM.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S CALL NYLA
AND HAVE HER MEET US
AT GARSONS.
YEAH. COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
HOW FAR IS IT
TO RATVILLE?
[SQUEAKS]
THAT DIDN'T TAKE LONG.
Ty: HERE THEY COME.
GIVE ME A 180.
Man: WHERE ARE THEY
ALL COMING FROM?
Jack: KEEP GOIN'.
GO DEEPER.
Ty: LOOK AT
THE DEBRIS IN THE PIPE.
REALLY CAUSED SOME
DAMAGE DOWN THERE.
Jack: PUSH THROUGH THEM.
WHAT'S THAT?
GOOD GOD.
HOME SWEET HOME.
TY, WE'RE GONNA NEED, UH,
5 TANKS OF PHENYLALKAPHINE.
LET'S DO THIS WHILE WE CAN.
5?
Jack: ALL RIGHT, 10.
[ALL SCREECHING]
15.
UH, WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT
A TOXIC SUBSTANCE
RIGHT UNDERNEATH
US HERE?
OH, NO. DON'T WORRY.
IT HITS THEIR NERVOUS
SYSTEMS, NOT OURS.
Man: THEY'RE
ALL OVER US, MAN.
UH, UH,
BACK THE CAMERA OFF.
OK, GET--
JUST GET A LITTLE CLOSER.
ALL RIGHT.
UP AGAINST THE WALL.
I HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.
THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF
TO LOOK OUT FOR
DOWN THERE.
[ALL SCREECH]
UH-OH.
Jack: WHAT UH-OH?
OH, NO.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
OH, SPARKS.
I THINK I JUST
CLIPPED ONE OF
THE POWER LINES.
Ty: DAMN, IT'S
MAKING 'EM CRAZY.
[ALL SCREECHING]
WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
Ty: ZOOM IN.
ZOOM IN THERE.
THEY'RE CHEWIN'
THROUGH A PIPE.
THAT LIGHT,
WHAT ARE WE LOOKIN' AT?
Tech guy: I THINK, UM--
YES. IT'S THE SUBWAY.
Amy: WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S RESEARCH
ON PLANTS.
RESEARCH?
YEAH, THESE
ARE RARE PLANTS.
THEY MAY CURE
DISEASES SOMEDAY,
SO THEY TEST THEM
ON THE ANIMALS.
AC-A-CA CA--
ACACIA FARNESIANA,
ALSO CALLED
GOLDEN RAINTREE.
DELONIX REGIA.
FLAME OF THE FOREST.
MOM, THAT'S
LIKE THE SCENT
YOU GAVE ME.
SEE? LOOK.
CHECK MY BACKPACK.
SEE? LOOK. SEE?
THAT'S
THE SAME FLOWER.
[SCREECHES]
AAH!
OH!
[ALL SCREAM]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[ALL CHATTER]
HEY! SHE'S GOTTA BE UPTOWN.
NO, NO, NO, WEST.
Amy: OH.
MOM, WILL YOU
GET ME ANOTHER ONE?
SURE, HONEY.
HEY, WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
Passenger: YEAH?
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE DEAD
ON THE TRACK, FOLKS,
SO I'M GONNA
GO CHECK IT OUT.
NOW, IT'LL ONLY
TAKE A FEW MINUTES,
SO EVERYBODY
JUST SIT TIGHT, OK?
ARE YOU JUST GONNA
LEAVE US HERE ALONE?
SIR, JUST CALM DOWN.
JUST SIT TIGHT.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ALL RIGHT?
OH, THAT'S NICE.
WE'RE TRAPPED.
Woman: JUST LIKE,
AND ONE THING--
LATE ENOUGH.
THIS IS NOT FAIR.
IT'S LIKE BEIN' TRAPPED
IN A TIJUANA WHOREHOUSE.
Woman: HEY, JUST
SETTLE DOWN, MISTER.
YOU'RE MAKIN'
EVERYONE HERE NERVOUS.
OH, SO WE SHOULD START
TAKING ORDERS FROM YOU?
Woman: JUST SIT DOWN.
[THUMPING ON ROOF]
Woman: IS IT RAINING?
WHAT'S THAT?
MOM, WHAT'S THAT?
I DON'T KNOW, HONEY,
BUT THE MAN'S
GONNA CHECK IT OUT.
[SQUEALS]
AAH!
[ALL SCREECHING]
[THUMPS ON ROOF,
SCREECHING]
COME HERE.
[DOOR BANGS]
[SCREAMING]
LOOK!
[SCREECHING]
AA-AAH! AAH!
[PANICKED SHOUTING]
[GUNSHOTS]
THEY GOTTA BE
DOWN THAT TUNNEL.
COME ON!
EXCUSE ME! EXCUSE ME!
FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
GET ANOTHER ONE,
ALL RIGHT?
[FRIGHTENED SCREAMS]
HEY!
AAH. AAH!
GET TO THE FRONT
OF THE TRAIN.
GET TO THE FRONT!
Woman: GET THEM OFF!
GET THEM OFF!
Woman: AAH. GET THEM OFF!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
[SCREECHING]
IT'S WORKING.
LET ME OUTTA HERE.
LET ME OUTTA HERE!
GET BACK!
[YELLING]
SUSAN!
GET BACK TO
THE STATION.
[PANICKED CRIES]
AMY. SUSAN--
PLEASE STEP
THIS WAY.
COME ON,
GENTLEMEN.
SUSAN!
JACK!
YOU GUYS OK?
WE'RE OK.
THE RATS, THEY HATE US.
THEY'RE IN THE APARTMENT,
THE TRAIN,
EVERYWHERE WE GO.
NO, HONEY, IT'S NOT US.
IT'S THE PERFUME.
JACK, THEY'RE ATTRACTED
TO FLAME OF THE FOREST.
WHAT?
YOU MEAN--
YOU MEAN
THE PERFUME BOTTLE
I BROKE
ON THE TRAIN?
YEAH. IT'S THE PERFUME
THAT'S ALL OVER
GARSONS' THIRD FLOOR.
IT'S ONE OF THE PLANTS
THEY TESTED ON THE RATS.
IT MAKES THEM
SWARM TO IT.
NYLA, TAKE AMY WITH YOU,
CLOSE EVERYTHING UP,
AND I'LL COME
GET YOU, OK?
HONEY, I'M GONNA STAY HERE
AND HELP JACK, ALL RIGHT?
I LOVE YOU.
MOM, KILL 'EM.
KILL 'EM ALL.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA
BE FINE, SWEETHEART.
YOU DON'T WORRY. OK?
JACK, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
RAY--RAY, LISTEN.
I WASN'T
BLOWING SMOKE.
IT'S A COLONY
OF RATS.
THEY BRED 'EM
IN A LAB.
THEY ESCAPED.
THEY GOTTA BE
DESTROYED NOW.
NOW, RAY,
BEFORE THEY SPREAD.
I'M NOT DOIN' ANYTHING
UNTIL THERE'S BEEN
A THOROUGH INVESTIGATION.
RAY, HAVE YOU
LOST YOUR MIND
SINCE YOU JOINED FORCES
WITH THIS CITY?
THESE RATS ARE CARRYING
WEIL'S DISEASE.
THEY'RE AGGRESSIVE.
IF THEY GET OUT THERE
AND CROSSBREED
WITH THE REST OF
THE RATS IN THE CITY,
WE'RE REALLY SCREWED.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
NO. YOU'RE GOING TO
BE THE ONE THAT'S SCREWED.
IF YOU STICK YOUR FACE
IN THIS MESS AGAIN,
I'M GOING TO PERSONALLY
SUSPEND YOUR LICENSE,
AND I WILL THROW
YOUR ASS IN JAIL.
THAT'LL FIX THE PROBLEM.
I MEAN IT, JACK!
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
OK, I GOT AN IDEA.
BUT I NEED YOUR HELP.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, MS. PAGE.
A MAN'S GOTTA DO
WHAT A MAN'S GOTTA DO.
ALL RIGHT.
OFF YOU GO.
I HATE RATS. UHH.
I THOUGHT I'D
SEEN IT ALL, JACK.
Jack: STICK AROUND.
YOU MIGHT SEE
ANOTHER SIGHT OR TWO
IF WE'RE LUCKY.
SO, UH, WHICH WAY
DO WE SEND THIS THING?
UPTOWN.
TOWARDS THE REC CENTER,
ABOUT 4 BLOCKS.
TY, LISTEN.
I CAN'T GUARANTEE
PHENYLALKAPHINE
WILL WORK.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
USE SOMETHING STRONGER.
SHUT UP.
LET'S FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE SHOULD
DO NEXT.
ALL RIGHT.
STAY HERE AND MAKE SURE
THIS DAMN THING
DOES WHAT IT'S
SUPPOSED TO, OK?
GOTCHA.
ALL RIGHT.
READY?
AM I READY? YEAH.
YOU READY?
I'M READY. LET'S GO.
WE'RE OUTTA HERE.
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS
FROM THE CITY
HAVE A HABIT
OF DROPPING IN
WITHOUT CALLING.
WELL, YOU KNOW
HOW THE HEALTH
DEPARTMENT IS.
YEAH, I HEARD THAT.
YOU'D THINK THEY WERE
THE SECRET SERVICE
THE WAY THEY
STRUT AROUND HERE.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA
DO IN HERE?
WELL, HARRY, WE'RE
GONNA BAIT THE POOL.
THEN WE'RE GONNA
LINE THE PERIMETER
WITH A SERIES OF LOW-LEVEL
INCENDIARY DEVICES.
THEN WE'RE GONNA
WAIT FOR IT
TO FILL UP WITH RATS...
AND THEN WE'RE
GONNA ZAP 'EM.
IT'S FINE WITH ME,
SO LONG AS YOU GOT
THE PAPERWORK.
[MOTOR DIES]
OH, THIS IS BAD.
I LOST A SERVO.
I DON'T HAVE ONE
TO REPLACE IT WITH.
SORRY.
[HEAVY SIGH]
I DON'T WANNA HEAR THAT.
NOT AT ALL.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
HEY--HEY, THAT'S
GONNA HURT THE POOL.
IT'S OK, HARRY.
THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT WILL PAY
FOR THE WHOLE THING
TO BE REDONE
WHEN WE'RE FINISHED.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
[CHITTERS]
[SQUEAKING]
[FRENZIED SCREECHING]
[RATS SCREECHING]
IT'S TIME TO GO.
TY, TALK TO ME.
YEAH, HEY,
I'M HERE, MAN.
NOT GETTIN' PAID
NEARLY ENOUGH MONEY
FOR WHAT I'M DOIN'.
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHY AREN'T YOU HERE?
Ty, over radio:
MANUAL DELIVERY.
LITTLE RED WAGON
BROKE DOWN.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
YOU GET OUTTA THERE.
WE GOT OUR FIRST CUSTOMERS
HERE ALREADY.
Jack:
YOU GOT PLACES TO BAIL?
ABOUT EVERY
20 FEET OR SO.
Jack: WATCH YOUR ASS.
[SCREECHING]
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
TELL ME TWICE.
[FRENZIED SCREECHING]
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS WORKING
A LOT FASTER
THAN I THOUGHT.
HERE, LAY THESE OUT.
WE'RE GONNA SET 8 OF THESE
AROUND THE POOL.
SPACE 'EM EVENLY.
THEN WE'RE GONNA
WIRE 'EM TOGETHER
AND BLOW 'EM ALL AT ONCE.
NO SHRAPNEL, JUST ONE
MAJOR CONCUSSIVE BLAST.
AS LONG AS IT
KILLS THEM.
HERE, RUN THIS DOWN.
[STRAINED GROAN]
[BEEPS]
WE'RE SET.
OK.
Jack: TY, I'M READY TO GO.
WHERE ARE YOU?
COULD YOU SHUT UP, JACK?
TY, WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU, DAMN IT?!
ONE MORE TO GO.
TY, I'M READY TO GO,
BUT I CAN'T DO IT
WITHOUT YOU HERE.
TY!
[PANICKED CRY]
AAH!
THE AIR VENT.
TY?!
[SCREAMING]
AAH!
SUSAN!
[SUSAN CRIES OUT]
[SHRIEKING]
SUSAN! SUSAN,
WHERE ARE YOU?
AAH!
SUSAN!
UNH!
REACH UP. REACH UP
FOR MY HAND!
SUSAN.
SUSAN, REACH
FOR MY HAND!
OH!
I'VE GOT YOU.
HOLD ON.
PULL, SUSAN.
[SCREAMING]
COME ON, COME ON!
[BEEPING]
[PAINED SCREECHING]
[SCREAMING]
Susan: TOLD YOU
I WAS LUCKY.
NOT LUCKY, EXCEPTIONAL.
EVEN THE DOCTOR
SAID SO.
SO, WHAT DO YOU GUYS
WANNA DO NOW?
HOW 'BOUT
SOME LUNCH?
YEAH.
I'M REALLY HUNGRY.
I KNOW A GREAT
MOM-AND-POP PLACE
IN LITTLE ITALY.
YES, BUT
IS IT SAFE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU KNOW,
I HEAR
THE CITY'S FINEST
HAVE A REPUTATION.
[LAUGHS]
SUSAN, DON'T WORRY.
THEY'RE A CLIENT.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
[TRASH RUSTLING]
[SCREECHING]