CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
CONCORDE-NEW HORIZONS CORPORATION
[CAWING]
[CREAKING]
[DOOR LATCH OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[CRASH]
[PANICKED CRIES]
NO--NO!
NO, PLEASE!
PLEASE, NO...
[WHIMPERING]
AAH!
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANYTHING
IN AN HOUR.
WHAT'S THE TRIP LOCATOR
SAY, DAD?
100 MILES.
NO PROBLEM. THERE'S GAS
IN LESS THAN 50.
WILL YOU FILL IT
WITH PREMIUM, PLEASE?
SELF-SERVE.
NO PREMIUM.
HEY...I'D LIKE
ONE OF THESE.
WHAT'D IT COST?
WELL, THEY'RE NOT CHEAP.
ABOUT AS BIG
AS MY TRAILER
AND A HELL
OF A LOT NICER.
[FLY BUZZING]
WHAT DO YOU THINK--
COW?
MAYBE, LIKE,
SOME GERIATRIC COW.
ROAD KILL.
3 DAYS OLD.
DISGUSTING.
Patty: ALL RIGHT,
YOU GUYS,
YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
DON'T EAT IT.
WE'VE GOT STUFF
IN THE CAR.
HEY.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE FOOD?
NO, NO, UH...
THE FOOD'S FINE.
WE JUST WEREN'T
THAT HUNGRY.
CAN WE HAVE
THE CHECK?
SURE.
SO, WHERE, EXACTLY,
IS THIS GHOST TOWN?
MINING TOWN.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF IT'S STILL THERE.
CHECK IT OUT.
ETHAN'S DAD HAD THIS MAP
FROM THE FORTIES
OR SOMETHING.
AND THE TOWN, WEAVER,
IS ON THE OLD MAP,
BUT IT'S NOT ON
ANY OF THE NEW ONES.
COULD BE REALLY COOL.
DON'T YOU HAVE
ENOUGH PICTURES
OF FALLING DOWN BUILDINGS
AND RUSTY JUNK?
COME ON, DAD,
WASN'T THAT THE DEAL?
WE'D ALL DO THE WHOLE
FAMILY ADVENTURE THING,
BUT IF ANY OF US WANT
A SIDE TRIP, WE'D DO IT?
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
THE TURNOFF'S
ONLY A COUPLE MILES
FROM HERE.
SO...HOW FAR IS
THIS MOTEL TONIGHT?
ABOUT 200 MILES.
I'VE GOT TO CHECK IN
WITH THE OFFICE,
SO YOU GUYS
FIGURE IT OUT.
I'M WITH YOU EITHER WAY.
THAT'S, WHAT,
3 HOURS?
YOU WANT TO GET THERE
AT 4:00 IN THE AFTERNOON
AND THEN WHAT,
WE WATCH TV?
I WANT TO SWIM.
YOU'LL SWIM,
JUST LATER.
COME ON, DAD,
WE'RE NEVER GONNA
BE HERE AGAIN.
WE'LL SEE.
THERE'S SUPPOSEDLY AN OLD
MINING TOWN CALLED WEAVER.
IT'S UP IN THE HILLS
NOT TOO FAR FROM HERE.
YOU EVER HEARD OF IT?
BILLY, YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT A TOWN CALLED WEAVER?
CAN'T HELP YOU
THERE, MISTER.
YEAH, WELL,
IT'S ON THIS OLD MAP--
NEVER HEARD
OF IT.
HOW WAS YOUR MEAL?
GREAT.
IT WAS GREAT.
KEEP THE CHANGE.
NO, I DIDN'T EXPECT THAT
FROM THE DISCOUNTS.
NO. IS ARTHUR HAPPY
WITH HIS TOUR SCHEDULE?
MM-HMM.
SHE'S ALWAYS
ON THE PHONE, DAD.
WELL, SHE IS NOW.
SHE'S GOT 2 BOOKS
COMING OUT NEXT WEEK.
MAYBE SHE SHOULD HAVE
STAYED HOME.
LISTEN, KATIE,
PATTY'S A MEMBER
OF THE FAMILY NOW,
AND SHE'S PUT
A LOT OF EFFORT
INTO MAKING
THIS WORK,
INCLUDING TAKING OFF
AT A BAD TIME.
SO CUT HER A LITTLE
SLACK, WILL YOU?
SORRY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
EXCUSE ME.
WE'RE TRYING
TO GET TO WEAVER.
LITTLE MINING TOWN.
WE GOT A MAP
SAYS THERE'S A TURNOFF
A COUPLE MILES
DOWN THE ROAD.
WEAVER?
MM, I DON'T KNOW
ANY WEAVER.
OH.
WANT SOME ADVICE?
STAY ON THE PAVEMENT.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
WHAT I SAID.
RIGHT. THANKS.
MAN, AND SHE WONDERED WHY
WE WEREN'T EATING THE FOOD.
[IMITATING WAITRESS]
"BURNT ENOUGH FOR YOU?
'CAUSE WE CAN INCINERATE
THAT PUPPY A LITTLE MORE."
THEY PROBABLY CRUISE
THE HIGHWAY EVERY MORNING
LOOKING FOR
THE LUNCH SPECIAL.
YEAH, BUT IF IT'S
REALLY FLATTENED,
IT'S HARD TO GET
THE HAIR OUT.
[ALL GROAN]
OH, GROSS!
THAT PLACE WAS
WEIRD.
CLOSE ENCOUNTER
OF THE WEIRD KIND.
KEEP YOUR EYE OUT, DAD.
IT SHOULD BE RIGHT
UP HERE SOMEWHERE.
OH. LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
A ROAD RIGHT UP HERE.
UM...
HOW FAR IS THIS RUIN
SUPPOSED TO BE?
ACCORDING TO THE MAP,
IT SHOULD BE JUST
IN THOSE HILLS.
ABOUT 35 MILES.
35 MILES?
YOU REALLY WANT TO
PHOTOGRAPH THIS PLACE?
I'M PSYCHED.
WELL?
WELL...
LET'S GO TO WEAVER.
ALL RIGHT!
PATTY ROCKS!
LET'S GO.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
Patty: LOOKS LIKE
AN OLD PLANE.
CAN WE GO LOOK?
WELL...NO PROBLEM.
HOW LONG HAS THIS
BEEN HERE, DAD?
I DON'T KNOW.
A LONG TIME.
THE SIXTIES, MAYBE.
IT'S AMAZING.
PROBABLY
RAN OUT OF GAS.
YOU DON'T JUST
NOSE IN LIKE THIS
IF YOU RUN OUT
OF GAS.
YOU GLIDE IT IN
AND TRY TO LAND IT.
IF HE CAME STRAIGHT IN,
IT'D BE IN 1,000 PIECES.
MAYBE IT WAS NIGHTTIME
AND THEIR INSTRUMENTS
WERE BROKE.
THEY DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THEY WERE GOING DOWN
UNTIL IT HIT.
[HORN HONKS]
Kate: COME ON, GUYS,
LET'S GO.
GOT ENOUGH PICTURES, MATT?
YEAH.
THIS IS SO COOL.
IT'S LIKE ONE SECOND
YOU'RE ALIVE,
AND THEN, WHAM,
YOU'RE TOAST.
NOT SO COOL
IF YOU'RE THE TOAST.
[HORN HONKS]
OH, COME ON, MATT.
LET'S GO.
I BET IT
DIDN'T EVEN HURT.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THEY HOLD THE ROOM.
I WONDER IF
THIS MINING TOWN EXISTS.
IF WE LOOK AROUND
FOR ABOUT AN HOUR...
WE OUGHT TO MAKE
THE MOTEL AROUND 9:00.
OK.
NO...COMPLETELY DEAD.
MUST BE THE MOUNTAINS.
HEY, LOOK AT THIS.
WE'RE HEADING EAST,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
A COUPLE MILES AGO,
THE COMPASS SAID
WE WERE HEADING EAST.
NOW IT SAYS
WE'RE HEADING SOUTH.
WE HAVEN'T CHANGED
DIRECTION.
OH, THERE WE GO.
OOPS. AND NOW IT DIES
ALTOGETHER.
[ETHAN HUMMING
EERIE MUSIC]
YOU ARE ENTERING A WORLD
WHERE COMPASSES GO CRAZY...
AIRPLANES FALL
FROM THE SKY...
CELL PHONES DON'T WORK.
A WORLD WHERE...
MORONS
ARE STILL MORONS.
WOW.
OH, THIS IS WAY COOL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE NO ONE
BACK AT THE DINER
KNEW ABOUT THIS.
MAYBE THEY DID.
YEAH. THEY DON'T
WANT TOURISTS
RIPPING IT OFF.
WELL, I DIDN'T SEE
ANY SIGNS.
NOTHING THAT SAID
"NO TRESPASSING."
WOW.
MAYBE THEY DIDN'T
KNOW ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT ON
ANY OF THE NEW MAPS.
THAT'S HARD
TO BELIEVE.
SURE DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE ANYBODY'S BEEN HERE.
WHY WOULD EVERYONE
JUST LEAVE?
THIS WHOLE MOUNTAIN
LOOKS LIKE AN OLD MINE.
HEY, GUYS,
COME LOOK AT THIS.
WHAT'S UP WITH THIS?
Patty: IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY JUST WALKED AWAY
AND NEVER CAME BACK.
HEY...A MANUAL TYPEWRITER.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ONE OF THESE
IN A WHILE.
HEY, ETHAN, WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE SOME OF THIS
AND SEE IF
ANYTHING HAPPENS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU SURE?
YEAH, BUT YOU
GO RIGHT AHEAD.
DON'T EVEN JOKE, GUYS.
HEY, IF ANYONE'S HUNGRY,
I THINK THEY'RE
STILL SERVING NEXT DOOR.
Matt: OH,
THIS IS TOO WEIRD.
REMEMBER WHEN
WE WENT TO BODIE?
IT WAS A LOT
LIKE THIS.
OLD MINING TOWN,
AND THE FURNITURE
WAS STILL OUT.
KITCHEN...
DISHES EVERYWHERE.
BUT THAT WAS A STATE PARK.
THEY HAVE RANGERS
LIVING THERE
TO MAKE SURE
NOTHING IS DISTURBED.
THIS CALENDAR IS FROM 1948.
THAT WAS 54 YEARS AGO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS,
LIKE, 1800s OR SOMETHING.
WELL, THAT'S WHEN
IT WAS BUILT,
BUT...ELECTRIC LIGHTING,
GENIUS.
SO AFTER LUNCH ONE DAY,
EVERYONE JUST LEFT?
HEY, DAD, I'M GONNA
TAKE SOME PICTURES
OVER HERE, OK?
YEAH. JUST BE CAREFUL,
WILL YOU?
THE FLOOR IN HERE
IS NOT THAT STABLE.
[DOOR CREAKS]
WHOA.
UHH!
CHILL!
YOU CHILL.
LOOK AT THIS THING!
YOW.
THAT'S SICK.
WHAT IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
SKIN OF SOMETHING.
YEAH, BUT WHAT?
DON'T DO THAT.
JUST LEAVE IT ALONE,
OK?
LOOK HOW THEY PAINTED
ON IT AND STUFF.
LET'S JUST
GET OUT OF HERE.
WELL, IT'S TIME
TO GO, ANYWAY,
SO LET'S NOT WORRY
ABOUT IT, OK?
BUT THAT WAS
A SKIN, DAD,
AND IT WAS, LIKE,
PUT THERE ON PURPOSE.
Ethan: I SAW A MOVIE
WHERE THEY HAD
WEIRD STUFF
LIKE BONES
IN A HOUSE.
AND THEN A GUY
WITH A CHAIN SAW,
AND HE WENT
AROUND-- ETHAN.
SORRY.
[ENGINE WON'T CATCH]
VERY FUNNY, DAD.
I'M NOT JOKING,
MATT.
[ENGINE WON'T CATCH]
HUH. LIGHTS WERE OFF,
TRANSMISSION'S IN PARK.
WELL, LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
LOOKS LIKE AN ENGINE.
YEAH, THAT WOULD
BE MY GUESS, TOO.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THE PROBLEM IS?
MM.
CAR WON'T START.
TELL ME WE'RE NOT
SPENDING THE NIGHT HERE.
Jim: MATT, PASS ME
THE CHEESE THERE.
Patty: THIS WASN'T
SO BAD.
IT WORKED OUT
PRETTY GOOD.
WHAT, EXACTLY,
IS VAPOR LOCK, DAD?
WELL, IT'S, UH...
A KIND OF HEAT...
CAR THING.
WHEN YOU DRIVE
FOR A WHILE,
LIKE WE DID TODAY,
AND THEN STOP,
VAPOR CAN ACCUMULATE
IN THE FUEL LINE.
YEAH, THE ONLY THING
YOU CAN DO IS WAIT
UNTIL IT DISSIPATES.
RIGHT.
HOPEFULLY IT'LL START UP
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
IT'S THAT WORD
THAT WORRIES ME.
WHAT WORD?
HOPEFULLY.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT ALL THAT STUFF,
PATTY?
IT'S THE GREAT THING
ABOUT BEING AN EDITOR.
WE PUT OUT THE FOOL'S GUIDE
TO CAR REPAIR.
I'VE HAD TO READ 'EM ALL.
[CHUCKLES]
COOL.
[OWL HOOTING]
HEY...
LOOK WHAT I FOUND.
THIS WAS BEHIND
A BOX.
IT'S ALL DIRTY.
THAT'LL PLAY IN OURS.
WELL, LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
Woman on video: WE DON'T
EVEN HAVE ENOUGH ROOM--
Man on video: OK...OK...
[SEVERAL VOICES]
All in video: WHOO-HOO!
[WIND INTERFERENCE
IN MICROPHONE]
Ethan: HEY, THAT'S
THE PLACE WE STOPPED.
Patty: THERE'S OUR WAITRESS.
HEY, THAT STORE'S HERE.
UH-HUH.
Woman: WHAT'S UP?
NOTHING HERE.
I KNOW. IT'S GREAT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
THIS IS WILD.
BRIAN'S BEEN MISSING
FOR OVER AN HOUR.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING,
WE KEEP LOOKING,
BUT THE CAR WON'T START,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY.
[VOICE QUAVERING]
I-IT'S JUST ME NOW.
EVERYBODY'S GONE.
[WOMAN CRYING, GASPING]
MITCHELL AND BRIAN
AND STEVE.
OH, MY GOD...
NO--NO!
WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
[MUFFLED VOICES]
Patty: IT COULD JUST BE
A JOKE.
THE ONE GUY
THAT WAS MISSING...
MAYBE HE'S PLAYING
A PRACTICAL JOKE
ON THE OTHERS,
TRYING TO SCARE THEM.
THEY'RE DEAD.
I DON'T THINK--
YOU DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
Jim: CUT IT OUT, KATIE.
DON'T USE THAT TONE
OF VOICE.
FINE. SORRY.
THAT LOOKED
PLENTY REAL TO ME.
AND SOMETHING
WAS AFTER HER.
HOW DO WE KNOW
IT'S NOT STILL HERE?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,
EVERYBODY JUST
COOL IT, OK.
NOW, WE DON'T KNOW
THAT ANYTHING'S HERE,
AND WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT TAPE IS.
WELL,
WHAT COULD IT BE?
WELL, IT COULD BE
A--A STUDENT FILM.
OR, LIKE PATTY SAID,
IT COULD BE
A PRACTICAL JOKE THAT
SOMEBODY LEFT BEHIND.
I MEAN, THERE'S ANY NUMBER
OF EXPLANATIONS FOR IT.
IT'S A...
LOOK, WHATEVER IT IS,
WHAT--WHAT HAPPENED
ON THAT TAPE
HAPPENED
A LONG TIME AGO.
Patty: ABSOLUTELY.
LOOK AT THIS.
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
THIS HAS BEEN
SITTING HERE?
ONE, 2 YEARS?
EVEN LONGER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THERE'S NO SIGN
ANYBODY'S BEEN
IN THIS TOWN.
THERE'S NOT A FOOTPRINT
OUT THERE,
NOT A TIRE TRACK.
THERE'S NO TRASH BLOWING
AROUND IN THE STREET.
SO I DON'T WANT YOU GUYS
WHIPPING YOURSELVES UP
OVER NOTHING, OK?
ALL RIGHT,
SO LET'S, UH--
LET'S LAY OUR SLEEPING
BAGS OUT ON THE FLOOR...
GET A GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP,
AND TOMORROW MORNING
WE'LL BE OUT OF HERE.
OK? GET TO IT. COME ON.
THIS IS BAD, MAN.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOUR DAD SAYS.
YOU SOUND SCARED.
YOU SCARED?
HELL, NO.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD A GUN.
YEAH, WELL, I--
I KEEP IT IN THE GARAGE.
I ONLY BROUGHT IT ALONG
'CAUSE--
WELL, IN CASE
WE BROKE DOWN OR SOMETHING.
YOU STILL SHOULD
HAVE TOLD ME.
RIGHT.
SORRY.
RIGHT ABOUT NOW
I WOULDN'T ARGUE
AGAINST IT.
THAT TAPE...
PRETTY SCARY.
YEAH.
I DON'T THINK
THAT GIRL WAS ACTING.
WELL, IF SHE WAS,
SHE WAS REALLY GOOD.
[CLOSES CAR DOOR]
I CAN'T IMAGINE THAT
WHOEVER WAS AFTER THEM
WOULD STILL BE HERE.
NO.
NO. NOT AFTER
SO MUCH TIME.
[CLOSES CAR DOOR]
THEN WE HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
RIGHT.
SO YOU WENT
TO GET THE GUN
BECAUSE...
I HATE TO BE WRONG.
LET'S GO.
Jim: I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETIMES
I DON'T GET IT.
I KNOW.
BUT MATT'S OLDER.
I THINK HE JUST
HIDES IT BETTER.
YEAH, WELL,
KATIE DOESN'T...
BUT SHE'S SUCH
A SWEET KID.
WHERE DOES THAT
ATTITUDE COME FROM?
FROM BEING 12?
IT'S HARD ENOUGH
WHEN YOUR MOM DIES
AND YOUR DAD REMARRIES.
IT'S TOUGH.
THAT WAS
5 YEARS AGO.
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS SORT OF HOPING
THAT THIS TRIP
WOULD BE A...
I DON'T KNOW.
A BONDING THING?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
NEW FAMILY CREATES
NEW MEMORIES.
OH. WELL, WE'RE
DEFINITELY DOING THAT.
OH, NO.
I'LL FILL IT.
NO, JUST LEAVE IT.
IT'S OK.
REALLY.
[OWL HOOTS]
[BUMP]
[SIGHS]
[SHRIEK]
DAD?
Patty: JIM!
DAD!
Matt:
WHO'S UP THERE?!
Kate: DAD!
HEY, IT'S ME, IT'S ME.
EVERYTHING'S OK.
IT'S ME, IT'S ME.
IT'S JUST ME.
EVERYTHING'S OK.
I DON'T THINK.
NO, THERE'S NOTHING
UP THERE.
NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
DON'T BE SCARED.
YOU WERE SCARED.
WELL, I--
I HEARD THIS NOISE,
AND I WENT UP THERE
TO CHECK IT OUT.
IT WAS--
IT WAS NOTHING.
IT WAS JUST THE WIND
BLOWING AGAINST THE WINDOWS.
WHY DID YOU YELL?
WELL, I--
IT WAS JUST THIS--THIS OWL.
IT CAME OUT OF...
IT SURPRISED ME, THAT'S ALL.
LOOK,
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT.
JUST GET BACK
IN YOUR BAGS NOW AND...
JUST GO BACK TO BED.
COME ON.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
I'M SURE.
COME ON,
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
GO BACK TO SLEEP, HUH?
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Jim: YOU CAN HAVE
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
I WANT PANCAKES.
ANYPLACE BUT THAT DINER.
WELL, IF YOU CAN WAIT
UNTIL THE NEXT TOWN,
SO CAN I.
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
EVEN PACKING?
'CAUSE WE'RE
OUTTA HERE.
IF THE CAR STARTS.
NOW, THINK POSITIVELY,
KATIE.
DAD, YOUR CAR IS GONE.
I DON'T GET IT.
I WOULD HAVE
HEARD SOMETHING.
WHERE ARE THE KEYS?
[CREAKING]
SOMEBODY STOLE THE CAR,
AND THAT'S IT.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY MUST HAVE
FOLLOWED US HERE
AND THEN SOMEHOW
DISABLED THE CAR
WHILE WE WERE
LOOKING AROUND.
SO WHY DIDN'T WE HEAR
THE CAR START LAST NIGHT?
I DON'T THINK
THEY STARTED IT.
NO, I THINK THEY--
THEY SLIPPED IT INTO NEUTRAL
AND PUSHED IT DOWN THE STREET
ONTO A TRAILER.
IT'S PROBABLY HALFWAY
TO MEXICO BY NOW.
[SIGHS]
WE'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO WALK OUT OF HERE
AS A GROUP.
I KNOW.
MATT, I WANT YOU TO STAY
HERE WITH PATTY AND KATE.
ETHAN, YOU'LL COME WITH ME.
IS THAT OK?
THAT'S COOL.
DAD, THAT GAS STATION
MUST BE 35 MILES BACK.
WELL, THAT'S IF WE
GO BACK BY THE ROAD,
BUT IF WE CUT STRAIGHT
ACROSS THE DESERT,
IT SHOULD BE MORE LIKE 20.
20's NOTHING.
YEAH, WE OUGHT TO BE ABLE
TO GET THERE IN, UH,
I DON'T KNOW, 6, 7 HOURS.
Kate:
THIS IS A BAD IDEA,
ANOTHER BAD IDEA.
WE SHOULD
STICK TOGETHER.
EVERYBODY HIKE OUT.
HON, 20 MILES IS A LONG WAY.
NOW, IF SOMEONE
CAN'T MAKE IT,
THEN WE'RE ALL IN TROUBLE.
ETHAN AND I OUGHT TO BE
ABLE TO GO FASTER
THAN THE GROUP.
WE'RE GONNA BE SKINNED
AND NAILED TO THE WALL,
AND NOBODY'S EVER
GONNA KNOW.
HEY, SWEETIE,
WHOEVER WAS HERE LAST NIGHT
WAS HERE FOR THE CAR,
NOT FOR US.
NOW THEY'RE GONE.
KATIE, NOTHING BAD'S
GONNA HAPPEN.
PROMISE.
AND YOUR DAD WILL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
THE WATER BOTTLE
STILL INSIDE?
YEAH.
I DON'T ANTICIPATE
ANY TROUBLE.
IF I DID,
I WOULDN'T LEAVE YOU HERE.
I WANT YOU
TO LEAVE THE GUN.
OH, BUT YOU HATE GUNS.
YOU EVER USE ONE?
YEAH.
MY DAD USED TO TAKE ME
TO THE RANGE.
I DON'T LIKE GUNS,
BUT I CAN SHOOT.
TRUST ME.
WHAT ELSE DON'T I KNOW?
OH. WELL...
LOTS.
I KNOW IT'S
OUR BEST OPTION...
BUT I DON'T LIKE
YOU GOING OFF.
SO...
GET BACK FAST, OK?
OK.
Jim: YEAH, IT HAPPENED
ABOUT 5 YEARS AGO.
SEPTEMBER.
LISTEN, IF YOU WANT
TO TAKE A BREAK,
WE CAN STOP
ANY TIME, HUH?
NO, IT'S OK.
I DIDN'T KNOW MATT THEN.
HE TALKS ABOUT HER
A LOT, THOUGH.
YEAH?
JUST HOW GREAT
HIS MOM WAS
AND HOW HE MISSES HER
AND STUFF.
HE NEVER SAYS
HOW SHE DIED.
DID YOU EVER ASK HIM?
HE JUST SAYS SHE GOT SICK.
WELL,
IT WAS AN ANEURISM.
IT HAPPENED
REALLY QUICK,
AND SHE WAS GONE.
OH. SORRY ABOUT THAT,
MR. HENLEY--
WHOA!
DON'T MOVE.
OH, MAN.
NO, NO. NOW,
JUST DON'T MOVE.
JUST DON'T MOVE
A MUSCLE, ALL RIGHT?
JUST GET IT
AWAY FROM ME.
NOW, JUST DON'T TALK.
OW! AAH!
I GOT BIT!
MY BATTERIES ARE DEAD.
DUH. YOU ONLY
USE THEM 24/7.
ARE WE JUST GONNA
SIT HERE ALL DAY?
THE FACT IS,
IF SOMEONE'S AFTER US,
THEY COULD GET US
JUST AS GOOD SITTING INSIDE
AS THEY COULD
WALKING AROUND OUTSIDE.
BUT DAD SAID THERE WAS
NO ONE HERE, ANYWAY.
WE STICK TOGETHER,
ALL RIGHT?
IT HURTS!
IT REALLY HURTS.
I DON'T WANNA
DIE, PLEASE!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DIE.
YOU WEREN'T BITTEN.
YEAH, I WAS.
THIS IS YOUR LUCKY DAY.
IT GOT YOUR WALLET.
SOME OF THESE
ARE REALLY OLD.
THIS ONE'S FROM 1850.
GREAT EPITAPH.
LISTEN.
"POORLY LIVED
AND POORLY DIED,
POORLY BURIED,
AND NO ONE CRIED."
COOL.
GOTTA GET THAT.
PEOPLE DIDN'T
LIVE VERY LONG BACK THEN.
SOME OF THESE GUYS
WERE DEAD IN THEIR 20s.
MM-HMM.
WELL, MINING
WAS DANGEROUS WORK.
HEY, GUYS...
YOU GOTTA SEE THIS.
I THINK DAD MIGHT HAVE
BEEN WRONG ABOUT THAT TAPE.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
THAT WAS WEIRD.
THOSE COLORS,
IT WASN'T
A RATTLESNAKE.
NO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
IT WAS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
WHAT'S THAT?
IS THAT
A HALLUCINATION?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL,
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S NOT A MIRAGE.
WE'RE TOO CLOSE.
COME ON.
DAD SHOULDN'T
HAVE LEFT US.
SOMEBODY KILLED
THOSE PEOPLE,
AND IT WASN'T
TOO LONG AGO.
MATT, WE DON'T KNOW
THAT ANYBODY KILLED ANYBODY.
YEAH, WE DO.
IT WAS ON TAPE.
I'M NOT A KID, PATTY.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU ARE.
THEN LET'S NOT PRETEND
THAT EVERYTHING'S COOL,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT.
SO NOT.
OK. BUT A GRAVE
DOES NOT MEAN MURDER.
HEY, IF NOBODY'S HERE,
NO PROBLEM.
THEN THAT'S OUR ASSUMPTION.
WE--WE HAVEN'T SEEN
OR HEARD ANYTHING HERE, RIGHT?
WE HAVE NO REASON
TO THINK OTHER THAN
BEING SPOOKED
BY SOME GRAVES
THAT SOMEBODY ELSE
IS HERE.
WELL, WHAT'S THE PLAN
IF WE'RE NOT ALONE?
YOUR DAD DIDN'T LEAVE US
WITHOUT PROTECTION.
WHOA.
NOW, I DON'T THINK
WE'RE GONNA NEED IT.
BUT IF WE DO...
WE'LL BE GLAD WE HAVE IT.
YOU SURE?
NO, IT'S GLASS.
WHY WOULD SOMEBODY PUT GLASS
OUT IN THE DESERT?
COME ON.
"GROUND ZERO:
"SITE OF THE FIRST
SUCCESSFUL DETONATION
"OF THE NEUTRON DEVICE.
"SEPTEMBER 21, 1948.
ATOMIC ENERGY
COMMISSION."
THAT LIKE
AN ATOMIC BOMB?
SORT OF.
WOULDN'T IT HAVE
LEVELED THAT OLD TOWN?
NO. THE NEUTRON BOMB
WAS A RADIATION DEVICE.
IT WAS DESIGNED
TO KILL PEOPLE,
LEAVE THE BUILDINGS
STANDING.
NO WAY.
YEAH.
MASSIVE AMOUNTS
OF RADIATION.
THEY NEVER USED IT.
SO WHERE'S THIS
GLASS COME FROM?
WELL, WE'RE STANDING
RIGHT WHERE THE BOMB EXPLODED.
GROUND ZERO.
INTENSE HEAT FROM
THE DETONATION MUST HAVE...
MUST HAVE TURNED
THE SAND INTO GLASS.
WOW.
ARE WE, LIKE,
GETTING RADIATED NOW?
NO, THAT WAS
OVER 50 YEARS AGO.
DO YOU THINK THAT'S
WHAT KILLED EVERYBODY
IN THE TOWN?
NO. I'M SURE
THEY WERE EVACUATED.
I JUST CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHY
THEY LEFT SO MUCH STUFF BEHIND.
COME ON. WE'VE BEEN WALKING
ABOUT 3 HOURS.
WE GOTTA MAKE TIME.
LET'S GO.
Patty: NO.
NO, HE SAID HE'D BE BACK
IN THE AFTERNOON SOMETIME.
HE SHOULD
BE BACK BY NOW.
HE'S ONLY
BEEN GONE 5 HOURS.
IF HE'S NOT BACK
BY SUNDOWN,
WE WALK BACK OUT,
STRAIGHT DOWN THE ROAD
TO THE DINER.
THAT'S 35 MILES.
BUT IT WILL BE DARK,
IT WON'T BE SO HOT,
AND--AND WE'LL
JUST TAKE IT EASY.
IT'S A BAD IDEA.
WHO KNOWS
WHAT THE HELL'S OUT THERE?
WHO KNOWS WHAT THE HELL
IS HERE?!
STOP IT,
BOTH OF YOU!
NOW...
I MAY JUST BE
YOUR STEPMOTHER,
BUT I'M THE ADULT,
AND I WILL DECIDE
WHAT WE DO
AND WHEN WE DO IT.
YOU GUYS GOT THAT?
I GOT IT.
YOU ARE JUST
MY STEPMOTHER.
NEVER TRIED TO BE
ANYTHING ELSE, KATE.
NOW, IF YOU TWO CAN
COEXIST FOR A MOMENT,
I'M GONNA GO FIND
A LADIES ROOM,
SUCH AS IT IS.
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHAT I DECIDE
WHEN I GET BACK.
[CREAKING]
AAH!
[GROANS]
OHH. OW.
MATT!
HELP!
I'M DOWN HERE!
MATT!
KATE!
OHH. OH.
YEAH...YOU'RE OK.
YEAH. YEAH.
OHH!
WHOA.
LONG WAY DOWN.
Ethan: CAN I HAVE
SOME MORE WATER?
THAT'S
THE LAST OF IT.
SHOULD BE
GETTING CLOSER.
ANOTHER HOUR?
MAYBE.
2 AT THE MOST.
NO NEED TO CARRY
THAT ANYMORE.
IT'S JUST ME NOW.
EVERYBODY'S GONE.
OH...MY GOD.
RACHEL
AND BRIAN AND STEVE...
OH, MY GOD.
NO--NO!
NO WAY
THAT'S NOT REAL.
PATTY SHOULD BE
BACK BY NOW.
OHH.
UHH.
YEAH.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
OHH.
PIECE OF CAKE.
OH!
[GASPING]
NO!
PATTY?
PATTY!
PATTY, WHERE ARE YOU?!
SHH.
LISTEN.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO HER?
SHE DIDN'T GO FAR, OK?
LET'S NOT PANIC.
LET'S JUST CHECK
EACH OF THESE BUILDINGS.
PATTY, WHERE ARE YOU?!
PATTY!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[RUMBLE]
WHAT THE HELL?
[HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES]
PATTY?
PATTY.
[LOUD BREATHING]
PATTY!
PATTY?
WE GOTTA BE
GETTING CLOSE.
I BET WE CAN SEE
THE GAS STATION
FROM THE TOP.
YEAH, I BET WE CAN.
I'M GOING TO SEE.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
ETHAN!
ETHAN?
ETHAN?!
ETHAN!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
[CLATTERING]
WHAT...
WHAT IS THIS?
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS JIM'S.
OH...
OH!
ETHAN!
OH, NO.
NO.
NO. NO.
PATTY?
PATTY,
WHERE ARE YOU?
PATTY!
COME ON, LET'S TRY
THE OTHER SIDE.
I THOUGHT
I HEARD SOMETHING.
I DIDN'T.
PATTY?!
[FAINTLY] I'M DOWN HERE!
HELP ME!
SHE'S SOMEWHERE
IN THERE.
PATTY, WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M HERE!
I'M DOWN HERE!
PATTY, ARE YOU OK?
YES, I'M OK.
I'M COMING DOWN!
MATT, DON'T
COME DOWN HERE!
WE NEED A ROPE.
YOU STAY HERE.
I DON'T CARE,
I'M COMING DOWN!
MATT!
[ENGINE DEAD]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
MATT! MATT!
JUST TOSS THE ROPE.
THERE'S SOMETHING
DOWN HERE.
I DON'T CARE,
I'M COMING DOWN.
DON'T COME DOWN HERE!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT IT'S DOWN THERE.
AN ANIMAL OR WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
MATT, YOU GO FIRST.
I'LL FOLLOW.
KATE'S UP THERE.
SHE'S REALLY SCARED.
YOU GO.
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
HURRY UP, YOU GUYS!
MATT, GO NOW.
OK.
[GROWLING]
WHAT WAS THAT?!
HURRY, MATT! HURRY!
IT'S COMING! IT'S COMING!
SHOOT IT, PATTY!
SHOOT IT!
[HONKING HORN]
DAD! DAD!
PATTY FELL DOWN
THE MINE SHAFT,
AND MATT
WENT DOWN,
BUT SOMETHING'S THERE.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I GOT IT.
I FIRED 3 SHOTS
AND IT STOPPED COMING.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
THE HELL'S DOWN THERE.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
COME ON! COME ON!
THE CAR?
WHERE'D YOU FIND IT.
THE DESERT.
WHERE'S ETHAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T KNOW?!
IS HE AT THE DINER?
WE DIDN'T MAKE IT
TO THE DINER.
WHERE DID YOU GO?
DAD! OH, NO!
DAD, GET US
OUT OF HERE.
WE'RE TRAPPED!
WE'RE NOT TRAPPED.
AAH!
WHAT WAS THAT?!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
HE DISAPPEARED?
YOU WERE
IN THE DESERT.
YOU--YOU CAN SEE
FOR MILES
IN EVERY DIRECTION.
HE DISAPPEARED.
HE JUST VANISHED,
ALL RIGHT?
HE WENT UP THIS
LITTLE HILL,
AND HE WENT DOWN
THE OTHER SIDE.
I WAS RIGHT
BEHIND HIM.
WHEN I GOT THERE
HE WAS GONE.
WHAT HAPPENED
OUT THERE?
I KNOW WE HIKED
IN A STRAIGHT LINE.
I KNOW IT!
WE ENDED UP
RIGHT WHERE WE STARTED.
WE HAVE TO
LOOK FOR HIM, DAD.
WE WILL.
I THINK WE GET TO
THE POLICE AND--
WE CAN'T LEAVE HIM!
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS.
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
WE'LL GET TO A PHONE,
WE'LL CALL THE SHERIFF.
THEY'LL ORGANIZE
A SEARCH PARTY.
IT'S GONNA BE DARK
IN AN HOUR.
THEY'LL KNOW HOW TO
COVER THE MOST GROUND.
DAD, WHAT'S
IN THAT TOWN?
I DON'T KNOW.
I NEED TO USE
YOUR PHONE.
USE IT ALL YOU WANT.
BUT THE LINE'S DEAD.
DAD, YOU GOTTA
COME, NOW!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[OWL HOOTING]
OF COURSE, I UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE CONCERNED,
BUT I REALLY
THINK IT'S BEST
IF WE JUST
WAIT UNTIL SUNRISE.
THEN I'LL HAVE
EVERYBODY OUT THERE,
AND WE'LL FIND HIM.
WELL, WHY NOT NOW?
HE'S A 16-YEAR-OLD BOY.
OK, LOOK.
THE DESERT IS A VERY
BIG PLACE, MR. HENLEY.
NOW, THE ODDS OF FINDING
HIM IN THE DARK
ARE EXTREMELY SLIM.
ESPECIALLY GIVEN
THE CONFUSION
YOU SEEM TO HAVE
OVER THE EXACT LOCATION.
NO, I AM NOT CONFUSED.
IT'S 2 OR 3 MILES WEST
OF WEAVER.
I TOLD YOU THAT!
OK. I'M GONNA
TAKE AT FACE VALUE
THAT YOU GOT A BOY
LOST OUT THERE
IN THE DESERT TONIGHT.
BUT YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU SOUND LIKE.
NOW, FIRST OF ALL,
THERE IS NO WEAVER.
NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
THERE WAS
NO TOWN OUT THERE
WHERE THE PEOPLE
WALKED OUT IN 1948
AND NEVER RETURNED.
LOOK, I WAS JUST THERE.
MY FAMILY AND I,
WE WERE JUST IN THE TOWN.
WELL, SEE,
THERE YOU GO.
YOU KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THESE THINGS
YOU SAY
ATTACKED YOU, BUT...
YOU DIDN'T SEE THEM.
YOU CAN'T EVEN TELL ME
WHETHER THEY WERE
HUMAN BEINGS.
YOU WANT TO VERIFY THIS
WITH MY WIFE?
SHE'S ACROSS THE STREET
GETTING FOOD FOR THE KIDS.
NOW, COME ON.
WE ARE NOT DESERT WACKOS.
I CAN SEE THAT.
BUT I CAN ALSO SEE THAT
YOU'VE HAD A VERY LONG,
EXHAUSTING HIKE
THROUGH A HOT DESERT
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DAY.
COME ON, LET'S JUST
STAY FOCUSED, OK?
YOU GOT YOUR
16-YEAR-OLD BOY
LOST OUT THERE
IN THE DESERT.
I PROMISE YOU,
AT SUNRISE I'LL HAVE
MEN ON HORSEBACK,
I'LL HAVE ATVs,
I'LL HAVE
A FIXED-WING AIRCRAFT
SEARCHING THE DESERT
LOOKING FOR YOUR BOY.
AND WE'LL FIND HIM,
PROBABLY BY 8 A.M.
RICH, COULD I BORROW YOU
FOR A SEC?
OK.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
MR. HENLEY.
HEY, MISTER.
OVER HERE.
Speaker: NUMBER 48,
YOUR ORDER'S READY.
THAT'S US.
I'LL GET IT.
SOMETHING WRONG?
NOBODY KNOWS WHAT'S
OUT THERE, OK?
BUT YOU SAW
WHAT YOU SAW.
WHAT, YOU MEAN THE TOWN?
YEAH. EVERYONE'S
PART OF IT ALL.
PART OF WHAT?
NOBODY KNOWS.
YOU, SEE, THERE'S
SOME PEOPLE SAY THAT
SOME KIND OF NEUTRON
BOMB EXPLODED THERE
BACK IN THE FORTIES,
AND THERE WAS
ALL THESE PEOPLE
DIDN'T WANT TO
BE EVACUATED,
SO THEY HID OUT IN
THE MINES UNDER THE TOWN,
AND THEN THEY GOT
ALL THIS...THIS RADIATION.
WHAT'S OUT THERE NOW
IS THEIR OFFSPRING.
ALL MUTATED AND WEIRD
AND BARELY HUMAN.
AND THE ANIMALS...
THEY'RE MONSTERS.
AND THEN...
THEN THERE'S
SOME PEOPLE SAY
THAT THAT AIN'T RIGHT.
THAT THE TOWN
WAS BUILT
ON SOME KIND OF SACRED
INDIAN BURIAL SITE,
AND IT'S THE SPIRITS
OF THE DEAD
COMING BACK TO HAUNT.
SUPERNATURAL.
YOU EVER HEAR
OF AREA 51?
YOU MEAN IN SCI-FI,
THAT GOVERNMENT
RESEARCH THING?
THAT DOESN'T EXIST.
DOESN'T EXIST.
OFFICIALLY.
BUT I'VE SEEN IT.
THEY'RE DOING SOME KIND
OF RESEARCH OUT THERE
WITH E.T.s
AND ALIENS.
AND THEY'VE GOT...
A BIG HANGAR
AND SOME KIND OF
CRASHED SPACECRAFT,
AND THEY SALVAGED
SOME OF THE BODIES
OUT OF IT.
WAIT, UH, YOU THINK
IT'S ALIENS?
I DIDN'T--
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
YEAH, WELL,
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M SAYING YOU SHOULD
JUST GET IN YOUR CAR
AND--AND DRIVE
OUT OF HERE.
DON'T LOOK BACK,
JUST G-G-GO.
GO.
JUST GO.
IT'S HER, I SWEAR.
SHE'S THE GIRL
IN THE VIDEOTAPE.
PATTY, YOU GO.
PLEASE.
I'LL GO.
HELP YA?
UH, WE NEED SOME KETCHUP.
WAS SOMEONE ELSE
WORKING HERE BEFORE?
BECCA, SHE
JUST GOT OFF. WHY?
NOTHING. MY SISTER
TOOK THE ORDER.
SHE THOUGHT...NOTHING.
THERE'S A MOTEL
AT THE END OF MAIN STREET.
I CALLED AND, UH,
THERE'S A ROOM
WAITING FOR YOU THERE.
THANKS.
TRY AND GET
SOME SLEEP, OK?
UH, SUNRISE IS AT 5:45.
WE'LL BE LEAVING THEN,
AND, WELL,
IF YOU'LL BE HERE,
YOU CAN RIDE WITH ME.
LISTEN, MY SON
HAS PHOTOGRAPHS.
THAT TOWN IS THERE.
LET'S JUST TRY
AND FIND ETHAN FIRST.
YOU CAN GO LOOKING FOR
YOUR GHOST TOWN AFTER THAT.
DEAL?
5:45.
YEAH.
HE WAS
TALKING TO ME.
I--I WASN'T
TALKING TO HIM.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
TO HIM.
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU THINK.
I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
DAD, THE GIRL
FROM THE VIDEO,
THE ONE WE THOUGHT
WAS DEAD--
WELL, SHE'S NOT.
SHE'S WORKING
AT THE DRIVE-IN.
HERE?
YEAH.
SHE MADE OUR FOOD.
KATE PICKED UP THE ORDER
WHEN OUR NUMBER
WAS CALLED.
THE GIRL--
WAS THE SAME ONE
ON THAT TAPE.
WHERE?
WHICH ONE IS SHE?
Matt: I ALREADY
CHECKED IT OUT.
SHE'S NOT THERE NOW.
SHE JUST GOT OFF WORK.
BUT SHE WAS THERE.
I SAW HER.
OK, OK,
I BELIEVE YOU.
THAT'S A GOOD
THING, RIGHT?
I MEAN,
SHE'S NOT DEAD.
WHAT ABOUT ETHAN?
ARE THEY GOING OUT?
SUNRISE.
FULL-ON SEARCH.
AIRPLANES
AND EVERYTHING.
DAD, WE CAN'T JUST
LEAVE HIM THERE ALL NIGHT.
IF THEY'RE NOT GONNA GO,
THEN WE HAVE TO GO, NOW.
LOOK, I HEAR YOU,
BUT WE'D NEVER
FIND HIM AT NIGHT,
AND I'M NOT TAKING
ANY OF YOU
BACK OUT THERE, OK?
WE SHOULD
CALL HIS PARENTS.
THEY'RE OUT OF TOWN
TILL SUNDAY.
THEY DROVE UP
TO SAN FRANCISCO.
OH, RIGHT.
I FORGOT.
WELL, THEN, I'LL LEAVE
A MESSAGE FOR THEM
WHEN WE GET
TO THE MOTEL.
WELL, LET'S HOPE
WE CAN LEAVE ANOTHER
ONE IN THE MORNING
THAT SAYS
EVERYTHING'S OK.
THEY OK?
YEAH. SOUND ASLEEP.
THEY'RE EXHAUSTED.
YOU SHOULD COME
TO BED, TOO, JIM.
NO, I WON'T SLEEP.
I'M FINE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
[SIGHS] I JUST
KEEP THINKING.
I KEEP SEEING--
I MEAN, I WAS
RIGHT BEHIND HIM,
AND THEN HE WAS GONE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE NO ONE
KNOWS ABOUT THAT TOWN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
DEPUTY DOESN'T KNOW.
YEAH, WELL,
I GOT A FEELING HE DOES.
THE FIRST THING
IS TO FIND ETHAN
AND GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
AND THEN WE TALK
TO THE FBI,
THE STATE POLICE, WHOEVER.
HOW MANY CARS
DID YOU SEE OUT THERE
IN THE DESERT?
UM, 20.
MAYBE 30.
THERE COULD BE PEOPLE MISSING
FROM EVERY ONE OF THEM.
I KNOW.
COME ON, LESTER.
DON'T DO THIS.
I BETTER GET GOING.
HEY, SHOOT ME FIRST.
FOR GOD SAKES,
YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE ME.
I'D DO THE SAME FOR YOU.
SORRY, LESTER.
[CAR STARTS]
PLEASE! DON'T LEAVE ME!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
DAD.
YOU OK, HON?
I THINK SOMEONE WAS
JUST AT THE WINDOW.
I LOOKED...
IT WAS GONE.
I DON'T WANT TO
BE HERE, DAD.
COME HERE.
YOU KNOW...
WE CAN'T LEAVE ETHAN.
AND THEY'RE GONNA GO
SEARCHING FOR HIM
IN THE MORNING, SO--
DAD...
TAKE US
OUT OF THIS TOWN.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
IT FEELS WEIRD.
THEY'RE GONNA SEARCH FOR
ETHAN AT SUNRISE, RIGHT?
TAKE US
TO THE NEXT TOWN.
YOU CAN DRIVE BACK
IN THE MORNING
AND SEARCH WITH THEM.
JUST DO THIS FOR ME.
PLEASE.
THANKS, DAD.
YEAH.
SO...
WHERE DO YOU THINK?
WINDHAM.
ABOUT AN HOUR EAST.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE A COP, DAD.
Jim: OH?
GOING THE SPEED LIMIT.
WHAT THE HELL
DOES HE WANT?
JIM...
THERE'S NO REASON FOR HIM
TO PULL US OVER.
YOU SHOULD STOP, DAD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE GONNA STOP.
OH, SORRY.
I WAS FOOLING WITH
THE RADIO AND...
KIND OF LATE TO BE
LEAVING TOWN, ISN'T IT?
OH, WE'RE NOT
LEAVING TOWN. WE--
WELL, I'M JUST TAKING
THE FAMILY OVER TO WINDHAM,
THEN I'M RIGHT BACK
TO HELP WITH THE SEARCH.
MOTELS HERE AREN'T
THAT BAD, ARE THEY?
WELL, IT'S NOT REALLY THE--
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
BUT YOU WON'T NEED
TO COME BACK
IN THE MORNING
FOR THE SEARCH.
WHY IS THAT?
BECAUSE THERE'S NOBODY
OUT THERE IN THAT DESERT.
NOT ANYMORE.
WE FOUND HIM.
[DOOR OPENS]
Jim: ETHAN. ETHAN.
Patty: THANK GOD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I'M OK.
I'M REALLY TIRED.
WHAT HAPPENED OUT THERE?
YOU WENT OVER THAT HILL,
I WAS THERE IN A SECOND
AND YOU WERE GONE.
I SLIPPED.
HIT MY HEAD, I GUESS.
LOOKS LIKE HE FELL DOWN
A SMALL RAVINE.
RAVINE?
I PRACTICALLY FOLLOWED
IN HIS FOOTSTEPS.
I WOULD HAVE SEEN THAT.
WELL, WE CALL THEM
BLIND FALLS.
YOU DON'T SEE THEM
TILL YOU'RE IN THEM.
YOU CAN WALK RIGHT BY ONE
AND NOT EVEN KNOW IT.
ETHAN...
HOW'S YOUR HEAD NOW?
IT'S OK.
A LITTLE SORE.
I HAD A PARAMEDIC
CHECK HIM OUT.
HE'S A LITTLE TIRED,
A LITTLE DEHYDRATED.
HOW'D YOU FIND HIM?
WELL, LIKE I SAID,
I WASN'T PLANNING
ON MOUNTING A SEARCH
UNTIL THE MORNING, BUT, UH,
WELL, I SENT A COUPLE
OF MEN OUT ON ATVs
JUST IN CASE
WE GOT LUCKY.
CAN WE GO NOW?
WELL, WE SURE DON'T
WANT YOU AROUND HERE.
LET'S GO BACK
TO THE MOTEL.
WE'RE ALL PRETTY TIRED.
LET'S GO. COME ON.
I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
YOU GUYS DID A GREAT JOB.
LIKE I SAID,
WE JUST GOT LUCKY.
UH, MR. HENLEY...
ABOUT THAT, UH, TOWN
YOU TALKED ABOUT...
IF YOU WANT TO GO OUT
IN THE MORNING,
I'D, UH,
I'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
OH, I GOT A FEELING
MY FAMILY WANTS TO GET HOME.
NEXT TIME THROUGH.
THANKS AGAIN.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE HERE FOR.
YOU HAVE A SAFE TRIP, NOW.
WELL, GUYS,
PUSH ON TO WINDHAM
OR BACK
TO THE MOTEL?
WE ALREADY HAVE A ROOM.
I'M STILL NOT SURE
WHY WE LEFT THE HOTEL
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
KATE?
I DON'T WANT TO BE
IN THIS TOWN,
ANYWHERE NEAR THIS TOWN.
CAN WE JUST GO?
ETHAN?
WHATEVER.
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS,
HEAVY BREATHING]
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING,
WE GO TO A ONE-HOUR PLACE
AND GET MATT'S FILM DEVELOPED.
RIGHT.
[FOOTSTEPS]
JIM...
IF YOU WERE WALKING
RIGHT BEHIND ETHAN,
WOULDN'T YOU HAVE SEEN
WHERE HE FELL?
THERE WAS NO RAVINE.
SOMETHING HAPPENED
TO ETHAN,
BUT WHAT HE THINKS
HAPPENED TO HIM DIDN'T.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
MATT.
DON'T YOU WANT TO TRY AND GET
SOME SLEEP, HONEY?
I CAN'T.
MY MIND IS JUST...
WHAT WAS IN THAT MINE SHAFT?
WHERE ARE THE PEOPLE
FROM THOSE CARS IN THE DESERT?
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM?
MATT, LISTEN, UH,
TOMORROW WE'LL GET
YOUR FILM DEVELOPED AND THEN WE'LL HAVE--
JIM! AAH!
[FOOTSTEPS]
[MOANING FROM CAR]
Jim: ARE YOU OK?
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Jim: IT'S OUT THERE.
Patty: NO, NO--
[ALL SCREAMING]
[CREAKING]
[WIND BLOWING]
[CAWING]
[CAW]
[CAW CAW]
[CAMERA CLICKS]
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
SO HOW ARE THE KIDS?
GOOD.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD.
NEED SOME MENUS?
NICE BIKE.
[CAWING]
[WINGS FLAPPING, CAWING]
[CAW]
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S IT.
[CAWING]
[CLICK]
[CAW CAW]
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
CONCORDE-NEW HORIZONS CORPORATION
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE --www.ncicap.org--