Single file.
Stay to the right
of the line.
Take your time.
Take a good look.
Hey, um, are you sure
they can't see us?
One-way mirror, ma'am.
Picture, in 3... 2... 1.
A heinous crime
has been committed here.
Should you decide
that your testimony
might jeopardize
your personal safety.
Look, Sipowicz
I said I'd tell you everything.
I was just hoping
we could finish this up...
before menopause kicks in.
Let's start with the one that
thinks her shit don't stink...
Diane Weston.
She's like a goddamn
poster child for high school.
Morning, sunshine.
Remember, these are
the best days of your life.
So far.
She's the "A" squad captain.
She stole that title from me.
You should charge her
with that.
All right, girls
let's take it from the top.
And one, and two,
and one, and two...
Hi, Bruce.
You look cute.
Tommy Hilfiger.
I'm hoping
fourth year's the charm.
Outta my way, fag...
I'm up.
Lisa... is that you?
I lost a little weight.
Wow.
This really should've
been my year.
I had a lot of work done.
I mean, I had done a lot
of work over the summer.
You could tell
I made her nervous.
But they have to, you know
spread the talent around, so...
I've been on the "B" squad
for 4 years.
Now, the squad as a whole...
they're closer
than Carolina cousins.
I mean, some people say...
they're, like
lesbos or something...
but that's just mostly
the yag-offs in band.
Truth is, they're so close...
they all get their monthly visit
from Aunt Rose at the same time.
This one's Hannah Wald.
She's like this uber Christian
doesn't really say much.
In fact,
if she wasn't kind of pretty...
you'd go,
"Hey, who's the thrt?"
Then there's Cleo Miller.
Number one: Not a real C-cup.
I've been in the locker room.
And number two...
she has to see
the school shrink.
She's completely obsessed
with Conan O'Brien.
Dreams?
You mean like where I'm in
Conan's all-leather apartment?
I mean,
I don't know if he has one...
but that's why it's a dream.
And suddenly, we're
buck-naker and all oiled up.
I don't know where
the oil comes from...
but, again,
that's why it's a dream.
Then, there's Kansas Hill,
the original bad seed.
Son of a blue-balled bitch,
I always get this one.
Mouth on her that could stop
a bull in heat.
She gets her nut brain
from her mother.
You see, Kansas' mom's
been in prison...
ever since
the day she was born.
She was just lying there,
in labor with Kansas...
when she hears something
going on in the next bed.
Turns out it's Kansas' dad
taking a nurse's temperature.
Stay with me.
I'm trying to be delicate.
Anyway,
she whips out a shotgun...
and blows his ass
to kingdom come.
So, she got
life without parole...
and now Kansas lives
with her grandparents.
And then there's Lucy.
Geek extraordinaire.
A walking left brain.
She's supposed to have
this genius IQ...
but the truth is...
she's an obsessive-compulsive
little freak.
OK, hands in, ladies.
Today,
we're gonna cheer loud...
jump high,
and look pretty because...
Cheerleaders kick...
Now, let's get going,
'cause no one ever got ahead...
by sitting on their behind.
The school year
started off like normal.
Principal smith
gave his pep talk.
If you are approached
to buy drugs...
let someone you trust know.
Lf... you are thinking...
of harming yourself...
or others...
let someone know.
If it burns
when you urinate...
have milky seepage...
or are being touched
by uncle...
let someone know.
Come on, you guys!
Let's hear it
for the Lincoln "A" squad!
"A" squad? Right.
I was doing better dance numbers
in grade school.
It really burned my toast.
Now, I know it's my duty
to give you all the facts.
So, I'm gonna have to say
that their cheer blew...
like a bulimic
after Christmas dinner.
Their blatant disregard...
for National High school
Cheerleading Association...
rules made me sick.
Basket toss flips
and wool fall pyramids...
over two people high
are strictly prohibited.
Yeah!
I made a complete report
and sent it in.
Hey! Go, Lincoln!
Hey... go... Lincoln!
And, finally, the moment
we'd all been waiting for...
Transferring from Truman High...
the new star quarterback...
of our
Mighty Fightin' Lincolns
Jack Bartlett!
That's when Jack and Diane met.
Nobody saw it coming...
especially not Jack.
Jack was fine.
Oh, man, was he fine.
It was like
he was a bar of chocolate...
and the whole school
was on the rag.
Everyone wanted a piece of him.
Jack Bartlett.
Is Jack Bartlett
interested in me?
I'm sorry... can someone else
please run the board?
It's creepy, it's wrong...
and it goes against
the teachings
of my Lord and savior,
Jesus Christ.
Hannah, in order to get real
answers from the nether world...
you've got to have a Christian
virgin run the board.
Your kind is pure of heart
the devil won't dick with you.
Well, uh, technically...
I don't think
I'm a virgin anymore.
What!
At church camp this summer
I'm pretty sure I had...
you know, my first orgasm.
Hold up.
Any sentence that starts with,
"At Church camp...
ain't leading to the big "O".
That's not true
those pictures of Christ...
all sweaty and bare chested
on the cross...
always kind of made me hot.
Well, I want to know
what happened.
OK, well, one night
around sunset...
I went horseback riding
with the nuns.
They went every night.
And we're trotting
pretty hard, you know?
All of a sudden,
I feel...
I feel just super-alive,
you know?
Maybe I'll just ask
the question myself.
Is Jack Bartlett
interested in me?
He is.
Hey, man,
is this thing, like on?
OK, I'm just here
to announce my candidacy...
for the homecoming queen.
Uh, I plan
to spread the world on 4-H.
It's all about
the cows, man...
Look, I'll be honest with you
most of us realized we didn't
have a whore's chance...
in heaven with Jack, the day
of the candidate speechers.
Youth...
and agriculture.
4- H, 4-H rules!
Thank you, sir.
Good job.
Um, as... as the A-V Club
candidate...
I think, for the...
for the first time in 50 years...
uh, we should...
we should say no.
We should... we should say no
to a football player as king.
Vote brains over brawn...
It was the first time
most of us...
even heard Jack speak.
Thanks, wow.
We weren't disappointed.
OK, guys...
hey, guys...
All right,
would you shut up a minute?
I was just joking.
Well, uh, I just think
it really rocks...
that the football team picked me
as their, you know, candidate.
Yeah!
We love you, Jack!
Well, I love you, too,
lunch ladies.
I just want to say that there's
only 3 things I want in life:
To someday become a senator
of this great state...
I want to lead
the Mighty Fightin' Lincolns
to victory
at the homecoming game.
All right!
And, uh...
I want to go
to the homecoming dance...
with Diane Weston.
Ugh, they were like
friggin' Barbie and Ken...
but without the pink
remote-control Corvette.
Overnight, people were going, like...
Oh, they're
the perfect couple.
They're so cute.
I'm sure it gave
the Internet whacks...
something to talk about
besides Agent Scully...
and their most recent
wet dream.
Now, I'm not one to gossip...
but I think Jack and Diane
got so close, so fast...
because they discovered
how much they both loved...
football.
Man, did they love
their football.
Hey, ho, let's go!
Hey, ho...
I don't know about the "hey"...
but "ho" is right on the money.
If they'd asked...
I so easily could have
helped them out...
with some new material.
Green 88! Green 88!
Set, hut.
I... love... you.
Woo!
Woo, yeah!
Yeah, baby.
Now, right about here...
is where the real shit
stated to hit the fan.
Don't worry,
I'll clean this up a bit...
if I have to appear
in court.
Especially
if we're on Court TV.
Ha, well, there's
a Christmas card!
Oh!
Oh, hey, Jack...
why don't you go light
a fire under Diane, huh?
Heh heh, I'm on it,
Mr. Weston.
All right!
Say,
where are my manners?
I'm Dee Dee.
You can remember me
because of my double Ds!
Oh, don't you
show them!
And I'm Diane's dad,
Dennis.
Now, don't try that after
one of my screwdrivers, OK?
So, who wants
pigs in a blanket?
Excuse me, Vendela,
have you seen Diane?
Because we were
supposed to go...
to the homecoming dance
tonight.
Oh, baby.
Now, I obviously wasn't there
the night they all met.
But I'm sure it was
a super goober fest.
Your Jack is one heck of
a good football player.
I don't know how
he can concentrate...
with your lovely Diane
cheering on the side line.
Aw, look at this.
Oh, my,
look at that.
Look at those two.
All right. Hold up.
I have
an announcement to make.
Me and Diane, uh...
Oh, what the hey?
We're getting married.
No! Yes!
Oh, what a surprise!
But, well...
Not before
I have our baby.
So, when your dad said...
I never want to see
your fing faces again...
do you think he meant
"Forever" forever...
or just until
your mom wakes up?
I don't know.
And what the hell was
that sound she made...
right before
she hit the ground?
Well, if I had to guess...
I'd say that, that was
the sound of a mother...
saying good-bye to her little boy...
and hello to the young man...
who's going to be
a daddy of his own.
Jack, do you know
what I see here?
Spit from your dad?
I see a flower.
And you know, even
the most beautiful flowers...
still grow from dirt.
Yeah.
And while we're knee-deep
in it right now...
and things may seem
pretty stinky...
in the long run...
we're going to
grow strong from this.
You think?
I sure do.
Diane...
I've loved you
since I first saw you.
Right before you
kicked me in the head.
Oh, Jack.
Now... I don't think...
Diane just up and told the squad
about the baby that night...
but somehow they managed
to figure it out.
No, thanks.
Don't need one.
So?
Holy shit.
You just became
a statistic.
Oh, my God.
I'm not the first.
But you're not married.
Wait, did you
say you are pregnant...
or you were pregnant?
You had it,
threw it out...
and now you're going to
go back and dance all night?
Shut up, Cleo.
Di, how much do you need
for an abortion?
What?
No.
Not an abortion.
My church can arrange for you
to go to Oregon...
and take care of
a sick aunt...
for 9 months.
Then they find
your baby a good home...
and you come back
a little dazed and puffy...
but everything's fine.
Oh, please, Di,
don't be a whore...
and a murderer.
Jack told the team
that night, too.
Hey, guys, I, uh...
I got Diane pregnant.
What?
Well, all right!
You nailed Diane Weston?
Ha! I'd never wash
my Johnson again.
Hey.
Yeah.
Ha-hoo!
I didn't mean to
say whore, Diane.
It's just that
I hear it...
so much at church...
it kind of came...
flying out of my head.
I know, Hannah.
Look... I'm not going
to get an abortion.
I've always planned on
getting married and having kids.
I'm just going
a little out of order.
Kind of reminds me
of another young lady...
who found herself with child...
unmarried...
on a long, long road...
with no place to sleep.
Of course, that was
a long, long time ago.
But no matter what...
she held her head high...
and said, "Papa, don't preach.
I'm in trouble deep.
Papa, don't preach...
'cause I made up my mind...
I'm keepin' my baby.
Yeah, I'm gonna keep my baby. "
The great one.
Madonna.
We're here for you, Diane.
You guys...
Thanks. Oh...
I'll pray for you
every night.
We love you.
I love you guys.
You're the best.
Oh, Diane!
I guess their little fairy tale
could have ended there.
The only problem was they didn't
have a place to live.
What?
But all of
our paper work's here.
My school records...
and Jack's football records.
Let me explain something...
No, wait... did I say...
Cross my heart, hope to die,
stick a needle in my eye...
that we will never,
ever miss a payment?
Uh, yes.
Yes, you did.
I think I know where
this one's going.
Um, listen...
I'm willing to put up my papers
on my GTO.
Now, she's got
a few miles on her...
but she looks great.
I'm sure, son, but, um...
She's twisting my arm.
I'm going to throw in
the speakers, too.
Why don't you just have
your parents come in...
and get the loan,
and then they can
give you the money?
With all
due respect, ma'am...
Jack and Diane Bartlett...
do not accept charity.
We are two young,
able-bodied Americans.
We're not looking for
a hand out...
we're looking for a hand up.
Give us food, and we'll
be hungry tomorrow...
but give us corn...
the kind
you plant, not eat...
and we'll grow it...
and uh, um... cut it...
and, uh...
you know, eat it.
Now, if you're interested
in giving us a home loan...
I will sit back down.
If not,
have a nice day, ma'am.
Sorry.
My hands are tied.
She's on the honor roll.
Somehow, they managed to find
their dream house anyway.
More of a dump,
if you ask me.
We'll take it.
Oh, fine. Fine.
Jesus, settle down, OK?
Let's just keep in mind here
I manage the building, OK?
I don't, like, own it,
and I don't fix shit.
And I also don't care
if shit breaks, OK?
All I care is
you little bastards...
shove the rent under my door
on the 1st, you got that?
You understand that?
OK. Oh, yeah,
and one more thing.
You see any packages
outside my door...
you leave them
the hell alone.
Capisce?
Two taco grandes!
One bean burrito.
A large taco chip.
And guacamole.
And that'll be...
35 cents.
We don't really have
fried rats in the buckets.
I know. I checked.
You know what? I'm going
to save you the time.
I'm not going to lie.
I don't believe in it.
If you pick your ass,
I'm going to tell people.
I have no idea
how to run your register.
You're Jack Bartlett, right?
Yeah.
So, you'd be, like...
hanging out with us...
every night after school,
then, right?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, after
football practice, yeah.
Football practice?
Fantastic.
You're so hired.
I'm on top of the world!
Hey, Di,
if we have a girl...
we should dress her
like Little Debbie.
Jack, honey, I'm only
eating for two.
No, I know
but all this food
reminds me of how much...
I want to teach our baby...
Cocoa Puffs: Good
Captain Crunch is bad.
It shreds the roof
of your mouth.
Now, you're not born
with that knowledge.
You hear "Trix are for kids".
And you think,
"OK, I'm a kid.
So I guess
they're for me. "
But your little baby brain's got
no idea...
that Lucky Charms are, like...
a million times better for you.
Jack.
Hey. Pop quiz.
If you could be Count Chocula
or Trix the rabbit, who would you be?
Uh... Trix.
Me, too. God!
Will it never end?
I love this lady!
Jack, I think I should
get a job.
No, but we agreed your job’s
running the baby machine.
I know, but that
was before I realized...
Oh... I almost forgot gas
for the baby machine.
I'm going to get
your snickers...
I'm going to meet you
in line, OK?
- Mm... love you.
- I love you.
Hey, Di!
Hi, I'm a little professor!
Wouldn't it be cute
if ours looked like this?
Yeah, you little marsh...
Honey?!
Oh, I am really sorry.
Jack...
I never knew you
dreamed of working...
in a grocery store bank branch.
Baby, we are living
the great American dream.
If you reach
for the stars...
you're bound to step...
Jack, pull over.
Pull over.
Oh, Jesus, ew!
Why do they call it
morning sickness?
It's OK.
Get it all out.
Do you have
any breath mints?
So, she's in my hands, right?
Moist to the touch.
Now, it's at that second
that I think I control her...
you know, she's mine.
But it's a false illusion.
You know, it's like
in that movie "Backdraft".
No man controls fire.
So, she's ready.
I'm ready.
She's ready.
I yell...
42-58. Hike!
Touch down.
Where were we?
I need a place
to keep this.
So if anyone asks,
what do you know?
That's right.
You don't know shit.
Diane, it says here you're going
to have mood swings...
uncontrollable gas...
It's more proof God's a guy.
And sex dreams where you
actually have an orgasm.
Well, the Virgin Mary
must have snuck that one in.
Come on, Jack, you promised.
OK. One question.
Oh, me, me, me!
Mine's great.
Proceed, Dungeon Master Quon.
OK, Jack.
You know how you
and Diane slept together?
Yeah.
Well, now that you can't
sleep together...
but you still sleep together...
don't you ever get just, like...
super horny?
And if so, how horny?
I'll be quiet now
so I can listen to your answer.
Yeah, Jack.
I'd love to hear your answer.
The answer's easy.
Oh, uh... "Lolita"
is due back tomorrow.
Same for "91/2 Weeks"
and ditto on "Wild Things".
Guys... I'm going to be a dad.
Dads don't get horny.
To the kids at school,
Jack and Diane had it all.
I mean, come on, their own
apartment, staying up late...
eating whatever they wanted...
plus Jack was getting
a discount...
on R-rated movies
at the video store.
Hello! Reality check.
School, practice, work,
and Lamaze class?
It was really starting
to take its toll.
2, 4, 6, 8...
Fighting Lincolns on to state!
Fight!
Lincoln! Fight!
Blue 42! Blue 42!
Set...
Hut!
OK, so they won state.
B. F. D.
The best part was...
Diane was really starting
to look like shit.
Diane?
Diane!
Huh?
What?
Oh!
I'm under the ice!
Oh, man, that was a weird one.
Another sex dream?
- Wayne Gretzky.
- Hat trick?
He is the great one.
Oh, my God.
You've been robbed.
No, I've been pregnant.
Di, are you OK?
We can skip the girl party
this week.
Everything's fine.
I'm just having
a little trouble...
turning my frown upside down.
Want us to help you pick up?
Don't
Martha freaking Stewart me.
You don't like it, you try being
a pregnant teen.
Jack.
Oh, Jack.
Can I help you?
Get your loser ass
away from me.
Oh, my gosh, Jack.
Are you OK?
Diane.
Brendon!
Go with them.
They're in the vault,
man. Go! Go!
Who's Mr. Duggan?
Mr. Duggan.
You want to open the vault?
Or do you want me to?
Do whatever they want, Terry.
Take the keys.
Take them!
I'm confused.
Pappas knew the bank robbers
were surfers...
because he saw a tan line?
Luce, it's "Point Break".
Just shut up
and look at Keanu.
Di, what would you do
if you were in a holdup?
Well...
I guess I...
I'd give them all the money
they could hold...
and wish them a good life.
Because the Beatles were wrong.
Love isn't all you need.
Love won't pay the rent...
Iove won't buy my baby
diapers...
and love sure as
hell won't buy me...
my new Dolce & Gabbana jeans
when I lose my baby weight.
Pretty soon we'll be broke...
and I'll just be another fat-ass
wearing Chic jeans.
OK, put the snickers down.
Come kick it over here.
Wait a minute!
Freeze that!
Too much time.
Yeah.
Can you imagine?
Conan's head on Keanu's body?
Unstoppable.
No!
That's it!
A bank robbery.
A big pile of money
and my little family-to-be...
could get our heads above water.
My God, I read about this.
It's called pregnancy insanity.
Look...
I might be moody...
I might be gassy...
but I am perfectly sane.
Think about it.
In school they tell us
dreams can come true.
Right?
Right.
But they don't tell us how.
Thanks to Keanu...
I've figured it out.
Money makes
your dreams come true.
Listen, Kansas,
I know you dream...
of springing
your mom someday.
Stop, you're gonna
make me cry.
If the O.J. Trial
taught us anything...
it taught us that in America...
you can cut somebody's head off
and still be found innocent...
as long as you have
enough money.
Your mom only shot a guy.
And Cleo?
I know you dream of
an all-leather apartment...
with Conan.
I overheard the school shrink
telling the lunch lady.
Hannah, you could give
your share to the church...
or maybe buy one of
those starving kids...
that Sally Struthers advertises.
Or I could buy my own horse.
Or that.
Look, you guys...
I just want to provide
a future for my baby.
I know my bank branch...
like the back of
my puffy little hand.
I could open that safe
in my sleep.
I'm in.
- Yes!
- What?
I mean it.
I'm in.
This is the closest thing to
a goddamn family I've ever had.
If one of us needs something,
then we all do.
Stop it!
This is crazy.
I'm in, too.
Cleo!
Kansas is right.
We're like sisters.
We're closer than sisters...
and you don't turn
your back on family.
Come on, Luce.
People do it in
the movies all the time.
And they get caught.
That's right.
So all we have to do
is watch a bunch of movies...
and learn from
their mistakes.
You know, real cops aren't
half as smart as Keanu.
Forget it.
I've got a scholarship to
Harvard hanging over my head.
I won't risk it.
Conan went to Harvard.
Lucy, are you sure you
have that scholarship?
- No.
- And if you don't?
Can you still afford
to go to Harvard?
I don't know, probably not.
So then this isn't crazy, is it?
- It's a sure bet.
- Well...
Come on!
- Come on!
- Please?
I guess we're all
in this together.
But... but!
We have to make a smart plan.
Of course.
OK, hands in.
All right.
We have to
cross our hearts...
hope to die...
stick a dirty needle
in our eye...
that we will never, ever
tell Jack.
We all know
he can't tell a lie.
That's why he's going to make
such a great senator.
Cheerleaders kick...
We have two very cool guests...
and I'm gonna start with...
something I read
in the paper today.
It involves sex.
You hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah, don't worry.
Not with me.
I feel totally abandoned
in a place that values...
physical prowess
over mental acuity.
I can't wait until
all that changes...
once we're out
in the real world.
I would.
I'd totally marry Prince William
even if he was gay.
I mean, in England, all guys are
kind of gay anyway, right?
Even cigarettes are fags.
The movie was so amazing.
He slices off the guy's ear,
and I mean you see everything.
The bloody pink hole...
Cleo, I already
threw up twice today.
Can you please get to any
relevant part of the movie?
Well, you know, they had
nick names, like Mr. Pink...
and I was thinking,
Di, you could be Mrs. Pink.
Could I be Mrs. Purple?
And I could be Mrs. Red
because I love red.
This is so exciting.
Di, how can you eat all that?
She's eating for two.
Jinx.
Page one is
a plot summary of "Heat. "
Two has
my character summaries...
3 is my overall critique...
and on 4 through 10
you'll find...
my Nexis search of all
prior analysis of this film.
In summation...
no part of "Heat"
is really applicable...
to a grocery store
bank branch robbery.
What the heck
is going on here?
Jack! I can explain.
Diane, there's no excuse...
for not taking
your prenatal vitamins.
I love you.
Cleo?
Would you just
say my name?
Ted.
Well, it's a laugh riot
for the whole family...
and Tim Conway is just about
as funny as they come...
especially in the scene where...
Wait a minute.
You watched "The Apple
fucking Dumpling Gang"?
I'm only allowed "G" movies.
Am I the only one
who cares about this?
I mean, at least I watched
"Dog Day Afternoon. "
Excuse me.
Could you try to keep
your voice down, please?
We're not introducing
anger into the womb.
How would you like me
to introduce my foot...
into your ass?
Kansas!
I'm sorry, Diane...
but I'm not gonna watch
my dreams fade away...
because
the Virgin Mary here...
thinks she can get ideas
from kiddie movies.
Those of us
who have parents...
know they have rules
because they care.
Are you sure you
want to go there?
Maybe.
You guys!
How do you like that?
Diane Weston?
Kansas, quit it!
Here.
God, we're sorry.
It's off.
I can't take
the fighting...
the backstabbing,
the open hostility.
We're not acting
like cheerleaders.
We're acting like
a bunch of sorority girls.
I'm sorry
I ever started this.
Di, it's not your fault.
We all wanted to do this.
Look...
maybe I can watch a PG movie.
I'll just say I'm...
counting dirty words
for Sunday school.
It's OK, Hannah.
It was silly
to think that we can learn...
to rob a bank
from watching movies.
Sex you can learn from movies.
But robberies?
Forget about it.
Besides...
TV Land had a "Little House on
the Prairie" marathon...
and the In galls made
baby Carrie's bed...
from a dresser drawer.
I guess I could just do that.
Oh, my God!
The baby's got two heads.
It's twins!
I'm not just super fat!
Oh, OK, we ain't
done with this.
Those babies are gonna have
a good start in life.
With a real crib...
one that costs as hit load.
We're gonna learn
how to rob a bank...
by the only people who
really know how to do it:
Criminals.
I'm gonna visit my mom.
You don't look nothing
like your picture.
Grandma and Grandpa sent you
a picture of a neighbor girl.
They didn't want
you to...
break out
and come kidnap me.
Thank God.
I was starting to think
I killed the wrong man.
So, what did you
come here for?
To tell me how much
you hate me?
I don't hate you.
I need your help.
Now, how in the hell
can I help you?
My best friend got pregnant.
Before you?
Yeah, I know.
That's what I said, too.
Um, anyway...
we want to help her get
some money for the baby...
by robbing a bank.
Well, shit fire, Kansas.
That's the sweetest thing
I ever heard.
But we can't quite
figure out how to...
you know, how to do it.
So you need my help?
Oh, my God.
This is like you asking me
for help with your homework.
Hey, Mink.
Come here.
Kansas, I want you
to meet someone special.
Jesus Christ, Mom.
Like my life ain't
a great big pile of shit...
'cause you're in here.
Now I've gotta add
"P.S. My mom's a dyke," too?
Shut up, you mouthy little shit.
Don't "mouthy shit" me.
I'm out of here.
Hey, wait. Sit down.
Now, I'm sorry.
Mama's a little over amped...
didn't get her yard time
this morning.
Mink ain't my bitch,
if that's what you think.
She's a specialist...
in banks.
Theme’s some sweet skirts
you got there.
Oh, thank you!
Actually,
they're uniforms.
We're cheerleaders.
You sure are.
Excuse me.
All right, same time tomorrow...
we have a visit
with our favorite aunts.
Listen, robbing banks
is like pulling a trick.
You gotta stay in control...
know how far you'll go
to get the dough...
and always put
the rubber on yourself.
You know what I mean.
Hey, and you gotta do it
the day after Christmas.
Why?
Banks don't have holiday
pickups, so vaults are full.
Besides, everyone's
at home eatin' left overs...
and beatin' their kids.
Really?
You were cell mates with her?
Oh, my God.
She was my hero!
Did she tell you what
Letter man's house was like?
You gotta buy your Gats
from the Terminator.
Tell him Itchy sent you.
And Gats are?
Guns, cutie.
You listen to Carol, pussycat.
Go rent "National Velvet".
It's got some awesome
steeple chases in it.
I'm gonna write that down.
So, although
their father said...
Don't get out of the car
till I get back with help...
they knew the sheriff's
voice when he yelled...
Run to my voice!
And don't look back!
The twins did as he said...
but at the very last second...
they turned around and saw
the escaped mental patient...
bouncing their father's head
on top of the car.
They jumped!
That's just gas, sweetie.
What are you working on?
Just some girly stuff
for the squad.
Well, whoever gets out alive...
have the authorities check
in the crawl space.
Kansas, you should never
judge a book by its cover.
I guess there's an exception
to every rule.
Could I help you?
You're the Terminator?
Did you come in here
to bust my balls?
Huh?
Well, I kill bugs for a living.
If God doesn't beat you to it.
No, wait, um...
We're the "A" squad
from Lincoln High school.
So, uh...
so, we were told
you could fix us up.
Fix you up.
Really.
Yeah, Itchy sent us.
She did, did she?
How is the old girl?
Definitely old.
Yeah, that's my Itchy.
How many?
Uh...
Um, well...
We'll each probably
want one, so...
We'll take 5.
5 should do it.
All right.
And, uh, how much ammo
do you want?
Ammo?
How many bullets do you need?
Oh, bullets.
No bullets.
Oh, my gosh. These are
just to scare people.
Kind of like around-off back
hand spring whip back double full.
You never really use it.
You just want the opposing squad
to know you've got it.
OK.
- $1,500 cash.
- What?
You piece of shit bug zapper!
Obviously that's a little more
than our budget will allow.
Um, basically, we're looking
for something around $200.
Oh, well,
why didn't you say so?
For 200, I got some
real nice rubber bands...
and some sharp nails
in the back.
I think I got 5 of them.
They come in pastel colors.
Why don't you wait
right there...
and let me go
gift-wrap it for you.
They are 1,500
cash on the barrel.
You take it or you leave it.
Well, what kind of deal
would you make...
if I told you we were going
to go tell the police...
that you're selling
illegal guns?
To minors!
To girl minors!
Then I'd just
have to kill you.
OK, well...
it was a pleasure meeting you.
Take care.
Let's go, you guys.
Hold it right there.
Oh, please.
We're not going
to tell anyone.
Maybe we can make a deal.
Look, buddy...
we're not gonna
trade sex for guns.
Unless Cleo...
Kansas!
I got a daughter.
And she's always dreamt
of being a cheerleader.
Aw.
Tell you what I'll do.
If you put her on your squad...
and I mean put her
on the squad...
don't make her haul around
your pompoms...
you give her something to do...
then I'll give you the guns.
You're kidding.
Hey, Fern!
Fern, come here!
She's out back siphoning off
the tanks.
It takes just a second
to cap off that cyanide hose.
Honey!
Oh, there she is.
Here's my baby.
Fern, meet your
new best friends.
We'll be right back.
Don't you take too long.
Let's do breathing
exercises, shall we?
Is Jack upset that
he can't be here?
We worked it out.
Doing good, sweetie.
Let's remember our focal point.
OK, don't stop now.
Come on, we're gonna make it,
baby. Come on.
What a sad waste of man.
OK...
Even with all our savings...
it's still only 654.
That's it?
Hey, I even took my parents'
foster kid money.
Philippe's going
to be gathering rice...
without pants this month.
OK, wait a second.
Hold on.
Now, what do we do
before a big game?
Use the bathroom...
because the port-a-potties
on the field are gross.
My fault.
What do we do that enables us
to be as great as we are?
I personally think
of how Conan...
started as a writer,
and then...
We practice.
That's right.
Practice makes perfect.
I'm practicing
to have a baby right now.
If we do a practice job...
we'll not only
get the experience...
but we'll also get the money
we need for the guns.
I've got the perfect job...
and I've gotta pee,
so help me up.
Hello.
How many would you like?
Seven.
- Hi.
- Hello. How many?
Two, please.
Oops!
Oh, please,
help me with her!
What the hell kind of food
are they serving us...
if they can turn
a prof it on 200 bucks?
Uh, Fern?
Yeah?
No more filling the tanks
before practice, OK?
OK.
So, you know,
what are you?
Anorexic or bulimic?
Just skinny.
Don't make me hate you.
OK, let's get going.
My grandparents get back
from dinner at 4:30.
Ready?
OK!
What the hell...
Oh, no!
He Ikea'd us.
How many signs do
we need.
We're not supposed
to do this.
Look, maybe Lucy is right.
Maybe this is a sign.
Kansas?
That you down there?
Yeah, Grandma.
Me and the squad.
You girls
talking about boys?
Practicing kissing
your hand?
Yeah, you caught us.
Oh, well, then
I'll put some cookies...
at the top of the stairs
for you girls.
Thanks, that'd be great.
You got that
big retarded girl...
down there with you?
Uh-huh,
yeah, Grandma.
Then I'll throw a few
more treats on the plate.
She doesn't mean that.
She kind of lost the old filter
with the last stroke.
Where's my smokes?
Oh, I'll have them for you right
before "Touched By An Angel".
Don't worry.
You damned well better.
Oh, this is great.
What do we do?
Threaten people with
a trunkful of parts?
I'm sorry, you guys.
When you're dealing with
south American rebels...
you kind of gotta to take
what you can get.
It's a trunkful of crap.
Excuse me, do you guys
know what I don't see here?
What?
I don't see a problem.
I see a great big
craft project...
sitting right
in front of me.
So, Kansas,
get me some glue...
some tape,
and a nail file.
Meanwhile, the most
important event of my life...
was about to take place.
Please join our "A" and "B"
squad cheerleaders...
in a salute
to winter sports!
The winter sports pep rally is
only, like...
the biggest cheerleading
event of the year.
I'd been practicing for months.
This was my big chance
to show the whole school...
that I really belonged
on the "A" squad.
I just want to say,
that normally,
I'm an excellent skater.
Some jealous fag,
who will remain nameless...
obviously sabotaged my skates.
I was completely humiliated...
In front of
the entire student body.
Talk about adding
insult to injury...
at the last minute,
Diane finagled putting...
that backwater mutant monkey
girl on top of the pyramid!
Yeah!
No way!
It ruined the entire finale.
Ask anybody!
Conan O'Brien...
Conan O'Brien.
Come on, Cleo.
We're not gonna waste
this week's question...
to the nether world
on Conan.
Who made up the
one-question-a-week rule anyway?
It's in the Bible,
so just shut the hell up.
OK, OK. Here goes...
Is the day
after Christmas...
the best day
for the heist?
Yes!
Girls, numerology
confirms it, too. Look!
So does
"Soldier of Fortune".
A great day to go balls out
on the offensive.
Then it's time
for my mom's present.
Be careful. Have fun.
Ski masks are so done.
Wear these masks
to fight the power...
and never bend over
in the shower.
Hey, Diane, you can be
Mood-swing Betty.
Hannah, you're
Virgin Betty...
with optional
horse and saddle.
And Fern, you can be...
Oh, God, we forgot Fern.
Oh, it's OK.
My mom and the girls just
got them for the heist.
It's nothing personal.
Hey, I got to cheer
with you guys.
I'm happier than
a Make-A-Wish kid at Disneyland.
Well, we'll all
sign your yearbook.
Here, take mine.
Look, I didn't know
how to tell you guys...
but I got my scholarship.
I can't go
through with this.
But we went
hands in on this.
You're breaking
the National High school...
Cheerleading
Association's pledge...
of allegiance
and conformity.
I'll turn in my pompoms
after Christmas.
You know,
you guys are insane...
if you don't think
those criminals would...
gladly turn you in
for a pack of Lucky's.
Oh, yeah!
Well, unlike you,
those criminals...
take an oath,
and they stick with it.
You don't mess
with another in mate...
and you never mess
with her kid.
I'm sorry, Diane.
I could take Lucy's place.
You can be Terminator Betty.
Fight the power!
1, 2, 3!
Oh, God!
Oh, honey...
Next Christmas...
I'm putting
a diamond in it.
I don't know
what to say.
Well, say you love me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Oh, God, here's mine.
It's so lame.
It's not romantic or anything.
No, no, no, shh.
I'm gonna love it.
Ah, a gift certificate!
For a new paintjob
on the GTO.
Yeah, I was thinking
that maybe you'd want...
to change the color
after Christmas.
Wow...
Do you like it?
I sold the car
to buy you that ring.
You're kidding?
No!
We don't have a car.
No.
Oh! Oh, sweetie.
Sweetie...
Kansas, listen to me.
Jack sold our getaway car.
It's some goddamn
"Gift Of The Magi" thing.
Oops, Mommy's sorry,
sweet peas.
Swearing is
the surest way to...
Oh, shit!
Mommy needs
a getaway car.
Jump in!
We can't stop!
The brakes are bad!
Come, Kansas,
let's hurry!
Fern, you've got to
slow down.
Oh, dear Lord... please don't let us
run over Kansas.
Help!
Get in! Quick!
The brakes are broken.
Grab my hand, Kansas.
Come on, Kansas!
Come on, give it a shot.
Oh, my God!
Anyone bring
a next repair of panties?
Who are you?
The goddamn Bionic Woman?
I just pulled it,
and it came off.
Great, this is great.
Now we have to enter
through the front door.
Look, it's not my fault.
Hey! God,
rule number 1:
You never take off the mask,
you hear me?
No matter what happens,
you never take off the mask.
I'm sorry, Kansas.
Oh! God, no.
Rule number 2: No names.
No goddamn names, you retard.
For Christ's sake,
White Trash Betty.
I didn't realize
the rules went into effect...
before we entered
the supermarket.
Well, use your head,
stalker Betty.
Bettys, stop it.
The best squad is one
that hopes for the best...
and prepares for the worst.
National High school...
Cheerleading
Association letter head.
Now, let's give a hands in.
We're ready, we're prepared...
and this is going to be
the best bank robbery ever...
because...
Cheerleaders kick...
It's me.
Lucy?
What the hell do you want?
I want to help.
I'm a part of this squad.
Oh, no.
You have committed
the ultimate sin.
You left your squad
to be with a guy.
And that guy is
the devil himself...
because only the devil would
turn you against your sisters.
Let's go.
What's this?
Get on the ground now!
We got tape.
Don't worry about it.
I said down!
OK, uh. Hello?
Yeah. Excuse me.
Yeah, hi.
Umm, are you robbing
the supermarket...
or the bank branch?
The bank.
OK, so...
do you want
everybody down...
or just the people
at the bank?
- All of you!
- Bank branch!
Will you shut up.
I'll handle this.
Bank branch only.
Everybody else, just go
on about your business.
Shit, this ain't working.
Everybody down!
That's an illegal dismount.
Oh, my God.
An "A" squad pompom string.
Keep your eyes
on the ground.
This is great.
How are we doing?
Quick. Big bills, big bills.
This here is bullshit!
That's what this is.
Shit!
I'm fine here. Go on.
I ain't going to let
some piece of shit...
Betty doll tell
me what to do.
No sire Bob.
Freeze or meet Jesus, asshole!
Don't never use the Lord's son's
name in vain...
around these parts
in the U.S. Of A.
What the heck?
Uh, I forgot
to tell you.
Sometimes when the rebels
take the gun off a corpse...
some live rounds
get left in the clip.
Good to know.
Christ on a cracker.
All right,
you guys, let's go.
I'm here live at the scene
of today's...
highly unusual bank robbery...
speaking with an eyewitness.
Can you please tell
us a little bit...
about what happened
here today?
Yes. In fact, you're talking
to the right person...
because I am
walking evidence.
OK. One of them stepped
right on my...
OK? Excuse me, can you
get a shot of me here?
This is important, buddy.
Hello? Can you dust my...
for prints? This is important.
I can't believe you're
standing there, you idiot!
Wait, hold on, I forgot.
I have this. This is
really important...
That's very nice.
Thank you for your time.
Well, as you can see,
this crime here today...
is affecting people
very seriously.
If you haven't heard:
Today, 5 pregnant Betty
dolls robbed the bank.
Can you believe this?
We're like celebrities.
Better enjoy it now.
Because tomorrow some little
kid falls down a well...
and we're nothing
but a distant memory.
Disguises incinerated.
Oh, bad news, Di.
There was one thing we just
couldn't fit in the furnace.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you guys!
Thank you. Oh!
Can you believe we did it?
I mean...
We did it.
We really did it.
I guess no one
could have predicted...
the shit storm that
was about to hit.
I mean, the only thing people
cared about, thought about...
or talked about was the robbery.
Judging by the way the
robbers practically flew up...
to spray paint
the security cameras...
I think it was an Asian gang.
Yeah. Because as a people...
they tend to be quite
tiny and very acrobatic.
That's all it took.
Next thing you know...
Dim sum Charlie's
being hauled in for questioning.
From there, the town just
seemed to go apes hit.
That's her! That's her!
This thing spread faster
than a canker sore...
on the girls swim team.
Someone in Lincoln would
say something like...
They was dressed
like a bunch of...
freakin' Betty dolls,
for... sake.
They had these...
little voices...
and only
a bunch of... damn queers...
would shoot up
a union cap.
All of the sudden...
it's on "Jerry Springer".
This thing was definitely huge.
And welcome to the show.
Today, we're going to meet...
a growing number
of transvestites...
who just don't like
to dress up as women.
They like to dress up
as pregnant women.
Eric Karros...
It was like the whole country
had come down...
with Betty doll fever.
Left drive over
the left field wall...
into a waiting
pack of Bettys.
And then it finally happened...
the moment I had
been waiting for.
The little dip shits in blue...
finally followed up
on my evidence.
Hi. I'm Kurt Loder
with an MTV News Brief.
Authorities now believe
a group of teenage girls...
are responsible for
the Betty doll bank robbery.
Stay tuned for my interview
with Alanis Morissette...
on the negative influence
of the Betty doll...
on young girls, right after this.
Hello?
It was Lucy.
Lucy went to the cops.
Remember, Kansas.
Every time you
point a finger...
you have three more
pointing back at you.
She's been the weak tit
on this mama cat...
since the beginning.
- That you?
- Yeah. Hold on.
Just call me later.
I got to get some
smokes for my grandma.
Don't use big bills.
For a pack of cigs?
I'll use her food stamps.
Hello?
We're dead.
They showed this prison movie
to my youth group on Sunday.
Hannah...
No, it wasn't like
the prison we saw.
All of these women had
to shave their heads...
because they got lice from
the filthy lives they lived.
Oh, no. I'm going to be
someone's bald bitch!
Oops. Hold on a second.
Hello?
Di? It's Luce.
Kansas just called and said
she's going to freak me up.
Then I heard coughing and a thud
and Kansas had to go.
I think her grandma had
another heart attack.
Anyway, why does
she want to freak me up?
She thinks you went
to the police.
What? That's insane.
Why would I go
to the police?
Relax. I've got to get that.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hello?
My Sunday school teacher says
that in prison...
women shove broom sticks
up your...
Hold on.
Yeah?
Hello?
No. This is Diane. I think
you have the wrong number.
Oops. That's me.
Gotta go.
Wrong number? No!
Hello?
Di, I just called to say...
that Conan talked about us
again last night.
Thanks, Cleo.
See you tomorrow.
Morning, sunshine.
Remember, except for
the morning sickness...
the blinding back pain...
and the embarrassingly
unpredictable gas...
these are the best days
of your life, so far.
Hey, hey, hey.
Not so fast.
Following your dream
isn't a crime.
Nobody suspects you.
Nobody even has a clue.
Hey, guys.
Someone not take a shower today?
Hey, Lisa, did you run into
Carmen Electra last summer?
No.
Oh, because it
looks like you got...
some of her tits on you.
This just came from...
the National High school
Cheerleading Association.
You guys might
want to look it over...
before you try any more
cradle dismounts...
from double-based
partner stunts...
that are over shoulder stand
level without using 3 catchers.
Oh, or before you think about
robbing another bank.
What did she say?
How does she know?
Move it, people.
FBI. FBI. Freeze!
I'm sorry to bother you, ma'am,
but is this gonna take long?
It's game night.
Face front.
Are you sure
they can't see us?
One-way mirror, ma'am.
Picture in 3, 2, 1.
Excuse me, ma'am.
On "Law & Order," they get
to make one phone call.
I need to call
the fat her of my babies.
It's a fungus.
Leave it alone.
There's nothing I can
do about it. Hello?
Lisa, it's Diane.
We need to talk.
And that's why I came forward.
I mean, even the kids
on the short bus...
can see that all
the evidence...
points to Diane
and the "A" squad.
Oh, it sure does.
Your testimony will
prove in valuable...
Unfortunately,
it wasn't them.
They were all waiting
in my suburban that day...
while I ran into
the supermarket for some cash.
We were on our way to practice.
Well, better get going.
Nobody ever got ahead
by sitting on their behind.
Hey! Over here!
Is that Lisa?
What's she doing here?
Come on.
They let you guys
keep your mug shots?
I don't get it, Lisa.
Why did you tell the cops
that we were with you?
Look, you guys,
a failure to plan...
is a plan for failure.
We needed an alibi.
And I'm not going to be doing
back handsprings anytime soon.
What's in it for her?
Well, the "A" squad is going
to need a new captain soon.
You can't be serious!
Lisa really does
know all the rules.
Look! If it wasn't
for my alibi...
you'd all be doing college
by correspondence.
Get away from me!
Diane!
God, roll down a window!
Sorry, it just slipped out.
OK!
Funny how things work out
in the end.
Diane turned in her pompoms...
and I'm the new
"A" squad captain.
After all, National High school
Cheerleading Association...
rule number one:
Always stand behind...
your fellow cheerleaders...
especially when they're
7 months pregnant,
locked in a holding tank,
and looking at 15 to life.
Actually, I made
that last little bit up...
but you know what I mean.