Omega! Omega! Omega!
Omega! Omega! Omega! Omega...
Just as much of a dump as it
was when I went to Hamilton.
How do you live here?
You know, they're
actually cool guys.
Cool guys?
Let me get this straight:
I'm paying 40 grand a year for my
son to be a creative writing major
and live with a bunch
of cool guys?
Dad, you don't have
to be sarcastic.
What was your g.P.A.
Last semester?
- It was a 3.4.
- When I went to Hamilton, I got nothing but 4.0s.
How do you expect to get into a
decent law school with a 3.4?
Dad-- - are you even
looking into law school?
Dad, I'm only a freshman! I'm not
even sure if I want to be a lawyer.
Pledge!
How was your Christmas?
Look what Santa brought me.
- Oh god, rich.
- No more rash.
You must be pledge's dad.
How are you?
I'll see you
at parents' weekend.
He's not gonna stay
for the party?
- Pledge, don't miss anything.
- All right.
Pick it all up now.
Aw, come on!
U.S.A., U.S.A., U.S.A.!
Hey-o! What do we got over here?
What do we got?
Hold that for a second. It's okay,
don't worry about it. Hold that.
Are you writing about the party?
Pledge, all right, look at this, okay?
This is a party.
- That's my journal!
- It's a party.
- Let's go! Come on!
- Attention, Hamilton.
Four score and many beers ago
our forefathers--
- You're doing a shot.
- I can't do a shot tonight.
Dude, you're fresh out
of a two-year relationship.
You're doing a shot. Let's go.
I'm the keymaster.
Merkhaus, it's really--
I shouldn't. It's inappropriate.
Hey, who wants t-brow
to do a shot?
Come on. Come on, t-brow.
All right, just one. This is the
only shot I'm taking tonight.
Whooooaaa!
T-brow! T-brow! T-brow!
T-brow! T-brow! T-brow! T-brow!
What's your major?
Women's studies.
Yeah. Studying women,
I understand.
So, um,
do you want to go to the back room
and show me how you swab a deck?
All right.
Let's go.
What's the next stop
for the "night train"?
- The pros?
- Actually, my fraternity's throwing a party tonight.
You got it.
Down the hatch. Down the hatch.
Down the hatch!
There you go! Animal!
Oooh.
Mmm, yeah!
Keymaster!
T-brow! T-brow! T-brow! T-brow!
Yo, Richie.
What are you doing, man?
I'm not doing anybody right
now, I'll tell you that.
I hung out with sailor.
She took me to sea.
She wrapped her net around me,
and I saw something bigger
than I've ever seen before.
So why is your omega name
"El nino"?
Because I come at you like a
storm, you know what I'm saying?
Like torrential downpour
and shit.
- So what's your omega name?
- Um...
Shut up, pledge!
He doesn't have one yet, okay?
Omega! Omega! Omega! Omega...
Whoa.
What a night, huh?
- Shut up, pledge.
- Ow.
Oh hey, what time is it?
Uh, it's 2:30?
- P.M.?
- Yeah.
Damn it, pledge, why are
you waking us up so early?
You sure the meeting was
supposed to start at 2:00?
No, giles, I decided to take
half an hour out of our day
to come sit here in the Greek board room.
Of course I'm sure!
Rico! Rico!
- Rico!
- What are you doing here, Max?
The omegas...
- Canceled the Greek board meeting.
- Canceled?!
- I never got a memo.
- Um, well,
they had a huge party
last night,
and because of that-- I mean,
they control the board.
That's it!
I've had it up to here--
With these omegas.
It's the first meeting
of spring semester
and they can't make it because
they're too busy partying?
Remember last year during finals when
they went streaking to the library?
Naked Christmas caroling
fundraiser, sir.
How about the time when they used the
science lab for a beer pong tournament?
All those beakers.
Or the time when they
canceled our quiz show
because night train wanted
to call a press conference
about his favorite food!
Corn dogs with teriyaki sauce.
And there was that time
a few years ago at their rush.
Ohhh.
Things are going to change
around here this semester.
The omegas' days of doing whatever
they want are about to end
and the rico Larsen era in charge
of Greek board is about to begin.
And the rico Larsen era in charge
I'm running
for Greek board president.
Rico, you did that last year and
you lost by 99% of the vote.
That was last year!
This year things are
going to change.
The omegas have an 88-year
streak controlling the board.
It doesn't matter
who runs against them.
- They always win.
- Then we need a new strategy, don't we?
Instead of trying
to beat the omegas,
it's time to break them.
It's time to break them.
So last night's total
was an estimated
1,054 party attendees.
Only a thousand? I thought we had,
like, close to 1500 last year.
That's true, but this year
we actually eclipsed
last year's two-to-one
girl-to-guy ratio
and jacked it up
to three to one.
So we may have had
less guests overall,
so we may have had
but we had more chicks,
hence a better party,
which enhances the probability
that our next party will be epic.
Nice. Good man, 39.
Did you get around to making the
assignments for this semester's rush?
- Mm-hmm.
- I like.
- Hodges.
- Thank you.
- Richie Sambora.
Where's t-brow?
Oh, he's passed out
in the other room.
Whatever, pledge. More for you.
Merkhaus.
- Stick that up your ass.
- Real nice, dude.
- Pledge.
- What?
- Thames.
- Mmm.
Now before you see your assignment,
it's important to note
that this semester omega's
looking for a different breed.
We don't really have too much room
in the frat considering it's spring,
so we need to be extra careful
in choosing any new pledges.
Maybe it's chicks.
What are you
waiting for, pledge?
- Broads. The door. Go!
- What? Stop!
Get the door!
- What's wrong with you?
- All right, I'm going.
He's been very disrespectful.
Man, I want waffles.
You gotta go a little easy
on the mustard there, night.
Um, guys?
You might want to take
a look at this.
Just send the girls in, dude.
No seriously, guys.
You need to come see this.
All right. Jeez.
This better be good.
It's a baby.
Does he belong
to one of you guys?
Yo, maybe someone left him here
after the party last night.
They sent out a message, and so we found
him here. Hey, man, what's your name?
Look, he's got a note.
"The baby is yours"?
Don't that thing have
batteries we can take out?
All right, so I Wikipedia-ed
"babies" over here,
and it says that "babies cry as a
form of instinctive communication."
And it says that "babies cry as a
- So the baby's trying to talk to us?
- Tell him to speak English!
Yeah, what is he,
some sort of immigrant baby?
- It's a male.
- Maybe he's crying because he's hungry.
All right, if you were
a baby what would you eat?
I know I could go
for a bagel right now.
Man, you go for a bagel
because you're a Jew.
Oh, so you're gonna
be prejudiced now?
What if I said you want a
burrito because you're Mexican?
I cut you!
Wait, whoa whoa whoa.
El nino, doesn't your name
wait, whoa whoa whoa.
- mean "baby boy" in Mexican?
- Hey, man, you calling me a baby?
Pull the knife. Think about it.
El nino means "the
baby boy." Right?
- Si.
- You're the key to what we should fee--
You gonna try to take my keys?
- Ese, I take the bus.
- I understand.
All right, class.
First day and all.
I am very excited.
I am professor street
and this is the history
of Hamilton university.
I see some supple
supple young--
Young minds.
Supple young--
Why don't we go around
and introduce ourselves?
Starting with the young lady
in the yellow dress.
What should I say?
I don't know. Start with...
Your major, your name.
Okay, um,
my name's Caitlin Greene
and I don't actually have
a major yet.
All right, all right,
how about, uh...
You with the sanitizer
and the glasses.
And the glasses.
'Kay.
Okay, my name is Rex moonberry.
I am a western Asian
anthropology major.
But my true passion is
the language of dolphins.
You see, when dolphins say,
"ee ee ee ee ee!"
That means
they're hungry for fish.
When they say, "ee eee ee ee,"
that means they're
hungry for love.
And when they say-- Fair enough, Rex.
Let's go...
How about the sexy gentleman
with the green water bottle
on his desk.
Oh, uh, me?
Hi. Um, my name is pledge.
I mean, Kyle.
My name is Kyle. And I'm a...
- Creative writing--
- Sit down, nerd!
I could see this is
going nowhere.
How about we talk about
steak mungro, the greatest
Greek board president
ever to live. Ever.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Hey! Hey, guys, yo.
- It's none of your business.
- What's up?
I just got out of class.
- So who's baby do you think it is?
- Yours.
- What? Really?
- I don't know, 39.
- Okay? I'm not Columbo.
- I don't think it's mine.
- How do you know that?
- I don't know.
- I think it's yours.
- I think you should blow me.
- Wow, intelligent. Nice.
- Thanks for giving me fair warning
- wow, intelligent. Nice.
on the cancellation of the Greek
board meeting today, collison.
- You're welcome.
- Well, I'll have you know
that I declared my candidacy
for Greek board president today.
Since Hodges is a senior,
I take it one of you two dopes
- will probably run against me.
- Didn't you
learn your lesson last year?
The better question would be
what lessons have you
learned since last year?
Okay, that doesn't make sense.
- Think about it.
- I just did. That doesn't make sense.
- See you around!
- I hope not.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, do that.
Here comes spider-man!
That's not gonna work, dude.
Babies don't like spider-man.
They like...
I don't know. Here comes babar!
I don't think
anybody likes babar.
Here comes a keg!
Yo, that baby likes beer.
Yo, that could be his name.
Yo?
No no no, beer.
I don't think that's
the best idea, dude.
Hell, you're right.
We can't name the kid beer.
That's a white boy's name. We need
something cool, something black.
Like d.M.X.
- President dumervile!
- Hello, rico.
I'm sure you're really busy. I'd like
to bring something to your attention.
- I am busy, I am.
- Yeah okay, this won't take a moment.
I've just come
from the first meeting
of the spring semester
Greek board.
Oh, I didn't know
you were on that.
Yes. We raised money.
Remember last year?
- I forgot.
- To help finish the science project?
- Yeah, of course, uh-huh.
- Yeah, anyway, the omegas
- yeah, of course, uh-huh.
again failed to notify
anyone and didn't turn up.
Oh no, really?
Oh, bad them, bad them!
- Okay well, I'm sure it's fine. Don't worry about it.
- Excuse me?
I said it was fine. Don't worry about it.
Don't make a big deal about it.
- Have another meeting.
- I don't like your sarcastic attitude.
Oh, come on. Hey, somebody's
blood pressure is up.
- You need to eat.
- Excuse me. Who do you think--
You're not a doctor. You're
president of this college,
and you should be setting an
example by teaching these idiots
that it is not acceptable-- - first of all,
we do not have to use those words, okay?
So today may not have been
exactly what we thought
we were getting into when we decided
to begin this semester's rush.
Nevertheless, I present
to you our newest omega.
Gentlemen, allow me to introduce
kegston omega!
It was my idea to name him
something beer-related.
Wait, hang on.
If he's gonna be an omega,
doesn't that mean
he has to pledge first?
- Can he be my pledge?
- No way, man. I saw him first.
Um, no, I saw him first.
Remember the whole get-the-door-
it's-chicks thing?
If kegston's going to be an omega,
he's going to be all of our pledge.
This morning we were bros,
members of a brotherhood.
Tonight,
we're dads.
Members of a fraternal
fatherhood.
Okay, I agree we should
pledge kegston,
but we shouldn't we all take
a paternity test to see
who the real father is?
You know, truth be told, that paternity
test was actually fairly easy.
At first I was like,
"screw that, bro.
I got enough 'tests' as it is,"
but that one wasn't so bad.
I can't believe that girls
are so into babies.
You would think they'd
like us less
considering that we'd had a child
out of wedlock or something.
You are so gay!
- How'd everything go?
- Good, man.
I tell you, this baby's
like a magnet.
Chicks can't get enough
of him, you know.
I got three numbers,
and he got a flower.
- Did he eat?
- No, man, I guess he wasn't hungry.
We took him to taco world
and everything.
But I got three combos, didn't I?
I ate them for you.
- Yes, he did.
- Don't touch him.
Don't babies drink milk?
Like from tits?
Yeah. You know what?
I know where we can get
plenty of those.
Breast milk over here!
Breast milk donations!
Come over here,
put your jug in the cup.
Donate your breast milk
for kegston!
Wow, you guys are really
horny or really dumb.
You wanna donate some
breast milk over here?
What, you guys run
a train or something?
Nah nah. Actually, he was
left on our doorstep.
- We just thought we'd take him in.
- Kinda like Moses.
All right, I don't know
what to say to that,
but you guys do know that
you had to have been pregnant
to lactate for breast milk?
Mmmm.
So you're saying we can't
get breast milk from hos?
No.
Then where are we
supposed to get some?
- The abortion clinic!
- Yeah.
- That's a good idea.
- You guys are really dumb.
All right, look.
There's a thing called formula.
You know?
You get it at a drugstore?
Yeah yeah yeah.
Like at big Vic's house.
- Oh.
- No no no, not "drug dealer."
Drugstore. All right, look.
You three guys get in the car,
go to the supermarket.
Look for baby supplies.
Get everything on the shelf.
And, thames, uh,
you do what you do.
Good luck.
- Hodges?
- Yeah?
We should get this--
This tape over here.
- What is it?
- We should get it for kegston,
- but we should get two of them.
- "Pokey dokey"?
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- How much do you think this is gonna cost?
- I don't know.
- But we're gonna need it all.
- Hi guys.
Hey, pledge, what are
you doing here?
Uh well, what are
- It's awesome,
- that'll work.
- Yeah, it's a keg crib for the baby.
- Yo, guys, what's up?
Hey-oh! What do you boys think?
- Huh, pretty cool.
- What's in the bags?
Tons of baby stuff. Enough to wipe
out the omega savings account.
What? Do you realize how long it took me
to balance our budget for this semester?
Okay, 39, let's not forget you're
only the omega rush chairman.
And treasurer
and vice president.
But I'm the president
of the omega house.
I have final say on what
we spend our money on.
Yeah, and as the treasurer, it's my
duty to make sure we have funds.
I can't do that if you're
spending them all.
- We're not completely broke, dude!
- How much is left?
- Like $27.
- Oh my god, Hodges!
You are completely irresponsible.
Our parents and trustees are
gonna kill us when they hear we blew through
over five grand in less than a week.
And they're not gonna come after you.
They're gonna come after me
because they know you're
completely incapable!
You know, I thought
about it long and hard
and, uh, came to
a decision that, uh,
my favorite food is corn dogs
with teriyaki sauce.
That's it!
That's reason why everyone
loves the omegas--
Because they're so visible.
You can't exactly join
the football team, rico.
I'm not suggesting that,
numskull!
What I'm suggesting is
what if we find a way
to turn the omegas reputation
- against them?
- Hmm.
- Ow!
- Idiots!
- Ow ow!
- Sorry.
You hit the broken part.
Don't touch it anymore.
I guess he doesn't
like the keg crib.
Ungrateful.
Should we play
with him or something?
Maybe one of us should
stay up with him.
We can take turns.
Yeah, good idea.
It's your turn, buddy.
- Hmph.
- Good night, Hodges.
Spending all our money.
What do you want, little guy?
You hungry?
Want some food?
Milk? Toys?
How's your diaper?
You want me to sing you
a lullaby?
Okay.
♪ You move like this,
you slide like that ♪
♪ you wiggle real slow... ♪
♪ And then you dance real fast ♪
♪ and then you dance real fast ♪
♪ you do it all over,
but you change it all around ♪
♪ then you jump
off the ground... ♪
Shut up!
Hey.
Hodges.
Hey, pledge. Sit down.
I'm just trying to figure out how
we're gonna get out of this debt.
Yeah, the guys seem
pretty mad about it.
Yeah, I understand
they're mad. We're broke.
You know, raising
a baby's expensive.
Yeah. I mean, I just
think that, uh...
That, uh...
- What are you doing?
- Shhh.
Oh! I get it.
Pledgy-poo has a little crush.
Shh.
Please, don't do anything
to embarrass me.
Are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
Okay, I kinda liked her,
but El nino
smacked me in the nuts
when I was getting to know her.
Hmm. Do you think
she liked you back?
Yeah.
No, I don't know.
- I mean, it was at the stars, stripes and strippers...
- Shhh!
...party.
She probably doesn't
even remember me.
There was like
a thousand people there.
Wait a second.
That gives me an idea.
- You know how some parties charge money to get in?
- Yeah, those parties suck.
Yeah. No no no.
That's beside the point.
What I mean is if people will pay to get into
those parties, which, as you said, suck,
they're definitely gonna pay
to get into one of ours.
What's going on, guys?
Nothing besides I'm hungry
and all we have is baby food!
Wait, what happened
to all that corn I bought?
It's all good, guys.
Look, pledge and I--
Actually, pledge here figured out what
we need to do to get rid of our debt.
Um, I've managed this fraternity's
funds for the past two years.
We've never been in this bad
of a financial situation.
Something pledge would
know nothing about.
Look, pledge may not have
been here for a long time,
but if there's one thing we
taught him, it's how to party.
You wanna know about that corn?
Let me tell you about the corn.
It took me six damn years
to raise that shit!
- When you rip it up...
- What does throwing a party
have to do with us being broke?
Well, everything, actually. We
can throw a party to make money.
You know, it'll be like
a kind of fundraiser.
We can charge admission
at the door, ask for donations.
The last party we had actually
cost us three grand.
And that was ultra low budget
for an omega party.
This time around, we don't even
have enough money for the beer.
I probably can get about 10 to 15 kegs of
beer from the guys on the football team.
- Yeah!
- Okay, great. Look,
- yeah!
39, you said at the last party
- we had over a thousand people, right?
- Yeah.
All right. So if each person
donates like, what, five dollars,
- that means we'd make...
- $5,000.
A lot of money. Yeah,
you said so yourself.
Our next party is gonna be epic.
Yeah, but this is all irrelevant
because we do not charge
money for our parties.
Oh, come on, man. It's easy.
It's like taking candy
from a baby
- and giving it back to the baby.
- You know, I'm in.
- I'm in too.
- What's it gonna be, 39?
Come on, man. Come on.
All right, all right!
- All right!
- All right.
But seriously, guys,
if we don't pull this off,
you guys have to be prepared
to either declare bankruptcy,
which would eliminate our status
as a recognized fraternity,
or give up kegston.
So the omegas think that
throwing a keg party
with a baby in their custody
is a good idea.
With a baby in their custody
Wait, who has the baby?
The omega's, you mule.
- The omegas have a baby?
- That's what I said, is it not?
Yeah, I just--
No, I just--
Well, we'll see what
the local authorities
have to say when
they hear about this.
I predict that not only
will the omegas go to jail,
but their bad reputation will ruin
their stupid fraternity forever.
Ah. But how is
local law enforcement
ah. But how is
even going to hear
about the party?
I mean, 'cause omega parties
never get broken up.
Leave that to me.
♪ Baby, if you're down ♪
♪ we can turn
this world around... ♪
Pledge, hey listen, we're putting
baby powder in the beer.
What-- what are you talk--
Ow. Ow!
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- Are you okay?
- It's-- yeah, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Hi, yeah, I'm good.
- Okay.
- Hi.
Hi, I'm Kyle.
I thought your name was pledge.
I'm kidding. I'm Caitlin.
Oh well, d-d-do you want
a drink or something?
- Um...
- Yeah no, I'm fine.
- I just--
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah?
- You sure you're okay?
Yeah, I was just more
surprised than anything.
- Yeah, sure, yeah.
- Okay okay.
All right. Yeah, let me just--
With your legs, not your back.
Who's the dude?
That dude is steak mungro.
He was the omega president
when I was a pledge.
Nice. So you guys still
keep in contact?
Only in my prayers.
What happened?
He died in a motorcycle race
against time.
Against time.
Oh, come on. Please?
- What's going on here?
- Please.
The girl want to know
why they call him 39.
- Come on, man.
- Hmm.
Two years ago, 39 here
was an omega pledge.
That year as part of the
initiation, we decided to time
how long each omega pledge
lasted in bed.
Whoever lasted
the shortest amount of time
would forever be known for how
long they lasted. Or lack thereof.
- It's true, I was there.
- Good job.
Whoa whoa.
Who called the wahmbulance?
Hello, boys.
How's it going?
The phi tau tau's are here.
Here's a hundred bucks. Be good chaps
and give us all cups, will you?
Oh, I want change
as well from that.
Hey, where's my cup!
Hey, give me my cup.
- Hey, you big animal.
- Kegston's adorable.
Isn't he, though? He's like got
the cutest cheeks and the hair.
They're huge. I don't know how
he walks around with them.
Yeah, he walks around.
- He's not yours, right?
- No.
Um, there's no possible way
he could be mine.
Now Richie on the other hand--
Does he talk like that?
- Kegston?
- No, Richie.
Oh.
Y-yeah.
♪ Shake... ♪
Oh my gosh, he's so cute!
Hi!
- I change his diapers.
- Hello!
Oh, are you the father?
Actually, uh,
I'm the father too.
Really? You are?
- Yeah.
- Oh my gosh,
that's so great that they
let you guys adopt.
You know, some couples
aren't as lucky as you guys.
In some states, it's not legal
for same-sex couples to adopt.
Oh, but you're so lucky.
No smoking.
There's a baby in the house.
Aye aye, captain.
I said there's
a baby in the house!
So I've been thinking about
publishing my memoirs
and calling them, How
I bring the rain."
'Cause El nino's like
a state of mind, you know.
And I was-- - actually, El
nino is a climate pattern
that occurs in the tropical pacific
ocean about every five years,
affecting the surface
temperature of the ocean water
and the pressure
of the air above it,
resulting in global climate
anomalies,
some of which are drastic.
It's awesome.
What?
- Tell me one thing.
- What?
Me too!
Is this a party? Yeah,
is there a problem?
- We got a noise complaint.
- Oh, sorry, sir.
- We can turn down the music.
- We also hear that there could be a baby living here.
Is that a problem?
Yes, that is a problem.
Yeah, 'cause I want to know what
kind of disgraceful, moronic inbred
would call the cops on such a
fine group of young gentlemen.
To raise a child at your age?
I-- I am impressed.
- Thanks, man.
- I agree,
'cause I got two of my own
at home and I gotta tell--
Excuse me, officers.
A keg party is hardly
a place to keep a baby, eh?
Surely one of you fine strapping
civil servicemen
will call somebody.
What did you just say, nerd?
Nerd?
Did you just call me
a nerd, Mr. pig?
Oink oink! Why don't you toddle
off back to your bacon wagon?
Go back to the station, have a
big jolly with all your friends.
You have the right
to remain silent, nerd.
Oh now, just you listen!
Who do you think you are?
Do you know who my father is?
He invented electricity!
Class of '98. You know, Dillon?
Class of '93.
Damn, night train is
going for a record up there.
It's been really great.
I thought it was hilarious
you guys hired fake cops
to kick rico out of the party.
- I hope you get enough money for kegston.
- Yeah, I hope so.
- Tell 'em I said bye.
- I-- I really hope
we get out of this situation.
So the total profit
for the party
so the total profit
is $14,503.
Did you hear what I just said?
14--
You know what?
I'm going up there
and I'm gonna get seconds.
- No, that's-- it's fine.
- They--
It's not a big deal.
Say it louder.
You like that, huh?
Oh, night train,
night train. Oh! Oh!
Night train! Night train!
What the hell you doing here?
I don't know. Just trying
to get to it, you know?
Get the hell
outta here, Sambora!
Anyway, um,
would you ever want to,
like, hang out
outside of here,
like somewhere else?
Yeah.
- Sure.
- Really?
Yeah. That'd be fun.
Okay, let's do it. I mean,
let's hang out, of course.
- Right. Okay.
- Yeah.
Um, cool. I'll see you around.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye. Yeah.
Boom, I'm going.
Ain't gonna stop me.
Alexander Hamilton
was the first treasurer of the
United States of America.
Do we wanna push it up over here
or we wanna push it up over there?
You have very very light hair.
That? That's steak mungro.
"Do ye know the white whale
then, Tash?"
Gonna go up, swoop swoop swoop,
- over there.
- Hut!
You gotta do what you
wanna do, otherwise--
You want some?
In a little bit, okay?
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Lie down and fight ♪
♪ lie down and fight ♪
♪ if I am not a man,
what am I? ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
This is my mask.
That is a--
Stuffed animal.
Okay, man, you got it.
All right.
It's--
I don't know, man.
I do it 'cause
I'm scared, you know?
You know what else?
He was shot by Aaron burr in 1804.
It was very sad.
Hopefully, one day,
you'll become that man.
My brother.
"And the great shroud
of the sea rolled on
as it rolled
five thousand years ago."
The end.
You know, I still
don't understand
how you're graduating college
and yet you can't remember
to put the diaper on a baby
before you put him in the crib.
Hey, you know what, pledge?
Enough.
You don't understand the pressure of
having to actually graduate college.
When my aunt Debbie
graduated college,
she opened up an orphanage,
an orphanage for midgets.
It went really well until they started
getting their hands on candy.
Couple years later, we never
heard from aunt Debbie again.
Anyways, this is boring.
I'm up for getting some drinks
and some food. What's up?
You're buying, man?
I saw you got drafted.
Congrats, by the way,
on the draft. That's sick.
- What's this, man?
- He-- night train got drafted.
What do you mean?
Everybody knew that.
Oh my god, man, you got drafted?
You're going to Iraq, ese?
Oh, man, you're gonna die!
You're gonna be like with the
freedom and the bullets.
They be like--
They're gonna shoot you!
That's not good for you! I don't
want you to die! You're my brother!
- I stand in the bullet for you!
- El nino, El nino.
He got-- he's gonna
play football.
- I'm so confused.
- Man, look see,
that's what you get for
smoking that emotional stuff.
- It's 'cause it's cheap!
- Anyways, this is kegston's stuff.
I'm not gonna clean this up
and I can't--
Dude, kegston's an infant.
He can't clean up his own room.
Say one more thing again and
you'll be cleaning my girdle.
What's up? I'm as hungry
as a bulimic hippo.
Man, I want waffles.
Whiff.
Meow.
- Hmm.
Yes-sss.
Yeah-hhhh?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I propose that we
put jaegermeister
in all the water fountains
around campus,
and especially in the quad.
'Cause I feel the girls there will be
more compelled to show their breasts.
- They have the biggest breasts out of the whole school.
- Objection!
The female anatomy is not
something to be drooled over.
I propose that we stop
making me the accountant.
Just because I'm brown doesn't
mean I'm good at math.
Objection!
It means exactly that.
I propose we initiate
a school-wide manhunt
for the former brilliant
actor Rick moranis.
Objection!
Rick moranis's whereabouts
are a matter for
national security only.
Hmm.
Whatever did happen to him?
Don't know.
All right.
Got all the notes from school.
I've got nothing else
to add so--
Hold it right there, hodgkinson.
Do you remember your little
- kegger for kegston a few weeks ago?
- Yeah, how was jail?
Laugh all you want, collison.
My brief incarceration allowed me
to catch up on a little reading.
I have some paperwork here
that you might be interested in.
I seriously doubt it.
"Article 7k:
All members of university-
affiliated fraternities
must be enrolled
as full-time students.
Must be enrolled
Furthermore, no non-affiliated
students or otherwise
can live in university
Greek housing."
- Does that include babies?
- Oh, why yes, it does.
Oh, but don't worry.
I'm sure there'll be an opening
at the local orphanage.
It'll actually be an upgrade
coming from the omega home.
Meeting adjourned!
Meeting adjourned?
What are you talking about?
Dude, the omegas control
the Greek board.
Not for long.
Maybe we could just
hide him, you know?
Dress him up like he's a little
koala bear or something.
Build him a tree house. Whoosh.
Yeah! Nobody would even notice.
That's illegal in so many ways.
What if we--
What if we oil him?
Hey, guys, I think
I found a loophole.
What are you talking about?
If we can get kegston
enrolled at Hamilton,
then he can live with us
and he can remain an omega.
Uh, yeah, pledge,
that's brilliant,
except how are we gonna get a
baby enrolled in a university?
Wow.
All right. Let me just
get this straight, guys.
You found a baby
on your doorstep.
- Yup.
- And then you took him back to the omega house.
- That sounds about right.
- And now you want me
to allow you to let
kegston become a student
at Hamilton
so he can remain an omega?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
Well, it's kind
of a ridiculous request.
And though I do love all of you
because you do so much
for the school--
I mean, Rodney
and Nicholas and Matthew,
you are, like, so high on my
list of everything that you do,
- because I so appreciate--
- What about me?
I don't even know you.
Anyway, um...
Look, I so wish I could give my
permission to do this for you guys.
I really do!
I would love to be able to say,
"yes, take the baby. Raise the baby.
Be happy with the baby."
I love babies. I wish I had a baby,
but I've had some complications.
Anyway, I wish I could allow this
to happen, but rules are rules.
My hands are tied. I'm just
not going to be able to.
We understand. We really do.
Thank you so much.
Sure, no problem. Okay.
Okay, have a good day.
Well, that didn't go so well.
♪ Perfect people
in this world... ♪
Come on, that's how you do it.
That's how you do it, right?
I got this. I got this.
Move out, man.
I got this.
Yeah! Just right.
Renato, the first thing you did
wrong is you had the laces in.
They supposed to be out.
And, El nino,
there is no way you're gonna
make the football team.
I could tell coach anything I
want-- me and kegston can lie--
- And you still ain't gonna make it.
- But let me play, man.
- Let me play.
- You ain't gonna make the Mexico soccer team
- with that kick.
- But I come to you with this,
- this little dream of mine--
- Well well well.
Look what I found. What is this,
a shades of brown meeting?
So which one of you einsteins
has worked out whose
mongrel child this is, eh?
Huh? None of you?
Well, bit too optimistic
on my part, I see.
I'm gonna go back to my chess
game, a real man's sport.
See how far playing
football gets you.
You all know what?
This gives me a good idea.
Hamilton university has given me
all that I can ask for.
They took me off the streets
and they made my mama proud
by giving me a chance to do what I
love, and that's playing football.
And now that I'm going pro,
I plan to give back.
And not just by building some pool
or donating a couple of weights.
No, I plan
to give back for real,
and that's the reason why
today I unveil to you...
The Rodney Maine
infant scholar fellowship!
Each year, I will sponsor
the full tuition
of an underprivileged infant
who just wants
the opportunity to get
what I've been given:
A chance to be a Hamilton duelo.
- Wow, that's great.
- Boy, this is a really historic moment.
Unprecedented. Bravo!
Please refer all further questions
to my consigliere merkhaus.
- How did he come up with the--
- Wait your turn.
Why don't you wait
your turn there, chief?
Infant scholar fellowship!
What sort of a country is this?
"I score touchdowns.
I'm dangerously charming.
I want to give babies--
An education."
Idiots!
Well, we'll see
who has the last laugh.
Hey, fellas, can y'all
do me a favor?
Don't mention the kegger
for kegston night.
'Cause moms provides
a beatdown like a bongo.
Okay. Speaking of which, they
should be here any second now.
What should I do
with this thing?
Hey! Anybody living in here?
- Hey, mama.
- Hey, baby.
- Ooh, boy, you skinny!
- Let me get that for you.
- All right. Y'all eating?
- Thank you very much.
Huh-uh. Are any
of y'all eating well?
- We will now.
- Just skinny.
- How you doing, Mrs. Maine?
- Oh, wonderful.
- Don't be kissing my mama.
- All right!
Hey, dad.
That shirt looks familiar.
I wondered where it'd gotten.
Oh, look how adorable!
Oh! What's that smell?
- What's a baby doing here?
- Um...
He's even cuter than you said
he was gonna look, Rodney.
I think it's a great thing that you boys
are raising this child, I really do.
Yeah. Fatherhood is really
carving you boys into men.
It's a damn shame those nerds,
the phi ta-ta's, are
trying to take him away.
The phi ta-ta's, are
Wait.
This fraternity is raising that baby?
Whose is it?
- Well, we don't exactly--
- Oh boy!
You're the only family
I got, t-brow.
Hey. I love you.
As shitty as you are in darts,
nobody would want to claim you.
Oh yeah?
Whoa!
Still got it, old man.
Love you, you son of a bitch.
Fuck. Thanks for coming, dad.
I wouldn't miss it for nothing.
Dad, this is t-brow.
T-brow, this is my dad.
- What's up?
- It's cool, it's cool.
You know...
Now let me get this straight,
with the accent on the word
"straight."
You live in a house
with a bunch of guys.
Can you tell me, please,
why a pair of men's underwear
is framed on your wall here?
Can you? Can you tell me?
No, I can't tell you.
I don't know.
Does prince Charles know
that you've got his--
Buttless underwear
up there in a frame?
What's that about?
Pansy. Come on. Want
to play with us?
We got you! Come on, eses.
Let's go.
Hey, Waldo, what's up with the do-rag?
You're from Ohio.
Dad, do not call me Waldo.
Here, my name is El nino.
- Come on!
- Is that a weather pattern?
Dad, you're ruining my credit!
Come on, man!
Hey, are you using one
of those marijuana sticks?
What? No! I cut you!
Respeta a tu padre!
At least one of us has balls.
I'm sorry, mami!
Well, I know he ain't Rodney's.
Have you looked at
the color of his eyes?
I'll tell you right now,
I know he's not merkhaus'
'cause number one,
he's not smoking.
And I been close to the kid--
He don't smell like bourbon.
Let me tell you about
the omega class
of 1932.
Yeah. The stocks were down--
Way way down.
Oh-ho! But so were
the girls' skirts.
Yeah!
And we, the omegas,
we invented the boobs!
The way to go! The way to show!
The way to get
the job done, right?
Skirts are down,
the boobs are out.
Everything is flowing, man!
Like who needed consequences?
We're no candy-asses.
We got it done.
We made it work, baby.
The omega omega omega!
Yeah!
- So who are these dudes?
- Well, that's renato
and those are his two dads.
Uh, he's the dad.
I'm the father.
Hi, I'm Bruce! Ooh, score!
Damn it!
I mean, it's still just
the second draft and...
I'm actually considering,
you know, changing some of the
things on the page you're reading,
- but--
- Mm-hmm. And this is
what I'm spending
40 grand a year for?
What I'm spending
You writing little short stories
about college parties, huh?
- Yeah, it's self-reflective.
- Oh.
Maybe that's what you should be
doing, Kyle. Reflecting on yourself.
Where are you headed
in your life?
- Why he got to pick on him?
- Come on, dad.
What do you mean,
"come on, dad"?
You expect me to just sit here and be happy
with what you're doing with your life?
You are raising a baby in a frat
house with a bunch of idiots.
Hey.
What's going on, Mr. motes?
Did you hear that Kyle here is going
to be representing the omegas
did you hear that Kyle here is going
- in the upcoming Greek board election?
- You are?
- I am?
- He is.
Yeah, absolutely. The omegas
have an 88-year tradition
of controlling
the university Greek board.
Kyle here is going
to be number 89.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well...
Now that would look great
on a law school application.
♪ Sweet and smooth ♪
♪ your love is
like chocolate... ♪
Who are you, pussycat?
I'm t-brow's mom. Who are you?
I'm merkhaus.
Are you, uh,
really t-brow's mom?
I'm as real as a mother can get.
I like that.
Here, try this.
Scrumptious.
Well, thanks, son,
for the great snacks.
Mm-hmm.
Congratulations
on the Greek board.
I suppose that is
an achievement.
Uh, do me a favor, would you?
- Would you find a real major?
- Okay.
And consider giving prince
Charles back his underwear.
- Okay. Bye, dad.
- May be getting cold.
- Yeah. Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Later, Mr. motes.
Well, Mr. motes.
- Oh my god.
- You ready to take over this fraternity?
Where's the cornbread?
Why are you wearing my shirt?
Are you constipated?
So you guys still have
no clue whose kid this is.
- No.
- All right, well, is there any hints?
I mean, what's the baby into?
Oh, he likes "the pokey dokey."
Man, to hell
with that "pokey dokey."
All right, well...
He doesn't look like thames.
And we know it's not
t-brow's or pledge's.
Professor street?
What is it?
Now is it possible
that it could be my child?
I mean, not unless
you had sex with Andre the
giant in the past three years.
Right? I mean, the kid's
bigger than you are.
- It's not possible.
- Maybe I'm just a late bloomer.
You keep telling yourself that.
That's a good call.
It was good.
Hey, guys, can I ask you
a quick question?
What's up, pledge?
Well, I'm taking
Caitlin out tonight.
- Nice.
- I approve.
Um, anyway, I'm taking her out
and I don't know where to go
and so I was hoping you guys
might have some suggestions.
Okay yeah, it stops right
there and it goes right here.
Okay, pledge, let me
ask you something:
- What do women love?
- Flowers?
Booze. Booze and dark chocolate.
This is what you're going to get--
Get a flask, half a bottle.
It doesn't really matter.
Take her to a park, alley.
It's irrelevant. About
halfway through the booze,
offer her some
dark chocolate. Why?
'Cause it's an aphrodisiac,
my friend. All right?
- She'll be wetter than ever before midnight.
- Merk--
- she'll be wetter than ever before midnight.
Don't listen to anything
he's saying, okay?
Caitlin's a nice girl. Take her to
a really nice Italian restaurant.
- Get a nice bottle of red wine.
- I remember my first date.
We went mini-golfing.
And we ate
and had a lot of fun.
And the best part was
we really got to know each other
as people.
Ugh. Another.
- That's a great idea.
- Really?
Yeah no, it's good because you
can show your manly side.
You know, be aggressive.
Show you like sports.
Ultimately, what you want to do,
you want to get that hole in one.
I'm not talking about
the golf course.
- I'm talking about putt-putt in her panties.
- That is repulsive.
It's not repulsive when you're banging
a girl in the back, you know that?
- It is repulsive, triple x!
- Just shut your mouth!
Okay, mini-golf it is.
Yeah whoo!
Clap it up.
Clap it up!
- Go ahead.
- Oh, um, which do you want?
♪ Feel that deja voodoo
electric... ♪
Okay.
♪ With all the gangstas
and all your friends ♪
♪ making me want you like
cheap trick... ♪
- Knees bent.
- ♪ Is it right? ♪
♪ Is it wrong? ♪
♪ Are you lonely? ♪
♪ Do you want something for your soul?
♪ - here you go.
- Oh, right.
- ♪ not your heart... ♪
- Hit it hard.
- ♪ but your body... ♪
- So it goes over the-- shoo.
- ♪ I want to feel good ♪
♪ I'll make you feel right ♪
♪ 'cause when the party isn't planned...
♪ - like that?
♪ Forget your ex-boyfriends ♪
♪ and your
ex-girlfriends too...♪
So, Mr. creative writing major,
have you written
anything lately?
- She's gorgeous.
- Uh, yeah.
- Sort of.
- So what's it about?
Well, um,
it's kind of like
my life as an omega.
- Oh, here.
- Yeah.
But, you know, not an expose,
but kind of just telling the
story how it is, you know?
Rushing and pledging-- - getting
your testicles smacked at parties.
Yeah...
That's actually
the title of the story.
- ♪ I want to feel good... ♪
- I think that's really cool.
You're doing something you
love and are passionate about.
I still have no clue
what I want to major in.
♪ When the party
isn't planned forget... ♪
My dad, he wants me
to go to law school.
- Is he a lawyer?
- Clap it up!
Um, yeah, he's a prosecutor.
You know, I really don't
want to go to law school,
but that's all
he ever talks about.
Sorry.
I just must sound like a baby.
No, it's okay.
- I feel the same way too sometimes.
- Clap it up!
Current polls show motes
leading Larsen...
Now the time where I can
finally exact my revenge
upon the omegas is
rapidly approaching.
Revenge? For what?
Yeah, rico, you're always
talking about revenge
against the omegas, but what
are you getting revenge for?
It was a long time ago.
I finally got to live my dream
of rushing the omega fraternity.
Champions!
- Champions! Champions!
- Whoo!
- Champions!
- Yeah, champions!
Champions!
♪ We are the champions! ♪
Hello. My name is rico.
Your name's... "Thams." Oh!
It's thames. My name's thames.
No no no, "thams."
- It's thames.
- No, it's "thams."
It's thames.
No, it's "thams,"
like the river?
It runs down from--
Let's see--
Round about Oxford way,
and it comes out through London
- and goes out into--
- I said my name's thames.
Okay, your name's thames. Okay.
Yeah. Hello, my name is rico.
Excuse me.
I wonder if I could ask
you a question about the--
Oh wow!
It's steak mungro,
the omega president.
Hi, my name's rico.
I've come all the way over from
england to join this fraternity.
I heard you have
so many hot chicks here,
and I really want
to get with girls. Hi.
I hear you have the best girls.
Although...
Yeah, I was expecting
sort of better.
But I'm sure you've been
with better before yourself.
Steak
out.
Okay well, nice to talk
to you, Mr. president.
Hey, do you want my number?
Hey, maybe later on?
Hi, hottie.
Oh yeah, cool. Can I play?
Hey, give me a go.
You all right? How you doing?
You fancy some white action instead
of some black action for a change?
Hey, we could tag-team, couldn't we?
Night and day.
- What?! What'd you say?
- Black and white, that could be the new thing.
You shouldn't have said that.
Night train?
Ow! Oh oh.
Like that? Huh, like that?
They ripped my underwear,
giving me what they called
a wedgie from both sides.
Giving me what they called
That's a Melvin-wedgie hybrid.
I can't believe
you rushed omegas.
It was a long time ago,
but in the time since
I have vowed to exact my revenge
upon the omegas. And now
I finally found a way!
♪ Don't let them go ♪
♪ beware ♪
♪ who your children stay with ♪
♪ they're coming out tonight ♪
♪ look out ♪
♪ For the baby killers ♪
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ they coming to your town...
♪ - boop boop.
He's so cute.
I'm just glad he's not mine.
Am I the first white girl
you've ever been with?
Hell no!
Well, it only takes
one white girl
- to make a white baby.
- What?
- Mom?
- T-brow.
- What are you doing here, mom?
- Have some respect!
- Hey, you're not my real dad!
- Hey hey! No fighting!
- You're not my real dad!
- I love her, okay?
- No, you don't.
- I love her!
You don't even know
what love is!
That's my boy!
So, rico, I still don't
understand what we're doing here.
Shush, you idiot!
You'll see soon enough.
Damn it, I feel like a
jackass from back there
with t-brow and his mom.
But you know what?
F-it, because I love
that woman, okay?
And she loves me and if
loving someone's a crime,
lock me up and throw away the
key, baby, 'cause I'm guilty.
What do you think about this?
Goo-goo gah-gah?
What?
- Gotcha!
- Damn it, renato!
What the heck are
you guys doing here?
We'll be leaving now.
Go go go! Get out, get out!
Definitely a good time. It was.
Wait. Isn't that the guy
we gave an atomic wedgie to?
Actually, night train, that
was a wedgie-Melvin hybrid.
Where's Einstein
going over here?
Pledge, you might be
interested in this.
Hey, rico,
you might be interested in this.
Lemon meringue-- not bad.
Ah-hh!
I'm going to crush you!
♪ Brandy! ♪
♪ Bra-aaandy... ♪
Mind if I cut in?
- Sure.
- I'll be over there in a minute.
So what's the matter, dude?
I'm just really really
nervous about the election.
What's there
to be nervous about?
You know an omega
has won the election
every year
for the past 88 years.
Exactly.
Rico just gave me
a copy of the "herald."
He's beating me by 5%
in the polls.
What if I lose? You should have
just picked a better candidate.
Somebody like 39.
Everybody loves 39.
Forget rico.
And you're a much better
candidate than 39.
I can hear you.
Yeah well,
39 is a legacy though.
And I'm just lucky
you guys even let me in.
You're not lucky at all.
Part of the reason why I chose you
to become my successor is because...
I see in you
what I could have been.
You have an opportunity
to change things.
Learn from my mistakes.
Listen,
you're gonna win the election
and you're gonna make
one hell of a president.
And you're gonna make
- You trust me?
- Yeah, I trust you.
Remember, be yourself.
♪ For you. ♪
- All right, this has gone beyond gay.
- Uh, yeah.
I'll tell you something,
night train.
- I am never going back.
- Hey, guys.
It must be Caitlin.
Come on in!
I'm from child
protective services.
- Is this the omega house?
- Yeah.
- Can we help you?
- There he is.
- That's my son.
- Your son? Whoa, excuse me!
Oh, I was so worried.
See? I told you they had him!
Thank goodness I took
those pictures.
It seems as though you had illegal
custody of someone else's child.
Wait. How was it illegal?
He was left on our doorstep.
- Did you ever consider calling the authorities?
- We took a paternity test.
- And what were the results?
- I don't know. Did we ever get the results?
I have some results here
that you'll be interested in.
These blood results state
that Mr. Larsen
is the father of this child.
I shall have to think
of a new name for you.
Oh, but how sweet is this?
In the very spot where you
once embarrassed me,
I take away everything
you ever cared about.
Rico out.
You know, before kegston
showed up...
I was thinking about sticking
around for another year.
Figured "why not stay
in college until you're 25?"
I feel you, man.
I think I finally realized
what it means to be an adult.
Something still just doesn't
make any sense to me.
Why would rico's baby
be on our doorstep?
- We gotta get him back.
- He's not ours.
We gotta get him back.
Gotta get him back.
- Jesus, merkhaus.
- Pull yourself together, man.
Come on.
- Gotta get him back.
- Yeah look, I wanna get him back too, man,
but he's not ours.
He may not have been
conceived by one of us,
he may not have been
but he's definitely one of ours.
He's an omega.
We gotta get him back.
How do we make him stop?
- I don't know. Do something!
- Like what?
Anything. What are you good at?
I can tell
really really good
knock-knock jokes.
- Let's hear one.
- Knock knock.
- Who's there?
- Fanny.
Fanny who?
Fanny body calls, I'm out.
That's even worse.
You just--
You made it even worse.
- Is that thing still crying?
- Yeah, rico, we've tried everything.
You're lucky I'm in a good mood.
I just got the latest
poll results.
As word of the omegas' little child
abduction continues to build,
my numbers continue
to skyrocket.
Why, if the election
were held this instant,
you'd be looking at
the new Hamilton university
Greek board president.
That way we can finally get
the annual "farmer's
almanac" ball approved!
Actually, when I win,
there will be no more
phi tau tau.
No more fraternities, period.
No more resistance to my power.
I can't believe rico is using
kegston to help him get votes.
- This is dirty politics.
- Hodges, pledge.
We just all came back
from the quad.
I gotta tell you, pretty much the
entire campus hates us right now.
And look what those phi tau tau
supporters did to my shirt.
It's lemon meringue, man.
They all think
we kidnapped kegston.
Yeah well, you didn't
really do anything
to help the situation,
Mr. press conference.
Now if it involved corn dogs, maybe
you'd be all up in that piece, huh?
You really want
to take it there?
What are you gonna
do about it, Rodney?
- Take you back to the hood!
- Hodges! Hodges!
No, put him down.
Night train, put him down!
Hodges, man, when rico wins
the Greek board,
does that mean we get to like,
you know, join the phi tau taus?
Hey. Hey, guys, come on!
No-ooo!
I know everything seems
really messed up right now
without kegston,
but we can't forget
that we're still omegas.
That's right.
Look, pledge, I just need you
to focus on winning
- the Greek board debate, okay?
- Okay.
Let me worry about kegston.
I'll figure something out.
- Hey! Hey you! Vote!
- Vote for the motes over here.
- Merkhaus, this guy.
- Hey hey, you!
- Vote!
- Vote for motes over here.
- Vote for motes.
Guys, I just got off the
phone with the clinic,
and they have no record of us
ever taking a paternity test.
Seriously, kid?
"Votes for motes"?
Is this the best you got?
What does this even mean?
Come on, streets. We're already
in a tight enough spot as it is.
Last thing we need is an omega alumni
pissing on us while we're down.
None of your alumni have ever
been in the situation
you guys are in right now,
all right?
You guys are in right now,
You're about to lose
Greek board.
I know this whole kegston thing
is messed up right now,
but I'm working as hard
as I can so I can beat rico.
Working hard isn't gonna cut it.
Have you seen the polls today?
You guys are getting killed. You're
going to have to have a plan.
A good plan.
Look, I remember some years back
when there was
another omega freshman
nominated
for Greek board president.
And everyone was walking
around saying,
"look, this dude's not
gonna win. The streak's over.
Streak's over." Dude was
prepared, got up on that stage,
streak's over." Dude was
- won the whole school over.
- Was that steak mungro?
No, it was Hodges. Same dude that
nominated you to follow in his footsteps.
You know what I'm saying?
But you know what?
I think you could be a better
president than Hodges.
I mean, you'd definitely be a
better president than that 39.
- I'm right here.
- Ha!
Anyway, rico is a prick.
So you know what? Kick some ass!
- Yeah!
- Kick his ass, man!
Ah, president dumervile.
Finally, a great lead.
I just wanted to let you know that
when I become Greek board president,
we will be spending
a lot more time together.
Oh, you know what though?
I don't usually spend
that much time
with my students during that.
Oh, really? Well, I'm sure
you can make an exception.
No, really. I've got so much-- and
you probably have so much to do.
- Don't you have a girlfriend?
- I did,
but she lost both her legs last
summer in a skiing accident.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Perhaps we can go to dinner one night.
- Chinese?
- Oh no, I'm allergic, heavily allergic to all that.
I'll cook it myself.
I can make you this lovely--
You know what? I am on a diet
and it's all just liquids.
- It's all I do eat.
- You don't need it.
Oh, stop it. I really--
I-- - oh please!
I've got to go to the bathroom! The
liquids are going right through me.
"As Greek board president,
I plan to keep these
traditions alive,
and I promise to preserve them
for future generations
of Hamilton students to enjoy."
What'd you think?
It was good.
- Yeah?
- I think you could do better.
How? This is the best I can do.
It's not like
I'm gonna win anyway.
What?
Look, have you seen
the latest poll results?
Rico's beating me by 40%.
Nobody wants to vote
for the fraternity
that is kidnapping babies.
Okay, the Kyle motes
I met a few months ago
may not have been the most
confident person in the world,
but he wouldn't be laying here
preparing to let rico Larsen
win Greek board.
Okay, I know you've been
trying really hard
okay, I know you've been
to get all the information
on kegston,
and you're under
a lot of pressure,
but come on, Kyle.
I mean, we're in round 12 here.
- Are you really just gonna give up?
- No.
Okay, if you go
up there tomorrow
and you show the entire
university who you really are,
they're gonna love you.
And who cares if you
don't win the election?
At least you'll go
out there swinging.
Sorry. My dad's a high
school basketball coach.
All I really know
are sports analogies.
I've just never spoken in front
of that many people before.
Well, there's a first time
for everything.
- I'm really nervous.
- So was Willis Reed before game seven.
Oh-hhh!
Look at pledge popping
his cherry over here.
With only days remaining
before the Greek board debate,
Richard "rico" Larsen
has surged into a commanding
25% lead in the polls.
Many attribute
the shift to the news
many attribute
- that omega fraternity abducted and hazed...
- Hey, vote for motes!
...Larsen's baby, rico, Jr.
Rex moonberry, a Hamilton
freshman, had this to say:
I'm voting for rico 'cause I heard
the omegas kidnapped his baby.
Do you know dolphin babies can't see for
the first two months of their lives?
And that's not
the only negativity
directed at the omegas
ways these days.
Damn omegas always make a mess!
And I always have
to clean it up!
Why can't you clean up
your mess, you potheads!
Can Kyle motes keep
the omegas tradition alive?
We'll find out very soon.
Hey, son.
Dad.
Um...
What are you doing here?
I have something to show you.
That's your mother
and me in 1978.
Wow. Um--
Wait. You were an omega?
Not quite.
I never made it past
being a pledge.
Why? Did they kick you out
for wearing those socks?
Not quite.
My father didn't approve of me
participating in such things.
Go figure.
But until the day she died
your mother always believed
that I never should have
given it up.
And I know that
she would be very proud
to know that her son
was omega material.
Well, I might not be
omega material much longer
well, I might not be
if I don't win this thing.
That really doesn't matter.
Because win or lose,
you're still our son.
All right?
Now just do me one favor.
- Could you consider becoming a lawyer?
- Yeah okay.
Just a little thought,
if you wouldn't mind.
- Yeah, I'll think about it.
- Okay.
I'm out there cheering you on.
Turns out your old man
was just a pledge too.
Maybe you could help me
with this thing.
Won't stop crying. Shut up!
You know I'm thinking
of naming him rico Jr.
Darwin was right--
Survival of the fittest.
See you on the other side,
pledge!
Rico! Rico! Rico!
Okay, all right, all right.
Everybody, please settle down.
Today's debate
for Greek board president
today's debate
features two candidates.
First, representing phi tau tau
is Richard Larsen, a junior.
Rico! Rico! Rico!
All right, and representing
the incumbent omega fraternity
is Mr. Kyle motes, a freshman.
Um, today's debate will feature
a series of questions
about each candidate's
vision of the university.
About each candidate's
And it is up to you,
the student body,
to decide who you think
is the best candidate.
So, Mr. motes,
the floor is yours.
Um...
Well, I've never spoken
in front of a crowd
this large before.
Wimp!
Um, let me start
by introducing myself.
My name's Kyle motes.
I'm a creative writing m-major.
- Um, I--
- Get off the stage, nerd!
I-I-I-I live about
20 miles east--
Oooh!
I'm a creative writing major!
- All right, all right.
- Enough of that.
Settle down, please.
We don't need that.
You sound like a little baby.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
All right. Why don't we
go to our first question.
Okay? Mr. Larsen,
this will be directed to you:
What would you do
as Greek board president
what would you do
to make Hamilton university
a better place?
As a father,
I have learned what is important
for the Hamilton community now,
but more importantly,
what is important
for the Hamilton community
in the future.
As any great parent would know--
Oh, um, do you--
- Do you need a moment?
- Uh, yes.
Thank you.
Come on, rico junior...
Are you hungry? Oh, cranky
little one I have here.
Shut up, shut up.
We're going to win.
The presidential
victory is ours.
Mmm.
It's all part of his act.
He's happy, really.
Wave! Come on!
- Wave with daddy!
- ♪ you move like this ♪
♪ you slide like that ♪
♪ you wiggle real slow ♪
♪ and you dance real fast ♪
♪ you do it all over,
but you change it all around ♪
♪ then you jump
off the ground. ♪
What is this, a circus?
Oh no. Maybe it's
just great parenting.
Something you would
know nothing about
considering
you are not a parent!
You're right. I'm not.
But neither are you.
What the heck are you
talking about?
Well...
What I've just handed
president dumervile
are the results
of a paternity test
to see if Mr. Richard Larsen
is the father of that baby.
That's absurd.
You don't have any of my DNA.
Actually, rico...
I do.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Well, Mr. rico,
it looks like you
are not the father.
Yes, you're right, I'm not!
But I was doing
this poor child a favor
by taking him away
from you scoundrels!
What?
Steak mungro.
Oh my god, he's alive!
Legend.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were dead.
I thought I killed you!
Steak out.
Steak out!
Steak! Steak! Steak! Steak!
Steak! Steak! Steak!
When I first rushed omega,
I didn't know what I was
getting myself into.
I-- to be honest,
I was just trying to fit in.
Then I found out what
being an omega meant.
And it's not just hanging out
with your best friends
or throwing crazy parties
or sleeping with the same
girls in the same night.
It's going
beyond being a brother.
It's going beyond
even a fatherhood.
And we help each other
become better people.
Become better people.
That's what fraternity
means to me.
And as Greek board president that's
what I plan on doing for Hamilton.
- He doin' a good job, ain't he? Mm-hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, I'm sure you've all
heard of the omegas'
88-year streak of controlling
the Greek board.
Well, tonight
that streak comes to an end.
From now on, it doesn't matter
what fraternity you're in,
what sport you play
or who you hang out with.
What sport you play
As Greek board president, I plan
on being there for everyone.
Because I honestly
believe that each
and every person
in this room is an omega.
Clap it up. Clap it up!
Omega! Omega! Omega!
Shortly after his presumed
fatal motorcycle accident,
steak decided to take time
to teach gifted children
in new Guinea.
- Omegas, listen!
- Whoa.
I ran here as fast as I could.
The hell you two doing here?
Hey, no, it's okay.
Let them speak.
Listen, we have some paperwork you
guys should really take a look at.
Yeah, rico stole those
a while ago.
We should have told you then.
Is there any way
you can forgive us?
Like the man said...
We are all omegas.
No, but, you guys, seriously,
if you would let me
do the honors.
I have the results
of your paternity tests here
that you took three months ago.
You guys sure
we're ready for this?
All right.
Man, hurry up and read it, man.
It's-- they're stuck together.
Renato.
You are not the father.
Oooh ooooh!
Sorry.
I'm on so many painkillers,
you should probably do this.
You should probably do this.
Are we really sure
we're ready for this, guys?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
The father is...
- 39.
- Wait, what? Are you serious?
Yeah. Says it right here, man.
- Wait, which one's 39?
- That guy right there.
Hey, babe.
I don't know if
I'm ready for this.
Hey, man, don't forget.
He's not just yours.
- He's an omega. He's all of ours.
- Yeah.
Do you have an idea
who the mother is?
No, I don't know.
I mean, to be honest
with you guys,
I really haven't had that much
sex in the last two years.
Okay.
- Come on.
- Sorry.
Except for that one time.
What it is,
it's actually pure silk.
And it's from a Dutch armory
in Switzerland.
It smells beautiful too.
It smells like roses.
Here, night train,
you wanna smell this?
- Hell no!
- The sailboat smells like a sailboat.
Yo yo yo. Dude.
That's 39 seconds for collison.
- Damn!
- That's very impressive.
- Oh, man!
- You can't be an omega like that!
39! 39! 39!
- 39! 39! 39!
- Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey, 39 what?
39 what?
It's gonna be pretty weird without
Hodges and night train next year.
Yeah, it's not gonna be
the same without them.
It won't, dude, but you know what?
It's gonna be great.
We got a lot of good things
planned for next year.
All right, guys.
I'm a little verklempt,
but me and El Ron are packed.
Ciao, fellas.
- Later, rich.
- Put her there, 39.
- Richie.
- It's good times. Pledge.
- Rich.
- You're gonna do just fine.
- Thanks, man. That means a lot.
- Be good.
Thames.
Oh oh.
Yep. A little more gel.
All right.
See ya later, Richie.
See ya alumni weekend.
Richie must have
forgot his hair gel.
Oh, hey, you guys remember
when night train
got all that mustard
all over his shirt?
Um, hey, guys,
you might wanna
take a look at this.
- Check it out!
- Oww!
Fool. Like a squirrel!
♪ Rock and roll all night
and party every day ♪
♪ I party till I puke,
but that's okay... ♪
Cut!
April fools, buddy.
♪ The newest pledge ♪
♪ I'm the newest pledge ♪
♪ I'm the newest pledge... ♪
In my opinion, the baseball team
is much cuter
than the football team.
- Child, please.
- Well, I mean, just like--
Just the way they
walk and look and--
Shut your trap,
guuuurl!
♪ Rock all night,
we study all day ♪
♪ the omegas are the rulers ♪
♪ don't you hear me say ♪
♪ I'm the newest pledge ♪
♪ I'm the newest pledge... ♪ - all right,
who here has had sex in the past two years?
- ♪ I'm the newest pledge... ♪
- ow!
So my name's Max,
and they gave me a red cup
but they've got blue ones.
And they've got white ones, but there's
white on the inside of the red ones
and they-- you can put--
I wish they'd--
Do you wear a cup?
Oh!
♪ Kappa kappa beta ♪
♪ omega... ♪
Hey, I thought we could eat
the last two togethe-- mom?
- T-brow!
- Whoa whoa, it's not what it looks like.
♪ I'm the newest pledge... ♪
- Just getting night train is--
- What's up?
♪ I'm the newest pledge ♪
Got mustard all over my shirt!
- Here's kiddy food.
- Stop.
♪ I'm the newest pledge ♪
♪ pledge, pledge! ♪
♪ Don't be deranged ♪
♪ Vote for the change ♪
♪ Vote for rico ♪
♪ Vote for him ♪
♪ Oh, please vote for rico ♪
♪ Because he is tasty
like gallo de pico ♪
♪ yes, he is ♪
♪ Oh oh, please vote
for the phi tau tau rico. ♪
And stop.
Hello, everyone.
Are you ready?
Is everyone ready to dance?
Whoop wow!
♪ You move like this,
you slide like that ♪
♪ you wiggle real slow,
then you dance real fast ♪
♪ you do it all over,
but you change it all around ♪
♪ then you jump
off the ground... ♪
♪ You slide like this,
you wiggle like that ♪
♪ you dance real slow,
then you move real fast ♪
♪ you do it all over,
but you change it all around ♪
♪ then you jump
off the ground... ♪
Well, let's do it again, okay?
♪ You wiggle like this,
you dance like that ♪
♪ you move real slow,
then you slide real fast ♪
♪ you do it all over,
but you change it all around ♪
♪ then you jump off the ground ♪
♪ you do it all over,
but you change it all around ♪
♪ then you jump
off the ground. ♪