SSA:Wait for audio trigger
The joint for the right arm is weak on this 96.
Just like the real thing.
I'm amazed at Banpure models.
Shinji.
Summer!
The beach!
And
One summer
The experience of the summer... Why
does it turn out like this?
Well, it is in the same district.
Listen to me!
We were supposed to go
to the beach in Kujyukiri!
Onjyuku!
The white beach!
The desert of the moon!
Camels!
There seems to be no
security problems here.
Stop messing around and come.
It's him.
It's his fault isn't it?
If you didn't like it so much,
you didn't have to come.
Yeah, yeah, you should've refused when
Sagara agreed to go with Kazama.
You're a high school student though,
you shouldn't ditch your friends just
because you're a little uncomfortable.
This might be more exciting than the beach.
Maybe some handsome BS pilot
will come up to you and go...
Want to BS with me?
What if something like that happened?
You mean AS right?
We will avenge our loss
from the Chuuton festival.
The team that challenged us is named the
Red Dragons, but it is full of stupid fools.
We'll show them hell.
I wish you all a good fight.
That is all
Board the mechs.
Yeah!
This is prime grade Nerima daikon.
Here...
Why don't you try it out?
The training demonstration by
the soldiers is about to begin.
Be sure to watch everyone.
Man, you look ridiculous.
This is cardboard.
The real ones look cool.
You're going to lose again this year right?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Jeez, even the little kids make fun of them.
The AS troop is weak as hell.
Do they have a problem with their equipment?
No, they have the best
equipment in the army.
Then why are they weak?
All they have is good equipment, nothing else.
Shinji.
Dad.
You are Sagara?
Yes.
I'm Sergeant Sagara.
I mean, nice to meet you.
I'm Kazama Shintaro.
I'm the commander here.
This is the first time that Shinji has
brought a friend along to this festival.
You don't need to say useless things.
I mean, he's a boy like this.
Sometimes I get worried.
Dad, quit it.
Please, do have a good time today.
Yes.
Commander!
An unusual boy.
He's formal, almost like a man in the military.
He's pretty skillful.
I should have gotten it without the aonori.
If it gets on my teeth, it'll
be harder to pick up men.
Kana-chan, want some?
Hey.
Where are you girls from?
Yes
From Sengawa.
What a coincidence.
I'm from Nerima.
Sengawa is very close by.
Who is this?
Yep, almost the same city.
He's sort of scary.
If you don't mind, want to AS with me?
What?
I'll show you the magnificence
of the Nerima Red Dragons.
Nerima daikon?
No!
Nerima Red Dragons, the Red Dragons.
How about it?
Of course.
I want to ride.
My name is Akagi Ryunosuke.
You are?
I don't really like AS's
And also people who are crazy about them.
No need to worry.
I'll teach you everything
if you know what I mean.
No thank you.
Wow, what a graceful way to get angry.
Commander...
It's time.
Understood.
Please excuse me.
Damn it, he pisses me off.
Why is it Kaname and not me?
I'm not going to get my revenge.
Why does it turn out like that?
Everyone seems down.
Did something happen?
Shut up!
Let us begin today's Chuuton festival's main event.
Various competitive games by the
troops of the Nerima training grounds.
Here they come.
Akagi!
We're going to win this year!
What are you joking about?
You guys are pathetic compared
to the Nerima Red Dragons.
Nerima daikon...
I won't forgive him.
We'll finish it in one blow.
Right grip, full power.
Right, full power.
Ready.
Go!
Wow, Nerima team is strong again this year.
More like Narashino is too weak?
I told you.
They are weak.
Damn, still weak?
Narashino is staying very close.
This year, it's down to the anchor.
Increase power.
We can't go any faster than this.
You are weak.
Take off the limiter.
Removing!
A strong hit.
Nerima wins again.
Nerima, you're dirty.
Kazama.
The opponent is a tandem.
They have a slight difference
in their synchronization.
That will be our chance.
We're on a tandem too.
Get ready for a smash.
Roger.
Sir, they're coming.
Their drive smash.
What?!
It's a feint.
Go forward.
Pathetic.
No!
Again!
Don't play so dirty.
It's over.
Everything.
Sir.
There's an unmarked AS approaching.
An AS with no name?
That's impossible.
This AS is going three time
faster than it's normal speed.
What?
Damn.
Wow!
Hey where did Sagara-kun go?
It can't be.
Listen to me Nerima Daikon.
It's Nerima Red Dragon!
This is supposed to be a friendly exhibition.
It's not war.
Stop using dirty tricks.
Step outside.
That was a graceful smash.
You, who are you?
I guess it doesn't matter
as long as you pilot an AS.
Fine!
I challenge you!
Sousuke!
What the heck are you doing?!
How did you find out my identity?
Only you would pull off something like THIS!
But since this is a friendly match, I
wanted to teach them about fair play.
Damn it!
I never should have come!
Give me back my fun time at the beach!
Here.
It must be hot in the GS.
That stands for Group Sounds.
That joke is so old.
Mizuki, what are you doing?
Stop messing with a kid like that...
And GS with me.
Although you're wearing a costume,
you must be really handsome inside.
Come on, take these off and show me your face.
You're being rude to the AS pilot.
Let's go!
Good luck.
Kana-chan.
So her name is Kaname.
It's so graceful.
Kaname-san.
Kaname-san!
According to the judges, the ping pong
match held earlier will be declared a
draw due to outside interferences.
Dad.
I didn't know a superb pilot
like you would be in Narashino.
I know it's sudden, but I
have a favor to ask of you.
So that's how it is.
We have nowhere to run.
Commander.
Kosuge, why are you hiding this from me?
You didn't tell me about
and awesome pilot like him.
I beg of you.
We have to win against Nerima.
Please take command of the forces.
What are you doing Dad?
Kazama.
Why do you lower yourself like that?
It's because you were no good at piloting
an AS, so you had to resort to this position.
That's all you could do right?
Is that true?
He has no sense of piloting whatsoever.
You know why I began to read AS-fan?
I wanted to make sure.
Is piloting an AS that hard?
Why can't my father do it?
I wanted you to pilot an AS.
I wanted to say my dad is an AS pilot.
Shinji.
I hate you Dad!
I'm sorry.
But...
You are forgetting something very important.
What?
On the battlefield, reinforcements
are very important, and necessary.
Without backup, the men in the front lines
cannot perform to their full potential.
The one, who commands those
reinforcements, is your father.
Well then...
Let's grate that piece of Nerima daikon.
Yeah!
Did you have a fight with your boyfriend?
He's not my boyfriend.
So I still have a chance.
Do you want to challenge him with me?
What?
By fighting him just once, I can already
tell that he is a very skillful AS pilot.
However, if I'm with you I won't lose.
I know I'll win.
I think this is a good time to AS with me.
What do you think?
Can you win?
Of course.
I've never made a lady feel regret.
Fine, I accept.
Thank you for your patience.
We will finally begin our
last event, the kiba-sen.
In this event, we will judge with special
standards, the winner of this event takes all.
Go! Go!
Where did everyone go?
Who knows.
Good luck, Mr. BS pilot.
I won't ask you anything about your background.
Let's do our best.
I thank you.
Since we put Kazama and his son
on one of the machines, we cannot
lose, or they will be blamed.
We must win.
Inexperienced moves by inexperienced pilots
can sometimes lead to astonishing results.
Let's go.
Why does it smell in here?
You won't be worrying about that soon.
Just like you do in P.E. class.
I'll follow you.
Don't touch me.
We are about to begin the kiba-sen.
It used to be like that.
But recently, things haven't
been going well for them.
The other day, they had an
argument like the one earlier.
And his son broke one of his precious models.
They're teamwork is horrible right now.
Teamwork is something that
is forged on the battlefield.
We won't know until we fight.
Ready?
Why am I
Dad.
I'll pilot.
What are you saying?
You can't possibly.
My friend told me to use this.
What are we going to do?
WHAT are we going to do?
It's simple.
Just throw out your punches
like you want to hit someone.
Fine.
Here we go.
Shinji!
Load.
Wow...
This AS is awesome.
They evaded.
It's fine.
You have a good feel for the AS.
One more time.
I do?
Alright then.
That commander AS.
He's not moving like usual.
Kaname-san, HE must be using that AS.
Ok.
Damn.
We can't take their commander AS lightly.
He is very skillful.
He is?
It seems his punch timings
are different from usual.
Troops C, troops D.
Cover the Kazama B team.
C team, acknowledged.
D team, acknowledged.
What are we going to do?
This is the point of our plans.
If we take out the head of the
dragon, we have a chance to win.
This is turning out to be
more exciting than I thought.
Acknowledged.
They're coming.
St...stop it!
Don't worry.
We're going to take their commander AS now.
What?
Team B, team C.
We're going to do the usual.
They're coming.
It's the Red Stream Attack.
What?
Using the AS's as a ramp?!
Down by low.
We lose to that every year.
Jumping all that weight.
Timing, jump ability, and guts
they have it all.
This feels great.
It'll feel even better when
you defeat the enemy.
Don't get close to me though.
Dad, the turning on the right side is slow.
I can't do anything about that.
Please fall back. We'll stop them here.
What are you saying?
I can't just leave you guys.
I'm always fighting, even if I'm not in an AS.
I'm still part of the team!
Narashino team is in a pinch!
Are the Red Dragons going to win as predicted?
Commander, I bid you good luck.
Please show them the spirit of our...
Shinji
I'm not very skilled.
I can't even fix models that well.
But...
I can't just retreat like this.
I know.
Will you fight together with me?
Yeah.
I will.
Ok.
We're going to win.
Message to the remaining fighters.
We're going to grate that
Nerima piece of daikon.
Dad!
Everyone forward.
Begin counterattack!
Yeah!
Shinji, ready the left counter.
Left counter, acknowledged.
What's going on?
I told you.
Teamwork is forged on teh battle field.
Hey, we're losing.
What's going on?
Narashino is coming back.
They're fighting back and getting even.
We're going to take their commander AS.
Everyone, ready?
Roger.
One more time, the radish jump?
It's the Red Stream Attack.
Here they come.
Our down by low won't make it in time.
We're not going to make it.
The 96's have a weak right joint.
Shinji, go for the right arm joint.
What?
Understood.
The arm came off.
What?!
Now!
Roger!
Go to hell!
We're going to win this year!
Game set!
Surprisingly, Narashino wins!
It's like a dream.
Thank you.
No...
You guys just performed at
your full potential, that's all.
Dad.
We did it.
We won.
Get away from me.
The match is over.
I don't want to admit it but
my immaturity made me blind.
You're annoying.
I found out today how important
my father's job really is.
Thanks Sagara-kun.
We were able to win because of you.
It wasn't because of me.
It was because of your father,
and the Narashino troops.
Me. BS pilot...
My...
Where are my summer memories?