Subtitles by Renatinha Tankinha
Ethan,
How do you know
that what you're saying is true?
You're asking me to
tell you what is real and what isn't?
I know what happened.
I know what my father did!
And I know what
you're trying to do!
Ethan, your disease has
altered your memory.
Unknowingly to you, of course.
But it's...it's there in
place to keep you happy.
That's bullshit!
You're using what condition
I had against me so no one will find out.
That is not true! We are here...Ethan...
Is my father in there?
Ethan, sit down.
-Dad?
-We have a situation.
Are you in there?
Huh?
Can you see me?
Can you see your son?
You promised me!
You promised!
Give me my life back!
Ethan?
Ethan...
OK...Ethan, Ethan!
Come on, say something.
Come on...
Who are you?
Let me help you up.
Easy. You can do it.
Easy...easy...careful, careful. Here.
He's experiencing temporary
memory loss.
He'll be OK.
You know, I've been
meaning to ask you something.
Was this ever about him?
Or was it always just about you?
Charles...
He's your son.
I'm well aware of that, Nick.
You did this to him, Charles.
This is serious,OK? This isn't a cold.
-He's going to be OK.
No, that's just storage.
Uh...your room's upstairs.
I'll show you.
These are all my things.
Yeah. Yeah, they are.
What else do you remember?
I don't know
if I can keep doing this.
Doing what?
Telling you how I feel.
Why?
Honestly, I still feel
uncomfortable calling you 'Dad'.
You're gonna be OK.
I think we're all gonna be OK.
We all just want you
to be happy and...
Please...
Hey, I just...you're here now...
This is your home.
I know it can't be
easy starting your life over.
New home, new wife, new kids.
You seem to be doing just fine
I need you to take
those twice a day.
You just got out of the hospital.
Doesn't come without
side effects.
What if I forget?
Don't.
Hey...Don't cry.
I remember everything.
But...I just can't feel it.
I know that doesn't make any sense.
But...
I mean, my head hurts sometimes
when I think about that stuff.
She smiles when she's
with you.
My sister.
She used to be that
way all the time.
You scared?
No.
You know I had
almost forgotten about it?
Sorry.
Call me when you get there.
-Mom, please.
You know you're my
best friend, right?
-I gotta go.
-OK.
I can't believe we're
not going to see him for seven months.
Why did you
go to the airport?
Why?
I was just curious. Jesus.
That picture.
I don't know who it is.
You?
No.
By the way,
mom wanted you to
have dinner with her tomorrow night.
Are you?
-I live there.
It's your turn to
deal with her shit.
Hey Ally.
Who's in the picture?
Why do you have
to do that?
What?
I hate it when you do this.
This is not exactly been easy.
Will you quit trying
to blame me?
Or Ally?
I don't.
I blame your father.
Oh, Jesus...
Can we have one dinner without
you digging his grave, too?
He did that himself.
You have no idea what it is like to
love someone for twenty years
And then watch them turn
and marry the next best thing.
It was his responsibility to help us
through everything and...
...and he let this family fall apart.
Let me tell you something, Ethan.
Look at me!
Love makes you blind.
Excuse me, miss.
Uh, you dropped this.
What are you doing?
I thought you were asleep.
Oh,
what do you possibly think you're
going to find here, Ethan, huh?
What happened to me?
We saved your life, Ethan.
I know you keep saying that, but
I really think I'm OK.
I just need to know.
Well, there are some
things I can't tell you.
Understanding it is with a
doctor-patient relationship.
What about a father-son relationship?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Don't come here ever again.
Are you sure it was her?
Yeah.
Well, what'd she say?
Didn't ask.
Why not?
Ally, I followed her.
-I never done that before.
-How do you know?
My memory's fine.
It's-it's not like I
don't remember stuff.
Like when I gave you that.
If you know something,
I wish you'd tell me.
I wish you didn't
believe I had something to hide.
OK.
Have you talked to Luke?
No.
I miss him.
I think I'm gonna go.
Ethan...
Our family...
You're the only one
who still wants it.
Let's not let that
get between us.
Shut up.
Seriously? Are you really
going to bring me here? Seriously?
Hi.
You're Camille, right?
What is it with you?
What do you mean?
You're stalking me.
I think you're giving yourself
too much credit.
No, I'm not.
OK.
Forget it.
Sit down, Ethan.
I was just kidding.
How'd you know my name?
Everyone knows your name.
Hey, Ethan. What a
pleasant surprise.
Hey, Miss Linda.
You got a minute?
Do you know Camille?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Do you remember this?
Look.
Who's that?
I don't remember that.
Ethan...
That...is your brother.
Adam.
My brother?
I don't remember that,
I don't have any memory.
Memory of that.
Do you have anything else
about that?
Ethan...
I'm sure it will come back to you.
Just give it some time.
I've been told that before.
Ethan.
Where is he?
Adam Galloway.
I'm here to see him.
I'm sorry, Ethan, you're not
authorized to go up there.
You know my name!
Everyone here knows your name.
You're Charles' son.
Would you  like me to call him for you?
Ethan, you can't go!
Ethan!
I know I have a brother!
Why didn't you tell me?
Where is he?
Ethan, Ethan...whoa.
Calm down, take a breath.
Take a breath.
Take a breath. OK.
Listen, listen...listen to me,
your brother...
Hey, your brother
Adam died.
Your brother's dead, Ethan.
Yeah. He killed himself
a little over a year ago.
Let's go.
It's going to be OK.
Yes.
It's going to be OK. Whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Ethan.
Ethan, you're alright.
Hey! Hey.
You're alright.
Say something.
Come on.
Why did she tell me that?
Who told you what?
Who?
Lucas' mom.
Why did she tell me?
-No, no. No. Ethan. You heard wrong.
You heard wrong.
No, you're alright.
Let's get you home.
I'm going to get you home, Ok?
Ok.
Come on, I got you.
I'm going to get you home.
You're gonna be alright.
You're alright.
What are those?
What are you doing here?
Your step-mom let me in.
-She did?
-Uh-hum
Excuse me.
Oh.
Sorry.
Please.
It's a little cleaner
than I remembered.
You've never been in
my room before.
Have you?
Uh...It's a little cleaner
than I would have thought.
What are you doing here?
Ok...
I...came to say I'm sorry.
About yesterday.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Ok.
So, you paint?
No.
Who did these?
You ask a lot of questions.
They're really beautiful, Ethan.
I mess around sometimes.
How come they don't have faces?
I can't do faces.
Have you ever read
the poem Bellustar?
I'm at the adapted play
tomorrow night.
You should come.
I believe you know where it is.
Right.
You know, you're supposed
to stand eight feet away.
Hmm.
So, there's a goddess in the poem
also faceless.
Laughing.
My first poem
you can't even see my face.
Anyway.
It's supposed to represent
the unknowable future.
And it's six feet.
Not eight.
No, it's...it's eight.
It's six.
No, it's eight.
You should come.
Say something.
Say something!
Mom.
What?
Mom, you need help.
No, I'm Ok.
Mom, please.
Ethan, give me some time.
I'll be alright.
I promise.
Don't promise.
If you don't mean it,
don't promise.
What makes you think
I'm not going to keep it?
Do you have any pictures of Adam?
What for?
Yes or no, please.
No, I don't.
Mom, don't lie to me.
I don't have any!
You need to help mom.
Why?
She hates me.
-'Cause she needs help.
-Don't we all?
Dad.
This is serious.
I am serious.
All she wants from me is money.
So don't stand there and tell me
about how much she needs help
It's a waste of time.
You were married to
her for twenty years.
And now we're divorced.
And it's about to
happen again.
Unbelievable.
Look around.
Like this little paradise
world you live in now?
Don't get too attached to it.
It will all be gone very soon.
What the hell does that even mean?
What does that mean?
Well,
it means that my good friend,
my former employee, rather,
Milo Sofley,
has filed a lawsuit against us.
Yeah...
I think you met him when
you left the hospital.
Dad?
What?
Can I live with
you from now on?
What's wrong with your mother?
Will you help her or not?
Can I take that thing
out of your lip?
I'll get my things tomorrow.
What's in this room?
I have no idea.
Yes, you do.
Ethan, what's wrong with you?
Do you keep secrets, Ally?
We all keep our secrets, Ethan.
Yeah.
Ethan?
What's wrong?
Why was I in the hospital?
-You were sick.
-I'm serious.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I promise.
I would tell you.
I think the answer's in there.
It's a storage room, Ethan.
There are secrets.
There are secrets in there.
Have you been taking
your medicine?
No.
I think you should.
Dad said he'd help her.
That's good.
Are you OK?
Is this a dream?
No.
It's something else.
You gotta feel in dreams.
You can only imagine.
Can you feel me?
This is not you.
This is you.
I can feel you.
Hold on.
I'm glad you made it.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
No problem.
What did you think?
It was interesting.
Yes, it is.
And what are you doing now?
I don't know. I hadn't
really thought about it. Why?
Are you sure you want to know?
Ok, I'll tell you.
We're having a party.
I took the key from
the hotel I work at.
Isn't that illegal?
No it's fine, they won't
even know we're there.
Ethan,
come on, we're leaving.
You should go.
Come on.
It'll be fun.
Hey, everybody.
Ethan?
Are you Ok?
Yeah,
I'm fine.
I've discovered something
about you, Ethan.
You are a compulsive liar.
You should smile more often.
What?
What's so funny?
You're not the first
person who's told me that.
Well, if I may plead
my case, Mr. Ethan.
A life...
is not worth living if...
you don't...
have something to smile about.
Well, you might not be
yourself, then.
Well, actually, I am a
figment of your imagination.
Really?
That's interesting.
I would think if I...
made up, then,
you'd be taller.
with a short skirt.
It's a shame I'm real.
No, it's not.
Hey. What's up?
Wake up!
Where are all the
boxes that were in that room?
I moved them.
Where?
There's something wrong
with me.
Why do you think that is?
You stopped taking your pills.
Look at me.
What?
These are important.
I forgot!
You can forget a
lot of things, Ethan.
but don't forget these.
Since when do
you really care?
Ethan, stop, you're
still my son. I'm still-
This is not about
these fucking pills!
You know something!
And you've gone to
extensive links to make
sure that I don't
find out about it.
I can't take it anymore!
You told everyone I know
never to speak about Adam?
I...I know this has
something to do with
the fact that I was
in the hospital.
And you're the only
one who can tell me about that.
Aren't you?
They day your brother...
...killed himself,
something happened
to you, as well.
Something?
You're a fucking neurosurgeon,
something doesn't cut it.
If you want me to tell you, I
would suggest you lower your voice.
Sit down.
When you saw him,
when you Saw Adam,
an artery ruptured in your brain.
And the lack of oxygen damaged
some areas that are necessary
for you to properly recall your memories.
You blocked out your
brother and everything
having to do with him.
So in essence you forgot.
I need you to know
that I was trying to help you, Ethan.
I thought it was best if
those things stayed forgotten.
and I tried to keep
it that way.
Ethan.
You blamed yourself
for what happened.
Do you know
what predetermination is?
Like fate?
No.
What do you mean?
There's a difference.
If you believe in fate, then
all the choices you make
both right and wrong,
are not yours.
You think that they are, but...
they happen that way
because they have to.
Love?
What do you believe?
I'd like to believe I'm
in control of my own life.
Although lately it
doesn't feel that way.
There are things in place.
But it's my decision...
to be here.
That's predetermination.
Ethan...
look at me.
I don't...
know why you...
worry about these things
you can't control.
Like...
your past,
your family,
your friends.
Thank you.
I like it.
I'm so sorry.
No.
Ally, Ally, whoa
whoa. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Let's go back.
-Alisson!
-Just leave me alone!
Do you need help?
Promise me
Ok.
I promise.
I promise, baby.
I'll see you in rehab.
Come on.
I love you.
Excuse me!
Um, will you take
our picture?
Say I'm beautiful.
I love fireworks.
My body. It hurts.
What are you doing here?
Can you...take a
look at something for us?
I was hoping you might
be able to tell me where you got it.
This isn't my room.
They're not in the right place.
Hello, Ethan.
How'd you know my name?
Everyone knows your name.
Who are you?
My name is Dr. Milo Sofley
I used to work with your father.
I'm filing a lawsuit against him.
I'm assuming he hasn't
told you why.
No.
What would you say
if I told you I knew
what was happening to you?
People cope with traumatic
events differently.
Some are worse than others.
What happened to her?
This isn't about her, Ethan.
This is about you.
How much do you know?
I know this is where
my dad works.
We're nowhere near
your father now, Ethan.
Or anyone else.
We're in a room
in my house.
Then what's happening to me?
Why am I seeing
what I'm seeing?
You are something, Ethan.
You really are.
And I think it's
very admirable of you.
Trying to find yourself
in such a way.
Ethan, you're asking
the wrong questions.
You saw the x-rays.
What'd you think
that was?
I don't know.
It's a microcomputer.
A silicon hippo campus chip.
We all have memories
which we prefer to forget.
Your father never told
you what he was doing
because he wasn't sure
that it would work.
To be honest, I think
you were in no position to argue with him.
The next thing you
knew, you awoke in a hospital,
unaware of any pf this.
Ethan, ever since
your surgery,
You've been combining your
past and your present,
to create your own happiness.
Your condition, Ethan,
causes you to think your dreams
are real life.
It stopped working?
Because I remembered
my brother.
No, Ethan.
You don't have
a brother.
It was you.
I need you to come
back to the real world, Ethan.
I need you to trust me.
This is your house.
Yes, it's...
...where we've
been the whole time.
Do you understand everything
that I'm telling you, Ethan?
This chip works as
an artificial part of your brain
Because it was damaged,
everything that you now remember
is directly connected to
the hippo campus chip.
You are dependent on it
For normal functioning.
I don't know what to believe.
Why are you helping me?
Ethan!
-Ethan!
-What?
What do you want
from me?
We have a case, Ethan!
You can't fight back!
Here.
I know everything.
Ethan...
It's over.
Ethan, I'm...
really not in the mood
right now,
can we just...
-I don't care!
I have something to say.
And you're gonna listen.
Let go of my hand.
Why?
Let go of my hand!
Why should I listen to
anything you have to say?
I haven't been in control
of my life in a long time,
and I have you to
thank for that.
This is ridic-
it's late!
Get out of my room.
I wanted to let
you know it's not working.
It stopped working.
Ethan...
-I don't think you
understand this...
-I had a talk with Milo
Sofley this afternoon...
Do you know him?
Don't you?
What did he tell you?
I know what you did.
I know everything.
I gave you...
a chance to s...
-No!
What you gave me was...
a life that wasn't my own!
I don't want that!
You've insulted me.
I want you to take it out.
-Well, I don't think you...
-if there's one thing...
I will ever ask of you,
This is it.
I'm not broken.
You cannot fix
whatever it is you think
is wrong with me,
I am who I am.
Ethan...
This chip is a major
part of your cognitive functioning.
If I remove it,
it'll be as if we never
had this conversation.
You will not remember
any of this.
-You don't know that.
-Yes, I do!
It is your hippo campus. It tells
your memories where to go
and how they will be remembered
Without it...
Ethan...
Please, please, please,
for the love of God.
Do not make this decision.
Despite me.
I've been there before.
Haven't I?
If I don't remember
any of this, then that's my decision.
Ethan, please, please, please.
If you won't do it,
I'll call Milo.
Ok.
I'll do it.
Do you remember what
you said when you gave this to me?
No.
You said that it reminded
you of me.
Because I was always happy.
And now the blue
bird reminds me of you.
Wish I had...
more things that I could
remember that were happier.
Truthfully you've been upset
for so long, I can't remember
a time when we were happy.
But that's why we're here.
I felt angry...
when you drank,
but I still love you.
I felt hurt...
and lonely...
when you tried to h-
when you tried to hurt yourself.
But I still love you.
I felt upset,
I felt ashamed,
when Ally told me
how she found you,
But I still love you.
I hate it when you lie.
But I st...
I still love you.
Lucas!
Baby, I'm so glad
you're home!
It's good to be home.
I missed you so much.
It's good to see you.
Hey man, welcome home.
Ah, thanks!
It's good to see you, man.
It's good to be home.
I'm glad you're back.
-Yeah, me, too.
Thanks.
Let's go back
inside, alright?
You coming?
I think I'm going to stay
out here for a little while.
Can you see me?
Can you see your son?
You promised me!
You promised!
Milo, tell him what happened.
Ethan, please, please.
Just calm down.
Truth...
is in fact the most
important piece of information
in any event with such
discrepancies
as the ones we've
been faced with here.
The brain is the most powerful...
and fragile part of the human body.
But in this case,
it's the object in question.
Mr. Ethan Galloway will
further undergo a
series of BCI tests,
which record the exact radioactivity
that his brain emits.
This tests do not confabulate.
And they will be done
before and after
the removal of the
hippo campus chip.
He's the son of Charles Galloway
whose wishes will be granted.
No matter how serious
the consequences.
This is it.
You have to be sure
that this is really what you want
before you take this pill.
After this,
there's no turning back.
Ethan!
You know I won't
remember any of this.
Yes you will.