Hold on a sec.
Let me call for backup.
This is car 46044
requesting a backup. pier 14.
[ Grunts ]
- [ Gunshot ]
- Let him go, Cordell!
Teresa get these cuffs off.
[ Teresa ]
The keys.
- [ Shotgun cocks ]
- [ Officer ]
Hold it there!
[ Sirens Wailing ]
[ Yelling ]
[ children ]
? Brass button, blue coat ?
? Cannot catch a nanny goat ??
[ Laughing ]
[ Engine Starts Revs ]
[ Man ]
And what can l do for you?
[ Shotgun cocks ]
Figure it out.
l got not money.
lt all goes down
that slot into a safe.
l don't know
the combination.
[ Chuckles ]
The boss don't trust me.
[ Female Dispatcher ]
in the 22 precinct
we got a 1 0-30 in progress.
Silent alarm at Julio's Bodega
at 725 14th Street.
This one's for us.
Shit.
22-Adam responding.
[ Siren Blaring ]
l need the money.
Look. No money.
Take merchandise.
Anything you want in the store.
- io, Dios mio!
- That's gonna be you
all over the walls in a minute.
So, when does your boss come in
to open up the safe, huh?
Uh 6-
6:30.
l'll wait.
okay.
But you don't have to hang around.
Why don't you try running
for the door, huh?
No. No it's- it's okay. l-l stay.
Hey. Hey.
Let's open up
some Lotto tickets, huh?
Sure. Sure. See? Okay.
- Maybe i'll be a winner.
- Okay.
l feel lucky!
Nada. Mira. Nothing.
Keep going.
Okay.
Nothing again.
We'll go through
the whole bunch, huh?
Okay. Nothing.
Nada.
l think you're lying!
No. l'm calling them
the way they're coming up.
Nothing. Nada.
No l think i'm a winner.
l'm telling you.
N- Holy shit.
iAy, Dios mio!
Mira. 54000 bucks.
54000 bucks.
You won 5,000 bucks.
Thank God you got here.
[ Laughing ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
can you believe it?
The fucker just won 5,000 bucks.
l mean, l guess he don't win it.
l guess l win it, eh?
[ Laughing ]
Like they say eh?
Goodness is its own reward, eh?
[ Whimpers ]
No.
[ Sirens Blaring ]
What for?
[ Footsteps Departing ]
Hey! Hold it right there!
Drop it!
Now! put the gun down!
lt wasn't me man.
- [ Shotgun cocks ]
- [ Whimpering ]
- put it down, man!
- lt was one of you!
Hey call an ambulance
will you?
Get a broom.
Look at this.
[ Police Radio chatter ]
Hey Frankie, get on the horn.
come on.
He blew the clerk away too.
[ Female Dispatcher ]
41 94 your request for backup
is confirmed. Over.
[ Bells Chiming ]
[ Horns Honking ]
Well, officer Forrest
officer Mallory-
[ Grunts ]
you've been cleared
of all wrongdoing.
ln fact you're gonna get commendations
for your actions.
So, uh does that mean
we're back on active duty again?
Not just yet.
commissioner um
what about Cordell?
What about Cordell?
[ Teresa ]
You didn't find the body in the river
because it wasn't there.
current must have
swept it out to sea.
No. He's still alive.
You're starting with these
ghost stories again?
cordell died in Sing Sing
more than two years ago.
l want you to see
this police psychologist.
- What?
- Her name is Susan Riley.
She's got an excellent rep
at helping officers readjust.
Aw, come on commissioner
we're not crazy.
Of course not.
So you shouldn't have any objections
seeing Officer Riley.
She's a cop too.
l set up a meeting
for tomorrow at 3:00.
Be there.
We've got
a 3:00 appointment-
[ Door Opens ]
Um officers
Mallory and Forrest.
We're a little early, l guess.
That's right. Um why don't
we go get a cup of coffee.
Are you gonna find us unfit
to go back on the job?
Well, l hope not.
What do you think?
Well i think we're both
just as sane as you are.
Well, then you both realize
that this Matt cordell
was killed in prison.
Yeah, right but you see
we both just saw him on the pier.
So, what? Does that make us nuts?
What you saw
was a very large man
with a horribly disfigured face.
- Did he say he was Cordell?
- No. He never spoke.
Well then it could have been anyone
in a policeman's uniform, right?
A homicidal maniac
with a grudge against
the police force maybe.
- Hey look, if this is the official line
that the department's gonna use great.
- No, that's a lie.
Would you excuse us for a second?
certainly.
Teresa all l know about
is being a cop.
l don't know about you
but i need this job.
When you think about it, l mean-
What the hell difference
does it make who he was?
Because you can't kill the dead.
Tere- Let her go.
[ Sighs ]
Doc do me a favor will you?
Don't put that in your report.
Jack l'm afraid i'm gonna have
to give her a negative evaluation.
Let me at least just talk to her will you?
She'll come around.
l cannot let anyone out on the street
that's got a gun with emotional problems.
[ Man Yells ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Gunshot ]
McKinney!
You okay?
Never better.
We were covering the front.
That's why l came around back.
[ Man Groaning ]
Too bad you didn't kill him.
Yeah. Too much fucking paperwork.
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Knocking ]
[ Susan ]
Come in.
Hi.
Lieutenant McKinney?
Yeah.
come on in.
Have a seat.
Thought there'd be a couch.
Just a chair.
Yeah.
So how you doing?
Not bad.
l haven't been to confession
in over 20 years.
But if the priests looked like you
l probably would have gone
more often.
- You mind if i smoke?
- Actually, i do.
Thank you.
So, do you wanna tell me
about the shooting?
Uh-
Well, what's there to say?
l mean, l shot him before he shot me.
Look Doctor,
let's make this easy.
l feel great about what l did.
lf you wanna psychoanalyze someone
why don't you psychoanalyze
the lawyers and judges...
who put that kind of scum
back on the streets?
First of all, I'm not a doctor.
l'm a clinical psychologist.
And l realize you're here under protest.
Well, that's good.
So you can tell me how long
my ass has to warm this chair...
before l satisfy
the mandatory requirements.
Well, every officer
involved in a shooting has to see
one of us for counseling at least once.
okay. l've been seen.
You counseled me. Thank you.
Excuse me, Lieutenant.
Did you have a partner?
Sergeant Joseph Minelli?
Yeah. Joe and l were a team.
He made an appointment
with me once
about six months ago.
He phoned and requested help.
That's a little unusual, isn't it?
One of you asking for help?
[ Sniffs ]
Well, he was a...
sensitive guy.
l never found that out.
He stood me up, never showed.
lt was a Friday.
The following night he committed suicide
with his service revolver.
l know all about that.
l found the body Monday morning.
i didn't know that.
Well there's a lot of things
you people don't know.
Well someone talked him
out of showing up here.
probably told him he'd be a wimp
if he admitted something
was bothering him.
- What are you getting at?
- You tell me.
[ Scoffs ]
Please don't slam the-
[ Door Slams ]
Hey, Harry.
Oh, Officer Forrest.
How you doing tonight?
lt's you.
They tell me you got
your picture in the paper.
l guess congratulations
are in order.
That's not such a bad picture.
l'll tell you what, Harry.
l'll take a dozen of 'em.
A dozen it is.
How often do l get
a celebrity around here?
[ Chuckles ]
okay, Harry give me your hand.
Okay, look, this is a five, okay?
You trust me?
l trust you.
- All right. You keep the change.
- Thank you. Thank you. All right.
[ Blade Unsheathes ]
okay, let's see
what they said about Terese.
- [ Stabs ]
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Gasping ]
- Jack! What's going on?
What's happening? Jack.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
police! Police! police!
Strangled like the rest.
All strippers.
Sure picks the pretty ones.
Lovejoy, you look sick.
Well l hate being around stiffs
ever since they made me kiss
my grandmother at the funeral.
Remove the sheet.
could you do it, please?
[ Sobs ]
[ Groans ]
[ Sobbing ]
Do you have any idea what the family
wants done with the body?
l'll call his mother in Florida.
[ Sniffling ]
Teresa can you think of anyone
with a motive to kill Jack?
You were at the lounge
in headquarters.
You had an argument.
You got angry. You walked out.
Where did you go?
[ Sniffles ]
Home.
You didn't wait outside the building
and try to make up with him?
l'd have no reason to kill him.
l loved him.
Well maybe you loved him
too much. Huh?
Maybe you- Maybe he thought
you were crackin' up.
He didn't wanna marry you
and you got angry.
[ Sniffles ]
This is bullshit!
Why don't you ask Commissioner Doyle
who killed Jack?
Look, l'm just
following procedure.
You know as well as l4
nine out of 1 0 times...
the prime suspects
are usually family, relatives or friends.
- That's where you find the killer.
- You bastards.
[ Teresa ]
Why don't you ask Commissioner Doyle
who kiiled Jack?
l don't like what you're asking me
to do to Officer Mallory.
You know as weil as-
We're just doing it
for the good of the department.
We don't even consider her a suspect.
lt's just our way of putting her
on the defensive for a while,
keep her under control
so she doesn't go to the papers.
My time would be better spent
finding out who killed Jack.
Your time, Detective,
is to put more pressure on her!
That's a direct order.
[ Door Opens Closes ]
Damn it.
l don't like it either.
You should talk.
Your report described her
as mentally unsound and unfit for duty.
How am i supposed to really judge her?
She's out there on the streets being a cop.
l sit behind my desk
like a social worker.
l just don't like people who try
and get inside other people's heads.
Yeah, you made that very clear to me
in my office yesterday.
ls there
any particular reason?
My wife was under the care
of a psychiatrist for over a year.
You know standard problems, cop's wife.
oh, l admit
l'm not the easiest guy to live with.
But she couldn't make a move without him.
Stopped communicating with me, only him.
Now she's my ex-wife.
ls that reason enough for you?
l'm sure the doctor was just doing
what he thought was best.
[ Sighs ]
l don't buy into this psychology stuff.
l think you're all full of shit.
So you can take
your carl Jung and Sigmund Freud
and shove em up your ass.
[ Sighs ]
And just to clear up matters-
l talked Joe Minelli into canceling
that appointment with you,
and l don't feel guilty about it.
How could you feel guilty?
You're a cop.
So are you.
[ Metal Clanking ]
Hey stop! Don't do it!
oh, for God sakes
you already did it!
Hey hey, hey hey! Come on.
can't we talk about this?
l'll move the car.
l was just coming back to move the car.
i got here first.
Yeah, but l'm here. l'm right here.
You can't tow me away.
Read the back of your summons.
Hey look, you're all alone.
can't we work this out
just between you and me, huh?
What?
You're offering me a bribe?
Not at all.
But if you tow my car
l won't be able to get to work tomorrow.
l'll lose a whole day.
You can afford it.
You enjoy this.
You son of a bitch.
You got a shitty nothing civil service job-
Oh, careful of my fender with that.
This is a new paint job.
l just had the whole thing waxed.
You'll be towing fucking cars
the rest of your life.
You know that?
You'll never be anything.
You can't even do this stupid job right.
l'd like to see
the piece of shit you drive.
You better start thinking about
getting out to Brooklyn early tomorrow
to reclaim this beauty.
A lot of cars
get stripped in our lot.
Stereo, the tires
the whole engine.
That's why i wouldn't own
a car in this town.
[ Chain Rattling ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Whirring Stops ]
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Man ]
Good night, Harry.
[ Harry ]
Good night.
Happy holiday.
- Here you go Harry. Good night.
- Excuse me.
Hi. l'd like to talk to you.
Do l know you?
l'm from the police department.
l talked to the cops
already enough.
l'm not an investigator like the others.
l'm a psychologist.
- l'm trying to do a profile on this killer.
- l've got nothing to say.
l'm trying to make a living.
Maybe you could tell from his footsteps
is he a large man...
or perhaps he said something.
No footsteps.
l just heard Jack screaming and-
That's all.
Did you touch him?
Not the victim, the killer.
Why did you ask me that?
You did4 didn't you? Tell me.
l lost my sight in combat in Sicily.
A German grenade
went off in my face.
Killed all the others
in the foxhole around me.
l lay there more than a day
surrounded by these dead bodies
buried in them.
At night they froze.
Them being on top of me
kept me from freezing too.
l never thought
l'd feel anything like that again.
Frozen dead flesh.
Then l touched his hand.
Just for a second, mind you
and i was back there again...
with the dead.
ow!
You killed him
you son of a bitch!
ow! Take it easy!
Look if he wanted
to tow my car, so what?
You don't kill anybody
over bullshit like that!
Well if you didn't kill him
who the fuck did?
You wouldn't believe me.
Why don't you try me, punk?
All right. All right!
lt was a great big cop.
Six foot three, maybe more
all scarred up.
And he never said a word.
You know something?
Ow!
l don't believe you!
Get the fuck out of here!
[ McKinney ]
Take a look at these reports.
lt's happening again.
l got on this job two weeks ago.
Give me a break.
l'm talking about a man
who killed your predecessor.
A man who may try to pull
the same number on you.
Then the wrong guy
died in that truck in the river?
When this leaks out
people are not gonna want
to pick up the phone and dial 91 1 .
They're gonna want
to defend themselves.
We're looking at a bloodbath here.
citizens blowing each other away
like there isn't any law.
Tell me the truth.
Do you think it's a cop?
Some officer
that's gone off the deep end?
Doesn't fit the description
of any cop I know.
Six three feet,
scars all over him.
Except one.
[ Doyle ]
Don't say it.
Don't even think it.
- What are you talking about?
- Nothing. Nothing.
We've got
to get this killer.
Better assemble a new task force.
Get some aid
from the governor.
Well, l got a lead.
This policewoman Teresa Mallory.
Mallory?
Oh, my God. Not her again.
Yeah, her.
Killed the boyfriend.
l figure he's gonna go after her.
l don't get it.
He's had a lot of opportunities to kill her.
Why hasn't he killed her?
Maybe he enjoys making her afraid.
l'm beginning to think
maybe you're not so crazy.
Great. Then you'll be out of a job too.
They've asked me to certify you unfit
but l can't do it.
l read all about cordell
and what happened to him.
Look if you want more information
just tune in to Criminals atLarge
television show tonight.
- Why would you go on that show?
- Why not?
They alert the public to wanted criminals.
A half dozen or so have been caught
or turned in as a direct result.
And who's gonna believe you
the lunatic fringe?
- Will you come with me?
- l can't.
- What are you gonna say?
- [ Horn Honking ]
There's my cab.
[ Sighs ]
All right, l'll go with you.
l'll even pay for the cab.
oh, where to, girls?
Mayflower Hotel.
Sounds good to me.
l just jumped out
to get a pack of smokes.
l hope you girls
weren't waiting in the cold too long.
No it's okay.
When l saw the bag l said
"'This is a run to the airport."
[ Chuckles ]
Guess you can't
win 'em all.
l don't see anyone following us, Teresa.
Some ex-boyfriend
giving you a hard time?
Yeah sort of.
The shows are gonna
be letting out now.
Um, maybe l can beat
the crosstown traffic
if l cut down this way.
No no!
Stay on the busy streets.
Hey what's going on here?
You ever seen one of these?
Yeah, l seen plenty of them.
And it usually means
l ain't gettin a tip.
[ Thumping ]
Damn.
- What's the matter?
- l don't know.
l think one of my tires
is going flat.
Driver, just stay in the car.
Don't get out.
You kidding?
Drive.
On my rim?
Teresa take it easy.
Anybody can get a flat tire.
Look, cop or no cop
l own this cab.
l'm not gonna fuck it up
for anybody.
Holy shit.
You're making it worse than it has to be.
Nobody's following us.
Just stay in the cab.
When you left your cab
to go for cigarettes, somebody must...
have messed with your tires.
Damn kids, l'll bet.
[ Tires Squeal ]
Where the hell you goin?
Teresa stop it.
What are you doing?
l knew it. l never should
have let cops in my cab.
- What's he want?
- l don't know.
Keep down!
Teresa!
Shit!
Shit.
Goddamn it!
Jesus Christ!
Teresa!
[ Screaming ]
No! No please!
No!
No! No!
[ Susan Whimpering ]
No!
[ Screaming ]
[ Groans ]
[ Screams ]
[ chain Saw Whirring ]
[ Screaming ]
No!
[ Bones crack ]
[ Screaming ]
No!
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Screams ]
[ Steam Hissing ]
[ Footsteps ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Man ]
Are you all right in there?
Hey who handcuffed you, lady?
What the hell
is going on?
All right,
easy does it.
We'll get you out of there.
Radio in for a hacksaw up here!
We got to get
these cuffs off of her!
All right,
just take it easy.
We're gonna get you
out of there. Relax.
You better lie still.
Your wrist is broken.
Better fix me up quickly.
l gotta be on TV in a few hours.
l'm Detective McKinney.
l'm gonna ride inside.
You okay?
l was on my way to Teresa's apartment
when the report came over the radio.
l guess you don't have to worry
about her doing any more talking.
[ Sighs ]
l'm not feeling too great about all this.
l doubted her in the beginning too.
But l saw him.
l saw what he did.
What'd you see?
Big guy in a bulletproof vest
dressed up like a cop?
Sean, l saw Matt Cordell.
[ Male Host ]
Tonight, Criminals at Large
goes after a serial killer...
who's claimed the lives
of beautiful young girls...
working as exotic dancers and strippers
in New York City.
And you the audience
may help us to catch him.
[ Man ]
Welcome to Ciub 694
here in the heart of Times Square.
I'm your emcee.
[ Host On TV ]
Tonight you'll meet detectives
assigned to this case.
But first l wouId like you to meet
Deputy Commissioner Edward Doyle
of the N.Y.p.D.
- [ Female Bartender ]
Do you want another drink?
- Yeah.
[ Host ]
Just what has your department done
about this case so far?
We've contacted and alerted
young women...
who seem to be
the killer's prime target group.
We have a special late guest here.
Actually, she's one of your lady cops.
She's also a police psychologist,
and her name is Officer Susan Riley.
Susan, welcome to the show.
Thank you.
Mr. Brady, the murders
of these exotic dancers
is a very tragic situation.
Now, my concern
is another series of killings
going on that's being covered up.
pardon me.
Mr. Brady, this is utterly nonsense.
The so-called "'maniac cop"
did not drown in the river, as reported.
Well commissioner what-
what do you have to say about this?
Well the homicides
that Officer Riley is talking about...
were deliberately set up
to imitate the earlier killings.
Then tell me something
commissioner.
Why is this being kept
from the public and the press? Hmm?
The killer craves publicity.
We're denying him that.
We hope that his behavior
will become foolhardy...
and he'll expose himself
show himself.
Then we expect to nail him.
Mr. commissioner why don't
you just admit that Matt Cordell
is responsible for these killings?
cordell died in prison.
[ Susan ]
He was brain-dead but still breathing
when his body was released.
He recovered and came back
to avenge himself...
upon the police department
and the city officials who railroaded him
into jail in the first place.
You know how many people
have been murdered already?
And yet their replacements
stilI insist upon hiding the facts.
The commissioner's trying-
[ Brady ]
We're running out of time here.
I'm gonna have to cut you off.
And, punk,
if you happen to be out there Iistening,
I just want you to remember this.
When it comes time
for your execution,
you can't con Con Edison.
Good night.
officer Riley.
[ Sighs ]
That was a pretty stupid thing
you did up there, young lady.
l'm gonna see
that you're suspended.
Teresa Mallory's dead
because she knew the truth.
Let me tell you something Commissioner.
cordell's gonna pay you a visit
and you'll see him.
Just like l did.
[ Emcee ]
Oh boys, look at this blondie here.
Isn't she beautiful?
Take 'em out, biondie.
Take em out. Let 'em breathe.
oh boy! Aren't they lovely?
Ooh, baby!
And on the other side, there's Red.
Take 'em out, Red.
Let 'em breathe too.
And be generous, boys
with that cash,
because these giris
are dancing here just for you.
Let's have a round of applause
for these two lovely young ladies.
And don't forget.
They'Il be back later, boys.
We're open 24 hours.
Don't go nowhere. Hang around.
[ patrons Whistling ]
And now for the first time on any stage,
the lovely CheryI!
?? [ Rock ]
Let's have a big round of applause, boys.
Come on.
Let's hear it for CheryI.
She's making her debut here
in the big city at club 69.
lsn't she lovely?
No one has ever had this girl
on the stage before.
We always are the first ones
with the best talent in New York.
So just keep your eyes on Cheryl.
Oh, boys, tell me.
Isn't she lovely?
Just keep your eyes on her.
You'lI definitely get an eyefuI.
Oh! God4 isn't she gorgeous boys?
Be generous. Spread out that cash.
?? [ Continues ]
[ Man ]
? Yeah, yeah, tonight ?
? l won't be coming home ?
? I'ii be running
with the children tonight ?
? Tonight ?
[ Female Backup Singers ]
? ChiIdren of the night ?
[ Man ]
? Yeah ?
? I hear them coming ?
? ChiIdren of the night ?
? I hear them coming
Hear them coming ?
?? [ Continues ]
? l'm making some new friends ?
? You never know
what the first night means ?
? We'll start us a new trend ?
?? [ Continues ]
[ Whistling Applauding ]
? Tonight ?
? l won't be coming home ??
[ Woman ]
Yes, Mom
there's plenty of room for advancement.
Are you eating weIl?
Yes, l'm getting plenty to eat.
They have an employee cafeteria.
[ people Shouting ]
Where are you living?
Well, um,
l'm sharing this lovely apartment
with um, a few of the girls
from the secretarial pool.
Are they nice girls?
Yeah, they're really sweet.
Make sure you call us
when you can.
Okay.
Well then, as soon as i get my phone
l'll give you a call and give you the number.
And your address
so we can write to you.
[ Horn Honking ]
All right. Okay.
But in the meantime, please
just don't worry about me.
l'm fine.
i Iove you sweetheart.
Take care of yourself.
okay.
Oh, and give my love to Dad.
i wili sweetheart.
All right.
i iove you.
l love you too.
Bye.
[ Line clicks ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
[ Sirens Blaring ]
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Door Closes ]
of course my typing's
getting better, Mom.
[ Knocking ]
[ Sighs ]
Who is it?
[ Rattling, Thumping ]
[ Shrieks, Gasps ]
- [ Man ] Desk.
- This is 404.
Someone is trying
to break into my room.
l'm telling you
there is somebody out there.
- He'li go away.
- No. please, call the police.
- please get me some help.
- We don't want any trouble.
call them!
Or give me a line out,
and i'll call them myself.
Have it your way.
But if l was in your line of work-
[ Hangs Up Phone ]
[ Baby crying in Distance ]
l called the cops.
They're coming
so you better get out of here.
- [ Shouts ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Shouting ]
Whoo! i feel like
John fucking Wayne! Whoo!
[ Grunts ]
Now, you got to listen to me.
Listen to me!
Now, l've been watching you,
and i say you're asking for it. Right?
Tell me! come on!
The police are coming.
- l don't care about no police.
This ain't gonna take long.
- What are you gonna do?
Think about it.
What do you think l'm gonna do?
come on.
What do you think?
You killed those other girls.
No. Let's just say...
that l need
another 8x1 0 glossy
for my collection.
- [ Shrieks ]
- [ Chuckling ]
oh, trying to do some dirt
to me huh baby?
[ Shrieking ]
l love the way you feel.
[ Grunts ]
Oh, yeah. Ah.
You got to be proud4
because you're the prettiest one
in my collection so far. You are.
And the best dancer clear out.
You could be in a Broadway show.
But no you've got to be up there
on that stage dancing like some whore!
You never know what type of person's
gonna walk in, now, do ya?
Do ya honey?
[ phone Rings ]
[ Crying ]
That's them in the lobby.
They're comin' up to get you.
lt's a slow elevator.
[ phone Rings ]
This ain't gonna take a minute.
[ Gasping ]
[ Screams ]
[ Both Gasp ]
[ Screaming ]
Hold it! police!
- [ Shouts ]
- [ Screaming ]
Don't hurt me.
[ Sobbing ]
[ Sirens Wailing ln Distance ]
oh, you ain't no cop man.
l know who you are.
Damn, she was talkin'
about you on TV.
You was in the headlines
last month and everything.
See you're front page stuff.
But me, l'm back on page five.
You know why?
You know what did it for you?
That uniform.
See that was a gimmick.
See, that's what got their attention.
l got a real nice apartment.
l mean, it's quiet.
Nobody ever comes down there.
private you know?
Uh, you could come there.
l mean, l ain't queer or nothing.
See but-but you'd be safe there.
And i've got a collection
to show you.
The city at night.
That's where and when
l do my work.
You know
l feel like l'm a crusader...
against the whores of the world.
[ Chuckles ]
That's me.
Turkell, crusader of the night.
[ Cackles ]
You don't talk much
but that's okay.
Was it the accident the same one
that screwed your face up?
l didn't mean
to offend you now.
l'm sorry if l did.
This- This here's my place.
Home sweet home.
These are my girls.
They ain't gonna dance
in front of nobody no more.
Now they're Turkell's girls.
Uh my first name is Steven.
Why don't you go ahead
and sit down?
You know most of the time
l just talk to myself anyway.
So- So it's okay.
l mean,
l don't hear voices or nothing.
l'm not like those guys
that hear angels and devils
tellin 'em what to do.
You see,
l know what to do.
Here, we'll have a drink.
You hate cops.
So you made
a fuckin' mockery out of 'em.
l mean, for a while,
everybody was scared shit...
to walk up to a cop
in this here town.
And that was 'cause of you.
You know i-i never thought, really
that i'd meet you.
or that-
Or that w-we'd become friends.
All right. All right.
Why should you trust me?
l got to earn it.
l got to make you respect me.
But l-l think maybe you see
the possibilities in me, huh?
can you write?
l mean, c-can you
write down your name?
See4 that way,
l'll know what to call you.
l'll go get a pencil and paper.
[ Straining ]
cordell.
[ Sighs ]
That's the name she said on TV.
[ Laughing ]
So, how'd you like me
on TV?
l loved you.
The mayor loved you
and the city council
was nuts about you.
Here.
check out your reviews.
The whole city's freaked
over this maniac cop.
Guess l really
started something, huh?
Maybe i should just go home
and wait for the ax to fall.
No chance.
So you mean
l can4t do any more guest shots?
No.
You think there's any reason
why Cordell would want
to come back and get me?
[ Clicks Teeth ]
l don't know.
But let me tell you.
lf he doesn't shoot you,
the commissioner himself might kill you.
- What?
- This4 uh, stupid rhyme
keeps going through my head.
We used to say it
when we were kids in Brooklyn.
l mean, it's just nonsense
but l-l can't get it out of my mind.
lt goes, uh
"'One bright day
in the middle of the night,
two dead boys
got up to fight.
Back to back
they faced each other.
With their knives
they shot each other.
A deaf policeman heard the noise
and came and killed
the two dead boys."
You know that?
Yeah, l remember that
when l was a kid.
"'Two Dead Boys."
What about it?
[ Chuckles ]
l don't know.
l guess l'm just cracking up.
[ Chuckles ]
You oughta know.
That's your specialty.
Yeah.
[ Turkell ]
Did you ever see anything so nasty?
Ooh! You got a big one too.
[ Laughing ]
Boy, they really did
a job on you, Cordell.
l mean, an honest cop.
What'd you think you'd get out of it?
You put the squeeze
on the important people,
you end up in the slammer
not them.
What happened to you?
Why don't you tell me
what happened?
l mean, l've never seen nobody
cut... that bad-
that deep-
and still be breathing.
[ Gavel Rapping ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Grunting continues ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Stabs ]
[ Shouts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Grunting ]
This young lady
was attacked last evening...
by the man we believe
killed those strippers in Brooklyn
Queens and Manhattan.
What can l do to help?
Tonight we're hitting
similar clubs in Lower Manhattan,
bringing cheryl here along,
hoping she can identify her attacker.
lf he frequents such clubs-
and we think he does-
he might show up.
We're gonna be going in and out
of these places as couples.
So we need a policewoman
to make a foursome.
l don't have any experience
on the streets.
[ Sighs ]
Why me?
Her assailant was rescued by a cop
who killed two policemen
in the process.
A huge disfigured cop.
[ Lovejoy ]
We put out a story that
cheryl died en route to Bellevue,
just to put her attacker at ease.
Did he do this to you?
Yes.
could you tell me
what his hands felt like?
Like ice.
So you want to come along?
- Do l have any choice?
- No.
You're under my protection.
Remember how to use a gun
Officer Riley?
What difference does it make?
Shooting cordell
is only good for getting his attention.
Hey wait!
Don't leave me here.
lt ain't safe out there!
oh. You're goin' someplace
l can't go, huh?
Got work to do.
Yeah, but you're
comin' back, right?
You know
l got things to do myself.
But then l'll be back here
waitin for you.
[ Man ]
? All day long ?
? l've had this funny feeling ?
? That tonight is the night ?
? Right all along ?
? lntuition keeps on telling me ?
? That love is in sight ?
? The stars are shining extra bright tonight ?
? That means something to me ?
How you doin'?
Hey. Four.
Four. $20.
? Love is searching for me yeah ?
[ Man ]
Enjoy the show.
? lt's a message from above ?
? Telling me to get ready ?
- You girls work hard.
- Yeah, we do.
l can make a thousand dollars a week.
How much money
do you make, Lieutenant?
Maybe i oughta take
dancing lessons.
You see anybody familiar here?
Just a bunch of regulars
from the other clubs that l work
but l don't see him.
Why don't we get out of here
and try someplace else?
Why don't we have a drink?
What the hell. We paid for it.
? lntuition keeps on telling me ?
? Just go with the flow ??
?? [ Continues ]
Lieutenant, it's him.
Hey.
- Hey watch it.
- Hey, man.
[ Gasps ]
- Hey look out.
- [ Shouts ]
[ Glass Shatters ]
[ Woman Screams ]
- l gotta get me one of those.
- [ Chuckles ]
Hey, you.
l want to see my lawyer.
That's no problem.
What happened to your friend
the big cop?
He's my friend, all right.
And he ain't gonna
forget about me.
[ Chuckles ]
How did you meet Cordell?
How'd you know his name?
Shit.
That girl that coldcocked me.
She's the one from that TV show
Criminals at Large.
Hey, you.
lt's gonna take more than
a TV show to catch my friend.
[ Chuckles ]
Hmm.
This your address Turkell?
Wipe your feet on the mat.
l think we got him.
That's great.
You want some company?
Haven't you seen enough action
for one night?
Why don't you go get some rest?
No i couldn't sleep.
l think l'll go fire
a few practice rounds.
l've never been
much good with guns.
Under the circumstances
l'd try to improve.
[ Gunshots ]
[ Man ]
l've never seen you
in uniform before.
l wanted to see if it still fits.
That's not
a very good shot pattern.
Maybe you're better at
shootin' your mouth off on TV.
Did they assign you
to a beat yet?
Maybe Spanish Harlem
or some nice place like that?
Maybe.
Well listen, Susan.
Just, uh- Just keep trying.
You'll get the knack of it
in about a year or two.
Just tell everybody that that broken arm
was your good one.
Right.
come on in fellas.
We've got ourselves a serial killer.
[ Turkell ]
? Don't you forget me, Cordell ?
? i'm waitin' for you here, Cordell ?
? We'll both probably end up in hell ?
? You'll need- ??
Motherfucker!
Will you hold it down?
Shit.
Get more privacy when I get back
in the motherfuckin death house.
ls that where you're goin', man?
Sing Sing?
What the fuck are you
Barbara Walters?
Shit, man.
Yeah.
Motherfuckin' mornin'.
Shit.
l stalled them motherfuckers
for five years.
Yeah.
The Supreme Court it fucked me.
And it wasn't even safe sex.
lt's cruel and unusual punishment.
No bullshit.
Listenin' to assholes like you
is worse.
Hey be nice.
When my friend comes
to break me out
l might take you with me.
Yeah.
l will hold my breath...
and my dick.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, hi there pretty lady.
Boy, don't you look great
in that uniform.
You want me to
autograph your cast?
Look, l still want
to talk to you about cordell.
lf you want to know about him
stick around here tonight.
You might learn somethin'.
What do you mean by that?
[ Chuckling ]
[ Gunshots ]
- [ Gunshots ]
- [ All Grunting ]
[ Grunts ]
Hey, hey!
[ All Shouting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Susan ]
No.
lt must be visiting hours
'cause my friend is back!
[ Laughing ]
Make sure that roadblock is set up.
[ Man Shouting ]
What's going on?
He blew away half a dozen men
downstairs on the firing range.
l don't know how many he killed upstairs.
We just got the hell out of his way.
That's a good strategy.
He's got Susan Riley as a hostage
on the cell block.
ls she all right?
l don't know.
What are we doin' about this?
l got the tactical squad on its way
and a couple of SWAT teams.
Doyle's been notified.
He's on his way over here
to take charge.
Take charge?
That's a joke.
You got any ideas?
lf he comes out
don't interfere with him.
Just follow him.
He had a reason for coming here.
He's got a reason
for everything he does.
ooh4 what'd you do to these cops?
Oh, l'd have loved to seen it.
See Blum?
l told you, treat me nice.
[ Susan ]
He's gonna get us killed.
Hey lady, close your eyes.
You may see something you like.
[ Chuckling ]
Going home.
How come he don't talk?
lt's weird.
Weird!
He just handed me
your transfer papers to Sing Sing.
l ain't goin' back there.
Well, l think that's
what he's got in mind.
Hey man, they gonna kill me!
No he wouldn't let that happen
to a pleasing personality like yourself.
You've been in Sing Sing before.
What's back there for you?
come on. You're a bright girl.
Haven't you got that figured out yet?
We're goin' there...
to break out all them guys
on death row.
There's about 20 of 'em
up there on appeal.
Real lovable types.
Yes, that's-
that's what we're gonna do.
'Cause we're recruitin' an army.
Aren't we?
Sure.
See 'cause it's like,
your thoughts are in my mind.
l got you figured out man.
We ain't runnin' away.
No, we're gettin stronger.
Yeah!
[ Chuckles ]
'Cause we got ourselves a leader.
oh, l don't want no part of this.
l'm not goin' to no state pen-
- ow!
- [ Chuckles ]
Uh say listen.
We gonna bring her along?
All right, sweetheart.
Here's a jacket.
You lead the way.
lf there's any shootin'
you'll be the first to know about it.
[ Cackles ]
Terrific. She puts on a uniform
and immediately gets taken hostage.
Some cop.
Why is he going back there?
Shut up and get in.
[ Engine Starts ]
Bumper cars!
[ Sirens Wailing ]
Let me give you a ride commissioner.
We gotta talk.
l have my limo.
We need to talk.
[ Cackling ]
[ Sirens Wailing ]
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Turkell ]
All right, hold on, y'all.
- Here goes!
- [ Tires Squealing ]
[ Turkell Whooping ]
l'm bad! Whoo!
[ Cackling ]
That's right, eh, Blum?
Don't change your shorts baby
'cause this ride's just startin'.
Do-si-do!
Ah-ha!
Yeah!
What do you think
of that, little lady?
Huh?
Going in the wrong direction.
That's the parkway up ahead.
Same route cordell took.
l think i know where he's going.
How do you know that?
one of the escapees
was scheduled for a transfer
to the death house at Sing Sing.
cordell's making the delivery.
He's homesick.
How come you didn't
say anything about that before?
'Cause all the cops in the world
can't stop Cordell.
Only you can.
Stop this car.
l'm getting out.
That's an order.
You lost the right
to make orders.
- You're going with me.
- No. No, i'm not going anywhere.
What's the matter Commissioner?
You finally believe in ghosts?
You oughta.
You made him one.
Turn this goddamn car around.
[ Chuckles ]
That's a dumb fuckin' thing to do.
Well, what do you
want me to do, huh?
Shove the gun in my own mouth?
pull the trigger?
That's too easy.
l want you to reopen
the Cordell case.
Get some judge to set aside his conviction
and then dig up his empty coffin.
That's right.
lt's gonna be empty.
come on.
- Then i want you to bury it again
with a police honor guard.
- You're fuckin crazy.
cordell got too close
to you people at city hall
who were takin' payoffs.
So you framed him,
put him in a fuckin' rathole
and set him up.
- You murdered him.
- You're pushin' me too far, McKinney.
- pull over!
- [ Tires Screech ]
[ panting ]
You're right.
l'm responsible.
What am l supposed to do now?
- Sign a confession.
- l can't do that. l'd be through.
Well you're through now.
You're not gonna see retirement.
He's gonna come after you.
[ Whooping ]
You sure is pretty for a cop.
Do you wanna integrate?
[ Knocking ]
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Whooping ]
This is McKinney.
Deputy commissioner Doyle wants
to speak to His Honor the mayor.
lt concerns the massacre
at headquarters.
Open the gate.
[ Gate Opening ]
Uh delivering the prisoner
Blum, Joseph T.
We weren't expecting
this guy till morning.
l got a tip his friends might try
to create a little detour, you know.
We're just playin' it safe.
Open the gates.
[ Gates Opening ]
Welcome home Cordell.
put me through to the warden.
Warden Blum's just been delivered.
[ Warden ]
I got word from the city
that he'd been broken out ofjaiI.
Well he just arrived under escort.
Seal off that section
of the celI block.
Put all men on alert.
We're in trouble.
Yes, sir.
[ lnmates Shouting ]
[ on P.A. ]
Attention. Attention.
This is the warden.
Deputy Commissioner Doyle
wishes to speak to Matt Cordell.
cordell? He's alive.
l told you so.
lf he comes after me
l'm ready for that bastard.
[ Neck Snaps ]
[ Turkell ]
Hey, death row people!
We're here to liberate you! Yeah!
This is Deputy Commissioner Doyle.
I'm here in the prison courtyard.
I'm taiking to Matt Cordell.
Cordell
Judge Arthur Claypool
has ordered your case reopened.
Bullshit.
Like you need a new trial, right?
Listen, cordell.
This is what you want.
- Hey you shut up. You hear me?
- Listen!
Keep going.
ln your first trial,
perjury was committed.
Even the presiding judge
was influenced.
l myself was involved.
We're the guilty ones.
Cordell, you were a good man once.
A good cop.
Fuck him. Good cop.
- You're every good cop's nightmare.
- Yeah!
Cordell, I repeat,
your conviction will be reversed
by the state supreme court.
[ lnmate in Distance ]
Open this door now!
Hey, come on! Open the door!
[ Overlapping Shouts in Distance ]
Where you goin' man?
Where the fuck's he going?
l don't know man.
Don't leave me.
Tell me what to do!
[ panting ]
No! Hey!
oh, God!
[ Shouting ln Distance ]
No.
Don't leave me.
[ Doyle ]
I've signed a confession.
l'm the guilty one.
Good.
He heard you.
l hope.
[ lnmates Shouting ]
cordell!
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Shouting Shrieking ]
No!
[ Shouts ]
[ Shrieks Grunts ]
[ Man Shouting Whimpering ]
No!
[ Grunts ]
[ Shrieking ]
You never cared for me.
You were never my friend!
[ Shrieking ]
[ Shrieking Continues ]
[ Man ]
We commend our brother Matthew
to you, Lord.
May he live on in your presence.
ln your mercy and love,
forgive whatever sins he may have
committed through human weakness.
We ask this
through christ our Lord. Amen.
And so the final remains
of Matthew cordell,
who died three years ago
are brought to rest with honors.
His remains have been brought here
so he may be placed
beside his fellow officers.
But l feel sorrow for all of those...
whose deceptions and lies
were responsible for this tragic death.
That's something
they'll have to contend with
when they meet their maker.
[ Honor Guard Commander ]
Detail. Attention.
present arms.
order arms.
[ McKinney ]
l'll take that.
[ Honor Guard Commander ]
Detail dismissed.
[ Nightstick Swinging ]
What is it?
Hmm?
Uh... oh nothin'.
There's a piece of cordell
in every cop.
Every time arresting
some mutt isn't enough,
because we know
they'll be back on the streets
before we even do the paperwork.
Every time we pull a trigger and-
and it feels good,
because that's something
the lawyers can't reverse.
lt all comes down to justice...
and pressure.
There's only that much difference
between a cop and a maniac cop.
[ children ]
One bright day in the middie of the night,
two dead boys got up to fight.
Back to back
they faced each other.
With their knives
they shot each other.
A deaf poIiceman heard the noise...
and came and killed the two dead boys.
[ children Laughing ]
[ Man ]
Yo, wait a minute.
[ Man #2 ]
What's that?
Something's sneaking
around the corner.
Here we come!
I think it's that maniac.
Hold on!
[ Together ]
Aaah!
?? [ Hip-hop lntro ]
Rock!
[ Rapping ]
? You better watch out
when you hear that sound ?
? lt means that
the Maniac Cop's around ?
? once upon a time he was a super cop ?
? But the bad guys framed him
to make him stop ?
? They put him in prison,
where they tried to kilI him ?
? But he broke out
Now he's the villain ?
? Bullets won't hurt him
I know it sounds like jive ?
? But we're not sure
if he's dead or alive ?
? Set him on fire
or shoot him with an Uzi ?
? But he'Il show up in your Jacuzzi ?
? You can run him over
You can feed him poison ?
? Push him out a window,
and it only annoys him ?
? You better believe me
if you think I'm lyin' ?
? When he show up
people start dyin' ?
? Yeah ?
? He's out for vengeance
and he can't be stopped ?
? That's why they cali him
the Maniac Cop ?
[ Man ]
You have the right to remain siIent.
[ chuckling ]
Huh!
Rock!
? When you hear that whistIe
out in the street ?
? You're gonna think
it's a cop on the beat ?
? But don't be thinkin'
about poIice protection ?
? 'cause this is one cop
with a bad connection ?
? When he shows up,
he's supposed to protect ya ?
? But Maniac Cop is out to get ya ?
? He's an anti-vigilante,
and they can't convict him ?
? So watch out Jack
'cause you're the next victim ?
? Don't hang around
if you see him comin' ?
? Just pick up your feet
and commence to runnin ?
? And don't waste time dialin' 91 1 ?
? Forget karate ?
? And forget your gun ?
? Don't play hero
Don't try to be brave ?
? This dude's gonna
send you to an early grave ?
? He's out for vengeance
and he can't be stopped ?
? That's why they cali him
the Maniac Cop ?
[ Man ]
You have the right to a mortician.
If you cannot afford one,
we'lI take you as you are.
Rock!
[ chuckling ]
? The law is equal
and justice is blind ?
? But this cop's justice
is one of a kind ?
? He's homicidal and maladjusted ?
? But when he busts in,
your ass is busted ?
? You won't get a ticket
or pay your fine ?
? You might as well be dealin'
with Frankenstein ?
? He's big and ugly with a busted jaw ?
? You know
he's the wrong arm of the law ?
? You better stay away
from this man in biue ?
? And don't call a cop
'cause he'll snuff him too ?
? They kilied him once
but he came back ?
? He's the
ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-maniac ?
? So when you're out on the streets
and you hear that sound ?
? It probably means
that Cordell's around ?
? He's out for vengeance
and he can't be stopped ?
? That's why they cali him
the Maniac Cop ?
? The Maniac Cop ?
Rock!
Wait a minute.
What's that?
I don't know, but I'm breakin' camp.
No, wait, Josh.
Come back.
Aaah!
Ah, man, l ain't with that, man.
Let's break.
Let's get outta here. come on!
Hey, man
maybe we should chiil.
i know.
And check out the movie again.
i think we should.
Rock!
[ Man ]
You have the right to remain silent...
forever.