(Foreboding music)
(Baby crying)
(Calming music)
God forgive me.
(Ominous music)
(Heaving)
(Speaking Latin)
Mom was right about you!
You're insane!
[Woman with knife] You're
my sister and I do love you!
[Bound woman]
What are you doing?
No, don't do this.
(Screaming)
(Praying in Latin)
(Calming music)
(Baby crying)
Only one more, baby.
One more.
(Ominous music)
(Door knocking)
[Eliza] Cameron, get
up, I'm leaving soon.
(Door knocking)
Cameron, get up, now!
I'm up!
(Rumbling)
(TV chattering)
Oh, great, oh hi,
you finally woke up,
Did you get enough sleep?
Morning to you too, Mom.
You know I've been planning
this retreat for months,
The least you could've
done is gotten up early
And helping out around here.
Calm down Mom, what can I do?
Take over!
Over here.
What's up Granddad?
[Angie] But Grandma
I'm trying to help,
He won't open his mouth.
[Eliza] I don't care.
I don't want eggs.
Angie you love eggs.
Angie, eat it.
[Angie] I'm not hungry!
What's up, turdburglars?
My unemployment check is late.
Oh, Joey, let me get my purse.
I don't have time for this.
No, the mail-system sucks!
Wow, beer for breakfast again?
What a surprise.
What about, "Hey,
how's my favorite uncle?"
[Eliza] Uh, would
the two unemployed ones
Not start again?
"Good morning, Uncle Joey?"
[Eliza] I don't
have time for this.
Or, "Hey drop dead!"
[Eliza] You better
not argue all weekend!
[Cameron] Drop dead.
Ah Jesus!
Fucking got to
(Mumbling), man.
Jesus Joey, take it, take it.
Yeah, well you're a dick.
You're a dick!
You guys stop,
enough, take this.
You go over here.
[Cameron] You're
such an asshole!
Angie go, go to your room
and eat your food there,
Right now, you get away
from me, you help me,
Right now, let's go.
Now Cameron, I
need help packing!
Oh my God, geez, why
am I getting yelled at?
Uncle Joey doesn't do
anything around here.
What the hell is his problem?
[Eliza] Language, Cameron.
I don't know why Nanny
lets him live here.
For the same reason
she lets us live here,
We're family.
You can't pick
your family, honey.
[Voiceover] Eliza!
One minute, mom.
[Voiceover] Eliza I
can't find my pills.
Will you please help
me finish packing?
And get my sleeping
bag from the cellar?
Come here, I love you.
(Ominous music)
(Squeaking)
[Angie] Uncle Cameron, I
have something to show you.
[Cameron] Hi.
When are we gonna
see Mom, you promised?
Ssshht!
I told you, I'm working on it.
Why doesn't Grandma like Mom?
Hey, Grandma loves Mom.
She just doesn't
want you around her
When she's sick.
(Sad music)
I made a painting for Mom.
[Cameron] Where
is the baby going?
It's Jamie.
I'm trying to grab
his hand to stop
Him from going to heaven.
Do you remember
your twin brother?
Only in pictures.
Well, it's beautiful,
And your mom is gonna love it.
(Laughing)
For the last time, I
don't want Angie around her,
Move!
Mom, she has the right
to see her real mother.
Actually, she doesn't, all
right, the court has decided
That when her mother overdosed,
Or did you forget your
sister is an addict?
Did you forget
you're an alcoholic?
Cameron.
I've been sober for 12 years.
Yeah, well Mom, when
you were getting sober
You still had the
right to see us.
Cameron, I was drinking,
Caitlin's a junkie!
So those mistakes
make her less fit
To be a mom than you?
(Sighs) Oh, that's it,
move, this discussion is over.
Hey, someone's cranky.
Cameron.
Listen, I pray
for Caitlin, I do.
But I lost one grandchild
because of her,
And I'm not gonna
lose another, okay?
So that's it?
That's it.
Now listen, Uncle Joey
has said that he'd help
With Angie, all right,
so no fighting, promise?
Oh, you trust douchebag
Uncle Joey with Angie
But not Caitlin?
Stop in, and Aunt Jean
is gonna come this weekend,
Check in, all right?
What am I, five?
No you're not five, but
Nanny would like to see her
Other daughter once
in a while, okay?
Besides, it'll give you
the night off, okay?
You worry too much.
I worry too much?
Come here, give me a
hug, I'm an expert at it.
I'll miss you, be good.
Yeah I won't burn down
the house or kill anybody
Or anything, so.
I love you.
[Cameron] Sure.
I love you too Mom.
(Sad music)
(Laughing)
Angie?
[Angie] Come find
me, Uncle Cameron!
Angie!
(Rumbling)
[Angie] Hey let me out!
Give me one good
reason to let you out.
[Angie] No, Uncle Cameron!
(Laughs)
Pretty soon you're gonna
need a new hiding spot.
When you go to college,
Who's gonna come find me here?
Hmm...
Looks like I'm not
going to college.
Are you ready to go see Momma?
But Grandma said we can't go.
Well guess what.
I'm in charge now,
and I say it's okay.
But if you say one
word little lady.
Go get your jacket.
[Angie] Okay.
Where are you taking her?
I'm taking her to the zoo.
[Voiceover] Don't
come here no more,
Why do you keep calling?
[Voiceover] He is your son
and you'll need to see him!
[Voiceover] You just want
money, I ain't got no money.
[Voiceover] I don't want
your paternity, (Mumbling),
I know where you get your money.
You have responsibilities,
you're supposed to be a man...
(Elevator dinging)
(Baby crying)
(Door knocking)
[Caitlin] Hi!
[Angie] Mom!
Oh...
(Foreboding music)
So tell me, how did
you convince Mom
To let you come here today?
Well, Grandma
doesn't know about
This little adventure, so,
keep it a secret, right Angie?
Hmm-mm.
Oh, disobeying Mom, I approve.
Well, she will kill
me if she finds out, so.
Not a peep.
How you doing?
You know.
I'm good.
Uhm, staying clean.
Trying to stay on track
And keep going to work.
For you.
(Laughing)
(Baby crying)
What's going on over there?
There's been awful
fights all week.
It's just been terrible.
Did you call the cops?
In this neighborhood,
there's really no point.
Around here, it's better
to mind your own business.
(Rumbling)
Uncle Cameron, don't go!
(Screaming)
(Rumbling)
Hey, hey, what the
fuck are you doing?
(Glass shattering)
(Screaming)
[Man] Get over there.
Get her away man!
What are you doing?
What the hell are
you doing here?
He's the last one!
What's going on here?
I'm here to help you,
calm down, calm down!
I'm gonna call the cops.
What happened, just
tell me what happened.
I'm here to help!
Are you bleeding?
[Woman] Stupido!
[Cameron] Who was that guy?
[Woman] This is
all your fault.
[Cameron] All right
slow down, slow down.
Tell me exactly what happened.
[Woman] I can't believe
you let him get away.
[Cameron] What's your name?
She's coming, she's coming,
I have to see my baby.
[Cameron] My sister
is calling the cops.
I have to see my baby.
(Baby crying)
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help!
(Eerie music)
Let me help you!
Tell me what happened...
(Incoherent heaving)
Calm down!
[Woman] No, no!
Angie!
[Woman] No, don't, don't!
[Cameron] Angie, Angie, Angie!
My baby!
No, he's gone!
No, no!
Angie?
(Screaming)
[Caitlin] What's
wrong with her?
[Cameron] She'll be okay.
What about the baby,
was there not a baby?
Listen, let's let the
cops deal with this one.
I called Dr. Mendez, he said
he can come by the house
In about an hour.
What if she caught
whatever that baby had?
You better get outta here.
Just call me, okay?
As soon as I
figure things out.
All right, take her.
Bye guys.
(Eerie growling)
(Ominous music)
[Voiceover] Eliza!
(Sighs)
(Eerie growling)
(Muttering)
Jesus, Nanny, oh my God.
Where's your mother?
Nanny, she went on a retreat.
You know that.
Let me help you.
Are you comfy?
[Nanny] Oh not the
comforter, it's too hot.
If you need anything else.
I want a good night
kiss from Angie.
She's sick, she's
already in bed.
Oh...
Poor thing.
She's so sweet.
Hand me my book, honey.
Good night, Nanny.
Take care of Angie, Cam.
(Eerie chimes)
(Relaxing music)
(Coughing)
You really just need to chill,
It's probably just a
little cold or something.
Yeah and you weren't
there, I'm telling you.
Don't be so dramatic.
You sound like your mom.
Hmm.
Shoot me now, please,
oh... (Coughs)
I swear, I heard
something coming up,
Like from under the bed.
Like weird breathing.
Oh, weird breathing?
Yeah.
(Giggling)
That's not funny.
[Megan] It's funny.
No, it's not.
It's kinda funny.
I mean that's what you
get for smoking this.
Where did you get
this stuff anyway?
From my Uncle Joey's stash.
Creepy Uncle Joey?
No wonder it tastes so cheap.
You know, this is
kinda creepy to do
With your sister
and Angie watching.
So, have you given
it any more thought
To going to college
with me after summer?
I've been a bit
preoccupied around here.
God, you're making
excuses again.
Look, I told you
I'd think about it.
This is our future, Cameron.
I know, Megan.
You graduated a year ago.
You wanna end up like
your uncle, or your mom?
Come on, how long
are you gonna wait
To start your own life?
Hey.
Do you like it?
(Door opening)
(Anticipating music)
Angie, Angie!
What, Cam, what the hell!
Jesus!
Angie.
(Laughing)
Oh you need to know
you need to be in bed.
(Rumbling)
I'm not doing this right now.
(Laughing)
(Rumbling)
Angie come on.
Get out of there!
(Ominous music)
(Eerie music)
Oh my God...
Angie.
I'm telling you Caitlin.
Something isn't right.
You should've seen the
look in Angie's eyes.
[Caitlin] Do you have any
idea how insane that sounds?
I mean seriously, you
probably just smoked something
That you shouldn't have.
Okay, can we talk about your
hallucinations later please?
Angie's gonna be just fine.
My doctor said that, I just
need you to watch her okay?
Love you.
See you later, let yourself out.
(Door knocking)
(Heaving)
(Ominous music)
I know you're in there.
(Heaving)
[Voiceover] Go away.
Come on.
I gotta talk to you.
Please.
It's my niece.
I have nothing to say to you.
No, help me, please.
Listen, whatever the
reason is you hate me,
Don't take it out on my niece.
She's just a little girl.
(Foreboding music)
[Woman] All you need
to know, is in here.
[Cameron] Who
are these people?
[Woman] They were chosen, so
that a child could be saved.
Their deaths were
wasted, they always are.
She dares you to
try, but she knows.
You will fail.
[Cameron] Who are
you talking about?
She's the child-stealer,
her name is Lilith.
She was Adam's first wife.
What do you mean,
Adam and Eve, Adam?
[Woman] Banished from
the Garden of Eden after
Refusing subservience to
Adam, as God commanded,
Lilith was punished.
Her mouth was sealed.
Her womb was cursed.
She would never bear children.
(Baby crying)
Lilith became a
creature of darkness,
Making a pact with
Lucifer to grant her
Unholy powers to
steal the offspring
Of Adam and Eve.
(Mumbling) children for her.
So what are you telling
is that Lilith has Angie.
No, not yet.
There's still time to save her.
I should go.
The cost of a soul, Angie's
soul comes at a price.
Okay, obviously you've
been through of a lot...
Sacrifice, it's the only way.
You need to offer six other
lives to Lilith in little
Angie's place, six lives
from her bloodline,
From your family.
What do you want me to do?
Are you expecting
me to kill them?
No.
You...
Mark them.
Lilith does the taking.
You have six days
to mark six members
Of the blood line.
And if you fail,
Angie will be gone.
Where is your baby?
I almost saved him.
And then you showed up.
You let my ex-husband escape.
Okay.
[Woman] He would've
been the last.
Okay, okay.
I wish you were
dead, and not my boy.
But this is fucked up.
But I can't stand the
thought of that little girl
Going through the same thing.
I spent three days trying
to understand this.
I wasted time on doctors,
Pis, paranormal experts.
Everything I could think
of to save my baby.
Three of my six days,
and now he is gone.
(Anticipating music)
You don't have time.
You need help.
I'm not the one who
needs help right now.
If I were to
choose six people...
How would I choose 'em?
The first one is unbearable.
And then it gets harder.
(Ominous music)
(Coughing)
Cameron!
(Rock music)
(Foreboding music)
(Coughing)
(Rumbling)
(Eerie growling)
(Sad music)
Oh my sweet Angie.
Nanny's here.
(Foreboding music)
(Muttering)
Cameron...
(Screaming)
(Heaving)
Nanny?
(Muttering)
(Anticipating music)
Nanny?!
Grandpa?
Are you okay?
(Muttering)
What happened?
Grandpa?
Say it, say what it is.
(Rumbling)
Jesus, Nanny!
(Ominous music)
Oh, fuck.
Oh fuck...
I'm sorry Nanny.
(Eerie growling)
(Choking)
(Screaming)
(Puking)
(Sad music)
(Phone ringing)
Hello?
Yeah Mom I'm here.
No, no, no, not at all.
No, Angie has just
run into fever.
It's nothing too serious.
Yes Mom, I called Dr. Mendez.
She's in bed already.
She took her pill.
Okay, thank you Mom, thank you.
I gotta go.
(Sad music)
[Caitlin] Okay, so
what does this book mean?
And where is Nanny, Cameron?
Why won't you believe me?
You need to trust
me on this one.
Okay, so, Lilith is a demon
And you sacrificed Nanny to her?
Although that bitch
probably deserves it,
I mean come on, Cameron.
I'm not lying, Caitlin.
Okay.
(Eerie growling)
(Coughing)
Caitlin?
(Choking)
Caitlin, Caitlin!?
Holy shit!
(Anticipating music)
(Screaming)
Caitlin, it won't open!
- [Cameron] What the fuck!
- [Caitlin] Hey, hey!
(Ominous music)
(Screaming)
[Caitlin] I need a drink.
Caitlin, that's not
gonna fix anything.
What we need is
five more people,
And we only have
four days to go.
And what are you gonna do?
Well I can't do this alone.
Okay, well, how do we choose?
It has to be
from our bloodline.
Well who's gonna be next?
Boo!
(Laughing) Like a little girl!
Pussy!
How (Mumbling).
(Foreboding music)
(Floor squeaking)
(Bottles ringing)
(Sudden chimes)
What are you doing, dumbass?
Uh, I'm grabbing
this aspirin for Angie.
Yeah.
Whatever man, just take it.
Oh, Cameron.
I just want you to know uh,
I hope Angie's okay.
I checked on her earlier,
she didn't look too good.
You checked on her?
Yeah man.
Yeah I do care, okay?
It's kinda hard to tell.
I mean we are family right?
Yeah, yeah.
I guess we are.
Yeah we are.
Did you check on Nanny?
Aunt Jean has picked her up.
Without Dad?
Well yeah, they just
went to dinner, so.
She said she'd be back soon.
Ah whatever.
Shut the door for me, will you?
Yeah.
(Burping)
(Yawning)
Caitlin.
It's done.
We just have to wait a bit.
(Sad music)
(Gasps)
Oh shit.
(Eerie humming)
(Eerie growling)
[Megan] Hey beautiful.
Meg.
Where did you come from?
[Megan] I missed you.
Oh I miss you too.
[Megan] Why are you sleeping?
I'm so tired.
It's been such a long week.
[Megan] But you don't
have time to sleep.
(Screaming)
Hey, hey, Cam, Cam, wake up!
Hey, it's time.
Come on.
(Foreboding music)
(Snoring)
(Ominous music)
(Burping)
Caitlin, his arm (Mumbling).
(Grunting)
So how do we do this?
You don't need to
stay here for this.
No...
I need to see this.
Caitlin, I'm gonna
take care of this.
Go!
(Door closing)
Damn.
(Foreboding music)
(Gasps)
What the fuck is?
What the?
Huh?
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
Where are you going?
(Foreboding music)
What happened?
[Cameron] I'm
sorry, I couldn't.
Hold still.
He was just lying there,
and he just woke up.
You still had time
to make the symbol.
He was awake, Caitlin.
We don't have time to
wait for natural causes,
I don't know what you don't
understand about that.
I don't see you volunteering
to cut your finger
And eternally damn
your family members.
Look, I'm not gonna
lose Angie, Cam.
Since when do you
care about Angie?
Or didn't you think
I would notice?
I'm gonna go.
Caitlin, don't
run away from this.
Caitlin, wait, I forgot,
It's not your fault.
But you know what, it is.
Okay, you have a daughter
who loves and adores you.
When Angie needs you the
most, you're walking out.
You know maybe Mom was right.
Maybe you don't deserve Angie.
Hey!
You know what, maybe
I'm a fuck-up, okay?
But you are the one that
brought this thing on Angie.
You are the one who
put her life in danger.
And you are the one who's
gonna take care of it.
(Phone ringing)
Hey Megan.
You're pregnant?
That's your reaction?
It's been a fucked-up week.
I'm sorry to
inconvenience you,
But we have some decisions here.
I can't do this
right now, Megan.
What can be more
important than this?
Look, I know you
don't wanna sacrifice
Your life for a kid.
Megan you told me
you were on the pill.
I am.
It doesn't always work.
Cam we have to make a choice.
It's life and death.
It's not an easy choice.
Yeah, well.
I wanna keep it.
I can't do this right now.
I just need some time.
Fine.
You know take all
the time you want,
It's not like
we're on the clock.
Jesus Cam.
(Sad music)
You're good?
All righty.
You missed a button right here.
You're looking sharp
today, Grandpa.
Granddad, you must be
wondering where Nanny is.
You know I miss you, Grandpa.
I really wish you
were here to help me.
(Ominous music)
What?
Can I help you?
No.
But I can help you, Cameron.
May I come in?
Lilith, she's here.
[Cameron] What do
you know about Lilith?
She took my little girl.
A long time ago.
Well, did you?
Sacrifice anyone, no.
I went through six days
of hell not knowing.
I had a way, a chance.
Lilith was haunting
me, mocking me,
The whole time.
That's what she does.
She took Rebeca.
Then I became a nun.
How did you find us?
The book.
The book Sabrina
gave you, I wrote it.
I've been tracking
her for years.
Helping anyone I can.
Trying to find a way
to banish the unholy
Beast back to hell.
Have you managed to
offer her anyone?
My Nanny.
My grandmother.
She fell.
So she was pretty much already
dieing when I found her.
You got lucky.
Or maybe you do have
some stones after all.
But three days down, you're
gonna have to push harder.
A nun is encouraging
me to kill my own family?
All of us are marked by years.
By bad habits.
Mediocre deaths
and the ease of it
Come into our petty lives.
But the children.
They are tabula rasa.
An empty slate.
Greatness can be written there.
There's no worse sin
than letting a pure soul
Be a servant to
that slut in hell.
That still makes me a killer.
(Doorbell ringing)
(Ominous music)
Aunt Jean, Randy.
Hi.
I thought you guys
were coming tomorrow.
Hosting a women's
luncheon, last minute,
Now tomorrow, so, as
promised to your mother,
I'm checking in.
Is this a bad time?
No, no, well
maybe a little bit.
Where's your
grandmother, upstairs?
She's out.
Out?
Where did she go?
The doctors.
Yeah they said she
was gonna be a while,
So I just came back home.
Not gonna ask
about my brother,
But what about little Angie?
She's sick and she's in bed.
Oh, I hope I don't catch
whatever it is she has.
It's just the cold.
I am so susceptible to colds.
True.
Well, I guess
we'll just wait here
Until it's time to go
pick your grandmother up,
And then we'll get her with you.
Would you guys like
something to drink?
A drink would be nice.
Orange juice, some warm milk?
Well I don't suppose
Eliza keeps alcohol
In the house anymore.
Uncle Joey has beer.
Shocking.
Whatever.
Be right back.
So how hard does
it blow to live here?
It's got this kinda
like antique shithole
Vibe about it.
If your mom would've
married into money
Like mine did, you
might better off,
But my mom's a total MILF, so.
I don't wanna think
of Aunt Jean like that.
Oh come, your mom
is totally doable.
You know in that born-again
Christian kinda way.
That is fucked up.
Yeah, it is.
So must be tough getting laid
Living in your grandma's house.
Well, I have a
girlfriend, so, not really.
You're straight?
Hmm.
Pfft, so what happened
to your finger?
I was...
I was cutting up XTC.
I was at a party.
You know, and the razor slipped.
What a noob.
Have any extra,
I'll buy it off you.
Yeah, give me a minute.
Nice!
(Foreboding music)
(Beeping)
Sweet.
Cameron.
[Cameron] I'm in Angie's room.
Hide your drugs
in Angie's room?
That's genius.
(Loud thump)
(Foreboding music)
I'll call you back.
Randy?
Cameron?
Get up here.
Look man, it's nothing personal.
Okay well you are a douche,
But it's just so convenient
you came with Aunt Jean.
You know, opportunity's
knock and whatnot, so.
(Foreboding music)
(Moves into ominous music)
(Sizzling)
Fuck.
[Randy] Wait...
What the fuck's happening?
Wait...
Guys!
Guys.
If you jump out
at me and scare me
I will pepper spray both of you.
(Eerie humming)
Guys?
(Door opening)
Hi Pops.
(Rumbling)
I swear to God
guys, one more time
And I'm gonna kill you.
Jesus Christ, Cameron!
Are you trying to give
me a heart attack?
Ma, Ma...
Ma...
(Scuffling)
[Aunt Jean] Cameron, stop!
(Choking)
(Screaming)
(Eerie growling)
(Anticipating music)
Randy...
(Screaming)
(Anticipating music)
(Muttering)
(Muffled screaming)
[Randy] Help!
(Phone vibrating)
Hey.
Aunt Jean's dead.
Caitlin I can't do this alone.
You're not alone, you're not.
Randy's tied up in the cellar.
What?
It didn't work.
She didn't take him.
I should start figuring
out how to do Uncle Joey.
Don't do anything
else, all right,
Just wait until I get there.
I gotta meet with my
parole officer, though,
Real quick, so let me do that,
And then I'll come.
All right?
(Phone beeping)
(Sad music)
You're tired
Gramps, aren't you?
You'll be with Nanny.
You'll be happier.
Jesus what am I doing.
You're doing what's
necessary to save Angie.
Your guilt is the only
thing that's stopping
You from saving her!
He'll understand, you know.
This shitty life he
has is no life at all.
I can't.
You have to.
That's easy for you to say.
You don't have to choose six
people over one little girl.
Don't ever tell me what
I would or would not do,
To save my Rebeca.
Lilith is a devil's whore!
And you're a fool.
A fool who's squandering
the only chance
You're ever gonna get.
There is no good option here.
Even God knows what
you have to do.
Your life is as you
know it is over.
There's no going back.
So snap out of it,
grow some balls
And do what you have to do.
Look.
I know he's old.
And sick, and he probably
doesn't have much time left,
But, he's still a good man.
A good man.
Wake up.
Don't bother screaming,
nobody's here.
Here, I bought you this,
it's a protein shake.
Drink up.
Fuck you.
Drink.
Look man.
What you saw upstairs was
a demon taking your mom.
And I know you won't be
able to understand this,
But, I had to do
it to save Angie.
No man I totally understand.
If you let me go I can help.
Sorry, I can't do that.
Come on Cameron, I'm
getting dizzy over here,
I feel fuzzy, I think
I need to see a doctor.
Well I can't.
People are gonna
come looking for me
You crazy fuck,
All right, and my
mom, she's important,
She's got stuff going
on like every minute.
You don't think people
are gonna notice?
You never shut up, do you?
(Muffled screaming)
(Clock ringing)
(Wood squeaking)
Angie, Angie you're up?
(Eerie humming)
(Ominous music)
Angie.
Angie what are you doing?
(Anticipating music)
(Muffled screaming)
Angie.
Angie, Angie.
Oh my God, oh...
Are you okay?
Come on, come on, come on.
(Serene music)
(Eerie humming)
Oh I didn't know you were home.
How is she doing?
Better.
Can I go see her?
You know, I just
put her to bed,
So, you probably shouldn't
just wake her up.
Okay.
I'll go check on Grandpa.
I didn't think you cared.
Well, that much I mean.
Well with your mom
and Granny out of town,
He's probably pretty lonely.
Well Nanny will be back
from Aunt Jean's tomorrow.
That's funny, I
called Aunt Jean.
Nothing.
You know Aunt Jean.
(Laughing)
Yeah, she's a WASP-y
bitch isn't she?
(Laughing)
Owh...
Are you good?
Ah, bet gone bad.
Looks like it.
Yeah.
It helped me put things
in perspective, though.
You know I care
about you, right Cam?
You know family,
it means something.
I just wanted you to know that.
Yeah.
Grandma Mollie?
Yes.
This is insane, we
can't just page through
Our family photo
albums and figure out
Who should die.
Okay, well that's
exactly what we're doing.
And what about Granddad?
Okay look, Granddad is
gonna be a natural choice.
But he has to go
after Uncle Joey.
Or else Uncle Joey is gonna
be way too suspicious,
And I'm running out of
excuses on why people aren't
Around anymore.
I really don't think
you need to worry about
Uncle Joey, I don't
think he's gonna notice
Or care.
That's the thing.
I don't know what's
been going on lately.
But he's a lot more...
I don't know, like
human than before.
Which is kinda messed up
Because it sure
would be a lot easier
If I still thought he
was a useless asshole.
Okay, so, we choose
douchebag Uncle Joey,
And Granddad,
that's four though.
Make a suggestion,
okay, that's exactly
What we're doing, we judge,
And then we get to pick
who lives and who dies
To save Angie.
Okay what about Dad,
he has a new life,
And new children, and shit.
Okay, yeah, Dad's
already on the list,
But he's out of town,
and I don't have time
To track him down.
Okay what about his
kids, they're blood related
To Angie.
Caitlin I'm not...
I'm not killing kids.
There's no way.
Then who are the
last two, Cameron?
(Muffled screaming)
(Rumbling)
(Foreboding music)
I think we got a problem.
(Rumbling)
(Muffled screaming)
Holy shit, Randy?
What the hell, man?
He thinks that Angie
is gonna be taken
By some demon.
He killed Mom.
He tried to kill me.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Get me out!
Cam, Cameron...
Randy!
Hey!
(Screaming)
Hey asshole!
(Anticipating music)
What happened?
Stay back!
(Screaming)
What did you do to him?
Oh my God!
Why!
You cocksucker!
Cameron!
Stop!
You're gonna die!
(Scuffling)
(Anticipating music)
Come here, cocksucker!
(Screaming)
I'm gonna kill you!
(Scuffling)
Cameron!
(Glass shattering)
Oh shit!
[Uncle Joey] Come here!
[Caitlin] Cameron!
[Cameron] Over here, dumbass!
(Screaming)
[Caitlin] Cameron!
(Groaning)
Cameron!
(Anticipating music)
(Grunting)
Cameron?
Answer me!
Cameron!
(Crying)
(Eerie humming)
(Screaming)
Cameron!
Hey!
(Sad music)
[Cameron] Over here, Caitlin.
Are you okay?
(Groaning)
Let me go!
Shut up!
We can't just leave
him tied up down here.
Okay well we are,
until this is all over.
He almost got away all ready.
(Spits)
I deserved that.
Cameron I have a really
big problem with this.
Caitlin, I'm doing
what I have to do
To save your daughter.
So shut up.
[Eliza] Cameron,
honey, I'm home!
(Muffled screaming)
Shut up, just shut up.
[Eliza] Hello?
Shit.
Where is everybody, Mom?
Hello Joey?
Great.
(Foreboding music)
Mom.
[Eliza] Hey.
You're home early.
Wait, what is this.
You're bleeding, Cameron!
I'm fine.
No you're not
fine, is something...
No, come here!
What are you doing, let me go!
Come here!
Cameron, what?
Honey what's the
matter, what's wrong.
If you had to choose between
Angie and Caitlin,
one of 'em had to die,
Who would you choose?
What kind of question is that?
Mom, answer me.
(Foreboding music)
(Footsteps walking)
(Gasps)
Caitlin.
Hi.
Is there something
wrong with Angie?
This sound crazy, Cameron.
I don't understand any of this.
Now what's going on?
Where's Nanny,
where's Uncle Joey?
What have you been doing?
What's happening.
Mom, listen to me.
There's no time.
I made some awful choices,
But it's because I had to.
This is all to save Angie.
Wait, what choices
are you talking about?
What have you done?
Save Angie from what, Cameron?
Come here.
Ow Cameron, ow
Cameron, let go of me!
[Cameron] Come on!
[Caitlin] Cameron stop it!
If you think none
of this is true,
And I'm crazy, there should
be no problem with Grandad
Seeing Angie, right?
What is he doing,
what is he even doing?
[Caitlin] Calm
down, calm down.
[Eliza] Daddy,
what are you doing?
[Caitlin] He just
wants you to see it.
Stop it!
Cameron what are
you doing, stop it!
What have you done?
Oh my God!
Angie needs you, hold her!
No!
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
Let go of me, no!
Stop!
(Ominous music)
Save her!
(Rumbling)
Daddy!
The devil has come
to this house.
This is my fault.
I knew that I'd be called
to the gates of hell
One day for what I did.
What are you talking about?
When the twins were
born Jamie came out
With all those problems,
he was so sick.
If he had lived, it
would've been a life of
Illness and hospitals.
Mom.
He went so peacefully.
What did you do to Jamie?
I took his frail, (Mumbling),
With these evil hands.
You killed my baby?
Oh my God Caitlin,
I'm so sorry.
Get away from me.
Get away from me!
For three years you've had Angie
Because I was called
an unfit mother.
[Eliza] You don't understand,
you were getting so high
When you were pregnant, and...
And you kicked
me out of my home,
And you wouldn't call
me, you took my children,
And you killed my Jamie!
You know, you say
that you love God
And you preach
all this bullshit,
But you're just a murderer,
You self-righteous bitch!
(Crying)
(Sad music)
[Eliza] I made the wrong
choice, I'm so sorry.
That wasn't your
choice to make.
No.
Caitlin!
(Sad music)
(Weeping)
Wild cats and hyenas
will meet there,
And billy goats
called to each other,
Lilith the night
monster will lurk there
And find herself
a place to rest.
Owh, Angie!
Angie stop!
Angie no!
(Eerie humming)
(Sad music)
Nanny gave this to me.
I want you to have it.
Caitlin.
I know there's no
way you're ever
Gonna forgive me, and I,
Lord knows there's
nothing I can do
To make it right, but,
There's something
I can do for Angie.
Mom.
There's one more thing.
What?
Randy's tied up in the cellar.
What, why?
I tried the symbol
on him, it didn't work.
Cam baby, Randy's adopted.
(Rumbling)
Oh shit, stay here.
Oh shit!
(Screaming)
Guys, guys, we gotta go.
We gotta go right now.
(Sad music)
You promise me you'll
finish what you started okay?
Promise!
I promise, Mom.
I love you so much, Cameron.
(Crying)
I want you to know
I always loved you.
Take care of Angie.
Okay I'm ready, I'm ready.
Oh my God, oh my...
(Foreboding music)
(Crying)
(Eerie humming)
(Screaming)
(Sad music)
We have our last sacrifice.
(Door knocking)
[Megan] Hi Caitlin.
Hey.
I'm fine.
Come in.
Where's Cameron?
Over here.
Oh my God, Angie.
Cam what happened to you?
[Cameron] I need
something from you.
What's going on?
(Foreboding music)
You were right.
I wanna be a good father.
And I don't wanna
keep this baby.
What are you doing?
Ssshht, it's okay.
No, you're scare,
what, Caitlin?
What the fuck, guys?
Calm down okay, just sit down.
Cameron, get her off of me!
Do it!
What the hell is going on?
Let me go!
Hold still!
Caitlin get off of me!
Let me go, please let me go!
(Crying)
What the fuck is happening?
This isn't my baby, is it?
Come on honey, let's
just talk about it okay?
Okay, shut the fuck up.
Please just tell
me what's going on.
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
How long have you been fucking
someone on the side, Megan?
Well that's it,
get outta here.
Go, get out of here!
[Megan] You guys are crazy.
[Caitlin] You have no
idea what you've done.
(Foreboding music)
I promised Mom
we'd finish this.
We are finishing this.
So maybe you...
Should do the same?
She is your daughter!
But you know what, you
were never her mother.
I am her mother.
You're a murderer.
Well maybe you should
take some responsibility.
She deserves better!
(Hissing)
Oh I can take care of Angie
better than any murderer!
(Foreboding music)
You can't even take
care of yourself.
What are you gonna
do for her, huh?
You're gonna be put away,
what are you gonna do for her?
They'll find
her a decent home.
One with a mom who
isn't shooting up.
No, we might as well just
let her get taken then.
Because I'm not
leaving her with you.
Baby come here.
What makes you think,
That you deserve to live
and she deserves to die?
I'm still here, and I have
a right to fight for my life.
Then fight for it!
(Anticipating music)
Momma?
Angie?
Honey?
Are you okay?
[Angie] I don't
feel good, Mommy.
(Crying)
(Door knocking)
(Ominous music)
[Voiceover] This
is the police!
Open up.
Here, come over here.
Help me draw the
symbol on myself.
There is no time,
come over here.
Help me draw the
symbol on myself.
Promise me, promise me,
that when they come,
You blame it all on me,
tell him that it was
All my fault, I just went
crazy, and you don't know
Where I went, tell them
I made you do this.
Tell me, promise me Caitlin.
(Weeping) I promise...
[Voiceover] This
is the police,
What's going on in there?
(Foreboding music)
(Crying)
Thank you...
(Eerie humming)
Caitlin, Caitlin go!
(Rumbling)
(Anticipating music)
Leave her alone!
Let's go to hell, bitch!
(Screaming)
No!
(Anticipating music)
(Coughing)
Angie!
Mommie!
Oh my God...
It's gonna be okay...
Okay, okay...
(Crying)
Come on Angie, we
gotta get going,
The movers are gonna
be here any second.
Ready to go, sweetie?
Let's go, huh?
Come on.
(Foreboding music)
(Anticipating music)
* Oh, this the realest
shit I ever wrote
* No, I'm playing but my
eyes are getting hella low
* I've been smoking hella
dope, life has been incredible
* Traveling around the country
doing things unforgettable
* When it comes down to
it, shit, I'm still a kid
* Younger brother, older sister,
I was just the middle kid
* The middle child, but
I had a little style
* My friends told me I
had something special
* So I spit a while, I spit a
couple of verses for my fans
* I spit a couple of
verses for my fans
verses for the ones
* That knew for certain,
and if I continue working
* The dream will become real
* It never seems real
till it hits home
* And I been on the
road so I been gone
* I remember coming
home from school
* And getting lifted while
I search the internet
* For any piece that
I could spit, uh
* I don't know what's happening
* But I don't know what's wrong
* All I know is
nothing's promised
* And one day it
could all be over
* Around here, I
wanna live my life
* For what it's worth
* Some days good,
and some days bad
* Cause that's just
how it is on Earth
* So, a little bit of
sunshine, a little bit of rain
* Yeah
* A little bit of sunshine,
a little bit of rain
* Yeah
* A little bit of sunshine,
a little bit of rain
* Work, hop in my
car and head to work
* Feel like I'm
falling head-first
* Into the ocean man
* Some days I don't
wanna fucking go again
* Cause work man, I can't do it
* There was something
special out there
* For me and I knew it
* I didn't wanna be
the same as everyone
* So I thought it was me
that's saving everyone
* But that's too much
pressure on a young boy
* Can't do it myself so
I rallied up with convoy
* We know two's
better than one person
* But two don't work if
actually one is hurtin'
* See reality took
away our mortality
* Tried to show us morality
* All they brought was brutality
* And that's the reason why
we still sittin' right here
* Searching for the answer
but it's never getting here
* Keep the dreams
* I don't know what's happening
* But I don't know what's wrong
* All I know is
nothing's promised
* And one day it
could all be over
* Around here, I wanna live
my life for what's it worth
* Some days good
and some days bad
* Cause that's just
how it is on Earth
* So, a little bit of
sunshine, a little bit of rain
* Yeah
* A little bit of sunshine,
a little bit of rain
* Yeah
* A little bit of sunshine,
a little bit of rain
a little bit of rain *