Jeff Speakman
S T R E E T   K N I G HT
(1993),  1hr26min
WMV  25.000 FPS  655 MB
Barett, this Lt Crowe. Check and secure building
Specialty Team will be there in five minutes
Do you copy?
Better make it two, shots been fired
I'm going in
Hang on, man. Help's on the way.
Alright, get out of here. Go on!
Please let her go, please
Don't, Don't, please let her, please / Momm
Freeze! Put your hands where I can see 'em
Now!
You, get away from me
-- Let her go
You make them move back.
Or she's dead.
Cleat the room. Go now.
If You put your gun down,
I'll let her live
Look, why don't you let her go,
take me instead
If you put your gun down,
I will let her live
PUT THE FUCKEN GUN DOWN
[child squeals in fear]
Ok, okay
Push it away
Hah, heh, Now you see there honey
Mr. Policeman is your friend
You want me dead, they all want me dead
-- No, nobody wants you dead
Just let the girl go
-- She wants me dead most of all
Don't do it, listen
Nobody's dead yet
We can all get out of here alive
They ARE trying to kill me!
-- No!
I'm ending this motherfucker!
-- NOO!
effort to expand future prospects regarding arms
roles to Poland and Hungary
And in local news, the weekend was relatively quiet
as rival gangs continue to honor their truce
City officials and community leaders
are encouraged by this sign
As the long wake of violence that has
besieged this city may be coming to an end
A spokesperson for the Police Dept, said
they are taking a wait and see attitude
Nah  -- Come on, man, Don't be a pussy
--- I just don't want it.
Don't tell me you're trying to quit
Shut up!
Check this holmes,
I don't buy this truce shit with the Blades
IDK what Cisco is thinking arranging this
meeting with that fucken mayugo, Willie
But I don't want to get my ass shot up
because you don't know what the fuck to do when
You stay here, and give us five minutes
and then you come and pick us up, comprende
Simon
Hey, say like you have got some huevos,
Faggot ass puto
I understand, Jesus
Are you Jesus?
Who the fuck are you, puto?
- Where's Willie?
-- Willie couldn't make it.
He wanted me to meet with you instead
Shit, I knew Willie ain't got no fucken huevos
He's got this white-ass mutherfucker working for him
So if you're his message boy,
What's his fucken message, boy?
Willie thinks that the fighting between the Lords
and the Blades is a contributing factor
to the breakdown of the moral fiber
in this neighborhood
All he is saying is
Give peace a chance
Who the fuck are you?
-- Get down you fucker, right now
Let the overture begin
Let's do this pendejo
The perfect end to a glorious day
This will end all talk of a gang truce
and keep our friends in the Dept busy
We lost 'im
You'll find him
Lt, looks like a gang massacre
I thought you said there was a truce
Truce my ass. Its blacks vs latinos
It's the same old shit, it ain't never gonna end.
- Well, it's about time that it does end
-- What can you do?
What do you mean, you?
WE are gonna shake down every
gang member in this neighborhood
I don't want a fucken war breaking out,
Do you understand?
We throw a net around the whole area
And you will make sure there
is no retaliations
Look, it ain't gonna help, Lt.
It's a waste of time.
I grew up in these nighborhoods
One day at a time, Fernandez, huh?
One day at a time.
Lucinda, you're early.
Lunch isn't for another hour
Early for what, I hadn't noticed
-- You know you're a lousy poker player
Let's see what we got here:
baked chicken, corn bread, AND apple pie
Now I now I'm in trouble,
what's on your mind Lucinda?
A friend of mine is in trouble.
Her name's Rebeca Sanchz.
I thought maybe you could help her.
What kind of trouble are we talking about here?
-- Car trouble
The only reason why she didn't come here herself
is she's working and her car ain't
I told her I would ask you if would meet with her
and here is her name and number.
You call her now.
Eat your lunch
Tell me -- There's nothing. No word on the street,
the kid split, he's gone
We know he hasn't gone to the police
-- Yet
I don't want anything to interfere with our plan.
I want a name, I want an address.
And I want the war to begin.
I promise if you're really good, I'll ???
-- Thank you  Here we go, -- Okay
Beca Sanchez?
Yeah, you Barett?
Well, you have some information for me or not?
I won't know what to tell you until I take a look at it.
You have it parked around here somewhere?
Do I have what parked around here?
-- Your car.
I don't even own a car
What kind of information are you looking for?
About my brother being missing
IDK what you're talking about. Lucinda told me
you were having trouble with your car
I callled Lucinda this morning and she told me that
she knew an ex-cop who might be able to help
Nww I know why I got the apple pie.
Look, IDK anything about your brother and
I don't do police work anymore.
- I'm sorry
-- No, that's fine
because to tell you the truth I don't
expect much from anyone anyway
fine, well, in that case
I wish you good luck
Hey, Barett, I'll let
you in on a little secret
the police don't do
police work anymore either
shhh, shhh, calmate,  calmate!
estas con familia
-- Who are you? What do you want?
Carlos, Where is he?
I sent him out to do something,
and he never came back -- He's just a kid
What did you get him into?
When he comes back,
you tell him to find me
You leave him alone. He doesn't
want to be part of the Lords
Too late.
Suentenla
[ Let her go ]
Barett, are you okay? Seal off the area
Keep everybody back
Hey, Jake, what about those Dodgers, six in a row..
Yeah, maybe this our year, huh?
Don't move, Don't move I said
or I'll blow you head off
Tu dame el dinero, pronto!
[ Give me the money, quick ]
I'll blow your head off!
You, dude, cargeme el dinero
Apurate
[ Hurry up ]
Andale
[ Go on ]
Damelo todo, damelo
[ I want all of it ]
Damelo todo -- esta bien, todo
Now!
Emilio, How can you charge so much for this stuff?
-- Get down, fuck-head
What're you getting so upset about?
There more orange juice back here
Hey, it's okay, it's okay, easy
You okay?
-- Just a little shook up
Gracias
[ Thank you ]
Que huvo, Barett -- What's the problem, Cisco
- I want to talk to you about what went down last night
Emilio is mi tio, he's my uncle
you did a good job, ese --
Yeah, well, Emilio thanked me last night
I don't want nothing from you man. Besides, I don't believe in freebies.
You saved my Uncle's ass. I'm saying thanks. That's it.
ahh, arrgh,, oww
Paso, Good Morning, ese. You got a friend
who drove a black Ford the other night?
ay, man, IDK nothing about nothing
-- You know what I say you know
And I say you got a friend who drove a black Ford
I asked you a question
-- And I told you, IDK anything, ese
Enough!  Leave Pee-Wee alone
Give me a name, and I'll stop all this.
Otherwise..
I'm gonna let you go. Give a chance to heal,
grab you, and bust you up again.
Let you go, give you a chance to heal,
grab you and bust you up again
If you don't..
Carlos Sanchez!
-- That wasn't so hard, was it?
Now I want an address.  --
the address..
Fuck you!
Hi -- Mr Barrett, I've got no one else,
I need you to help me find my brother
I told you I don't do that kind of work anymore
-- Lucinda tells me that the past two years
you've been helping her and her kids.
Mr Barett, I'm scared
I need you, I've got no one else to turn to
alright, how old is he?
-- Fifteen
How long's he been missing?
-- Two days  - Two days?
well, maybe he's with his girlfriend,
or out with his friends somewhere
Not Carlos, he wouldn't just leave
me without telling me
Even his own gang can't find him
-- He's with a gang?
Yes
-- I'm sorry, I can't help you
Oh, you're some hero, aren't you.
A regular knight in shining armor.
No.  I never was.
You'll have to excuse me now.
You got a problem, Fernandez.
I told you no retaliation.
Make the net tighter. I don't want a goddamn cockroach
to get through. Do you understand, huh?
What's up, 8-Ball?
-- this don't make no sense, dawg.
Well, it makes sense to me.  Motherfucken Lords
have been chewing us up and spitting us out, man.
Word is we been taking the heat for them Lords, man
One time they picked us out
cause the man ain't got no proof
Well, I say we take Cisco and the rest of
them bean-eating Mexicans and pop a cap in they ass
Better chill
-- just fuck taking it chill, Eight
them motherfucken Lords been moving in on
all our business G, and we gotta blast them
Fuck that, man. We're moving now
yo, Willie
Don't you ever tell me what I gots to do.
You got that motherfucker?
Van a pagar, Pee Wee
Look at what they did to our homie, man
Look at him.  Since you started dealing
with that leva 8-Ball
Our homeboys, been getting smoked
Fuck the dumbshit
I say we hit them now
You know what ese, we gotta do them up
Take out those pinche mayates, before
the pigs take over our streets
Alright, we run deep
We get the rest of the homies
Do it now
Rebeca
Look about that stuff that happened
last night at the garage
I'm just glad you called
I can't make any promises, but,
come on let's talk
So where're your folks?
They died when Carlos was five, I was eighteen,
so I brought him up
We're all each other has
You always lived in this neighrbood?
Yes, What about you?
Yeah, all my life
That ballfield over there, my Dad used
to take me there every Sunday
A lot of this have changed since then
Well, in this neighborhood, if you were
a boy and wanted to survive
you joined a gang
Carlos used to be beaten up by gangbangers
every day, coming and going to school
They wanted him to join, kept calling him a coward
Becoming a member was the only way he could remain in school
He's in the Westside Latin Lords, isn't he?
Yes
-- Is Carlos still in school now?
Up till this happened he never even
missed a day of homework
He's a great student. Math, Science
He wants to be an astronomer
It's all he ever talks about, as though life here is
so lousy, He wishes he lived on another planet
Yeah, I know how he feels
Barett,
I need to know. Do you think you could help me?
Let me see what I can find out,
Did you bring that picture of Carlos
Yeah
Ok
You wanted to see me?
-- Carlos Sanchez, I need to find him
Same here, ese. You're asking for his sister, que no?
She's being looked after
If she prays, I hear about it before god does
What's with all the soldiers?
Three months ago, 8-Ball and I
came together to end the war
Two days ago, I sent four of my homies to talk business
and now they're dead.  That same night,
Carlos was there. And now that chavala is missing.
This morning we find Pee-Wee, with fifteen caps up his face
8-Ball wants war, I can have seventy-five hundred
soldiers in one hour
The clicks will roll, Barett. The word will get out.
And this hood will be full of homies in no time.
Do you understand, Barett.  And the lives of everybody
in this hood will never be the same.
This city will burn.
Is that what you want, Cisco?
It's what they want, homes
What're you gonna do if you find out Carlos ran?
-- That's not your problem ese
And so, in conclusion, forensics
began as an inexact science.
But has since, used the cutting edge
of bio-medical technology
to provide for the policeman in the field
the greatest amount of information
with the least amount of evidence
So forensics truly is the best thing to being there
Lady, gentlemen, I thank you,  good day
and so, in conclusion, forensics began
Jake,
-- Hi, Ray -- How you doing?
Good to see you again, man
-- You too, my friend
How you feeling? -- Well, truthfully,
Jake, I'm tired and I'm bored
How are you? -- I'm good, you know
- Don't you miss active duty, just a little bit?
Well, I don't think about it much
-- So, Why you here?
I need to see a police report. The one on that
gang shooting the other night. Seventh Street alley.
You know, if I didn't know better, I would think
you're conducting an informal investigation
Let's see what the machine tells us, let's check it out here.
Here we go, we have one dead black youth,
four dead hispanic youths
ballistics match on the one of the hispanic's
youth guns as the gun which killed the black youth
shell casings all over the ground.
Just another hot day in L.A.
Now this is odd. According to the report,
one group of shell casings had oil deposits
from where fingers touched them,
- Did they run a make on the prints?
well, that's just it, there was oil,
but no fingerprints
I don't get it, Did anybody investigate this?
-- Well, apparently not
Whose signature is on the report?
-- It says here Lt Bill Crowe
You don't think the Dept is involved, do you?
-- I don't know
See what else you can find out for me, if you would,
Hopefully we won't find out any John Does
in the morgue that fits this kid's description
Give me a call later on, will you? -- Ok, will do
- And thanks  -- You got it, Jake
This is going to be an interesting evening
Yo, Barett.  Fuck you doing with
them motherfucken Lords, man?
You got five to tell me what's up
Come on, motherfucker, come on.
I'mma cut you bitch
No, noo, nah, man. Don't you even think about it
You 8-Ball?
--  Right
You Barett, huh? One that runs with the kiddies in the hood
Your set put a hit on me. Why?
-- Been hanging with the them Lords, man
An ex-cop ought to know enough to stay out of the gang business
-- Not interested in your gang business
Cisco is ready to go to war. Cause the other
night you called a meeting, and four of his are gone
Now, what's up?
I ain't done nothing
I lost one last night, and another one
this morning. So all meetings are over
Somethings not right here. They lost
four and you lost two.
Nobody wants to be responsible.  It's gonna
take some time to figure this one out.
Time..  time is something that we ain'ts gots
Heat's on, and we getting burnt
-- Look, you give me two days
I think I can get the same thing from Cisco  -- I thinks not
You wanted a truce!  Nobody benefits from war, 8-Ball
I'll see what's up
How I look ese, ah? Que paso
Ya lookin good mun
Move fast, we're just taking the automatics
My, my, my. Who do we have here?
-- Alright, let's make it quick
Come on, let's load 'em those up
Franklin, we got two birds perching
-- Copy
Ese man, don't mess with the Westside Latin Lords  -- What?
Hey, fool, what's your problem man.
Get off of me, man
You don't know who you fucking with. My brother Willie's
gonna put a cap all over somebody's ass.
That's I'm counting on
Who's this?
-- Willie, por favor
What?
-- Ahorita matamos a tu hermano [ We killed your brother ]
Lo hubiera oir gritar,  Hey Willie, ese,
We just did your brother, ese
You should've hear him scream,,
Pendejo, aay,, Just like a woman
Why did you leave the force, Barrett?
-- That shop I've got used to belong to my Dad
Fixing cars with him, was one
of the best times of my life
You didn't leave the force to fix cars
About three years ago, there was a situation
Some psycho took an eight-year old hostage
When I put my gun down, the son-of-a-bitch killed her
So when I got out of the hospital,
I left the force and came home
All of my life, I've lived scared in these
streets, scared for myself, scared for Carlos.
It's no way to live
And then the President added, with economic
indicators on the rise
even though there were some difficulties ahead,
the country's prognosis is a healthy one
In local news, it looks like the
gang truce is definitely over
Two men were killed last night when a gun
warehouse was robbed in Downtown Los Angeles
One of the men found dead at the scene,
belonged to the South Central Blades gang
And according to witnesses, the robbery and murders
were committed by members of the rival gang, the Westside Latin Lords
And in city hall today, Councilwoman Lana Lee
proposed restrictive anti-smoking
This is your idea of a truce?
I told you those goddamn mayugos can't be trusted
You're not gonna be happy till you have a fucken war, are ya?
What're you talking about, they just blasted us, Barett!
You hit a wharehouse last night, and you killed a Blade
Why?
-- What're you talking about?
I gave you two days, I haven't touched
those goddamn chanates!
There were witnesses describing..
For the last time, puto. I put this on my mother.
IDK what the fuck you're talking about
But as soon as those pigs go back to Winchell's, it's on
Fuckers are having to learn to respect me, man
A gun doesn't get you respect, Willie.
-- Don't front on me man. Them motherfuckers killed my brother
And they fixing to pay, now
-- The Lords didn't kill your brother
You can't stop me, man.  Eight-ball can't stop me.
The man can't stop me.
How're you gonna stop me? -- Listen to me,
you're gonna start a war for no reason
Somebody's messing with you and the Lords.
Somebody else killed your brother, Willie
Now, I need a meeting with 8-Ball,
and I need it now.  It's up to you.
Give me a reason to respect you, man
The truck'll be ready tonight?
-- A couple of hoses, new shocks, she'll be ready
We still had no luck finding Sanchez.
But I have feelers out everywhere.
I want double shifts on the streets. And I want
pay-offs made at all the schools and hangouts.
I want every rock turned over, and every door kicked in.
I want Carlos Sanchez.
We still have a problem. -- A problem?
-- A guy named Barrett
Willie was supposed to take out Cisco, but,
Barett stepped in and stopped it
Word is, this guy Barett is an ex-cop
Jake Barrett ?
-- Right  -- You know him
I know of him. Graduated Stanford, the top of his class.
He's a highly decorated cop
He even got the Mayor's Commendation award the same year I did.
But now, he's dysfunctional
kid was killed in an incident,
he felt guilty. He quit the force
Now he's wasting his life,
doing penance for kids on the streets
But he's part of the equation I didn't count on
(John) Kane, (Charles) Lovinger, take care of him.
Make it look like a gang hit
Hello -- Hi, it's me. I was
thinking about what you asked for
Something about Carlos and IDK
if this means anything but
something Carlos always used to
say to me was, "Esta en paz"
He found peace with the stars.
He was always looking to the heavens
We'll find him, Rebecca. -- I, I just wish
there was something more I could do
I'll call you back later, okay?
Yeah? -- Go downstairs to your garage, now. Don't ask any questions,
I'll be there in about ten minutes -- Jake?
We'll, what a pleasant surprise
-- There's another one in the back seat
Remember those shell casings?  -- Yeah
-- oil, no fingerprints.  Here's why, look at this they used acid to remove them
and this guy dyes his hair, he's wearing colored contact lenses.
these guys went through a lot of trouble to hide their identities
They tried to kill me tonight. They're professionals.
I need to know who they are, Ray
Well, this guy's had major surgery.  That's a start.
Look, I need to keep this between you and I, know what I'm saying?
-- Hey, I'm up for this, I'm in.
So what're you gonna do?
Are you okay?  --  Yeah
I need to find Carlos Sanchez.
He's the missing piece
How many guards in Section C and D?
-- In section C, only one, we terminate
there's an add'l maintenance man ten yards past the freight elevator,
it'll be closing time, so he won't be too alert, we terminate
We follow the ramp 12.3 yards until we hit Section D.
We can expect no more than three guards, we terminate
That's it
A few more jobs like this and we can retire
-- And you thought working for the Dept was fun?
We lost five years in prison, I can't wait to see this city in ashes
Believe me, the crescendo will soon be heard.
It'll burn, it will burn good
Kane and Levinger still haven't checked in
-- Has Barett's body been discovered yet?  -- Nothing on the scanner
Barrett 's dropped out of sight  -- Appears Barrett
is functional again  -- Maybe he just got lucky
I don't believe in luck.  We will take of Barrett in a different way
I just got off the phone with Barrett,
somebody tried to kill 'im last night
He wants to have a meeting with me, right away.
-- Where at?  -- Spanky's
You sure on that, chief?  -- He's down
Barrett's crazy, but he ain't no fool. Besides,
he actually may do something that saves us a lot of time
Ah, haa, now we're getting somewhere.
Remember, once inside the safe, he'll have
two-and-a-half minutes. -- What if it's closed?
If the safe is closed, I'll be inside in four minutes
-- It's too long, make sure it stays open
Eight-Ball in the side pocket  -- Thousand dollars
Barrett's off'd by sunrise  -- Tap's been activated
This is Barrett Auto Body, I can't get to the phone right now, but if you leave your name and number, I'll get back to you
Hey, Jake. Jake, you there? It's Ray  -- Damn  -- Listen I ID'd one of our friends
So get back to me soon as you can, Ok  -- Ray, Ray, it's me, what do you got? -- Are you ready for this?
The guy had a plastic heart valve, it's French made.
Only two places in the country you can get 'em.
Now, I was able to ID him through his blood type and X-rays
-- Alright, where should we meet?
Listen, meet me in the alley at 8th and Atlantic, okay.
One more thing, your hunch was right, my friend
What? cops?
-- I'll tell you about it when I see you
You will never meet Barrett
Hey, Raymond
Ray!
Jake... my pocket
Ok, Ray, I got it
Now it's my turn
Let's get the fuck out of here --  Move it
- You honky, motherfucker
Hello  -- It's Jake Barrett
- Hey, Jake, How you been?
It's been a long time, huh?
-- What the hell is going on, Crowe?
well, there's been a murder, you've been ID'd
as the shooter -- Who's been murdered?
a gang member, named 8-Ball.  Listen Jake, why don't we sit down huh?
We'll meet, talk this over, see what's going on
Sorry, I'm not up for conversation right now Crowe
-- Jake this is serious
yeah, I know. And don't bother tracing the call
-- Jake? Jake!
Get 'im!
Yes  -- No luck on Carlos,
but we found his sister
I just need an address
-- 1824 Delaney, we'll pick her up
No, no, no. I'll handle this myself
Excuse me, -- Yeah
-- You seen this kid around here?
It's okay, I'm a cop
-- Yeah, I know where he is
Ms Sanchez?  -- Yes  -- I'm officer Green,
I gotta talk with you  -- About what?
It's about Jake Barrett. We used to work together,
not too far from here. I need to talk to him.
Try directory assistance
-- Yeah, Jake told me about you
He said you're someone who can be trusted.  The Dept is looking for Jake,
they have this crazy idea that
crazy idea that he's involved in the murder of a gang member.
He's in trouble, I've gotta warn him
What is your badge number, Officer Green?
3-5-6-2
Charlotte, easy!
Thank you
-- I got two of my own, Jake also likes kids
They say the motive for the murder was Jake was
trying to get information on a missing boy... your brother
I'm very sorry to upset you
Officer Green, he called me this morning
He went to Griffith Park
Charlotte, where's Rebecca?
Carlos?  My name is Jake Barrett.
I'm a friend of your sister's.
I'm here to help you
I'm not here to hurt you, Carlos.
I'm gonna put my gun down, okay?
You,, you don' know my sister!  -- Yes, I do
-- You don't know my sister!
That's how I knew you were here, estar en paz
I know something terrible happened that night,
I'll take care of it
You don't have to be afraid anymore, Carlos
-- I'm tired
I don't want to be running no more
You and me both
Officer,
Not again
I was scared, man
He was killing everybody,
I didn't know what to do
You think you can identify him?
-- I'll never forget his face, man
The look in his eyes... he wanted me dead
The problem is, I can't go back
See, I didn't do anything, I didn't help my homeboys.
I ran. They're going to kill me.
Not when they hear the truth, Carlos.
That there was nothing that you could've done
So we have something in common.
I've been through this before.
We're not goint to have to run anymore
It's this shack, let's check it out
You usually hear cars around here -- No never.  The cops
only come around at night, to check things out
I need you to hang tough.
Try to get us out of here
This way
We've sighted the target, we're in pursuit
-- Come on
There!
Faster, faster, come on!
get up, man
yeah, alright!
Hello? - Lucinda, it's Jake
-- Rebecca is gone
What do you mean, she's gone? -- IDK, I thought it was the police
but when I called them,
they didn't know nothing about it
then I got a call from someone who says he wants you
to bring Carlos down to the
train yard tonight at nine, alone
And then work out a deal, What're you gonna do, baby?
Whatever it takes
John Cain, ahh, the guy with the artificial heart
Joined the LAPD in '78, convicted of corruption and brutality
served five years with seven other officers
Charles Levinger, Harvery Cruise,
Holy shit,  James Franklin
Captain Special Forces, military
intelligence three years...
LAPD, decorated,, led unit two years in arrests.
Commander of Operation Dropkick.
Infiltrated gang activity, in secret...
ahh, wait.  That's him, that's the
one I saw in the alley.  -- Are you sure?
Like I said, I'm never gonna forget that face, yeah, I'm sure
okay, Raymond.  Where can I find him?
I want you to stay here, tonight.  I've got
some stuff I gotta take care of
They've got my sister, don't they?
Yeah, they got her
They want me to take you to the train yard tonight
-- Then, I'm coming with you  --- No, you're not
They'll kill you on sight -- What about my sister?
-- She's safer without you there
She's the bait.  Unless they find you, she's safe
But I can't just...  -- Look, I don't
have time to argue with you
about this.  Emilio is waiting
Look, he understands everything.
I need you to stay here tonight
Alright  - Hey
-- Don't worry,  I'll handle it
You like my sister?
Yeah, sure, I like your sister.
-- You wanna know something man?
What? -- You're not good enough for her
He's probably right
This is your room.  This used to be my
son's room before he got married
Mi casa es tu casa
Thanks
All secure
Roger, we're proceeding as planned.
We're on our way
Tunnels..
Vaults...
Hey, Barrett
I've been waiting for this
Where is she?
Where is she?!
You're not that big, Think about it
Fuck you!
Come on!
618 Olive, October 19. That's today!
You guys with New Shield Plumbing!
- Yeah we got a call about a leak
Yours
Put him in the van
Clear!
Hey, Lt., you just got a call about a 211 in progress
at Alameda Mall (?)  -- Who made the call?
Jake Barrett
Come on, let's take a ride
Everybody eyes on the floor, and you will not be harmed
Silence!  Do not move, and you will not be harmed!
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
Bingo!
Stauts?
-- All clear
Time!
20 seconds to the elevator
Let the fat lady sing
Let's go!
Move it!
That's it, back it up, back it up, facing the wall
Excuse me, one second
--  Yeah?
Would you make sure that Lt. Crowe gets this please?
-- Yeah, sure  -- Thank you
He's alone, he didn't bring the kid
-- That was to be expected
We'll use the girl to smoke out her brother
Take him out,  Barrett(?)
Guys
Very slowly, toss the gun away
One time,  Where is she?
Think about it
Hey Barrett, you should've brought the kid!
hah shit!
You've been setting us up all along, man
My brother ain't coming home again
He's fucken finished
Let's get them other motherfuckers
That was for Jesus, and my homies
A familiar situation, ay Barrett?
Let her go.
You know the routine, Barrett
Put down the gun..., and I'll let her live
Put down the fucken gun
Loose it
You never could make the right decision
Wait, wait... we're not clear.. wait
It ends tonight, Barrett!
You wouldn't shoot a man in the back, would you?
-- The fuck I wouldn't...
Good night, sweet prince,. And flights of angels sing thee to thy rest!
Shakespeare ( Hamlet Act 5 Scene 2)
Jake!
Hasta la vista, baby!
-- Schwarzenegger ( 1991, Terminator 2)
You okay? -- I'm okay
Becca, you alright?
I'm okay
Did you do all this?
Yeah,
I explained to everybody what was going on
How they were being set up... I convinced them
Hey Barrett
Make sure you come in and file a statement
You'll find the statement forms,
right next to the re-instatement forms
I'll think about it
-- You do that
What do you got?
Officer Moe, will you please
get this creep out of here
This is a night, I'll never believe it
Like I said Fernandez,
One day at a time
THIS FILM IS DEDICATED TO THE UNITED KENPO
FAMILY AND FOR GANG TRUCE EVERYWHERE