- ( Alarm blaring )
- ( Rumbling )
- ( People clamoring )
- ( Glass shatters )
( Man yelling )
( Creature growling )
- ( Static buzzes )
- ( Screaming )
( Beeping )
( Overlapping radio
transmissions )
( Woman speaks over radio )
( Inhales )
( Exhales )
- Where we at?
- ( Taps keys )
He's dropping in five.
What's up,
little sister?
Where's this moppet at?
( Whirring )
- Man: I hope he enjoys himself.
- All right, here we go.
- ( Switch clicks )
- ( Explosion )
Shit.
( Clicking )
Your middle name should
have been "abortion."
He at
the shoot house yet?
He's pretty close.
We made it impossible though.
- Eight rounds, nine targets.
- That's not very nice, Henry.
Yeah yeah,
he shot Michael.
It's way too soon.
Way fucking too soon.
All right, here we go,
last room.
- Oh!
( Laughing )
- Why don't you ever do that?
- Fuck you.
Bring him in.
( Switches clicking )
( Camera whirs )
Man #2 on intercom: "G"!
Enjoy your run
back to base.
( Gunshots )
( Man humming )
( British accent )
Top man!
Oh, thank you.
- Preston.
- Jonathan...
- Gates.
- Seriously, who throws
a fucking pistol, mate?
Just seemed like the thing
to do at the time.
- Banger?
- Absolutely.
Good, how you doing?
Good to see you, gates.
- You too, Henry.
- We've gotta get the rest
of your paperwork
- ironed out. Locke's inside.
- Roger that.
- Hang tight on that.
I'll be back.
- No worries.
Oi!
Food's ready.
- ( Radio playing music )
- Well, this is home.
- I like it.
- This is "v."
Hi, how you doing?
- He's shy.
- Man: Gates!
You, my friend,
are a complete
fucking psycho.
- Henry: He's certainly got--
- don't you have some goddamn
paperwork to do?
- Henry: You got some
child support to pay?
- Man: Fuck you.
- Welcome to the blackjacks.
- Thank you, sir.
Follow me.
I have thrown
a pistol before,
but never
in a shoot house.
Yeah, me neither.
I almost
didn't do it.
It held up pretty well.
Springfield.
- I'm a Kimber man myself.
- Gates: I like Kimber.
- ( Gun clicks )
- Springfield just feels right.
So, gates,
what was your monthly
take-home in the army?
- 4170 with b.A.H.
- Mmm.
Our minimum contracts
are six figures apiece.
The thing is
I've seen a lot of guys
lose their shit
when they start making
that kind of money.
Trust me, you're gonna
need help figuring out
what to do with it.
I know a few bean counters.
They'll get you squared away
and make sure you don't
blow it up your nose.
Appreciate it.
- You got some talent.
- Thank you.
Talent just tells me
that you can.
What concerns me
is if you will.
I got one rule, gates.
Never question me.
Welcome aboard.
( Beeping )
( Water rushes )
( Water rushing )
( Distant barking )
Miss!
We already checked
that whole South sector.
Jesus!
Smith, over here!
Don't worry, sir.
We'll get you out of here.
( Beeping )
( Distant barking )
( Water running )
- ( Bird cawing )
- ( Barking continues )
( Wind gusting )
( Machinery whirring )
Hi.
( Beeps )
( Keyboard clicking )
You get any sleep
last night?
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Alison.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not.
It's just that...
There has to be
something else we can do.
- Like what?
- We could do nothing.
I did this.
I cannot let anyone else
be responsible
for its outcome.
It's too valuable.
Is it worth it?
- I miss your mom.
- Me too,
- and I want to go home.
- We are going home.
( Chimes )
( Beeping )
Hey.
( Machinery whirring,
crackling )
( Shower running )
( Alarm blaring )
( Beeping, alarm stops )
( Latches clicking )
- Man: Of course
I'm a cutthroat.
- ( Camera clicking )
You don't get
to where I'm at
by being a pussy.
I'm unapologetically
ruthless,
or ruthlessly unapologetic,
but there's no mystery there.
You don't need that
for the article.
Why don't you
get to the point
and ask me what
you came here to ask me?
What did I come here
to ask you?
You want to know
where Dr. Whitmore is.
Okay.
One of the finest energy
researchers in the country
has been missing
for... nine months.
Where is
your former partner?
- I don't know.
- ( Camera continues clicking )
We think
he was kidnapped.
What I do know
is we have
a $3.5 million effort,
and the finest people
in the world
are looking for him.
Why don't we take
a few pictures...
In the bedroom?
Woman: Sir?
- There's a situation.
- Mm-hmm.
Give me 19 minutes.
We don't have
19 minutes.
( Camera clicking )
Mmm, this interview...
Is over.
( Whirring, crackling )
- ( Alarm blaring )
- ( Rumbling )
( People clamoring )
( Whooshes )
( Creature noises )
( Alarm continues )
( Snarling, screeching )
( Snarling )
( Screams )
( Sobbing ) No.
( Screaming )
( Growls )
Tell me... everything.
We lost all communication
with the facility
approximately
26 minutes ago.
We were alerted
when the reactor
started producing
dangerous levels
of energy.
Just as we got online,
the entire facility went dark.
When can
we be back online?
We can't,
not from here.
Someone has to
re-establish communication
from the inside.
Fuck!
Whitmore has something
to do with this.
We should terminate
the project.
- I can fix this.
- Sir, if this gets out--
I'm not gonna blow up
a billion-dollar facility
just because
the phones are down.
I want the best
combat extraction team available
to go in and get me Whitmore.
I don't care what it costs.
( Engines revving )
( Cellphone buzzing )
- Hey.
- Locke: Hey.
Get to the airstrip.
Now?
Yeah.
( Jet roaring )
- What's taking so long?
- Just waiting for a signal.
Should be about
five minutes, sir.
Henry:
You guys got me?
Locke:
We got you, Henry.
Cromwell:
We don't have time
for formalities.
Apparently
your team is the best,
so I've hired you.
To the point:
Two days ago
i lost contact with
an off-the-books facility
Now if you watch the news,
you would know my partner
Dr. mark Whitmore
has been missing
for some time.
He's not.
He's here working for me
at this very location.
The following is the last
footage we have of him
before the drop
in communication.
- ( Alarm blaring )
- ( Rumbling )
There was seismic activity
at the time of the recording.
It might be the reason
for the drop.
I don't care.
I just need to know he's alive.
I've lost contact
with above-ground security
that guards the entrance.
Link up with them
- ( Door closes )
- I understand your team
has worked
with psychic operators
before.
Lisa westbrook is
the best in the business.
If Whitmore is down there,
she will find him.
Don't fuck this up.
Please.
I'll be in your ears
till you reach the base,
then we're going to be black
until you fire up the link
underground.
Roger that, Henry.
- ( Chuckles )
- Miss westbrook?
Lisa, please.
It's fairly straightforward.
I just need to get close enough
to get a lock on the doctor.
And once I have positive I.D.,
you will get him and get out.
Exactly how
are you going to "lock in"
on their location?
So I round the corner, right?
And this fucking guy
is shirtless
and he's holding back
four of these huge
Brazilian dudes,
guns drawn,
and he's got a knife to
the throat of the bouncer
and I'm like, "Jesus.
What the fuck have I
stumbled into?"
- Preston: They were
puerto rican.
- Ed: What?
Hey, I got this round.
- Preston: Thanks, gatesy.
- Ed: Fuckin-a, new guy.
Right on.
Make it a double!
- Can I get you something?
- No thanks.
I got one.
Can I ask you
a question?
( Sighs ) Sure.
How long have you
been psychic?
Or whatever the gift is
that you have.
Why?
Sorry.
Didn't mean to pry.
No no, it's--
it's fine.
My mom has
some sort of gift.
She gets these feelings
about things.
- Empathic.
- Yeah, maybe.
But it was kinda rough
growing up like that.
I can't even imagine
what it was like for you.
You know,
you don't strike me
as the operator type.
( Team laughing, chatting )
Ed:
Yo, v, what is up?
Nice!
Where are we going, huh?
You want to get
out of here?
Yeah,
the air force is full
of alternative units.
- Do they recruit or what?
- Uh-huh.
My first unit was
a remote viewing squadron.
- And what was your job?
- I worked with a lot
of para-rescue guys.
You know, finding
downed pilots and such.
- Oh.
- And then the last few years
I worked strictly with
a snatch-and-grab team.
Like kicking in doors?
Yeah.
Well, I was there
more to find the target,
obviously.
So why'd you get out?
I, um...
I did some things that
I wasn't proud of.
So tell me how it works.
- What?
- Finding people.
Okay, so your body
gives off a vibration
that I can feel.
And everyone's is
slightly different.
And you can feel this
anywhere in the world?
Oh no no no.
I mean, I can only do it
- within a mile or so.
- Oh.
Here, watch.
- ( Distorted static )
- Oh shit!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to freak you out.
No, that's--
that's incredible.
Can you do that again?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can't do it
for very long though.
- ( Distorted static )
- Jesus.
- Oh God, I'm so sorry.
- ( Hisses )
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What was that?
That's never
happened before.
Are you sure
you're okay?
( Chuckles )
Yeah, you know, I'd better...
- Go to bed.
- Yeah.
Sorry about
your finger.
( Distorted snarling,
screeching )
( Machinery whirring )
Man: Oh.
- ( Snarling )
- Oh!
( Screeching )
( Screams )
There you go, swag monkey.
Good boy.
( Clinks )
( Engines humming )
I can't believe you're
actually jumping with us.
I hope you don't burn in.
I only weigh 100 lbs.
I'd just bounce off the ground.
( Laughing )
- ( Beeping )
- All right, blackjacks!
Don't be pussies.
( Cackles )
That's cute.
Are you gonna walk
10 paces behind us?
Are you gonna button
your fly?
Preston:
Underwear, mate.
Knock it off.
Let's go.
It chafes too much.
- Locke: "Men in black."
- Will Smith.
"Independence day."
Brent spiner.
Who the fuck is Brent spiner?
( Chuckles )
He was
the scientist dude.
Challenge.
Brent spiner was
data on "Star Trek:
The next generation."
You are such
a fucking nerd.
( Birds cawing )
- So what do you do for fun?
- ( Laughs )
- Just making small talk.
- Shh shh shh.
- What's up?
- Hold on a second.
( Thunder rumbling )
- Locke: What's up?
- I'm picking up
a group of people
about a mile away.
- Can you tell
who they are?
- No.
They're all males.
There's about 15 of them.
Henry, any chance we can
get eyes on location?
Lisa's picking up
targets nearby.
Negative, Locke.
Your sat's still down.
You know what?
Let me see what
I can piggyback on.
Locke, wait one--
there's a Russian satellite.
I'll give it a shot.
Locke, I got eyes on,
but the image is
completely scrambled.
Roger.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
Hey, v.
I need you right there.
Ed, Preston.
You guys post up
right here.
- Lisa?
- Yeah?
You're with v.
She can tell us
where everybody is.
Stay at least
40 meters behind me.
And don't give away
my position.
Okay.
Gates.
You're with me.
( Thunder rumbling )
Locke:
What do you think, v?
- Looks like a merc group.
- Gates: They're chechen.
I've seen
their kind before.
Yusufiyah '05.
They're nasty.
I've had some experience
with these clowns as well.
( Whimpering )
V:
Hey, they have
an American down there.
- Locke: Henry.
- Go ahead.
We have eyes
on location.
There's a group
of hostiles on the ground.
Hey, I've got casualties
in the west corner.
Looks like they've killed
the security detail.
There's one left alive.
V: Locke.
I'm gonna drop
this motherfucker.
He's about to take
this guy down.
V:
I say again,
i have the shot.
Locke:
Negative.
Don't compromise your position.
We can't maneuver
from here.
Gates:
Locke, they're gonna
kill this guy.
- V: We're running
out of time.
- Stand down.
You take that shot,
we'll have 20 a.K.S
lighting this hill up.
Henry, you tell cromwell
we're taking
these fuckers out.
Henry:
That's a go, Locke.
- All right.
- V: Fuck!
God damn it,
God damn it.
Fuck!
All right, we're gonna
secure this compound.
V, you wait for us
to get into position,
then on my signal
start putting fuckers to sleep.
About fucking time.
Gates and I will lead.
Ed, Preston, you two
follow and flank.
Let's get as close as we can
before we go loud.
Lisa, tell me how many targets
are down there.
16 total targets.
Most are
in the main building.
All right, gentlemen,
nothing fancy.
Straightforward
violence of action.
Let's go.
Locke: Go hot
in three...
Two...
One.
( Yelps )
( Shouting )
Motherfucker!
Fuck, ed.
Locke:
V, a little help!
I don't got a shot
on the guys inside.
V, there's three coming around
the back of the building.
- There's nothing there.
- Just wait, they're
coming around.
Lisa, don't let
that fucker flank us!
- Gates?
- Clear!
All clear, Eddie.
V, we're coming out.
( Clicks )
( Distorted static )
( Locke groans )
( Groaning )
Get away from me.
Ed:
Blackjack!
Don't say
a fucking word.
Never shoot through
a fucking door, fuck!
- All right, all right.
- Motherfucker!
Getting a bit old
for this, Locke, eh?
- Fuck you!
- He's hit.
Just cover it.
Lisa, are we
clear down here?
No one around
but you guys.
All right, v, bring it in.
Ed:
These assholes stink.
Look what I found.
Oh shit.
- Henry.
- Go ahead.
The chechens were here
for Whitmore.
We found his pictures
on one of them.
- What? Did they
find the entrance?
- No.
It was covered
when we got here.
- ( Locke groans )
- Cromwell: Fuck!
Okay, tell me
when you have him.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Get it off.
( Beeping )
Shit.
On me.
Hey, hold up.
Can I take a look
at that map for a second?
Gates, map.
All right,
so I'm picking up
what looks like
the reactor right there.
It's giving off
a lot of interference.
And I'm picking up what
I think is Dr. Whitmore
right here.
He's in the lab area.
Good.
I'm not picking up
anyone else down here.
It doesn't matter.
Our mission's the doctor.
- We get him, we get out.
- Gates: Roger that.
On me.
It's blood.
Somebody was pissed off.
You don't have to worry
about it. There's no one
else down here.
I think
we've got it, westbrook.
- Clear left!
- ( Grunts )
Clear right!
- Ed: Center clear.
- Room clear.
What the fuck?
Are you sure you're not
picking up anybody?
No one.
Tell me when
he gets close.
100 meters.
On Eddie, let's go!
Move out.
Which way, gates?
Okay, left takes us
to the comm room.
And if we head right
that should take us down
to the lower research lab.
Eddie.
Take Preston, go left,
set up comms.
We'll grab the target
and meet you there.
Be fast. I don't want
to be here all day.
Are you sure you want
to separate?
Yeah, I'm sure.
- Westbrook!
- Yeah?
You're positive
he's down this way?
Gates.
V.
- ( Rattling )
- ( Creature snarling )
- Clear.
- Fuck off.
Is it gonna work?
I sure as shit hope so.
- Bingo.
- ( Laughs )
( Keyboard clicking )
- Clear left.
- Clear right.
Room clear on me.
- He should be right about here.
- Locke: Go go.
Whitmore!
Dr. Whitmore.
Open the door!
- No.
- Locke: Open the door.
Cromwell sent us.
Open the door.
( Whitmore mutters )
- ( Bangs )
- Open the fucking door.
No.
( Keyboard clicking )
I got you, ed.
You got picture?
Ed, do you have video?
Do you have audio?
- Ed!
- I heard you
the first time, fuckstick.
Hey, I'm not paying you
to fuck around!
Show some respect.
Where's Whitmore?
The rest of our team
are acquiring him.
- They'll be here shortly.
- All right, what's the status
of my facility?
Unknown. From what
the psychic tells us
there's no one here
except the doctor.
- There's nobody down there?!
- No.
- Son of a bitch.
- ( Bangs )
The doctor should
be here shortly, sir.
Find him.
Find him!
( Pounds on window )
Hey, Whitmore,
open the door!
Dr. Whitmore?
Dr. Whitmore, look at me.
Look at me.
I need you to open
the door for us.
Can you do that for me?
We're here to protect you.
Can you open the door?
( Whispers )
V:
Open the fucking door.
( Yelps )
You gotta--
you gotta close the door.
I'm sorry-- ow!
Ow!
Close the door!
You have
to lock that door!
You have to lock the door!
- Close it,
please please please.
- Do it.
You comfy?
( Bangs )
I'll get it, I'll get it.
Ahh.
( Whitmore grunting )
What happened down here, doc?
Where's your staff?
V: Hey!
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
( Distant bang )
( Snarling, screeching )
- ( Garbled noise )
- Cromwell: What are they doing?
Preston, can I get
an e.T.A. On the doctor?
Yeah, hold on a sec.
- ( Squelches )
- Ed, what the fuck?!
Preston:
Contact, contact!
- Whitmore: No,
I'm not going out there!
- Let's move, move move move!
- I'm not going out back there.
- ( Gunshots )
Preston:
Ed! ( Screams )
Preston!
Motherfucker!
Preston, Preston,
wake up.
Preston, hey!
Come on, Preston!
Fuck!
Come on, man, come--
move move
move move!
( Grunts, gasping )
- Breathe breathe.
- Ed, ed, ed!
- Oh shit.
- Gotta breathe,
gotta breathe, come on.
Breathe breathe breathe.
Come on,
let's get up.
You can stand.
Ready?
Let's go.
Get him the fuck
in there!
Henry:
Ed? Fuck!
Locke, they got ed!
Who got ed?
What the fuck
happened, Whitmore?
Ed, ed!
Ed!
( Squelches )
- ( Snarling )
- ( Gunshots )
( Screeching )
( Gunshots continuing )
Fuck.
Come on, gates.
Fuck. Come on.
Cromwell:
Whitmore.
- Whitmore!
- Talk, fucker.
There was an accident.
Henry:
Locke, where's ed?
- Shut the fuck up.
- You shut the fuck up!
Henry, calm down.
I need you
to get us out of here.
Don't lose your head.
- Cromwell: Whitmore!
- Whitmore: There's some
kind of creature
running loose down here.
It killed everybody.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
- Henry.
- What, the entire
staff is dead?
Whitmore:
Everybody.
Cromwell, you get
that door open!
Cromwell, open that
fucking door!
All right.
V?
V.
Henry!
- ( Gunshot )
- ( Groans )
( Groans )
You motherfucker!
Fucker!
( No audible dialogue )
...fucking kill you.
Goddamn motherfucker!
( Keyboard clicking )
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
( Shouting )
Motherfucker!
Goddamn motherfucker!
Fucker!
V.
We'll fix it.
Let's finish this mission.
Gear up.
We need an exit.
Ideas?
- Blow the door?
- We don't have enough c-4.
Plus it's
a fucking shaft.
Tell us how to get
out of here.
- Take me with you.
- V: He'll slow us down.
- You want to go or not?
- Hey!
Fucking cooperate
with us, all right?
Just cooperate with us
and we will get you
out of here,
you understand that?
There's a tunnel
at the far side of the complex
leading into the valley.
Show me.
- That's a tunnel?
- Yeah.
All right,
I can get us there.
- Alive, I hope.
- Locke: That depends on you.
What are we up against
out there?
It came through the reactor.
I developed a machine
that could capture
ribbons of energy
in a parallel dimension.
Cromwell was funding it.
But three months ago
he started to threaten
me and my daughter,
and I knew that
if I delivered him
the complete works,
I would be dead.
So I overcharged the reactor
causing a distraction,
during which I was
supposed to meet
a rescue team that would take me
over the Russian border.
Your rescue party was
a group of chechen terrorists.
No! No no, they were just
supposed to escort me.
I had to get somewhere where
cromwell couldn't get to me.
Focus.
Describe it.
Is it biological?
Is it mechanical?
What is it?
I only saw it
for a moment.
To come through the portal,
I think it has to be
biological.
- Why didn't you
pick that up, huh?
- I don't know.
- That's your job!
That is your job!
- I don't know, okay?
It's not giving off
anything I can pick up!
I'm sorry.
Whatever that thing is,
let's headed for the tunnel.
Staggered formation,
keep your heads on a swivel,
360 at all times,
watch your overheads
and put rounds
in anything that moves.
Let's go, come on.
( Snarling )
- Locke: Preston!
- I'm all right.
( Low growling )
( Growls )
( Bangs, screeches )
( Screeches )
Let's move!
Move move move!
Come on! Go go go!
( Beeps )
( Beeping )
- Gates!
- Clear!
- Gates?
- Clear.
V:
Clear right.
- Preston?
- Clear!
V:
All clear.
Watch up top!
- What the fuck
was that thing?
- ( Lisa coughs )
- Are you okay?
- ( Alarm blaring )
Aw, no.
No no no no no.
- What's going on, doc?
- He's overloading the reactor.
It's-- it's gonna fracture.
This whole place is
gonna implode.
- Shut it down.
- I can't shut it down!
Gates:
All right, how much
time do we have?
Nights on!
There's no point.
He cut the power.
- Locke: So what?
- So...
You don't understand.
We cannot open the door
- without power.
- There's always
a backup generator.
You just gotta find it.
Yes yes yes,
right there, right there.
- That is
a generator, I know it.
- V: It's far.
- No, we can make it.
- We gotta move.
No, listen listen.
I'll get the power on.
- I'll meet you guys
at this door right here.
- No no no.
- We stay together.
- Do it.
Are you sure you want
to split us up again?
'Cause we're a lot more
effective together.
We lost ed, you saw
what happened to Preston--
what the fuck
is wrong with you?
Fuck, think outside
of the fucking box!
God damn it!
Listen to me
very carefully.
Right or wrong,
I make the decisions
for this team.
You follow orders
or you're free
to go on your way.
Is that clear?
Yeah.
Okay.
Do it.
Let's go.
( Beeps )
I'm picking up something
coming in fast.
- Where?
- It's right in front of us.
It's closing.
Put rounds on this thing
till it's down!
Lisa:
It's closing.
It's closing!
Wait wait,
it's a female!
Hold your fire!
Cover.
Covering.
- Locke: Stay down!
- ( Yelps )
Who are you?
Whitmore:
Alison? Alison!
- Oh oh.
- ( Sobbing )
- Who is she, Whitmore?
- It's okay.
- She's my daughter.
- Alison: It's all our fault.
No, we did
what we had to do.
- ( Bangs )
- Check her out, Preston.
- Preston: Are you okay?
- Yeah.
10 seconds, Preston.
Stick with me, yeah?
Let's move.
Move move!
( Chain rattling )
Gates:
Watch your overhead!
Shh shh shh shh.
We'll get out of this, okay?
( Growling )
Locke:
Holding!
- ( Growling )
- ( Gunfire )
( Roars )
- ( Growls )
- ( Alison screaming )
Holding!
- My dad is out there!
- Locke: Clear left!
- Gates: Clear right.
- Locke: Cover!
- Covering.
- Preston: Put your head down,
put your head down.
Okay, get me some light
over here.
- Yeah yeah.
- Some light.
Preston:
Okay, baby,
okay okay okay.
( Shrieks )
I-- I can't
pick up v anymore.
Preston: What?
V!
V?
- ( Snarling )
- V! V! V!
- V!
- ( Beeps )
( Chomping )
- V!
- Is he alive?
I-- I don't know.
You don't fucking know?
I don't know!
I can barely pick up
you guys.
- ( Lisa sobbing )
- This is fucking bullshit.
Get your shit
together, Preston.
What the fuck am I
supposed to do?
- You do your job!
- Gates: No no no, hold it.
I dumped a whole magazine
into that fucker!
So did I.
I'm gonna keep on doing that!
- There's no
rolling fucking dice!
- What options do we have?
Hey hey,
shut the fuck up!
Listen to me!
We can't beat it.
We can avoid it though.
Now get the fuck
down here and hold this
and I'll show you how.
- You got it?
- Yeah, I think.
This tunnel, right here,
that can't be more
than a few feet wide.
I don't think that thing
can fit through it.
But if he does,
we can focus all firepower
into one direction.
- ( Wheezing )
- Gates: All right?
Now it's gonna drop us
just shy of the door.
- You see that?
- Good idea.
Preston, can she move?
She has to. Yeah.
- All right.
- Gatesy, help me out with her.
Three, two, one.
Locke:
Come on, come on,
come on.
- All right, clear.
- Gates: Clear!
Men:
Go go go go!
Lead on.
Preston:
Stay with me.
- ( Sobbing )
- Okay.
- I can't.
- Preston: Come on,
stay with me.
I can't.
( Sobs )
( Coughs )
( Moans )
( Coughing wetly )
Preston:
Sweetie, are you all right?
- Locke: Preston?
- Just wait!
I wanna see my dad.
Where is my dad?
It's all right.
You're gonna see him soon.
( Gasping )
- Good boy.
- Preston: V, you're a beauty.
Locke:
Good to hear your voice, v.
What's your status?
I'm good.
Found a way around.
I'll be there soon.
Hustle.
We're close.
( Rumbling )
Fuck, the reactor!
Get the fuck out of here!
Come on, move!
Gates:
Watch your top.
Watch it.
- Locke: Preston, with me.
- Open left, over left.
- Locke: On me, watch out.
- ( Clicking )
Come on, come on!
- Clear left!
- It's not working!
- Check for a manual override.
Here we go,
here we go.
I think I've got it.
This is it.
Yes!
Yeah, that's it!
That's it!
( Grunts )
Keep going, Preston.
( Yells )
( Snarling )
( Screeching )
( Distant shouting )
Move!
( Screeching )
Get this fucking thing open.
( Clicks )
( Shouts )
( Screams )
( Clicks )
- Gates: I got you.
- ( Creature screeches )
V!
Nice fucking shot.
( Groaning )
( Rumbling )
Oh fuck.
Come on, we gotta get the fuck
out of here, come on.
How many rounds you got?
Gates, how many rounds?!
Nothing, I'm out.
I only got one clip of .45s.
- Locke: Shit.
- ( Gates groans )
Preston, let's go.
( Snarling )
Preston!
Preston's dead.
We've gotta go.
- ( Screams )
- Preston!
- ( Growls )
- He's gone!
Preston, Preston!
Go go!
Go go go go!
You go first.
Go go go!
Hurry, get the fuck
out of here. Fuck!
Come on, Locke.
Come on.
( Screeches )
( Screaming )
Locke! Gates,
get some slugs
over here.
What the fuck?
Shoot, man, shoot.
- ( Gunshots )
- V: What the fuck?
Come on!
- I'm out.
- ( Locke continues screaming )
Shit!
( Screaming )
Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck
out of here!
- ( Screams )
- What the fuck are you doing?
- No no.
- Get the fuck outta here.
- Gates, fucking go.
- No no no.
Fucking go, fucking go!
- V: Get the fuck--
- fuck!
( Screeches )
- ( Distant siren )
- ( Footsteps )
( Deep sigh )
This changes nothing,
you know.
( Distorted static )
( Screams )
And that wasn't my only
base of operations.
Locke's voice:
Talent just tells me
that you can.
What concerns me
is if you will.
( Rock music playing )
♪ If I choose to see you ♪
♪ would you take me
far away? ♪
♪ And would you try
and change me? ♪
♪ And would you want things
your own way? ♪
♪ 'Cause I am ♪
♪ difficult to tame ♪
♪ and I am ♪
♪ difficult to train ♪
♪ and I will ♪
♪ disappear for days ♪
♪ but I-- I will ♪
♪ love you my own way ♪
♪ if I choose to see you ♪
♪ would you make me
your own slave? ♪
♪ And would you
make me suffer ♪
♪ when I don't do
the things you crave? ♪
♪ If I choose to see you ♪
♪ if I choose ♪
♪ 'cause I am ♪
♪ difficult to tame ♪
♪ and I am ♪
♪ difficult to train ♪
♪ and I will ♪
♪ disappear for days ♪
♪ but I-- I will ♪
♪ love you my own way. ♪