- Hiya.
- Hello.
Sure is pretty.
Sure is.
- What's your name?
- Why?
Just curious is all.
It's Lovely.
Is your real name Lovely?
That's the only one I got.
I'm Tom.
Is your real name Tom?
That's funny.
You from around here?
Why are you so curious?
I already told you my name after all.
I got a pretty good reason I suppose.
Oh, yeah? And what might that be?
Because you're just about the prettiest girl
I've ever seen in my entire life.
Oh, yeah? You think so?
I do.
- That's really sweet.
- Thanks.
So, are you from around here?
Oh, God. Pick up! Pick up! Pick up! Pick up!
Please pick up!
- Hello?
- Tom!
- Who is this?
- Tom, it's me!
Lovely, why are you calling here?
- I told you not...
- Listen to me!
Something happened.
It's bad. It's really bad.
Where are you?
The sinner! The defilers!
He's sending them right back to us!
Why?
Because of you.
Because of the sins
that you perform each and every day.
You have sexual relations out of wedlock.
You kill and abort children.
You are a man lying with men.
Same sex marriages.
How do you think your God will judge you?
Well, my brothers and my sisters,
now we know.
Now we know.
When there is no more room in hell,
the dead will...
Hey, kids, welcome back to KZMV.
Hokey Halloween weekend nightmare.
We're rolling through
our annual terror-then.
We're about halfway through
Boris Karloff s 1945 radio play,
The Wailing Wall.
But first...
Still rushing to find
the perfect last minute costume
for your Halloweekend?
Well, why not
head down to Randall's Pennysave
on Jimble road just off
Route 1 in Macon County.
Choose from a wide array
of ghosts and ghouls...
Everything you need
to make this Halloween
the spookiest one yet.
Hello?
It's me.
Tom?
Yeah.
Did you... Did you come alone?
What's going on?
Did you?
Lovely!
Tell me.
Yeah, I did.
You did what?
I came alone just like you asked.
Now open the door.
Hello?
I didn't... I didn't mean to call
you out of the blue like this.
Are you all right?
Tom, would you please
promise me that you'll help.
Tom.
Look, I don't much
like talking about these kinda things
through no door.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna open the door,
but I need you to make me a promise, okay?
What?
I need you to promise that you'll forget
who your brother works for.
- Why?
-'Cause I...
I don't want you calling the police just yet.
Just let me in.
Promise.
All right, fine, I promise.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
What is going on, then?
You're the only one I thought to call.
Is that so?
I knew you'd come.
You wanna tell me
why you called me all the way out
to some rat trap on Route 6,
or are we just gonna
stand out here all night?
I swear I wasn't gonna do it again.
You listen to me, all right.
You gotta tell me what's going on.
So you either open this door,
or I'm gonna turn right around and leave.
'Cause I told you
I was fed up with this shit the last time!
Don't yell at me!
Then you let me know
what you pulled me in to, all right?
What the fuck is that?
I think I hurt him really bad.
How did this happen?
- Answer me!
- How do you think it happened?
Would you keep your voice down?
How'd you get here?
Brenna picked me up and we went to a bar.
Okay, which bar?
Some dive in Madison County.
What was it called?
- I don't remember.
- Well, try to.
Silver Fox.
- The Silver Fox.
- Yeah.
Did Brennatake you here?
- No.
- Well, where is she?
She got really drunk
and called Louellen and they went home.
Who is this man?
Who is he?
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
Is he alive?
I don't know.
This is bad, Lovely.
This is real bad.
No!
- We have to call somebody!
- You can't!
- Are you out of your fucking mind?
- I called you.
Well, I can't help you with this. No way.
You don't even know what happened!
You don't even know!
Get back!
They're gonna blame me for stabbing him!
They're gonna throw me into jail!
You should've thought of that
before you stuck that knife in him.
Is that what you want,
for the police to come down here
and take me away?
I didn't do this to you, you did it to yourself.
-It's not my fault!
- Certainly.
Fuck.
People are gonna say things,
terrible things about me, about us.
Well, your brother's probably
gonna be the one in charge of all this.
He hit me, Tom.
He got real angry and he hit me.
You said you were
gonna never let that happen to me again.
You promised me.
911, what's your emergency?
Don't you bring my brother
into this situation again.
It was never supposed to be like this.
This is so fucked.
I never meant to hurt anyone, Tom.
You know that I wouldn't do that.
What'd you just say?
I said I never meant to hurt anyone.
What, did you think
you were doing me a service
calling me down here? Huh?
- I don't know!
- Of course not.
-It wasn't my fault!
- Yeah, well, it's never your fault.
You don't know what happened.
- Oh, I don't?
- No.
Well I think
I'm pretty learned on the subject.
All right? Same story, different night.
Only this time
you have the audacity to take me here.
So what'd you think, huh?
You think I was just
gonna come down here to the rescue?
After everything that you put me through.
Tell you what. Not a problem here.
After all, it ain't your fault.
But if I don't you threaten to embarrass me.
I mean,
haven't you embarrassed me enough?
Just stop being mean to me, Tom!
You're the only one I called.
What makes you think
I'd do anything to help you?
Because that's what
a husband does for his wife.
You were some wife.
You were some fucking wife!
All right. Okay, listen to me, all right?
You gotta stop crying
and start answering my questions.
All right.
Does anybody know you're here right now?
- You sure?
- Nobody.
Did anybody see you leave the bar with him?
- No.
- Not Brenna? Not Louellen?
No, they left 'cause she was too drunk.
Tom, I already told you so.
And besides,
we didn't even know anybody at that place.
He just came up to me and asked me
if I wanted to go back to his place
and have a drink with him.
Did he check in here or did you?
He did, Tom, this is his room,
I've already told you so.
Okay.
So nobody saw you leave the bar with him.
Right, he checked in here.
Did anybody see you walk up
when you got here?
No.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Fuck.
All right, who is he?
I don't know.
I hate it when you lie to me.
You know,
I don't even know why I'm here right now.
Because we care about each other, Tom.
Don't you do that, all right. Don't you dare.
That statement was rhetorical anyhow.
Because the only thing keeping me
from running out that door right now
is that I'm a fucking accomplice!
I mean I can't exactly leave you here
and pretend it didn't happen, can I?
How many times?
I swear, he was the only one.
How many times
did you stick that knife in him?
He dropped it when I kicked him.
Here you go. Drink up.
I don't know if I should, darling.
The room's all sorts of spinning.
Oh, come on.
There's always room for one more.
You see?
Maybe in a little bit.
It ain't polite
to turn down a gift from the host of a party.
You and me ain't much of a party, sugar.
Someone offers you a drink, you take it.
No whore is gonna
walk into my room and insult me.
Now drink the fucking cocktail.
That's a good girl.
Are you fucking kidding me?
We can do this dance the easy way.
But I prefer to tango just as well.
Come here.
Calm the fuck down.
Calm down. Calm down.
- You're gonna like this.
- No!
Fuck!
Twice?
Yeah.
Fucking hell.
You think he's dead?
Certainly.
But I ain't a professional.
We gotta get rid of him.
Get rid of him?
Hide him somewhere,
bury him or something.
What, are you out of your fucking mind?
I can't do it myself, Tom.
You wanna tell me
how we're gonna carry a man's body
out that door, down those stairs,
past the manager's office and in my truck.
Just you and me.
We can't just leave him here!
Tom!
Tom.
So nobody knows nothing
involving anything
about this situation, right?
For the thousandth time, Tom, yes.
You swear to me?
I swear.
Can you explain the meaning of this?
I guess it never came up.
O key-d o key.
What're you doing?
I wanna know who I'm dealing with
before I make my final judgment call.
I don't wanna make a rash decision
and come to find you killed an undercover.
Well, at least he drives American.
Did you take a sip of this?
What is it?
Looks like your man
had a few party plans of his own.
Come here. We gotta get you cleaned up.
Thank you.
I think I'm gonna go
to hell for what I've done.
Tom...
Just stay here.
Well?
Oh, he's a man of mystery.
Found these, though.
There ain't no bowling ball in that bag.
Bowling seems like it'd be the better option.
No, instead you gotta run off
with a man who's
got a pocketful of sleeping pills
and a video camera in the trunk of his car.
Did he tell you he's going to Hollywood?
- No.
- Well, then how could you be so stupid?
I didn't think I had any other choice.
That ain't true and you know it.
Then tell me, Tom.
Tell me what was I supposed to do!
You were supposed to come home.
Now, let's see what your boy here was up to.
No.
Come on, sweetheart.
Don't you wanna see his other works?
Stop it, Tom.
I want you to come over here
and see what you could've been part of.
You have made your point.
I said, come on!
He was gonna do that to me.
What?
He was gonna bring me here
and his friends
were gonna do the same thing
they did to that girl on the movie.
- All right, just stop talking like that.
- No, it's true.
What if they're...
What if they're on their way here right now?
What if that was their plan all along?
They can be...
Okay, okay, you just calm down, all right?
What if they're coming here to get me, Tom?
That would serve you right!
- You don't mean that.
- All right?
You wanna know if
we were going to hell for what you've done?
Well, you should
take a fuckin' look around you, all right?
You were there,
and you dragged me with you.
All right, okay.
Now, the only option I foresee benefiting us
any which way is we just gotta split.
What?
Split, all right! Leave now!
No, we can't!
They'll find him and they'll know I did it!
Will you stop talking about them!
You don't know nothing about anything.
What about him, Tom?
He will not miss us.
They will come after us!
You're right.
It's better than us sitting around
waiting for somebody to show up, okay?
I mean, it don't matter if it's the police,
the men in that video,
or the Almighty himself, okay?
Look, we'll leave the video camera, all right?
Anybody who watches that tape,
they'll know that
the holes in his chest
were a direct follow-up from that.
Tom.
I don't know.
Let's just hope
nobody saw you here, all right?
Sir?
Sir, is everything all right in there?
Everything's fine.
Well, I heard what I perceived to be
a domestic disturbance
coming from this room, now.
Some signs of distress...
No, everything's good, it's all right.
The missus and I, we were just watching
you know, one of those
Halloween films on marathon too loud.
Is that true, ma'am?
Ma'am, I said, is that true?
I'm gonna have to hear it from you now.
Yes, yes, it's true.
Well,
it's that time of year as the man says that.
I reckon everyone's in for one good scare.
You just keep that volume
on the television turned a bit low,
you know as a courtesy for the other guests.
Thank you.
All right, you have a good
rest of the evening, then.
Now get your things.
Stay close.
No, don't!
But this, this is impossible!
I saw him die with my own two eyes,
I saw him die.
But he cannot ever die.
Once bitten by the beast,
the victim will rise
from the dead and continue to kill.
The people they bite
will get up and continue to kill.
There is no stopping the curse.
There's got to be a way to break the spell.
They said you're the only one who can help.
If one brandishes
the blade against the beast,
the deal will crumble,
as h' it were made of sand.
Only beneath the full moon does...
I used to look forward
to these radio shows when I was a kid.
Never cared much for trick or treatin'.
It's the Halloweekend Frightfest, I loved.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I used to sit around with my grandpap...
Pappy, and he'd tell us,
"Hey, you ankle biters,
you shut up down there.
"Radio show ain't gonna hear itself."
We'd always have to sit real quiet,
'cause Pappy, he couldn't hear so well.
I was always scared right outta my wits.
You never told me that.
But, you know, as strange as it sounds,
somehow, just hearing them,
even as I grew into a man,
something about it
felt comforting, you know?
Not no more.
What? Tom, what is it?
- You have my lighter?
- What lighter?
Your purse! Check your purse!
Get in your purse!
Jesus, Tom!
Hey!
Fuck!
Shit!
You think he's dead?
Certainly.
But I ain't a professional.
Tom!
Shit.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
We shouldn't go back there, Tom.
It's just a lighter.
How many people named Tom Moses
do you think
won the South Texas marksmanship award?
Are you certain you left it?
Maybe you didn't have it
when you came in the room?
I smoked a cigarette in the room, remember?
How can you be sure?
'Cause I bought
a fresh pack on the way down
and there's only one missing.
There's two missing, Tom.
I don't wanna go back there.
We shouldn't go back there.
We can just drive and never look back.
- What'd you just say?
- We can just go, we don't have to go back!
How far did you get
when you ran off with that first clown?
Macon County?
How far you think you're gonna get
with a Texas Ranger hunting after you?
Now, get it through your head, sweetheart.
There ain't no movie stars in Gateswell!
Fuck!
There's no turning back now.
Just wait here.
Don't you want me to come with you?
It ain't your problem anymore.
Okay.
All right.
That's it.
- Tom!
- Get in the truck!
Get in there.
All right.
Come on.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Jesus!
God, you scared me.
I'm sorry I didn't mean to.
I just noticed you could use a light.
Where'd you come from?
Nowhere in particular.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
What are you doing out here?
I'm just waiting for somebody.
It can get mighty quiet out here.
Yeah, it does.
They say this is the closest
the moon's gonna get to us all year.
You know some folks
calls it a harvest moon?
Is that so?
Yeah, that so.
Hey, honey?
Whose car is this?
Why?
Where's Michael?
Tom.
Tom!
What are you doing here?
They're here.
We're coming to get you, beautiful.
Hey, Lovely, all right. Listen to me.
Sweetheart, listen.
I need you to listen to me, okay?
Do you remember that day
we first met on the beach?
Well, you remember I told you
you were the most
beautiful girl I'd ever met?
I meant it.
Okay?
He'll kill us all.
Hey, you listen to me, all right?
Listen.
You think I'd let anybody take away
the most beautiful girl
in the world away from me?
Huh?
Okay.
I need you to take this for me, all right?
Now, anybody gets through that door,
you know what to do.
- All right?
- Okay.
Somebody help us! Please! Please help us!
Please!
Step back.
Lovely! Come here!
All right.
I need you to squeeze through, okay?
I can't fit.
I'm gonna fall!
No, go fast!
Try to hold on.
Lovely, go!
And with the closing of
that cryptic tale of horror...
Boys and ghouls,
we conclude KZMV's
super spooky Halloween weekend...
But don't you fret, in a short, 365...
I've always liked this car.
You know,
Maynard stopped by the other day.
Stop the fucking presses.
It was only for a couple minutes.
It was good to see him.
Couple minutes with Maynard
seems like days.
What'd the little son of a bitch
have to say for himself?
Nothing much, nothing much.
Didn't, didn't say too much.
Yeah.
He don't know a whole lot of words.
Yeah...
Laura, Laura Louise,
she's giving him a little verbal hurting
because of the move.
You know, she be like, "We gotta move,"
and he's like, "No, we don't."
Like, "Yes, we do."
He say, "No, we don't."
Castrating bitches.
Shouldn't marry them,
should kill them.
Yeah, but, you know, still.
You know, it would've been nice
to have him tonight, right?
Would've been helpful.
Not particularly.
Done this shit a thousand times.
You hear that?
Tell me,
after you dumped her in the trunk,
did it occur to you at any point
you might wanna tie her down?
Fuck! Stupid! Fuck!
Man, I'm sorry. I just... I wasn't...
I just threw her in, and I'm so...
- Just pull over. Pull, pull over.
- No. Forget about it.
Forget about it, kid.
It's all good.
But...
Remind me to tell you
sometime about what I did back in '69.
Now that was a fuck-up.
Well, what happened in '69?
I said ask me sometime.
No.
No!
No. No.
No.
No, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
N'), m, no, no.
No!
Get me out!
No! No!
No! No! No!