What are you doing to me?
Stop! That's not part
of the initiation!
God, no!
Oh, my God!
What have I done?
Let me out of here!
Help me! Help me!
Anyone here?
Guys?
I'm here for the initiation.
You guys can do
whatever you want to me.
I'm ready for anything.
Just don't hide and scare me.
Guys?
Anyone home?
You guys are watching me,
aren't you?
All I have to do is make it
through this weekend, and I'm in.
[Thud]
Guys?
[Heartbeats]
Guys? You up there?
[Flies buzzing]
Dude, when you said the woods,
you weren't kidding.
Are we there yet?
Shut up, pledges.
So this is it?
So, where are the chicks?
This weekend is about bonding,
Eddie, not bondage.
Besides, you don't want any chicks
to see what's gonna happen
to you this weekend.
This is Gamma Kappa property.
Show some respect.
This place has been around
for over a hundred years.
And it'll be around
long after we're all dead.
Sorry, master.
Would you leave
the poor kid alone?
You speak to me out of turn,
pledge?
Give me 10 now.
Sorry, Kevin.
Don't worry, mate.
If this thing weren't so primitive
and juvenile, I might be angry.
Like I said,
this is Gamma Kappa property,
which means it's home
to any member
of Gamma Kappa
right across America.
We can't hold our initiation
at Whitman anymore
due to some unfortunate
legal matters.
So from now on,
initiation will take place here.
Hey, it looks like Andy boy
beat us here.
Hope he followed our directions.
Me, too.
Pledge, we're here.
Hey, Andy!
Where the hell are you, Andy?
Don't be afraid.
Man, I don't know
what they're gonna do to us.
I'm scared.
I don't know if I can take it.
Dude, relax.
It's only a weekend.
What's the worst thing
they can do to us?
Think about what being
a Gamma Kappa means.
Better grades, better social life,
better job after graduation.
Chicks.
Hey.
Andy's stuff was in our room.
I sent him up here early
to set up for initiation.
Well, where is he?
I'm sure he's hanging
around here somewhere.
Why are you even
in this fraternity, man,
if you hate these guys so much?
[Scoffs]
Damn legacy.
Father founded this damn frat.
He probably helped pay for this
little piece of lakefront property
with his alumni donations.
Hope they boot my ass out.
I've heard what they do to pledges.
I don't even know what to expect.
Just the same
old juvenile frat stuff.
[Chuckles]
What are they gonna do?
Kill us?
What's the worst
that could possibly happen?
This is great.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
I'm just looking for a room, sir.
Boyd, house masters
get their own rooms.
Not bitch boys like you.
I'm sorry.
We're gonna have fun with you.
I really am a fun guy
to have around.
When I say fun, I mean torture.
Get out!
Where's the beer?
We gotta spank that Andy kid.
He probably forgot the beer,
and he's hiding in the woods
'cause he's scared
of what we're gonna do to him.
Hey, did you guys
know there's an attic?
Of course, I knew that.
I thought you said you've
never been here for initiation.
I'm a senior.
I know everything.
Who owned this place before?
It was a summer camp
back in the '80s.
Then a lumberjack lived here
with his wife and kids.
What happened to 'em?
You don't wanna know.
[Sighs]
What the hell happened to you?
Where are you, John?
[Heartbeats]
Help me.
Please, help me.
Man, how'd we get
this place so cheap?
It wasn't that cheap.
But we had to have it.
Was he up here
when he vanished?
You know, that missing kid?
Yeah.
John Ralston.
He was a dire pledge,
same as me.
The police came by the house
again the other day.
They think
he vanished from school.
They're still asking questions.
Look, it was three years ago.
I was a freshman.
We came up here for initiation.
It was tough on him
like it was for all of us.
And he vanished.
We didn't kill him.
I don't know what happened to him.
The alumni thought it'd be best
if we buy this place.
And we all pledged
to keep it quiet.
And that's what
we're gonna do, okay?
It's over.
John Ralston was never here.
And no one at Gamma Kappa
remembers him.
So Why'd you have
to come back, then?
I'm sorry for my transgression
with the room.
In every group of pledges,
there's a whipping boy.
A Boyd.
So, where do you
want me to sleep tonight?
Man, Boyd, I think that you should
probably sleep out there.
It's time to begin initiation.
So, take off your shirts.
And your pants.
It's just the beginning, boys.
First day's always a piece of cake.
It just gets harder
and harder from here.
How do you feel after that?
Do you feel emasculated?
Violated?
Do you feel impotent?
Do you still want the chicks?
Bend over.
NOW!
Are we having fun yet, boys?
Yes, sir.
May I have another?
To be a Gamma Kappa,
you must show leadership, loyalty,
and be willing to sacrifice
yourself to the fraternity.
And to do that, you have to bear
the mark of Gamma Kappa
for the rest of your days.
You gotta be kidding me.
I am sick of your attitude,
Mr. Trust Fund Rich Boy.
If you're not man enough
to go through initiation, fine.
I'll just call your daddy and tell him
his son's being a big pussy.
Oh, wait.
Does he already know that?
You can't break me.
I will break you.
[Flies buzzing]
[Screams]
Gamma Kappa
is more than a fraternity.
It's a way of life.
A brotherhood.
We must bond like brothers.
Only way to do that
is to be blood brothers.
I hate blood.
Anything but this.
You wanna be a Gamma Kappa?
You can leave at anytime.
You're all expendable.
I'll do anything
to be a Gamma Kappa.
[Groans]
You dare defy me?
I'll cut myself if you don't mind.
Man bleeds.
Man can be killed.
Are you guys gonna cut
yourselves now?
[Laughs]
Man, Boyd, I'd really love to,
but I'm a hemophiliac.
We've already survived initiation.
You must be willing to lay down
your lives for your fellow brothers.
That's what brotherhood is.
Now, slap hands
like blood brothers.
Go gather some kindling
for a campfire.
Go!
Sorry, guys.
Just passing through.
You guys should probably
put on some clothes.
This is bear country.
They'd like you.
I'm Kevin. This is Boyd.
Doug. Eddie. And Garrett.
Tatianna.
So what are you guys
doing out here?
Oh, we're with Gamma Kappa
fraternity.
This is initiation.
Don't apologize.
This is Gamma Kappa property,
and you're trespassing.
Well, be careful.
I've been hiking around this area
for 10 years now,
and you can really get hurt
if you don't know what you're doing.
There's a girl in the woods.
Actually, she was kind of hot.
Hey.
Where's your car?
I just took the bike up here.
You must have strong legs.
Morris, how long
is this going on for?
Tomorrow. Just do what I ask.
It's initiation week, you know.
You wanna be
Gamma Kappa, right?
Aren't you sick of babysitting
to pay tuition?
Your next task
is a scavenger hunt.
There are ribbons hung
in certain trees in the woods.
You must find a ribbon
if you want to eat or sleep
in a cabin tonight.
And if you find a ribbon,
you can sleep in a cabin, too.
Wait. We can't do it like this.
This is bear country.
Oh, yeah. And watch out
for the bears... or you're lunch.
[Blows whistle]
Stop playing around.
Where's Andy?
I don't know. You tell me.
Maybe he's in the lake.
Maybe he's still finishing
his scavenger hunt.
I hope so.
This is gonna be the best initiation
we've ever had.
Oh, yeah, as long as no pledges
disappear without a trace.
We don't have a problem, do we?
I don't know, Morris.
Why'd you come back up here?
Well, we're barred
from using the school. And --
And you wanna find the missing
pledge, right? That's it.
John Ralston?
You know, why didn't you just
come up here by yourself?
Because this place is creepy.
Don't you think? I mean, that's
why it's perfect for initiation.
Look, I --
We didn't kill that pledge, okay?
Do you really think I'm capable
of murdering a pledge?
[Exhales]
Hey, where are they?
This sucks.
I found a ribbon.
I found a ribbon!
I did good.
Guys? Where are you?
I think I'm lost!
I think I'm lost.
Boyd!
I guess he's the only one
who found a ribbon.
Looks like he's not staying
out here tonight.
Boyd'll never survive
out here all weekend.
We have to find him and get him out
of here before he gets himself hurt.
Where the hell were you, Boyd?
I found a ribbon.
I passed the test.
Did you check to see
if all the ribbons were out there?
That was Andy's job.
I gave him detailed instructions.
Hope you guys
found all the ribbons.
We didn't find any
'cause there were none.
Well, actually, Boyd yelled out
and said he found one.
We didn't find any, though.
Out of all the pledges,
you're the only one to find a ribbon?
I found the ribbon.
I passed the test.
What'd you do,
kill someone to get it?
You guys are gonna have
to repeat this test tomorrow.
[sighing]
Go.
Go!
[Birds chirping]
Has anyone seen Andy?
Don't tell me he's still playing
hide-and-seek.
He didn't put the ribbons
on the trees. He's gone.
Where is he?
I don't know, man.
Maybe the pledges are playing
a trick of their own on us.
No. That would
require imagination.
Hey, we were pledges, too, once.
We were just like them.
No. I was never like them.
Come on. Where is he?
I don't know, okay?
You never know with you.
Did you guys know that this place,
Lake Matawaska,
has a bloody legend?
A pledge vanished
a couple years back.
What I was gonna say
is that the lumberjack
who built this place
went mad and chopped his wife
and kids to pieces.
Would you believe that?
Go in and get cleaned up
for tomorrow.
It's gonna be hell day.
You're gonna need rest.
Sorry, man. It just slipped.
Do you know what happens
if the cops find out that kid
was up here when he vanished?
It's been three years,
and everyone
thinks he left for school
or went to Europe
or has been kidnapped.
We made a vow of silence.
Do you wanna go to jail?
I wouldn't really
go to jail now, would I?
I'm just a sophomore.
You're a senior.
Boyd!
We're gonna go get cleaned up.
Join us when you're done.
Hey, was that a joke
about that pledge
disappearing from school?
Uh, yeah. John-- John--
Ralston.
Yeah.
It was a big deal, actually,
when he went missing from school.
Case went cold and no one knows
really what happened to him.
Jesus.
I'm joking.
They're just messing with us.
Don't fall into that trap.
Come on.
Oh.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to scare you.
Just looking for some
good kindling for a fire.
What are you doing out here?
I'm just planting these ribbons
for initiation.
Where are your brothers?
They're cleaning up.
Need a place to sleep tonight?
I'm at the house, thanks.
Okay. Well, I've just got
my little sleeping bag here.
Just looking for a man
to keep me warm.
I --
Later.
What was your initiation like?
Unspeakable.
What, like, torture?
Bondage? Sodomy?
Oh, come on, Morris.
We've done it all, haven't we?
Worse.
What's worse than that?
When you figure that out,
you can have my job.
I thought maybe I could sleep over
tonight if you guys have any room.
I don't wanna sleep alone
in the woods tonight.
What's your name, honey?
Morris.
What's your name?
Tatianna.
[Knocking on door]
[Moaning]
Hey, Morris! I thought we were
gonna have a threesome.
I'm really pissed off
at you right now.
[Tatianna moans]
STACEY: Love you. I wish you
were back here at school with me.
I miss you like crazy.
I don't know why I came up here
for initiation.
I don't even know why I wanna be
in this stupid fraternity.
Gotta be just like the old man,
right?
Why don't you get the hell out
of there right now?
Where are you, anyway?
Somewhere near loko.
It's a place called Lake Matawaska.
And I can't just leave.
We're in the middle of nowhere,
and I don't have my car.
Don't let them scare you.
Don't worry.
They can't kill me.
Any girls out there?
Yeah. We met this one chick
in the woods.
Unbelievable.
She's actually kind of hot.
[Tatianna continues
moaning in background]
Shut up, jerk.
I'm joking. I love you.
- Love you, too.
- I'll see you on Monday.
- Okay.
-Love you.
- Bye.
You know,
they have pills for that.
What are you talking about?
[Tatianna sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
Trash.
[Cheers and applause]
I am out of here, Morris.
[Heartbeats]
Guys?
I hid the ribbons!
I hid 'em really well.
I went all over the forest.
[Sighs]
God...
It's freezing out here.
[Screams]
[Tatianna continues screaming]
What are you doing here?
Is this a joke?
The first day wasn't so bad.
I've been scarred for life.
It'll all be over by tomorrow.
I'm not even scared anymore.
I think I saw Boyd.
He's outside the window.
He's probably just taking a walk.
Might still be hiding the ribbons.
Poor bitch boy.
Oh, Boyd can't survive, like,
10 minutes out in the woods.
You saw how scared
he was today.
Maybe he's with a girl.
What are the odds
they're together right now?
[They chuckle]
Hey, maybe Andy's
living out in the forest
like that lumberjack
and his family.
Is there really a lumberjack
that killed his wife and kids?
What are you? Stupid?
10 years ago, this place used to be
one of those juvie delinquent camps.
The water supply got poisoned
by toxic waste.
That's why no one
comes up here anymore.
ORGY-
So if Andy's not living out
in the forest, then where is he?
Don't forget about Boyd.
I mean, like it or not,
these pledges are under our watch.
I mean, we can't just kill 'em.
Can we?
Let's split up.
All right.
I'll go down here.
Hey, Boyd!
Andy!
Do you guys have any idea
how dead you are?
Shane? Pledges?
You wanna play a game?
You like hiding out
in the forest alone?
It's the only place
you can hide from me.
Scare you, pal?
I found a weapon.
Let's go find these clowns
before the pledges get up.
Why?
Look, Morris,
I know why you bought this place.
Why'd you come back up here?
-It would look suspicious --
-Morris!
[Sighs]
I want to make sure he's gone.
I want to make sure no one else
finds him, except maybe me.
You want to find his body,
don't you?
So you and the rest of the alumni
don't have to worry about it anymore.
[Sighs]
Did Boyd come back?
I want to know what happened
at your initiation.
Just between you and me.
I don't want to talk about it.
It was horrible.
I'm talking about the pledge
that disappeared“ John Ralston.
I told you. He vanished.
Yeah, you told me.
And that makes me
an accessory to you
and the rest of the alumni
if you did something really sick.
- We buried him, okay?
-You buried him?
We buried him alive in a coffin.
It was a shallow grave.
He was the whipping boy.
The leaders really
had it out for that kid.
I was just a pledge.
He was down there screaming
his head off for a couple of hours.
When they finally
had me dig him up,
the coffin was there, but...
he was gone.
Morris, you realize
if the cops found out --
I know.
We'd go to jail.
They'd think we killed him
and buried him somewhere.
I looked everywhere for that kid.
He was just gone.
I don't know what happened.
So we just went back to Whitman.
Pretend like he was never here.
His parents were dead.
No friends came calling.
We just thought it'd blow over.
But then the cops showed up
a week later.
We just kept to the story.
Where are Andy and Boyd?
Where are they, Morris?
I don't know!
I don't know.
You knew where he was buried
and you did nothing to save him.
I told you, he vanished.
How many times
do I have to tell you that?
I gotta take a leak.
Well, hurry up.
We have to find these kids.
If we go back without 'em,
there's hell to pay.
Let's go.
[Heartbeats]
Hey, did he plant the ribbons?
If you can find the ribbons,
we can figure out where he --
[Shane screams]
[Morris screams]
Guys?
[Garrett yawns]
I'm thirsty.
Too much porn, eh?
[Laughs]
They take our pride,
I take the beer.
Is Boyd back yet?
Yeah. I think he's just playin'
out in the woods.
Morris and Shane'll find him.
They're gone.
I found this.
Here we go again?
I woke up this morning
'cause I thought I heard screaming.
Look, today is the big day.
There'll be lots of screaming
before the day's over.
You gotta be ready for anything.
It's just initiation.
It's all a test.
[Heartbeats]
[Screaming]
We've got a long day ahead.
Don't get up until they make us.
Do you hear something?
Man, there's a lot of weird sounds
out there.
You gonna go check 'em all out?
No.
It sounded like a scream.
It's initiation, fool!
Unless you see a guy out there with
a hockey mask, don't worry about it.
They're just trying
to scare the hell out of us.
[Door closes]
Where's Boyd?
It's hide-and-go-seek.
Well, let's go find 'em.
Hey, every minute
they're gone and we're alone
is another minute we're not getting
our balls shaved
or our manhood glued to a tree.
I scouted these guys
before I joined the house.
I know what happens
on final initiation day.
We should get lost
and stay lost.
They're watching us right now.
You think so?
It's all part of initiation.
They're watchin' us,
waiting for us to go crazy.
And then...
they're gonna pounce!
You know, if they're playing
some kind of game,
we're not gonna get home
unless we find these guys.
And Boyd, Andy --
What?
Maybe they're in the attic.
Probably laughing
their heads off up here.
Is that real blood?
Whose blood?
Let's get outta here.
You tell the others.
All right, let's do a check
on the rest of the cabin area,
then do a check in the forest.
All right.
If they're not here,
we're gonna leave.
Yeah, cool.
[Heartbeats]
Go with him.
Garret and I will search
the camp area.
What the hell?
How are we supposed
to get home now?
We'll hike outta here
if we have to.
Were you asleep
on the drive here?
The nearest crossroad is,
like, 10 miles.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
STACEY: Hey, honey,
just checkin' in.
Is that girl still there?
No girls.
Look, I have to go, baby.
Okay. So do you wanna
call somebody?
Let's go find these jerk-offs.
Feels good.
Eddie?
Eddie, is that you?
[Heartbeats]
[Grunts]
[Screaming in distance]
Morris?
You guys out here?
I'm comin' to get you!
"I lost my virginity
at Lake Matawaska in 1980."
Hm.
Good for you, kid. Lucky.
[Knocking]
Who is it?
Scare 'ya?
Find anybody?
We're runnin'
out of places to look.
I'm a bit nervous.
What are we supposed to do now?
There's only one place
they could be hiding.
That's a big forest.
Let's go, dude!
Hey, man, let's go back and tell
the others we can't find anyone.
Dougie.
Dougie?
[Screaming in the distance]
Where did Eddie go?
I sent him to go with Doug.
Right. Right.
Well, let's stay together, okay?
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
Kevin, I've been thinking
a lot about our relationship, and --
Look, I can't talk right now.
Why don't you get the hell out
of there and come back to school
and be with me right now?
Baby, I'll be home by nightfall.
But I need you to do
something for me, okay?
You need to call
the pizza place -- Sharkey's --
and have them deliver 10 large
pizzas up to Lake Matawaska.
Okay, it's way out of their zone,
but tell them Morris
from Gamma Kappa made the order.
Gamma Kappa has
an account with them, okay?
I need you to do that
for me right away, okay?
Okay, I'll do it.
See 'ya later.
Sorry.
You ever had a girlfriend?
They're high maintenance.
You say what you have
to say to make 'em happy.
Yeah, listen.
What if they don't deliver?
I mean, this isn't exactly "30 minutes
or you get it free" territory.
Doug! Eddie!
What's goin' on here?
I don't know, man.
But they're both naked,
so they can't be far.
[They chuckle]
Two naked pledges in the forest?
That is a bad combination.
Man, but I've had it with this crap.
It's just a fraternity.
Is it really worth it?
- Yeah, it is.
-Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Let's comb the forest up and down,
and then we're outta here.
All right.
You think they're
playing a prank on us, dude?
They're leading us into a trap.
What, so they can shave our balls?
That's not gonna happen.
I really need to get
into this damn fraternity, dude.
[Heartbeats]
What kind of pizza did you order?
What?
Well, I mean, you didn't tell her
what kind of pizza you wanted
when your girlfriend called.
Idiot, I just did that
to get someone up here.
In case we need a ride?
Which it looks like we do.
Well, I mean, if they don't know --
Shut up!
[Sighs]
Where are they?
Hey, don't fear. I'm here.
Andy! Boyd! Doug!
-Sh!
Finally, civilization.
Who the hell
would be living out here?
Game over!
We found you!
[Flies buzzing]
Oh, my God.
Garrett.
Kevin, over here.
I think --
This is a prank.
The smell --
It can't be real.
I don't know anymore.
They gotta be here somewhere.
They're all dead.
Don't you get it?
They were all murdered.
This was a trap.
Initiation.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna get outta here.
We're gonna go back to the cabin,
and I'm gonna hot-wire
one of the cars,
and we're just gonna leave.
We're gonna get outta here, okay?
- Who is he?
-Quiet!
Let's go.
Garrett! Garrett!
Run!
Fuck!
Garrett!
[Dialing cell phone]
They're all dead.
Kevin, I spoke to the pizza guy,
and he told me --
Stacey, shut up.
Kevin, he hung up on me
when I told him where you were.
Stacey, look,
I need you to call the police
and get them up here
immediately, okay?
Tell them the other pledges
are dead, okay?
Is this a joke?
It's not a joke.
Listen, I need you to call the police
and get them up here right now!
Tell them everyone's dead, okay?
We're at Lake --
Lake Matawaska.
Yeah, okay, okay.
[Line disconnects]
The call, make the call --
[Line busy]
Help!
Garrett?
Garret?
I'm in the forest!
Garrett!
Help! I'm bleeding like crazy!
The killer's dead!
Oh, dude,
thought you were dead.
How do we get out of here
is the only thing that matters.
Okay. Stacey called me.
I told her what happened.
The cops'll be here.
Can you trust her to do that?
They'll be here.
Where is he?
I don't know, man.
He took me back to his shed,
back to that little closet so he could
cut me up into little pieces.
I grabbed his ax, man,
and I attacked him.
I fought for my life.
And I escaped.
Is he dead?
Man, I don't know.
Maybe I should go check.
Sounds like a stupid idea,
don't you think?
Should quit while you're ahead.
Let me get you out of here.
[Garrett groans]
It would take you a hundred days
to walk to the nearest crossroad.
[Garrett groans]
It's okay.
Just go. I'll be okay.
The cops should be here in,
like, 15, 20 minutes tops.
Yeah, if your girlfriend called
the cops like you told her to.
Maybe one of the guys
left his cell in his room.
Go. I'll be okay.
I can't leave you alone, dude.
You'll bleed to death.
There's probably
a first aid in the cabinet.
ORGY-
I hope you didn't find anything.
What?
It's almost over, Kevin.
I like you.
This is gonna be hard for me,
believe it or not.
You're bleeding.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Not physically.
I didn't know you had
your cell phone on you.
I checked before we left.
What's goin' on, Garrett?
We gotta get outta here.
Three years ago
when I was still in high school,
I had a brother at Whitman.
He joined a fraternity
called Gamma Kappa.
They took him here for initiation
and they buried him alive!
His name was John.
John Ralston.
- John Ralston.
-Was he up here when he vanished?
I looked everywhere for that kid.
Where are you, John?
You knew where he was buried
and you did nothing to save him.
I know. We'd go to jail.
I want to make sure he's gone.
I want to make sure no one else
finds him, except maybe me.
You want to find his body,
don't you?
John Ralston was never here.
And no one at Gamma Kappa
remembers him.
- My real name is Garrett Ralston.
-Garrett --
You think we could let them live?
Could we?
Somebody had to put an end to this
barbaric tradition called initiation.
In my brother's case,
it was murder.
They tried to keep it a secret.
And they said it was an accident.
It was murder.
Almost.
I was the only one
he told where he was.
I came up here looking for him
when he didn't come back to school.
We found him.
He found us.
Who the heck is "we"?
The family. Blood is blood.
The cops are gonna be here soon.
The cops aren't coming, Kevin.
I'm the only one who can help you.
What about Stacey?
Stacey is my sister.
No one knows you're here.
No one knows I'm here.
Because we're not even
supposed to be here,
'cause initiation
is immoral and wrong.
But I'm your best friend.
Yeah.
You are my best friend.
And I couldn't have made it
through college without you, pal.
This is gonna be hard for me.
Don't make me call
Brother Johnny.
I found a laptop in Shane's room.
I e-mailed the cops, our friends
at the dorms, my friends,
the dean, everybody.
You can't run, Kevin.
You can't hide.
I don't believe you
about that e-mail. I know you.
Don't make me enjoy killing you.
I don't want to enjoy this.
I know this place better
than you do.
I've been comin' up here
for three years.
My brother knows this place
like the back of his hand.
He was buried here, remember?
I would never hurt your brother.
You know I would never
participate in something like that.
I know. You're a good person
with strong morals.
Unfortunately, I knew you
wouldn't be part of my revenge --
murder.
Which is why you gotta go, pal.
Can't leave any witnesses.
Look, I told you I sent
that e-mail.
You are not gonna
get away with this.
I sent an e-mail, too,
and it got bounced.
The forest, the trees?
They block all the signals.
I'm not stopping.
I love you, but...
blood is thicker than beer.
[Groans]
[Heartbeats]
[Ring tone]
911 OPERATOR:
911 emergency.
Hello? My name's Kevin.
I'm a student at Whitman College.
Okay, I'm with the Gamma Kappa
house, and there's been murders.
They're all dead.
Okay, I need you guys
to send up the cops right now.
AH right, sir. Calm down.
Where are you?
Okay, they'll be here soon?
The police are on their way.
Keep your phone on
because I put a trace on your line
in case you were wrong
about your location.
That way takes much longer.
Can you just hide
until the police arrive?
Yeah, I can hide.
I'll be in the attic, okay?
[Heartbeats]
[Whispers]
They'll be here soon.
Come on. Get here.
Look, John!
Look, you killed them.
You got your revenge...
against the ones
who put you through initiation...
who buried you alive.
I'm glad you killed them.
I'm just a pledge like you were.
I'm innocent.
John, you have to understand.
Initiation's over.
No!
[Groans]
That one was for me.
Everyone's dead, aren't they?
Are you the one
who called the police?
It's okay. We're here.
It's over.
Initiation's over.
What happened here?
They're all dead.
[Groans]
Who did this?
He's in the attic.
I killed him.
He used to be a pledge like me.
We searched the cabin,
the whole area,
and all we're finding
are your dead friends.
There's no one else.
In the attic. I killed him.
We looked everywhere.
There's nothing in the attic
but lots of blood.
Kevin, is it possible that you
murdered your fraternity brothers?
No! I'm not a murderer!
Well, how else do you
explain all of this?
Look, I killed him, okay?
He killed everyone except for me.
Who, Kevin?
Who?
John Ralston, Gamma Kappa.
He's still out there.