What about the mess hall retard?
Her name is Tanakoff.
The less she knows the better.
All we need her for is access to
the kitchen then she is cut lose.
I don't know man. This whole
plan just seems kind of fucked.
Look we only get one shot at this.
One time.
That is it. Just one chance.
It just seems halfassed you know.
I just I don't think it's gonna work.
What the fuck isn't halfassed
to you private?
It's the dyke.
Tartakoff.
He's got a thing for the dyke.
Is this true Riggs?
You have a thing for Retardakoff?
She ain't a dyke.
Admit it.
She wants your cock in her orifices.
Fuck you man!
Fuck you!
Riggs! Is that it?
She is not a combat solider alright. I do not
feel right using her like we are doing.
Yeah were all being used solider.
Her no more than any of us.
Now I need to know
are you in or out?
Are you in?
Or are you out?
Alright. Im in.
Yeah motherfucker!
Alright!
Quit it man! Quit it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Stop!
Don't move a muscle.
Fucking trip mine.
Oh shit.
Sergeant check your feet.
I'm fine. It's not me.
Shit.
You are on a motherfucking
landmine.
Looks like Riggs won't be joining us
unless we need an amputee or something.
Hey, fuck you man! If you hadn't pushed me
I wouldn't be on this thing!
Riggs! Riggs! Easy okay?
My face is a little too fucking close
to this so I'm kind of attached to it.
Let me have this.
Thank you.
Okay.
Okay, when this detonator springs we
have about a half a second to bat it off.
Like baseball. Fun.
Yeah. Only we get one swing
and one pitch. That's it.
Uh, that does not sound like too
good of an idea sir.
- Anybody play baseball?
- Sir that does not sound like a good idea.
I am pretty good at Wii.
Oh yeah? Who the fuck are you?
Johnny Damon?
No way man. His long hair made
him look like a gay lumberjack.
Who does not look gay to you?
- Dude it's just my gaydar.
- Do you have a problem...
-...with homosexuals being in the Army?
- Not at all man!
Hey guys! Get me the fuck
off this mine!
No, I know. I'm working on it.
Jesus Christ.
Okay. So um...
On three jump off.
Whoa hang on hang on.
What am I doing?
You're the jump off pan.
Maybe I should I will pull him off.
- I will pull him this way.
- I don't know if--
- No, I don't think that's gonna--
- No I've done it before. It's okay.
No, let him jerk you
off. He'll get off on it.
Come on I will give you a little
momentum. Pull you off. come on.
Alrighty on the count of three
you wanna count?
Yeah, maybe you should
count to three.
But you have to ask yourself is
this where you wanna fucking die?
I'm not gonna count.
He cant count to three.
Come on. You count.
- No I'm swinging.
- Count of three. Your count.
Im not gonna count.
- Let me count it out.
- You count to three.
- Okay, I will count. come on.
- On three. It's on three.
So it's one two and then go.
Right? One two go.
Ready? Okay. One two three!
That was kind of anticlimactic.
♪ Oh beautiful forspacious skies ♪
♪ for amber waves of grain. ♪
♪ For purple mountain majesties... ♪
Mr. President.
They're ready for you.
Alright.
Be right there.
I'll say hi to my wife
back home in Atlanta GA.
I miss you babe.
I'll be back there really soon.
Twenty three years and I'm
sticking around.
They'll have to drag me out
kicking and screaming boys.
The President is going to come out
here and we are going to be enjoying
Thanksgiving turkey with him.
I'm so nervous.
I've always wanted to meet him.
Ready for some turkey?
Absolutely Mr. President.
I'm looking forward to
the stuffing myself.
I hear there's a
special ingredient.
Good evening solider.
Mr. President sir.
Mm hmm. At ease.
Thank you sir.
Tenhut!
At ease everyone.
Smoke em if you got em.
How we doing here?
Happy Thanksgiving.
Smith good to see ya.
Nothing like having
Thanksgiving in 96 degree weather huh?
Smoke
that turkey all by it itself.
Good to meet you. How are you?
How are you?
Little sunflower seeds before the turkey?
Jones how are you?
You're the boy the boy from Texas huh?
It'is an honor Mr. President.
Yes sir.
- You wanna take a picture?
- Sure!
While I'm still will good
looking? Uh-huh.
Thank you.
- Let's take care of that ight now.
- There you go.
Get my good side.
That's basically everything.
- There we go!
- That's it right there.
- Very nice. Nicely done.
- Thanks. I will email you.
- Yeah keep your day job alright?
- Good to see ya.
- Captain.
- Mr. President.
How are you?
Captain Garrison
nice to see you.
Is this the culprit right here?
Is this the American stuffing or is this local?
Beautiful turkey.
Beautiful beautiful turkey.
This'll be my first turkey of the year
and I will have seven or eight more
by the time I get home.
I know that we have uh much to
be thankful for this evening.
What Im must thankful for
is that um Im nut a turkey.
In all seriousness I know uh you
are along way from home.
I know that many of you wish you were
with your family and friends
back in the U.S. but you have
made a sacrifice tn he hare
and help fight for democracy and peace
for citizens throughout the world.
We have made everybody safer--
You have made everybody safer by removing
a dangerous regime and America
will continue to fight
extremism and spread
freedom to other oppressed areas.
So tonight I'd like to thank you for putting on
the uniform and showing all of us
what honor courage and freedom
is all about.
Now I know you didn't come here to listen
to me ramble all night long so uh...
Who wants turkey?
Turkey! Turkey! Turkey!
As I understand it this is 100%
pure American turkey.
The best in the world.
Can I get a hooah?
Hooah!
- And another!
- Hooah!
- One more!
I think you are hungry.
Knife and fork is ready.
I'm lefthanded. Everybody back up.
Get this started.
Here we go. There it is.
Mission accomplished sir.
For starters...
Stay back! Stay back! Stay back!
Drop your weapons!
I will kill him!
I will put a bullet in his fucking head!
I am not afraid to die!
Have a fucking happy
Thanksgiving cocksucker!
Happy motherfucking Thanksgiving!
I will kill him!
Come on up! Up!
Stay back!
Go around the back!
Downey!
Sergeant!
Down down down!
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Move! Move!
Where the fuck is Riggs?
Put him over there!
Whats happening?
My leg!
I've been shot!
It's Riggs! Don't shoot!
Damnit Riggs!
Sorry. It's crazy out there sir.
Holy shit.
Move! Move! Move!
Back away from the door now!
Go! Go!
- Riggs!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Open this fucking door
right now!
I'm shot!
Somebody shot me!
This is ate the fuck up man.
Will someone tell me whats going on?
Goddammit!
Downey kill that horrible music!
Sergeant secure the area!
What's she doing here?
What the fuck are you doing here?
I'm sorry I just didn't
know where to go.
Are you brain dead Tartakoff?
We told you to stay away from the kitchen!
Can somebody tell me
whats going on?
Should I waste her sir?
No! Hey!
Stand down sergeant! No one's
getting wasted, not yet!
Hey! I am your commander in chief!
I demand to know
what the fuck is going on!
Riggs! Chair!
Relax! Relax!
Mr. President,
you are being held prisoner.
By who?
Really?
By us dumb-ass!
This is an outrage.
Let me go now!
- Hold this! Neck! Balls!
- What is this?
That's duct tape sir.
Do you have any idea what
you've gotten yourself into?
Yes sir.
Yeah, then you understand the
gravity of your actions.
Do you see this uniform, sir?
Yes I do!
Those of us that wear it face death
every day prepared to die at any moment.
The question is are you?
Are you sir prepared
to die at any moment?
Happy Thanksgiving!
Gobble gobble gobble!
Riggs! You shoot anything
that comes through that door!
Hey cheesedick!
Tanakoff! Make yourself useful!
Grab that med kit!
The President is alive and well
but you keep banging on that door
and it is gonna turn all
Peckinpah in here.
Riggs! Check all frequencies!
- Peckin what?
- Peckinpah. Film director.
Bloody Sam?
Where you from?
- Uh, Charlotte sir.
- Straw Dogs.
Fuckin Nazis man.
Is that for me?
Oh I don't know.
You'd have to ask Garrison.
- Right there.
- The Wild Bunch, 1969.
The Wild Bunch.
Jesus. come on.
Let's take a look at it will ya?
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Let's go!
Got your headphones?
Yes sir.
- Whats your first name?
- Alexandra sir. Alex for short.
That's a pretty name.
My first puppy was named Alex.
Really?
Yeah, very smart dog. Obedient.
Did whatever I told him to do.
Now why do not you be
obedient and untape my hands.
Do not talk to him.
You oughta apply to NASA Tartakoff.
You're that smart.
Medical kit!
Show me your lag.
What do you think?
That Im not prepared to die?
I get death threats every single day.
But you know what the thing is?
I expect it to come from
whackos and terrorists!
Not from U.S. soldiers who have--
Oh ow! Ow!
We're Army Rangers, sir.
Looks like it passed through the
soft tissue and didn't hit any bone.
Tough old cowboy like you?
You oughta be able to shrug
this off no problem.
So who shot me son?
Was it you?
Hard to tell in a firefight
who shot who, sir.
If you like we can measure it
from the inside
and narrow it down based
on possible caliber.
Or we can shoot a hole in the
other leg and see if it matches.
Garrison talk you into this son?
Because you are so fucked!
I suggest you direct all
questions to me Mr. President.
I don't know what you are after soldier
but it's not gonna work.
Did you miss the pan about us
being Army Rangers, sir?
Hold him.
Ow! Ow shit!
It's gonna feel like a little
mosquito bite there Mr. President.
Oh my God!
Strong one isn't he?
Tartakoff, let me make this
perfectly clear.
You can leave now but you are facing
almost certain court martial.
That's to say you don't get shot
to shit walking into that hallway.
So the million dollar question is...
do you want to stay
or do you want to go?
I'll stay.
The man in that chair, he is not
your president, he is not your friend.
He is nobody.
I am your commanding officer.
- Hooah?
- Hooah.
And under my command that
means no complaining,
no freaking out and
no fucking whining.
Yes sir.
What did you inject in me?
Acetonitrile derivative.
Less than two hours it'll induce a
chemical paralysis in your brain.
It will lead to cranial hemorrhaging.
What?
Blood vessels in your brain will
rupture first causing blindness,
excruciating pain, leading
to paralysis and death.
Of course you can have the antidote but
only if you cooperate.
Cooperate?
Cooperate with what?
I don't even know why I'm here.
Hear anything Riggs?
Not much. Mostly just fighting
about whos in charge--
the military or the
Secret Service.
Fighting and bureaucratic bullshit are about
the only two things can rely on out here.
Downey! Boob tube!
Tartakoff! Med kit!
This is Captain Hank Garrison.
Anyone copy?
I say again this is
Captain Garrison. Copy?
- We hear you over.
- Identify yourself.
This is Agent Stenson of
the Secret Service.
Is POTUS with you?
Affirmative. The President of the
United States is here he is safe
and relatively unharmed.
What is it you want
Captain Garrison?
For right now I just want you to
stay the fuck out and cooperate.
I will cooperate
as long as The President remains unharmed.
We need confirmation he is safe.
We're sending in a medic.
Negative.
You send in the Civi news crew.
The British chick and her cameraman.
- I don't think that's possible.
- Yes it is. You just try asking them.
Standby.
Let them send in a medic.
I need a real doctor alright?
Who the hell is this Garrison?
Give me some stats on him.
Sorry sir there's no medics
available.
Casualty of your latest cutbacks.
Okay, Melody Stone and cameraman
Steve Ullmer are heading in.
Only two are allowed in.
I see anyone else
and we kill them all.
Copy that?
Copy.
It's the moment you've been
waiting for.
The best day of your life
with that special someone.
The gin of your dreams.
So you pledge your love knowing
that this moment is forever.
And then the ultimate nightmare!
Dumped at the altar!
Eh his heart's been broken.
What a damn shame.
Doesn't look like they know
about us yet.
Let's go!
Come on! Come on!
Tight fit! Come on in!
Come on! Tight fit! Tight fit!
Welcome!
Check em!
I mean he was an okay
fuck and all but he always wanted
to do it in the ass and I was
like no way.
You gotta go down on me
if you want some of this.
They're clean sir.
Let's see your pretty faces.
Come on.
Hang on!
Who are you?
Im Steve.
Im camera.
Bullshit! It was a different
cameraman in the mess hall!
- Who is he?
- Hes the cameraman.
A cameraman?
No he is my cameraman.
Any weapons on him? A wire?
Man just leave her alone!
Shut the fuck up!
Was I fucking talking to you?
The camera!
What's in the camera?
I don't know.
It's just a camera!
Maybe you care to explain this
little doodad there Stevie.
Ah man, they just gave
me that camera.
Look at him! He's one of their own!
Clean shaven! Secret Service!
This wasn't my idea!
All of you need to fucking stand down!
You think you're gonna get away--
Head or chest SteveO?
Head is more efficient but sometimes messy.
Stand down Sergeant.
Son of a bitch.
He could be useful.
Melody Stone.
Get me on the air.
I'm sorry?
I want to be live on the air now.
I do not have that authorization.
Surely we're more important
than that shit!
Yeah, I mean the Walmart dude
said it was the best ring they had.
This show gets really
good numbers.
Do it!
Uh, we're on a military base!
I need clearance from them!
Jesus fucking Christ we have
The President of the United States hostage!
I'm sorry. I cant do anything.
I haven't got my cell.
You really are Tit is McGhee.
Garrison for Stenson. Over.
This is Stenson. Over.
I want to be live. On the air. Now.
I want this camera broadcast live.
Negative.
I do not have the authorization.
Are you guys fucking kidding me?
You make this camera broadcast live
or you bring in a dozen fucking shovels
to clean up the body pans when we're done!
Standby.
See what you can get.
Hey! You realize the only
thing you are going to
accomplish here is embarrassing
yourself and the United States?
Mr. President!
Did they hurt you?
No one speaks unless spoken to!
Riggs! Come on!
Don't worry sir.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Shut the fuck up!
Stenson!
You have 5 minutes
to get me live feed!
Garrison it's not that easy.
There is a lot involved.
They're not gonna
work with you.
We don't negotiate with terror--
Sorry Steve.
You fucking maniacs!
You fucking--
Sit the fuck down!
Shut the fuck up.
What was that?
Garrison?
Garrison, was that gunfire? Over!
Standby.
I didn't have anything to do with this.
I'm just a reporter.
Please. You've seen
me on the TV before.
I just did what they told me to!
Please!
Steve is dead.
Now give me my live feed.
Let me hear The President's voice.
You're gonna say this
is The President. I'm okay.
This is The President.
This is more fun than
a Texas rodeo.
That was real cute.
Now get me my live feed.
Give me 10 minutes.
You got three. Out.
What are you doing?
Get up.
What I'm doing is something they should
have taught you in Journalism 101.
Ask real questions, expect real answers.
You just killed an unarmed
American in cold blood.
Killed a lot of people.
Novelty wears off after awhile.
Negative sir.
I still enjoy it every time.
You see Downey here is your best
friend in a battle.
He has an instinctive knack for killing.
Of course you wouldn't want him
around in the civilian world.
He'd probably just get bored
and start a shooting rampage in a
shopping mall or some other place.
KFC. Bigger targets there.
You think this is funny?
This is sick.
Sick to you. Reality to us.
You see Steve here?
That to us is nothing.
We have lived through the worst
neckdeep shit you can imagine.
Stuff that would make your pampered
collagen head spin right the fuck off.
But you wouldn't know about
that would you?
No because we have never seen your
types out in the places we have to go.
You report about these wars from your cushy
comfy airconditioned studios.
Well honey
welcome to Bumfuck Iraq.
I don't use collagen.
Sir. I could use the camera.
I used to be an AV tech in school.
Outstanding.
Let's see what you can do private.
Downey. Put Steve on ice.
Nice shoes Steve.
Riggs?
Yeah?
Are you okay?
Yeah Im fine.
Hey! Tartar Sauce!
Let's go! They patched us in.
This is Adrian Davis.
We have interrupted your regularly scheduled
programming to bring you breaking news.
The President of the United States
has been kidnapped in the green
zone in Baghdad Iraq.
You set?
We're going live right now.
Okay Mr. President.
Hey it's warm in here.
Yes sir it is.
Please. Focus and
say hello to the outside world.
I am The President of the United States.
I'm being held hostage.
Very good sir. Very good.
Outstanding job. Come on.
This here is Melody Stone.
She is usually cast as a cleavage-baring
ovely opinionated talking head on cable news.
Today she is in
the middle of the shit with us.
Oh shit. Am I allowed to
say shit on the news?
No.
Oh fuck. Maybe we can edit that
out can't we?
Tell me Melody Stone,
what is your assessment here?
I'm in a kitchen in the green zone
and The President is being held
captive by several U.S. soldiers.
Army Rangers!
Hooah!
Excuse me.
Army Rangers.
And do you see any terrorists in here?
Any guys with camels?
Any turbans?
No guys with turbans or camels.
Just soldiers, the president and me.
And what is the condition
of The President?
He has a leg wound but other
than that I do not know.
I'm not a doctor.
And neither was the hack who put
in those lopsided tits of yours.
The fuck?
They injected me
with something.
Wait sir!
Wait! Hold.
Go ahead.
Put a needle in my neck.
Some acetonotrilsomething. I dunno.
- Acetonitrile sir.
- Yeah.
It's a derivative.
Yes, The President has been injected
with a timed release substance
that will kill him in an hourand a half.
The correct antidote is rare
but I have it in one of my many pockets.
It's in a glass container.
So if I get shot or even perchance
fall down there is an excellent chance
that it will shatter.
So tune in later for
must-see TV!
Will somebody shut him up?
I've tried Mr. President.
Feel free to give it a shot though.
Once again this is Adrian Davis.
Breaking news.
The President of the United
States has been kidnapped
by four U.S. Army troops.
That's correct.
American Army Rangers have taken
The President of the United States hostage
in a kitchen in the green zone in Iraq
during a Thanksgiving dinner.
We have absolutely no idea why--
Alright Im just being told that
there was a handgun hidden in side.
They are just telling me right now
there was a handgun hidden
inside a Thanksgiving turkey.
Hopefully we'll have some information
coming to us pretty soon.
Sir!
Cut it. Cut the camera.
They're trying to get
through the vent shaft.
Private show me.
Right there.
Ready to roll?
Don't look up.
Oh!
I told you not to look
at the ceiling.
This is Garrison for Stenson.
Over.
Pick up the fucking radio!
Garrison for Stenson. Over!
You son of a bitch.
What? You think we didn't
expect you to use the vents?
Come on Stenson!
Who do you think we are?
Grayson and Jones are dead!
Everyone pull back!
Those were two good
Americans you killed.
I had a Jones once in my unit.
Had his leg blown off
and severe head trauma.
He will spend the rest of his
life in and out of VA hospitals.
I think your
Jones is better off.
This has to stop.
I agree. Your three guys are
dead because of you!
So the sooner you stop trying to
fuck with us
the sooner this will all be over! Copy?
Do you copy?
I Copy.
Garrison out!
You put bombs in the vents?
Yeah. I was in charge of the tact team that
cleared the area for The President's arrival.
Camera. Makes you feel all
safe and snuggly doesn't it?
There is no security. Boo!
Come on! Stan the camera.
Welcome back to America's funniest
home away from home videos!
Let's go.
Let's get The President.
Come on.
What do you got sir?
You don't think I
feel them also?
I'm responsible for these soldiers.
I know the names and faces and families
of everyone Mo's died for this country.
That must be so taxing
on you sir.
No. do not take this
lightly soldier.
Every one of them died for something
this country asked them to do.
Something that I
asked them to do.
Did you say asked?
Did he say asked?
So we can opt out at any time?
We can just pack up our shit and go home?
Fuck yeah! Let's get the
fuck out of here!
I'm going to Disneyland.
That's nut what I meant.
Mr. President, have you ever
had to stuff the intestines
of your best friend back
into his own body?
Many soldiers have made
great sacrifices, son.
That still does not
justify your actions.
Do you know who this man is sir?
No I do not.
Neither did I. I slit his throat
a few months ago though.
Yup. Tums out he is got a wife
and two daughters just like you, sir.
Any particular reason why
this man was on a hit list sir?
We do not have hit lists.
We don't. So there is no particular
reason why this man was killed then?
How about this fella?
There are many things about war
that are unpleasant
but I trust the capable people in charge on
the ground will come up with
tough but good decisions.
Just like you trusted the capable folks
about the links to Al Qaeda and WMDs.
Pesky things, those WMDs.
It's annoying when things don't
turn out the way Jesus intended.
It wasn't Jesus's fault.
It was nine.
But I thought you were divinely
guided by God's own hand sir.
And to be human is to err.
So what's the point of
having Jesus as your guide
if you're just going to
fuck up anyway?
What does religion
have to do with this?
I do not know. You tell me. You're the one
who is shoving it down our fucking throats.
Because it sure as shit
isn't written in the Constitution.
You should read it some time.
Mistakes have been made.
But our core beliefs
and the determination of our young
men and women in uniform
will show in time that
our cause was just.
Where do you get this shit from?
Do you stuff this crap up your ass?
Sir!
Turn the camera off.
What is it?
Nothing. That is just it.
All radio communications are stopped.
I ain't heard
nothing the last couple minutes.
Well they must have figured
out we have been listening in.
How's the perimeter mic?
- Mr. President?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry this is happening.
And I just wanted to say
if we don't get out it has been an honor
absolute honor to be here with you, sir.
It is still working but it only picks
up noise 25 feet from the main door.
Thank you Melody. And by the way
I think your tits are fine.
Honestly?
Yeah yeah. And my
wife loves your show too.
Well that is better than a porcupine
stuck up our ass isn't it?
Keep listening.
Captain Hank Garrison.
Captain Hank Garrison is the
ringleader in this hostage situation.
Garrison apparently requested
one of our best and
our brightest Melody Stone in
there with him.
Mr. President I was just wondering if it was
possible to get an interview at some point--
What the fuck is going on?
Im sorry. We were just
making small talk.
I do not care what kind of talk it was.
Shut the fuck up.
Tartakoff.
Up. Up!
- Are you pan of this team?
- Yes.
Yes sir!
Then you gotta watch out for this.
You have to be alert.
I want you to let me know the moment
these two do or say anything.
- Is that understood?
- Yes sir!
- Good. You're a heck of a soldier.
- Thank you sir.
Where are you going
with all of this?
We have all heard about the soldier's
sacrifice the civilian deaths the WMDs.
Taliban in my basement.
Surely you didn't go through all
this trouble just to rehash...
...something that could easily be discovered
in the archives of the New York Times.
Would you prefer to talk about
the economy? Afghanistan?
How about uh the auto industry, sir?
So many great legacies.
Hey I'm not afraid to die.
If I get killed on the
battlefield sewing my troops
it will counter everything
you are trying to do.
I will be a hero.
And finally live up to your
dad's expectations.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
I read your book Mr. President.
I was struck by one particular story.
When your father said to you
"An honest man can see the lies leaving
his mouth like steam from his breath."
I wonder what he meant by that.
Should I be getting this, sir?
I do not intend for you to die, sir.
But you will feel pain though.
As we do. We feel pain every day.
Pain and rage.
I can't live with myself anymore.
I do not know how you do.
Get the camera.
Let's go.
So where were we?
You can't tell me any reason
why these men were killed?
Talk to your commanding officer.
You are my commanding
officer, sir.
Th at is why I am talking to you.
Your immediate
commanding officer.
You want to ask me why any particular
person here has latrine or garbage duty?
I'm not responsible for
everybody giving orders.
No. How about the orders to
ignore UN weapons inspectors?
Orders to set up
detention camps?
That's an old story Captain.
You want to blame that on me go ahead.
Hell blame everything on me, alright?
Are we done now?
No. We are not done.
We're still stuck in this endless
fucking hell hole with no exit plan.
Tell me sir. How do you explain this
quagmire to your children?
I give them the facts that the
news fails to report.
Jesus Christ.
I can't win with any of you.
I tell them about the hospitals
and the schools being built.
About democratic
elections free markets.
Electricity where there was
no electricity once before.
You mean like the electricity
that is killing soldiers in showers
because of shoddy work by
shitty overpriced contractors!
Contractors who were
your pals before the war!
Ah come on you know as well
as I do mistakes are going
to be made when you're
rebuilding from scratch!
Who asked for any of this?
This was supposed to be the war on terror,
on terror.
Not the war on whatever the fuck you
say it is after the fact.
I made choices I had to make
to keep America safe!
Like ensuring that levees and
bridges are properly maintained.
No ensuring that terrorists did
not attack us on our own soil!
Oh by signing off on torture?
- No, we do not torture!
- We don't?
No, we interrogate.
America does not torture!
- Is that right sir?
- Yeah, that's right!
Shut off the camera.
Stand up.
- Why?
- I said stand up!
He's been shot in the leg.
He shouldn't be standing.
You shut your cakehole!
Stand up!
Walk over to the sink!
Why?
You've heard of
Abu Ghraib haven't you?
Oh yeah what are we gonna
rehash that now?
No. We're gonna relive it.
Fucking contractors.
What the hell--
Riggs! Riggs! Lend a hand!
Tartakoff! Grab a rifle!
You're on guard! Up!
Let's go! Up!
Table! Bring it under!
You just relax.
Relax Mr. President.
Everything were about to do you
personally approved so it's all perfectly safe.
And legal.
Hey, how about some music huh?
How about some mu sic? Yeah!
Sergeant! Grab a towel!
Now we're talking!
Ah! And oldie but a goodie.
I get it. Yeah.
This is a joke, huh?
Come on stop! Stop!
I get it!
Riggs! Grab your rifle.
It's a joke right?
Come on!
Hey! Hey hey hey! Stop!
Stop it now!
Downey fresh.
You do not need to do this!
Please! Don't do this!
Ah!
Fuck yeah! It don't Gitmo
better than this motherfucker!
Imagine being haunted by the
faces of the people you killed
day after day, night after night.
Not knowing who they were or
why you killed them.
I killed them on their way home
from work, coming out of mosques.
Collateral damage, oh that's all
okay as long as you hit the target!
We all have friends that we have seen get
killed or maimed in every way possible.
Stop it!
You want us to shut that off?
Mr. President, when you've been
in hell long enough you become the devil!
So consider this your cleansing.
Your exorcism!
Or your fucking baptism!
I don't fucking care!
Jesus, you are killing him!
Hey prez. You might like to know that the
water you are choking on is contaminated.
That's due to the no bid contractors
who were overpaid to do the
piping and water treatment.
So you can thank them
for that tasty flavor.
Please stop it. Please.
Still it's not neany as bad as
some of the shit they call food.
You know sometimes we had to wait three hours
in the fucking desert for food to arrive.
Have you ever had muddy spaghetti before?
Crunchy mashed potatoes?
Mmm good!
Had enough yet?
Water in the lungs stings
doesn't it sir?
So what do you think your father meant?
When he said "An honest man can see the lies
leaving his mouth like steam from his breath."
What do you care?
What do I care?
Why don't I do this again sir?
No. No, no, no, no, stop.
My family had a cabin in Minnesota
we'd go to in the winter.
I was 10 years old and my mother
forbade me from walking on the frozen lake.
I promised her I wouldn't.
But I did anyway because I
liked to go ice fishing.
My father caught me and he punished me
by making me shovel snow for hours.
He loved metaphors.
And he said that the steam coming from
my mouth were the lies of an honest man.
I tried to hold my breath for a
long time to make the lies go away.
But it kept coming back.
And reminded me of my wrong.
You see?
Hey Riggs!
What?
How come you are not
talking to me?
I've been busy.
We've got got The President
hostage and stuff.
I knew this wasn't a good idea.
You know the reason I came in here--
You know I gotta listen to
what's going on out there.
Riggs, if you would
just listen to me!
Every little sound,
every little noise...
Riggs! The reason I came in here
was because of you!
Son, you keep watching the door.
Tartakoff camera.
Yeah, yes sir.
Sergeant.
Stenson for Garrison. Over.
Go for Garrison.
What's going on in there?
Oh we're just playing
a little drinking game.
I need visual on The President.
Tanakoff let's roll.
Welcome back America.
How you feeling Mr. President?
I'm fine. I feel better.
- What the hell did you do to him?
- Nothing much.
Garrison what the hell did you
do to The President?
Nothing even close to torture.
Ain't that right Mr. President?
The deal was The President
was to remain unharmed.
You broke that deal a
longtime ago Stencil Dick!
Garrison if this continues
we're going to need to use extreme force.
I'm looking forward to that.
What are you trying to prove?
I still don't understand the point of all this.
That is a good question sir.
What is the point of all this?
I don't know soldier.
You brought me in here.
No sir. You brought us here.
Like a lot of people I was
sick to my stomach after 9/11.
I'm a patriot and I wanted bad to avenge the
deaths of those poor innocent Americans.
So I believed in you sir.
I trusted you, sir.
Now I may not have been a
professional athlete but I quit
a lucrative engineering job and
I recommissioned.
I know you're sick to death of looking at
these pictures because
I am too sir.
I am too.
Now I expected to be
going from cave to cave
looking for the bastards
who plotted those attacks.
I expected to be shot.
I expected to watch friends die.
But it'd be for a cause worth fighting for.
But you know what? Not a single one of these
motherfuckers had anything to do with 9/11.
Not one of these men had ever
planned to attack America. Ever.
So my question again sir.
Why was I ordered to kill these men?
Why are we here?
I think it is highly unlikely that I'm going
to come up with an answer to satisfy you.
On the contrary.
This is your one chance sir
to do something you have never done before.
To openly and honestly level
with the American people.
No dodging or grandstanding for the press.
Just the cold honest truth sir.
You know despite what you think
The President doesn't actually
have that much power.
A single term is four short years.
Lot of obstacles trying to move
through both legislative branches.
9/11 was a tragedy we all wish
we could have avoided.
But I'm gonna tell you something.
There wasn't a single soul in my
administration who feels otherwise.
Ow! Goddammit!
Is that that fucking soldier?
You're lucky Steve
only had two feet!
Downey knock it off.
Want me to answer these or not?
God yes, please sir.
Continue.
9/11 forced us to look
at the bigger picture.
We had an opportunity to stop a rogue
regime and make our
presence felt around the wand
where trouble was festering.
Everybody was on board.
Bipartisan.
Not a single decision
was made in isolation.
But your administration had a heavy hand in
forcing the issue and doctoring evidence.
We used the information available.
Yeah sure we emphasized evidence
that supported our position but
we did not doctor anything.
Did George Washington mislead his men
into fighting a war they couldn't win?
They ran from the British
army for seven years.
Not a popular item at the time either.
I didn't know you knew any
history Mr. President.
Yeah I didn't flunk
all my classes.
So let's just say that the
grand scheme of all of this
was to secure American
interests in hostile regions.
Was that the overall goal?
Longterm stability and security.
Okay, well how is security and
stability obtained when you
disband their entire military turning
loose half a million armed soldiers
who become the backbone of the insurgency.
We couldn't take any chances.
They were all members of a rogue regime.
Happy Thanksgiving!
Gobble gobble gobble!
For weeks after defeating
Saddam's pitiful resistance
we did nothing to restore order
and basic human necessities.
The top priority was to make a
mad dash for the oil wells.
The oil industry is the center of their
infrastructure and their economy!
It was vital that we
secure them immediately!
And while the country crumbled
and the insurgency took hold
assholes like us were sent in to
pick up the pieces.
These wounds they don't heal Mr. President.
Not ours, not theirs.
The anger will live on for decades.
Do you understand that?
Looks to me like you've
got all the answers.
Or at least the answers as
you believe them to be.
Gas!
You! You! Freezer!
- I don't have a mask!
- You don't need one. Go!
But what about The President?
He stays here with us!
You! Sit down!
Get in the fucking freezer!
Hey! Guard her!
Yes sir!
Hello everyone! Right now your
own beloved government is
pumping gas in here in
an attempt to incapacitate us.
Including your president. Fortunately
for us though we brought our gas masks.
Sadly we forgot
to bring one for The President.
So given the trauma that
The President has already been through,
even a small dose of an
incapacitating agent might be fatal.
Agent Stencil Dick of the Secret Service
if you're still watching...
I'd advise you to figure
out a way to reverse this.
Can you lower that please?
Thank you private.
So uh, how did you get into this?
Don't play no mind
games with me.
I'm not playing mind games. I'm
just asking questions.
That's what reporters do.
Cuz I'm on their side.
100%.
And whoose side is that?
Shit did he just move?
I don't think so.
Why did you join the Army?
I don't know.
Some of my friends were doing it and
it's better than working at Wendy's.
Is Riggs your boyfriend?
Riggs? No.
He ain't my boyfiiend.
He's just my buddy. You know.
Yeah yeah. I've got lots of guy
buddies back at the station too.
Yeah you mean like
guys you have sex with?
What? No! I do not have sex with them.
They are just my friends.
Oh. Right. Yeah.
Do you have sex
with your friends?
What? Me? No. Not all the time.
I mean no.
What's with all the
damn questions?
I'm a reporter.
I ask questions.
Oh.
Hows it looking Riggs?
Oh it's going down.
Still not totally safe yet though.
Yo Riggs. How long you
been nailing Tartakoff?
I'm not. I mean I haven't.
No worries bro.
I've boned lots of hoes too.
She ain't a ho.
Look man. When I was your age
anything with a hole was good to go.
So does she take it up the ass?
You gotta use the ass, man
because with the mileage on her the other
side is like fucking a glass of water.
Fuck you man!
Hey! Stand down!
I'm sick of this shit!
Sergeant go tug your turkey.
I think Captain Garrison is kinda right.
But The President is sorta right too.
I mean it is like how were we supposed to
know the Iraqis wouldn't be team players?
I mean know we kind of fucked up
some of their shit, but...
...we're trying to help
them and everything now.
I mean it's like show some
appreciation you know?
I mean it's like there is
no I in team you know?
Nope. And there is no
U in intelligence either.
What?
Oh forget it.
What? Oh.
It's all clear, sir!
Let's go.
Nice job Tartakoff.
Thank you, sir.
Keep an eye on her.
Looks like Saddams old chemical stockpile
finally went to some good use, huh, sir?
We've just gotten word that
The Secret Service...
Jesus I cant see.
...flooded the room with tear gas.
We're trying to get an expert right now
to join us over--
Come on just free
up my hands.
satellite to--
I still can't see.
...give us some information on
the chemical makeup
of that substance and what the
effects can be on The President.
Relax. It's just CS gas. It'll sting for awhile
but your body's gonna flush it out.
- On your feet.
- Why?
On your feet!
Shit.
Walk over there.
Riggs you set up over here.
Downey.
Come on, you're breaking
my fucking heart.
You want to know why your hands have
been duct taped to that stick sir?
Fuck off.
Infrared is being used to see
through those walls.
To them you look like a grunt.
I'd hate to be the poor dickhead
that shoots you thinking you are one of us.
May I sit?
No, you may not sit.
Sir, making prisoners stand
for extended periods of time
is another coercive technique
that you authorized.
Therefore it should be
perfectly acceptable.
Not when they're shot
in the goddamn leg!
Stand up!
Oh no actually sir, prisoners are often wounded
and fatigued when employing these techniques.
Stand up goddammit!
Can't I just lean against the--
Stand up!
Garrison stop him!
Cheer up buttercup.
I said stand up!
Tartakoff! Camera.
Act like a fucking man!
Alright I'm up. I'm up.
- Okay. Your turn.
- My turn for what?
Dildo torture. What do you think?
To ask him questions.
That's what you've been
waiting for isn't it?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh come on that's the reason you
came in here isn't it?
No they asked me to.
I had to.
Right. Right. You had a choice.
You have free will. Could have
said no but you didn't. Why?
In case you had not noticed he's
The President of the United States.
It was a completely selfless act.
Nice. A silicone Mother Teresa.
Alright. It was an opportunity. Okay?
Well darling here's your
chance to prove to your mummy
and your daddy how truly awesome you are.
You are on.
Tartakoff get him.
I'm sorry Mr. President.
It's okay Melody. I'm with you.
So uh, where's the
First Lady right now?
The First Lady oh she's at the ranch.
Maybe having dinner I guess.
And how is she?
Ow! Fuck!
What kinda bullshit
questions are these?
I want tough questions.
I want real questions.
No fluff less smile.
Be nice to the camera.
Go.
Okay. Um so whose idea
was it to go to war?
It was a collective decision.
But who was pushing for it most?
The VP, the Secretary of Defense.
But ultimately the decision fell upon me.
And do you think that your
legacy will be defined by
failed domestic and
international policy?
I don't know Melody.
Do you think your legacy will
be defined by your cup size?
Did you know that
Saddam was preoccupied
with finishing his fourth
novel before the invasion?
Nice one. Keep coming.
This for real?
Crime thriller.
No, I didn't know that.
He was a fan of
American pulp novels.
Do you think it's possible that
if he was busy writing his book
that he wasn't thinking about building
a nuclear arsenal to attack us?
Yeah I also think it's possible he
was doing both at the same time.
I made a judgment call and we erred
on the side of keeping America safe.
He was a third-rate dictator whoose
country was ravaged by sanctions.
Now how do you think he would
have had the infrastructure
to build and deploy nuclear weapons?
Well Melody. In addition to his novel writing
apparently he had some other hobbies.
Like gassing civilians.
What are you doing?
No dodging!
Ask him about his dad.
So uh, what about your father?
Did he approve of the war?
Yeah, he thought Saddam
was a threat to peace.
Actually he was urging restraint.
He knew an occupation would
be an endless hell hole.
I can't do this.
No, you do not get to walk away!
You do not get to tum a blind eye
to the realities of war!
Pretend it's all clean and sanitized
and that horrible things don't happen.
Get up!
War doesn't create guys like Downey.
It just gives them a creative outlet.
What were you neglected as a child?
Violent video games not
satisfying enough?
Not neany. I like to feel
the blood touch my skin.
So in fact you owe
this all to me, huh?
Because without this
war you're nobody.
You're right. I have a strange way
of showing gratitude don't I?
Then why are you in here?
Why aren't you out killing women and
children if you like it so much?
Because I figure by torturing
The President of the United States
I will be the envy of sadists
for generations to come.
Yeah, you're still a nobody.
You know that?
That makes two of us!
You know what?
Garrison doesn't even like you.
He uses you because you're helpful.
Nobody likes you!
- How can you let this go on?
- Easy Sergeant.
Have you ever smelled your
own flesh burning fucker?
Downey! Do not deviate
from the plan!
Sergeant! Back down!
Back down sergeant!
Sergeant! Sergeant!
At ease sergeant! At ease!
Stand down!
Stand down sergeant!
Stand--
Fuck! Goddammit Riggs!
You're out of your fucking mind.
Get him off me!
Breakit up! Break it up!
Break it the fuck up!
Get off me!
Come on! I don't have
time for this shit!
You are jeopardizing the
mission sergeant!
I always knew you were the fucking
weak pussymmipped fucking link!
You piece of shit.
You ugly--
Fuck you Downey!
Fucking--
Fucking cunt!
Call me a cunt again.
Private.
Come on.
Fuck.
You provoked him.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Sir! They're getting
ready to break in!
Rifles!
Back away from
the door Stenson!
Give me a visual on The President.
Back away from the door first!
What is that sound?
They're backing away.
Does anyone smell that?
Up there!
Stenson I need you
to turn this gas off!
Goddammit Stenson!
Down! Down! Down!
Tanakoff! Get down!
They're shooting
through the walls!
Get down!
Goddammit!
Freezer! Freezer!
You two! Freezer! Come on!
Now! Go! Move! Stay down!
Stay down! Riggs!
Riggs! Riggs! Motherfuckers!
Fall back Riggs!
Bring it on!
Do not discharge your weapon!
You're all fucking faggots!
Riggs! Riggs!
Fuck you!
Riggs fall back!
Fall back Riggs!
Fuck you!
Point the camera.
Isn't this over yet?
What more do you have to prove?
My mission is almost complete.
Point the goddamn camera.
Mr. President
are you In there?
Mr. President!
Mr. President can you hear me?
The door is rigged like
the vents Stenson!
I wouldn't touch it!
Mr. President!
Back away!
I still have a gun and The
President, Stenson!
Your antidote. Where is it?
Oh uh, I must have forgot
that in the kitchen. My bad.
You never had an antidote did you?
You just intended for me to die?
Sugar water sir.
What?
It was sugar water, sir.
That's another interrogation technique
that you and your cronies love. Sweet huh?
Put that down for just a second?
Why?
Can you just have her turn
off the camera for a minute?
Hey, let's, let's, um,
let's make a deal huh?
We uh... we walk
out of this together.
We can say whatever we see fit.
Anything you want.
You can come out of this thing
looking like a hero.
Like shiny medals and parades?
A new car every month sir?
Yeah sure.
Can you make me a senator?
Or a high-ranking cabinet position?
Oh no wait! How
about FEMA sir?
I don't know if I
Make me FEMA.
No soldier. I'm serious.
Me too. Camera back on.
Soldier I'm The President of
the United States.
This will embarrass the office
and the country forever.
You already did that
without any of my help sir.
Stand up. Stand up!
Don't. Hey come on.
Don't shoot me now.
Don't shoot me.
You don't have to prove anything.
Just don't shoot me.
You don't have to do this.
Sir is this how you want
to be remembered sir?
I've seen stray cats
die with more dignity.
No. No no no no. Please.
Im begging you. Not like this.
Your father was a man
of honor and integrity.
He believed in fighting for what was right.
Don't talk about my father.
But not you sir.
You are a dishonest man whose lies have killed
Americans for the sake of personal profit.
Shut up.
Your father was right sir.
An honest man can see the
lies leaving his mouth.
Only after you have been broken and beaten
and forced to see the truth
you see your own lies.
I want you to shoot me sir.
Your lies and actions have
killed thousands of people.
But you've been shielded by
impenetrable layers of bureaucracy.
I want you to shoot me because I want
the wand to remember this as your legacy.
When they speak or hear your name the
lasting image will be you putting a bullet into
a soldier's brain. Nothing
between me and your bullet sir.
No spin. No Patriot Act.
Just me and whatever's in
that rotten soul of yours.
Mr. President! Are you okay?
Mr. President!
Jesus.
Oh my God.
Mr. President.
We made it.
This is the most amazing thing
I've ever been through.
It was like being in a war.
I mean I know we're in the
middle of a war but this...
this is going to change my life forever.
Oh thank you Mr. President!
It's all possible now!
The Pulitzer Prize. My own show.
Oprah.
Mr. President. Are you okay?
No Stenson. I'm not okay.
Get me the fuck out of here.
No fucking way.
Get that out of here.
Prick.
Hey Stenson got your walkie?
Agent Davis. Nice set.
Where you at?
I'm in the mess hall, sir.
Very convincing. You might have
a second career as a reporter.
I appreciate that sir but
I still enjoy my day job.
See you in the
hospital shortly.
Yes you will.
Not a word of the broadcast left
the building Mr. President.
That's good. Hey uh get the VP
on the phone and my press secretary.
Yes, sir.
- Oh and one more thing.
- Yes, sir.
Bring me my cowboy hat.
Jesus Christ.
This is breaking news.
Good evening. We bring
you breaking news from Iraq.
The President made a daring
landing in Baghdad early
today to show his dedication to the troops
while honoring them on Thanksgiving.
Details are still coming in but we
do have reports that The President
has been taken hostage by--
Wait. Uh he isn't?
Yes. It has been confirmed that
The President of the United States
has been taken hostage by some...
...group of people.
The evidence shows that the
Islamic call to prayer
was heard moments before The President
was taken hostage.
A clear indication that Muslim
terrorists were involved.
At WOV News we always
bring the most equal
and equitable perspectives from some of
the most diverse minds around the world.
With us today are Dr. Francis McCarthy,
associate professor of theology at the
Christian American Academy of
Patriotism and Gerald Jones,
senior administrator at the Ayn Rand Institute
of Prosperity and Anti-Socialism.
Dr McCarthy what do you make
of what you have just heard?
I need to interject here Whit.
You heard the waver and
the call to jihad thing?
The call to prayer.
Clearly that was not a
heterosexual man.
A normal person who loves God does not
make that kind of a sound.
Our country is being actively
destroyed by gays and Muslims.
And liberals.
Since news broke of The President's
abduction many have been quick
to use it as a pulpit to peddle
their skewed political objectives.
From gay marriage to phony
claims of Sharia law
being enforced in your neighborhood
pundit is have flung
every right wing scare tactic in the book.
Of course the last thing
they would want is...
...real dialogue because that would
actually require you to think.
We go to our correspondent on the
ground in Baghdad who has more.
David what details can you give
us of this shocking event?
David can you hear me? What's
going on with The President?
Apparently David is unable
to hear me at this time.
Yes, we have reports from
the green zone in Baghdad
that The President has...
David we're having
trouble hearing you.
David?
And that is all we have been
able to find out so far.
I'm sorry David.
We missed all of that.
We want you tn think though.
So were putting the question out there.
What should we do?
Do they know who it was that
took The President hostage?
We believe it was a group
of people who took him hostage.
Now giving some uh, fresh perspective on the
issues are Dr. Norman Jasper Friedberg,
executive director at Washington
Think Tank "People Unified"
and Rupert Brannigan Emmy nominated
actor on the hit political drama
"The Oval Office".
Dr. Frieberg there's been a lot
of speculation on how, why and
who is responsible for
President's abduction.
What're your observations on the
circumstances leading up to this?
Well the symptoms of
contention in this debate
are en gendered by perpetual
historical amnesia.
The hostilities arising from the
chaos of conflicting ideas
cannot be diagnosed by
simple reflective analysis.
I see. So what you mean is uh...
What exactly do you mean?
Do we know if there were any
witnesses? Was anyone hurt?
Is The President okay?
As far as we know it happened
when a group of people
we believe took him hostage and took
The President to a being held hostage.
How could this have happened?
Clearly these raghead Muslims
want to destroy our freedoms.
It is the decline of moral
civilization.
This is leftist agenda at it is worst.
It's a symptom of big
government and overregulation.
So Rupert. Please share your perspective.
What do you think The President
is going through right now?
Well on The Oval Office I play the chief
adviser to The President not The President.
Of course.
So there is going to be a very
different character analysis
between The President and
the chief adviser.
Okay, so from chief adviser
perspective what are your thoughts?
Hmm.
As chief advisor I think I would have
recommended that he not go to Baghdad.
Well it's a bit too late for that.
What about now that he's been abducted?
Well now that he is abducted
I'd say the only person...
...to solve the problem
would be Jack Bauer.
If we do not do something soon this
country will lose all its moral compass.
I mean what should we expect next?
A black president?
Or a foreign-born president.
Even worse a foreign born
Muslim black president!
That is where we are headed.
Oh me oh my!
Thank you for your trust.
Im Whit Whitley WOV News
around the clock. Thank you.
Now for the results of our survey.
67% say not to negotiate.
Looks like you are SOL Mr. President.
Best of luck.
If you just tuned in we're
bringing you breaking news.
The President of The United States has been
taken hostage. By whom is still unclear.
and for what reason we're
still trying to determine.
How he was taken hostage is
still inconclusive and whether
anyone was hurt in the
incident we do not know.
We'll bring you the facts and be the first
to bring you the facts as they emerge.
This is Laura Reed for GNN
Global Network News.
What's so funny?
Dude this is hilarious.
You gotta check it out.
it's a news clip from the
comedy site The Artichoke.
The most awesome
news on planet earth.
Good evening. This is the
Artichoke and we are the news.
The President was abducted in Baghdad
while sewing Thanksgiving
turkey to American troops.
There have been many questions
surrounding how this happened.
We now have answers.
It was not Iraqis foreign Jihadists
or even Fidel loyalist Cubans. No.
It was U.S. Soldiers.
That's right. Members of our own
military have abducted The President.
We can't even blame the
French for this one.
Apparently unimpressed with The
Presidents faux concern for
troops that he sent to this
hostile place for reasons yet
undetermined a soldier grabs The President
and pulls him through an open door.
While in captivity the solider and several
others list their grievances to The President.
And more importantly #5.
Why the fuck are we here?
Hm. that is weird. It's
not there anymore.
Good evening my fellow Americans.
Tonight we had a terrible tragedy.
I personally witnessed evil
acts committed by cowards...
...bent on destroying our noble efforts
to make this a peaceful free country.
For those responsible for this,
they will soon feel the full
might of our determined efforts.
They can run but they can't hide.
We will find them and in
the end they will be ours.
Happy Thanksgiving to you.
God bless you and God bless the
United States of America.
Thank you.
♪ America kicks some ass. ♪
♪ From the NASCAR in Daytona to rodeos... ♪
Hi Ma.
Dad.
I guess if you are watching this you
probably know I'm not gonna be coming home.
Our government is fucked up.
And look I know it's gonna be
hard for you to understand
but you gotta try to see
it through my eyes.
You don't know how bad things are because
they wont let you know. But I'm telling you.
Things are really messed up here and they
is not getting better. The shit I've seen.
Headless bodies of marines
lying on the side of the road.
Kids blowing themselves up,
there is no god here.
It's just soldiers dying for oil.
For a lie. That's the shit
you don't see on the news.
You know I didn't think it was right at first
what we intended to do with the president,
but then I thought about it and uh,
I almost died myself on many
occasions and I got angry.
Angry because my life was about to be sacrificed
for some bullshit surrounding this war.
Angry because my buddy stepped on a mine.
You tell his parents that I
still cry every night.
There was this time we shot
this kid and his father.
We got the order from Centcom. They were
on a kill list and had to be taken out.
They were aiding the insurgency.
A9 year old boy
who knew how to build
sophisticated roadside bombs.
It was bad intel.
We killed the wrong people.
We weren't even in the correct province.
We killed innocent people because
this administration is so incompetent
and desperate to make good news
that they'll spin any intelligence
to make themselves look like kings.
Look at me. Look at my hands.
These hands you used to hold.
They murdered an innocent 9 year old boy.
Well you taught me right from wrong.
And this war is wrong.
Our government is wrong.
President's wrong.
We gotta make it right.
♪ We give thanks for this day ♪
♪ that all have in adoration. ♪
♪ Except for the poor natives ♪
♪ quarantined on reservations. ♪
♪ We give thanks for this day ♪
♪ that all have in adoration. ♪
♪ Except for the poor natives ♪
♪ quarantined on reservations. ♪
Don't worry.
I will pray before the mission.
Everything is gonna be okay.
I'm not going to hell.
I've already been there.