I've heard people say
that life is like a river.
And we're all
just tiny minnows
struggling through the freeze,
the thaw and the flow.
Sometimes it's
a momentous event,
a birth or a death that
causes the currents to shift.
And sometimes it's something
as simple as your best friend
going home early one night.
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
What is wrong with me
for ever fucking
being with you!
Listen...
-You make me so mad!
Will you listen to me? Please.
Sleep in the
fucking greenhouse.
- Dad.
Hey! Look who's still up.
Where's your best bud Teddy?
He went home hours ago.
He did, huh?
Here, sit down. Join me.
Take a load off, my man.
--Okay.
I bet you're wondering
why Mom has me out here, huh?
Mmm.
Well, can I tell you
something, hmm?
I'd like to talk
to another guy.
You know mommy's friend,
Mrs. Donahue,
did you know she's pregnant?
Hmm? She's gonna have a baby.
Oh.
The trouble is you know
who made her pregnant?
Me.
Mmm.
Is Mom pissed?
She is. I mean,
she's really pissed.
She doesn't think she
wants to be married
to me anymore
and now she's gonna be
even more pissed that
I told you,
but I think, you know, you
deserve to know the truth.
You're a big guy now.
What's gonna happen
to the baby?
Some babies are never
born at all, you know?
And some babies are born,
their parents take care
of 'em,
some babies, you know,
somebody else raises 'em.
You know, like, uh...
What's that stupid TV
show you always watch
with your sister?
With the two little black kids
and the rich white guy.
Oh,  Diff'rent Strokes.
Right, okay. Well
they're adopted, right?
So, you know all
about that, right?
I mean, that's...
That's another thing I've
been wanting to tell you,
you know, but
your mom's like...
You know, it's
gotta be the perfect time.
But I think that you should
know, you know?
Know what?
The truth about your life.
You're adopted.
It's not a big deal.
I mean Aristotle was adopted.
Lee Majors, you know him,
The Six Million
Dollar Man, right?
He was adopted.
Tons of people are adopted
and you wouldn't even know it.
Yeah, so...
I mean, there it is.
Does that mean
Mr. Donahue is my dad?
No!
Champ, come here.
Come here, come
here, come here.
I'm your dad for
crying out loud.
I'll be your dad forever.
Get up here.
Can I sleep
here with you, Dad?
Oh, I'd love that.
Mmm.
But I think your mom's
pissed enough at me,
don't you?
So get your butt
back in bed, huh.
You'll be here
in the morning, right?
Mmm, we'll see what
tomorrow brings.
I often wondered
if Teddy hadn't left
so early that night,
maybe I would never have
had that conversation
with my dad.
Maybe our lives would have
stayed secure and naive.
Maybe we would never
have met Eliza.
Maybe this whole story
would never have happened.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, God damn it, Teddy.
Okay. Okay.
Thanks, man.
Jesus, we have
a front door, you know.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Guess what?
-What?
-My mom took off again.
Shit.
She got shit faced last night
and then when I woke up
in the morning
her and all her stuff
were just gone.
Well, I mean she'll come back.
She always does.
Yeah, well, fuck it.
I don't even care.
I'm all about trying
to get to New York now.
My brother had the right idea.
Well, I'm all about
getting some weed.
It's New Year's Eve
and we're bone dry.
Hey, Prudence, can
I borrow 40 bucks?
What happened to
your glasses, Teddy?
I got contacts.
Oh, you looked better
with glasses.
My, uh, my
brother, he was telling
me about this college.
It's like, right
next to CBGB's.
It's free, it's just
really hard to get in.
You know college
is gonna suck just as
much as high school.
Yeah, but we'll
be in New York.
What's so great
about New York anyway?
No parents for one.
Speak for yourself.
Oh, shit!
-What is in there?
-It's resin.
I scraped it
out of my mom's pipe.
Well, at least she
left you something.
I think my dad's down
in New York too, actually.
What?
I thought you said
your dad died.
Yeah, that's what
my mom says, but...
Well, Johnny seems
to think she's full of shit.
Well, you know, this is beat.
Oh, shit.
-Check it out.
-What?
What are you doing?
--Oh, dude, gross.
Oh, yeah, it's Sandy McCoy's.
I'm telling you.
Oh, great.
Oh, it's hitting me hard.
-Okay, I'm ready.
-Wait.
Is it panty or panties?
Oh, okay, so panties
is plural...
- Shut up and take it.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, Mrs. H.
Hey, guys.
Mom, can I get a loan?
I already gave you
your birthday present.
Yeah, but I spent it.
Your father called again,
that girl Eliza will be
here at 6:05 now.
She's taking a different bus.
Who's Eliza?
Eliza Caplan.
The ballerina's daughter.
-Who's a ballerina?
-My dad's girlfriend.
Apparently Eliza was up
at a ski trip with some
prep school girls.
She's making a pit stop
here before heading home
after midnight.
That's even more of a reason
I'll need some money.
Well, let's hope your dad
sent her with some.
You know, I don't even
know why he sent her.
I don't know her.
Well, maybe he's finally
reaching out to you
without getting his own
hands dirty, of course.
You know my dad is an
absolute fucking asshole!
I mean, what, I've seen
him a few times in the
last seven years?
And out of nowhere he
sends this fucking girl.
Yeah, I mean like, your
average Manhattan girl is
way hotter than the
cream of the crop here
in Lintonburg, so...
Dude.
- You think that's...
- I don't know.
Excuse me are you, uh,
are you Eliza?
Which one of you is Jude?
That would be, uh, me.
You don't look like
a Prudence.
Oh, uh, no, Prudence, uh...
She's at home, I'm Teddy.
What's on your face, Teddy?
Is that some sort of Dracula
skate punk thing, uh...
Oh, right, um...
It's, we get it from...
We huffed turpentine.
Shit.
That is like, that's sad.
Happy New Year!
Wow!
Welcome to
exciting Lintonburg.
Yeah, this should be
interesting, right?
You know we should
probably just crash
Tory Ventura's party.
I mean, he's a total douche,
but he is a
major drug connection.
--Everyone goes.
Yeah, unfortunately
it'll be filled with
like, jocks and metal
heads, I don't know
if your boyfriend's
one of those, but...
No, uh... No, I
don't have a boyfriend
and if I did he wouldn't be
a jock or a metal head.
So you guys strike me
as Misfits fans.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
-No, we love Misfits.
I mean, we're into
all kinds of hardcore,
but, uh...
Are you? Nice.
Uh, my brother
actually has a band
in the East Village,
it's uh, Army of One.
They're like hardcore
but they're also like,
Straight Edge.
What's Straight Edge?
It's a whole other scene,
no drugs, no sex, no meat,
-like drinking or weed...
-Boring.
-Basically.
-Yeah.
-That's pretty boring.
-But, uh, their music's
pretty awesome.
I saw the Misfits once at
Irving Plaza when I was 11.
It was my first show
with the Necros and
the Beastie Boys.
You went to a show
when you were 11?
Yeah, I mean
I didn't go alone.
Who did you go with?
Your dad.
He put me on his shoulders.
I could see everything.
It was such a good show.
Christ!
Look, how long are you
gonna keep writing, huh?
It's New Year's Eve.
No, I've got to
finish Eliza's essay
for the Taft Academy.
Yeah, well shouldn't she
do that herself, hmm?
She did.
And she answered the question
about her future goals
with a 250-word essay
on her ambitions to be
a makeup artist.
-Mmm.
-Written in eyeliner.
-I applaud her creativity.
-Yeah.
-You would.
-Mmm.
You got any New Year
resolutions, Princess Di?
-Yes.
-What are they?
To stop dating my dealer.
Why would you do that?
With me you get the
whole package.
-Sex and drugs, huh.
-Oh, yeah I forgot.
...clocks, and then 1988!
I wonder how Eliza's
doing in Vermont.
She's doing great. Mmm.
Well, if your children
are anything like their father
I should be very worried.
Mmm, my kids are good eggs.
You'd have to actually be
around them to know that,
wouldn't you?
Well, I've been around your
daughter for years and let
me tell you something.
She is no delicate flower.
Dude, did I piss you
off before when I said that
thing about your dad?
Why would I be pissed at you?
It's not your fault
my dad's a prick.
Les is not a prick,
all right?
I actually think
he feels extremely bad
about everything.
What's everything?
Deserting you, uh...
Not being there for you guys.
You should have seen
him at Christmas.
He got drunk, all right,
and he was outside on
the balcony crying
like a baby.
It was right after he
talked to you on the phone.
You were standing there
when I talked to my dad?
He was in my apartment.
I mean, don't you
think it's sad though?
No, what's sad is how
he sent you to be his
little messenger.
Oh, my God.
Les would never do that.
In fact, he called me
a drama queen
and a sad story addict
for wanting to come.
No, you know my dad
is a sad fucking story.
Not me, all right?
Whoo!
Did I say something?
No. I'll be right back, okay?
Can you hold this?
Jude!
Oh, shit.
Whose car is this, man?
Who cares?
Jude, are you just
gonna sit there and be
pissed off at the world?
Eliza was just
trying to be nice.
She was also being
pretty fucking nosey.
Yeah, but she's also
pretty fucking pretty.
Right? You've got to admit.
She's pretty enough.
Enough?
Wow, you're picky.
You think she's hot,
don't you?
You got a boner for her, huh?
-Will you stop, asshole?
-Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Dude! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
- What?
Dude!
I lost my contact, man.
-Aw, shit.
-I spent all my money on that.
Uh...
Oh, wait. Wait, is this it?
Jesus, you found it.
I'm gonna find the bathroom.
Are you gonna come back
to the party?
Teddy!
There you are.
I've missed you, baby.
-Hey, Annabelle.
-Annabelle?
Yeah,
keep going just go.
Where are you going?
Oh, my God, that guy was
totally about to maul me.
Did you see that?
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Is that coke?
You can't be that country.
Have you never
done it before?
I, uh, snorted some
ground up chalk as a
joke once.
Well, your luck's
about to change.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit!
Whoa, whoa.
-Fucker!
-Oh, I'm sorry!
What the fuck are you
doing in my car, huh?
I didn't!
No, I wasn't!
You touching my
herb in my car?
-You fucking leaf thief!
-I wasn't!
- Have you lost your
fucking mind, Judy?
Uh...
Jude so hates
my guts, doesn't he?
And I came here to be
friends and as usual
I've screwed it up.
No.
Jude's actually really sweet.
He just doesn't like
to show it.
Something tells me
you're the sweet one.
What's this?
Oh, it's um, it's a
token for the subway.
--Get out!
Yeah, uh, my brother
gave it to me.
It's supposed to be good luck.
I'm sure.
Hey, can I ask
like a weird favor?
Depends.
If I gave you his address,
could you go see him
and get him to call me?
He doesn't have a phone.
Are you Indian?
What?
Uh, yeah...
Half.
Uh, Gandhi not Geronimo.
You have the most
amazing eyelashes.
Like the women in the
Bollywood movies.
Thank you.
There.
I like that better.
Oh, it doesn't matter to me.
I can't see anything anyway.
My contact fell out.
And where is it?
In my hand.
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm getting it moist.
Come here.
Which eye is it?
Is it in?
Think so.
I think so too.
Oh! Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Ahhh!
Three, two, one,
Happy New Year!
Jude!
-I'm fucking over here!
Jesus!
You okay, man?
-Untie me.
-Jesus.
What happened?
-Oh, shit!
-What the fuck happened?
Oh, my God!
Let me get this out.
Where were you guys
all that time?
Uh, just, you know, talking.
Did she say anything about me?
No. No.
Just that maybe
that you hated her.
I don't hate her.
This whole night
is just fucked up.
Pretty pissed, huh?
Sure you okay?
Yes.
We can begin with the panties
again if you want, man.
No, I have a better idea.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Freon, dude.
It's free.
You sure you know
what you're doing, man?
Yes, I've done it before.
I kind of just wanna go home.
-Jude...
-Jesus!
Stop being a pussy.
You owe me.
Okay.
I think we're good.
Dude, dude!
Take it!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Happy New Year's.
You're a dick.
-It felt good.
-Oh, shit!
Hey.
What the hell are you
two doing out here?
Jude!
You okay?
Are you okay?
What is it?
Oh, my God!
Oh, Teddy.
Teddy, wake up, honey!
Teddy, Teddy, honey, wake up!
Teddy!
Stay here, I'm gonna...
Don't move. Jude,
don't move, okay?
Don't move.
I'm gonna call an
ambulance.
Jude.
And a happy
New Year's Day, New York.
Here's to your hangover
with this classic
from Traffic.
Jesus Christ.
Lester's pad.
Hey, Harriet.
How'd it go?
You and Eliza have fun?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, what?
What? Who?
Oh, my God!
What you want, baby?
I got what you need.
Who are you
looking for?
I'm looking for Johnny.
His brother Teddy sent me.
You just found him.
You want a cigarette?
No, I'm Straight Edge
and Krishna.
Wow.
That's, uh, quite
a double bill.
Well, not really.
They complement
each other perfectly.
Clean living, transformation,
and transcendence.
It's funny you, uh,
having a brother that's like
completely opposite you.
We have different fathers but
we're more alike than we look.
Yeah, I don't really even
know him that well.
We just met actually.
So, you got no phone
in your place?
I've got no nothing in my
place. I'm squatting.
Rise and shine, Louie.
Need to use the phone.
All right, Johnny.
-Jesus, you all right?
-Yeah, thanks, man.
Mom?
What are you home now?
Where the hell have you been?
What?
What the
fuck are you saying?
This is all your fault.
You fucking cunt!
For the Lord does not
abandon anyone forever.
The book of Jude
tells us that when
Christ reappears,
he will not be alone.
But instead surrounded
by 10,000 saints.
Let us take comfort
in knowing that today
this number becomes
10,001.
Who's "TM"?
Just a boy who died.
Jude!
Is he ever
gonna go back to school?
Hey.
It's me!
Whoo!
I hope I didn't alarm you.
I just thought maybe
it'd be good if we had a few,
few seconds before the
girls knew I'm here, huh.
Nice.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
Come to kidnap you.
What did you...
What's with your hair?
Huh?
I'm sorry about your
buddy, Teddy, you know.
You hardly knew him.
Yeah, but I'm still
sorry, you know.
You got weed in here?
Maybe.
Maybe. Come on,
don't bullshit me.
Where is it?
Let me see it.
Mmm.
Ugh!
Where did you get
this ditch weed?
I stole it.
Yeah, well stealing's
not cool, Jude.
It's not cool at all.
All right?
From now on, you're only
smoking your dad's shit.
Phew!
What did you mean when
you said you were here
to kidnap me?
I'm rescuing you.
Taking you to the Big Apple.
And why would I go with you?
I'm offering you
Manhattan, champ.
Don't play hard to get.
Would I have to go to school?
Afraid so.
Well, fuck that.
I'm never going back.
Except for, I mean,
driver's ed, but...
Okay, New York public
schools blow anyway.
You're safer on the street.
But you're gonna have to
have gainful employment
and promise not
to tell your mom.
When will we leave?
Tomorrow morning.
Don't you just feel the
bad vibes in this place?
Seriously.
Pack up your shit, huh?
I'm gonna go say
hi to your mom.
Good talking to you.
You know what? Fuck you!
Uh...
-Hey, hold on a second.
-Prudence, my baby girl, hi!
- Um...
What are you doing here?
Look at you.
Growing up into
a stone-cold fox.
Uh, I'll be off in a
couple of secs, okay?
Yeah, I'm back. Sorry.
No, that, yeah,
that's what I'm saying.
Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm...
Hello, Les.
-Remember me?
-Yeah, hello.
How long have you been here?
Damn you look good, huh.
Long enough to have a
successful father-son reunion.
-Really? It went well?
-Yeah, yeah.
No, it went great.
We're gonna leave in
the morning.
I figure you might make us
something delicious, you know?
And then, maybe I
crash with you?
-Oh, really?
-For the night, yeah.
-Is that the plan?
-That's the plan, yeah.
Thinking you wouldn't have
worn that patchouli,
- if you didn't want a little  bit of Lester.
-   -Come on!
Stop, please!
Les.
-Come on, wake up.
Flashback's over.
-Mmm...
I thought we were gonna
have a lost weekend.
Oh, no.
I've had enough of
those to last a lifetime.
-One more time.
-No.
You have a long road
ahead of you.
-Come on, come on.
-Get up.
It'll only take
another second.
Your son is packed
and ready to go.
Harriet, come on,
come on, come on.
Baby.
This place is a shoebox.
Yeah, well it's a rent
controlled shoebox.
I got it off this lady
friend of mine who went
back to her husband.
The one you got pregnant
and left your family for?
Uh, no.
A different one.
She never had that
kid, by the way.
What about Eliza's mom?
Did you break up
that marriage too?
Uh, no.
Eliza's dad dropped dead
of a heart attack when
she was about...
Three.
He was some kind of fancy
pants lawyer I think.
Eliza's dad,
Teddy,
the almost-Donahue kid.
It's almost as easy to not
be here as it is to be here.
Yeah, pretty much.
Okay, I cleaned this
off for you.
Okay, this is your domain.
No pets.
Otherwise anything goes.
How about a little
pack-a-lolo before unpacking?
Hmm?
-That's fine with me.
-Yeah?
This is one of your
mother's finest.
I call her Gertrude.
"Hamlet, cast thy
knighted color off."
I guess you can see why
Eliza's mom won't spend
time here, huh?
Would you hold this for a sec?
It's all part
of my master plan.
These are tips that
you need to learn on
your way to manhood.
Truthfully you'll probably be
pulling a lot of ass now
that you're a New Yorker.
Did I already tell you
that I have a handgun?
You're serious?
Yeah, yeah.
.38 Special,
it's right underneath
the kitchen sink there.
His name's McQueen,
but don't ever touch it,
unless I tell you to.
Why would you tell me to?
I guess we should probably
talk about curfew, right?
What curfew?
Exactly.
As long as you demonstrate
that you are somewhat
in control of your
faculties, all right?
As long as you return at night
from wherever it is you go,
I am willing to forgo
any curfew.
Is Mom cool with all this?
If you stay out of trouble,
your mother doesn't need
to know everything.
She seems to be of the
opinion that this is some
kind of rehab clinic.
Which it clearly is not.
Understood?
Understood.
Glad to hear it.
Eliza!
I've got good news.
Les' son is in town,
and we're all having
dinner tonight,
which is, you know, I...
I think's a really good thing.
I'm in the shower.
You see, Diane used to be
a world-class ballerina.
And the thing about
ballerinas is,
when they're dancing,
they do a ton of blow.
And when they're retired,
they smoke a ton of grass.
So that's how you met her?
Yeah, well, no, actually I was
dating her friend first...
Hello.
Thank you.
Hi. We have a table for...
Oh, hey, hey!
Ladies...
Hi.
Come and join us
for a drink.
- Look at you.
- Hi.
How are you?
Jude!
Well, we're all
just so thrilled
you're here with us in
New York, aren't we Eliza?
Eliza, come on,
you've been whining about
meeting my kids forever
and now one of them
finally materializes
and you check out.
I'm not checking out, okay?
How do you like it
so far in New York?
Oh, it's so much better
than Vermont.
--And the music's great too.
And what kind of music
do you listen to?
Hardcore mostly.
Hardcore...
Is that one you know, Eliza?
Eliza knows it.
And she even saw
The Misfits in concert.
Right, Dad?
And what does
it sound like?
Um, have you ever
heard of punk?
Darling, I'm from England.
What do you mean,
The Clash, the Sex Pistols?
It's kind of, but a
huge scene in New York
right now is Straight Edge,
which basically means
no drinking, no drugs,
and, uh, just not
being promiscuous.
In the old days we
called that "square."
I'm not square, Dad.
-Yeah, well...
-Some of them are
recovering addicts.
-Mmm-hmm.
Some of them have
parents who are addicts.
Well, do you know what,
I think that sounds
like a fabulous organization,
don't you, Eliza?
Fabulous, darling.
Eliza.
Teddy's brother is in a really
popular Straight Edge band.
-Is he?
-I'm trying to find out
where he lives.
Well, that shouldn't be
too difficult, doesn't his
mother know where he lives?
Oh, his
mother's nice but...
She's crazy.
Off her rocker, yeah,
that too, right?
Do you have, um,
some more sake?
Yes, I'm dying for some
more sake. Let's get some
immediately.
Excuse me, hi, could we have
another large sake, please?
You have Johnny's address?
That's right by us. I mean,
it's a fourth tier hell,
but I'll take you over
there if you want.
This is Teddy's
handwriting.
How'd you get this?
Yes, how did you get
that, darling?
Excuse me, I need
to use the restroom.
Feels weird that she
got to Johnny's before me.
Yeah, but now I
get to show you.
I'm the best tour guide
in the world, man.
I'll tell you everything
there is to know about
this lovely little hamlet
known as Alphabet City.
Okay, the A in Avenue A
stands for, "Asking."
As in, "You're asking
for it."
The B stands for
"Buddy, watch your back."
The C stands for "Crazy."
As in, "Are you fucking
crazy?"
And D is for "Dude,
you are dead."
What, you serious?
I'm absolutely serious,
but the road to hell is paved
with some fun along the way.
Like check this out, right,
you see this right here?
-Does that ring a bell?
-Not really.
Album cover to Led Zeppelin's
Physical Graffiti.
-Oh, shit!
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got Lenny Bruce's
apartment somewhere down here
and Abbie Hoffman was
somewhere up here.
Back a block, you got the most
famous bathhouse in the world.
-Bathhouse?
-Yeah, it's like a place where
dudes like to soap each other
up and get crazy, you know.
That's gross.
Yeah, that's what the city
thought too, that's why they
shut it down, man.
AIDS is changing everything
around here.
Look how lucky
we are, you know?
World-renowned Tompkins
Square Park is right
outside our door.
Doesn't look,
uh, very park-like.
You sound like
all the yuppies
who want to get the homeless
out of here and make it
look pretty.
Like that's going to happen.
Well, don't be so sure, champ,
money's got a big mouth.
All right, this is you,
this is your block.
Should be right down there.
Yeah, but this is about
as far as I'll go,
it's too dangerous.
Well, thanks, Dad.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
-Thanks a lot.
-Okay.
Jude, run! Run!
Keep running, white boy.
Fuck you!
Hey, Johnny, it's, uh...
It's Jude, Teddy's friend.
I just moved here with my dad.
Thought you know, uh...
You made it out
of Vermont, buddy.
Come here, man.
It's like a little piece of
Teddy just walked in my door.
Guys, guys.
Meet Jude K-Horn.
He's a kid from my old hood
who just relocated to live
with his drug-dealer dad.
He was my brother's
best friend.
It says everything about him.
Hey.
-Hey, what's up.
-Hey, man.
Here, sit down.
-Cool dragon tattoo, man.
-Thanks.
Yeah, Johnny's masterpiece.
He's an artist with a
needle or a sharpie.
So, uh, Jude, tell me...
Word is that daddy's weed is
pretty out-of-this-world, huh?
Yeah, no, it's incredible.
Oh, excellent.
How long do you plan to exist
in the greatest city in the
world like a fucked up zombie?
Indefinitely?
Gentlemen.
Army of One has just
inherited their first
official charity case.
-Whoo!
-Yeah!
Oh, whoa, wait.
-What are you doing?
-Well, you still play,
don't you?
-I mean, a little, but...
-Yeah, okay, let's see what
you got, Vermont.
We'll start at the basics.
Minor Threat.
Darling, do you like
this shade of red?
Just bought it at Saks and
I'm not sure it's my color.
-Looks fine.
-Really?
We've got to go shopping
when I get back.
They've got some really
cute new things for
spring, you know.
Right.
Okay, darling, well the
car's downstairs.
I'm only going to be at
this silly dance conference
for three nights.
All my contact info is on
the fridge, Nina's here.
-Curfew's at 9:00, okay?
-Mmm-hmm.
And Les is around if you
need him for anything.
I love you.
I'm going to miss you.
-You won't be lonely,
will you?
-No.
All right, sweetie, call
me anytime, okay?
Have fun.
Your bag, miss.
-I'm sorry?
-Your handbag, miss.
-I'm just... I'm just
going in here.
-It's policy.
Fine, I'll just... I'll just
go leave it in the car then.
Hey.
It feels weird that we
haven't hung out, you know?
Yeah, I know. I've
been kind of preoccupied.
Well, I'm psyched you want
to check out Johnny's matinee.
You seem so different.
What do you mean?
More serious.
Well, look, I think I know
how to change that.
Check this out.
What is that?
It's shrooms.
I thought it'd be fun.
And Johnny mentioned
something about going
to a Krishna temple,
which could be, like,
seriously trippy, you know?
I thought you were going
whole-hog Straight Edge
with the new haircut
and all, no?
I just say that to bug my dad.
I'm mainly into it
for the music.
Well, I don't want any.
Come on, a little won't hurt.
I said no, Jude!
How come you would with
Teddy, but not with me?
What is that supposed
to mean?
You know,
they found coke in
his system.
So I figured, he had to
have gotten it from you.
You don't even know what
you're talking about.
Why would you say something
so shitty to me?
Do you have any idea
what I'm going through?
Calm down! I just...
I just thought...
You thought what?
I just... I just
thought we could party
a little.
Like when Teddy was here.
And maybe it would
feel like he was still
with us, you know?
I'm sorry, Jude.
Yeah!
What's going on?
We're right here
with you, we're on the train
going to Brooklyn.
You'll be fine.
Am I dead?
We're right here
with you.
Please, God, tell me
he's going to be okay.
This can't happen
to me again,
tell me he's going to be okay.
--Am I dead?
-Am I dead?
-No, you're fine.
You're all right.
Oh!
-What is going on?
Listen, you guys are
both just shrooming out, okay?
You got trampled on and
she got paranoid.
Is this your idea of fun?
She didn't take any.
Eliza, are you okay?
What the fuck?
Everything is
my fault, Jude.
I'm the one who gave Teddy
coke, don't you get it?
That's why I'm being punished.
No, no, I made him huff
fucking Freon, okay?
I'm the one who needs
to be punished.
My God!
This isn't about
punishment, okay?
I just want to stop it all.
No more drugs,
no more fucking up.
Abstinence and restraint
make one fit for immortality.
That's what these people
here believe, that's what
needs to come out of all this.
True commitment, all right?
Commitment from you, Jude.
-I'm ready to commit.
-Yeah.
I'm ready to stop.
-Eliza?
-I have to stop.
Don't you two get it?
I'm fucking pregnant.
Les.
-Yeah.
What's going on? I haven't
heard from Jude in over
a week.
Harriet, Harriet, that's
too much stress, too early.
It's not healthy
for you, babe.
Not healthy at all.
Put Jude on.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh, looks like he's
up and at 'em.
It's 7:00. You told me he
leaves for school at 7:40.
- Yeah, well...
Just hold on one second,
okay? I got another call.
-Les.
-Yello?
-Yeah, I, um...
I just spoke to
the housekeeper
and she told me that Eliza
was out all night with Jude.
You do know that she's
on strict orders to
be home by 9:00?
Oh, yeah, well,
they went to, uh...
Uh, Johnny's show I guess,
and it got late.
Who the hell is Johnny?
Jude's new best bud.
You know, he's Mr. Clean,
brainwashing my kid
to stay off drugs.
Just put her on, will you?
She is there, isn't she?
That's what she told the
housekeeper.
Well, yeah, look,
she's just, uh...
She's in the shower
and so why don't I just
have her call you back
in 10, okay?
Listen, I got somebody else
on the other line, all right?
Just hold on, hold on
one second, yeah.
--That's good.
Should we tell your mom?
She'll just make
me get an abortion.
What makes you say that?
Because she said to me,
"Eliza, darling,
if you ever get pregnant,
"you're getting an abortion."
You know, it's like Teddy
died that night
to be born again
inside you.
Yeah, that's kind of
how I feel.
Like it happened for a reason.
But sometimes I don't
know how I feel.
"For the soul, there's
neither birth nor death
at any given time."
What is that,
the Old Testament?
The Bhagavad Gita.
Maybe we should tell my dad.
He'll just tell my mom, Jude.
We shouldn't tell anybody.
That way we can control it.
Well, I obviously can't
keep it a secret forever.
Yeah, but after a certain
point, they can't take it
away from you.
And where is the baby
going to live?
I mean, are you planning
on staying in school?
You cross one
bridge at a time.
At the very least,
you should see a doctor.
I'm sure he'll ask to
see an adult.
Well, Johnny is an adult.
From here on out,
I'm going to be anybody
Eliza needs me to be.
We're in this together now,
we're a little family.
Right, Jude?
Jude!
- Jude!
- Shit!
Okay, okay, okay.
Jude, we need to discuss
this whole curfew again.
I thought we had kind
of a working arrangement.
You know?
Huh?
So you're just going to play
father now and lay a whole
new set of rules on me?
No, no.
I am going to revisit all this
after I have digested
my vegan breakfast, eh?
You know what I'd
like to know is
what my girlfriend's
daughter and my son,
and some weird Hare Krishna
dude are all doing together.
We're just friends, okay?
No, I'm not judging.
I mean, I met your mom
at an orgy.
So tell me, what did you think
of the show, last night?
That was last night? Feels
like 100 years ago.
I thought you guys
were really good.
It's a very weird
scene though.
In what way?
Well, I mean...
First of all, I might as well
have been invisible
to most of the guys there.
Do I look that disgustingly
pregnant already?
No. Don't take that
personally,
Straight Edge guys
are different.
They're not just about
meeting girls.
Well, what about you?
What about me?
Well, are you gonna...
Are you gonna wait till
you're married, or what?
I mean, that's what the whole
thing's about, right?
Not that there is anything
wrong with it, I'm obviously
a walking advertisement
for abstinence.
What the whole thing is
all about is community.
A hardcore family that's
free from all the bullshit
that was spoon-fed to
us by a generation
that would rather fry their
brains than purify them.
But I was,
I was asking specifically
about you.
Oh, well, you know,
I'm committed to the
Straight Edge life
but I'm also just as
red-blooded as the next guy.
Well, that's a very
vague answer.
It's none of my business.
I don't even know
why I'm asking.
Hey, listen...
I happen to think
you look really great.
Thank you.
And I meant what
I said before,
about being anybody that
you need me to be.
I know you did.
Hey, I thought I'd never
get away from him.
You didn't tell him
anything, did you?
Of course not. I promised
Eliza I wouldn't.
So when Eliza's mom
finally finds out about
our secret,
I think we should tell
her I'm the father.
Why you?
Well, I'm Teddy's
brother, so it's blood.
And I'm also not a minor,
which you know,
could help us out in a lot
of legal situations.
And, and then what?
And then we tell her, Eliza
and I are a committed couple.
Why would we do that?
'Cause maybe we should be.
Except for the fact that you
barely know each other.
We're already getting to know
each other, right, Eliza?
We did have a nice brunch.
Yeah.
Anyway, look, nothing
should get in the way
of what is in the best
interest for Teddy's child.
You know.
This is about love.
Plus, there's nothing
not to like about me.
I got to go.
-I'll call you.
-All right.
Spare change?
She's something, isn't
she, Uncle Jude?
Gross!
Mademoiselle Eliza?
Okay, we're here.
I agreed, we're on the
train. You want to tell me
what's going on?
Eliza's bleeding.
Bleeding? What kind
of bleeding?
You know, like a,
like a woman bleeding.
Okay. So what makes you think
I'm more qualified to deal
with that situation
than her mom?
She's pregnant.
Are you shitting me?
Jude, what are you
thinking about?
You know I got a buttload
of condoms in my pad.
It's not mine, Dad.
And even if it was, you're
in no position to preach.
Okay, okay, well who...
Who's done the deed then?
Johnny.
Johnny?
Why is Johnny not on the
train going to meet her?
He doesn't have a phone.
Perfect.
You can't tell Diane yet, Dad.
You have to promise.
In downtown
Manhattan's Alphabet City,
tensions continued to rise
today, when a stand-off
occurred between squatters,
their supporters and the
police over a building
deemed unsafe.
If she loses the baby, okay...
I mean, you hate to say
this, but it's probably
for the best.
You know, she's not
ready to be a mom.
It's nature's way of
taking care of things.
How does it happen?
I mean, is it just
like blood or...
I do not know.
I'll tell you this though.
It's a relief to me that
you're not the dad, okay?
You don't want to get
tied up in that.
You know, the lady's
grieving, she's distraught,
she feels guilty,
you feel guilty.
Babies.
You know you were born here?
It's true.
The night we adopted you,
your mom and I we were
up in the nursery
in these rocking chairs,
they gave us scrubs
with these little
shower caps for our heads
and for our feet,
like they thought we were
going to give you the plague.
We just waited and waited
and waited
for you.
Seemed like we'd wait forever.
Rocking back and forth,
you know,
your mom was so uptight.
She was so worried your
birth mother changed her mind.
She had this king size
bag of M&M's right,
and she just
ate the whole thing
while she was waiting
for you.
And then they, uh...
They let us hold you.
And you were so little,
like a rabbit or something,
you know, with this
shock of black hair.
And you looked at me
and I was like, "Holy shit!
"This kid is mine,
"and the world's a fucking
mess and I just wanna...
"I want to protect him
from everything, you know."
I mean, I have to protect
him from everything.
Oh, I walked out of here
a different person.
Yeah, well...
So I thought.
And then Prudence
miraculously shows up.
Right, first they tell you,
it's impossible.
Next thing, you're swimming
in babies, two in one year.
You know women,
they make their decisions
and men, we just do our best
not to be men.
The whole system needs
a looking over.
Les.
Oh, Jesus...
Hey, sweetheart.
"Bacterial vaginosis."
Sounds exotic.
It's just an infection, Les.
Yeah, still, it sounds
scary, you know?
He saw her on the monitor,
you know?
She was jumping around
like a jumping bean.
She?
-So they told you?
-No.
No, I mean, I didn't
want to know.
For some reason I keep
calling it Annabelle.
Oh, well, your mom's
gonna be psyched.
You know, we're getting
you home before 9:00.
-No screaming, okay?
-Yeah.
All right. Okay.
I can't believe you, of
all people, ratted us out.
I didn't tell her!
She got the one bill the
hospital didn't send to
my apartment.
That's how far I've gone
to cover for your asses.
Anything for
a pound, right, Les?
Leave the actual parenting
to somebody who has the time.
Okay, you can blame me for
screwing up my own kids,
-but this one you
can't pin on me, okay?
-Thank you.
Well, I suppose I could've
kept better tabs on her,
if I just let her drop out and
smoke reefer all day, hey?
I don't smoke reefer anymore.
Okay, listen, you two are
peas in a pod, all right?
You know why she doesn't
tell you anything, Diane?
Because you try to control
every situation you get
your hands on.
And you know why she does
that, 'cause you are totally
out of control, all right?
What, you been kicked out of
19 schools already.
Two, Les, two.
You love to exaggerate,
don't you?
Yeah, well no wonder she wants
you to go to this Florence
Critteren facility.
Shit!
-Florence who?
-Oh, God.
Why would I need to go
to a facility?
It's the only place
that'll have you.
It's a place where
they take your baby.
No, no, they don't take it.
-They don't sell it
into slavery.
-They don't.
They give it to loving
parents who can take care
of it properly.
You mean people
like my dad?
Oh, God! Okay.
Okay, that's this, this,
what's his name?
Johnny.
-Johnny, thank you.
Okay, so what I don't
want right now, is a big
scene, okay?
Okay.
This is an adult situation
which we're all going
to get through
like civilized people, right?
I've even had Nina make us
all a nice leg of lamb.
We're vegan.
So I hear you three have
been spending quite a
bit of time together.
- Oops, sorry.
It's like they speak
in code, isn't it, Les.
They say, um, "Straight Edge,"
-vaygan...
-Vegan.
-Vegan's are from the
the planet Vega.
-Vegan, sorry.
Vegan, yeah.
We just go to the
temple mostly.
Yeah, I heard.
The, the temple.
Not like the temple where
Eliza was bat mitzvah'ed, no.
-Hmm.
-It's the Hare Krishna temple
in Brooklyn.
No, of course it is.
So what do you do for
a living Johnny?
I'm a musician.
I'm also a tattoo artist,
but I don't... I don't tell
too many people that,
'cause it's illegal in
the city right now.
- You don't have
to worry about
telling her anything,
she's practically married
to a drug dealer.
-Uh-uh, a botanist.
-No, we're not even
remotely married.
Specialty in cannabis.
So do you manage to make
a decent living applying
your tattoos?
Um, I'm getting there.
I work out of my
squat right now,
so there's not a whole
lot of overhead.
-That's smart.
-In fact, there's none.
What about your family,
where do they live?
You know, I don't really
have much family, ma'am.
-But I will soon.
-Christ!
Sorry.
-Sorry.
-No, I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry that my
entire existence
- has disappointed you.
-Okay...
You know I bet that first
kid you aborted would have
been a real winner.
-Eliza!
-You obviously picked
the wrong fetus.
For God's
sake, Eliza!
-Oh, my God!
Here's the fact, ma'am.
I want this baby just as
much as Eliza does
and nothing in this world
is going to change that.
So given that, I feel like
now is as good a time as any.
What, no, stop.
Wait, okay, okay...
Sorry, hello? Dinner
is officially over. Les!
Yeah, okay, yeah.
Hey, hey, Johnny, Johnny...
It's a school night,
so I think you should leave.
-Les, could you help him go?
-Yeah, come on, man.
I thought this
is what we wanted.
-Bad timing, bud.
-Bad timing.
-Good night, sweetheart. It
was really nice to meet you.
I'm sure I'll see
you again soon.
Um, thanks for coming, okay?
You're not going anywhere.
Les!
Shh, shh! Hey, come on now.
Hey, it's 3:30 in the morning,
all right? Jude's asleep.
Good. I need to talk
to you alone.
Oh, my God!
How did you escape?
Waited for her Valium
to kick in and slipped
out the service stairwell.
Oh, great, great.
So, what, you're gonna,
you're gonna move in with us?
-Only temporarily.
-Yeah?
Johnny and I are getting
married and I'm going
on tour with the band.
Okay, well, just so you know,
that's about the worst
fucking plan I've ever heard
in my whole life, okay?
I do know. Have you got
a better one?
I do. You have the baby here
and then, you know, we sell
it on the black market.
I got a dude in Brooklyn who
says he'll give us an easy
10 grand for a white one.
And what if it's not white?
Well, that sounds like a
conversation you should have
with good old Johnny.
Come on, you really
want to marry this
necklace-wearing Hare Rama?
You love this guy?
-I love how much he cares.
-Right, and...
And we can't get a real
marriage license till I turn
18 without parental consent
and that's obviously not
going to happen.
It's more of a spiritual
union thing at the temple.
Okay. All right, well.
Why don't you just try playing
it all a little bit by ear,
you know?
Is that what you do, Les?
You just play it all
by ear?
Yeah, I find it's the best
organ to play by.
Yeah, I mean, I have been
accused of playing by another,
but, uh...
Come on.
No, hey.
Come on, you're just so young,
sweetheart. You are.
I just need some place
safe to go, Les.
Some place
I can actually think,
away from her.
You know, if I help you out,
it'll pretty much destroy
what's left of my relationship
with your mother, right?
Well...
Oh.
Did you meet my old lady
when you were out there
in Vermont?
No. We were too busy
with sex and drugs.
Well, she's a piece of work,
you know, but...
...she's better at this kind
of shit than I am.
You know, I believe in
this and I have to do it
for Teddy.
Neither of us had
a father in our life.
It would mean a lot to me if
you'd say, you'd understand.
I can't say that
because I don't.
There's a strong tradition
in lots of cultures
that when a man dies,
his brother steps in
to marry his wife.
It's even in Krishna
consciousness, re-read
the  Laws of Manu.
They call it
"widow inheritance."
Now that's fucking romantic.
So you're just going to carry
your brother's ashes around
with you, forever?
Rooster, come on.
Not even the dead
get to be free.
Les!
Open the door, you fuck.
I know you're in there.
-Just trying to get
my daughter.
-Oh, all right.
Les!
Hey!
Take good care of her,
Saint Jude.
It's a bit late for that, Dad.
The van's a piece of shit.
I'm talking about
Eliza, champ.
- You should talk to
Johnny about that.
-He's her husband now.
-Mmm.
At least in the
eyes of Krishna.
You don't sound too
happy about that.
-What are you going to do?
-Hmm.
Try to get Princess Di
off your trail,
if she'll even talk to me.
You know, I really
appreciate all this.
What else am I gonna do?
After being such a
useless shit for...
Let's get this show
on the road!
Yeah, all right, all right!
- Take it easy, Jude.
- Sorry.
God, he's only had his
license for, like, a week.
Oh, I hope we make
it there alive.
Is, uh, is Rooster
not coming at all?
Oh...
Rooster is, uh...
He's gonna play with
another band for a bit.
Why's he doing that?
Well, the lead singer, uh,
had a really bad
heroin problem
and needed a good influence.
So who's gonna play
guitar for Army of One?
Well...
There is an open slot, my man.
This time
you've really crossed
-the line.
-Okay, tell me, what
was I supposed to do?
Certainly not lend
them your van, Les!
They were gonna run away
to God knows where.
I convinced them to
take her to Harriet's
-where she will be safe.
-Well, now you can
take me there then.
-No, I can't...
-Okay?
No, she says if you show up
there, she's gonna go on
tour with the band.
--Hopping from
motel to motel...
Come on, that's no life
for a pregnant teenager.
Why is she
doing this to me?
Look, I, I have their
confidence, okay?
There's a, there's a open line
of communication, right?
Now, Harriet will tell
me everything.
Eliza is in good hands.
Come on, babe.
I know it doesn't
seem like it,
but I've been doing
all this for you.
You really need
to leave now, Les.
-Jude.
-Hey, Mom.
Hi.
Look at your hair.
-Is it really you?
-It really is.
-Something smells good.
-Mmm, come in.
And you must be Eliza.
- Hi.
- Hey, Prudence.
Tell me, sweetie,
you're how far along?
-I'm almost six months.
-Wonderful!
Then you're way past all that
morning sickness nonsense.
- Mom says you started smoking.
-  I hope it's only cigarettes.
Come in, it's nice to see you.
Come in, I have a
vegetarian dinner...
Oh, my God.
-...or breakfast,
or whatever, on.
-Hey, hi.
-Well, come on, come
in. Hello, Johnny.
Harriet's so great.
So easy to talk to.
Yeah.
She was... She was so
good to Teddy too.
You know?
She was like... She was like
the mom he never had.
So I guess this is, uh...
It's kind of like
our honeymoon, huh?
Yeah.
Well...
It ain't exactly
Hawaii, but it'll do.
Yeah, but it tastes
so much better without the...
No, I asked for
a salad and you would come
back with one-inch carrots!
- I remember that,
I remember that.
"Okay, need a few
more." Very sweet.
No, no. We
were just gonna have one
carrot, that was dinner.
How much of this do you want?
Um, well, I see four
there, so probably four.
I'm hungry.
Excuse me one
second, guys.
Sure, hon.
Hello?
Eliza?
Yeah, but... But...
Why, why...
Why would you move
to California?
That isn't fair.
It's not like we ever
had anything that was defined,
you know?
That's how you wanted
it, Rooster.
Maybe we both use the scene
as a cover, huh?
I know.
Please don't do anything
until I see you.
I just lost my brother,
I don't need to lose you too.
And the first leg
of our world tour
comes to an end.
Whoo!
What're you doing
up at this hour?
I could ask you
the same question.
Annabelle won't let
me sleep anymore.
Plus...
Johnny boy snores.
What're you writing?
-It's just some lyrics.
-Hmm.
For a song.
Is it about a girl?
No.
No, it's not like that.
Oh, come on.
With that beautiful face,
I'm sure you have to beat
the groupies away by now.
You know that's not
what our scene's about.
Jude...
Are you really gonna
let those stupid,
Straight Edge rules keep you
from finding true love?
You know, today is
Teddy's birthday.
He would have been 18.
Happy birthday, Teddy.
I don't, I don't understand.
You said that whenever
you weren't playing,
you would be with me.
I know. I got to make
sure my squat's okay.
You know, the city,
they're evicting people
left and right,
now that the yuppies
want to live there.
It's crazy.
Don't be mad, okay?
I'm working on a new
plan for both of us.
Jude, have you...
Have you ever thought about...
Searching for
your birth parents?
Not really.
I, uh, I was talking
to Eric in your band.
He told me he met his
birth mother in Korea.
He said it was
a great experience.
Eric's adopted?
His last name's Steinberg,
what do you think?
I don't know, I mean,
he never talks about it.
That's because
he's okay with it.
He's got such an
interesting perspective
on how life works, that guy.
Why're you talking to Eric
about stuff like this?
I think Johnny's got
someone else.
Why aren't you
saying anything?
I don't know what to say.
Maybe you do.
Maybe you do, Jude,
and you just won't.
Eliza...
Just say it.
Johnny and I
are a sham.
Oh, God.
This whole thing's a big joke.
You're gonna have Teddy's baby
and it will be beautiful.
I don't even remember
what Teddy looks like.
Fuck!
I try.
I try really hard when
I'm falling asleep at
night, but I just...
I can't seem to put his face
together in my mind.
You should have said.
I, I have pictures of him.
It's not... It's not
about pictures, Jude.
You and Johnny are
exactly the same.
You both want some little
replacement for Teddy.
That's why I call her
Annabelle.
So that everyone
will just stop it
and think about me
once in a while.
- Listen...
I will always be here for you.
-Hey.
-Hmm?
Eliza...
Jude, Jude...
-Stop.
-No, I wanna be with you.
Jude, Jude...
Do you really want to lose
your virginity
to some messed up, pregnant
girl in a green house?
Yeah.
Wait, what makes you think
I'm a virgin?
Teddy told me you both were.
Thanks, Teddy.
Oh, God.
Sorry.
Oh, Jude...
So, how long
will you be gone?
I don't know. I just
need to confront Johnny
and then I'll decide.
I can't just sit
around here anymore.
-But you'll come back before?
-Yes, I will.
Whether he wants it or not,
I want you, of all people,
to be there when it happens.
That means the world
to me, hon.
Thank you.
You'll come back soon?
So I can tell you how
very proud of you I am.
I will, Mom.
Hello?
Harriet?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Diane.
Diane Caplan.
Oh, shit!
So, I'm sure you've heard
that I was against all this.
But I'm...
I've had some time
to think about it now
and I'm prepared to accept it,
and to help her in
whatever way she needs.
That's what I came
to tell her.
Well, I feel awful.
It didn't occur to me that
you would actually come
when I called.
I just wanted you to know
how much she missed you.
No, you were just trying
to help. I...
I'm famous for my bad timing.
I actually would have
been here sooner
but I was terrified of
driving myself and...
God, that must sound so silly
to a woman like you, but...
I didn't want Les
to bring me here
because I thought
that might be, um...
You know... Awkward.
That could be awkward.
Little bit.
Well, I'm curious,
you just said,
"A woman like you."
Uh, what did you mean by that?
No! I didn't mean...
God, no. I, I just
meant that you, you...
Strike me as
somebody who's, um...
You know, who's hardy.
Ha, that sounds like a
polite way of saying bumpkin.
Gosh!
-I've insulted you
already, haven't I?
-No, no. It's fine.
I am a bit of a bumpkin,
and I'm hardy too.
It's okay, it's okay.
But you know what,
believe it or not,
I don't drive either.
-Really?
-Mmm-mmm.
God, how do you
manage that out here?
You're in the middle
of nowhere.
Wow!
What's so funny?
Do you think that when
we get older and...
We've, like, drifted
apart 'cause...
Let's face it, the odds
are that we will, right?
Will you remember me as
the most fucked up girl
you ever knew?
Hmm.
I would.
And in the East Village
the police set up a perimeter
around Tompkins Square Park
in anticipation of a clash
over the community board's
new rule.
Angry locals blame
gentrification...
Just leave us off here.
Excuse me?
What is all this?
Fucking mayor wants a curfew
in the park to get rid
of the homeless.
But we know he wants
to get rid of us too.
Come on, let's get
out of here.
I really don't
know how to thank you for
everything you've done.
I feel like I should offer
you money or something.
Don't be silly, I've enjoyed
having Eliza here.
I think it was good for me.
In what way?
I don't know, really. I...
I suspect it had something
to do with the idea of
Jude's birth mother.
She was apparently
the exact same age.
-Was she?
-Mmm-hmm.
What happened to her?
I don't know.
I do think that even
with all this mess
we've somehow managed
to raise spirited,
-smart kids, you know?
-Right, in spite of ourselves.
- Yes, and especially
-despite Lester.
-Yeah.
Hey, Mr. Clean.
Come on in, there.
-Yeah.
-Hi.
Okay, I, uh, I
organized this little soiree.
Have a seat, uh...
These two showed up
at my doorstep.
And it seemed like
there was some serious air
-that needed to be cleared.
-Yeah, I know.
You haven't called us
for two weeks.
You really think
that's acceptable?
Only because I needed to wait.
For what, Johnny?
For the baby to be born?
No. To be 100% sure,
but now I am.
So I'm really glad
you're both here.
Sure about what?
What is this?
That's Ravi Milan
and his wife, Arpeeta.
Ravi's a lawyer.
Why do we need a lawyer?
Ravi's also Teddy's dad.
I knew, I knew from my mom
he was in New York somewhere
but I, I never
attempted to find him.
I, I always figured
that Teddy would do
that someday, but...
You know, lately,
it occurred to me
that Teddy's dad might
be able to help us out
with money.
You know, for the baby.
And, and after having
finally met him,
I think he can help us out
with so much more.
Like what?
Well...
Like with a home.
What're you saying?
The Milans, they have
no children.
When I spoke to Ravi
he was crushed by what
happened to Teddy.
He felt like he completely
missed out on the chance
to ever get to know him
because of my mom's insanity.
What're you saying?
Adoption is something the
Milans have discussed
for some time now.
Oh, my God.
This is what you've wanted
the whole time, isn't it?
-No, no.
-Isn't it?
Well, why didn't you
just fuckin' say so from
the beginning?
-Why did you have to
put me through all this?
-Whoa, whoa...
Eliza, Eliza, what I wanted
was for Teddy's child
to be with family.
Teddy's child?
Teddy's child.
-At the time I thought that
that could only mean me.
-It's Teddy's child?
I can't believe this.
I can't fuckin' believe this.
But Ravi has so much more
to offer a child than us.
It's everything
we wanna give Annabelle.
But better.
I can't believe this.
Oh!
--Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa! Hey, Jude...
You're a fraud! He
just wants to be with
his fuckin' boyfriend.
He wants to run to California,
just toss Eliza and
the baby aside.
-That's not how it is.
-Tell the truth!
Jude, hey, hey.
Fuckin' liar!
Eliza!
Excuse me, excuse me.
I don't really know
what's going on.
Jude is right.
I've fucked everything up.
All I wanted was to finally
do right by Teddy.
We say fuck you!
Eliza!
I have the
right to be here!
Eliza!
Get back here!
Hey, hey!
Eliza!
Asshole!
Hey, Eliza! Are you okay?
All right, watch out,
all right?
She's pregnant!
-Nobody gets to lay a claim
on this baby but me, Jude.
-I know.
Nobody!
I wanted to have a family.
Just a family, a good family
who wants a baby,
not people trying to
bring Teddy back,
not some long-lost father
who's trying to make up
-for his shitty past, okay?
-I know.
I just want a family,
that's all I want!
Whatever you want,
that's what we'll do.
Okay?
Now let's just get
the fuck out of here.
Is the baby okay?
Oh, hey, hey, hey,
the patient speaks.
Baby's right as rain,
sweetheart.
How are you?
Oh, I kept my eyes shut
tight the whole time.
I didn't want
to see anything.
-Then I asked for them to
give me something to sleep.
-Mmm.
You know, you've been
asleep for seven years.
-This is your fourth child.
-Stop it, Lester.
It's okay, Harriet.
He means well.
Sweetheart,
the nurse wants to know if
you'd like to hold the baby.
They say it's too easy
to fall in love.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
But I want Jude to.
Now?
Yeah.
Follow me, Jude.
Oh, my girl.
My brave, brave girl.
You know, I was
thinking that, uh...
You know, if you wanna be
we could be roommates again.
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got a lead on
an apartment that...
Looks like it could be
a lot bigger, you know,
two rooms.
-Yeah, that'd be awesome.
-Hmm.
If a guy's gonna get his
shit together, you know,
he needs a little space.
And I'm speaking
for both of us.
Here it is.
I always thought
he'd look like Teddy.
He doesn't look
like Eliza either.
He just looks like himself.
You think I'll ever
see him after this?
In 10 years, he's going to be
a completely different person.
And so are you, champ.
Go in there. Go say hi.
There you go.
- Make sure to
support his head.
It's okay.
If Teddy hadn't
left us for good,
if he was still somewhere
up there, 10 years later
hovering above the city
in the troposphere
of the earth,
he'd see a little part
transformed.
He'd find Eliza in Brooklyn,
starting her own family.
And his best friend,
believe it or not,
about to become
a father himself.
He'd know that he had
not been forgotten
even if the outlines
of his face
grow fuzzier with
each passing year.
Maybe he'd also see
how fragile each
and every life is.
And that they all just fall
to earth and scatter
hoping to settle
somewhere and stick
like big, dry snowflakes
from a white Vermont sky.