David, writing:
"Dear Vicky,
"during my time away from you,
"I've learned more
about the circumstances
"surrounding the death
of my brothers
"at the hands of tong po.
"Tong po...
"The same man that had me framed
"and sent to prison.
"It started with my brothers
Eric and Kurt.
Eric went to Thailand
to fight their champion."
Reporter: How do you feel
about fighting
our champ tong po?
Piece of cake.
Reporter: Think so?
That's the way they fight here,
I told you!
Motherfucker wants
a street fight?
I'll show him.
Let's cancel.
No.
Let's cancel, please!
No!
David: "He permanently
crippled Eric by cheating."
No!
"Kurt wouldn't take Eric
back to the U.S.
"Until he avenged the defeat.
"To prepare
for his battle with po,
Kurt studied with
the legendary Xian."
Xian: You must learn
to be faster
than any punch or kick.
David:
"After months of training,
Kurt was ready
to face tong po."
I'm a better fighter
than I ever was before.
I'll win that fight
for you and me.
Yeah!
"Kurt won his fight."
"He avenged our brother
and dishonored po."
"Disgraced by his loss,
"tong po tracked
my brothers down
"and shot them to death
in an ambush.
"But killing my brothers
was not enough.
"Po traveled to America
to force me to fight him
so he might regain
his honor."
The most dangerous weapon
in the universe
is a focused mind.
"Having quit fighting to teach,"
"I wanted no part of this war."
David Sloan will give
tong po the rematch
that his brother's
death denied us.
"His men set fire to my gym,
killing a young boy."
David!
"Now I had no choice
but to face the enemy."
This is my fight.
It's just something
I got to do now.
David:
"After winning that fight,
"I thought I'd seen
the last of tong po.
"Then you and I met,
started our school,
"and everything
was wonderful, Vicky...
"Until my arrest.
"But even that isn't enough.
"I've heard tong po's men,
"the same ones that framed me,
may be after you.
"You must hide and remain safe
"until my release.
I love you, Vicky.
David."
Man: Get out of the car.
Come on!
Vicky: I can walk!
You'll walk when
I tell you to walk.
Come on!
You see this?
This is home.
Ha ha!
Let's go.
Let's go pronto!
Come on, baby.
Asshole!
Both of you shut the fuck up.
You think you're tough,
you got a big boyfriend.
Get down!
Take the cuffs off.
You sure, amigo?
Just do it.
Hey, you the boss-man.
Come on, baby.
Like that, right?
No boyfriend's gonna
save 'em now, huh?
Aah!
Uhh!
Let me tell you something!
Listen to me, huh?!
Only men got balls,
you stupid bitch!
Hello, Mrs. Sloan.
I hope that you had
a pleasant trip
crossing the border.
Vicky: Who are you?
Why have you brought me here?
Maybe...
You've heard of me.
Tong po.
I've heard of you.
You're the pig
that framed my husband.
I am afraid so.
However, I thought
I'd make it up to him
by taking care
of his little wife.
Go, po.
No! No!
Aah!
Guard:
Sloan, Jackson,
Martinez!
Mail call.
Sloan.
Martinez.
Step back.
Place your hands
behind your back.
He's all yours.
It's been a long time, Sloan.
Every time one of you assholes
from the DEA shows up,
my life takes a bad turn.
I don't blame you
for being bitter.
I get busted trying to bring
a major dealer
to the U.S. for trial...
You weren't supposed
to kill him.
Hey, it was him or me.
Tong po saw to that.
That's not how the court saw it.
He's got my wife, Casey.
It's been 2 years.
She's probably dead.
Maybe you can do
something about it.
In the last 5 years,
tong po has become
the most powerful
drug lord in Mexico.
He's got a damn fortress
in the desert.
The DEA has been
trying to take him out
the last 3 years,
and has come up empty.
We can't get close,
but you might.
Yeah.
Every day of the dead,
tong po invites
all the top fighters
from around the world
to compete at his compound.
The winner takes on po
for a million bucks.
So the agency needs me again
and just like that,
I'm out of here.
It's all been arranged.
Po's men in here
will be made to think
that you're in solitary again.
You'll compete
in the tournament...
If you qualify, that is...
Under an assumed identity.
Remember...
If po recognizes you,
you're dead.
It's been a lot of hard years
since tong po's seen me.
Casey: Remember,
we know you want
to rescue your wife.
We think that's fine.
The prime mission here
is the elimination of po.
David:
I'll kill him.
Casey, reading:
"There's a street fight
"at 3rd and Santa fe.
"Brubaker has to invite you
to po's tournament.
P.S. Good luck
saving Vicky."
Biker: Hit him!
Come on!
Hit him! Get him!
You're the man!
Come on!
I'm coming for you!
For you! Come on!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
Can't take your girlfriend
anywhere, can you?
Maybe I make you
my girlfriend, huh?
You're the man!
Come on!
Yeah!
Hit him! Go!
All right!
Uhh!
Brubaker:
Hell of a fight, Jack.
Practically had him
sucking eggs in there.
I ain't never seen anybody
fight like that before.
5 centuries ain't gonna get you
far in this life.
You in the mood for
some serious action?
Depends on
your definition of serious.
What are you, some kind
of intellectual or something?
I'll tell you what, Jack.
Why don't I make a call,
see if I can get you
into a heavier grind
with some serious client?
Do it.
You'll probably have
to go to Mexico
for the score.
Is that a problem, Jack?
Only for the federales.
Good.
You make it down to calixico
by tomorrow night?
For what?
Big tournament,
but you got to qualify.
They like you,
they pay my commission.
So do me a favor, Jack, huh?
Kick some
royal ass, o.K.?
Jack. Jack!
Don't you want to know
what the payday is?
Doesn't matter.
A cool million.
That sound good to you?
Yeah, it doesn't sound bad.
But I'm warning you,
some don't make it back.
Ah... That's too bad
for them.
Strange motherfucker.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sending you a new guy.
Yeah, some bastard
who fights like the devil.
His name's Jack Jones.
And, listen...
Don't piss him off.
What's up, blondie?
You're looking
pretty good, baby.
Looking real good.
Don't piss me off.
Oh, yeah?
Uhh!
Oh, man.
Hey, look.
Uhh. Bitch!
You got a problem with this?
First of all, you see this?
Aah!
Ah! Aah!
You know, you should
be more careful...
Fuck you.
Keep your opinions to yourself.
You know, a simple
thank you would do.
Yeah, o.K.
Thank you, asshole.
You're going to Mexico
for that competition,
aren't you?
When we meet, let's just assume
we never met each other.
Jesus.
You had to have
the last word, didn't you?
Si?
Guard: Jack Jones
esta aqui.
Bueno.
Gracias, Mateo.
Mr. Jones, we've been
expecting you.
I'm Darcy.
This way.
You're one of the last
fighters to arrive.
I just found out
about the tournament
a few days ago.
You almost missed
the final qualifying matches.
Oh?
I thought I was in.
A lot of people want
to get into the tournament.
We only want the very best.
Yeah.
You're lucky to have
gotten this far.
Impress the man up there,
or it's a long trip for nothing.
I'm in charge of hospitality.
So if there's anything you need,
just ask me.
Oh, I'm sure I'll be fine.
Some of the world's
most dangerous men
are here.
Brubaker was
very taken with you.
He said you're a hard man.
Just how hard
are you, Mr. Jones?
Um... Hard enough.
Go on. Get him
out of here.
Good luck,
Mr. Jones.
Looks like you just made it
in time to qualify.
Better strip down, pretty boy.
Ok, next!
Rodriguez and Thomas.
Let's go, center of the ring.
Any style, everything is legal!
Which means there are no rules,
so let's fight!
Ah!
Hey...
Don't you think that's enough?
That...
Is enough.
Get him out of here.
Excellent, Thomas.
O.K., next.
You...
And you.
What, you need q-tips
in your ears, boy?
You gonna fight or what?
Ya!
Ahh.
Are you in or out of this thing?
Look, don't fight it.
I'll put you out easy.
Yeah?
What makes you think I'd let you
put me out at all?
You don't want to be
involved in this.
Man: Should I order
some Chinese food
or something?
No!
You're right.
I wouldn't want a chance
at winning $1 million.
Eat me, motherfucker.
How lovely.
Maybe you need to train her,
pretty boy.
I'm not gonna fight her.
I'll destroy her short life.
Hard head, huh?
Look, I'm giving you
a break, ok?
You ain't nothing,
shit-for-brains.
A pathetic way
for things to end.
Your next fight
won't be so easy!
Get this little mouse
out of here.
I don't like being followed.
8191 mannix Avenue.
Sound familiar?
Maybe.
Your house...
And your dojo.
Am I right, sensei Sloan?
I don't remember you.
How about my brother Andrew?
You saved his life.
You got him out
of red ball pirus,
and you made him an instructor.
You're Andrew Smith's
punk kid brother?
Yeah.
I don't remember there
being much hope for you.
Andrew straightened my ass out.
Said you got fucked over
and ended up doing some time.
That's history.
Wait'll everybody finds out
that sensei Sloan is here.
There'll be the sound
of 100 bricks
shitting at the same time.
You can't tell anyone who I am.
Anything you say.
You need anything,
sensei, just ask.
My wife's being held here.
Come on!
Let's move it, guys!
By tong po?
We'll talk later.
That guy's a lowlife
sicko scumbag.
You see all kinds here.
Yeah, I bet.
So, what do you do here?
A lot of things,
but not what you seem
to be thinking.
I'm very particular
about who I sleep with.
Well, they must do something
for sex around here.
Is that where
they keep the women?
You don't need
to worry about that.
I'm sure you have no problem
getting your own girls.
Hey...
What's gonna happen
to that young girl?
Is tong po gonna send her home?
The punk?
Yeah.
I wouldn't count on it.
Tong po has a particular
fetish for young girls.
And that's all right with you?
I didn't say that.
What happens
when they get older?
They become me.
Get cleaned up.
The party starts soon.
The rain in Spain
falls mainly on the plain.
The fighters are being called in
for the celebration.
May I have
your attention, please?
Shut the fucking music off.
Welcome to the sian memorial
tournament of champions,
the greatest competition
of its kind in the world.
My name is bill.
If you have any needs
to be taken care of...
Food, beverages, sunblock,
extra pillows,
pussy...
That goes for you, too, girls...
Don't hesitate to call on me,
bill, your humble
fucking servant.
Now let me introduce our host.
A great humanitarian,
board-certified
psychotherapist,
a visionary record producer,
3-time national
thai champion,
6-time sian
memorial tournament
of champions champion,
tong po!
I would like to make a toast
to all the wonderful men
and women here today.
It is an honor to have
such a distinguished group
participating this year.
As you know,
the lucky winner will receive...
$1 million!
Yeah! All right!
Yeah!
All right!
Yeah! Yeah!
Enjoy today's festivities,
for tomorrow at 7 A.M.,
the competition begins!
Hi.
How are you gonna compete
in the tournament?
Won't tong po recognize you?
I'll find Vicky tonight
and get this thing over with.
How long has po had her?
2 years.
Last time I saw her was
at that birthday party
you had for her
at the dojo, remember?
We had a great time, man.
Boy, I got wasted.
Yeah, you sure did.
So, Mr. Jones,
see anybody you like?
Nobody here's our type.
I certainly hope
you don't mean nobody.
I've had enough of this.
I'm going up to my room.
Silence, please.
A fighter who was eliminated
has requested
a second chance to compete.
I have decided to allow her
an opportunity
to prove her worthiness
before us all.
She may look sweet, gentlemen,
but I assure you,
inside there is an iron tigress.
Who among you will risk
his or her place
in the tournament
to fight miss Laurence?
A $25,000 bonus
to whomever defeats her!
Bastard.
She'll be killed.
Who would like to take her on?
I'll take her on!
Bill: Bitch!
Who was gonna get killed?
Maybe we should forget about
the tournament bullshit
and go for the million
right now.
Bitch.
Much too pretty a face
to be punched out.
Don't be stupid, boy.
Now go back and enjoy yourself
while I take care of this...
Little distraction.
No.
Take them.
You heard Mr. po.
Get that little bitch!
Well, well, well...
It's exciting to have
such a talent
in our humble tournament.
Fight me now.
You win the tournament,
you get me.
If you wanted her
all to yourself,
why didn't you just say so?
Well...
Enjoy the rest of the party.
I guess I should thank you.
I just got tired
of listening to his shit.
Come on,
let's get you cleaned up.
What are you gonna do
with a million bucks
if you win?
I don't know.
Retire, I guess.
From what?
Yeah, from what?
You know, like a job?
Well...
Right now, I'm unemployed.
I thought you just said
you'd retire.
Yeah, well, I'd retire
from unemployment.
Ok.
Here...
Keep this on your face.
It'll keep the swelling down.
You don't intend to go
through with this, do you?
I have to win.
You're gonna lose.
It's just another beating.
It's a chance to make
something of myself.
Here, keep this on your face.
I got to go.
Hello, lando.
I thought you might
be lonely here
by yourself.
What gave you that idea?
Let's call it woman's intuition.
Aren't you gonna invite me in?
Uh, sure.
I'm having a little
trouble with this.
Could you help me?
Darcy...
Mmm, I knew...
You'd have all I want and more.
I can't do this now.
What are you talking about?
I can't explain.
The tournament?
That sex-before-the-fight
stuff's just a myth.
Look...
I can't do this now.
Just leave...
Please?
You're a damn pussy tease.
Or maybe you really
don't like girls.
Or maybe you just like
underage tramps.
I'm sorry.
Go to hell.
No, I got nothing here.
Nothing, man.
So, uh...
Ohh.
Woman: Mmm.
Mmm!
Hey, don, o.K.?
All right.
Security break-in,
section 4.
Guard: Let's go! Let's go!
Sian, because of me,
you are dead.
I shall not rest
until you are avenged.
Excuse me, master.
May I speak with you
for a moment?
Why do you interrupt my prayers?
There's a trespasser
in the containment area.
These two failed.
Sound the alarm.
I want the intruder...
Alive.
Uhh! Aah!
Aah!
Uhh! Ooh!
Look, I'm sorry
I choked you out.
Yeah, you got lucky.
You didn't belong
in the tournament.
I guess we'll see.
What, they didn't throw you out?
They're giving me
a second chance.
The tournament's wrong for you.
At least maybe I can help you.
What's it to you?
Do you want my help or not?
Well, that move you did
on me was pretty good.
Why don't you show me that one?
I got a better one for you.
See, you're small,
so you got to use
the art of surprise.
When you face your opponent,
make him focus on one
of your weapons... your legs.
Get him to start staring
at your feet.
Make him look at your feet.
Make him be focused
on your feet.
And then, when he's
looking down...
Pop up with a hook.
You try it.
Tong po: Last night,
someone took advantage
of my hospitality.
Please be warned.
This compound
is private property.
You are guests here.
All trespassers will be
severely punished.
Now, the first day
of the tournament will begin!
Bill on P.A.:
Vernon and Craig,
enter the ring.
Jackson, Wilson!
Center of the ring!
Let's go!
Vincent, Chang!
Enter the ring!
Aah!
Amin, carnowsky!
Center of the ring!
Bill: Bannen, vargas!
Center of the ring.
Ooh!
Grab her!
Hold her, man!
Hold her down!
Oh! Bitch! Ow!
Aah!
Ah!
Uhh!
Uhh... Uhh... Uhh!
Laurence... Black.
Center of the ring.
Come on, beautiful.
Man: All right, baby!
Second man:
No way, no way!
I got her, man.
Ooh!
You dead meat, baby!
Come on!
Bring it on to me now!
You got rid of him.
I ain't nothin', huh?
Well, come on, show me then!
Show me what you got!
Come on, shorty!
Come on!
I'll kick your ass!
You hear what I said?
Come on...
Oh! Uhh!
Damn.
Man: Oh, man.
Second man:
Get up, coffee!
Third man:
Get up, man!
Smith, kid Wheeler.
Center of the ring.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Jones... Matthews.
Center of the ring.
Darcy, you didn't
even smile at me?
You're not gonna talk to me?
Darcy: There's
a tournament going on.
Yeah, I know that.
Hey, wait.
Where are you going?
You did pretty good today.
Want to go dancing later on?
Fuck you!
I got to find a way in there.
I might know a way in.
Hi.
Whoa.
Get the hell out of my doorway.
Wait a minute, Darcy.
I just came to make
a peace offering.
I wouldn't drink
champagne with you
if you were
the last man on earth.
It's a good thing I'm not
You're wasting your time.
You had your chance,
lando, and you blew it.
Fuck the champagne.
Darcy, I got to
ask you something.
Yes?
I need to know where
tong po keeps a woman
and how to get to her.
You can't possibly be serious.
I'm not enough to satisfy you?
That's not it.
I need some help finding her.
She's been here 2 years.
Oh, my god.
You're here to free that woman.
I need to know how to get
into that building.
It's guarded.
Lando, I can't.
I'm sorry.
She doesn't belong here.
None of us do.
She's my friend.
I have to save her.
And who saves me?
Tong po will kill me
if he finds out.
What if I tell you
I can get you out of here?
Start you off with some money?
Who are you, lando?
I'm just here to save a friend
that needs me, that's it.
I can offer you the same.
You want to stay here?
I mean, what's gonna happen
when you get older?
I don't see anybody
around here that age.
I can leave here
whenever I want.
Can you?
How can I trust you?
Who else do you have?
Lando, you son of a bitch.
Thanks for the help.
Good luck.
Uhh! Oh!
You're mine.
Lovely.
Just beautiful.
You are surprised
to see I have...
Music talent.
Do you play an instrument,
my friend?
I'd like to,
but I'm a little
tied up at the moment.
Once more,
Mr. DEA agent?
I'm Mr. Smith to you,
and I'm nobody's agent.
What are you doing here?
I'm doing an article
on your house
for architectural digest.
"The homes of the evil
and depraved."
Aah! Aah!
Answer my questions!
I said go fuck yourself!
Oh, great.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Darcy...
Is a beautiful woman.
What are you going to do?!
Aah!
All right, I'm DEA!
Anything else?
No, damn it!
Please don't cut her anymore.
Lando: No!
You motherfucker! No!
Aah!
Sloan!
I had to, sensei.
I didn't know... oh!
Bill: It's your fault
she's dead, lando.
There's something
I got to tell you.
What?
I haven't told you
what I grew up to be...
DEA agent.
I'm your backup.
You're DEA?
I guess you were right
when you said
there's no hope for me.
Every contest today
is a fight to the death.
Some of you are not prepared
to go to this distance,
so now is your opportunity
to leave.
Thank you for the hospitality.
Get out!
Anyone else?
Finish it.
All right, right here!
Aah! Aah! Uhh!
Finish it.
Hmmph.
This tournament is a memorial
to my wife sian.
5 years ago,
the DEA tear-gasses my home.
Sian was caught
in the fire that followed.
David Sloan was responsible
for sian's death.
He will be punished
in the thai style.
For $500,000 bonus,
who will challenge?
Just have my money ready.
This is not gonna take long.
It's time you learned
to show a little respect.
Tong po: Win...
And you get me!
And perhaps,
Vicky might be saved.
Is that enough?
Yeah!
Th-that's enough.
That's enough.
Ok!
Tong po: Who is next?
Tong po: You!
Fight or die!
You don't have the guts
to fight him yourself.
Kill Sloan!
Or you all die!
Megan:
It's all been a lie.
There is no money.
You saw what he did
to the others.
He intends to kill us.
You're mine!
You're a little bitch.
Uhh!
Aah!
Oh...
Oh... Ah!
Ow!
I thought you wanted
to fight me,
defeat me in a match,
regain your honor.
Killing my wife
only shames you forever.
Maybe he's right.
Uhh! Uhh!
Haaa!
Hold it, or she's dead!
Move away real slow.
Subtitles uploaded by: Daniel Oliver
06/12/2015