And he said to me, "Son of man,
dug in the wall, and I dug in the wall,
and now - in the wall of the door. "
(The Book of the Prophet Iezikilya, 8.7)
As it was,
from the beginning ...
Fell in love with a girl that
known since childhood.
Ordinary Story. As thousands
other at the time.
How could this happen?
Love died in an insane hatred.
Vukovar, the usual story
Two-family house repaired, thought
a good future days ...
... If it depended on us ...
- The Berlin Wall had fallen.
- This is a good sign.
- The Berlin Wall fell, Mom.
- Thank God!
Finally.
I melt from your kisses.
End of the millennium, the end
of utopia, Berlin Wall fell,
Leningrad again, St. Petersburg, Europe
wants reunion new hope fills the world...
Done!
- Hooray! - Hooray!
- Cheers! ...
When you are happy, the sun
warm warmer.
This is a new dress from Sweden?
Bruno's back?
Miss.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
All good
but home is better, right?
When flying home, looked down
under the wing of the aircraft,
Page of history, or of the land.
Let the new house
fulfilled all the wishes!
And a lot of kids!
"In our new house
the sun shines ... "
"Croatia, Croatia!"
- I'm hot, Tomo
- We're almost there.
"Yugoslavia, Yugoslavia!"
- Open the door!
- Ana!
Wedding, and demonstrations around ..
"Serbia, Serbia!"
All boils Belgrade.
Look at what is in Zagreb!
"Croatia, Croatia!"
Now wait and let's go.
And the same thing here.
Laura, the music!
Wait! What silence.
See how quiet flows the Danube.
There is nothing. Red or blue
strong or weak. Smart or stupid.
Now everything is just Croats or Serbs.
- Over the top, Ana!
- Do not overdo it.
Taught us that one history and geography,
brought us that we are one.
But our generation does not think,
Who are we, the Serbs and Croats,
Orthodox or Catholics ...
Two celebrated Christmas, two New Year
two Easter ..
Married to each other ..
Had children.
I love you!
For the first time we part for so long.
The army will not hold me long.
Do not worry!
See what happens?
Europe will not allow the country to
disintegrate.
Pusni Nashat Ploce!
Late!
Beware!
Rain came ...
Mom, why are you here? I'm leaving the
army; not the end of the world.
Good luck!
Good luck to you!
"Serbia - Get out!"
Daddy, look!
Crap at home.
shitting on the Constitution.
In our own country
we are second class citizens.
I will not allow it!
Go, my son, go late!
Do not worry, we will not be gone.
What's up, people .. ..
Who's that?
How quickly things change.
throughout the city.
Suddenly my former friends
changed.
Many are leaving. But Vukovar
still my city.
I remember the day when Tom drew beside
me and lifted his face, all in the paint.
To love? Now the holiday
color is not what it was ..
Got to go to Sweden. More there is
nothing to wait for. We'll go together.
I've been wanting.
Children, what are you doing? - Colima it
because it is not ours, that's what.
- It's your baby?
- No. - I know whose.
Bring him to the doctor.
Passport, please!
- Where do you work?
- In Sweden.
- I know you ... Were
military training? - Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Now what ...
Trait that is going on in the country and
elsewhere, the absurdity of absurdity ...
The outer limits of cracking at the seams,
and on the interior building walls.
Along with the regular army, which all of
us are created and paramilitary formations.
Kostevski! - J.
Vorants! - Thank you.
Fadil! - J.
Bosnian pizza. Yum.
What they say about Montenegro?
Dalmatians, try, can
for you it's the last one!
Eat bananas from Honduras,
Montenegrin plum far now.
The longer, the better.
Something I do not like
what you're talking.
Here are bastards.
It's okay.
The main thing is still alive ...
Ana, Ana ..
Ana!
There all the back is broken.
Whatever you do - all black.
There is no death, there is movement.
I'm not going anywhere. Sons
will be on the doorstep.
Tomorrow and our home
going into the air.
You, my dear, you will go with us!
She would not go anywhere!
Leave alone.
Here we are among their
Croatia - a country where
there is a place for everyone.
Again, it starts in the same
1941st we also referred to as "brothers."
This is not the Croats, and freaks.
Horror around, friends.
All of fear.
Many of them have left.
Listen to me, all too
bloated. All the better.
I do not want to tempt fate,
my father during the last war.
It seems to me that those killed in
Jasenovac again float in water.
Every night, all the shooting, and in the
afternoon work as if nothing had happened.
And they both went crazy.
All these terrible tales.
What stories? All of us will swallow
this fratricidal war, Stepan!
In life, it does not allow it!
-There was a world, mate? -What kind of world?
For what it is to us what we do with it?
Reservation.
We do not know where the house is,
or where we go.
Or in Serbia, or the sky.
I think that'll take
the whole garden.
Who do you leave the house?
You run, right?  January 28
- I shall return. - You know Qom, not as
others, but I keep his house.
Why you can not stop them?
- It's a family heirloom.
- I know, from 1687-th.
Sometime in Vukovar after fire
left 106 people and 44 homes.
I will stay with the house.
Darling, there you will be safe and
return to his.
When you throw the land on which he lived
life, in the heart of unbearable emptiness...
I feel all never again
be the same.
Give me the ball! Hey!
What about you, huh? You can not let go
mad with from the latest news?
Asleep in their country, and
woke abroad.
And I think:
How are my in Sarajevo ...
-"There is no death, there is a movement."
- My father is fond of quoting.
"Dear friends, listen to the news."
"Dear friends, let those come to love
yes kiss each other in the ass. "
I can not understand what is happening.
One war.
The thought does not leave me ..
.. Now, I know that every
has 20 million ancestors
And... I'll never believe that someone
not a drop of human blood.
Good morning, neighbor!
How did you sleep?
Ana!
Keep an eye on the house, Jovan!
Come here!
Mother, full service.
What does this mean?
Today, the best fish of the Danube.
Capture still and wine.
Just like always, only
one is missing.
Well, for you!
If you have always lived
in our home.
Tom!
Toom!
I can not hear.
Speak up!
Where are you?
That is good. Relocating.
Where to? ... Where?
Being moved closer to us.
Do not worry,
We do not Beirut!
Now listen to me!
Thou shalt be a father!
Father!
Have you heard?
I'm sure ..
And I love you ...
You know, we have many, many children.
Connection was lost.
Do not know where to being moved.
- Let me know when you can.  - It is
important that he is alive and well.
- For you! - For you!
"... If no agreement is reached, the
boundary will be monitored "UNPROFOR ..."
- Oh, good evening. - Good evening.
Where are you from?
- On the case for you. Well, Stepan,
time to join.
Do not you think I'm a little
old for this?
Or maybe you do not allow
this is your Serbian as well?
Or do you want to slip between
two drops?
- Comedy, and ...
Far away you are from the care
about our country ...
There are many ways to distort
love of country.
Ana!
Where is your husband?
Has not deserted?
Peter, do not today .....
Family feast, you know.
- Come on.
- Help yourself!
No, thank you. Good night.
- Good night.
Open and breathe a little air
Breathe.
"Clean air Croatian"
Exercise on an air-raid.
Necessary to go to the basement.
I do not want in old age
play war
Please do not take into
by heart the news ...
Put out the light!
I remember this window I looked
at the people, the Danube, the sky ..
She felt it all: the city,
landscape and my cloud ...
And there was a part of their ...
Here, with which I grew up.
Patriotism to me .. love.
I spent a few months
outside the city.
It was not possible to call Anya
I did not know where I was.
Both in this country and in the army
Strange things were happening.
Betrayal. Deserters fled to
another country, or abroad.
Left whole barracks.
Did not understand ..
To whom is this war?
Shoot them to attack
enemy.
Such as I had
very little.
Well, as the world through the scope?
As if for the first time I've seen
human face.
Get used to it.
Sick at heart?
Will I be able to kill?
"Sometimes I dream, to fly away ...
"Take off like damn ...
"Right on the north,
until they get tired wings ... "
After the call
Tom vanished into thin air.
I'm concerned that is thrown
throughout Yugoslavia.
He talked about a military
ground in Slovenia, I remember.
"This is our home ...
"Oh, no land is better ..."
"There's a long way ...
"There daleekoo ...
"Far away from the sea ...
"Far away from the sea ..."
"This is our home ..."
He said that he could send to Dubrovnik
like there is now the southern front line.
Seeing the besieged barracks I realized that
the war was everywhere. Yves our heads.
"There daleekoo ...
"Far away from the sea ..."
- Where to? - In the barracks.
Husband looking for.
Military or what? Get out!
Hands up!
You carry the water to her husband?
Not seen 20 days.
Checks clear whether he pants, aha?
Do not fuck up in fear.
- What kind of relationship?
- You're a freak, shut up!
- What to do with them? - If their lives
road, let them return home.
Ana!
What happened?
Denied.
Why was I refused?
Because your husband - a Serb.
And what about you?
I am very loyal. My husband -
Croats.
What about me?
Come on, I'll show you where
You can buy flour.
Stepan, no time for empty cases.
Now in vogue for coffins
Dead.
Whew. I will not go with you.
Well, unless of course, you must ..
- It is with a weapon that does not
know how to handle.  - To learn.
And you? When you get
back to your parents?
Cute - your country ...
Stop it!
The country has a civil war broke
out. Rose Vukovar, all mixed up.
Which of my friends dressed in a form
Croatian armed forces?
Another 100 miles.
Ana ...
So we're going to Vukovar
that everyone wanted.
5 minutes free.
5 minutes to the toilet.
The smoke could not see anything.
It hurts when you realize that there
nothing is left of my life ..
I never thought that I would look
to his native town through sniper scope.
And Ana is so close
and so is not available.
I remember sailing boat on the Danube ...
Did I want to kill someone?
First shooting in his hometown,
I felt real hatred.
No, I did not kill, despite the growing
anger to those who knew until yesterday.
"Yeah, I'm friends Belgrade,
"In Slavonia burning village ...
"I can not over!"
And you loved someone.
Does anyone cry for you?
You think I brought
on their shoes Serbian land.
How to understand this?
Leko now understand ...
Yes, I'm friends Zagreb.
Cease fire!
Guys! Ideal for
recovery and tracking beauty. Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Who did that, Ana
back in love with you.
Macedonian! Only you can
entrust their head.
I will try, and we will then
remember what you had a beautiful body.
- What is it?
- Shaving cream.
Look, in our house
will not listen to Serbian lies.
How do you know the truth, if not
listen to both sides?
"As the people who stayed
without homes and property ...
"... Will survive in the area in
coming winter ..
"No one can say for sure ..."
Listen: some scholars argue
that space - a living creature ..
And if we are descended from monkeys,
in the words of Darwin?
Decide which country you will be
to live, and who will bear ...
What happened? Are you nervous because
things that can not change.
Hunger is much better
transferred alone.
Where to?
For bread.
For bread?
Everywhere in the city there is no flour.
No need for flour
danger.
I know where to eat bread
exchanged for gold.
Wait a minute!
On!
Did not bring me peace
last look at the parental home.
Why I went to buy bread?
All ran out of the city ..
around was indifferent ..
Those pictures could not
erased from my memory ..
And always thought that among the dead
living or find a husband.
Can be walked through the streets with
the hope I catch up with that bullet ...
Vukovar became a cemetery ..
At the place in the city museum,
between archaeological finds,
Tom showed and explained
everything to me ..
what do you need to achieve
just one kiss.
I was so in love that five thousand years
culture I was completely indifferent ...
But now I realized that intolerance
all turned to dust and ashes.
In gordskom museum I realized
that love to death.
In the museum, I proposed to her.
Anya "yes" sounded fine
between these walls.
Ironically, this parable
was a story about the kiss.
I am fascinated by your essay
the kiss.
Orphan. Do not know
that her father had died.
He should have stayed
in Sweden.
If it had not been taken to the front.
How absurd!
Maybe our husbands shoot
each other.
Good evening, women.
Are you alone?
Let's see what we have here ...
And how are you?
Carried away!
Who are you?
We?
We have dogs of war.
Hush you.
Carried away! You know how many
it now stands?
Sit ... Bore!
I can see the rings as well?
Women, women ...
Let me go, I'm pregnant!
Let me go.
Let see these men.
That's how I am! I'll show you!
Watch it, break it.
Someone is coming!
This is my chance!
ShPodumay head, it's dangerous!
Not! By Ani!
The bird will not fly.
Where is your home?
Here, behind the theater, along the water
tower, and through the gardens ...
At this point I and Ana
watched last performance.
Breathed a crowded theater ...
This is a ghost?
Where have you gone, when
my heart beats here?
Earth revolves stupid
around its axis ...
Ana!
That's his way,
go and hug.
It is dangerous ...
Are you hungry?
What happened?
All sold,
to eat.
Tell me.
Does not matter.
It is important that you
are alive and well.
And on the right side.
And which side is right?
Dead.
I'm sorry.
And I do not know anything about his.
Why this war,
if all were killed ...
I could not come earlier.
- I'll take you out to safety.
- How far away from here.
In Tasmania ...
at the end of the world.
Well dad said ...
The truth
at one time, tomorrow - confusing.
It was all a lie ..
Everything was destroyed ...
Ana, listen to me!
I love you!
Here's how it happened ..
know what I mean ...
and children will not be.
You see, there was all the worst.
Neither you nor I are not to blame.
Why, instead of happiness, of
a curse on us.
And nothing can be done ..
I'll never forget ..
With the new life that
born in such chaos ...
It seems to me all at once
both inside and outside ...
May at the time of death
I wake up a woman?
Seems to stop time of year.
In memory of one eternal winter.
Everywhere street fighting
We must go!
Come on, no doubt,
we can not go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll take you to safety.
A safe place is in the
basement of the Radko.
Take care of yourself!
Wake up, open your eyes.
Tomo!
Cease fire!
Repair the roof,
to not flooded.
No one.
Where are the others?
I am alone, my husband disappeared.
I do nothing about it I do not know.
Who from this shoot?
I do not know how to shoot.
Now learn, not special
wisdom.
What is your nationality?
Croatian.
Do not be afraid ... Go!
Come on, soldier!
Tie your wounds.
Do not be afraid ... Go!
How many today spilled blood.
Except menstruation ...
Money. War is business.
Show wound!
Preparing for the orphans
in the basement.
Cook a pig that ate people.
Varish that then?
Pork or human flesh?
Are you hungry, son?
I'm sick.
Now, let go ... sginesh
Do not listen. Go all the way!
I'll explain about
The "butterfly effect."
In the Balkans pomashut wings
a hurricane in the Atlantic begins.
In other words, with each offense
the whole world is getting worse.
There are many correct,
everything is destroyed.
Teach her to shoot!
Replace us in battle,
if anything, huh?
So, so ...
That's it.
Gently ... but firmly.
As a woman.
Woman, violated the truce!
I. .. always afraid
... snipers.
What a life ...
In the home garden, there
enemy nest.
Call to Arms!
Push to the ground, here for
snipers good view!
We were well in sight!
When all this is over, you postroyut
even better than the old city.
Stop it!
There is a Serb?
- There is.
- No.
No!
You're always raving in his sleep.
Who are you?
Nobody's.
Itself.
Are you thirsty?
How are you little?
It's nothing.
Do not cry, do not.
Live.
Stuffy!
Do not choke, do not worry.
You warm, darling?
As we were in the thick of it?
Forgotten and the day and month, more
little and forget the year.
This is my calendar.
Whom bear?
Croatia? Serbia?
Yugoslavia.
Congratulate her husband.
What to do
when the time comes?
We'll see ...
I want out!
Take it easy!
Your kindness does not unwind
my illusions about humanity.
I'll cook something hot.
Now you see how you
castrates a real woman.
Where to?
I want to have a baby, not a mouse ...
Take all
I like it.
Today, all for free.
We reached the goal.
Long live the people ...
This movement ....
But it is death.
Yes, I can answer your questions:
who, what, where, when, why ...
It is necessary to consider not only
last days and years ...
... but the past century.
Maybe it's not that.
But if the world was different.
We must protect our memory.
It seems to me that all
this time I was sleeping ...
Every day - history.
Nightmare
A terrible awakening.
"Early Spring Awakening ...
"And the sweet pain in my chest ...
"A song is ..
.. What can and can sing ..
"And the most votes will be heard
beautiful women ..
"And then the bass ..
"And the old thunder ...
"And the barrage -
like Tchaikovsky's "1812, that" ...
"Early Spring Awakening ...
"And the sweet pain in my chest ...
"A song is ..
.. What can and can sing ..
"Then come to vote,
strong, masculine ...
"All veterans and
forgotten heroes ...
"With the heart of a young falcon ...
"And with the song instead of cold ..
"Blossoms land flowing river ...
"Early Spring Awakening ...
"And the sweet pain in my chest ...
"The song is so ...
what can and can sing. "