In order to protect habitat.
Follow the paths.
Shuttle 11S1 and BAXTER-satellite, air traffic control calls
-
and makes the registration of
at 01:00.
Minus three minutes to launch.
OSM, third stage. Lock
S & A, you are authorized to close.
SSC, third stage S & A locked.
One of the pillars, the fuel tank open.
- Fuel hose is cleaned.
SSC, the number one valve
thermal management out of it.
SSC, second valve
NSC report. Space Shuttle
ready to go.
Time of about 30 seconds. SSC,
hydraulic external energy on.
Up and down 100%.
25 seconds. The distance from the check.
Indicate the distance.
Air traffic control, ready to launch.
Right. Shot 20 seconds.
Prepare to go.
Weather unchanged,
orbit locked.
Output minus 10, 9, 8, 7, 6...
5, 4, 3, 2, output.
Congratulations, Palatier. A great performance
Vasglobelta and from yourself.
Thank you for Gibbons.
Is everything all right?
Ylitämmekö our authority
watching the world like this?
Do we deserve this...
divine power?
Depends on point of view. This is only a supplement
wonders of the world.
Examination of the work of art with a magnifying glass does not detract from the elements -
but only reveal things. -
, They may not supposed to see.
So, after all, it is true.
BAXTER  is in orbit. Time
output, 6 minutes, 13 seconds.
Jamie, I'm home.
That's cool here.
I talked to Mike Johnson.
We talked about Christmas. I said that
we do not have any Christmas Eve.
I thought that Ruby's choir sung
five o'clock Mass -
would be nice to go to them.
They always invest to Christmas.
Ruby? Dad came home.
Jamie, I guess you did not put
star tree without me?
For...
Ruby, eat your food.
- It's too hot.
Blow. - I look forward to
it cools down.
What are you doing?
- I eat these out.
I do not want to waste food again.
- It's not your bread, Rich.
Jamie, it's not anyone's food.
We have already talked about this.
My kids are eating, when the table is set.
And I'm covered.
And that's Robbyn place.
- Will Robby back?
I'm sorry.
You're right.
You're cleaned well, girls.
Do not dispose of stars without me.
It's our thing.
There we no longer have stars.
But the angel Robbylle.
Well.
You are both dear to my angels.
See, Abby. There we live.
Sometimes life is much more beautiful,
when you look at it from a distance.
Abby, come on. What is a girl?
Why did you sleep with clothes on?
I bought you a Father's Day pajama.
I do not think it was so horrible?
Hello, Richard Hadley.
Well, would you say your name clearly
camera?
Richard Hadley.
I-R-C-H-A-D-D or H-A-D-L-E-Y.
Well done, Mr. Hadley. Welcome to the
Chris Hapshow program.
Our guest is Mr. Hadley.
More and more people are aware of Baxter.
Tell me more about it?
- BAXTER means -
bi-linear, axial thermal
receiver. Monitoring Satellite.
It allows the armed forces
detect foreign objects -
spectrometry and thermodynamically the earth's surface.
Could you open that?
- Sure.
Spectrometric measurement is a way of
to measure the energy and mass -
termoenergia and, of course, related to
lämpökeskittymiin.
By combining these techniques can be
to detect all of the Earth's surface -
and explore it from space.
Thus, terrorist organizations through
used by the world's radar jamming -
sites and projects to conceal
will be obsolete technology?
Right. - Wow,
quite an accomplishment.
We are very proud Vasglobesta.
The biggest thank you is Edgar Palatierin.
He was the originator of the project.
-He Was here last week. The intelligent man.
Could you tell inclusion
Vasglobe project?
I receive information.
Interviews and press releases.
I believe that the world must be
the right information puuhistamme.
When this super satellite is now in orbit
...
Please explain why Americans
can sleep better.
Well, I imagine that it brings people
-
a certain sense of certainty
images and details.
Evidence for the existence of one. Thus
no longer need to guess.
Do not need to think about whether
a fact or fiction.
Right. Thank you, Mr. Hadley.
It would be in it.
Abby, go home.
Where were you?
I waited for you last night, Rich.
Reply to Rich.
Where have you been last nights?
You have not spoken to me.
You will not even looked at.
What is going on?
I have seen something.
It's crazy.
I do not know what, but -
it is magical.
You saw it, Abby. Or what?
Yes you saw.
Is it something new? - None.
First broadcast in an hour.
- Gibbons wanted to be involved.
He told me to send the data in it.
I'll be back.
Baxter thermal imaging ready to
7435980 deviation found
You have then you have seen them.
I can see it in your eyes.
It is a rare and unfortunate sight.
You are a lucky man.
You have a lot of questions,
and I have a lot of answers.
Sit.
Tick any checkboxes are portals.
Niistähän you know.
Portals? - Yes, they
Light buoys.
March opens, and send them to the
to the skies as a school of fish.
Send  what up? - The souls.
Last night, how the portal.
There.
What are they?
What is your name?
Rich. - Well, Rich.
This means that the dead are among us
. I hate the idea.
After his time in purgatory...
- Purgatory?
March spits out the insides
as the bad-tasting piece of meat.
But how?
If they are picked, they go to heaven
portals.
If it is rejected... They catch fire
and ash raining down back to the ground.
One was left yesterday.
As you saw.
All these charts and tables...
Sieltäkö them you found?
Their search takes a lifetime.
I will not change no longer part of all.
That's what happens to you soon.
How do you know all this?
I died once.
But I remember everything I saw there.
This purgatory and hell 9
circuit, just as Dante predicted.
The doctor from my heart started
I have seen all the more clearly.
I've atoned for my sins,
but I know what I experienced.
You will look for souls rest of your life.
Still see all of them?
Why did not I know?
Cover your eyes.
Can you see me? - I do not.
I see thee? - Yes
probably, if you look.
Right.
We both have to want to see each other.
Dead  appear only for those who really want
to see.
And...
They live deep in your heart.
Those who have that gift
see the same as you.
They will see more than just the world.
No one has talked about this.
- Are you gonna talk about?
I do not.
Why not?
Well.
I'm sorry if I was rude.
You do not even know my name.
Lou Demoine.
Very nice to meet you.
You have not been drinking your water, Rich.
There seems to be a little sugar...
Hey, only Lou.
Rich!
Hey, you called Richard Hadley,
Vasgloben information to the master.
I do not return to work before...
I do not know when.
If you need assistance, please contact Wayne Peterson
-
personal counseling,
ext 891 Thank you and bye.
Jamie! Jamie, wake up.
Rich. Were you out again?
- Get up now.
Where are you going? What is this? -
I have to leave for a short period of time.
Go to awaken Ruby.
- Where are you going?
A small trip. - Where to?
I might be able to find Robbyn and save him.
I might be crazy -
but this explanation would be even more difficult than
not to explain.
Is needed confidence. As if
when you fall backward, and someone -
will receive you. Confidently
downfall. That's what this is.
Rich, what's wrong with you?
- Nothing!
There is nothing wrong with me.
I am sure of this.
Who said that the dead can return to the
?
Dear. I know that this seems like a
crazy, but do not worry. Ruby!
Do not bother to wake him up.
- There is nothing to worry about. Ruby!
Honey, come back to bed.
- Hey, pumpkin.
Now look what you've done.
- Stop that, Jamie.
Listen. You know that I
walked out last night.
Abby walks in the canyon,
when I saw the beam of light.
She saw it, too. It was a portal,
this vortex up to the heavens -
and the earth opened as a small
volcano, and the people...
They had a  urns and bags,
, and they collected them, souls!
Do not you understand? - I really do not.
I can find Robbyn and talk to him.
No, you can not blame me.
I do not you should.
I do not blame did not know, Rich.
Is that what this is all about? In this case, the
I'm sorry.
Maybe you go to talk to someone? Debbie.
Henderson recommended.
Settle this mess. Please,
do not bother to be like that.
Be what? I'm serious.
Listen.
Write Robbylle. Something
want me to say to him.
I will say just about anything. Write
message from you and Rubylta.
Jamie, you do not write.
Write  now!
The Lord's sake, get me...
I am afraid of you.
I do not understand what is happening and why.
But please stop.
Two days is Christmas Eve.
I'm sorry.
I have to do this.
The last goodbye. The soul can get back to the physical form of human
-
a while. Then it thank
pickers delivery -
and say the last goodbye
before leaving the country.
All those people. .Jotka See
overnight glassy eyes.
With a selection of boxes,
urns, whatever.
What do they only get their hands on.
They picked up the souls. Dead
dear and close.
They will find the soul through the
sleep and send it to heaven.
But if the soul is not
anyone who cares...
If no one has the
loved, it's black soul.
Then it stays here and
returns to the fire of hell.
When the obsession takes over,
, nothing is insignificant.
Moments in life are the signs.
Questions remain unanswered.
The riddle remains the norm.
Provide details of the afternoon.
Paper.
Right. Right.
Yeah? - This was the night
Baxter.
It is a graph of the
south-western parts of the above.
What does it mean, Gibbons?
- It can be anything.
It can be something
very dangerous.
It may even be a fault Baxter
.
Impossible. - The thing is, however,
investigated.
A test very carefully.
Preparing to. 0 degrees Kelvin is impossible to implement
artificially.
Physically impossible.
20 years ago the Baxter
was considered impossible.
Something is amiss.
Absolute zero is the theory.
The nearest equivalent is one of the
nebuloosa in outer space.
High school chemistry student can say
impossibility.
I do not ask for anything in the status report.
I like you worried about -
seriousness of the situation and the theoretical impossibility.
I ask you the experience-based
your perception of all this.
What it is, it
is not of this world.
Who are you? Can be more embarrassing
?
What else should I say?
- That's just more embarrassment.
He's trying to say that it would be in place to greet
. That's right.
Hi. - Hi.
Piikittelet Why is it always me? Not
you need me to observe.
I do not observe, but to fix.
Otherwise, you do not learn from your mistakes.
What is your name, stranger?
- Rich.
Hey, Rich. - Hey, I'm...
No need to explain, we are friendly to
.
I'm sorry, I'm Grace. - Grace?
Grace and all the other...
- Jermaine.
Andrew. - Where's Arnie?
I do not care. - I'm sorry,
that I came to disturb.
I forgive you.
We come here every night.
Not just here, but every night.
We have a kind of tradition.
- Kutsumuksellinen obsession.
Hobby, which includes
camping and viewing.
We do not look at the stars. For it
is not in the sky, but in the country.
Watch in the country to see them.
You seem to know what I'm talking about.
You were actually the same errand.
How you know? - No
a lot of people move here.
And you have that look.
- What's gaze?
As you would have seen God.
Now is the time.
You do not sleep a lot?
- I'm not at night.
I have become in recent weeks
night person.
The same with us. Hard to sleep when the
at night so much is happening.
I hope I do not switch off the idea.
You looked intently.
I thought.
I watched only.
I try not to think about anymore.
Yes, it is easier.
But I would like to ask you something.
- Let's hear it.
How the information can live with?
When you know -
that God really exists.
You know it before thinking...
Because the Church says so, and
parents say their child.
Back of the head was still always the suspicion.
When you do something bad -
can convince himself that God does not exist.
No, it's not so bad.
Then you're doing something good, and you say:
"Okay, God,
reward me."
That it is true
beyond comprehension.
Thats us...
Considered  so close eye on.
You think pretty much the man,
who does not want to think about.
I do not try to understand it.
Hulluksihan it should be.
I try to live my heart and instinct, according to my.
They are divine qualities in this world.
You would be best to give the brain a rest
-
and monitor the heart and soul.
So get to him.
Thank you.
Good night.
Good morning, Richard. - Good morning.
Where do tonight? Middle-aged
about 20 miles away.
A couple of oldies 3 miles away.
Both start at 01.13.
I want to see something new.
- Where's toddlers are?
Forget them. Too depressing.
Little husbands are the best.
Their loved ones wobble syrup...
No, middle-aged
get the widest sampling.
There are pimps, whores, gangsters and
proffia. Do you remember John McCainen?
There one sees celebrities.
- This is how it is.
Arnie, considered to be the elderly.
- I'm always in favor of the majority.
You get to decide.
What would you vote for Rich? -
How do you know all this?
Where it all?
Time, place, age. You know exactly
every night...
We have documented the
outputs and pickers.
After years begin to show a pattern.
The purgatory is on schedule.
What about maps and spreadsheets, Rich?
- They look like just the place.
You know, therefore, where, when and how
old souls are?
Unbelievable.
Rich is looking for his son, and we
help him search.
Arnie, this is the place
but it does not start for a while yet.
There is a place below,
which could see something -
just a few minutes.
You're in control.
It's nice, when it comes to
new people.
I think it's nice that there is
other equally crazy as I am.
You're not crazy, Rich.
You're just a crazy situation.
Rich? What's going on?
Rich? - He is Jamie, my wife.
Rich, I do not think so. - He is the only
kyhjöttänyt at home.
He does not even believe in, and now he gets
Robbyn first create a. No way!
Rich! - I have to see Robby.
Jamie... I'm sorry.
Rich.
Sorry, Rich.
Who is he?
His mother.
There is a swing hard. The best thing to put
heavily armed men about it.
The best husband.
Errors can not afford.
Errors, Hobbs? It is the smallest
concern.
This is not a war, but the research.
The Ministry of Security -
is ready to provide any assistance
completely secure evacuation.
You do not know what is needed there.
My husband can not cover everything.
Your husband will not...
- We need to focus on...
Lieutenant Commander Sterling.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
I want to talk to you, gentlemen
Palatier and Gibbons.
This is the then top secret.
The President sent a special forces operation
10 years ago.
"Operation Firefly". Only 3 people
in the White House knew about it -
and it soon swept under the carpet
twin towers after impact.
Drones looked the same as BAXTER now.
This image southwestern area.
None of the technology does not explain the phenomenon,
but this was a thermal camera.
At night, something strange happens,
, and has been ever since.
Persons  decided to leave the
ignored. I with the others.
2007 Michael Newdow took the
of the Supreme Court in front of the story -
trying to remove uskollisuuden-
whales phrase "name of God".
The case was considered to be unfounded, and was not processed.
The president dismissed the case due to fear of
a.
Fear,
that we now have to face.
Vasgloben When the news reached the President finds
-
the project came a new light
and it was re-opened.
And I watch function
presidential edict.
I'll be back, I promise. - No
hurry. Your family needs you.
This. I do not expect you to
searching him, but if you...
If you happen to see
him, let me know.
Click here to reach me. I want to know.
- Sure. I am looking for a night.
I hope you're located,
when we find him.
Father, one more thing.
Guys have a party and...
Clean up your room. Mother
nag about it all the time for me.
You can do it now.
- Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God. -
It was the last word.
I do not care. I'm out of here. - Robby!
Did you find him? - I do not.
I'm sorry, Rich.
I should not have come back.
Your family needs you.
Why, then, did you?
When did they come from? - At night.
In the morning, everything was in place.
Where are the others?
- Those took them.
We met another group.
When I returned as a gunslinger.
Do you know who they were?
- They talked about Vasglobesta.
Four hours of the time received.
Staff information, please.
Mr. Hadley. I'm really sorry for the confusion
.
I, Herbert Gibbons,
in this Edgar Palatier.
I Vasgloben BAXTER program
task manager.
I know who you are.
And we know who you are.
I see You've been
Vasglobella for almost 14 years.
We were lucky to have
about a loyal employee.
What is the exact job description again?
- I am the spokesman -
Vasgloben less
Department of Rockdale.
And you gave an interview with a local satellite channel.
So you know Baxter?
- Yes.
Good. You will be wondering why we are here
. Do you have information?
None. - It is associated with Baxter
very much.
Last heat transmission refers to a strange
activity in this region.
You certainly know how to
interpret these images?
You can see these small spots in the region.
And the larger the red stripes.
- Yes, I see.
The spots and stripes point
area to be every night -
dramatic temperature fluctuations.
Such temperatures have previously been considered impossible.
The past?
So, until recently.
- I understand.
Really? - After all, it makes sense.
I would say that about all. No it is not.
Why it makes sense to you?
I just meant that
I understand what you are saying.
So epäilimmekin.
Why are you here?
You have experienced something incredible -
and that is why we want to ask you
nocturnal visually.
Mr. Hadley. Yet
one question.
What do you see at night?
Of stars.
Excavation center
pressure suits for deployment.
Palatier Lord, I guess you realize that it is
is too far-fetched.
Doctor, all this evening
seen is very far-fetched.
Yes, it is. She weighed 74 pounds and
43 grams before his death.
76 seconds later, 4 seconds after the death of
-
she weighed 74 pounds and 22 grams.
Exactly 21 grams less.
Massaako? - 21 grams of pulp -
inexplicably disappears from the heart stops.
The theory is that at death...
- Soul...
leave the body. 21 grams of pulp
leaves the body metaphysically.
Wonderland.
Two months later
seems to be lucky.
- A little to the north. Soon it will be displayed.
Camp? - No. This is
Rich States.
We will stay only for a moment. - And the shit.
I put the tent up.
A perfect night, Grace.
- How do you know?
Dreamed about her again last night.
The Moon was his favorite thing.
Rich, wait. - Grace, it's him.
I feel it.
Wait one minute. - Why?
I am tired of waiting.
Rich!
I'm sorry.
Grace. He goes out of hand.
He ??can not stay here.
He will destroy the souls of the possibilities.
I do not want to be in his presence.
None of us want that.
He is a friend, which has its own
journey, but we have ours.
He should not to lead us.
This he must do by yourself.
Do not you see it?
I understand.
Therefore, her on too. You will not be
feel like dancing to the tune of others -
Rich  but needs me.
- He has a wife, Grace.
I know that. I did not go to his
marry him, I'll help only.
Can you help? Would you have left me
unless there would be in such a hurry to help him?
Rich! Rich!
Rich!
Tell the angels, Daddy.
It is in the archangels
that the cherubim.
Then there is the heaven of angels singing.
And of course, guardian angels.
They protect each to their own human.
Also you have a shoulder.
- Where is that?
There it is, you just do not see it.
I'll teach you a little first
technique prior to the throw.
Always a step back,
thread and throwing.
Well.
Pull  when the jerks and then rewind in.
Do not give up.
As you continue, the fish surrenders
and you can drag it ashore.
Anna, I'll try to! - Okay.
"The Greeks called their land
Hellaaksi him."
Now is the time to sleep, Robby.
Daddy? Do you sing a lullaby yet?
- One only.
Monitor indicates that this area
happens next bulge.
Drilling is
start immediately if we are going to make.
Are you sure this works?
It is a deadly counter-
contact with the air.
If your machine gets it up before the
surface, no problems should not be.
Right. Drill off the ground.
Stop. Make the diagnosis.
Are you sure picker do not know about this?
It is, therefore, come to the surface?
Yes.
It is very beautiful. - It's funny,
that you see it that way.
So is karhunpentukin until
game warden put it in the cage.
I think you're opposed to it.
Why?
Curiosity to get you to repeat the
of Adam and Eve's sin.
All information
is not intended for humans.
Do not you understand that this is not only a scientific
try out?
It is life. Spirit, who has been sacrificed
and on behalf of which has been sacrificed.
I agreed to help you, and I sold my soul to the devil
.
Your time has come to pay me a ransom
Father. - Grace.
Escort both
away.
Let's start with the transfer to removable tank.
Morning till the time -
before the soul disintegrates.
Demographic Research done.
Let's start with the genetic structure of the study.
Calculate the memory of neurological networks. The nuclease
synapses.
How much time? -
Two hours to dawn.
Let's start with the cytoplasm
kernel distribution.
It can cause serious damage to the structure of the
.
I know.
We are already well advanced. Collected all the data.
Ready incision.
Stop it! - Guards the scene.
The moment Palatier. Please.
Have you ever loved something so
to do everything in front of it?
Even you died for it?
I've given up everything
To find my son.
Sacrificed my whole life.
Up to my family.
I'm not going to let my son be lost.
He's...
my trip.
And if you do not give him to me
-
I'm going to help her body
each bone and the muscle.
Give him to me.
Robby Hadley...
I should have known.
Thank you.
No one is released before the
fully conscious soul.
Watch out and hurry.
Go on, Rich. - God bless you.
Gentlemen. It is mine,
White House -
and no doubt the whole nation in the interests of -
that this project will be buried immediately.
All the information of the existence of
disposed of -
And all participants
swear eternal vow of silence.
This is one of those moments when we have to accept
-
that there are things in the world,
that we should not intervene.
At least not yet.
These events in the light of
Vasglobe has decided to stop -
BAXTER program. Such progress
reduce the world too quickly.
Thank you.
Robby. - Hey, Dad. Do not cry.
All is well. -
If I could just say...
That you love me?
I love you, Dad.
You do not have to say it.
I will always be with you.
I'll always be watching you.
Just look at the stars.
I look.
I have to go now.
I know. Give the mother and Ruby
all my love.
I give. - Goodbye, Dad.
Goodbye, Robby.
Father, enkelilleni
up there