I'm worried the restaurant,
it lacks something.
Customers?
No one will be surprised
when they come in anymore.
- Have you seen their faces?
- Yes. "Is the place still here?"
Okay, so the restaurant is trustworthy,
but not surprising.
- What would surprise you?
- Customers.
I never liked you.
I tolerate you,
but I've never liked you.
Here you are.
I can show you what I have today.
This fountain was built in 1903
Mortimer Hayward.
- Have Beekman changed the design again?
- For God's sake.
- It is Saturday.
- When does he expect it?
I wish you spent as
much time on your privacy.
- Mom, I have lots of starlets.
- First Dates.
- Hey!
- Your father and I ...
... Soon celebrate 40-year anniversary.
Do you know why?
Because he asked me out
on a second date.
- Sorry, Joe.
- You have not much time.
- Your father was bald at an early age.
- Wait.
Dad has hair.
Well, it can be discussed.
No, it's my mother who harasses
me about my love life again.
Yes, if there was ever reason,
to come in to the office one weekend ...
I have distributed leaflets
local kontorsbyggnader-
-Short campaigns on social medier-
- Donated to local events
to raise the profile.
Nat, we've been friends a long time now-
- So I think I can say this,
without hurting your feelings.
Stop with the opera.
There is a wall of opera,
as soon as you come through the door.
Mom loved the opera.
She loved the customers too.
I know the restaurant
is your familjearv. I understand that.
But it has not been the same.
I know. Do not you think I know that?
That's why I have a new chef on the road.
I was hoping that after six
months would have found that ...
- I do not know.
- Magic?
Yes, I figured I
perhaps could find it.
- Oh my God, it's Lori Beth?
- Who?
Lori Beth Wacker.
From the seventh grade, remember?
Lori Beth.
- Hello.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Yes.
Your mother told me
that you were at home again.
- Lori Beth. How are you?
- Nick. Hello.
I moved home for a couple of months ago.
How wonderful to meet you.
- How long ago was it?
- 15 years.
My one true love.
And my biggest regret.
To lose touch when we moved.
But what a coincidence.
You know, Nick is a talented architect now.
He constructs bridges.
Nick, give her your card.
You always wanted to build things.
- Change the world.
- I do not exactly, but ...
Lori Beth works with
landscape planning.
Architect. Landscape.
It must be fate.
Speaking of work,
I like to work.
- Really nice to meet you, Lori Beth.
- You too, Nick.
- I'll call you.
- Awesome.
We have lots to catch up after so long.
There you have indeed.
- So call him.
- Okay, I will.
- Bye.
We just happened to run into each other?
What a coincidence.
Life is full of coincidences.
Although sometimes
need to give them a little push.
I feel so bad about
you do not earn any tip.
Want to quit?
I want you to stop.
Stop believing that you have to drive instead
exactly as it was when your mother was alive.
Sorry, Nat.
- I did not mean ...
- It's okay. It's just that ...
If it does not start to go well
I will lose the restaurant.
Both I and the restaurant
is stuck in the past.
Come on.
- Grandma!
- Uncle Nick!
Ungar. Hello.
- Look.
- I like these.
Are we late? We took a detour
past the girls' favorite store.
- Neon and glitter house.
- So it is said not at all.
Mom found yet another way to
introduce me to a future daughter in law.
Lori Beth Wacker.
He used to be crazy about her.
- I was 12th
- Grandma.
- Can we get 25-centare to the wishing well?
- 25 cents?
In my time it was a penny.
Do not look at me, I spent all
my money on neon and glitter house.
- It's not that.
- No?
25-centare.
Uncle Nick has 25-centare.
- Now we go and wish us something.
- You will be glad you did.
They are beautiful. Maybe I should
buy some at the restaurant.
Good morning, ladies.
A bouquet to brighten up the day?
- Yes. They are wonderful.
- 5.99 per bouquet.
All right. I'll take these.
- Please.
- Keep it.
No, she takes it.
- No, it's okay.
- Take it, just.
Thank you.
Sorry. What do you do?
All right.
You need this.
Wishing you a surprise.
To bring order in a restaurant
does not happen by magic.
If you knew surprise
would go 'compliance
What would you wish for?
You should always hold on
with my love life ...
Looking for a penny?
I have everything I could dream of.
But if I had one wish for you ...
Then you would wish
I did not have to become bald.
I wish
that you would forget her.
I know how you felt about Jessa,
but you must go on, darling.
You have to find the right one.
I bet that my desire
wrapping before yours.
The time is almost 11:00. We must draw.
Goodbye old man.
- Did he give you truly bill?
- The waitress came to us ...
... And then he put the bill
in front of me, as if I'd ...
No, I do not believe you.
- Hold on.
- How long were we together? Two weeks?
I have trouble believing it.
- What kind of guy does that?
- A 44-year old man.
I guess it is.
OPEN
I saw it.
If the city chooses solar,
we can connect the bridge to nätet-
- Then you get the power when it needs to,
and gives back what is left over.
Would you tell him?
Mr. Beekman, sir. Good morning.
- Thanks for coming in over the weekend.
- A deadline is a deadline.
We understand. And do not worry.
I'll give it a Beekman-touch.
It is therefore planning committee
will come to you.
- Have you been presented to any customer?
- Not a chance.
Where is he?
I'm not sure.
He would fly into yesterday.
I can cook, if he will not.
Thanks, Damien, but you may
can replenish the salt and pepper pots.
Sure.
There he is. Our new chef.
Natalia.
What's he saying?
He thinks I'm
a radiant beauty. Sweet.
You are not bad yourself.
My name Sharla.
With "A", which kind is Italian.
Yes, keep staring at me,
with the dark brown eyes.
His name is Mario. Mario.
You said he was an old man
from Italy. He is not old age.
I hope he can cook,
for it promised my relatives.
I'm sorry that I could not
welcome you at the airport yesterday.
I do not know how to
say it in Italian.
No problem. I feel
your warm welcome.
- Okay, Natalia.
- And he speaks English.
- Should I cook tonight?
- Yes, let me show you the kitchen.
It is a rather simple kitchen.
- Everything ...
- Idiot.
Anyone here?
Hello? Hello.
No, mom. I told you
did not have to bring your lunch.
I just want to be sure
you get a decent meal.
- Hey, Joe.
- Hello.
- I have something for you too.
- I love your mom.
Told Nick that we ran into his ex?
- Love of his life.
- Yes, when I was 12th
Then she moved
and broke his heart.
I was 12th
His first kiss.
- When you were 12th
- So it got stuck.
- I want you to take her out.
- No, Mom.
You're a super-mom.
I love you.
How many times have I told you
not to fix me up with ...
Stand-up evening at the Comedy Cellar.
Tomorrow, noon. 20:00.
Lori Beth loves to laugh.
It's a date.
- I fixed it for you.
- Yes.
There are only two here.
Did not you buy three?
- So you can put yourself in a little more.
- May I?
There are extra mustard in the bag, Joe.
Your mom is the best.
Do you think Lori Beth has a friend?
Do not let me down.
She might become your come true
fountain desire.
No, my desire was to win
environmentally friendly bridge contest.
Come on, not so loud.
Beekman will find ...
How is it?
It's not the same.
It is better.
Awesome. I'll tell the chef.
- Wonderful.
- I think it's great.
- Is it a new dish?
- Where's the garlic?
Right.
They love the food.
- What are you looking for?
- One of the regulars like extra garlic.
Alfredo sauce.
I know it's weird, but ...
- Wait, wait.
- No, do not worry.
- It's just his thing.
- His thing is not my thing.
- What? Wait. Mario.
- Alfredo sauce.
Mario.
- Hello.
- Extra garlic?
- Please.
- Additional more?
What he means is that he appreciates
Your suggestions for extra garlic.
I told you to eat like a pig.
All right.
No no no. The house offers ...
Natalia, you need more clienti.
I can not cook without customers.
I can cook.
You have two new voice messages.
New message.
Hey, it's Amanda.
Thank you for dinner the other night.
Hey, I heard about the art show
and I wondered ...
Hello, this is Kelly from the coffee mill.
I do not usually do like this,
but I thought of you ...
PRICE FOR ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY BRIDGE
ARCHITECTURAL INSTITUTE
Together we build
When the cycle repeats itself,
along Aruba's coastal
- Seeking the male flamingo
for a partner.
You have a new voice message.
Hello, Natalie. It's Ellis, Sharlas cousin.
We met at her party.
Sharla said you need to get out.
No, wait, that did not sound good.
Anyway, I like to eat food.
Wait, wait, it rings.
But it is not good on the island,
and our flamingo family kämpar-
- To survive the harsh,
windy autumn.
Want a table?
A table?
Wait.
How did I get here?
I recognize this place.
Where is everyone?
It's just us.
My name is Natalie.
Hello, Natalie. I called Nick.
- It feels like I've seen you before.
- I know. It feels ...
I feel like I know you.
Excuse me.
I think it's for you.
To me?
It is you.
No, it's my mother.
You've obviously inherited her spirit.
Thank you.
Who are you?
You are so beautiful.
Did I like it?
It's nothing.
During the summer months,
the snow penguins water source.
When he received nourishment, he
viability to proceed.
It was a dream, but it was so real.
Especially the part where you woke up
alone in your pajamas.
- On my sofa.
- Did he look like Justin Timberlake?
- Better looking.
- No one is prettier ...
... Than Justin Timberlake.
It was definitely a dream.
- Called my cousin Ellis you?
- Yes.
Why did you say to him to do it?
Heart, I say this with love,
you have to call him up.
If you do not like to work on Saturday,
did not come in on Sunday.
- I know, buddy.
- Is that brotävlingen?
We have drawings to finish.
Lori Beth has set a countdown clock
for our date tonight.
I get alerts every hour.
- Has she always been so?
- I do not know. I was 12th
- She was sweet. Who remembers?
- Hon.
Doomsday Clock back?
Now texting me she outfits to
see what she'll wear tonight.
She sends copies to the mother also.
It's amazing.
Dates are canceled.
I can not. My mother would kill me.
Mother Pig?
Kiddos. How is it going in the sandbox?
Are you finished with the drawings?
Almost.
Very, very soon.
We're doing it. No problem.
- Set aside brotävlingen.
- I will.
Hold on.
- What is it white?
- Do you like it?
I added this solar array,
to help the bridge to generate power.
- It's brilliant.
- I know right?
I mean it. But you heard him.
We must focus on the drawings.
If he finds out the competition, you are screwed.
You can not only participate in various
races when you're working for him.
I know. I just ...
I have to keep the brain in shape.
Hey, Mario.
Limoncello?
Yes. For tiramisun.
It is not possible.
Yes, it is possible.
No. This is my kitchen, okay?
This is my kitchen.
Our kitchen, no problem,
però no limoncello in tiramisun.
It is a recipe from my grandmother
with a twist.
But she was well Greeks?
- What's the difference?
- Another recipe.
Not only does this recipe, all recipe.
It is time, Mario.
Come and taste with me.
Together we create magic.
All right. About five minutes.
Five minutes.
What? He is Italian.
He is so with all women.
Well, he does not want to
cook with me,
- Which is a shame,
for it would be tough.
Okay, I'll see about it
are any clienti. I'm okay.
- Madame.
- Will.
Excuse me.
- It will be good.
- Excuse me.
What do you think?
Outfit. Yes.
I think it is the best.
- Do you think?
- Yes, absolutely.
I do not look like 12 anymore?
Do I?
- Nice to see you again.
- The same.
We're going to hit.
FREE TIRAMISU
- What's this?
- "Storage b ..." What?
- Some kind of pasta?
- 'L'Agrifoglio. "
Something sort of wine.
L'Agrifoglio.
It means "holly" in Italian.
It was the name of my grandmother
restaurant in Italy.
The place was covered with holly.
- It was exactly like this.
- So it is authentic Italian?
With a twist.
And tonight we tiramisu.
- On the house.
- I am in.
- Come on, Gloria.
- Okay.
- Awesome.
- What's the twist?
Tonight? Two new customers.
Then it is best that I go.
It was hilarious.
Sure, he was funny?
Yes, he was ...
He was pretty funny.
What do we do now?
Should we relive time-
- When we skipped homework
and hid in the library?
- In this case, it would be adorable.
- Then we'll go.
Your mother thought it was super fun.
- Really?
- Or when my brother Luke ...
... Got his driver's license and
took us to the drive-in?
- Do you remember the children's banned the film?
- Yes, so you ...
So you told everything to my mom?
Yes, today, when she helped me
to choose the outfit.
You, I think I
is a bit overworked at jobbet-
-so I should probably go home and sleep.
Tip. Accurate tip.
- Tiramisu.
- Thanks.
- On the house.
- Awesome.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Damiano, the floor is wet.
It must be dry.
My ... My hero.
I am a hero, huh?
- Yes. Can ...? Can you help me?
- Yes.
- Yes, we have to work.
- Okay.
Remember when you found out
I wrote "Mrs. Lori Beth Smith" -
-over my notebook?
I was ashamed as an animal.
- Here is my car.
- Okay.
Lori Beth, I really appreciate
you went out with me.
I was really my mother.
That's not why I'm here, Nick.
I thought maybe it would
was something between us.
I've always wondered about you.
But now we're together again.
I updated my online status
to "In a relationship with Nick Smith".
You might want to remove it.
Are you breaking up with me?
It does not end
if not even been together.
I've just taken me through something
quite intensively with someone and ...
- It was great, Nat.
- Thank you, Sharla. Good night.
- Thanks. Have a good evening.
- Good night, Damien. You too.
Natalia.
Limoncello in tiramisu is not original
recipe, but perhaps not so bad.
- That's big of you to admit, Mario.
- I am great.
Big heart.
Do you like me?
- As a chef?
- Yes.
Yes. The paste is incredible.
And main dishes
we can work on, but ...
Che "working on".
Okay, Natalia.
You teach me how to cook?
- No.
- Natalia teaches Mario. All right.
No, it was a ...
It was a good night, Mario.
Now we will be sure to get some sleep.
Some sleep.
You get some sleep.
You go to your home, and I ...
Now we sleep.
Yes.
All right.
Natalia, your mother and my mother,
were friends in school.
My mom wanted to tell
she is very sad.
Your beautiful mother.
The trees were taken over by savannen-
- And giraffes fighting
a war against the woods
- To claim the country
we now call Africa.
The highest animals
devoured the highest grenarna-
- While the elephants used their strength
to lift the trees for nourishment.
- Careful!
- It's okay.
I can fly.
Do not do that. Please.
I just got here.
I want to feel alive.
Really live. Would not you?
Only ...
I want to take risks.
Is not it about time?
Look, it's so beautiful out there.
Look there. Do you see?
- I see nothing.
- Exactly.
This is where I hope
my bridge will stand.
What bridge?
I submitted a design
to a city contest.
You design bridges?
I do most drafts, but yes,
this is mine.
I think that is good.
I see it.
There it is. I see it.
- Have they built it? How is that possible?
- It is fantastic.
You are talented.
That's why.
It must be amazing.
To create something,
and make it a reality.
It's not as scary up here.
No.
My mother used to say:
"Spread your wings, Natalie."
You smell good.
Amaretti. I baked today.
- What is amaretti?
- Cakes.
To the restaurant.
Let me show you something.
The floating ...
Liberate themselves from their frames.
You get a taste of the magic.
What? And you say
you do not create something?
I? Create? I just ... I cook.
For me ...
... It tastes like a creation.
You may be right.
DREAM ENCYCLOPEDIA
You interpret dreams?
Do you dream of me?
Dreams revealing
our innermost secrets.
And desires, bella.
Yes. I have to work.
Here, an old family recipe
from Umbria. With a twist.
She called me in tears.
Okay, I'm a pig.
You and several others.
She has had three broken engagements
recent years.
- Three?
- Two, three.
It means that she is ready,
but have not found the right person.
Have you ever dreamed
if someone you've never met?
As the dream of Jack Nicholson?
A young, virile, Jack Nicholson?
No, mom.
Forget I mentioned it.
Have you found a dream girl, darling?
This is going to sound ridiculous,
but I dream about this nice girl.
She is so real.
More real than any
I ever met.
That's wonderful.
If you dream of a special GIRLS
- Prepares your brain you on
to fall in love for real.
This is very promising.
My job as a mother is ready for today.
Good to know.
Mario, an excellent evening. Thank you.
- Thanks, you guys. Good night.
- Bye.
- We'll see.
Neither a wink or kiss
for poor Mario?
Do you dream about that guy who is
prettier than Justin Timberlake again?
Two nights in a row.
- Wow.
- I know.
He's just like anybody I
would be with the real thing.
Why do not I have such dreams?
When I'm with him, it feels like
we have always known each other.
It's like a fantasy.
I agree probably going mad.
I can not wait until I go to sleep
so that I might get to meet him.
- Am I crazy?
- Yes. Maybe.
What do you do if you met the love,
though he exists only in one's fantasy
- And there is no chance of it
will meet, for he is pretending?
And what if the life-
- Are so much better in dreams,
that it never felt more alive.
I think you should get some sleep.
This is crazy.
All right.
Will this continue
night after night?
I was hoping to see you here.
Plums. My favorite.
Oh, this.
It is unreal good.
You must taste.
- Careful.
- I'll be careful.
Wow, wonderful.
- Like a snowball fight?
- You lose.
I doubt it. Oh, no!
Wait, you can not ... It's not fair.
I beat you.
You let me win, right?
I used to have a picnic on a
place like this when I was little.
Had the mood lighting?
Plums and plates with food.
Everything is good, except the broccoli.
You've never tasted my broccoli.
I own an Italian restaurant, you know.
Is that so?
What are we doing here?
I guess I can take you there,
and cook some special broccoli.
If you want.
I would love to.
All right.
Harat.
When she fell ill, I cooked food
and took me to the hospital.
But she was so weak
that she could not eat.
The food was something we shared all these years.
Since she died ...
As soon as you think of her,
reminds the restaurant you about her.
I ... It must be difficult.
That every day reminded anyone
you love that can not be there.
You have to put
your own stamp on the place.
Really make it your own.
How long have we walked?
I think we're close.
All night?
It's nothing.
You will become a famous designer.
It shows.
Do you think so?
I do not know.
Do you believe, deep down, that it is
normal to doubt himself?
I think it is abnormal
not to do it.
But you will win the prize.
You'll see.
Oh, I ...
I think we went wrong.
I think we should be there.
It's okay.
- I've been nice.
- Me too.
Tomorrow night perhaps?
Definitely.
- I think I'm starting ...
- I know.
So do I.
- Tomorrow.
- Yes.
You must try. Squid pasta.
All right. With a twist.
This is definitely not the opera.
- What do you think?
- It was about time. But this ...
I can hardly believe.
It is hard to say "L'Agrifoglio".
"Russo's Italian."
And you can say it.
And customers too.
Only it's a coup.
I had a dream
and woke up and tänkte-
- I must make it my own
without forgetting its history.
Suggested dream guy there?
No.
No, I just ... It was just me.
Of course it was you.
You can not trust men.
They are unreliable, even in fantasies.
- What do you do?
- What? The desire to share with you?
Come on, stargazer,
otherwise we will sit all night.
No, not all night.
- I have plans.
- Me too.
I know I do not have much of a life
outside this place, but ...
Excuse me?
- It is Jessa, heartthrob.
- No.
Hello, Jessa. It's Joe.
- Do not ...
- Yes. No, yeah, actually.
- I watch all Nick calls.
- Hang up.
Well, right now, Nick the manager.
- It is good.
- Yes, he's on the rise.
I'll tell you called? All right.
Okay, bye-bye.
- She's back.
- No.
No no no.
- Yes.
- No, listen.
- Goddess Jessa.
- Gone.
No.
- Do not do it.
- Gone.
- No.
Not that, please.
- We might retain it.
- Yes.
Nick? Come in.
Jessa?
- What is it?
- A mouse.
A what?
Is that why you call in the middle of the night
and says it's an emergency?
It's really great.
It's over there.
Under the sink.
I did not know who I would call.
Why not call Bob or steak,
whatever his name was.
Steak.
It's a really big mouse.
That may be a rat.
Do not leave me.
Hello?
Where are you?
I made a mistake.
I made a terrible mistake.
You hit Jessa again.
Have you put a GPS in my neck
so you can track me around the clock?
I do not need a chip.
I have a mom radar.
When I said you should dejta-
- I did not mean with that
was unfaithful and broke your heart.
I'm a big boy.
I have released it. You should too.
- Please.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- How do you know that I met her?
I saw it online. A photo of a rat
and her hero ex-boyfriend, Nick.
So my mom's friend
with my ex-girlfriends.
I accepted her friendship
when I thought she was human.
They should keep your generation
away from the Internet.
You do not look to have slept at all.
Thanks, Sharla. I slept long enough to
realize that I do not want to live in a dream.
I want to feel alive again,
I used to do.
The restaurant is my moment.
I have to put a spin on it.
I can not keep it
Mom's sake, but for my own.
There she is.
We pulled in twice as much last night
we made all week.
I will continue to work with the recipes,
put my stamp on it-
- Inserting it in the 2000s
and then maybe I can dating.
My cousin Ellis still waiting.
Hello, Mr. Taylor.
Nick Smith. I'm working
on your project, with Beekman.
I just wanted to introduce myself
and tell me that my partner and me
- Here at the company, has boiled
together some innovative idéer-
- Who can save the city money,
raise the environmental profile of a component
And maybe get a tax credit.
- Really?
- To be specific ...
... I think we can incorporate
collecting rainwater
- Sewage, recycling,
without much additional cost.
Interesting.
I look forward to hearing more.
Nick. Nick Smith.
- George Taylor. Same to you.
- Nice to meet you.
Jeez, it looks much better
without it, right?
Oh, Mario. I thought we
should have the risotto as a special right tonight.
Awesome. And after work,
I wondered if ...
I'm not so good at this.
Will you go out with me?
All right.
- How long did you talk to him?
- 20 minutes.
Light 20 minutes.
You will experience Beekman-
touch, but not in a good way.
What's the point,
if we do not show up your feet?
If you do not want to work here.
Do not you think we should
few make ourselves heard?
What happened to you?
Hello, Jessa. It's Joe.
How are you? What, do you want ...?
- Hello.
- I just wanted to ...
Tonight?
If he wants to go back to Jessa,
it is his own affair.
He needs to dating someone serious.
Get married, have children, be happy.
Mom says marriage
do not make you happy.
Okay, it was a message
the authorization for my girls.
Taken out of context,
let it probably ...
Nick might avoid intimacy to ...
See on your perfect marriage.
Can you blame him if he thinks
he can never get it.
I hate broccoli.
Sarah, no.
Oops, prinsesstallriken
was not to you.
It was the Princess
Tatiana of Morania.
She is in town and always come here
our secret broccoli recipes.
She says it makes
hair long and thick.
- I'll take it.
- I'll keep it.
All right.
Excuse me. Are you in a relationship?
For I believe that you and my son ...
Mom.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
What?
- She is wonderful.
- Seriously.
Hold on.
Are you saying that you turned down her?
Liberty Jessa invading
my dreams in a chaste manner.
I said I needed to get to sleep tonight.
I wish I had your problems.
Smith. My office, now.
I'm just really surprised that you
discussed my project with the customer.
You are here to draw.
If you have a problem with it-
- Maybe you should find another job
that suits you better.
Yes, sir, I hear you.
And by the way, I really hope
your contribution to the competition is on your time.
Yes. It is embarrassing to
a colleague in finalistjuryn-
- Contact me
if your contribution to my firm.
I am ...
I'm sorry.
I should have told you ...
- ... That I attend.
- Yes.
I downloaded a drink.
Is it ...? Is it limoncello?
It tastes much better
in a efterrätt-
-an in a drink.
- Do you like to dance?
- Not directly ...
- Come on.
- I like to dance alone.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- I ... I'm horrible at dancing.
- You're a very good dancer.
- Okay.
- This is great.
Natalie?
Natalie!
- You like kicks and jazz hands.
- I can no movement.
- You sing.
- I'm trying.
Yes, it makes you really.
- You're a good dancer.
- No.
All right.
Natalia.
- Not so bad, huh?
- No, not so bad.
- Our mothers might was right.
- What do you mean?
The last time your mother came to Italy
talked of our mothers.
I heard them say:
"Mario and Natalia, is ..."
- "They are made for each other."
- Did they say that?
Good night.
How long have you dreamed
this fictional person?
Three nights.
And then I missed one.
And last night, she appeared not up ...
I do not know.
I found her
and made her disappear.
I could hardly wait to go to sleep
to meet her.
To be with her,
was fantastic.
I was invulnerable.
I could do anything.
You are really calm right now.
That worries me.
I thought you would be angry.
- I? No.
- Yes.
Things you can not explain
happens every day.
Yes.
Yes, but you do not want
live in dreamland.
If it's worth anything,
maybe you sheepmeat
- A price in the weekend,
in this real world.
I'm not so sure that it will be so.
60 percent in the evening.
Any changes you have made
really worth.
One feels almost back instead.
You should call the TV restaurant critic.
It is not a bad idea.
Maybe when the menu is in order.
Are you okay?
Some good dreams lately?
No, I hardly slept last night.
I was out with Mario yesterday.
We danced, if you can imagine it.
You know how it is said
Dissolving things in their dreams?
Dream guy maybe your way of
show yourself that you could go on.
And you did.
Good for you.
- Hello. Welcome to Russo's.
- Hello.
Just three? In this direction.
I thought you said that we
would eat at home tonight?
You know I'm not laws
food, so we're going out.
I've had a really tough day.
I'm tired.
The clock is 19:00, so ...
It was bedtime long time ago for you.
Okay, pick a place. We can go out.
Thank you.
Have you been here before?
It is new.
Six new just arrived. We are almost
crammed. What should I do?
I'll help you.
Give me a couple of minutes only.
- Download.
- Excuse me.
I can cook. I can cook.
All right. Thank you, Damien.
- Hello. Welcome to Russo's Italian.
- Thanks.
For two. Do you have anything?
The last table. This way.
- Thanks.
- Please.
- Do you want to start with something to drink?
- Yes.
- Thanks.
- I take a pinot.
Wonderful choice.
Same for me. Thank you.
All right.
Wait, we should ...?
- Should we order?
- Yes.
We should probably order.
You seem really busy.
You can order well for me?
Now I feel stressed.
She takes anatra ...
- Okay.
- ... And I will take the lamb.
Perfect. Thank you.
If you add the broccoli, please.
Yes.
Thank you.
You hate broccoli.
Maybe I'm a changed man.
Nick.
Nick. Come on, please.
For a fresh start?
Yes. A fresh start.
Cheers.
I'm thinking of leaving Beekman.
- Are you going to leave Beekman?
- Yes.
It would mean
to be out on their own.
Or with Joe if he wants to.
You mean really seriously.
It does not feel like the right time to take risks.
Why not?
Right, I have not even told.
I am a finalist in the city brotävling.
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh my God. Congratulations.
Is it a large cash prize or ...?
No, it is more about prestige.
So there is no money?
No, but, I mean, if I win
people will take notice of me.
- And maybe I can ...
- Maybe you should wait until you win.
Then we can talk about
that you should leave the Beekman.
Yes.
- Yes.
- I did not mean that.
Give me a second.
Oh, God ...
Clean up only, Damien.
Sharla, which table should anatran
and lamb with broccoli to?
- Table nine.
- Hot!
- Download.
- Okay, anatra.
- Thanks.
Would you like some pepper?
- Not for myself, but for my boyfriend.
- Okay.
Say to. All right.
He likes a lot of pepper. Thank you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry.
Are you okay?
- Excuse me.
- It's okay.
This looks good.
Nick?
Table Three.
Natalia.
Nick, what is it?
Yeah, I just ...
I was looking for pepper.
Seriously, you and your pepper ...
- What is it?
- Who was sitting here?
Lamb-and-broccoli-guy.
- Broccoli?
- Yes.
You saw him, right?
And the girl he was here with?
Are you looking for him?
The man of your dreams?
Hold on.
You are the woman who sells flowers?
- What are you doing here?
- I come here when I can not sleep.
I saw my true love
in my dreams for seven nights in a row.
That is how the legend is working.
- What legend?
- Hayward fountain.
Legend has it that throwing a coin
- And seven nights dreaming man
of his true love.
And if you really love him,
- Will stones spirits
to make him real.
It is ...
It is pure fantasy.
Did it happen to you?
Take my advice.
Find yourself a real guy
and save yourself the pain.
During a short period of time,
found beaver water
-skapade ponds and found frid-
-in a dangerous and tough ecosystems.
Hello?
Hello.
Did not think I ever
would see you again.
Here I am.
Must be fate.
Really? Do you believe in destiny?
I'll find you, again and again.
Yes. And it feels right
When I'm with you.
Right?
It feels like I
can do what I want.
- I can win brotävlingen.
- Or as I can ride me ...
... And restore my family's restaurant.
Just.
What more can I ask?
- Something real.
- But it is real, somehow.
It's just ... not fair.
Same thing again.
Another night where we just go round and round.
I'm tired of this.
It is unrealistic. The more I see you
the harder it becomes.
- But you said it feels so good.
- Yes I did.
But that is only an illusion, okay?
Even if the legend is true ...
We only have one more night.
- What legend?
- Seven nights ...
... Seven chances to dream of you,
then it's over.
Okay, but it is not over. Not yet.
Hoping helps nothing.
- Stop. I wake up when we touch each other.
- Exactly.
You're all I ever dreamed,
but you are not.
Why do I go through this?
I must move on.
- Stop.
- No, I must go on.
Do not look for me tomorrow.
I will not sleep.
What if you're wrong?
What if we can find each other?
- You are not real.
- Natalie.
Jessa?
No, just a reminder for
award ceremony on Saturday night.
This is our chance.
Although there is
there is a future in which out-
- Which does not have to include
Lance Beekman, because I'm completion
-with make tråkgörat.
If I leave now,
and choose to become self-
-följer you with me?
Are you ...?
Have you any idea what it takes?
To arrange customers, provide office,
hiring employees?
- Pay ... Pay the Bills?
- I know. I know.
It will be tough, but if I win,
it will generate interest.
- Do you expect that?
- We will be crushed.
Competition on price is enormous.
- So you do not think I can win.
- That said, I do not.
I need the papers in the office.
All right.
Let me ask this:
Do you like it here?
Do you enjoy giving everything you have
to perfect Beekman-touch?
- Yablonski, Smith and co-workers.
- No no.
Smith, Yablonski, so you get to be with.
Yes.
- Damien?
- Yes.
I have hired a new busboy,
so you get to be Deputy Director tonight.
- Serious?
- Then you must listen to me.
Now we run all weekend, and I
just want to say how grateful I am.
Very good.
- Grandpa, can we get a cookie?
- What? A cake?
Sure, you get a cookie.
We go and find them.
Where are they? Oh, cakes.
Hey, hey.
- Uncle Nick.
Here they are.
Hello.
Glad to see you.
Jessa, good to see you.
Mr. Smith.
Mike, do you remember?
Do you remember those two?
Hannah and Sarah,
you have been so long.
We eat broccoli now.
Congratulations on the wedding, Charlotte.
Mrs Smith.
Thanks, Jessa.
Remember to keep the floor dry.
- Got that? In this direction.
- Everything okay for tonight?
- I know. Classico Italiano with a twist.
- Okay.
Twist, twist. I give you
more twist than a pretzel, huh?
Do not be mad at me.
It does not sound good.
It can be good.
Okay, spit it out.
I called the TV station and
urged food critic to dine here.
- Rodney Sims?
- We're ready, Nat.
If he hates us he digs us down
in a deep hole that we can not get out.
No, he can not.
This is your dream, Nat.
And it's so good for you.
The restaurant and Mario.
I raise my glass to my bride.
Charlotte, my beloved älskling-
- You are just as beautiful today
the first day we met.
40 years of happiness.
- I was a child-bride.
- I know right.
- Grandpa kisses grandmother again.
- They do that sometimes.
I was scarred for a long time ago
the sight.
Casanova, toddlers watching.
- Stop.
- No, you can stop.
- Sarah.
- Girls. You and you, outside. Come now.
- Give them no attention.
- Now you did it.
You emptied the room.
You know what keeps me, Nick?
At my age?
- What?
- The heart.
Without the heart, there is no passion.
No passion, no life.
And I thank my luck
that Charlotte is my passion-
-My heart and my life.
May you all find the same.
It's about time. Happy birthday.
- Congratulations on the wedding day.
- Thanks.
Congratulations on the wedding day.
Thank you, darling.
Here you are.
Can I interfere?
You always interfere.
We know that about you.
Your sister says
To avoid tying you-
- Because you think you can not get
the relationship your father and I have.
Mom, you and Dad have
is astounding.
I would love to have it so one day,
but I have not had the luck.
Then you wait.
But do not settle for less.
You have dreamed of the girl,
now you have to go out and find her.
- You will not find fantasies.
- It was not what I meant.
Do not be so literal.
We have the old Hayward legend.
You may be able
dream up a looker.
- Excuse me?
- Do not listen to your father.
- He thinks he's funny.
- You know ...
... The legend of Hayward Fountain.
People throw coins in fontänen-
- And then they dream about
their true love for seven nights.
Is it not so?
If you can dream it, you can get it.
Take the plunge.
Thank you.
But I'm not going to chase after a dream.
As food critic, Rodney Sims-
- Appears well just up,
without warning?
Yes, unfortunately.
Appeared dream boy up last night?
No.
I do not dream about
the impossible anymore.
Mr Beekman,
This is not working.
You have talent, but there are
something called rightful share.
I've been here for three years.
Do you know how long it took for me
to get my big break?
No, but you know what I know?
That it is time for me to get out
my name and my designs.
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but it will not happen here.
I know.
She would be proud of
what you accomplished.
Yes, I think so too.
I was awake all night yesterday
so that I would not dream.
Why?
We got seven nights.
Seven nights to dream,
and now it's over.
It's over.
It is already queued.
All right.
Nick. Did not you get my mess?
We would eat breakfast together.
I waited.
What happens?
I quit.
The expression on the face Beekmans
when I told? Priceless.
Have you stopped?
Would not you wait for the award?
Why are not you happy for me?
I stopped because I wanted to.
I needed to do
a big change in my life.
But what if you do not win?
And you said that there is no prize money.
- It's not about money.
- I can not believe you said you up.
Do not do that. Not now.
I just want what's best for you.
What is best for us.
I'm sorry. Your table is ready
for a few minutes, I promise.
- Jamie, can you hurry?
- Yes. All right.
I ask again so awful
very sorry.
- Natalie, you're needed here.
- Okay, I will.
Mario, was the gnocchi to table four?
- Grab it.
- I dropped the pasta.
My finest plate.
Excuse me.
I dropped it almost.
PRICE FOR ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY BRIDGE
- Please.
- Thanks.
Jessa. Back and more beautiful than ever.
- Why are you with him again?
- This time it's for good.
- Do you have a twin?
- They made only one of me.
I agree.
What?
- What?
- Nothing.
- Will it be this good?
- Yes, good. Thank you.
Tonight is our specialty
a wonderful mushroom risotto.
I look forward to the "wonderful".
The bill is on me.
OK good. Then we will arrange it.
Mario, I need a little extra risotto.
Nat. Nat ...
- Sharla!
- Oh my God. Sharla.
- Sharla.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, God.
- Yes, I'm okay.
I feel good.
- Are you okay?
- Oh yes.
- No, Nat, I would never ...
- No no no.
Sharla, it's perfect. I ...
I have tried to find the feeling of ...
I did not want to hurt you, Mario.
- What's he saying?
- Chemistry. We have no personal chemistry.
No spark.
However, Natalia, you are
a very close friend.
Yes, of course.
I must do something.
Wait, Nat.
Rodney Sims are here.
- Is he?
- Yes.
- How did I miss that?
- I have to go. You solve it.
- You can not go. You need to be here.
If I do not try to find him
I will forever regret it.
Sharla.
You just ...
Keep the idea, okay?
Everybody, just ...
All hands on deck, okay?
We do this with the heart,
and we do it for Natalie.
All right.
Clean the floor!
Nick, this is it.
It is best that you win.
Sorry. I can not do this.
I thought it would
be different. Sorry.
- What?
- I must find her.
- Nick!
Italian.
Italian. Italian.
MEN NICK SMITH WITH GUEST
PRICE FOR ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY BRIDGE
ARCHITECTURAL INSTITUTE
Excuse me. Excuse ...
- Units owner of this Natalie?
- No.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the price for green bridge.
Excuse me, this is Natalie's place?
- Is she the owner here?
- No.
... For the most environmentally conscious
and aesthetically innovative bronchiolitis
-is year's recipient ... Nick Smith.
Yes! Nick!
Yes!
Thank you.
I'm not Nick Smith,
I'm not nearly as talented as he is.
But I am his friend and partner
in our new company:
Smith, Yablonski and employees.
I am overjoyed to receive
this award on his behalf.
Thank you very much.
Mushroom risotto, sir.
Want something more?
No, thanks.
Sir ... Can I ...?
Is it ...? Is it ...?
It is ...
... Perfect.
Wonderful.
Download it.
- Excuse me.
- Yes? Yes.
- Is Natalie owners here?
- Yes.
- This is Natalie's place?
- My name Sharla. And you are ...?
- She do not know me.
Or she knows me, but ...
Where is she?
I do not know. She just went.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, I'm sorry. Sorry.
How about it?
- Good work.
- Thanks.
Hello. You know Nick.
- Where is he?
- I do not know.
I must find him.
Do you know where he went?
- Do I know you?
- No.
- Good work.
- Neat.
- Did he say where he was going?
- No.
- He left without saying where.
- I do not know where else I can look.
What if the magic stops working
after tonight and we never ...?
And we have never seen?
- Nick?
- Natalie?
What if it's just a dream?
There is only one way
To find out it.
You are real.
Come here one minute.
- Hello. $ 5.99, right?
- Yes.
There he is.
- Here.
- Please.
All right.
No, keep it.
Goodbye.
Here it is, ladies and gentlemen.
The famous Hayward fountain.
Built in 1903 by Mortimer Hayward.
The stones are from the ruins of a castle
was supposed to be enchanted.
The legend said that the magic
still in the stones.
It is said that if you make a wish,
one can dream of their true love.
Translation:
Stephanie Clarke
www.HoundDawgs.org
Newest Nordic Retail!
Get your own free account. Write to us
hunddawgs@gmail.com