Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
And welcome to our little show.
Tonight, we got ourselves...
...a bona fide multiplicitous...
...conglomeration of cubanos...
...on this here stage tonight.
We got...
...Paquito D'Rivera!
We got Ignacio Berroa!
And...
...we got my newest...
...Cuban son...
...Arturo Sandoval.
Here by special permission
of the Cuban government.
I'd like to say something.
Ever since I was a little boy and...
...since the first time I heard his music...
...I had a dream to be able to play
with maestro Dizzy Gillespie.
So, to me right now, life is truly a dream.
Mari, it's me, Arturo.
Arturo, where are you?
I'm in Athens.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
You're in London, this is it.
We're halfway there. It's all arranged.
Tonight?
I will be in Italy tomorrow.
Be careful.
I'll call you when I get there.
Tell 'em none of that feta cheese.
-Got that? "Un-feta."
-You got it.
Don't go away.
Arturo, what's going on?
Quick, give me a cigarette.
My wife and son are in London.
They're where?
We're not going back.
It's not done yet.
It's okay. Don't worry.
We'll get you out.
Arturo, man, let's go.
I called the embassy.
They're expecting us.
What's the matter?
I still got family there, Diz.
When you leave, the government
punishes those you leave behind and love.
Then are you sure you want to do this?
I've been in jail all my life.
Freedom's a scary thing, but...
...I gotta get on the bird.
Well, come on, let's do it.
-The embassy's closed, sir.
-You better get it open.
This is an international incident.
My Cuban friend--
-Sir, the embassy's closed.
-Not for me. I'm Dizzy Gillespie.
-Open the gate, Sergeant.
-Yes, sir.
It's an honor to meet you, we got your call.
You must be Arturo Sandoval.
That's the second greatest
trumpet player in the world.
Someone should be....
-There you are.
-Good evening, gentlemen.
I should say, good morning.
I'm Michael Tasker.
I'm a big fan, Mr. Gillespie.
Thank you. This is Arturo--
Arturo Sandoval, yes, petition for asylum.
How long's this gonna take?
Red tape respects no boundaries.
That's an international fact of life.
-If you'd like to--
-This is the American Embassy.
I know you got some
apple pie around here.
I think we can arrange something.
-You be cool.
-Thank you, Diz.
Enjoy. Right this way.
Your Mr. Gillespie
is one of the few people...
...who can open this place
in the middle of the night.
Have a seat and I'll be back in a moment.
Thank you.
Coffee?
Thank you, yes.
I'm scared.
Trust me.
I think I should explain...
...there are certain criteria that must be
met before we can grant asylum.
An individual must prove
that he is unable to return...
...to his homeland for fear of persecution.
I understand. That's why I'm here.
You've been touring
with Mr. Gillespie's United Nation band.
-Are you here with your family?
-No.
My wife and son
are waiting for me in London.
-You're seeking asylum for them as well?
-Yes.
Is there a problem?
I just need some information.
Okay.
So, you've been a musician
for how many years?
Since I was six years old.
I taught my cat how to walk on a tight rope
while I played the bongos.
It was like an animal act.
And you were educated at
a government-run music school?
Yes.
You were classically trained?
It says you were a member
of the Cuban Music Academy.
Is that right?
Yes.
Is that a state-sponsored organization?
Your first professional job....
What is that? "Orquesta--"
Cuban Modern Music Orchestra.
-Government sponsored?
-Yes, of course.
If the government doesn't sponsor it,
it doesn't exist.
Maybe I'm missing something here,
because it seems that on paper...
...that the government
treated you quite well.
They supported you as a musician.
Yes.
Yes, as long as I did what they wanted.
That's the shit!
That's what we should be playing.
I know!
Start a band and get on the bird and fly!
-You haven't changed.
-What for?
You look good, very handsome.
Even without the hair, very handsome.
-What's this about?
-Nothing.
Come on in, guys. Relax, please, sit down.
Here, don't burn my couch.
Jaime, why are we here?
What is this meeting about?
Compañero Somavilla
brought a matter to my attention.
I just mentioned to Jaime, that...
...you want to start your own band.
You're own band. It's a good idea.
It's a shame we just can't do it.
Caballeros.
I'm an artist just like you are.
I understand the need to invoke the muse.
But as Cubans,
we have to present a united front.
Politically and musically.
Destroying the orquesta
is not in our interests--
No.
We do not want to destroy anything.
Just the best band in Cuba, that's all.
There's room for
another great band in Cuba.
Normally I'd agree with you
but we're living in times of scarcity now.
Exactly. Besides....
I just can't see why you can't play
what you want in the orquesta.
In the orquesta,
we play what you want us to play.
We need to experiment.
You don't want to experiment.
You just don't want to play our music.
You want to play their music.
-The music of the enemy.
-What is the music of the enemy?
That's enough!
Our comrades are losing
their lives in Angola.
You guys are thinking
about your little music.
Just about yourselves!
There's no time for that.
There are limits!
-Leave the cowboys alone.
-I never saw that picture before.
I don't care, this is dominoes.
-Pay attention to the game!
-One more coffee, please.
Wait, it's not your turn.
Gracias, Mama.
Your coffee is like a wake-up kiss
in the morning.
Cirita bonita, tan bella y sabrosita.
Gracias.
Tastes like the fourth time
through on these grounds.
You boys wanna play?
Maybe later, Papi.
This is going nowhere.
You heard Jaime?
They pull us out of venues.
They pull the equipment.
They won't ever do it.
We'll be so good they'll have to support us.
How are you gonna get 'em
to support a jazz band?
Never call it " jazz."
Don't ever even use the word.
They'll know. They'll hear it.
These guys, they're not musicians,
they're bureaucrats.
You're Cuban, I'm Cuban. Chucho's Cuban.
Whatever we play
is gonna be Cuban music.
We'll need some kind of camouflage,
you know?
Congas.
Big ones.
-Up front.
-Up front!
We called ourselves "Irakere."
It's an African word meaning, " jungle."
We played jazz...
...but we gave it our own swing.
Wait a minute, excuse me.
They didn't stop you.
And this band was a success.
Yes.
The camouflage we had worked.
You toured extensively.
You did a record for CBS.
You even won a Grammy.
It seems like the government
didn't care what you were playing.
They chose not to notice because we
were making a lot of money for them.
I imagine you were making some money
for yourself as well?
It doesn't work that way.
The clubs pay
the Ministry of Culture directly.
All we got was meal money.
You know you can make a lot more
money if you weren't in Cuba.
It's not about the money.
It's about the music.
They let you play the kind of music
that you wanted.
American jazz and Gershwin and Ellington--
You're always taking a risk because in
Cuba you never know where the line is.
You can play Gershwin once too often.
Not being able to play Gershwin
does not constitute persecution.
It is if they decide it's
counter-revolutionary and you're put in jail.
In Cuba you live with that fear every day.
Someone might come to you,
your house, your family...
...and hurt you because of a song.
Just a song.
And that is persecution.
If you felt that strongly about it...
...why didn't you defect earlier?
I was about to. I had it all planned out.
But you stayed.
Let's go!
Life has it's own plan.
C'mon!
C'mon, let's go!
I'm here, let's go. The bus is coming!
C'mon, what are you waiting for?
If you don't get this one,
there won't be another bus for hours!
-I'm with him.
-C'mon!
I've been here all along, right here.
She's with me.
She's the love of my life.
By the way, what's your name?
"Marianela Marianela
"Marianela
"When she walks
"All the buses have to stop
"And when she laughs
"She has to cry"
What's wrong?
My mother just died...
...a week ago.
I'm sorry.
Did your mother have
something against laughing?
-Where are you going?
-This is my stop.
Really? Mine, too.
What a coincidence.
I wanna see you before I go.
What's the point if you are leaving?
Why does there have to be a point?
When does your tour finish?
In a month.
Let's have dinner.
Ask me when you get back.
That's too long,
I need to see you before I go.
What's the hurry?
I'm afraid you might forget me.
That's very unlikely.
CUBAN MINISTRY OF COMMERCE
Excuse me, do you work here
at the foreign trade ministry?
Sí.
Don't tell me that you work here as well.
No.
I don't think so.
Is there a problem?
No problem.
"Marianela Marianela
"Marianela"
I'm gonna see you before I go!
That's a warning!
These are the East German purchases.
She sold everything?
And she actually left.
To Miami?
Both kids, the mother, the father,
the grandmother, on a raft.
This is Cuca we're talking about.
What happened to Cuca?
They left a couple of weeks ago
from Cojimar at about 3:00 in the morning!
-The whole family?
-Yes.
The whole family, even the dog.
-The dog?
-Good thing she escaped.
She didn't escape. She gave up.
She gave up because
things got a little tough.
She wanted to go shopping in Miami.
Please, she bought everything
she could in Havana.
-Hello?
-May I speak to Marianela, please?
Marianela, for you.
Oigo?
-Marianela?
-Sí.
-Arturo.
-Who?
Arturo Sandoval.
You don't remember me?
Of course I remember you.
It's been less than an hour.
Listen, you like baseball?
Do I like baseball?
What are you doing out here?
This is where I practice.
I like to come here 'cause the music....
My playing comes back to me like a wave.
What were you playing?
Something I just wrote.
What is it called?
Marianela.
Really.
Put your hand on my heart.
Right here.
Nice.
What's her name?
Marianela.
-Where does she live?
-None of your business.
She was the waitress
we were chasing around--
You were chasing.
Marianela works for the government.
The government?
You think I'm crazy?
I think you're in love and
that's a dangerous place to be.
What are you talking about?
You know I wanna leave.
I can't take my family.
You're free. You get on that plane,
you never come back.
You get hooked, you're stuck.
Don't complicate your life, hermano, okay?
There she is.
What do you think?
It's worse than I thought.
Be careful. You know how it works.
They get a spy to dress up
like the woman of your dreams.
It must be quite a temptation for you.
What?
Traveling to all those countries.
Nice cars, nice clothes.
Do you ever want to get off
the plane and not come back?
You know, Arturo...
...you'd miss Cuba.
You'd miss the way
everything smells like sugar.
You'd miss the baseball.
You'd miss our music.
I'm still sitting here.
I don't understand why people leave Cuba.
Especially you, who's gotten
so many things from the revolution.
Marianela.
My talent comes from God, not Fidel.
Do I have "defector"
written on my forehead?
What are we talking about here?
Do you get this nervous on stage?
Only at auditions.
How am I doing?
I'm still sitting here.
Wait!
This is Marianela!
When she walks,
all the buses have to stop!
That was the last bus.
That was the only bus.
Okay.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I could stay at my friend's apartment.
I should call home.
It was a lovely day.
Yes.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Goodnight.
I'll walk you there. Come on.
No, it's okay--
It's okay? Okay then, let's go.
Come on.
I'll protect you.
I also was married.
It was a mistake.
The husband, not the son.
-You have a son?
-Yes, he's eight.
-Eight?
-I was very young.
Very young.
She lives here?
It's not much further.
Emilia?
Emi?
She must be staying
at the colonel's house.
-The colonel?
-Yes.
She has a colonel?
Yes.
Thank you for the walk.
Goodnight.
Mari.
Are you really leaving tomorrow?
That's what I told you, yes.
Will you promise me you won't come back?
I don't understand. What are you saying?
Promise me you won't come back
and I'll be with you tonight.
Why?
Because...
...I'm afraid I might fall in love with you.
It would never work.
-We are too different.
-Different is good.
Promise me this will be our only night.
I don't understand.
If I promise you, you'll be with me tonight?
-I promise.
-I'm serious.
Promise me.
I promise.
I'll be there in a minute!
Smells good!
Come on, Willis.
Hey there, this is Willis Canover
bringing you jazz on the Voice of America.
Yes, go on, Willis.
What are you listening to?
Dizzy's Atmosphere, Dizzy Gillespie.
Charlie Parker live at Carnegie Hall, 1947.
Side B, track two.
You know what I mean.
It's just music.
Great music.
You're not supposed to
listen to that station.
Now we're safe.
It's not funny.
You could get in trouble.
Believe me, I know.
I spent four months
in military jail for listening to that.
I think I earned the right.
Time to go.
You have your tour and I have my work.
What are you doing?
Memorizing your face.
Oyeme!
Are we going?
What?
Tell me one thing. Can the colonel dance?
Please.
Do you love him?
Ay, chica.
C'mon, let's go.
I'm here.
See you tomorrow.
You promised you wouldn't come back.
The last promise I'll ever break to you.
-She wasn't an informer?
-Of course not.
-But she did work for the government?
-Yes.
She's still a member of the Party?
Yes.
She's an active member?
Not anymore.
She sees things
completely differently now.
That's convenient,
now that you're seeking asylum.
"Convenient."
It seems that her politics didn't bother you.
I never said that.
We had many disagreements
about politics.
You had disagreements?
You claim to be on opposite ends
of the political spectrum.
How can two people that far apart
stay together?
Papi and Leonel, this is Arturo.
Mucho gusto, Señor Sosa.
Leonel.
Say hello to Arturo.
I'm sorry, I'll be back.
What's so great about him?
He's funny.
He makes me feel good.
You are the musician.
Trumpet player.
Mr. Trumpet Player.
May I know what are your intentions
with my daughter?
I want to marry her.
I want to have a son with her
and live with her for the rest of my life.
She never mentioned that to me.
I haven't asked her yet.
Señor Sosa, with all due respect...
...I know when you look at me,
what you're thinking.
I'm a musician, she's your daughter--
I suppose you would like
to move into my house.
Yes, for a little bit.
I have something for you.
It's soap from London.
You keep it.
-You know Félix Chapotín?
-Of course.
I was admiring your taste in music.
Now, he was a trumpet player.
You like baseball?
Maybe we can go see my favorite team,
Los Industriales.
You're trying to make me like you.
How am I doing?
Not good?
Let's try a bribe.
Sandwich?
No?
It's turkey.
Turkey sandwich.
When's the last time
you had a turkey sandwich?
Never. Where do you get it?
Right there.
That's not turkey.
-What is it?
-That's vulture.
Vulture?
No, it's not. It's turkey from heaven.
Bad news.
You know him?
Who doesn't know him?
Is he in the Party?
I don't think he's in anything.
He belongs to a different world.
Different way of thinking.
I don't understand you
and neither will anybody else.
You have a good position here,
a wonderful reputation.
Why do you want to risk it?
I'm old enough to know what I'm doing.
Not as old as his first wife.
You know his first wife?
Alba Marina.
Alba Marina, the singer?
Honey, what else don't you know
about the man you're gonna marry?
We hear what they want us to hear.
We play what they want us to play.
You know what we're missing?
Miles Davis.
Charles Mingus, Maynard Ferguson.
While the rest of the world
is painting rainbows, we paint in one color.
Me? I'm getting outta here.
What about your family?
I'll get them out somehow.
Look.
I'm sick and tired
of playing these fucking games!
Be careful.
Everybody in Cuba has an ear
and not only for music.
Where have you been?
-What is it?
-Somebody's following me.
What?
Somebody's following me.
He was not supposed to be following you.
Wait....
You know him?
He's a friend of Emilia's.
He was only supposed to ask around.
He's been looking for things.
-What?
-About you.
About me? Why?
Because I asked him to.
-You asked him?
-Yes.
If you want to know something about me,
why don't you ask me?
Because I don't know if I can trust you.
You don't trust me?
I've told you everything.
That's not true.
You never told me about Alba Marina.
-I told you I was married!
-Not to Alba Marina.
What difference does it make?
Do you have any doubts that I love you?
Listen, Arturo.
I had one husband walk out on me.
He walked out on you and your son.
Yes, and I won't go through that again!
Don't compare me to him!
Go home.
You all right?
You're not gonna have a heart attack,
are you?
You scared the hell out of me.
I'm better now.
Stop following me.
I'm not coming around here no more.
You were such a nice couple.
Thanks.
-You gonna make it home okay?
-Can't go home.
Why?
Because my wife kicked me out.
Did you hear the one about Fidel's zoo?
No.
In 1960, there was a sign there saying:
"Please don't feed the animals."
In 1970, they changed that sign
for another one saying:
"Please don't eat the animals' food."
Yesterday, they changed the sign
for another one saying:
"Please don't eat the animals."
Isn't that funny?
-You're a comedian.
-No.
I am an orthopedist.
Don't laugh, it's true!
Yes, bone surgeon.
That's me.
I'm honored. A specialist.
I'm honored, doctor.
You know the real money's
in the taxi business.
I have a cousin who drives a taxi
and he gets a lot of money.
I endorse. That's very important.
He's a doctor, too?
Don't laugh...
...physicist!
We have the most talented
taxi drivers in the world!
How did you find me?
The doctor brought me.
The shawl is beautiful.
You should have asked me about Alba.
-I came here--
-I'm not finished.
-Arturo--
What do you want to say?
I don't know.
What I feel about you...
...I've never felt it before.
I don't know how to feel it. I don't trust it.
What if I told you that I love you?
Just because I love you.
No reason, I just love you.
I loved you the first time I saw you.
You're here with me now and I love you.
I love you.
You could send 100 guys to follow me.
All they'll ever find out is that I love you.
I love you.
You trust me?
Ay, hijo mío.
You found yourself a good woman
and you're gonna be a great father.
-And a great husband.
-Gracias.
Great father, great husband,
But lousy domino player.
Sounds like a wedding to me!
Ay, chica.
-You look amazing.
-Thank you.
Where is everybody?
Oye, oye! Don't I get to kiss the groom?
-Once.
-Come on!
Havin' a good time!
Thank you.
You better be good to her,
or I'll have to talk to the colonel.
-I promise.
-Okay.
I promise.
You know, Rosalina has a migraine,
poor thing.
What about Yami?
-Militia duty.
-What about the rest?
I'm here. I came, didn't I?
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Is that the colonel?
Ask him in, he's welcome here.
I'm sorry, I really have to go.
You look wonderful.
You look like a virgin.
All right, I'm coming!
What's wrong?
They didn't come.
Who?
My friends.
None of them are here.
If they didn't come,
they're not your friends.
Who's coming?
Dizzy! Dizzy Gillespie!
What kind of name is Dizzy?
His name.
You really expect me
to get this thing running?
-You're the best.
-He's better than the best.
I'm not this good.
Bury it.
That's the wrong size tire.
It's round.
How you doing?
Welcome to Cuba, Mr. Gillespie.
Welcome to the beautiful Havana.
Mr. Gillespie, first thing we're gonna do,
we're gonna tour...
...one of our internationally renowned
health care facilities.
Thank you,
but my health don't need caring.
Can you take me to Chano Pozo's crib?
Chano Pozo's crib?
You don't know who Chano is?
I know who Chano is!
This has nothing to do with you.
No, hold on a second.
Can you take me to his crib?
His crib?
Yes, of course.
Mr. Gillespie, we have a tour. We have
the entire day planned out for you.
That's okay, thank you very much.
My boys'll go on the tour with you.
Go with 'em, enjoy yourselves.
It's a real honor.
-What is this?
-It's my car.
-Keep telling yourself that.
-Yes, sir.
Watch yourself there. Okay, here we go.
Okay, here we go.
It's okay, thank you.
You sure you know who Chano Pozo is?
Mr. Gillespie, Luciano Pozo y González.
Better known as "Chano."
Cuban conga player you met in 1946.
Chano's from Belen,
which is just up the street here.
Dizzy Gillespie and Chano Pozo added a
whole new polyrhythmic structure to jazz.
You read the liner notes.
-I've read everything to be read about--
-I gotta tell you something.
Your car smells funny.
Gasoline.
Gasoline and tar.
I painted it with gasoline and tar.
Gasoline and tar?
You're supposed to put the car on the road,
not the road on the car.
Understand what I'm saying?
Anti Imperialists
REVOLUTION
Is there a statue or something?
Statue? No, there's no statue, Diz.
Then take me to Chano Pozo Street.
Street? No, there's no street.
-What do they got?
-They don't got anything.
How do people remember him?
-Most people don't remember him.
-That's criminal, man.
One of the greatest players
that ever played.
Chano Pozo transcended the vicissitudes
of the contingent world...
...and moved in an odyssey
into the realm of the metaphysical.
I'll betcha Karl Marx got himself a statue.
A statue and a theater, too.
Karl Marx can kiss Chano Pozo's ass.
You hear it? That's the sound, Diz.
Chano Pozo learned how to play
the conga right in this neighborhood.
What's this, a show or something?
It's actually a party.
It's here every afternoon.
We'll stop here.
You can shoot as much as you want.
This is Chano's world.
This is the real thing.
They're doing a traditional yamboo.
Dedicated to the city of Belen,
where Chano's from.
You all kept it alive, man.
When they dragged us over to America,
they took our drums...
...our religion, our language.
We had to learn theirs.
But the true African heart's
still beating here in Cuba.
I mean it is what it was.
There's more. A lot more.
That reminds me, they're putting together
some sort of jam session for me tonight.
You ever heard of this band called Irakere?
Irakere?
I heard of 'em.
You're about to hear
the best musicians in Cuba.
Like, Paquito D'Rivera.
I like the sound of that.
Gracias.
What the hell's my driver
doing playing a trumpet?
Your driver?
Gimme my horn.
The African and the Cuban...
...transmogrified on
the great ethereal plane.
I smuggled this thing in from Frankfurt.
The government here,
they don't support jazz.
As soon as you get on that boat tomorrow,
the so-called "Jazz Festival" is over.
Musica non grata.
That show tonight was just for you.
It's not like that every day.
This your stuff?
I didn't hear any of this tonight.
Just some stuff I'm working on.
That's nice.
Musica non grata.
You know...
...Miles Davis came to me
for a trumpet lesson once.
I said, "Let's go to the piano."
Miles looked at me:
"I don't play no piano."
I told him, "The only way you
can really get inside the music...
"...arranging, composition,
is with the piano.
"You learn it,
then we can better understand each other."
Why don't you come on tour with me?
Me, come with you?
That horn I heard tonight
doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to the whole world.
Boat leaves mañana.
Tomorrow?
I wish, Diz. I wish.
You don't understand.
Dizzy Gillespie saw something in me.
In me.
So now you want to go away with him?
I don't know what you want anymore.
You are already in a band.
You tour, you're famous.
I'm on display. I am in a cage.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm in a sanctioned band,
playing sanctioned songs.
We're going on tour next week
and I don't even feel like going.
The music that I played tonight,
that's what I need to be playing.
Don't you want that?
Of course I do.
You know that I've always supported you.
We're a family.
There are limits.
Limits?
Who am I talking to here?
I don't see why you
have to complicate things.
Look at this.
Ten thousand Cubans have stormed
into the Peruvian embassy...
...in a desperate attempt to flee the island.
The Castro regime is waging a crackdown
on descent after a chaotic 48 hours...
...that began when a Havana
bus driver seeking asylum...
...for himself and his passengers,
crashed through the embassy gates...
...prompting a cross fire
that left one guard dead.
In retaliation for the embassy's refusal
to turn over the gate crashers...
...the Cuban government
removed its guard...
...triggering a stampede
of refuge-seeking Cubans.
I left my sax on the plane.
You forgot your sax?
-Watch this for me, okay?
-Okay.
Hurry up, the plane's gonna leave soon.
Why did we cancel the tour?
We canceled the tour to protect
Irakere's reputation and yours.
This is Osvaldo, our compañero
from state security who attends to us.
I'll call you later.
Sit down.
As I was saying, Irakere is a very important
voice of this revolution.
-So is your voice.
-And so was Paquito's.
And he betrayed us.
And now, with Paquito gone...
...we think you should play
a more prominent role in Irakere.
You know I appreciate that, Jaime, but...
...I got some other plans.
You got some other plans?
I want to start my own band.
I want to do some fusion, I want to expand
the whole concept of Cuban music.
I want to bring it to
a new international level.
-Your own band?
-Yes, my own band.
All right everybody ready at 5:00
for sound check.
It's out of my hands. You can't play here.
I have been to every club in this town.
I cannot get a gig.
Word on the inside is you're
on the outside, that's what they say.
Angel, this is your club, your rules.
You love this music, but what?
I'm your friend.
It would make things a lot easier
if you just joined the Party.
Very simple.
What?
Listen!
You don't have to believe it, just sign.
No.
You wanna play the horn, right?
You gotta play the game!
Partner, you watching?
Go sit down and play with your father.
I can't. I gotta go.
Why can't you stay longer?
Marianela, let's go.
Vámonos.
You never want to play.
-He never wants to play.
-Come on, play.
-Sit down, you got time.
-Maybe you win.
Marianela, let's go!
I'm coming!
Weren't you a friend of Paquito D'Rivera?
-I'm still a friend.
-Really? Even after he defected?
Paquito turned his back on our country.
To me, he's a traitor.
He made a choice.
He turned his back and he had it all.
If he had it all, he wouldn't have left.
-He's just another worm.
-A worm?
Just like the 100,000 that are leaving
from the Port of Mariel by boats?
-I guess they got tired of having it all, too.
-How can you say that?
Are you listening to your son?
I think we should play.
It's my turn.
Marianela, let's go!
Talk to me.
You lose your temper
every time we go there.
You can't even sit down
and play dominoes with your father.
-'Cause I can't watch it anymore.
-He likes to play.
-What's wrong with that?
-He's throwing his life away.
My father used to be a great mechanic,
and they came and took his garage away!
Why do you think I bought that car?
I bought it for him,
to get him away from that goddamn table!
Keep your voice down.
What are you afraid of? The revolution?
Remember, it gives us everything.
They didn't take your father's garage.
He gave it up.
They nationalized it!
They took away what he believed in!
They took away his dream,
his love, his trade!
The thing that he did!
-We all make sacrifices.
-For what?
For what? For the country! For an idea!
-Free hospitals, free education.
-Of course.
And by the way, those 100,000 people
running away at Mariel, they are giving up.
-Giving up?
-Yes!
That is exactly what they are not doing!
By the way, what good is free education
if you can't read and say what you want?
-What good are eyes if everybody's blind?
-I've never heard your father complain!
-Not to you.
-Or you.
-Your father supports this revolution.
-Because that's all he's got left!
If he denounces it now,
what does he have?
If he denounces Fidel,
his entire life would be meaningless!
He would have given up
everything for a fucking lie!
Turi is sleeping!
The whole neighborhood is sleeping!
The whole country is sleeping!
My kids will have to wake up!
My kids will not sleep through this!
-Let's go, wake up, right now!
-They can hear you down the street.
Let 'em report me to the committee
of the defense of the revolution!
The Sandoval family
will not sleep through this!
Are you listening?
Let's go, time to wake up!
Nobody's sleeping in here!
Let's go!
-You gonna sleep all day?
-What do you want?
You can play.
Business has been bad,
and you bring in the customers, so--
How many nights?
We'll see how it goes.
One, two.
One, two, three, four.
Okay? Like that. One, two.
What's the matter,
you forget how to play the trumpet?
No! Johnny!
What happened?
They kick both of you out of London?
-Hello, darling.
-Good to see you.
You couldn't come to our club,
so we came to you.
We had Dizzy back at the club last week.
He couldn't stop talking about...
...his Cuban compadre.
He's an honorary Cuban now.
He has a special respect for you.
And he agrees with me.
You gotta be somewhere
where your talents are truly respected.
Not so loud.
I just want to hear the end of it.
Turi, off to bed. It's late.
Sí.
You should see this on Ochoa.
Come.
This is General Ochoa.
Led the troops in Angola, Fidel proclaimed
him the hero of the revolution.
Now he has him on trial.
-What's his crime?
-He got too popular.
You see, in Cuba there could only be
one hero of the revolution.
Unless, you're dead and then
you can be as popular as you want.
Don't let Arturo brainwash you.
Ochoa is only accused of drug trafficking.
Mari's the only person in the country who
believes he did it without Fidel's blessing.
I don't even think he did it
and I'm not the only one.
We have a judicial process here.
He will be exonerated.
-Exonerated?
-It's a fair trial.
You've been watching this trial for a week
and it's not a fair trial, it's a farce!
He will end up in the firing squad.
-He will never execute Ochoa.
-It's already been fixed.
His lawyer has begged
the judge to execute him.
His defense attorney has turned into
his prosecutor. You call that a fair trial?
I'm so sorry.
I just wanted tonight to be perfect.
Darling.
I've never had a dinner party
without a fight.
Usually, I'm the one who starts them.
I don't know what he wants. He's so...
...unhappy.
Of course he is, he's a musician.
I've been around them for 40 years.
You know, in all that time I've never seen
another one like Arturo.
I'd like to dedicate this show tonight
to my main man...
...my inspiration, Mr. Dizzy Gillespie.
I'd like to play a tune entitled,
Blues for Diz.
Sorry, I'm late.
This is Paloma.
-I'm glad you could come.
-I wouldn't miss it.
Johnny and Sally, our friends from London.
Mari, you have to know something.
People are watching.
There have been reports about him,
about both of you.
What are you talking about?
They're gonna shut him down.
They won't let him play after tonight.
Great show.
You know that if it was up to me,
you could play here every night.
You know that.
You were wonderful.
Wait.
Why do you think the Cuban government
is so afraid of your music?
They're not afraid of my music,
they're afraid of ideas.
Come on,
Fidel Castro is afraid of your ideas?
Fidel Castro is afraid
of any idea that's not his.
-You know how he overthrew Batista?
-It was a popular revolution.
It was a popular idea, it was a great idea.
He promised Cuban people
what they were desperate for:
Restoration of a constitution, democracy,
freedom from a dictatorship.
He did it with 80 people and 50 guns.
And a boat that nearly sank
because of a running toilet.
That can't be all they had.
That's all he needed because the idea
gave him the strength of an army.
The reason I've come here is
to see if maybe I could talk about Arturo.
So he could be allowed to play his music.
It's not entirely an issue of music.
-I'm sorry?
-And it isn't entirely about Arturo.
You were also seen entertaining
foreigners in your home.
Are you questioning my loyalty?
There is a pattern
of counter-revolutionary behavior.
With all due respect,
what revolution are you talking about?
-Is there some confusion?
-Apparently.
My revolution doesn't sound
anything like your revolution.
Mine is not about informing
on your neighbors.
It's about creating a new society.
Genuine equality, remember?
A place where our children can thrive.
I'm sure you will agree that no country
loves its children more than Cuba.
Until they grow up.
Compañera.
I know you love your husband, but
don't say something you may regret later.
The revolution needs
everyone's support to survive.
Excuse me for saying this...
...but if the revolution can't survive...
...two people from England
having dinner at my house...
...or a Cuban man playing
the music he loves...
...why bother trying to save it?
They're showing this all day long.
-What's the verdict?
-What do you think?
He already shot him.
Where did he go?
AT ANY COST
Were you there that day when
Fidel marched into Havana?
I was there.
I was a child.
And I saw him riding in that jeep.
That beard, that smile.
He was like a saint.
And I fell in love.
I fell in love with Fidel,
I fell in love with his dream.
It was going to be paradise.
I didn't know.
I didn't know they would stop you
from playing your music.
My wife got her heart broken.
It's like finding out that your lover
had been cheating on you all this time.
And it was over for her.
Just so I understand...
...what you're saying is you never
sympathized with the Castro regime.
Please, I mean no disrespect,
take a piece of pencil and write this down.
I have never ever,
sympathized with Fidel Castro.
He betrayed the idea,
he broke every promise he ever made.
Please, just write that down.
This is from The London Tlmes
earlier this year.
You're quoted as making favorable
statements about the Castro regime.
This is from a German newspaper,
Frankfurt, I think.
"The revolution gave me
everything I needed."
Is that an accurate quote?
I said it in Frankfurt,
in Stockholm and in Havana.
I had to say what I had to say.
I had to play the game.
You have to understand how that looks.
You come in here with an American icon--
Everyone in Havana,
every single person in Havana...
...has to have a double-face
in order to survive!
You must understand,
you have to play the game.
I plead with you.
My wife and my son are waiting for me.
My son is in London waiting for me!
This was intercepted by the U.S. Interest
Section in Havana six months ago.
It confirms your membership
in the Communist Party...
...and your acceptance of all its principles.
Are you a member?
Are you a member
of the Communist Party?
Thank you.
If you enjoy my music and the way I play...
...it's because the revolution
has given me the opportunity.
Thank you and goodnight.
It's not gonna work out.
Yes, we're so close, don't say that.
-He won't go for it.
-He will.
Just do what you have been doing.
Give the government credit for everything.
Even the air that I breathe.
A personal gift from Fidel.
I thought you only got nervous
for auditions.
What do you think this is?
Mi socio,
all the bookings have been arranged.
Have a good trip.
Be careful with the women over there.
I need a favor.
A favor?
I was hoping that my family
can join me on this tour.
I've been on tour three times this year.
It's too much time away.
Let me be honest with you.
It's the United Nation band.
Paquito, Ignacio, two defectors.
We're concerned that you're going to be
playing with two counter-revolutionaries.
It's not gonna be a problem.
-Are you sure?
-No problem.
Are you willing to denounce Paquito?
No.
If a foreign reporter asks you how you feel
about Paquito, what would you say?
I would say we share the same stage
but not the same views.
Good.
Had you denounced him, I would've known
there was something wrong.
Come over here.
I'll see what I can do.
I'm going to try my best.
Okay, my friend?
We can't tell anybody about our plans,
not even our parents.
It's for their own protection.
When I leave,
it has to be like any other trip.
No crying, no problem.
We just leave, okay?
You can't pack too much
because you'll call attention to yourself.
But I've got to bring so many things.
I have to pack for you, Leonel and Turi.
Thank God Emilia gave me that suitcase.
They didn't authorize Leonel's visa.
He's of military age.
But we got permission.
-You said we got permission.
-We did, but not Leonel.
I just found out.
He's my son,
they have to let him go with us.
He is forbidden to travel, no exceptions.
-We can't leave him behind.
-We'll find a way to bring him.
How?
Paquito was going to bring his family
and they're still here.
We said we'd go as a family.
I swear to you, I tried,
but there's no exceptions.
He's on call for seven years.
Seven years.
We will wait, that's not so long.
Turi's gonna be military age,
that's another seven years.
If we don't go now,
none of us will ever get out.
You want me to leave my son?
He's my son too, you know.
Then how could you think
about leaving him?
You go.
Listen to me.
You know I'm not gonna go
without you, anywhere.
-I won't leave my boy.
-He's not a boy anymore.
He's my son.
Listen to me.
No matter how long it takes...
...even if I have to take a boat back...
...I will get Leonel
and bring him back to us, I promise you.
He will be with us. We have to be strong.
Look at me! We have to be strong.
We have to make the first move or else
we're never gonna get our family out.
Come on, trust me. Come here.
-Let me help you with that.
-I got it.
-Come on, it's my job now.
-Nice taxi, doctor.
-Thank you.
I have realized my full potential.
-I wanna go with you, Papi.
-I know, Turi.
I'm gonna see you in London
in two weeks, okay?
You take care of Mommy.
Take care of yourself.
Be careful.
Thank you.
For what?
For teaching me how to play dominoes.
You still got a lot more to learn.
Take good care of the car. Don't bury it.
I'll see you soon.
I'm scared.
Trust me.
Take care of Mommy, okay?
And bring her to London.
We'll be there in two weeks.
I don't want to make a scene
in front of my mother...
...but I don't want to pretend
like I respect you.
You don't have all the information.
I used to think that you were something.
The way you never backed down.
You're just like the rest of 'em.
I'm so sorry you feel that way.
Sorry?
Don't feel sorry for me, be sorry for Turi.
Because all you ever do
is teach him how to sell out.
You're still not packed?
I don't know, Papi.
I don't know what I will need.
I saw your Mommy last night.
No, in a dream. Papá no está loco.
-How is she?
-She's worried, mi niña.
She said to me, "Sosa,
our daughter is leaving...
"...and you must do everything
in your power to help her."
Mi niña, mi amor.
Quite a dream.
I tried....
-I tried to tell you--
-Don't.
In my old age...
...nothing will give me greater peace
than to know that you are safe.
And happy.
Mi cielo, wherever you are...
...we'll always be together.
Come here.
You know I love you.
I love you, too.
Don't worry, I'll take care of him.
It's only gonna be a month, okay?
Take care of yourself.
You make a very compelling case.
But I have to be honest with you.
I don't think this is going to be easy.
-Maybe I could try to explain better.
-You did explain to me.
But this application is going
to be reviewed in D.C.
On paper it appears that
you benefited from the system...
...and that your motives are financial.
That's just not true.
The burden of proof is on you,
you see and on paper--
-Change the paper.
-Excuse me?
You tell'em. Please.
I will make my recommendations.
I will start the process, but--
How long is the process?
It's hard to tell.
It could be a week, a month.
There's no way of knowing.
What am I supposed to do?
Do you realize how hard it was
to get my family out of Cuba?
Do you know how long we've planned this?
We are completely exposed.
You must find a way of protecting us.
The law states you must be in immediate
and observable danger--
They shot two defectors
in London two months--
I can't offer official protection.
You must understand.
My wife and son are by themselves.
Listen to me.
No one will know you were here.
You just continue the tour
as if nothing happened.
-I can't go back.
-It's not up to me.
There's nothing else I can do.
I'll tell Mr. Gillespie that you're waiting.
-What am I supposed to do?
-Just do what the man says.
Go on the tour and be cool, baby,
we'll work it out.
We gotta go, come on.
Hold on!
Damnit!
They hung up.
Listen, I've been through this, okay?
Ten feet, but you're not gonna
get there if you don't move.
We intercepted this
from the U.S. Interest Section.
Arturo Sandoval.
What's this?
Johnny, line two, It's Havana.
Hello?
What?
Something's up.
They know Marianela's in London.
-They're asking questions.
-Slow down.
Listen to me, they're gonna find out
and take her back to Cuba.
That ain't gonna happen.
I gotta go now, man,
I gotta defect right now.
Take it easy.
One in there from the White House.
-You gonna call the President?
-Vice President, met him on Air Force One.
The cat said if I need anything,
give him a call.
Play the gig tonight,
and then you'll be on the plane.
Wait for me!
If you get through to the embassy,
tell them it won't take us too long.
-You're Mrs. Sandoval?
-Yes.
Come with me, quickly.
These are your documents, all in order.
When you get to New York
just stay on the plane.
This man from the State Department
will meet you on the plane.
Do not get off the plane with anybody else.
What about my husband?
I'm sorry, we haven't heard anything yet.
You really don't know
what this is all about.
They defected?
It's up to you to bring
them home where they belong.
There's nothing that I can say
that could ever bring them back.
Mr. Sandoval,
please, come with us.
Pappy!