In the public eye
and in the underworld,
John Gotti has taken on
mythic proportion.
Gotti is kind of
a working class hero.
Gotti, the reputed head
of the nation's largest
mafia family, the Gambinos,
has beaten prosecutors
in the last three cases.
For the government,
this is a must-win case.
They've said it before,
but this time the feds say
they've really got the goods
to lock the
reputed godfather away for life.
I think we can end the
mafia as an institution
in the next three or
four years, five years,
by keeping this kind
of pressure on them.
Every day on my
wabc radio program,
I will continue to hammer away
at the revisionism
that is the Gotti legacy.
In New York, the Gotti trial is
the hottest show off Broadway.
Every day at the courthouse,
the dapper don
plays to a sellout crowd.
It's not just average guys
caught up in
the Gotti spectacle.
A who's who from Hollywood came
to Brooklyn to take in the show.
The decision by Sammy
Gravano to testify
is certainly a big, big event.
Gotti's brother Peter
indicated the affections
between the two men have faded.
You ready to see
Sam Gravano today?
You ready yet, sir?
Your honor, the state would like
to postpone until tomorrow.
The state's witness,
Sam Gravano,
was unable to appear
due to illness.
Postponed until
tomorrow morning.
Let's not make this a habit.
Also, Mr. Gotti,
if you have any idea
who is behind putting
these in car windshields,
kindly ask them to stop.
Court is dismissed.
If I want anything done,
I do it myself.
Yeah, you always was
a fair guy, Eddie.
Eddie!
Crazy! Eddie.
This is one rap you won't beat.
Crazy!
You like to laugh, do you?
Well, here, see if
you think this is funny.
Eddie!
Now, who is this guy?
And how are you
hooked up with him?
I never figured it out.
What was his business?
Hey, John, how are you?
He used to be a big shot.
I'm ready.
Let's go, man.
Yeah, I see you.
Mierta. You had me waiting
for like 20 minutes, man.
John gotti's a hero in queens.
Forget queens, all over new
York, all over the country.
The city denied the club
a fireworks permit
for the first time this year,
but that hasn't seemed to stop
the celebrations one bit.
Neighbors say that
mayor Dinkins is doing this
as an attack on ozone park's
favorite citizen, John Gotti.
This is Pablo guzman in queens.
News channel 10, back to you.
Pablo.
Don't write
the history books yet.
All right, everybody,
this one's for John!
John!
Could you light this
for me, please?
Give me that.
You're so rude.
Boom.
Who's he? The ice cream man?
Shut up, Ann.
Yeah, you in
the communion suit.
You been here all day,
and nobody knows you.
What... what are you
looking for, huh?
Huh?
Where are you from?
I'm from the Bronx.
The Bronx? Then what
are you doing here?
I'm celebrating.
You're celebrating? What?
You're celebrating? Yeah.
No, no, no, this is
a private block party.
I was invited by junior.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Are you
saying you're with junior?
Am I stuttering?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Are you with junior?
He's with me, Jerry.
He's with me. What do you mean?
Here. You got
a problem with my friend,
you go in the hunt club.
You tell him he's with me.
Move it.
Yeah, I'll move it,
I'll move it.
So, what, you're just gonna
stare at me all night?
Hmm?
You wanna split this?
You're skinny,
you gotta eat that.
What's your name?
Thomas.
What's yours?
Easy, easy, speed racer.
Not so fast.
Ohh.
You're gonna make me come.
I'm gonna come.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
Oh, you feel good.
Come on. Ohh!
Don't... don't come out.
Stay. Ohh.
Ohh...
Yeah, stay like that.
Stay inside.
Kiss me.
You're beautiful.
You're fuckin' beautiful.
It's safe. Quiet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on, hold on.
Shh.
You feel that?
What?
It's like it vibrates in here.
You Italian?
Half. My mother's side. Here.
My father's Irish.
That's a deadly combination.
Thomas Lucaze.
We called him
three-finger brown.
Could have been
a pro ball player.
A bunch of wiseguys buried him.
Al Capone here, too? No.
Mount Carmel cemetery,
Illinois,
'cause of his years in Chicago.
Do you know he's from Brooklyn?
He got married there, too,
to an Irish woman,
Mae Coughlin.
It's funny,
it's like your family,
but the other way around.
How do you know
all this crazy stuff?
Nice.
Why, you wanna know?
No.
It won't come true.
You wanna come home with me?
Yeah.
Stay the night?
Well, there goes your theory.
Yeah? Yeah.
You don't know what
you're in for.
Yeah, I can handle it. Yeah.
Yeah? Yeah.
Come here.
Got me excited now.
Hey.
Oh, shit. Hey.
You scared the shit
out of me. Oh...
I got an appointment
at... oh, okay.
You seen my shoe? Do you
remember where I parked?
No, I didn't want you to go.
I thought that, uh...
That I'd bring us
back in some breakfast.
You got coffee?
Yeah.
No...
That was a lie.
I don't have coffee.
But I can go around
the corner and get it.
What is this?
Like I told you last
night, I'm working on
some things that
might help out John sr.
Who's "the twin"?
I can't say right now.
But I got some things
in the works.
"It's my family, Kay.
It's not me."
My name is rose.
"The godfather."
Oh.
Michael...
Your eyes look like
sunflowers in the light.
You know what would be nice?
Why don't you come with me?
What? Come with me.
Where? I gotta go to work.
Call in sick. I can't.
Come on, come with me. I'm telling
you, you're gonna love this.
Can I kiss you?
You better come.
What are we doing?
Is he the twin from the photo?
Come on, you'll see.
Watch this, ready?
It's gonna be like
a Swiss watch.
One, two, three.
There's nothing to it.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Oh, excuse us.
Hey. Sorry.
Good morning.
What was that?
Huh? Come on. Who is he?
Is he the guy from the photo?
Come on, you'll see
in a moment.
Come on.
What? Wait.
Thomas. Oh, hi, Christine.
How you doing?
How are you? Good.
Be right up there.
You're gonna love this.
You gonna leave me
at the steps?
Come on, it's history
in the making.
Come on. Come on.
Thank you, Christine.
She's a great artist.
I got one of her pieces.
This fuckin' place
gives me the creeps.
What are you up to?
You'll get used to it. Come on.
Oh, I hope not.
I didn't have good luck last
time I was in a courthouse.
And to quote prosecutor Malone,
"after reviewing
"the tape recordings
from the Ravenite social club,
"it is clear that Mr. cutler
and his associates
are house counsel
to the Gambino crime family."
You see the twin?
Now look at the guy
on the jury.
Second guy in.
You see?
Hmm?
They're brothers.
Look.
They make eyes at each other.
Mm, I'm not sure. Mm.
What? Rose...
It's right under
their fuckin' nose.
Look at him, come on.
I don't see it.
I quote John Gotti
from the tapes.
"Where does it end?
The Gambino crime family?
"This is the cutler, Shargel,
and who-do-you-call-it
crime family."
I'm disqualifying
Mr. cutler and Mr. Shargel
from defending Mr. Gotti...
this is an
obstruction of justice.
Those tapes are
attorney-client privilege.
May I remind you that's an
American flag, not a swastika!
Yes!
One more reaction like that,
and you will be
removed from this courtroom!
You're basically taking away.
Mr. gotti's god-given
right to exist.
I would suggest that you
save the histrionics
for the TV reporters
outside of this courtroom!
Dismissed!
Maybe.
Look.
So you get Gotti off.
What then?
We make history. We're in.
"We"? Me and you?
Yeah, me and you.
What do you think?
You're crazy.
You can dance!
All the black girls
in high school loved me.
It's my butt.
I got a big old butt,
and I know how to move.
Sure do. You know
what you nearly did?
You wore me out.
Listen, uh, I gotta
get going, all right?
No, come on, cous,
let's kill this.
All right. We gotta do a toast.
You know what?
If Gotti got off, that would
be one hell of an ending.
Right?
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
Is that a little inside info?
Maybe.
Do you guys still talk?
Oh, you know,
we're not supposed to,
but, uh, I get bits and pieces.
Know what? Why don't you
talk to him?
Maybe he can help us.
Maybe.
How much?
50k.
50k, we get "not guilty"?
I'll talk to my brother.
We'll talk to our people.
You know, John Gotti,
he's being persecuted
by the United States
government.
The same government
that stole the land
from the Indians and
enslaved your people.
I'm Jamaican.
Well, you're soon
to be a rich Jamaican.
It was nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Take care.
I'm right.
Oh, my god.
Am I right?
My god!
You're an angel! Whoo!
It's closing time.
Hey, Timmy,
wanna give these two
a few dollars for a motel, man?
What'd you say?
Motel? This is my wife.
Okay.
You apologize to Mrs. Greco.
Come on, Thomas...
Nah, no, I want
an apology for Mrs. Greco.
This is my wife. Hey, man,
listen to your woman.
Get the fuck out
of here, asshole.
What?
You heard me.
You call him an asshole?
Hey, yo!
My husband's
waiting for an apology.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Is that okay, honey?
He said sorry.
Go, go, go, go. He said s...
go. Slowly.
Go!
Hey!
You okay?
I'm sorry. That was crazy.
Sometimes I do crazy things.
I don't know why.
Okay, I get it.
Get out!
Get the fuck out! What?
What? No. Yes!
Get the fuck out!
No, that was incredible.
That was amazing.
Rose...
Rose, stop.
Look at me. No.
Look at me, that was amazing.
I'm sorry I was quiet.
I'm sorry, I wasn't even...
I wasn't even thinking.
I should have done something.
I think I was just
really embarrassed.
Oh, come close. Shh, shh.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Oh.
Shh, shh.
You coming back?
Course I'm coming back.
32, 33, 34, 35, and 40.
Thank you, Donna.
That's for you.
Donna, please tell
Jimmy we miss him a lot
and, uh, you...
If I ever make it to Phoenix,
although I doubt I ever will,
I will get in touch.
Thank you.
Hi. Hey.
The shop looks good.
Same old shit.
You believe this weather?
It's hot, it's cold, it's hot.
Cold again.
Joey bagels?
How'd you guess?
Holy shit.
Yeah. So young.
What happened,
someone punch his ticket?
Yeah, god.
Clogged arteries.
Well, look, ally, I appreciate
you helping with this.
It's just 'til this business
deal goes through, all right?
Um... After you called,
I spoke to Ann
about this, okay?
Ally, they just need
to see I got a job,
and then I'll get
out of your hair.
I can't put you
on the books, okay?
Uh, she doesn't think
it's a good idea
to lie to your parole officer.
Hi. Hi.
And I don't either.
All right.
What if they come in here,
they start asking questions,
they start... nobody's...
nobody's gonna
ask any questions.
Well, how do you know
what they're gonna do?
So you're not gonna
help me with this?
No.
Can I help you, ma'am?
I didn't mean to interrupt.
This is rose.
She's from queens.
It's my girlfriend.
Oh... okay.
This is my brother Alfonse.
Hello.
I just wanted
to see the inside.
It's so cute.
Well... Uh...
we should go.
You know, Thomas
told me a lot about you.
You should come out
and visit our place
with the family
when we're settled in.
I didn't know
you guys were, um...
Yeah, no. We're in
ozone park now, and...
Uh, we were keeping it quiet
for a little bit, but, yeah,
we got a big backyard,
the grass, everything.
You... Ann and the boys
have to come out.
Be nice... get
everybody together.
Sounds good.
Well, it was nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you.
Hey, come here.
You know what? Do me a favor.
I wanna show her
out back, all right?
You got the keys?
Okay.
You gotta... you gotta see this.
Thank you. After you.
In the '60s and '70s,
this was the busiest
florist in the Bronx.
Probably the whole city.
Wow.
The Ivy.
I'll get you a job.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You're listening to am 77.
This is
"the Curtis Sliwa show."
We're taking calls
on the Gotti trial,
which, to me, is a big joke.
Man should have been put
behind bars a long time ago.
Good morning.
Do you hear this?
Sammy "the bull" Gravano...
This guy, gotti's
gonna whack this guy.
There's not even
a question in my mind,
he's gonna get whacked.
Ooh, you're testy.
Why are you listening, hmm?
I don't know.
How's it going? John Gotti...
Is going to spend the...
it's going.
It's going.
All these people owe money?
Yeah. That's a lot
of broken thumbs.
These people will be better off
getting their thumbs broken.
Rose! The tile fell.
The water's coming down. What?
What time did the plumber
say he was gonna be here?
He was supposed to be here.
I am gonna break some balls.
He said he tried to call,
and nobody answered the phone.
What?
How's everything working out?
You finding everything okay?
Smooth. Good?
Yeah, all right.
Rose, don't tell me
I'm gonna lose you
upstairs now, huh?
Hey, Arthur, I love my job.
Okay, duchess.
I'm taking care of you.
Good day. Okay, duchess.
Duchess of, uh...
That's, uh, that's
Rosie, queen of corona.
Duchess of queen of corona.
That's good.
We got Julio
down by the schoolyard.
I'm happy that I was able
to help you with your parole.
Rose is a good friend.
I know.
I appreciate it.
Well, that's good.
See, that's important
because, you know,
when you reintegrate back
into the real world,
it's important to have
appreciation for what you got.
Right?
Yeah.
Did you get a smock?
A what?
Smock. Where's your smock?
Oh, the...
Yeah, where's your smock?
Here. The apron.
It's up here. Good.
Okay, but you gotta wear it.
Oh, wear it now?
Yeah, you gotta
wear it all the time.
You take it off when
you go to lunch.
I thought I was just
doing files, it wasn't...
nah, but when you're
in the warehouse,
you wear the smock.
Okay?
Everybody wears a smock.
Ah, tie it up, tie it up.
You can't walk
around like that.
You gotta tie it up.
Let it do its job for you.
You don't wanna get your...
your shirt messed up.
If you need anything, Julio.
Julio. He knows everything.
In the schoolyard.
Yeah.
I'll see you later.
Thank you, Arthur.
Keep up the good work. Yeah.
"The Curtis Sliwa show."
We're taking calls
on the Gotti trial,
which, to me, is a big joke.
Man should have been put
behind bars a long time ago.
Today's the day, boys.
Sammy "the bull" Gravano,
John gotti's most trusted
soldier, will sing like a bird.
John gotti's on trial for the
last time, you mark my words.
John Gotti is going to spend
the rest of his miserable
freaking life behind bars.
I hear newsmen like yourself
calling Sammy the bull a rat.
What kind of message
is that supposed to send
to the kid in the street
who's trying to stay clean
and trying to do
the right thing?
And the media,
they want to portray him
as this Robin hood figure.
Let's call a spade a spade.
The man is a murderer.
Thomas!
It's on.
Great. That's great.
Talked to my brother. Yeah?
Yeah. All right, all right,
well, tonight I got a meeting
with my guys on the money.
Okay.
You just make sure...
shh.
Just make... shh.
Make sure you're giving
him... wait, what?
Come on.
Wait.
Just make sure you
give me mine, all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, hold on.
Half now, the other half
when John walks.
Half now? Yeah.
No, no, no, not right now.
I'm talking about
after the meeting.
Okay. Hey.
Get the fuck out of here.
What's the problem?
Take a walk.
You know my father... he don't
want you 100 feet near here.
Come on, I wanna get a cup of coffee.
No, you're out!
That's it. I'm telling you!
We got it.
Make him get the fuck
outta here!
Come on, let me
get a cup of coffee.
He's a fuckin' whack job!
Take him for a walk, please!
Hey, I got it.
Don't worry, go back.
Motherfucker.
What's the problem? Come
on, let's go for a walk.
All right, all right, I get
it, I get it... no worries.
Get outta here!
All right, I got it.
Don't worry about it.
It's all good.
What are you doing?
I'm not the one who...
you know you're not supposed
to be around the clubs.
You know that.
Come on, I'm back now,
Mickey, all right?
I didn't name names.
I did the right thing.
What names?
No one told you to
go rob the blockbuster.
You were on your own.
Come on, I was
just trying to be
a good soldier for
big sal and ern.
Hey, Thomas...
You're not with us, okay?
You freak out big sal.
You need to cool it down,
or you're gonna get hurt.
All right, do me
a favor, all right?
You talk to big sal,
you tell him I understand
there's a little bit of
heat on me right now,
and it doesn't look good.
Okay? But I'm right
and I'm loyal.
Ah, you gotta stop
talking like that.
You're a fuckin' florist.
Now go help Alfonse
and cut this shit out.
Come on, Mickey,
I got something big.
Mickey, I got a fuckin' jury.
I don't wanna fuck... i
don't wanna hear about it.
What do you mean,
you don't wanna hear?
I got a fuckin' juror
on the Gotti trial.
I got his twin brother.
I need to talk to John.
You are crazy.
No, 'cause John ain't gonna
sit down with you on this.
He's not gonna sit down?
Well, then he doesn't
get the juror.
You fucking with me?
I swear to god,
may he strike me dead.
On my life. I'm dead serious.
Look, they ain't selling you
no junk, you understand?
You think this is about junk?
I'm fuckin' clean.
Why don't you fuckin' tell me?
Mickey, I'm clean,
I'm telling you.
All right, I'll see
what I can do.
Yeah? Yeah.
All right, then I
get to meet John?
Yeah. Let me
figure everything out.
I'll call you.
Go home. Good-bye.
Cacciatore is nice, mom.
I made it because you like it.
Anthony, you want some more?
No, mom, I'm full.
I can't eat anymore.
Mr. Avello making you a
good deal on the apartment?
Yeah. Mm, it's okay.
I mean, it's a little moldy.
We're fixing it up
as we go along.
That takes time. Ma, you
should come see it.
Come meet Thomas.
You'll like him.
It'll be nice. What?
Uh, yeah. Uh, maybe.
Ma, what are you
looking at him for?
It's my house.
She doesn't wanna meet him.
She knows all she needs
to know about him.
How? Huh? How do you think?
Did you run my name
at that little computer
of yours at work lately?
It's not a pretty picture,
either!
What are you doing?
Rose, rose, sit down.
Rose, please, sit...
you didn't finish your...
he's a kid, rose. He's a kid.
Oh, get a life, Anthony!
Rose, don't start, please.
Ma... I love you.
Do you wanna meet my boyfriend?
Sit and finish.
See my place?
I'll come pick you up.
Mind your own business,
Anthony!
You are my business!
Rose, sit down.
Daddy is rolling over in his
grave 'cause of what you did.
What I did?! What I did?
Hey... Hey...
what?
You using again?
Ma, he's got his hand on me!
I got a job, I got a
boyfriend, I got an apartment.
You're using again.
Do I look like I'm using again?
I know it! I know you.
Get your hand out of my face!
And I know him!
I don't want any trouble.
Well...
You can have my coffee.
You lost your way?
I think I may have something
that interests you.
We've always known that, rose.
It's not like that.
I have a boyfriend now. Ah.
Congratulations.
It's about your friend.
Let's go outside.
Let's go talk.
Not in here.
Come on, huh?
Mmm!
So how do you know
this Richie guy?
Hey, hey, hey, you know what?
You know what?
I don't even care.
You're the real deal.
There he is.
My favorite twin.
Cous. Come here.
Hey, do me a favor, huh?
We gotta talk a little
business over here.
Maybe...
Hey. Hi.
So what's the word?
Yeah, my brother's ready.
What? My brother's ready.
Your brother's ready?
He's ready, so, you know,
when I get mine, it's all set.
We're all set?
You know, but we gotta
wrap it up because, you know...
Gotta move, 'cause the trial
is gonna wrap up and...
no, no, you don't understand.
We don't gotta move
no more, you know why?
We got the clearance
from the tippy top.
We're all good, cous.
That's gonna come in
handy, I tell you.
Hey, well,
that's your business.
Yeah, now let me tell you
something. Tomorrow,
we're gonna call you
in the morning, okay?
All right.
And we're gonna tell you
where we're gonna meet, all right?
Okay.
How do I say it
in Jamaican? Tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
All right, hey,
why don't you stay for a drink?
You want a drink?
No, no, that's all right.
Nah? No.
All right. All right.
Not my kind of place.
Oh! What's that mean?
It's not your kind of place.
I don't know, it was...
This is not my kind
of place, "mahn."
Mmm!
This my kind of place.
You... oh, shit. Don't look.
Don't look behind me.
It's Paulie.
It's Paulie all right, I'm
gonna look over this way.
From the fuckin'
"pope of greenwich village."
Look!
It's fuckin' Eric Roberts.
Holy shit.
He's fuckin'
standin' right there.
Maybe should we
buy him a drink?
Yeah. Come on.
Paulie...
To the end of the bed bug.
Yeah, that's good.
Holy shit.
Disco, Paulie.
Paulie, anything you need,
you talk to me, all right?
Eric. You gotta start
calling me Eric, man.
You know, it was nice to see
Charlie at John's trial.
It was good to see him
show support.
It was solid.
Charlie?
You mean Mickey, Mickey Rourke.
You heard it here.
Uncle John walks.
Mark my words.
Hey, you need anything,
name's Thomas, all right?
Thanks, Thomas, I really
appreciate the cocaine
and the conversation. Um...
Hey, you know, I was glad you
poisoned the bed bug's Espresso.
Um... You should
have never ratted
on your buddy Charlie,
but you know what?
You came through in the end.
Well, uh...
oh, the movie, right?
Uh... I'm glad you liked it.
Thanks, brother.
His nose is like
a fuckin' vacuum.
Really?
It was just, oh, forget it,
he was snorting everything up.
You kidding me?
Ooh, I wanna go to Hawaii.
Are you kidding me?
You know how many
fuckin' big shots
are in here?
They're called
Hawaiian moonlighters.
They're in there,
playing cards,
probably 30,
40 grand on the table.
You wanna moonlight
in Hawaii with me?
Let me take you to Hawaii.
Tomorrow, we're gonna be able
to walk into that place...
We're gonna lay down 30 grand
of our own money on the table.
Like a king and a queen.
You know that?
What's the matter
with you? Hmm?
Promise me something.
What?
Promise you what?
That I'm never
going back to jail.
Rose, I promise you.
You better fuckin'
be for real, Thomas.
Rose...
Come here, give me your hand.
I promise. All right?
Come on.
We got a big day tomorrow.
Come on. Let's go home.
Uh...
I look all right?
Yeah.
He said he'd meet us outside.
Or should I, uh...
Maybe I'll just go inside?
What are you doing? No?
Oh!
Richie, this is Thomas.
This is rose.
Yeah, I know rose.
I don't wanna talk in here.
Come.
I thought... we're not gonna...
nah, it's okay.
Talk down there, you talk to
him by yourself, you know?
Okay.
I thought the twin
was coming with you.
Well, yeah, no, no.
He was supposed to
meet us outside,
and then I figured
I was gonna check inside.
'Cause, you know,
if you're not on the inside,
you're on the outside, right?
When do I get to meet John?
He's not coming, Thomas.
No, no, I know he's not, um...
I know he's not gonna be here
right now, but I'm saying...
not Gotti. I meant your twin.
I don't wanna
see you around here.
You understand?
I, um... no, no,
he's supposed to be here.
I think there's a mix-up, because
he was supposed to meet us outside,
but I think maybe he got scared.
See, he's a black guy.
Mickey, I thi... he's a black guy.
Did I tell you that?
You're being a fucking
wiseass, huh? No.
Hey! You... hey!
You know what it's like to get
slapped in the mouth, rose?
There you go.
What, are you fucking them
out of the cradle now?
You know better.
I ran into your twin.
What'd you think,
I was gonna set this up
without looking out first?
First of all, twin?
Are you kidding me?
He don't even know him.
He played you.
He's just a fuckin' fan
watching the trial.
Smarten up.
You okay?
Hey, man, yeah, they
closed the doors early.
It's totally full.
This is
"the Curtis Sliwa show."
The jury is out
in the John Gotti trial.
My friends, trust me.
They won't be out
for long, mark my wor...
Rose, I'm sorry,
but he's fired.
This is his check for
whatever he supposedly did.
Arthur... There's a mistake.
I'm sure there's
an explanation.
No, rose, you know what?
You are making the mistake.
You are making a big mistake.
What's that supposed to mean?
You could do better.
Like you, Arthur? Is that it, huh?
No, not necessarily.
No, you wanna fuck me,
I know it.
You know what? I wouldn't
fuck you with Julio's dick
and blame it on Marie
in accounting.
So draft out my fuckin'
check while you're at it.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Fuck yourself.
Fuckin' hell hole!
You're listening to am 77.
This is "the Curtis Sliwa
show." Jury's still out.
He was hit with
a double-barreled case
consisting of Gotti, "the
genius", his own taped words,
and the testimony
of Salvatore Gravano.
The ship is sunk and...
Shut this fuckin' guy up.
John Gotti is a pariah.
I hope he spends the rest
of his ugly life...
guilty!
It's been a long road.
Justice has been served,
and it feels awfully good.
The teflon is gone.
The don is covered with velcro
and every charge
in the indictment stuck.
John Gotti,
the modern godfather,
the so-called teflon don,
convicted here of 13 counts,
including five murders.
Oh, dear god.
Oh, my god.
On June 23rd.
John Gotti will be
sent away to federal prison
for the rest
of his natural days.
It is not including...
Michael, the gun.
Nice college boy.
Certainly here in New York...
Don't wanna get mixed up
in the family business.
Are currently awaiting trial...
Now you wanna gun
down a police captain?
Why? 'Cause he slapped you
in the face a little bit?
Huh?
Made them the best-known
gangsters in Chicago's...
He's okay?
He's fine.
Get up.
Look at me.
We're going to Hawaii.
Here, I got some...
You're gonna be great.
It's your time.
Giovanni, you ready?
Who's got the nerve?
Hey!
Hands up!
Put your fuckin' hands up!
Hurry up.
Up!
Good.
Here, here.
Here, money in the bag!
I want all the fuckin' money
in the bag.
Come on, put your
fuckin' hands up.
You special?
Put money in the bag, hurry up.
Pick this up. Pick this all up.
Now we got a system. Come on.
Put the fuckin' money
in the bag.
Put your fuckin'
money in the bag!
Everything. Everything.
Come on, all this.
You think I got
fuckin' all day?
Here!
Put this in the fuckin' bag!
Now give me...
give me his watch.
What does he want?
He wants your watch!
My what?
Forget the fuckin' watch!
I don't care about the watch.
Hurry up, go.
I want everything else.
Go ahead, go, put it in.
Hey, what are you
saying over there?
Huh? What are you saying?
Turn around. Turn around.
Don't make eyes at him.
You, what are you doing?
Give me the fuckin' bag.
Piece of shit.
All right, the bag broke,
what do you want me to do?
Better watch your ass.
Aah!
Stop fuckin' lookin' at me!
Get in the car! Come on!
Get in!
- Get in.
Whew.
Oh, fuck.
Ohh.
Oh.
I pissed myself.
Well...
Ah, it fuckin' happens.
It happens, honey. Pssh.
Fuckin'...
Hey, you're amazing.
Okay? You're fuckin' amazing.
You did it. You fuckin' did it.
You fuckin' did it!
There it is. You ready?
I think this is real.
They look like
solid gold heels.
Oh, look, we got laserdisc.
This machine plays
movies like a record.
Okay, it's like a record
but it's a movie.
Look at that, rose.
And a rope like that
with the Christ.
Christmas came early.
A new TV.
No, no, no, wait.
Hold up, we wanna try this out,
and we wanna
try it out on video.
Ma, uh, no, but this phone,
I can't... it's not
hooked into the wall.
I can just go anywhere.
I could call you...
i could be on the bus,
I could be walking
down the street,
I could...
you could go to church,
you could call me
from inside church.
Ahh, some of it
just dropped... fuck.
You ought to try smokin' it.
You sure?
Yeah.
Fuckin' hold it.
Wanna smoke the fuckin'
shit out of this.
You wanna try it?
You wanna come with me?
It's gonna fuckin' launch you.
It's gonna fuckin'
launch you up there.
You understand?
Ooh, I don't know.
Hold it up. Be careful. Okay.
No, get... i got it.
I got it.
Pull it, pull it.
Pull it right the fuck down.
Pull it.
Smoke the fuckin' shit
out of that.
Holy shit!
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Ohh... oh. Yeah.
So what's...
What's with the getups?
Tell me the story.
December 16, 1985,
sparks steakhouse.
6:00 P.M.
Hmm? There were four
designated shooters.
Vincent Atuso, John Carneglia,
Edward lino, and his
brother-in-law sal Scala.
Pull it. Pull it.
Deep. Take it deep.
Holy shit.
They wore white trench coats
and cossack hats.
Ohh.
Oh...
Gotti knew they'd
pay more attention
to the outfits
than the shooters.
The fuckin' man was brilliant.
Who's he? Paul Castellano,
a. K.A. The Howard Hughes
of the mob.
Never left his mansion.
That's scary.
Never even saw it coming.
Bang.
Take over an empire
of dirty money
and power built on drugs,
flesh-peddling, violence,
and intimidation.
As he stepped from
his black Lincoln,
three men wearing
fur hats and trench coats
pumped six bullets into
"big Paul" Castellano,
the man considered boss of
all mob bosses in the country,
and then calmly walked away.
Excuse me! Hi, dreamboat.
Can you help me out here?
I'm lost.
Oh... back.
Come on, get in!
Get in, get in!
Fuck. Get in.
Get in. Hey!
Turn around. Turn around!
He's fuckin' following us!
Nobody's following us.
Put all the fuckin'
money in the bag!
Come on!
All right, hands up!
Put all the fuckin'
money in the bag.
Come on, this watch.
Get in the car!
We got everything. Ha!
Put your fuckin' hands up.
This is for you.
This is heavy.
Back the fuck up!
Come on, I'm gonna make
an example out of you!
Oh, my god. Who knows that guy?
Who knows that guy?
Get in, get in! He's dead!
Whoooo!
They robbed six fuckin' clubs
in the last month.
They robbed the Hawaiian twice.
It's Colombo. Do you think
it was Colombo or...
I have no idea. Gambinos?
He looked high as a kite.
Yeah, took her watch
instead of her cash.
Duke, I think
I know who's doing this.
Give Johnny Lacola a call.
The cocksuckers took
my fuckin' watch!
Who would hit that place?
It's supposed to be protected.
The kid just robbed us.
No, they didn't touch bergen.
They can try.
Nah, I know rose.
I know where
their mother lives.
She's fucking crazy.
Sure, no problem.
All right, give it to me.
H529u... Something.
Look at that.
I already got... aah!
Let it go.
Mmm, that's good.
November 22, 1992.
With my lovely, lovely rose.
My girl, my lady,
my queen, my queen bee.
Keep your eyes closed.
Are you ready? Do you trust me?
I trust you.
Up your nose. It's glitter.
Oh, my god.
You're short.
You're tall.
Do you wanna stop?
Are you scared?
I don't wanna stop.
You sure?
Hey, wait here.
I got something for you.
I thought we were
going to the diner.
In a minute.
What is it?
What'd you do?
Holy shit.
It's a surprise for you!
"Since John gotti's conviction,
"there have been
reports of deaths
around his old stomping..."
does it say our names?
No.
"No one's really sure who's
behind these recent events,
"but it seems clear
that these occurrences
"would likely not
be taking place
if it wasn't for
his recent conviction."
How the fuck did they get this?
You did this? Yeah.
Now they all know. Yeah.
Holy shit. I can't
fucking believe this.
I'd have 'em put in
fucking stone if I could.
You like it?
Are you kidding me?
I fucking love it.
You... i fucking love this.
Okay. Come here!
Mmm.
Fuckin' love it.
You know what?
You look amazing.
I just... I wanna
save this right here.
Wherever the fuck we are.
Just give me a second.
Will you marry me?
Don't fuck with me.
I'm not fucking with you.
Will you marry me?
Don't you fuck with me!
I'm not fucking with you!
I'm on a knee!
Will you marry me?
Come on, rose.
I do! I do!
I do!
Bellissimo.
Bene.
Capone was smiling or no?
No, he's, uh, serious.
Wow.
I wanna see the look.
Okay, look at the look.
Look at the look.
First of all, my wife is
a lot better-looking
than Mae Coughlin,
that's all I'm gonna say.
You know what it is?
You got no love in your life.
I see the same bullshit
over and over.
You're all fucking miserable.
Each and every one of you.
You know that?
What town is this?
The town of Vizzini.
What is it? Vizzini.
Vizzini. That's what this is?
How come everything
looks the same?
Looks like a shithole.
We just got married!
Okay, now smile...
is there teeth or no teeth?
Little teeth.
Here she goes. Ah-boom!
Oh, you caught it!
You caught it!
You're gonna get married!
You're gonna get married.
See? Married?
To a guy, I think.
Congratulations.
You know what? Drop your pants.
Come on, is it necessary?
We already gave you the money.
It's fuckin' necessary.
Drop your fuckin' pants.
Come on, you got the money.
Just leave us alone.
We're playing cards.
No, I know that
you were playing cards.
I'm not fuckin' stupid.
Drop your fuckin' pants!
Are you fuckin' kidding me?
What, do you got
the Yankees game on that?
You got a fuckin' rat in here?
I'm not a rat.
Nah.
Hey, good luck with that.
This is what I wanna do.
I wanna make a toast!
Whoo!
To my bride!
To my fuckin' bride.
Last call. Drink up,
drink up, now.
Hey, we want two more! Oh, fin!
Hold on, fill this up here.
There you go, fill...
fill this up.
He's okay, give him a couple
of drinks, all right?
Enjoy.
Ohh!
Come on! Look at this!
The best fuckin' wedding gift.
Look who it is,
Paulie... Paulie!
Take it easy.
Hey, look at this,
we got married.
Hey, Paulie, how you doin'?
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I been looking for you.
Sorry, man. What?
What are you sorry about?
I... I don't know who you are.
What, you don't remember me?
You hear this? Wow!
You don't remember me?
You don't remember
your fuckin' friends?
You should get a real
fuckin' slap, you know that?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I have
to ask you to... ohh!
Don't fuckin' touch me, all right?
I said I'm gonna
ask you to leave! This here
is my fuckin' wedding night.
What are you asking me for?
Come on.
This cocksucker?
Take it outside.
You fuckin' rat.
Take what out...
you know what I'm gonna
take outside? This.
Look, what are you... I'm
gonna take this outside.
Now cool down, man, come on.
Yeah? Yeah? Thomas!
What's the matter, Paulie...
what the fuck?!
Asshole!
Fuckin' ruined my wedding.
Know what? Fuck all of youse.
Here, here's the bar.
Here, you know what?
That's what it means. Nothing.
Fuck you, you fuckin' rat.
You're listening to am 77 wabc.
It's "the Curtis Sliwa show."
Tomorrow, the Gotti sentence
will be handed down.
And I am guaranteeing you
right now
that the sentence
will be life in prison.
I have ears on the...
Do you hear this?
They tell me Gotti sr.
Is a scared old man in prison.
That's right. Tomorrow...
Can I tell you something?
What?
The hero worship must
and will end.
I need to kill this bastard.
I mean, he was found guilty...
He's going to prison
for the rest of his life.
I'm gonna make my bones
on Curtis Sliwa.
You're fucking kidding.
You... listen...
In the business
of this enterprise.
You hear that?
He wants to talk this way
about John while the rats
sit around and let him?
Fine. I don't want
to hear it anymore.
You think they fuckin' care?
Nobody cares anymore.
'Cause he's a fuckin' rat.
Fuckin' rat... rat!
Hey!
Let's go. Let's go.
Anthony, what? What?
You're coming home with me.
Where... what...
a few guys came
to mama's house yesterday
asking questions,
and they weren't cops.
Let's go. Let's go!
She's not going anywhere.
I don't wanna fuckin'
hear it from you.
Hey! Hey! You hear me?
Anthony, hey! Relax!
Relax, Anthony.
Mama's in the hospital.
She had a stroke this morning.
When does it end, rose?
When does it end? Let's go!
Let's go, get your clothes.
She's not going
anywhere... rose!
Rose! Let's go.
Where are you going? Let's go.
Rose! It's my mom!
You're my wife. What're you doing?
You shut the fuck up!
Rose, come on,
he sold you out once.
He's gonna sell you out again.
I will fucking kill you.
Hey! You understand me?
Anthony! You gorilla! Get off!
You fuckin' jackass. Get off!
Go!
Free John Gotti!
Thousands of John Gotti
supporters gathered
in downtown Brooklyn
to protest the sentencing
of the mob boss.
What do we want for John?
Free John! What do
we want for John?
John Gotti was sentenced
to life in prison
without parole.
Hey, Thomas,
I didn't see you there.
Why weren't you there?
Every day on my radio show...
Aaaah! I will continue
in my efforts to take down
organized crime.
The fight is not over.
Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Severed, and the body
is still moving.
We all saw those
degenerates on the street
rioting after
the Gotti sentencing.
The hero worship must end.
This is not a movie,
my friends.
There is no violin music
playing in the wake
of the bodies left behind.
Hey, Thomas, did you hear?
John gotti's going to jail...
For life...
Without the possibility
of parole.
No more five families.
The mafia...
As an institution,
is no more.
Yeah.
So why don't you put that
in your pipe and smoke it?
I have personal
friends out there.
I know firsthand
the damage that
this degenerate does is real.
It is all smoke and mirrors.
This man's business is murder.
I get press all the time.
They inspire me.
They give me new life.
I know I'm doing my job.
It's you guys
who are myth-makers.
You gotta sell your newspapers,
you gotta sell your air time.
Let's call a spade a spade.
The man is a murderer.
And then I hear...
I hear they're reporting.
Sammy the bull as a rat.
I hear newsmen like...
I found out where he lives.
Who? Sliwa.
Fuckin' Sliwa.
I know exactly where he lives.
I need my driver.
What are you talking about?
You think I'm shit?
Is that what you think?
No. Why do you say that?
What are you talking about?
Come on, rose, I need you.
I need your help.
He takes a taxi
every morning at 7:15.
Thomas...
You're not coming in
that clear.
You're not coming
through clear.
I think it's the pollution.
You're coming through
in waves, rose,
you're coming through in waves.
Honey... I can't
come back right now.
I can't leave her yet,
not like this.
I'm scared for you in queens.
I wanna come get you.
Get the fuck out.
No.
I hear him back there.
I gotta go.
Aah! Aaaah!
Fuck!
What? Get a life, Anthony!
This is my husband!
Okay? He needs me! He needs me.
Tell me what kind of
trouble you're in!
I'm not in trouble!
I can help you!
I talked to Theresa.
She'll put you up.
You can get work up there.
Just get away from it all,
just get out.
Get away from it.
Una space.
Hey...
Hey, Sally.
Get the fuck out of here!
Motherfucker!
Now! Leave, motherfucker!
Hey!
Huh? That's it!
Hey! Hey! Hey! That's it!
That's it.
Pick him up and put him out!
Get the fuck out of here!
Piece of shit! It's all over.
Make sure he stays
the fuck out of here!
It's over!
Make sure he stays out!
You know now.
Don't be coming around here.
Take a walk, piece of shit.
Fuckin'...
Get the fuck out.
Get him out of here.
Did I tell you?
I told you, Thomas.
Yeah, inside report said.
Gotti was taken
to the infirmary...
With a busted lip
and swelling to his cheekbone.
Little-known African-American
bank robber.
He had his way with
the coward of all cowards.
See, Thomas?
He is just like you.
Hey.
Hey, wake up.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
It's me. Hold on.
Thomas, you okay?
Uh... yeah. Huh?
What happened?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I had an accident.
What kind of accident?
Where's rose?
She's in queens.
He's here? Who's here?
Did you hit your head? No.
He's here? Turn around.
He said so. Sit down.
Come inside. I'm all right.
I'll give you a band-aid.
Take this. I want...
No, no, no, no.
I don't want your money.
That was... i gave that to
you I want to make good.
To get you back on your feet.
There.
It's all right,
I don't need it.
No, I don't want it.
I'm on my feet.
You're barely on your feet, okay?
I don't want it. Take it back.
I don't want it.
Take your money.
Take it.
What?
Come inside and let me
clean that up, okay?
Hey. Hey. That looks
really fuckin' bad, man.
You gotta do me a favor. What?
If you stay here,
it's gonna fuckin' kill you.
You gotta get out of here.
Okay. Okay. I'm serious, ally.
Ally. I'm going to
park Avenue tomorrow.
Don't go, okay?
You can't drive like that.
You're fucked up.
Wake up, Thomas, wake up!
I missed you.
I'm here.
This is exactly
where I met you.
Huh?
Give the boys my best.
That's what they are, right?
Little fucking boys.
Is it just you?
Huh?
This is it?
Who's in there? Huh?
Buona sera.
Who else is here?
It's just you two?
Huh? Nobody.
Just you two?
Yeah. What about you?
Are you alone?
You mean business, huh?
You... you got big balls.
Me and you, come on.
John? Si.
Why is the door red?
The door, why is it red?
Nobody knows.
It's red.
We sicilians,
we've been grounded up
like coffee.
Arabic, Norman, Spanish, Greek.
We don't know
anymore who we are.
No.
Hmm.
It's a dream.
I wish I was there.
But things have
changed there, too.
They made the canyon
to build this guy.
Ah, things are not
the same anymore.
Got your...
I'm sorry.
There's nothing in it.
Look, there's a flower.
Go to sleep... Go to sleep...
Go to sleep.
Here he comes. Here he comes.
Is the light on? The light on?
67th and Columbus.
Aah!
Fuck! Fuck!
Shit!
Aah!
Go! Go!
Aah... help!
Help!
Aah...
come on... hey.
Hey, we gotta ditch this car.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, okay?
It's all over.
Okay?
It's over.
We don't have to do it
anymore, huh?
I'm sorry. I promise.
Don't cry, baby.
Don't... don't cry.
It... it's okay.
All news, all the time.
This is 1010 wins.
You give us 22 minutes,
we'll give you the world.
Curtis Sliwa, founder
of the guardian angels
and talk show host,
has been shot
outside his home this morning.
Sliwa is in stable condition
at mount sinai hospital.
He is said to have
identified his shooters
as Gambino soldiers sent
by John Gotti, Jr.,
the son of the deposed
mob boss.
In other news,
quest labs' Nicoderm patch
was put on the American
market today.
It is the first transdermal
patch for smokers...
thank you.
Two lobster tails.
Just two?
Your brother Anthony
was in this morning.
Hmm.
I guess you don't see him much.
The baby is so cute.
Mmm.
What about you, rose?
What about me?
When are you having one?
I'm pregnant, Annie.
Oh.
I didn't know.
Who's the father?
The ice cream man.
Ahh...
Sliwa's not dead.
They're saying
junior's boys shot him.
I don't even know
what to believe anymore.
Where you wanna go?
Why don't we just
drive around for a while?
It's all these people.
I don't know.
What?
Hey, close your eyes.
What? Shh.
Oh, what are you...
Shh.