Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
[Car horn honks]
[Audience cheering]
[Announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage
Mr. Jim Jefferies!
[Upbeat music playing]
Hello!
Sit down, sit down, sit
down, sit down, sit down.
[Chuckles]
Thank you, Boston. I appreciate that.
[Whooping]
Uh, that's very sweet of you.
[Man] Love you!
I'm at the end of the tour right now.
I'm very happy to be on tour
because I now have a child.
Ah, so...
any time out of home is good for me.
Um, I got my girlfriend pregnant
after knowing her for two months.
So...
[Audience cheering]
Thank you. Thank you. Life decisions.
And she's a nice girl, and
I love her in a way, sure.
My problem with my girlfriend is,
she's very sweet, but she's
shit at telling stories,
and I'm awesome at telling stories,
so it really bothers me when she talks.
And I don't know if that'll
be a problem in the future,
but it's a problem now and I
don't see it getting better.
Um...
I'll give you an example, right?
I was in the car,
and my son Hank was
asleep in the back seat,
and we're driving along, and
on the radio comes Madonna,
and my girlfriend just
slips into conversation,
"Oh, I used to party with Madonna."
And I went, "You fucking what, when?"
And she went, "I used
to party with Madonna."
Now, I should fill you
in a little bit on this.
My girlfriend used to be
a model in Miami, right?
I'm not bragging. I
didn't get the model years.
I didn't get those years.
I've seen the photos. Very impressive.
Um...
So, I said, "So you used
to party with Madonna.
Madonna used to have big parties
and invite models over, right?"
And she went, "No, no, it would
just be me and a few other people."
I go, "You need to elaborate
on this story right now."
And she goes, "Oh, okay, I used to
date the center for the Miami Heat."
As soon as you hear that
the mother of your child
used to date an NBA center,
even if this guy's even
slightly in proportion...
a lot of things flood through your head.
First thing is, "That's why
your cunt's so fucked up."
That's a big one.
"That's why our child came
out while you were walking.
I understand."
So she said, "I used to date
the center for the Miami Heat.
His best friend was Dennis Rodman.
Dennis Rodman used to go out with Madonna,
and we used to go over to Madonna's house."
And she goes, "This one time,
the four of us were
over at Madonna's house,
and we were all fucked up on drugs,
and one thing led to another..."
And then I went, "Shut the fuck up!"
And she went, "What?"
I said, "I know what 'one
thing led to another' means!
You all started fucking each other!"
And she went, "We did. We
started..." "Just shut up!"
And she goes, "What do you care for?"
I said, "You're the mother of my child!
I don't wanna picture you being
fucked by a 7'2" NBA player
while you're licking out
Madonna's muscular vagina
and Dennis Rodman is in the corner
stroking his tattooed cock, going..."
[Moaning]
And she goes, "Oh, you're being silly.
What do you care for?
You've partied way more
than I have in my life."
And I went, "That is not true.
I've gotten wasted way more than you have,
but I have, in no way,
partied way more than you have.
Often, I get wasted just by myself.
I wouldn't call it a party."
For most of my career, I was
a struggling comedian, right?
And this is how struggling
comedians party, right?
It's 5:00 a.m., Monday, right?
We're in a one-bedroom apartment.
Seven of us are standing
around a coffee table,
trying to stretch out two grams of coke.
One of us is at the end of the
table giving conspiracy theories...
and the rest of us are talking
about where women might be.
One of us has come up with a plan.
The plan goes like this,
"Well...
nurses will be finishing their shift soon.
Maybe if we just stand
out the front of the ER,
they'll appreciate seven funny guys."
[Chuckles]
I don't... You know, I've
never partied like a model.
I have partied twice in my life. Twice.
Like, really partied.
I've had good nights out,
but I've really partied twice.
If you really party,
and most people never experience
this, it's an amazing thing.
It happens in Vegas. It
can only happen in Vegas,
and it's gotta involve celebrity, right?
I'm not famous,
but the people around me were super famous,
and I was at this party in the
night club, and they took me in.
And then there's the night club,
but then there's the real
night club out the back,
which is, like, the size of this
stage. It's only a little room.
And you go back there and you can just...
They encourage you to
take drugs in the open,
and you're just doing
it off a key, [Sniffs]
and they're going, "No, dude.
Use the table. Don't use your..."
And I go, "Oh, oh. Oh, sorry. Um..."
And it's confusing at first,
and then their security will drag women
off that other night club into your room.
Just bring 'em in like, "Huh?"
And you can do this. You can go...
"Uh..."
Like that.
And they'll drag these women away.
It is the best thing you'll
ever do with your life.
When you party that hard as a
man, there's a lot of remorse
'cause you have to tip
everyone a lot of money.
You wake up in the morning
with a terrible hangover,
and you go to your friends.
You go, "Oh, my God.
We partied so hard last
night. I spent $5,000."
When a hot girl parties that hard,
she wakes up in the morning and goes,
"Oh, my God.
We partied so hard last
night. I made $5,000."
And that's a vastly
different emotion that...
I don't think women
will never... Yeah, okay.
This is the thing.
In America, at the moment, they're
trying to raise the minimum wage
to, I don't know, $16 an
hour or something like that,
and whenever they bring up this argument,
they always go, "And still to this day,
women only earn 70% of what
men earn in the workplace."
And of course, that's disgusting.
How dare women earn so much?
Like...
a lot of things that I say tonight will
be jokes that I don't actually mean,
but this is something I'm
really passionate about.
Women do not deserve to earn as
much money as men in the workplace.
I'm sorry. I...
[Audience whooping]
I'm not being a
misogynistic bastard, right?
I'm not saying that
women don't work as hard.
I'm sure they do.
I'm not saying they don't do as good a job.
What I'm saying is
they don't deserve to
earn as much money as men.
Right?
Men need that extra 30%
to buy meals and drinks
and Jim Jefferies
tickets and all that shit!
[Audience cheering]
Now...
I'm sure there's women in
this room that are saying,
"Oh, I pay for my drinks.
I bought my own ticket."
And don't think we don't
appreciate the uglies,
'cause we do.
Right? We do.
But there's little things in
society that you can't change.
Men have extra expenses
that you'll never understand.
There's holidays that are just for women.
Like Valentine's Day is just for women.
They say it's for romantics.
They say it's for couples
or something like that.
It's just for women.
There's no man who gets
excited by Valentine's Day.
There's no man that when he sees
the Valentine's Day decorations
go up in the shopping mall,
he goes, "Oh, Valentine's Day is coming!"
Valentine's Day is a mathematical
equation that every man has in his head,
and it goes like this,
"How much money do I have to spend today
so that you won't act like a cunt?"
It doesn't stop there.
Mother's Day!
Mother's Day rocked around in my
house when my son was six months old.
My girlfriend's first Mother's Day.
And she went, "Oh, I wonder
what I'll get for Mother's Day."
And I went, "Probably fucking nothing.
He's got no money. He's six months old.
What do you think he's gonna buy you?"
Within an hour, her friends
were over at the house,
just by coincidence,
telling me what a bad person I was
and how important Mother's
Day is to a new mum, you know?
And so, I went and bought
her a cappuccino machine
'cause I assumed that's what Hank
would have wanted her to have...
and I wrote a card.
I'm not a bastard. I wrote
a card. I'm right-handed.
So I got my left hand.
Every new dad knows this.
You get the crayon and you go,
[Imitating child] "Happy Mother's Day.
Love, Hank."
And I went,
"H-A-N..."
And then I did the "K" back-to-front
because he's a fucking moron.
See, now I know there's people in the room,
they're thinking, "Well,
fathers have Father's Day."
Father's Day is bullshit.
It's fucking shit, Father's Day.
Father's Day came around
and my girlfriend went,
"What do you want for Father's Day?"
And I went, "I don't want anything.
Don't even worry about
it. I don't want anything."
And she goes, "Come on.
You gotta have something."
I said, "Honestly, I don't want
anything." And she goes, "Come on."
And I went, "It's my fucking money.
Just don't touch it.
Just leave my money alone.
How hard is this?
How about, for 24 hours, you
don't touch my fucking money?
That would be a gift."
That's why every single father
has that one Father's Day
gift that they cherish,
and it's shit!
It's, like, a fucking ceramic
mug that the kid made in school
where the handle's too big,
and it says, "I heart Dad."
And they keep that for 20
fucking years, this mug.
And do you wanna know why they like it?
Every now and again,
they look at it and go...
"That cost me nothing, that mug."
[Audience whooping]
See...
wouldn't it be nice to have one day
that was for men and for fathers
and all that type of stuff,
but didn't cost anything, that
everyone could participate in, right?
I've got it, right? April 18th...
Anal Sex Day.
[Men cheering loudly]
It's good, isn't it?
Everyone's girlfriend or wife has
to take it in the ass on April 18th.
It's nice.
A month before, you'd be walking
around the shopping center going,
"Oh, the decorations are up!"
[Men whooping]
And it's good 'cause if your
bird didn't take it in the ass,
you could do the same thing
that women do on Valentine's Day
when they don't get a gift.
You could go like,
"Oh, me mate, Jason, his
wife took it in the ass twice.
Yeah, obviously, they're
more connected than we are.
They've, uh..."
I'm thinking, I don't do much
merchandise after my shows and stuff,
but I'm thinking of bringing
out some April 18th T-shirts.
Not even putting "Jim
Jefferies" on them or anything.
Just T-shirts that say, "April 18th."
'Cause it's good, right?
You're in a bar. You're a guy.
You see a guy at the other end of the
bar with an April 18th, and you go...
Fucking friends for life, right?
But even better, you see a
girl with an April 18th T-shirt.
The weird thing is I'm
bigging-up anal sex here,
and I don't even really like
fucking girls in the ass that much.
I'm not even a huge fan.
I much prefer the cunt.
I think it's a much more...
I think that a cunt is a much
more purpose-built thing to fuck.
But, you know, anal sex... Oh, you know...
I do it.
I get involved, 'cause
I feel like I have to.
You know, I...
But I've never been a big fan
of the ass fucking, I, uh...
When I watch it on porn,
it seems very inviting.
The girl's taking it
so fluently in her ass,
and she seems to be having fun, and, uh...
But the thing is, you can't
smell porn. You don't smell porn.
You just...
You just watch it. They never...
And it's different, porn. It's different.
They clean the girl's asshole.
They pump water into it
until it's very hygienic.
I'm sure.
And the girl seems to be
so happy. She's like...
You've got it in her
pussy, you're fucking her,
and then she's like, "Put it in my ass."
She's inviting.
It's like you're doing her a favor in porn.
And then she's like... She says things...
I don't know, things like,
"I'm enjoying that. Keep
putting it in my ass.
Fuck my ass. I love a cock in my ass."
And...
And the experience I've had in my
own life has been vastly different.
I've...
My experience has been a lot of crying.
Now, although that can
help you come at times,
it's not what you want...
It's not what you want for every day.
I like the girl who acts
like she's enjoying it.
Like, you know when your girlfriend's
like, "I'm gonna act like I enjoy it."
She does that whole,
"Yeah. Oh, no, that's good."
[Moaning]
Ahh!
♪ I'm having a good time ♪
And then they're always going, "Are
you done? Are you close to done?"
You never fuck a pussy and they go,
"Are you almost done? Finish this."
Like that. If you're fucking
ass, they don't want you...
They want it all over, quick.
And they do other things, the porn girls.
I don't know how much they get paid.
I'm sure it's more than
what the men get paid.
It's the opposite bit of society.
Um...
But they do a thing called "ATM."
I don't know if you
know what that is, kids.
That stands for "ass to mouth."
That's where the porn girl will
pull the cock from out of her anus,
and she'll put it directly in her
mouth, and she'll say something like,
"I love the taste of my ass.
Let me taste my ass."
And then the man, as a favor to this woman,
puts his cock in her mouth
to congratulate her on the fine work...
[Applause]
she's been doing.
Now, I had a drunken
night with my ex-girlfriend
where she thought she'd
be all wild and try that.
Once again, vastly different experience.
I'm not a big fan of the ass fucking,
and I don't know of any man,
if they're truthful, really is.
Now, there's women in
the room who are thinking,
"Well, why does my guy constantly
bother me to fuck me in my ass?"
[Woman shouting]
What a good question.
[Woman whoops]
Women, the reason that men like
fucking you in the ass is because...
we know you fucking hate it.
[Cheering]
So...
I'm a father.
Um...
I love my son! I love my son the
same way that I love cigarettes.
I like to hold him for
five minutes every hour,
and the rest of the time,
I'm thinking about how
he's fucking killing me.
He's a good little boy.
No, he's a great little
fella. I really like him.
Um...
My girlfriend super loves him,
though. It's fucking creepy.
And...
I'm glad I have a son.
That worked out good for me.
I wouldn't be a good father to a
girl. It wouldn't be good for me.
Nothing weird. Wouldn't fuck it. I...
I just don't get along with
women. You know how it is.
I don't want them in my house, and...
So...
Because you dream, see...
For example, okay? When Hank was born...
the couple over the road, within
two weeks of Hank being born,
had a baby girl,
and rightly or wrongly, the first
thing that went through my head was...
"Aw, that's great.
I hope Hank fucks that one day."
That's what I think... 'Cause
that's what I think about my son.
I hope when he's of age,
he just fucks everything.
I don't care if my son is gay or straight.
All I care about is, when he is of age,
that he gets every bit of fucking
pussy or cock that he desires.
That is my dream for my son!
[Audience cheering]
But never in the history
of fathers and daughters,
has a father held his baby girl and gone,
"Oh, I hope you have a lot of
cocks through you in your life.
I hope you're never shy of a cock.
I hope you pass out at parties
and all the boys are queuing up."
Right, you know...
And it's not just me.
Women treat baby girls and
baby boys differently as well.
My girlfriend goes to
the gym every morning.
I go there very occasionally,
and when you go to the gym,
there's a little daycare
crèche thing in the gym
where you can hand your child off,
and inside that daycare, there's,
like, three women in their 50s.
They're very nice ladies, and you
hand your kid off and he plays.
Then when you finish your
workout, you come and get him.
And there's a woman that works
there who just loves my son.
She sees all the other
kids, but she loves Hank,
and Hank fucking loves her,
and the two of them light
up when they see each other.
And it's super cute,
I bring Hank up the stairs,
and he starts going, "Uh, uh!"
Trying to reach at her, all right?
And she does this, she goes,
"Everyone, my boyfriend's here.
Here's my boyfriend. Give
him here. He's my boyfriend."
And then she kisses him, and she goes,
♪ My boyfriend gives me kisses
My boyfriend gives me kisses ♪
It's fucking adorable.
But I tried doing that with a baby girl...
Let's say you go to the
gym and there's a daycare,
and me and a couple of my
mates are working there.
"Hey, everyone...
me girlfriend's here.
Give her here. Give her
here. She's my girlfriend.
My girlfriend gives me
kisses. You know that, right?
She's always giving me kisses.
Enjoy your workout. Don't
worry about a thing."
[Applause]
[Cheering]
So...
Also...
it's just easier to bring up
a son than it is a daughter.
It's just little things.
Even when they're babies, it's just easier.
There's a wiping technique
when you're wiping a baby's ass.
I don't know if you have children,
but this is how you do it.
The baby lays on its back.
You put their feet together.
You lift the feet up, and
then you go in and wipe.
With a boy, you can wipe like that.
Up and down, side to side,
whatever the fuck you want, right?
With a girl, you gotta
wipe downward and away.
Downward and away.
It's very important that
you wipe away from the cunt.
Very important.
'Cause it turns out that women of all ages
hate having shit in their cunts.
They do. They fucking hate it.
Boys don't give a shit. Fucking...
My son will have shit all
over his dick and balls,
and I'll be cleaning it
off under the foreskin,
and he'll be laughing like
it's the best day ever.
Even at my age now,
I find it funny if I have shit on my dick.
If I fuck my girlfriend in the ass,
I pull out, I've got shit on my dick,
I'll ring me mate Jason
up and go, "Hey, Jason...
It's happened again.
I got shit on my dick."
And he'll tell me a similar story
about when he had shit on his dick,
and we'll laugh and laugh and laugh.
But never in the history of women
has there been a woman with shit
in her cunt and she's thought,
"Oh, I can't wait to
call Karen." [Chuckles]
[Laughs]
When you...
When my girlfriend got pregnant...
When you meet...
When you haven't got a child,
couples who have children
are always bragging about how
cool it is to have children.
Whenever you meet couples with
children they're always like,
"It is the most fulfilling thing
I've ever done with my life.
My heart grows larger
and larger every day."
And then the second that
my girlfriend got pregnant,
those same people went like this,
"You're never gonna sleep
again! [Laughs maniacally]
Forget about it. It's over.
You're not gonna sleep."
They're constantly telling
you you're not gonna sleep.
Raising a baby is not that hard.
I'll tell you what, it's
easier than a coke habit.
I had a coke habit for
seven-and-a-half fucking years!
At least it's not me who
wakes up crying anymore!
I can sleep through other people crying.
I've had girlfriends.
That's like white noise
to me. I find it soothing.
See, me and my girlfriend,
just two months, we went,
"Fuck it! Let's have a
kid." Fucking did it, right?
These other people, man...
You know these couples, and
they date from high school,
and then they go out for a bit longer,
and then after being together
for like, seven years, they go,
"We're getting engaged. You
wanna come to the party?"
And you wanna say, "No, you're
really boring and we hate you."
But you go, "Oh, okay, great.
You're still together, are you?
You fucked one person,
have you? Oh, how exciting."
And...
And then what they do is they
don't have a kid right away
because they're still not ready.
"We have to see how our
careers are going and shit."
And what they do is they get a dog,
and then they act like the
fucking dog's their baby.
They refer to it as their fucking baby.
They send you a Christmas
card of them holding the dog...
and it says, "From our family to yours."
And then you have a barbecue, and
you invite them, the humans, right?
Then they come over.
This fucking dog runs in,
jumping over everything,
and you're like, "What
the fuck is this shit?"
And they're like, "We had to bring
him. We bring our baby everywhere."
And you go, "Well, your baby
is biting my actual baby.
Can you control..."
And then, eventually, they
decide they're gonna have a kid
'cause they've learned
so much from the dog,
and then they bring the kid back,
and the dog runs up, like,
"What's happening? A new person."
And they're like, "Fuck off.
We don't love you anymore.
We're going."
And they think they've
learnt something from the dog,
and they haven't learnt anything.
What happens if your
girlfriend's away on work
and the dog dies?
You go off, you buy another dog
that looks similar to the original dog...
try to pass it off as the same dog.
What happens if your
girlfriend's away on work
and the baby dies?
Very hard...
to get a baby that looks exactly the same
in the short period of time that you have.
Easier if you're black or Asian.
[Audience cheering]
Boston, no!
No! No!
Shut up!
I will not put up with
racism at my shows, okay?
I'm not saying 'cause they look the same.
I'm saying 'cause they're
easier to purchase.
[Audience cheering]
[Audience whooping]
If Angelina Jolie and Madonna
have taught us anything...
it is that you can buy
black and Asian people.
I'm yet to see a black celebrity couple
come home from Norway
with a child, going...
"Yolanda, quick, get Hans.
Bring him over. Come on."
[Jeffries chuckles]
I'm gonna talk about something now that
sort of splits the crowd a little bit.
Uh...
Gun control.
Now... No, wait. Before you...
Don't get excited because
the other people have guns.
The anti-gun people are
like, "Yeah! Do it, Jim!"
No, let's just... [Shushes]
Now, before I start saying
this, I wanna say this, right?
I believe in your right
as Americans to have guns.
I'm not trying to stop
you from having guns.
All I'm saying is this is my
personal belief on the opinion.
My opinion on the... Oh, it doesn't matter.
I don't like guns, right?
I'm gonna say some things
that are just facts, right?
In Australia, we had guns,
right? Right up until 1996.
In 1996, Australia had the
biggest massacre on Earth.
It still hasn't been beaten.
And...
Now, after that, they banned the guns.
Now, in the 10 years before Port
Arthur, there was 10 massacres.
Since the gun ban in 1996, there
hasn't been a single massacre since.
I don't know how or
why this happened, uh...
Maybe it was a coincidence, right?
Now, please understand that I
understand that Australia and America
are two vastly different cultures
with different people, right? I get it.
In Australia, we had the
biggest massacre on Earth,
and the Australian government
went, "That's it! No more guns!"
And we all went,
"Yeah, all right, then. That
seems fair enough, really."
Now, in America, you had
the Sandy Hook massacre
where little, tiny children died,
and your government went,
"Maybe...
we'll get rid of the big guns?"
And 50% of you went, "Fuck
you! Don't take my guns!"
[Whooping]
So, here's where it gets confusing, right?
Now, as I said, I am all for
your Second Amendment rights.
I think you should be able to have
guns. It's in your constitution.
What I am not for is
bullshit arguments and lies.
There is one argument and one
argument alone for having a gun,
and this is the argument...
"Fuck off. I like guns."
It's not the best argument,
but it's all you've got.
And there's nothing wrong with it.
There's nothing wrong with saying,
"I like something. Don't
take it away from me."
But don't give me this other
bullshit. The main one is,
[In American accent] "I
need it for protection.
I need to protect me. I
need to protect my family."
Really? Is that why they're
called "assault rifles"?
Is it?
I've never heard of these fucking
"protection rifles" you speak of.
Protection? What the fuck
are you talking about?
You have a gun in your house,
you're 80% more likely to
use that gun on yourself,
than to shoot someone else.
And people think, "Well,
that'd never happen to me."
You don't know that, because you know what?
♪ From time to time We all get sad ♪
♪ One day you're
happy Then you're sad ♪
♪ And then, uh-oh ♪
Protection.
I had a break-in in Manchester, England,
where I was tied up, I had my head cut.
They threatened to rape my girlfriend.
They came through the window
with a machete and a hammer,
and Americans always go,
[In American accent] "Well,
imagine if you had a gun."
And I'm like, "All right.
I was naked at the time.
I wasn't wearing my holster.
I wasn't staring at the window
waiting for cunts with
machetes to come through."
What world do you live in where
you're constantly fucking ready?
You have guns 'cause you like guns!
That's why you go to gun conventions!
That's why you read gun magazines!
None of you give a shit
about home security.
None of you go to home
security conventions.
None of you read Padlock Monthly.
None of you have a Facebook picture
of you behind a secure door going,
"Fucking yeah!"
Like you're going to be ready
if someone comes into your house.
You have it at all fucking times.
By the way, most people who
are breaking into your house
just want your fucking TV!
You think that people are
coming to murder your family?
How many fucking enemies do you have?
Jeez, you think a lot of yourself
if you think everyone's
coming to murder you.
See, if you have it readily
available, it becomes unsafe.
You have it in your bedside table,
one of your kids picks
it up, thinks it's a toy,
shoots another one of your kids.
Happens every fucking day, but people go,
"That'd never happen in my house
'cause I'm a responsible gun owner.
I keep my guns locked in a safe."
Then they're no fucking protection!
Someone comes into the house,
you're like, "Wait there, fuck-face!
Oh! You've come to the
wrong house here, buddy boy.
I tell you what.
I'm gonna fuck you up!
Okay.
Is it 32 to the left or 32 to the right?
Your mother's birthday?
Why the fuck would I know
your fucking mother's birthday?
Maybe if you didn't leave the window open
[In whining voice] 'because
it's too hot in here,'
we wouldn't be getting
fucking murdered, right?"
I find the NRA to be hard work.
The fact that they always
think the answer is more guns.
After Sandy Hook happened,
the NRA said, and I quote,
"None of this would have happened
if the teachers had guns."
I...
I think they're forgetting
what school was like.
Does anyone remember that
casual teacher that used to...
Whenever she came into school,
that relief teacher came,
you and your friends would see her and go,
[Chuckling] "Oh, we're gonna make her cry."
And then she'd stand in front
of the class with a bit of chalk
and her hands would be shaking,
and you'd go,
"You're never getting
married, are you, Miss?
Never gonna happen for you."
Then she'd get back to
her 1967 Volkswagen Beetle,
and she'd be crying
over the steering wheel,
just, "Why don't they like me?"
Let's give that cunt a gun
and see how things work out!
[Audience cheering]
And then they go,
"Oh, well, answer to that,
we'll just add more guns."
They go, "We'll put an armed security
guard at every school across America."
Yeah, that'll work out.
The average security guard
in America earns $16 an hour.
Not a lot of wiggle room
to be a fucking hero!
Someone comes onto the school and...
[Mimicking machine gun]
And you've got Kevin.
Now, I'm sure Kevin's
shit-hot at Call of Duty,
but it might not fucking
cut it, ladies and gentlemen.
Now, I understand that when I'm
doing this joke in this room,
50% of you agree with me, 50%
of you don't agree with me,
and I do respect the people
who don't agree with me.
Don't think I don't.
Out of the 50% that don't agree with me,
20% of those people are
smart enough to realize
this is a comedy show and
it's not to be taken seriously,
and they're laughing along 'cause
it's just funny jokes, right?
And then the next 20%, have
sort of phased out a little bit.
They're looking around, going,
"Wonder how they got
that chandelier up there?"
And then...
there's the last 10%.
And they're fucking furious.
Right now, in this room and
the people watching at home...
10% of you are fucking seething. Just...
And for a couple of reasons. First
reason, I'm making good points.
[Audience cheering]
Second reason. Second reason.
Second reason, and this is the big one,
I'm foreign...
and that's pissing the
fuck out of you right now,
and your brain is on a loop and
you can't fucking turn it off,
and it's just going around in
a circle, and you're just going,
"If you don't like it, go home!
If you don't like it, go home!"
And my answer to that is, "No."
I came here legally. I pay my taxes.
I'll say whatever the fuck I want.
Your First Amendment means that I can
say the Second Amendment sucks dicks.
And...
unless you're an American Indian,
you're a fucking immigrant as well,
so fuck off.
People get so precious about it.
I understand that to Americans,
your constitution is very important.
I respect it,
but please understand that
every country has one as well.
It's no more special than
any other constitution.
We have one in Australia.
I don't know what it says.
I've never seen it.
If there's a problem, we'll check
it, but everything's going fine.
And don't get me wrong.
I get that the constitution
is important to you.
I have had... Fucking, I get it, right?
I've had people come up to me in my face
and scream at me in car parks as
I'm leaving the theater, going,
[In American accent] "You cannot
change the Second Amendment!"
And I'm like, "Yes, you can.
It's called an 'amendment.'"
If you can't change something
that's called an "amendment",
see, many of you need a thesaurus
more than you need a constitution.
And if you don't know what a thesaurus is,
get a dictionary and work your way forward.
Don't think your
constitution is set in stone.
You've changed things before.
You used to have
prohibition in there, right?
And then people were like, "Hey,
who likes getting fucked up?
Yeah, I like getting fucked
up, too. Let's get that one out.
Let's get that one out."
You used to have this other
thing in America called, uh...
slavery!
And then Lincoln came along and
went, "That's it. No more slaves!"
And 50% of you went, "Fuck
you! Don't take my slaves!"
And the same bullshit arguments
came out that you have with guns.
"Why should I have my slaves taken off me?
I'm a responsible slave owner.
I'm trained in how to use my slaves safely.
Just because that guy mistreated his slaves
doesn't mean that my rights
should be taken away from me.
I...
I use my slaves to protect my family!
I keep my slaves locked in a safe!"
That's the thing.
"Why should I have my guns taken
off me? I've done nothing wrong."
Look, I agree with you.
If you're a responsible gun owner
and you don't fuck around with them,
then you should be allowed
your guns. You really should.
But that's not how society works.
We have to play to the
1% that are such fuckwits
they ruin it for the rest of us.
We have to walk as slow
as our slowest person
to keep society fucking moving, right?
I take drugs like a
fucking champion, right?
[Audience cheering]
We should all be allowed
to take fucking drugs,
but we can't, can we?
Because Sarah took drugs and
she stabbed her fucking kids.
Oh!
"Oh, thanks, Sarah. You
fucked it up for everyone."
Right?
Everyone should be
allowed to drive their car
as fast as they can do it, right?
But we can't because Jonathan
got drunk and ran over a family.
"Thanks, Jonathan!
Now I have to drive at
30, you fucking idiot!"
See, that's the thing. "Why
should I have my guns taken off me,
I'm responsible, just
because that guy's crazy?"
Who's to say you're not crazy?
That's the thing about crazy people.
They don't know they're crazy.
That's what makes them crazy.
The only thing you know
for sure on this Earth is,
"I think, therefore I am."
You know that you exist.
Anything past that is open
to interpretation, right?
You know you exist and that's it.
Right now, I think I'm in
Boston talking to 1,200 people.
That's what I think I'm doing,
but there is a good to fair
chance that I'm in a mental home,
standing in front of a white wall, going,
[Slurring speech] "I hate
guns. I hate guns. I hate guns."
[Audience applauding]
See, one of the better arguments is,
"Well, if you take the guns away, then
only the criminals will have guns."
Not true.
When they banned the guns
in Australia, it worked.
When they banned them in
Britain, it worked, okay?
The Bushmaster gun that the
kid was gonna use in Sandy Hook
costs, like, $1,000 American
and you can buy it in Walmart.
It'll be delivered to
your house. That's it, man.
1,000 bucks, right?
That same gun in Australia on
the black market costs $34,000.
Now if you have $34,000,
you don't need to be a criminal.
You've got $34,000.
You're a great little saver. Keep going.
So that covers the criminals,
but that doesn't cover the people
who wanna murder your family,
that are coming after you and your family.
It kind of does.
The people who do the massacres,
it covers them 'cause they go...
The kid at Colorado who
thought he was The Joker,
let's say that he had some social issues.
The kid at Sandy Hook
was Asperger's as fuck.
Right?
I don't know if you know a
lot about the black market,
but you can't just rock
up at the docks going,
[Slurring speech] "Guns!
Who wants to sell me a gun?"
Now, I'm gonna wrap this up. We
won't talk about it anymore. Now...
See, the one thing that
I do really agree with
with the right to bear arms,
I really agree with... That
the real reason it was written
was so that you could form a militia to
fight against a tyrannical government.
In case the government
became a bunch of cunts,
you could all get your guns and fight back,
and that's why it was written.
- [Audience cheering]
- Yeah!
And that made a hell of a lot of
sense when it was just muskets.
But you do know the government
has drones, right? You get that?
You're bringing guns to a drone fight!
If we went back to muskets, I'm all for it!
Keep the Second Amendment.
If we all have muskets...
Muskets are awesome!
Every cunt should be carrying
a musket with him at all times.
You know what's good about the musket?
It gives you a lot of time to calm down.
Someone calls your wife fat, and
you're like, "Fuck you, buddy!
Ah, you're not a bad
guy. You're all right."
Now...
after the show, we're gonna go out,
have a big party around
Boston, see how it goes.
I'm not allowed to go
to strip clubs anymore.
My girlfriend has said that's a no...
'cause I don't behave myself in there,
so I'm not allowed to go to them anymore.
'Cause strip clubs aren't
what women think they are.
[Stammers] It used to be like...
Okay, so, when a man goes to a strip club,
it's all about girls being as dirty and
as horrible to each other as possible.
That's what men want to see.
Women, when they go to
their Magic Mike clubs
or whatever the fuck they are...
women wanna see a guy, "Hey,
ladies. He's a fireman."
And he comes out with
his hose and like that...
And whenever a stripper
takes their clothes off,
they've still got the fireman's
hat on or a tool belt on
or policeman's gun on a holster, right?
Because even when a man's naked, a
woman wants to know that he has a job.
When men watch strippers,
we want them to have a job,
and that job's stripping.
We want to just look at that girl
dancing and have a hand full of money,
and just go...
"You can't take care of your kids."
It's...
And when men get private
dances in these strip clubs,
I don't know...
I don't know if women actually
know what goes on in those rooms,
but basically, it's dry humping.
There's no dancing.
The girl gets in front.
She gets where your cock is,
pushes it to one side
and then she rubs on it...
and then she stands over and
puts her cunt right in your face,
and you go...
That's what a private "dance" is, right?
I don't know if there's private
dancing in female strip clubs.
[Stammering] I can't
imagine that there would be.
I don't imagine a woman
getting out of a back room
and going up to her friend and going...
She goes, "How was it?"
And she goes, "Well...
he just sat me down and then
he grabbed my genitals...
and then he dragged his
scrotum over my forehead.
I got to go to the ATM."
So Legit got canceled.
[Audience booing]
Yeah.
I know. I know it.
Who would've thought it would've struggled
on that great FXX channel
that everyone knew about?
The first season is on Netflix.
This special is being recorded for Netflix.
So you can go watch it there
if you're watching the special.
It was...
I'm very proud of it.
We had two great seasons
of really good television,
and if people didn't...
Now...
The whole TV show is based
around one standup routine
that I used to do about having
a friend with muscular dystrophy
that I took to a brothel,
which is a true story.
And so, when we cast a character
with muscular dystrophy who...
In the end, we used DJ Qualls,
and DJ Qualls is the skinny white
guy out of the movie Road Trip.
He's the skinny white guy out
of the movie Hustle & Flow,
and he's the white guy out
of the movie Hustle & Flow.
Now...
the great thing about DJ is...
he already looks disabled.
He has that "latter stages
of AIDS" thing going on.
It's great for casting. Anyway, but...
I didn't want DJ to begin with.
I wanted a person with muscular
dystrophy to make it look authentic,
and the Actors' Union of America
said, "You cannot do that."
Because basically the problem is
people with muscular dystrophy, I think,
are only allowed to work for two
hours a day before they get too tired.
And I said, "All right, what
other disabilities and diseases
are allowed to work longer?"
And they sent me a list.
And on this list, I said, "Can you
get rid of all the contagious ones?
And what have we got left?"
So I saw every disabled actor in Hollywood,
and I'll be honest with you,
not that many of them.
I don't know why.
Maybe they're just lazy.
They don't wanna work.
Maybe they give up on
their dreams rather quickly.
And none of them were very good, either.
Everyone we saw, none
of them were very good
'cause acting is all about
what you do with your hands.
None of them knew what to
do with their hands, and...
they all came in.
Until this one guy came in.
I had seen a lot of people that day.
This guy was the most disabled
person I'd ever seen in my life.
He was like...
Think of the most disabled person
you've seen, then double it.
...really super disabled.
He was shaped like a pretzel.
He was being carried in
by this big Russian nurse,
carried him in.
He made that great disabled
sound of... [Groans]
That one.
I just loved him.
Anyway...
so he comes in for the audition...
and I'm sitting there, and
we're doing the lines together,
and at first, I didn't know if
he was mentally all there either,
so I was being a little bit patronizing.
I was going, "Thank you
so much for coming in."
And then we did the dialog together,
and I didn't have to worry about a thing.
This kid was funny. He was
smart. His timing was impeccable.
I thought he was just great,
and I helped him out of the room,
and I come back to the director and I said,
"That's our guy. That's who we gotta pick."
And he agreed,
but we had to see everyone else
who was still in the waiting room.
So the next bloke wheels himself in.
Now, obviously, he's just a
paraplegic if he's wheeling himself in,
which means the waist down,
and that didn't really suit me because...
paraplegics can get themselves
to a hooker without my assistance.
But I thought...
"If he's a good enough actor,
maybe he can quad-up for the role."
So he comes in...
He comes in, I shake his hand,
and his leg slightly
comes out at the same time.
And I went, "Whoa!
What's going on there, kicky?"
And he goes...
"Oh, you got me!
I'm not disabled."
And I said, "You're fucking what now?"
And he goes, "I'm not disabled.
I just really wanted the role,
so I rented a wheelchair."
And I said, "Just shut up.
So let me... This is how your
day has mapped-out thus far.
You woke up this morning. You drove
to the wheelchair rental place.
You rented a wheelchair.
You carried it out, I assume.
You put it in the trunk of
your car. You drove here.
You got the wheelchair out.
You carried it up three flights of stairs.
You went to the waiting room.
You put it down next to
the severely disabled man
and his nurse.
Then you sat in it and
practiced your lines."
And he went...
"Yeah."
And I said, "You're a
fucking asshole, mate.
Get the fuck out of here."
And I kicked him out.
And later on that day, I'm sitting
there with all the headshots
of all the different actors I'm gonna
call to tell them they've got parts,
and I'm holding this
disabled guy's headshot,
and I just think, "I'm
gonna call this guy up.
I'm gonna change his life. This
is an awesome moment, right?"
And I'm looking at it, and he looks
super handsome in his headshot.
He looked really like...
And I thought, "This has gotta
be the greatest photographer
with the fastest shutter
in camera history."
The shutter on his camera
has gotta be like...
[Mimicking camera shutter]
Like...
[Audience applauding]
And then I read the guy's biography...
and then it dawned on me.
"This guy's not disabled either!
I hated the other fucker
for renting a wheelchair!
This cunt rented a nurse!"
Do you wanna know the
level of fucking psychosis
you have to go through
to rent a fucking nurse?
I'm all for a method actor.
Get into character three hours before,
but once you finish the audition,
stand up and go, "Ta-da!"
And we would have gone,
"That was very good."
But I'll tell you what you don't do.
Don't make me carry you to your car!
I carried him down three
flights of stairs going,
"You did very good."
He's like, "Thank you, Jim." [Laughing]
[Chuckles]
I was, uh...
I go to a therapist...
'cause I get depressed.
So I got a therapist every now and again.
I literally had one of those
moments with my therapist
where she was saying words like,
"I'm gonna say a word and you say the
first thing that comes in your mind."
Like just out of the movies, right?
And she went, "Red," and I went, "Blue."
And then she went,
"Cooking," and I went, "Food,"
and all that type of stuff.
We went like this forever.
And then she went...
For the last question, she went,
"And what's your favorite
thing in the world?"
And I went...
"Coming on a girl's face."
Now...
Now, I could've said things like...
"Ice cream" is a good answer.
"Hank" would've been an excellent answer.
But I said, "Coming on a girl's face."
And I've had six months
to think about my answer,
and I stand by it.
- I...
- [Cheering]
I'm not proud of it.
I hate myself for thinking it.
It's such a horrible thing
to do to another human.
When a girl's on her
knees and you... It's so...
And as an atheist,
I believe in Darwin and all
the things that he wrote,
but he never had a bit
where he explained that.
There was never a bit in
his book where he went,
"When a caveman loves a cavewoman,
he'll ejaculate on her face
so that flies won't come near."
There was never that...
never that moment.
But, by golly, if it's not fun.
I find it... To...
Look, to all the girls who take a
load on their face from time to time,
may I say, "Bravo!"
Don't...
don't think what you do...
has gone unnoticed.
We notice. We appreciate your work.
I think you deserve a parade of some kind.
During Memorial Day,
after the Vietnam vets,
before the First Gulf War guys,
we could bring in,
"And here's the women who
take a load on their face."
And you could march out,
and married men would stand there
going, "God bless you, ladies."
[Audience cheering]
I enjoy your acting that you do.
The standard tongue out
and the... Like that...
I don't know why, but I enjoy...
I know it's a lie. I
know you're not excited,
but I still appreciate
the effort is what I enjoy.
I love the look because it's such
a, "Oh, jeez, I'm excited, too.
When this come hits my face, there's
a good chance I'll also orgasm.
Anything could happen in this crazy world."
But this is what redeems us as
men. This is what redeems us.
Just know that the second the
come shoots out of our cock
and hits your face,
our bodies flood with remorse.
The next 20 seconds is the
nicest we will ever be to you.
[Men whooping]
I go from being an animal
to the sweetest guy on Earth.
I'm like, "You fucking slut...
Oh, I love you. Ah...
Uh, all right. No, no, no.
Put your tongue back in. Um...
Keep your eyes shut. Just keep them shut.
Uh...
All right, I'm going to get
a towel. I'll get a towel.
I'll get you a towel.
All right.
You're a wonderful mother to our child."
[Laughs]
[Audience cheering]
See... this is what kills me.
My son will one day watch this DVD.
And I'm the guy who's meant
to teach him right from wrong,
and I'm there wiping come
off his mother's face.
I think I did something illegal
with my son the other day.
I think it might be illegal.
Tell me if this is illegal.
All right?
I'm in the shower.
My girlfriend goes off
to the gym in the morning,
and when she came back,
I was in the shower,
and Hank ran up,
and he started banging on the glass door
of the shower like, "Argh!" Like that.
And I went... [Vocalizing]
And I saw his little face
and I went, "Hello, Hankie."
And then in the condensation,
I drew a little bowtie on him...
and a little suit...
and then I gave him a
voice bubble that said,
"I love my daddy. Love, Hank."
But I did it so I could read it.
Well, of course he could
read the "K," and...
then I stepped out.
I stepped out of the bathroom and I went,
"G'day, Hankie!"
And he slapped my cock and he ran off.
Now, is that illegal?
I don't know.
Is it illegal because, A,
a child touched my cock,
or because, B, I found it really
funny and I've been telling everyone.
And I can't get angry at him
because his whole life,
he's been lying on mats
with things dangling over.
He's been training for
this his entire life.
I think I've, uh...
I think I've become American,
more American than I am Australian lately,
and there was a moment where I tipped over
where I went, "Oh, I think
like an American person now."
And I'm happy to do it. I just...
I'll tell you what happened.
I was flying around... I was
doing a tour of Australia,
and I was flying
domestically around Australia,
and I'm so used to airports and
stuff here in America that...
Okay, what happens is, when you go...
I was flying Sydney to Melbourne.
When you fly domestically in Australia,
you go up to the machine, put your name in,
prints your ticket out,
it prints your bag thing,
you put the bag thing on your bag yourself,
and then there's a
conveyor belt underneath.
You throw your bag on. Bag fucks off.
You don't speak to anyone.
Then I go up to the gate bit, and
the lady's going, "Tickets, please."
And I'm holding my ID out
like a fucking simpleton.
'Cause I get through airports quick,
man. I'm like, "Fucking there you go."
And she went, "Put your ID
away. I don't need to see that."
And I went...
"I think you do."
And she went, "I don't... Why
would I need to see your ID?"
And I said, "I might be a terrorist."
And she went, "Would showing me your
ID stop you from blowing the plane up?"
"No, I'd probably still blow the plane up."
So then I get up to the
TSA conveyor belt thing,
and I'm so good at the airports.
I'm already taking my shoes
off as I'm walking, right?
And all the Australians behind
me assume that I'm American,
and they're losing their fucking shit.
They're like, "Oh, for fuck's
sake! One of these cunts, eh?"
And the TSA guy goes,
"Hey, mate, what are you
taking your shoes off for?"
And I went...
[Shouting] "I don't know!
Maybe they're bombs?"
And he went...
"But they're not, are they?"
I put me shoes back on.
I get my laptop out.
Everyone's going mental.
And the TSA guy says,
very politely, but
extraordinarily sarcastically,
he goes, "Jeez, mate.
That's a nice computer.
Why are you showing it to everyone?"
"It might also be a bomb."
And then the guy said
the most Australian thing I've ever
heard come out of anyone's mouth ever.
He went...
"Oh, come on, mate. You
wouldn't have two bombs."
[Audience laughing]
[Chuckles]
I'm not even quite sure what that means,
but it does make some type of sense.
All right.
Oscar Pistorius.
If you haven't been following
the case, you're missing out.
This is the greatest
thing since OJ Simpson.
You're fucking missing out, mate.
If you don't know who Oscar
Pistorius is, let me fill you in.
Oscar Pistorius is a legless
man from South Africa,
known as the Blade Runner.
He ran in two Olympics,
the disabled and the
able-bodied Olympics in one year.
No one has ever done that.
He's an inspiration to
hundreds and millions
of disabled and able-bodied people alike,
and on Valentine's Day last year,
he shot and killed the
hottest girl on Earth...
and that's when he became
an inspiration to me...
'cause hot girls have been getting away
with too much shit for too fucking long.
Let that be a lesson to
all you hot girls out there.
You can't just say
whatever the fuck you want
whenever you fucking want.
[Mock tearfully] People
have feelings, you cunts.
Now, there's a lot of rumors going
around on what happened on that day.
One of the theories is that
they found in her phone...
He went through her phone,
and on her phone, he
found some text messages
from a South African rugby
player on Valentine's Day, right?
Now, I don't know if you've
ever been to South Africa,
but in South Africa, rugby is
more popular than legless running.
It goes, rugby, legless running, cricket.
Legless running's their second
sport. You wouldn't have thought that.
Anyway...
I'm going to reenact what
I believe happened that day.
To do that, I will now be
doing a South African accent.
Now I know, many of you can't
tell the difference between
my accent and a South African accent.
Here's the difference.
Picture my accent, but I'm
punching a black person.
What I'm trying to say is South
Africans are horrible people.
So...
she's coming out of the shower.
She's been drying her hair. She's
listening to Rodriguez or something.
She comes out.
He's laying on the bed.
He looks up at her, he's
holding the phone, and he goes,
[In South African accent]
"What the fuck is this?
I've been through your phone.
You have been texting a rugby player."
And she's like, "Oh!
Fuck you!
Who the fuck do you think you are?"
"Who am I?
I'm Oscar Pistorius, the greatest
legless runner that has ever been.
That's who the fuck I am."
"Well, I would rather
be with a rugby player.
At least he is a whole man, not
a three-quarter man like you."
- [Audience exclaiming]
- I know.
[Audience laughing]
"Oh! Fuck you!"
"No! Fuck you! I'm leaving you!"
And then she storms out of the room,
and then he was like...
"You fucking bitch! [Grunts]
I hate you!
[Grunting]
You will rue the day...
that you left Oscar
Pistorius, the Blade Runner!
Don't go anywhere!
[Grunting]
I hate you!"
That's where he keeps his legs.
All right.
Then he put the blades on.
"Oh, you're in trouble, missy. I tell you.
I go to my gun safe."
She locked herself in the bathroom.
He shot her through the bathroom door.
Seems like overkill, doesn't it?
Bathrooms only have
little tiny locks on them,
but Oscar's one of the few men on Earth
that couldn't kick the door in, right?
He was wearing the blades, so...
Boing! Ah!
So...
I think Oscar will probably go to prison.
Now...
in South Africa, one in
four people have AIDS.
I assume it may even be worse
in the prison population.
Now, can I say this? Look...
I've never raped a man.
I hate that I have to put "a man"
in that sentence, but whatever.
I've never raped a man, but...
if I was going to rape a man,
it would be a legless Olympian...
'cause in prison, it's all about
getting one up on other people,
and making people think
you're tough and all that.
Like, "You want to fucking rape me?
I just raped an Olympian, bitch.
Is that what you fucking want?"
There'd be a wonderful moment...
when you're in the showers
and he was crawling away like
the end of a Terminator movie.
[Chuckling]
You know what I like about that joke?
So often when you tell a joke,
the rapist is the villain in the story,
but not in that one.
Not in that one.
He's the hero.
All right, we have to get going soon.
Before I leave,
- I thank you very much for coming.
- [Audience groaning]
No, I said, "soon," not "over."
It's just soon, you cunts, so calm down.
[Chuckles]
[Man whistles]
I always...
I always find that weird when
someone, like, whistles like that.
What do they think is going to happen?
Like, I'm going to go,
"Fucking you know me, mate.
I was enjoying claps and cheers,
but what I needed was a
high-pitched squeal noise.
Thank God you came along
to pick up my spirits."
[Man] Love you!
All right, final story.
Now, I was in South Africa again.
Jeez, I don't think I'll
be working in South Africa
after this special comes out.
I used to do, like, one tour
in South Africa every year,
and I just don't know if
I'll be invited this time.
They'll be like, [In South African
accent] "We don't like him. He's no good."
Anyway, so, I'm in South Africa,
and I had to fly back from
Cape Town to Los Angeles,
which is, like, a 26-hour flight.
You've to go up to London and go across.
Cunt of a trip.
Um...
But it was all right 'cause
I had a business class ticket,
so I didn't give a fuck.
And when I travel economy,
I try to dress up nice
'cause I like to look good
in case someone recognizes
me and I might get an upgrade.
But when I've already got
a business class ticket,
I try to look like a bag of shit...
'cause it's important to me that
everyone else in business
class doesn't want me there
and they're annoyed by my presence.
So...
I'm wearing a white T-shirt
that's got brown stains on
it with a hole in the side.
I'm wearing these small shorts
with just one testicle hanging out.
So, anyway, I go up to the counter, up
to the business thing with the thing,
and I go, "Hello," and the lady goes,
[In South African accent] "Oh,
Mr. Jefferies, I'm so sorry,
but you have been downgraded."
I said, "You what now?"
She goes, "Business class is
full. You have been downgraded."
And I said, "I understand
that business class is full.
I bought one of the
tickets that made it full."
And she went, "I'm sorry,
sir. There's nothing I can do."
And then I just went, "Are
you fucking kidding me?"
Now, you know when you're dealing
with customer service people,
and they want you to swear,
'cause as soon as you swear,
they don't have to engage with you anymore.
They can act like they're the first
adult never to hear a swear word,
and they can get really offended, right?
So I went, "Are you fucking kidding me?"
And she went, "Please do
not speak to me that way!
I have done nothing wrong!"
And I said, "Are you,
a white South African,
telling me you've done nothing wrong?"
Anyway...
tensions rose.
The manager comes over. Big fat
cunt called Simon Fulcher, right?
He walks over and goes,
[In South African accent] "What
is wrong here? What is wrong?"
And I said, "I bought
a business class ticket
and I want a business class ticket."
And he goes, "What do you want me
to do? Make a new chair for you?
There are no more seats.
I can't do anything."
He goes, "I'll tell you what I can do.
Go up to the executive
lounge. Have some peanuts.
Enjoy a beverage. Listen to Rodriguez,
and if something opens up, we will
move you back up to business class.
So I thought, "There's nothing I can do."
So I walk off with my ticket. I'm
walking through the airport like,
"Fucking British Airways,
bunch of fucking cunts." Right?
I get up to the counter.
And the woman behind the
counter said, "Tickets, please."
And I hand over my ticket and she goes,
[In South African accent] "I'm sorry, sir,
but this is for business
class passengers only.
Your ticket says 'economy'
on it." And I said...
[Inhales sharply]
"I bought a business class ticket,
but you people have downgraded..."
And as I was doing my little speech,
she looked past me and went, "Next."
[Audience exclaiming]
"Listen here, you fucking cunt."
[Audience laughing]
All right?
Now, you say "cunt" in any foreign country,
people lose their fucking shit.
Security came from everywhere.
I was going, "Don't you
fucking come near me, cunt!"
And I said, "I want to speak
to Simon Fulcher," like I'm...
And they go, "All right."
They ring the manager
up, and then they go...
He goes, "Is it the pale Australian
man?" And the guy went, "Yes."
He goes, "We've had problems
with him. Let him through." Right?
So I go through. I'm sitting
there, I'm eating my peanuts.
And I'm just angry now, going,
"Fucking British Airways.
Fucking cunts, fucking..."
Like that.
And in walks in a group of
Americans, about 30 of them.
You know the type, right? They all...
And whenever I see Americans abroad...
I'll do my impersonation
of any American abroad.
When Americans are abroad, you're
just pointing out shit you see.
You're just walking around going,
[In American accent] "Oh, this is great!
Look at that. That's a
chair right there. Okay.
Oh, what's that over there?
Okay. Wonderful. Great."
Right?
And this group walked in,
and one of the women in the
group went like this, she went,
[In American accent] "Did anyone else see
that Australian guy speaking
to that lady out there?
Some people have no class."
And I put my head around
the pylon, and I went,
"You can fuck off and all!
You don't know what I've been
through! I've been downgraded!"
And as I said that,
18 other people who were given
the same lie that I was given,
that they were going to be the next
people promoted up to business class,
the penny dropped.
None of us are getting promoted.
They all lied to us, and we
formed an angry militia in seconds.
It was like a scene out of Braveheart,
and they all stood up and
went, "Fucking downgraded!"
And the woman in the group was doing this,
"Don't speak to me that way. Who
the hell do you think you are?"
And all the men in the group were like,
"Hey, why don't you shut the fuck up?
Just shut the fuck up."
♪ It doesn't matter These
people seem very angry, so ♪
And a guy breaks from the group
and he tries to calm everyone down.
And, sometimes, Americans, sometimes,
you can seem a little insincere.
And he came up and he went,
[In American accent] "Hey. Hey.
Yeah, I get it. [Exhales sharply]
Downgraded, yeah.
That really grinds my
gears, I tell you that.
Yeah, I would write a
strongly-worded letter.
I really would."
And then I thought, at
least this guy's being nice,
and I said, "Look, mate,
don't worry about it.
It's not like it's your fault."
And I said, "Why are you
in such a big group anyway?"
And he goes, "Oh, we're
in Neil Diamond's band.
That's Neil Diamond's backup singer
you just called a cunt there."
And as he said that,
Neil Diamond walked around the
corner like a fucking superhero...
and I reacted like he was
one. I went, "Neil Diamond!"
And Neil Diamond went,
[In husky voice] "Hey, what's going on?"
And then, for a second there,
there was a bit of my brain that thought
maybe Neil Diamond could solve problems.
And I went, "Neil!
Me and all these people,
we've been downgraded!"
And Neil went, "Oh! Oh, right.
Uh, well, maybe that's our fault.
We decided to come back a day early."
"You can fuck off and all, Neil Diamond!"
And then a fight breaks out amongst the
Neil Diamond band and the downgraded.
Punches are thrown. Not by me.
I don't know if you have the Internet,
but I'm not much of a fighter.
I'm an excellent scurrier-awayer.
I get down.
"Hey, what have you got there? Hiya!"
Anyway, the airport police came.
Three people were arrested
from the downgraded...
but three people were arrested
from the Neil Diamond band,
and that meant that three seats
opened up in business class.
[Audience cheering]
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
very much. Good night. Appreciate it.
[Audience cheering]
[Upbeat music playing]
Thank you.
Go home. Let's have a drink. Bye.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com