Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Are you ready?
Ready.
Kingdom called Samarza.
Samarza.
The King's bloodline.
King's family...
...must die.
Present day
Present Day
Kingdom of Samarza - Located in the Himalayas
A young soldier accompanies the King
during the last days of peace
Adam, ride next to me.
Your Majesty,
I'm just a soldier.
I could never ride next to you.
Adam , some day you'll make a
fine soldier.
Some are born great.
Some achieve greatness.
And some have greatness trust
upon them.
October 10th , the United Nations
has rejected our need for help
Our situation becomes desperate
with every hour.
In a few days ,
The Skanji Empire
will unleash their entire fleet.
Today they send the taste
of their wrath.
I am paralyzed of disbelief.
A part of me dies inside.
Their war is to eliminate our kind
and rule over our land.
We have no means of fighting back.
We are not violent people.
Nadia was born into culture
where women were treated like animals.
beaten and discarded.
She was thrown into world
of violence.
And the only way to survive
was to be stronger , smarter...
to kill.
He was ordered to assassinate our king.
and all the heirs to our throne
One by one , the heirs fell..
Until only the king remained...
...my poor king.
breathing his last breath ,
in my arms.
I know without the heir to
the throne
The Skanjis will forever rule us
But then he whispers
one hope,
One child, in a far away land.
Nadia sets out for this land
to kill this remaining heir.
I am Adam Arthavan
An ordinary soldier
in king's army.
what makes ME special
Is the king spoke this final
words to me .
Adam, come closer.
listen carefully
the great duty.
The last hope is upon you.
You are ours people only hope.
protect my last
remaining child.
The last princess.
NINJA'S CREED
National Cathedral, WASHlNGTON DC
To save the princess,
I must first start by finding the
royal maid.
Only she would know the location
of her Highness.
A royal maid to the Abassi Kingdom.
RIGHT LANE EXIT ONLY
Sorry , business or pleasure?
Pleasure.
Some girl I know is going to die.
Best friends , friends forever...
Katie,
second grade,
she is so hot.
- dude she is so hot.
- oh hell no.
- Andrea.
- hey look it's Jan.
- Heads up.
- she's gonna catch it.
Oh yes , did you see that?
You know the one with the
Jean-Luc Picard?
The dude who is the captain.
You know what I'm talking about?
BUt Jean-Luc Picard is bald.
Haven't you ever thought:
Why is this guy bald?''
I mean they are like 1000 years
into future and the guy is bald.
I mean wouldn't they come up with
some kind of oil or soemthing
to cure baldness by then?
Why? You losing hair aligator?
What? I'm sorry what did you say?
Is it receiding on the side
or at the top?
...the game.
That's how we do it.
- You know.
- Alright man.
See ya.
- Jim is coming over tonight.
- you're like his next thing?
He broke up with Amy like
three weeks ago.
- You still wanna go to the mall?
- No.
I wanna buy this really cute blue
halter top.
- I really need to take a shower.
- Shower later.
You said you wanna get
your nails done.
No way.
What are you doing?
What are YOU doing?
There are people, they can see you.
Yeah well you won't let me
smoke in your room.
It's your move.
- How's Jan?
- Good.
Just good?
I can't help but think she is
missing out though you know?
I mean , she can't say things
to me , her dad.
But she might say to her mom,
right?
Doug, you're great dad.
You don't wanna her the things
she says to her mom.
She's a teenage girl.
- What do we have here?
- Don't.
Come on,let's hear it.
Doug, it's the rules.
Come on, let's hear it.
You are the champion.
Thought that the real maid
was older.
Excuse me?
You've mistaken me for
someone else.
The King always felt threatened
by the evil Skanji Empire...
so I was afraid
constantly that ...
one day his family could
be eliminated.
Then, 17 years ago
secretly ...
gave his seventh child
for adoption ...
to ''American Guardian''.
The princess grew up as an
American
never knowing
her royal descent.
And only one person in our
country
know the whereabouts of the
princess ...
a Real maid
You.
The King always felt threatened
by the evil Skanji Empire
I came to protect
the Princess.
You must feel so special
with what you know now.
Rest assured, the princess is safe.
Only the American guardian
knows where she is.
The American guardian is now
her father.
Only he should be concerned
with her safety.
No one else will ever find out
Who she really is.
That is an oath I gave to his
Majesty,
An oath I will never break.
Especialmente no por
un soldado COMUN.
I thank you for your time.
We have a trouble.
We have a big problem.
How could this have happened?
Dad you rock.
Because I promised
she is gonna move upside.
Do me a favour.
Yes.
The American guardian.
One of the king's soldiers just
visited me in the chappel.
He could be working with
the Skanji army.
We need to involve the police.
You must tell her who she is.
It's very important that Jan
doesn't know.
She get's worried for nothing.
You know. -I know , I also know
that you care so much for her
but circumstances have just changed.
I know but I don't want her life
turn upisde down.
You put her to great risk.
Do you have any idea what Nadia
is capable of?
Do you have any idea
what Nadia did to the king's family
in Samarza?
I'm giving you one hour
to tell her who she really is,
and then I'm calling the police.
Aviation 1, Aviation 1,
we have a 10-4-4
In the Bathesda area in sector 3.
Ground unita are requesting our
assistance.
Aviation , copy.
Lead us to 9-2-5 area.
It is park Bethesda, two
blocks away.
All units to the Bethesda area,
responding to 10-10
and 10-15.
At least one person is confirmed
to be stabbed.
- Jan.
- GET OUT.
Oh I'm sorry.
Sorry I didn't know you
were naked.
Dad I'm not naked.
You're not going out are you ?
I'm a big girl now.
Chill out because I'm not
going out now , okey?
Good , we can play Boggle.
No, Jim is coming over.
Cute Jim?
- I didn't know you find guys cute.
- Uhm.
Dating?
Where did that come from?
dad , I bet you will be like this
even when I am 30 years old,
aren't you?
An international news,
there is growing concern
in the entire region of south Asia
as Samarza is the second country
the Skanji empire has invaded
within the last six months.
Now we've got all that clear.
And without a living heir to
the kingdom of Samarza,,
The people have no choice but
to accept this brutal regime.
- Jan?
- Hey.
My friend has just came down
from LA.
- Where are you?
- Quit fooling around man.
What are you doing?
I'm on the phone.
Sorry. Anyways,
Should spend some time with them.
Oh , err , are you both getting
come over?
Do you mind if we do this
another time?
Cuz we are just gonna chill out
and do the guys thing you know.
- You know how it is.
- Ah, yeah.
Yes of course, it's not a problem.
- Okay,cool. See ya.
- Hello?
Maybe if you were blonde.
Two women and one child are now
confirmed dead
in the park Bethesda murders.
We still do not know if police
have any leads.
Doug, you're great dad.
She is a teenage girl.
You don't wanna hear the things
she would say to her mom.
I'm teaching her how to play.
You're teaching her how to play?
That's so good.
Come on.
Come on this way.
She's pretty good for a beginner
isn't she?
- Yes.
- Yes she is.
with the killer still at large
Police are advising all residents
of Bethesda
to take basic precautions
and Immediately report
any suspicios activity.
We're gonna take a break,we're
out of the news.
Don't go away , we'll be
right back.
Run to the window.
Come on, run.
Go.
Run.
I know you're scared but you
must be brave.
I'm here to protect you.
you do not know
who you are.
Look, you've got the
wrong person.
I have the right person.
You are the King's seventh child...
The only living heir
to the Abassi dinasty.
I'm not what you think I am.
Who are you?
- Please. No.
- Please calm down.
At your right leg you have
birthmark, resembling a heart.
Let me go.
Only the real princess has
that birthmark.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Stay close to me.
It's safe.
I will be outside.
What the hell do I do?
911, what is your emergency?
Connect me to the
police department.
The police are on their way.
Trust me.
You're going to need their help.
The person who attacked you is
an assassin.
Her name is Nadia.
And she has never failed a mission.
But you managed to escape
from her.
Do you know why?
Cuz you are not an opponent
to her.
You're a pray.
She doesn't want just, kill you.
She wants to enjoy it..
So if you want to go out there,
alone...
Go.
Or you can stay with me
if you want to live.
If you do not believe me,
call your american father.
Please leave a message
after the signal.
Dad, pick up the phone.
I'll get back , just don't
freak out, okey?
I was attacked at home.
All the windows are broken.
I just didn't know what to do.
I didn't know where you were.
I'm safe , okey?
Just come and get me.
I'm at 1.200th block of
the Massachussets Av.
I am Adam Arthavan.
I was sent by his Majesty,
Niaz Abassi II,
To protect you.
If you want to evade such
injuries,
listen to me carefully.
You are from Samarza.
I'm at 1.200th block of
the Massachussets Av...
The assassin that tried to kill
you belongs to this tribe.
This has what to do with me?
5 days ago,
they attacked the palace
and killed your entite family.
Princess, our people have
lost all hope.
But if they knew an Abassi
were alive...
it would give them the momentum
and the heart to fight back.
You have royal blood.
And that symbol is more powerful
than an entire army.
How did you know...
about my birthmark?
I found the king just
before he died.
In those moments ,
he told me everything
about you.
Look, I'm not a princess or,
whatever.
I'm just an ordinary girl.
Well, ordinary girl,
Some achieve greatness.
And some heave greatness
trusted uppon them.
Your father was more than
just a king to me.
Your Highness.
Restricted area
NO SMOKING
Stay here.
Understand?
Okay.
- Hey buddy.
- Hold right there.
- Take out your guns.
- Take a step back.
- Is the building secured?
- Building's closed.
- What are you doing here sir?
- I'm the one that called.
- Take out your guns.
- I want you to take step back.
You don't understand.
Is the building secured?
- Listen to my orders.
- take a step back.
Put your hands on the wall. Turn around
and put your hands on the wall, sir..
The building is closed in
this after hours.
I don't need questioning.
What are you doing here?
Take a deep breath and calm down.
- Freeze.
- Now put your hands slowly...
All units, repórtense
the Massachusetts Avenue building.
Officers. Units need
immediate assistance.
- Drop your weapon.
- Do not move.
Units at the Massachussets Av.
come in, adelante.
Where are you?
Do you copy?
Get your radio.
What is going on?
You are the best they
could send?
RUN!!!
All units at the
Friendship Heights,
respond  immediately.
There are reports of an explosion
on Massachusetts Av. and 34th St.
Respond  immediately, all unis
respond  immediately.
Dad.
Let go off me.
It's me.
This is the first place they
would look for you.
I just wanna get to my dad.
- Calm down Princess.
- My name is Jan.
I'm not a frickin princess.
No...
The king entrusted me with a task
greater than you or me.
That is all that I know.
Now I will go in there
and find your american father.
But I don't want you to
be anywhere near.
Listen to me.
Take this road and go to
other white building down
the street.
I will bring your american
father to you.
Do what he would want you to do.
The Leaders of the Skanji empire
consist of the handful of ruthless
military generals.
Political analysts have
predicted
that if the Skanji Empire is able
to establish it's rule
in Samarza,
It will immediately strike at the
neighbouring countries.
of Myanmar, Bután
and Nepal.
Thus far , the USA
is the country which has
demanded Skanji Empire
withdraw from Samarza
and all other occupying
territories.
You don't want to
wake him up.
Aviation 3.
I think this area is clear.
Just a little smoke
nothing more.
not much movement.
Alfa 1, return to the site
of explosion.
They need you out there.
Over.
Jan. listen to me.
You are special.
A wise man once told me
some are born great,
some achieve greatness,
and some have greatness
trusted upon them.
I have to go now.
It's very important
Samarza.
Princess?
If you look hard enough ...
Only if you look hard enough ...
you'll find what you're s
earching for.
Adam, talk to me.
Ah you have something going on
in that pretty little head
of yours.
How you know my name?
How come you're not here, ha?
Let me ask you somethin , what
you work here?
I locked up the exhibition room.
How you know my name?
Are you serious?
See you tomorrow, Adam.
- Princess.
- Where's my dad?
- We have to go , we have to go now.
- Just tell me. There is no time.
Answer me.
He's on his way here.
- Princess, we have to go.
- Why did king give me up?
Why did he give up?
Why?
His Majesty did not give you up.
He sent you on a journey,
for a reason.
And that reason is gonna save
our people.
How is she finding us?
- We must go.
- No.
Go, give me your hand.
Come on, give me your hand.
I cannot run any more.
The Skanji Empire
will rule Samarza.
But first, your princess
must die.
I'm sorry, I wish I could
be stronger.
Princess, we have to go now.
Please, I'm sorry but I can't.
OK.
No more running.
Are you disappointed in me?
Close your eyes.
- What?
- Close your eyes.
At times, even I thought I
could not go on.
I could not go on.
Looking at you now,
I see your courage.
I see Samarza's heart.
I see that I must end this.
Now.
For freedom.
My father was a blacksmith.
I tested every sword he ever made.
Leave and I will let you live.
Fight and you will surely die.
You betrayed the King.
You do not know what happened.
Look at what you've become.
For what?
You do not know what happened!
What happened, then?
You are pure evil.
Impressive...
You are going to find out
what happened...
Very soon.
It's beautiful.
My next strike, won't be
beautiful.
Dammit.
Adam,
the line between good and evil
is so blurred.
Sometimes you can barely see it.
- Boom.
- Adam.
It's over.
Oh, God.
Wait, what ...?
- Something's wrong.
Adam!
?
Answer me.
What does Nadia look like?
The line between good and evil
is so blurred.
How is she finding us?
You do not know what happened.
She was ordered to
assassinate our king.
My poor king
breathing his last breath.
...to assassinate our king...
There's one girl I know.
Some girl I know is going to die.
Wait, what?
Run , run...
Go.
RUN!!!
JUST RUN!!!
Why?
Wake up.
Yes, Adam.
I am you
and you are me.
together , we are
the perfect weapon.
You killed the king.
You killed his family.
Ironic, isn't it Adam?
Now we must finish our mission.
Adamn, ready?
You do not exist.
No.
Princess.
Adam.
What are you doing?
Adam, wait a minute.
Adam.
Adam, stop.
Why?
Wait.
Adam.
Adam, please.
Dad.
Jan, where's my kiss?
Dad, I'll give you two later.
I told you to give two later.
Just beautiful.
The assassin.
Well done, Nadia.
Thank you, Great General.
The Empire is Skanji
proud of you.
Salutations to Skanji Empire.
Empire send me a mission.
I give the orders to good Adam.
He does not remember what I say,
but you summoned ...
...
The evil Nadia.
Combine good with evil...
the perfect weapon.
One day the Empire will
dominate the world.
Go, cleanse your soul.
Adam...
For now, forget everything
from last night..
Forget... forget...
Forget...
6 hours later
Forget everything
since last night.
A massive explosion
rocked Washington D.C.
at 2:1 3 AM.
The explosion originated
in the University building
on Massachusetts Avenue.
Firefighters are
currently fighting
residual fire that was
caused by the explosion.
Ffficers of the Washington DC
police department
were involved in shootout
just before explosion occured.
All five officers present at that time
are confirmed
dead.
A single father was killed in his
house late last night.
The police are still unclear
if this murder was related...
Those paintings are so cool
uncle Rochy.
It's an exhibition.
You know, the art, the culture,
the entire whole experience...
Hey, boss.
Sorry to disturb you,
but that security guard is
on the phone.
He sounds really depressed.
Rochester speaking.
Hey boss, I don't think I'm
coming today.
Alright.
What happened?
I bruised my shoulder a
little bit.
I went to the doctor and he
said it's sleepwalking.
You hurt yourself before you know.
It was also sleepwalking right?
I should be fine.
In next coupple of days
I'll come in.
Answer me something.
What do you work here ,
in my building?
It's monday.
You wake up in the morning,
you brush your teeth
take a quick cup of coffe,
Go to your job.
And I know you had many better
career options,
but you continue to stay here,
why?
I like being security guard.
Boss, I'm not the type of guy
who wants to save the world.
The bag number one there..
is 678.
678. Let me fix
this belt.
A single father was killed at
his house
late last night.
the police are still unclear if
this murder
was related to Massachussetts
Av. building,
which occured only half a mile
from the murdered man house.
The victim is teenage daughter, is
still missing
and the police  are not discarding the
possibility of kidnapping.
11th century: 'An extraordinary
life'' by Pär Olofsson
Security Identification
So majestic.
Extraordinary.
Come on ,darling.
Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Hey boss.
Oh you're back.
Hey Kathy. Did you see all these
wonderful paintings?
- Yeah.
- Did you have a good time?
Yeah ,you should see new Colieans.
Yeah, that are new copies from India,
beautiful.
Kathy, you know,
kings, queens,
princes and princesses ...
I wish we had them
in America.
I wish I was a princess.
There are no more princesses.
But you are as pretty as princess.
Listen, Adam, I wanted to tell you.
Do not take it personally
what I said
the other day by telephone,
OK?
I mean, I do that.
I say things I should not.
It is not my business to get into,
so please forgive me.
Boss, err, you believe
too much in me.
But I know it's because you
care for me.
So I don't mind,
you know,
you get personal.
Thank you.
- Bye.
I told him I am not the
type of guy
that want's to save the world.
I lied.
My life is every man's
biggest fear,
To be ordinary.
No, stop, stop.
Stop.
I know her.
How could...?
The cathe... the cathedral.
The cathedral.
I was there.
I was looking for someone.
Something about the painting.
I really believed that
the kindgom was real.
The kingdom needed to
be saved.
Save this realm ...
Princess, Nadia ...
was real.
I imagined that I was
the assassin.
Visited a royal maid.
I followed her.I remember I
followed her to the park.
Wait, wait.
There was no maid.
But there was a man.
He was not my imagination.
He wasn't talking to anyone.
He was...
I followed the man
who led me to...
an ordinary girl.
How did you know
about my birthmark??
What did I do?
Why you look so sad?
It's like you lost
something precious.
Adam.
Are you ready?
- No.
- are you ready,
Adam Arthavan?
I killed her.
... ready to become
a great warrior?
And a great murderer.
What could be more great?
Save the only hope
of our people.
My life
is the greatest fear
of every man.
To be...
Ordinary.
2 HOURS LATER
The American Guardian.
NINJA'S CREED
Translated by Bull_the_Great
Adjusted by Vasago
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org