Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Tomo por mientras lo no enseñado...
por la mañana:
para mañana se cuidara...
de las cosas de si mismo...
el dia final será su demonio  .
Matthew 6:34
Carl to say something...
Let me ask you something first:
They describe me as a B?
Well, I think that.
You know what?
Carl we are 800 lbs gorilla.
We sell the starter.
What do they do?
The bluff is Carl.
Even Lucy does not think so.
Hold my wife calling.
Hi honey, I'm late today.
I'm with Carl...
Did they?
We take her home,
that will be better.
They will never want to leave.
Hey Gab, I switch now, okay?
I love you.
Carl it is so, listen...
I'm brand new.
I have a formula.
Change the formula
and lose your listeners.
It is as simple as that.
People listen to who I am...
and what I say...
and nobody wants to listen to a
man 's hair ball in his mouth.
This is radio.
If you want to talk, call your
and talk about it.
And can you explain
anyone who listens...
you 't likes that
The FCC thus you slijmt.
You can 't just say.
Bye.
Hurry up friend.
You owe me five.
Did they now
put on the payroll?
I swear Lucy succeed everywhere.
Logan. Hey.
Nice that you visit.
I thought Gil
it would take you?
Not as long as I live.
What about with you Max...
your tunes tonight?
Logan Well I do not know?
I was planning
go to sleep tonight...
to ignore what tomorrow
weather will bring.
Ignore 's division.
Hi Doc.
Maggie, hold the door against?
I'm not late.
Do not say that.
Greetings from the powerful.
I'm your host Logan Heart Burn.
The man with all the answers
of your pathetic life.
The reason why
at night awake.
The personality
you can not resist.
The psychiatrist
you can not afford.
Welcome to Harper.
Burns talked about...
I am accompanied
employed by your favorite...
Gilbert dibs Brickman.
You are much too kind.
How do you feel tonight,
Gilman?
I'm ready to buy
and to work with.
It is not about your sex life,
This is my show.
All lines are open.
Ready for action.
How do you feel private?
I feel its a little...
paranoid my friend.
You know?
It stinks here...
So you must hate mail
read again.
No, probably about my
ex without stamps.
It is something else, something that
troubling since my childhood.
And why 't get in me
comes up is...
because I was certain
in traffic and I...
I did not prepare
for the evening show.
It looks
that evening full of...
encourage and abet.
And that high entertainment
makes us...
The number one
most listened show...
in the pus.
Most.
Yes, the world's third
best training...
I'm right back to questions
answer...
immediately after these words.
That was a close call,
was it not?
Not my fault I had Gaby's brother
to 't airport.
You brought my family is there.
Because you 've never asked.
Because I knew you would say no.
That is not fair,
I took Gaby's brother.
You do a lot for Gaby
you never did for me.
I made you my producer.
I hired you to fill the time.
Back in ten.
I brought you this far because I
made us number one.
That was a part of the
separation agreement.
What that means, because you my best
lawyer, you are my better man?
Do not make me laugh.
One.
Yes we are back.
This is Logan and Heart Burn
next five hours we are talking about...
paranoiac a.
Paranoia.
I hope that I did well predicted.
I'm not sure.
What?
Are you in shape?
It is, Tashmahall.
The Tashmahall makes you paranoid?
Yes, and I will tell you why.
Please do that.
Have you ever, I mean seriously.
Have you ever seen a picture not
taken from the front...
You know with 't pool
on the front?
I do not make jokes now,
't make me afraid.
Consider this to:
Have you ever seen
large 't there?
Well I think about it, no.
Is it real or is someone
world fooled.
What do you what it is?
A cardboard sign...
what is painted and
onto a palace looks?
Maybe?
And that makes you?
That is why I am so paranoid.
I mean 'it's a famous palace?
I recommend it to be in India.
I do not know whether
Royal residence?
Is it a sort of White House...
or a Vegas casino?
You know...
I've never really there
deep thought.
And I'm for...
my loving friend.
For clarity and respect to create
of the things we do not think.
I think: you easy
can be found online.
No, make me redundant here.
You are paranoid.
Or not?
Yes, and I am not alone,
therefore, they may call us and...
tell you why so
paranoid America?
You mean the guy
who lives opposite me?
He sits on his porch
knife sharpening and stare...
every time I pass.
You live in a guest who
his porch sharpens his knife?
Yes.
And he's creepy.
I'm afraid that he
One day passes by...
puts me...
and then for a cup of sugar asks.
In that order? Yes.
That is something to worry about.
Okay, the lines light up.
Why America
are you so paranoid?
Caller number two:
You are now in the broadcast.
Cat.
Did h. ..
Why does Mrs.
cat food you paranoid?
I look at the different flavors
they have...
and I see beef
't look stand.
So you is concerned,
in beef flavor cat food?
Yes. It is a strange thing
a cat to enter, do not you?
I mean, I understand chicken and fish...
because that is my cat dead.
Cats kill fish?
I can imagine that you 't
complex math is...
but he would 't easy
may in its claws.
They hunt not something dead.
You cat does not come from Texas?
If the cat food manufacturers
Our cats beef perform...
which will "end up then?
Who know, really?
Maybe it is, as
into a film in 1970...
where people use them for food?
Solid Green?
Paranoid.
Our first caller is not only
paranoid but totally insane.
That is my record are
is not it Gil?
I think so.
If you roast cow cat
balls or ears eat, be happy.
Be glad it's not free
than 49 cents per can.
I hope you think I
gene who have food...
Lady, you're an idiot.
Thanks for the call.
Well there is someone who 's real
has reason to be paranoid?
Caller number three:
you are now...
Heart Burn with Logan, and Bikkel Brickman.
I must admit Logan,
I'm paranoid about aliens.
Aliens...
Are you afraid they the Mexican border
cross beef cat and you perform?
No I see people in shows
are taken to the room...
and there were things
stopped in their rectum.
Rectum, damn man kill them.
Please sir,
This is a family show.
Sorry. It is only...
I hear these things all the time...
and it is not alone in the country...
but also in the city.
They take you into their ship
and experiment with u. ..
do what they please.
Have you ever heard of crop circles?
Yes, I did.
And what do you know what they are?
I do not know.
This is another good example.
Okay good.
But just for fun,
what is the aim?
Perhaps it is their way
for sending messages...
they try to communicate with us.
I thought you would say,
I knew you would say.
Let's put it this way:
If these aliens
want to talk to us...
communicate,
say: pull...
secret information from us.
Sir, you know how
looks like an alien!
Aliens have a rectum?
Burck? Have aliens that?
You sir are a moron.
If you're so paranoid about aliens,
you must not watch much television.
Why our show is always
alien involved in pornography?
That's what I also wonder.
Okay, we go further.
Our next caller...
Wijgerde to give his real name.
Okay, let's call him...?
Fred's your turn.
What makes you so paranoid?
Muslims.
That 's good.
Fred, would you be more specific
want to be?
They blow their own for a
Some of our soldiers to kill.
Much Muslims...
inflated his own yet.
Maybe something else?
The way they talk?
Of their dark skin?
Their body odor.
I mean, they keep goats.
It's the fact that they are obsessed
have to hate us.
You know?
Fred I think you have something.
Perhaps that is why
they move to America?
Closer to us?
You ever heard to old adage:
Keep your friends close...
and your enemies closer.
I mean they live in
Middle East more than 10,000 years...
and still
they can not live together.
Have you seen them live?
I would also be jealous of America.
They live in a country full of oil.
But living in houses of beetroot
The move by the smallest earthquake.
But I think that not much
buildings to provide in...
In a country full of
C4 and barbarians and murderers themselves.
Logan you know what your talking about?
It is his wife she would see him.
Tell her that he call back.
Gaby I call you during commercials, okay?
Military leader and hate everyone,
it does not on its way.
I hear what you say sir.
Haternij is a terrible thing
no one does good.
Is that not true, Gil?
-Yes...
Perhaps is it the business man
who sells American flags?
Good point.
Above all, you do not fool around.
So you people hate Fred
the Middle East?
I just said: anyone who does not...
So you say you hate them?
That said, I can not twist the facts,
you present the words...
Since you have the people.
Fred hates Muslims.
Fred hates Arabs
Fred hates Persians.
Fred probably hate the Jews.
And this just after I have said...
haternij that nobody does well.
Fred expresses his true thoughts...
America and shows real voice.
Paranoia:
Fear of the unknown...
what will emerge from
the shade and we will intervene...
and taking away from us as we love.
Fear of Japanese technology
that depends on our ears...
as a claustrofobiezak.
We are right back after these messages.
- The Tashmahall...
lies not in the Middle East?
What is that?
What is an ear thing?
That.
Yes.
It is a bluetooth for my cellphone!
I need to poop.
You gonna tell him that Gaby
has called? No, not yet.
We have a good evening.
Tell him:
I expect him, okay?
You say it.
I can not go.
We can not stop.
They sit right behind us.
I did what I would put out.
-You must stop here.
I want to die by their hands.
You make it without me.
Please, stop it here.
Do you want me to do?
No.
I am his brother. I do it.
We are back in twenty.
You Vernin on a line that is paranoid
that his government phone tapping.
And a man on line two, who wants to know
why you hate Muslims so much.
And guy who is offended because
You have not answered call.
A few others talked about
a kind of attack.
What line does Vernin?
Line one.
Four three...
And we are back and...
the one who now tune...
our topic tonight is...
paranoia.
On one line we have
an old friend.
You're turn.
Hi Logan, Gil
I am Vernin.
Our favorite caller who thinks
his phone is tapped.
Again.
Vernin you already
look under your bed?
I am sure that somewhere there
Your flashlight is missing.
I have a problem...
I am concerned to make.
All clicks in a conversation,
all the time when I'm on a call.
I think the FBI tapping my line.
Show an interest.
Vernin you considered the possibility,
you might have a bad phone?
Or skip that and go
you right off at the FBI?
I am quite sure
that the FBI is.
I think Vernin a good point.
Do you think you are so high on their radar is
they kind of research.
I think I am, there is
no other explanation.
I smoke weed sometimes and I...
Do not say that.
I would if I drain his line
his last conversations was heard.
Vernin your phone is not tapped.
I think that!
You think?
Your phones are tapped.
I think the president you tapping.
I must go.
I hear a kind of noise outside.
And put the Minister of Defense
greetings from me.
Vernin Day!
Yes I am quite sure that
FBI listening to this program.
Our next caller is now.
Hello? Am I in the broadcast?
He he easy. You sound...
whacked on the face.
Besides the building.
There is a kind of attack after
I think the game started.
People are crazy here.
- I saw them running along in front of me.
It is everyone in the street.
It is a bit early to
championship to celebrate, do not you?
Should not they have
three races this year?
The police is there, but they do
nothing. Calm down.
I'm not joking man!
It is here in the city, you can
not see from your window?
Gil? Let's go to the window.
Okay people stay with us.
Look out the window?
Sorry buddy I see
just buildings.
We hear sirens.
And I thought not.
They run like mad crazy.
Well people this is not a family show...
but no freak show.
Check the locks on the door...
and we again
work.
Great not only the FCC hates us,
but God has it in our targeting.
Sorry people the light
out in the studio.
Burck I talked to someone?
The back-up check everything
and the computers are blocked.
Yes people, I believe that God still
saves. The lights are entered again.
Maybe the aliens
Lo for us?
I mean, they love
that flashing thing.
Why they show so much hate?
There are many reasons.
Let us try to go back
to the community here.
Caller number four you are now.
Please save me here.
Can I get no television,
this is real?
I am beginning to think that paranoia is not
was a good topic for tonight.
I ask myself the Gilman...
where would the city when I
imparted no sense?
I ask me all the time.
Throw the dice
and we will show another caller.
It is time the truth
to face.
There is no time for innocence
not because he looks in his domain.
The age of innocence,
the end is near...
it is a centuries old saying.
Pa? Are you the weather.
I change my number.
The call is free tonight
VEE to this hospital psychiatrist.
Let's take a call.
Logan you hear me?
There is something wrong.
There is another attack.
In seven States.
People have been here a situation.
I'm going to break...
to get more information.
Please keep listening.
I'll be back.
Close doors and windows stay inside.
Come quick advertising.
Listen very carefully:
Call the children together
and...
No, I do not understand what
is going on.
I can not explain it.
Call the children together
and...
What do you think?
You can not stay home, now.
Listen to me.
I look!
I can 't explain.
Listen I gotta go.
I love you. I must go.
We will stop above
for injections.
What?
In the confusion I lost my bag.
That happens now.
What happens?
I do not know.
A kind of rebellion
broke out after the game.
All people
running around and screaming.
Tourism will take them.
Look where you talkin 'snippet.
This woman, she was...
I understand now that...
they go completely through the ribbon.
We thought we looked
to a picture of my body.
And so suddenly jumped on.
She was totally crazy.
I get 'm.
Hello?
How many stations?
We can if we want.
Let me ask it to Logan?
It is Carl...
He says:
All stations are overschakeld...
to go to the emergency broadcast system.
He wants us to switch.
- What...?
Carl I'm 't Logan.
Well we can not switch
We are in the middle of the show.
We are a few
blocks away from this thing.
Let them
switch if they want.
The people with one voice
a reason and not a stranger.
I am calm.
I must continue to broadcast.
I must tell people that:
they stay away from the city.
We have half million listeners
without access to television.
Are we the only 't building?
Yeah I think we, the
some of the studio but...
I do not know
the rest of the building.
Yeah I think so
but I'm not sure...
I mean it's Friday.
What? Why this strange questions?
What time does the door
locked down?
The front of 't building
automatically closes to nine hours...
who is on a timer, but...
the garage and elevator are always open.
Should we lock?
Find I'm Nathalie,
I report from the city.
And this is one of the worst incidents
we have seen so far.
Oh my god.
They pull the officer out of his car.
They attack him.
Carl you see this,
they seize a cop now?
I stay in the air
until this is under control.
I gotta go.
Exactly a moment ago
was a reporter...
See that?
How can they live broadcasting?
What have we?
What is his name?
Tom. It is Ted.
We must tell them the
door lock to do.
Come on.
What about the garage?
Call them. Yes.
This way.
Still no answer?
Burck I must return
the air!
It is all yours.
I see what
going on. Gil search.
Wait Burns.
Logan, Gaby called earlier.
What? Where?
Early.
Why did not you?
You were in progress, there
was nothing to worry about.
Reply:
Please try again later.
Please. It is for us both.
I do not know. Let me think...
You're such an idiot.
You can not blame me.
It was your brother
the early release.
Khalil's death.
He paid for his mistake.
And you also pay. There is no
enough for both of us.
Come on now.
I'm down...
on 6th Street Bridge.
All cars are stopped
and everyone is there.
They honk but...?
It is not...! Hold on.
What do you see?
God no... please!
Sir, you remain in me,
what happens?
They are on foot.
I guess' t people
the cars must be!
They have kids.
They draw me into the street.
I can not explain.
Is there any police
or first aid personnel.
Please someone do something good
and go to the 6th Street Bridge.
It's unbelievable.
There is something seriously wrong, it is
not the normal course of business.
It is not fucking normal.
It is not normal.
There is something wrong.
It is their eyes.
They bleed from their eyes.
Someone has sprayed them with
pepper spray and then became mad.
But that 's not.
No
words' t explain.
Old Corn are you still there?
Mr. you hear us?
Yes I'm still here.
I'm in my truck.
I lie on the floor.
They are out here.
Shit. Please.
You should send somebody over.
Sir I have asked for help.
- Stay low...
Stay calm, be quiet.
Darling I love you so much.
- I come home.
I'm so scared.
We will send help to you
Help is on the way, stay calm.
If someone in the
close to the 6th Street...
People running around,
they bleed.
Please God,
let me find them?
Oh damn.
Oh, no, no.
Shit they see me.
The guy sees me.
No god... no!
No...
We need to know
is going on.
Let 'get away.
No.
We are much safer here.
Where is Burck?
Close.
Help?
Give me coverage?
Asked little help here?
Come on. That 't.
Get him out of the elevator.
Is he still alive? No.
Everyone remains remote.
Gil what is going on here?
What did you do that?
What?
Now they can come up
when he comes down.
Not be thought not to
friends to bring?
That was not the intention
I saw him down.
We must do something
before he wakes.
We must do something now!
Stop.
Stop it, he is already awake.
We must do something
she stops for good.
How do you do?
Burck?
Come on guys...
we keep on with what we did.
This is a joke... Burck
would it kill them?
Quiet man.
Keep everyone away.
Stay away.
That is not good.
I'm not sure I happy or
afraid that he is here?
It would not take so long for
him to the garage to come.
He is a floor
of us got off.
Shit. He closes.
The release button is there.
I got it.
He has keys, right?
Yes it is security guard.
We are not finished here.
And what would that do?
The elevator is broken.
I go with the stairs.
You can not leave me.
You can not infection
The show...
take over.
I trained you not to panic
in every situation, but you did 't.
I will not risk the risk of
I survive because of your mistakes.
There is not enough
antiserum for both of us.
How you leave the world
is yours.
I honor you have learned.
Ask me here do not disappoint them.
I need to Gaby, she has to
the car and start driving.
Where?
Everywhere, makes no difference.
- Just away.
Seriously the roads are blocked,
you heard what happened on the bridge.
Tell her that the door
and finally, to 'light up...
and she just does not at home.
I'm sorry I did not
said that she called.
Whatever.
Shit, in conversation.
Here, I will try.
- Leave it.
Burck? Are there any callers?
Okay, you are.
Where are you man?
What happened?
You sounded rather overwrought, sucker.
Well we had something to settle here.
And leave your post,
that you can not do it.
We had things
our plates here.
Paranoia.
What is it? You asked for it.
I recommend that you have now, sucker.
You're an asshole.
People it seems that we nou
get the news on TV.
Good evening.
This is an announcement,
I do not ask.
Around 23.05 in the East...
and 20:05 at the West Coast have my number
been explosions at sports events...
and public places
throughout the country.
The report says that explosions
little damage done.
There is evidence that these explosions...
the beginning of the release of toxic
substances in the vicinity of explosions.
We are not sure of the nature
of what is released at this time.
The Center for Diseases Control....
are engaged in many tests
and with their finding...
as soon as possible.
Eventually it happens.
The total number of....
victims who are infected
can run in the 10,000...
and maybe more.
The state police...
is put to work in all States.
And an immediate terrorist threat, the National
red status issued.
All Americans are considered
to remain calm.
Stay home and stay inside.
And turn on your television and
radio broadcast for further information.
Is this all they know?
Unless they are free to advertise.
That is not logical.
How can an explosion of people together
so let rip apart.
Carjacking: Maybe if people
leave as soon as possible.
My partner Gilman agrees.
You are in the broadcast.
Man I'll tell you what I know because
it is much worse than you see on TV.
And I do not know why they wait?
It is obvious that everyone
can see that these things are sick.
They consume us ugly quickly.
These things man...
run on the street...
with bleeding eyes
It is not a rebellion that I know.
I live 2 km from the arena and...
There is no Star Drag me where I
may add to, you follow me?
No, I do not know what you say!
Can you be clearer?
I try.
It's like rabies.
You sometimes have a dog
seen to that.
They bite and scratch you.
They have and are
as fast as a rabbit.
Someone has damaged them well.
- What you say is...
that this is a hondsdolheidbom?
Logan got a situation here.
I'll be back with you
Hey guys!
Security Agent Tanner has
gekrapt me in the elevator.
Should I be worried?
Blood you?
No. I think not.
Feel that you are going crazy?
Yes all the days of my life.
You're right.
Uh, are you there caller?
Okay, people...
I look at a map on the
TV in our studio.
I recommend so that the displayed cities
the one who attacked.
In no particular order,
We have...
Washington, DC...
New York City...
Pittsburgh...
Seattle...
Santiago...
Los Angeles.
The disastrous.
Gaby if you can hear me?
Please call me?
People Gaby is my wife...
I hope that first call.
But our lines are open.
We will take your call
tonight...
So please call us.
Our lines are open.
I do not know.
These terrorists are smart?
Or stupid.
They have a super virus...
where they know
very effective...
they should know that
This is global.
And with them comes back
and will distribute them.
Nobody has said:
it comes from the Middle East.
What do you think it comes from?
Perhaps the Tashmahall, Gil?
- That's good.
Anthrax came not from
the Middle East.
Let us a call.
You are.
With Logan and Gil and Lucy.
Logan Hey listen:
I call from the bridge and they are the
craziest of the entire city.
I can see them running on the streets
they are crazy and...
go in and out of the houses and get...
all women and children out.
You saw that?
Yeah that shit is right for me.
Sorry, I can say is that
in the broadcast?
You do not have to make your
the FCC.
You said: Eastbrook?
Yes South just after Monrou.
What happens there?
They are crazy. They are everywhere.
- I gotta go.
I must go now.
Gaby if you hear me baby...
you must lock all doors...
and barricade the house.
Please call me?
I am sure
Logan that they are in order.
I must go.
Logan, wait.
Wait. Think.
- You'll never.
She's right.
The roads are blocked, as
you will get stuck running.
Unless you have an engine.
Say you're with the engine today?
It's in the garage.
You must give me the keys.
You have never driven motor,
that your death.
How hard can 't be?
You just need to give gas.
No man comes to your garage
not even out.
He goes on.
You have contact with the Burn Harts.
- Here comes the beep.
Gaby?
Gaby, are you there?
Honey wake up in hell
and answer the phone.
Look, if you receive
close everything off and call you 'precinct.
I do not know what else to do.
I love you Gaby.
I'm afraid.
Find somewhere safe
to you hiding.
You'll be safe.
Okay it'll go fine with you.
I love you.
I.
What?
I'm the only one who can
motorcycling.
It can kill you.
I can not ask you to do.
You don 't even ask...
because I won 't al
The craziest sit right in the city,
I have invented.
I go through the side roads and
you continue to broadcast.
And you do that for me?
But let me not play violin.
Of course I do 't for you
Keep it in the air.
Do what you do best.
I do not know what to say?
Well that was the first time.
Ok.
If your house gets my...
when the roads are open...
Didi you get and Gaby,
that stop you in the SUV...
and you leave the city.
What if 't as bad as we thought?
Then barricaded the house.
You may even screw it up Gaby's curtains.
Hey!
That ear thing...
that fits under your helmet?
Okay, I've brought him,
long...
He should not be covered
He is able to broadcast.
This is an amazing traffic report.
Be careful.
That will be good radio.
I don 't owe, Pali.
No, you have me
number one radio show put...
when I had no salary.
But...
there is one thing.
If I survive...
I want Tuesday.
Reach my family...
and I play for you
all my charity.
Hear that?
Yes.
Ok.
I go with you down.
I can bring up the elevator.
'm Sure he leaves the garage.
Sure that you
The elevator will go?
I'm definitely not the stairs,
if you mean?
I'm probably weird
but not crazy.
Showtime.
Talk to us.
Good luck.
Are you ready?
Ready.
Everything okay?
Are you there friend?
Yes, I am.
We are now down.
People 's next...
I hope that short
will be expensive.
Will you listen to my live
broadcast...
of my very good friend of mine.
Actually my very good friend...
Gilbert Brickman.
He goes into the street.
To my attempt to get my...
family to reach ..
my wife and daughter.
But also to our lives
to ensure...
and not lose, by...
the terrible events
today.
I will gladly die for.
Shit, you bastard Murphy.
They are again.
All good guy?
Oh shit!
I 't.
Dirty freak, fuck off.
Please help me?
Get off me?
Do not force me...
Sorry Lora.
Sorry.
I put him first...
in his stomach.
I got it stuck.
I get it out of the elevator.
I'm not sure what you want
I do this but...
I love me the plan.
I send the elevator back up...
Burck but will not sit.
Look, you know?
I had no choice.
I really had no choice.
Keep the door open.
It is not your fault.
Bit crazy that you say.
Are you OK?
I have the feeling that I
vomiting.
No, no Gil...
fuck you go to my family.
Are you OK?
Yes.
Happy.
He could not touch me.
I'm with my engine.
Come on.
My engine.
Fucking come on...
I try to get away.
- Here we go.
There is one just behind me.
Hands off!
Okay, take this motherfucker.
I'm at the gate.
Get out of here.
I'm out.
I'm on the street.
We are close to your friend.
Disconnect sometimes but
We receive you.
She followed me out,
but the port is still open.
There were a couple back inside,
I do not know what they are.
Did you lift off?
Lucy is working on it.
Ok.
I would say anything barricade...
and open for anything or anyone.
I think I'm lost.
You see street signs?
No nothing.
Are you still in town?
Hold on.
Gil what happens?
Can you hear me scream?
Oh, shit. What?
I must get out of here.
There are freaks everywhere.
Hang on.
I'm going off.
There is a back ..
Well I drive the streets again.
Drive to "T intersection.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Yes, I'm okay.
Well I drive to downtown
via West Burn, okay?
It's a ghost town Well.
It is not as we thought
the many more people.
I do not know, the people
his death or something.
Or changed.
People in groups, alone?
Is everyone up?
I wished that I knew it.
I seem the only one who
not infected.
It's like 9-11.
It seems.
Yes but 20.
I'm outta here.
Turn the phone off.
Wait, Logan.
Hey Logan!
If your wife then listening
makes them the door.
Oh, dear help!
Gil are you there?
Can you hear me?
If you can hear me, please Gil.
I'm okay.
People, the one who listen
and just switch...
We have my live connection to...
My partner Gil...
that 's way through the city.
We seek "to restore contact.
So please stay with me.
How many men are you
in this building?
I do not know who in
This building is...
We were with four,
I do not know who left?
What do you mean, I do not know?
I can not think of
that thing at my head.
Who was with you?
One is gone.
Maybe two?
I hope for you that there are two.
Good evening this is Logan Heart Burn...
what you have in your mind?
Logan, I'm 't Vernin.
Vernin, it is good to hear your voice.
I remember that I
said one sound.
I had to go. I was right
somebody spied me.
I found it in my living room.
It had to...
the FBI or the CIA or something.
- He attacked me.
I discovered that she heard us talking.
They must really hate us and may
We do not talk about their secret.
Vernin have you watched television?
Have you listened to the show?
I was so scared that I
own death and was...
They apparently believed that
because they left.
Vernin, this is not something
you think...
something has happened.
You're not alone.
I know 't.
There are many more
it looks like Big Brother.
Logan I do not know whether I
the end of this conversation take?
I would tell you that I love them
to listen to you.
There's a reason that you
're number one.
Vernin are you still here?
I can not see...
my eyes are inflamed.
The pricks.
My God.
I'm bleeding.
- Vernin, stay with me.
We are right back
after this break.
What is this?
- Who are you?
A fan who hijacks your listeners.
What are 't now?
What?
How many listeners are
at this moment?
One million per show.
Sometimes more. Tonight
probably many more.
Tonight...
what happens?
You have something to do.
I want you to send and
one million listeners that says:
you my phone have been
by Fima.
That 's very important
they go out of their homes...
and left town.
That is crazy,
they are much safer inside.
The streets are completely...
Yeah, I know 't.
But that's what you tell them,
you should tell them.
It would just 's nuclear explosion
take place in the city.
He is lying.
I lie when I say: I you
shoot her and then...
I have no regret.
Sit.
Go back and tell what broadcasting
I will, otherwise I'll kill your friend.
I want people to their homes.
Do not know that I am present.
Everyone...
I got a message from
my producer and...
as terrible as the evening
is...
Now we are worried...
because a nuclear device
that is activated...
and is set to explode...
at an unknown location somewhere
in the city.
You think I'm stupid?
Do it otherwise I'll do it myself.
I want you to blame the Muslims
gives...
for everything.
I would hate to have your say.
This is nonsense Logan.
What?
I want you to Muslims
framed.
Doe 't.
Thank you, you,
left off with us.
We should not just watch
for 10,000 maniacs...
who run around in the streets
in the center.
There is also a:
potential nuclear threat.
This is the first to report.
But it seems to Muslim terrorism.
Look. I take that back.
There is nothing that it did not seem
it is the Muslims.
Who else could it be?
That headscarves with camel jockeys.
They are responsible for
all terror since 11/09/2001.
And damn, many
longer than that.
Can anyone remember his own
that no terrorism...
fucking shit out of catastrophic
Middle East arrived.
Take your pick. You...
Ilatola...
Bin Laden...
Sedat...
Sadam...
Arafat...
Chechen rebels...
Suicides.
Damn you can
people do not have a hobby...
which one would not die
ends in the street?
We live in a new era
people...
anthrax is for wimps
we are now long gone.
These are toys for big boys.
We'll have another short break
and we are back after after... nothing.
I have no complaints.
Please stay with us?
Very good.
That would 't do.
Why the Muslims?
Anger, hatred.
You turns you against your own people.
You make fire...
you should also sit on the blisters.
Same as politics.
Yet seven hours to go.
Continue with what
using 't doing.
When a call comes...
Let you not notice that:
I'm here.
Thank you still with us.
Excuse for this
psychotic break.
This is not my typical
show tonight.
We begin this evening with...
the subject paranoia.
How appropriate is it for now.
The lines are open.
You are in the broadcast.
I'm Logan 's Gaby.
Thank God, all right?
Are you safe treasure? Yes.
Did Gil 't taken to the house?
Would he come here?
Logan what is going on?
I returned to your show
After I heard your message.
Why do you say those things
about Muslims?
Sometimes the hard truth and to
Some things are said.
I know you do not believe.
Didi is in order?
She is okay.
Logan tell you why
these things?
Honey I must tell you something:
I am...
Oh God.
Gaby are you still here?
Logan? Hello!
Mommy.
Come to the front door.
Go there sweetie.
Logan, Gil is here.
Okay great.
Tell 'm. ..
Go.
Call 112.
He is busy.
Run!
Mom...
Mommy.
I want you to tell them that 't virus
Designed by the USA.
Under contact
Ministry of Defense.
Another lie to panic
to cause?
Everything is true.
Here we focus on...
spreading hatred
in the right direction.
People interested in hate
and fault...
they try to survive, moron.
You have a big mouth.
About seven hours is...
a dead man's family
as he speaks.
And he thinks of
whom the debt.
The fact that blood on your stick.
Your Nation designs new diseases,
new bombs.
Always new ways to
to kill and control!
You think a man with my bomb this
gun holds no virus can make?
Make an announcement.
People need to know
Who created this hell.
Doe 't.
Lucy pak 't gun?
Enough.
Sit! Before I kill you.
Do that again and you
brains are against the wall.
Sit!
Serum.
You have slain me.
I have a child.
Me too.
Well we know that:
your father.
You have destroyed my serum.
I need that vaccine?
Where did they at all
require.
They can care for one another.
Wait.
I 's serum for you.
Below is our account...
He has diabetes he has needles
in his office.
You go. Arise!
Take the stairs. Go!
I trust that you
't building not leave.
If you're not back within ten minutes
I kill her and get your search.
I'm back within five.
Is water anywhere?
My God, your eyes!
I need water?
The pantry is here by the door.
You change into some thing,
is not it?
I am exposed
The serum that will change.
How long do you have?
Now you 're a researcher and reporter?
I did not wait for the press
to say what I think.
I did the important news
for six years.
Your important news
is about how celebrities recover.
What does your body language on the news?
Where is the American media
with my report as a...
bombing of Lebanese children
that night was?
Where are they like Osama Bin Laden
receives his salary from the CIA?
So Osama Bin Laden is not
bad enough for you?
Osama Bin Laden is your Santa Claus.
Lying to a bunch of kids.
So what happens after seven hours?
In seven hours does' t virus
prevailed and you are infected...
and you will fall down dead
and then you will be destroyed...
and then it's over.
There is no global scourge is just
enough for a city to destroy.
Tell every man, woman and child.
As if it was intended
sick of your government.
If you hate government so...
Why do you lose 't
American people think of?
Your people and government
are 't the same.
So lock in your people.
Shit! What are you doing here?
Do not know?
I wanted to go up...
but all lines are busy.
Have you heard
what's going on?
Stop.
I know 't.
I know everything.
Look there's a top score.
He has a gun and Lucy.
You can help. No.
I have up now.
- No.
Listen.
Maggie listen to me?
It's okay...
Everything is good.
What you ask is my command.
Come on the move.
Logan?
I come... but not alone.
Stop!
No.
Serum.
Give it up to me.
Hurry!
Are you okay?
What?
You gonna shoot us now?
, I 'm loving my friend.
I just saved your life asshole.
You know what your problem is?
You give nothing for nothing.
It is much talk talk talk.
Shooting your gun into the air.
The burning of flags.
You're the one
who blame the country.
But what actually is the cause...
you love killing.
It feeds you.
Gives you strength.
Makes you a man.
Are you okay?
Yes.
No.
I seemed 'n scratch it.
Logan lie down.
Not moving.
I want to be together again.
We seek him.
Stay with me Logan.
All listeners, good morning.
They are just flying.
There are six or eight of my house.
I'm so tired.
People: This is your host
Logan Heart Burn...
and we are almost done here.
It will probably
a few days but...
We have...
continue to survive.
I wanted to seriously thank you...
for the last time.
For 't listen.
You vote.
And it most especially...
for us to help...
and helping each other.
You say you were a antiserum have?
Yes.
Join me in the back.
So what happens after seven hours?
- Here.
About seven hours, the
virus prevail...
and will be effective and will kill you
fall down and destroy you...
and then it's over.
You hate the government...
you must not
American people attacked.
The virus was designed by the USA
You saw 't.
I want clarity?
Have you heard or seen?
I would like to hide but...
I think this is my resignation.
My producer is left now
the world relief organization.
All our hope is to her...
something that they think of 'n....
solution for this virus.
At this moment, I just
but my family.
Gaby?
Gil?
I'm so glad you're okay.
10,000 years...
in the history of mankind.
Millions of years of evolution...
and still we are building something...
what more to destroy
than to create.
That circle of inventions...
A knife for the community...
literally a knife.
And not just a community...
but humanity.
We are all victims...
the same terrible impulses.
And we show how to find...
to store and recharge our energy
into something positive...
and to resist the darkness.
God help us all.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org