Some people can see
all your mistakes.
The way you hold it
in your shoulders.
Show it in your face.
I made a lot of mistakes
in my life
and they were
my mistakes.
Nobody else's.
Mine.
When you get older,
all those mistakes
start piling up inside you.
Regrets, blame.
It's enough to make you
sick to your stomach.
Problem is,
there are certain things
that I just can't
change about myself.
Fill it up, will you?
- Morning.
- Good morning.
$20 on eight, please?
Where are your cards?
Cards... Backside of
this aisle right here.
He almost finished
out there?
Yeah, almost.
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
Hello? What's the address
of your emergency?
That'll be it.
Okay, $20 on
the pump, $24.
$24. That's a steal.
You have a good day.
Boy.
You're the one
from the paper.
I think you got me confused
with somebody else, all right?
No. I know who you are.
I know who he is too.
The truth, sir...
I assume you're a friend.
I'm sorry.
A friend of
the family?
Yeah.
I'm sorry for your loss.
What's gonna happen
with the boy?
He's going to his
grandparents' place.
Where were they?
They live in
Farmington, New Mexico.
But I hear his
grandfather's gravely ill.
You driving him?
Oh, no. I'm just gonna chauffer him
over to the bus station.
Do you know Louis?
No.
Thank the Lord,
he's got his grandparents.
Yeah.
All right, son.
You ready?
Yes, sir.
Let me help you.
Right over here.
All right, son.
So all right.
Here we go.
Now I've got your ticket.
Your money's
in the envelope.
They're gonna put your skis
and bags underneath.
I hate buses.
Can't you
just drive me?
Aw, son, I'm needed here.
But you'll be fine.
Nothing to worry about, okay?
It's uh...
It was nice meeting you.
You too, Louis.
I'll be praying
for you, son.
Hey, Louis.
I'm John.
Yeah, you were at the church.
That's right, that's right.
Nice to meet you.
Listen, I'm sorry
about your mother.
It's a shame.
Listen, I just got a phone call
from your grandparents.
Apparently, they don't
love the idea of you
riding on this bus
for three days.
They asked me if
I'd give you a lift.
Meanwhile, I was headed
that way
so I told them, shit, why not?
Sir, I don't know you.
Yeah, well, I don't really
know you either and,
frankly, this is
a pain in my ass.
But, like I said,
I know your grandparents
and your mother was a...
She was a good woman.
You knew my mom?
Yeah.
She never really
talked about you.
Yeah?
Well, I guess I didn't make much of
an impression then, did I?
We kept in touch.
I'd call, she'd call.
- You know how it goes.
- Yeah.
Listen, I got to hit the road.
I understand if you don't
want to come with me.
Besides, buses ain't so bad.
Perfectly civilized mode of
transportation, if you ask me.
But, hey,
good luck to you, kid,
and my deepest condolences to
you and your family, all right?
Kid, you getting
on the bus? I gotta go.
Sir.
Sir?
Get in.
You, uh... You live in
this car or something?
No, of course not.
I just wasn't
expecting guests.
Your mother was
a wonderful woman.
Classy lady, fun gal.
Full of spirit.
She was...
Sparky.
- Oh...
- She was...
I forgot.
What do you got there?
Pictures.
Ah.
This is
my grandparents' house.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Good, that's good.
You know, the only time I really visited
them was when I was little.
Mom didn't get along with
my grandparents too well.
Didn't really talk.
Hey, how long do you
think it'll take?
I don't know.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, I got to make
a couple quick calls.
Should just take me
a couple minutes.
- Moody residence.
- Mrs. Moody?
John Wheeler here.
How you doing?
You have got some
nerve calling here.
I was just at your daughter's
wake. Where were you?
Earl's sick.
Now what do you want?
I got Louis, her boy.
What... why would
you have Louis?
Now, look, there's been
a change of plans.
I'm gonna drive him home.
Where's that priest?
Put Louis on the phone.
It'll just take
a couple of days.
You got nothing
to worry about.
Now you put Louis back on
that bus and get back...
One more stop.
Stay here.
Hey, I need that
to get home!
What's up, John?
Will you excuse us
for a moment, please?
Okay, thanks.
This is a fucking joke,
right?
There's a little over
6,000 bucks right there.
You're short $14,000
and change. Maybe more.
Well, what are you...
you said $10,000.
I owe you $10,000.
You're late, John, again.
So it's $20.
What are you doing, huh?
How long have
we known each other?
Long enough for you
to know better.
This is fucking bullshit, John!
Do you understand?
What the fuck
do you want from me?
John,
protection in jail
is very expensive.
Do you understand that?
I didn't ask you for
any goddamned protection.
Yeah, but you took it.
You know jail could have
been dangerous for you, John.
I'm living out of my car.
I don't have
anything else.
I just gave you everything
that I got, okay?
Boy, do you want
to go back to jail?
You like the bed and the three meals of
crap they serve you every day?
'Cause I can arrange that with
just one fucking phone call.
Freddy, give me
the fucking phone.
No, no, no, no.
You're not gonna
make any phone calls.
I got just as much shit
on you as you got on me.
6,000 bucks.
That's all you get.
We're closed!
Goddamn kid.
Hey, are you in
some kind of trouble?
It's nothing.
Did they
do that to you?
I don't know
what I was thinking.
You ain't worth the trouble.
The closest I could
get you is Albuquerque.
I'll call your grandma and have her
pick you up in a couple of days.
Good to meet you.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Louis!
Louis?
Louis.
Hey.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
I don't want
to be alone.
Why did she have to die?
There's no good reason.
I don't know, man.
I don't have anyone else.
Hey, you're
gonna be all right.
Hey! Hey!
Hey, let's get
something to eat.
I'm hungry.
What's with these skis?
For skiing.
Yeah, well, there ain't
no snow around here.
The skis were a gift
from my mom.
You probably never
even skied before.
She wanted me to learn.
Skiing's expensive.
I just saved you
a shitload of money.
It was the last thing
she gave me before she died.
Yeah, it's a dumb sport.
I can't believe all you got was
$20 bucks and that stupid ring!
Are you hungry?
I'm starving.
Let's go.
Mm, mm.
Good.
What, you're not gonna eat?
I'm not hungry.
Fine with me. Starve.
Look at that
little piece of ass.
Hey, you like women?
Yeah, I guess.
You guess?
All right, well, know this.
A scorned woman will
tear your heart out,
put it between
two buns and eat it
just as your life
slips away before you.
Don't ever forget that.
Hey, you wanna drive?
Yeah? You wanna drive?
All right, can you
see over the hood?
I guess.
All right.
Your feet touch the pedals?
I think so.
You think so or you can?
It's kind of a big deal.
- Yeah, fine.
- Okay, all right.
So this is an automatic.
So all you gotta do is pull that
lever down from P to D.
There you go.
All right, now take your
foot off the brake.
Push down on the gas.
There you go.
All you gotta do is avoid other
cars and that's pretty much it.
How fast you going?
Uh, 32 mph.
No, no, no.
You gotta get it up.
At least 50 or 60, even 70.
There you go. See, faster is
way better, isn't it?
You're blind! Oh!
Oh!
All right, the first rule to
gun fighting is having a gun.
All right, I prefer
to have something small.
Something easier to carry.
Easier to conceal,
all right?
Can't go hunting with
something like this, though.
Why not?
You just can't.
It ain't right.
What's the point, then?
The point is,
if I have the gun...
I have the control, right?
You want to give it a shot?
If I let you shoot this,
you owe me a favor.
Okay.
All right.
Go ahead.
Go ahead,
shoot it again.
All right.
Turn it, gangster style.
There you go.
Let's go.
Hey, give me my gun.
Wake up.
It's time for that favor.
All right, now keep
the engine running.
Don't turn it off for any
reason, you understand?
Where you going?
I gotta run inside and
grab a couple of things.
Just keep it running.
I'll be right back.
Now jump in
the driver's seat.
Wait, what?
- Howdy.
Let me know if I can
help you with anything.
We got some
specials back there.
Are you gonna get it?
Yeah, that should...
oh, the newspaper.
Get on the ground.
Get on the fucking ground!
- Get on the goddamned...
- I heard you!
- I'll beat you with this fucking gun!
- I heard you, damn it!
Listen, this store's all I got.
You leave me something you hear?
There you go.
You're a real
son of a bitch.
Hey! What the hell
are you doing?
Hey, hey!
Get out of the fucking car!
Get out...
Hands off the boy!
Easy, easy!
Go!
Ha!
All right!
Now keep it up over 70.
Keep it on the right side
of the road.
- Just like I told you.
- I'm gonna be sick.
What do you mean,
you feel sick?
- I'm sick, I'm sick.
- What are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
Get in the back!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, shit!
God damn it!
Son of a bitch!
- I need some air.
- Yeah, well, shut up!
I need air.
- I need some air!
- What are you doing?
Shut that door!
No!
God damn it! God damn it!
Stay here.
Where you going?
Get your things.
- Where'd you get that car?
- Shut up and get in!
Did you steal it?
I will leave you here.
I swear to God, I will!
You cost me a lot
of money today.
I don't want anything
to do with you.
Well, that's not
an option, is it?
You can't make me stay.
I can leave.
Just hitchhike.
Yeah, okay.
You're gonna hitchhike?
Yeah.
Why don't we find a place
to sleep tonight?
With a bed?
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
Fine.
You awake?
What?
Just wanted to see
if you were awake.
Why'd you do it?
Do what?
Rob that place.
Because we didn't have
any money and we needed it.
To get me home?
Yeah, to get you home.
Food and gas.
This bed.
Why do you live in your car?
Because I can't
afford anything else.
Most adults have jobs...
Just go to bed, Louis.
Just go the fuck
to bed, please.
All right.
When you're done in there,
I want you to pull
the truck around.
Understand?
Hey, you paying
attention to me?
Yeah. I heard you.
God damn it,
you pay attention!
Wake up!
You're not gonna go
fucking this up for me again.
All right, Louis.
Stop fucking around
and open up the door.
A couple of days.
That's how long
you said it would take.
You're a liar.
Open up the door.
Come on!
The fucking...
Open up the fucking door!
God damn it! Okay.
Now take your hands off the wheel
and get out of the car.
Just one more day
and I'll take you
to your grandparent's,
all right? Now come on.
Open it up, please.
You need me.
Hello.
How's your day?
Oh, just going great.
Good-looking boy
you got there.
Yeah, yeah, he
is adorable, isn't he?
Got a daughter myself.
Huh. I'll take $20
on two, please.
No gas. Pump's broke.
Been broke for months.
Oh, shit, all right.
Would you grab me a can of that
Black Bear Longcut Wintergreen?
You don't want any
trouble now, do you?
- Open it up.
- Yeah.
Ain't much in there.
Well, that'll do.
Boy, what are you doing?
Come on!
This ain't no fucking library!
Hurry up!
Quit pissing around!
Now get back there
and clean that up.
Come on.
In and out just like
a couple of ghosts.
Gimme that.
Thank you, sir.
You got a safe?
Christ!
Go, go, go, go!
Fuck you!
God damn it!
God damn it,
I can't believe that.
Shit.
I'll tell you what, boy.
Life can be
such a bore sometimes.
But this...
This is great.
Well, don't
look at me like that.
You and me make
a really, really good team.
Shit, they probably got
nicknames for us already.
Who? The papers?
Yeah.
Don't they have
better things to do?
Shit, no. Bonnie and Clyde
was all over the newspapers.
Billy the Kid, too.
He was famous.
Like in movies?
- Exactly.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, in the movies,
they all got shot to death.
Aren't you having fun?
If I was your age,
I'd be having fun.
No, I'm not having fun.
You think this
is easy for me?
Dragging your skinny
little ass all over the place?
This ain't no fucking
holiday, all right?
This is a job.
This is work driving you home.
You know, it'll all be
over soon enough, all right?
Yeah, I hope so.
Did you, uh...
Did you see that shotgun under
the counter earlier today?
No.
No?
I just figured you
might have seen it
underneath there when you
were, you know, down below...
I didn't see any gun.
Okay.
Ma'am?
Do you have
chocolate ice cream?
I'll have to check
in the freezer.
Okay. Well, we'd like
one scoop.
Two spoons for me
and the boy, please.
One scoop and two spoons.
Two spoons.
That's right.
Okay.
Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ice cream.
We're leaving.
Come on.
- We have plenty of money.
- We gotta keep moving.
I'm not even done
eating yet.
Yes, you are.
Let's go.
Get out here!
God damn it.
Here we go, honey.
One scoop and two spoons.
I love chocolate.
Thank you.
Oh, he just needed
some fresh air.
Uh, he'll be back, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
I can share if you want some.
Honey, I don't
need the calories.
You enjoy that
chocolate ice cream.
Let me know if I can
do something for you.
Thank you.
That'll be $14.50.
You're welcome, sweetie.
I'll tell you what.
You tell his mama that
she raised a gem of a boy.
Yeah, I'll be sure
to tell her that.
We gotta get rid
of that truck.
I like that truck.
Yeah, well, it's not
safe to drive anymore.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
Come on, lady!
I got a kid here!
Jesus Christ.
We should have
kept the truck.
Yeah, well...
Hey!
Just keep walking.
Shit!
Keep your mouth shut.
Neither one of us want
to go to jail, right?
Hello, Officer!
Hitchhiking is illegal.
Particularly on Sunday.
Yeah, our car broke down.
Uh-huh.
Let me see some ID.
Come on.
Turn around, over there.
Spread your legs. Come on.
Where you headed?
Uh, his grandparents' place.
I'm real sorry
about this, officer.
It's just that, you know,
we didn't have much of a choice.
Our truck broke
down back there, so...
Well, now is it a car
or is it a truck?
He meant car.
You better both come with me.
We'll clear this up
down at the station.
Come on.
Uh, sir?
We're just on our
way to church.
What was that?
We're going to church
to pray for my mom.
Yeah, his mama died.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Is that right, son?
Your mama just died?
Yes, sir.
Just last week.
I'm sorry to hear that.
All right, get in the car.
I'll give you a ride.
- Come on.
- No, no, we can do...
No, it's all right.
Don't worry.
Come on.
Don't make me wait.
Can I sit in the front?
Sure.
Thank you, Officer!
All right, let's get
the hell out of here.
Hey, where you going?
Church.
Louis?
♪ Sweet by and by... ♪
♪ We shall meet ♪
♪ On that beautiful shore ♪
♪ In the sweet ♪
♪ By and by ♪
♪ We shall meet ♪
♪ On that beautiful shore ♪
♪ In the sweet ♪
♪ By and by ♪
♪ We shall meet ♪
♪ On that beautiful shore ♪
- Praise the Lord!
- Amen!
I am so pleased to see some
visitors with us this morning.
Come on up here, son.
Come on up here, son!
I'm not gonna bite you.
Come join me here.
There you go.
Let him by there.
Here you are.
What is your name, son?
Louis.
Everyone please welcome
our child of God, Louis.
- Welcome, Louis.
- Welcome.
What is your name?
John.
- John.
- Yep.
Why won't you join us?
Nah, I'm good right here.
No, no. I'm extending my hand
in the name of the Lord
so we may greet you
as a congregation.
If you wouldn't mind removing your cap
here in the house of the Lord?
Everyone please welcome
these brothers in Christ,
John and Louis.
Welcome, John and Louis.
Thank you.
Yeah, can we sit?
- Please do.
- All right.
Take your seat, gentlemen.
We don't see too many
new faces around here.
It's exciting when we do.
We won't be staying for long.
What, you just
passing through?
Yeah.
Listen, I want you
to know something.
You're welcome to stay
as long as you like.
My mission is
to grow this family.
Spread the word of God.
Well, like I said,
we won't be staying for long.
All right.
He's a quiet one.
Got many friends?
I have no idea.
A boy needs friends, you know.
Jesus had 12 of them.
Yeah.
Well, look what good
that did him.
Listen, we're having
a retreat tonight.
Want to stick around?
The boy will love it.
You gonna have
food there?
We'll have food there.
One piece of advice.
What's that?
You want to save a little room
for the coconut cream pie.
Good to know.
Louis, hello, my friend.
- Hi.
- How are you, son?
Good, thank you.
I'm gonna sit here and
join you if you don't mind.
It's fine.
We're happy to have
you with us today.
Happy to be here.
So tell me about yourself.
Hey.
Louis. Louis?
Hey, hey, wake up.
We gotta hit the road.
Come on.
What the hell is...
What the hell
are you doing?
- Come on.
- I don't want... I'm not fucking leaving!
Come on, it's time to go.
- What the hell's your problem?
- Hey, come on!
Come on!
This is yours.
I hate you.
I think you were scared.
You're scared they'd find out
you're a bad person.
A wolf, like
the pastor said.
A wolf?
He called me a wolf?
Beware of false prophets
who wear sheep's clothing
because really
they're ravenous wolves.
He said that?
That's...
I'm not doing
this anymore.
What do you mean,
you're not doing this?
I'm not doing it.
Hey, get up!
Come on!
We've been over this!
Hey, get up!
We gotta keep moving.
Hey!
Can't just sit
around all day!
Come on!
Let's go!
Thank you.
I need a lift for me
and my friend back here.
Just take a minute.
Hold on one second.
Louis! Come on!
Louis.
Grab our things and take
them to the room, will ya?
I'm gonna go grab a drink.
How long?
I don't know.
As long as it takes me.
Give me a whiskey
and a beer chaser.
- Oh, God.
- Okay.
Ah!
I don't know where the damn kid is.
How can you drink those things?
They give me heartburn.
Yeah? I think they're just
fine in the morning.
Oh, there he is!
Great.
This is Louis,
Louis Moody.
- Hi.
- Hi, honey.
I'm Mary.
This is Rose.
Mary and Rose are
headed into Mexico.
That's right.
You're gonna pay for the gas, huh?
'Cause she pissed off
our meal ticket!
Oh, Rose, shut up!
So there you have it.
Well, get in.
You're driving, right?
Oh, yeah.
Should I put
the stuff in the trunk?
- Just throw it in the back.
- Back there?
Why don't you guys both
get in the way back?
We got some adult
conversations to have.
Get in.
This is gonna be fun.
Were you the one
knocking on my wall?
No.
Yes, you were.
Why didn't
you knock back?
That's how it works,
you know.
You're supposed
to knock back.
I don't know.
How old are you anyway?
I'm 13.
Well, I mean, I guess, 14.
Is that your mom?
You could call her that.
It's that you don't look
like each other, so...
I was just wondering.
People say I take
after my dad.
after my mom.
That's an amethyst.
That's turquoise.
Oh, I know turquoise. I got a...
check that out.
Brand new ring.
- That's nice.
- Turquoise.
Well, that's what
they call kismet.
Oh, yeah?
What's that mean?
Well, it's a Middle Eastern word
for coincidence or serendipity.
Ah, kismet.
Kismet.
So here's the deal.
You pay for the gas.
We'll pay for our
own lodging, okay?
All right.
You know, I don't just let
any stranger into my car.
These are unique circumstances,
you understand?
I understand
completely,
and we're not exactly
strangers at this point.
Just don't get any ideas,
lover boy.
I won't get any.
Well, I might get
a couple ideas.
I'll just keep 'em
right up in here.
Don't go telling 'em
too much about yourself.
Remember what
I told you about women.
Well, look at us.
Just like one big happy family.
Hardly.
Hey, you know what I think we
should do?
We should go shopping.
Might as well have a little fun
while we're on this trip, right?
I don't know.
She loves buying stuff.
All right, y'all.
What do you think?
Well, well, well.
Just like Miss America.
Can we go now?
I'm gonna buy that for you.
- We need that money.
- I got plenty.
I'm gonna go pick out
some things for the kids.
Oh, yeah.
I hate dresses.
You two look adorable.
You look nice.
You know, I'm usually a pretty
good judge of character.
But I'm gonna admit
I read y'all wrong.
I thought you were gonna
be greedy and selfish
like most of the men
I've been with.
But you ain't
and I like you.
Yeah? Well,
I like you too.
You know, my mama
always said,
"Don't waste time waiting
for the perfect man because,
well, life is too
goddamned short."
That's what she said?
Wish I could just
run away, don't you?
I don't know.
There's nowhere
to really run off to.
Where would you even go?
Ever been to the beach?
Never really had a chance to.
That's where I'd go.
Somewhere with a beach.
You could always come
to the beach with me and,
you know, we could have
our sandcastle house.
Go fishing.
We'd survive on fish.
Could be a lot worse.
If you could, if there
was any place on Earth
you could run away to,
where'd you run?
If I had to choose?
I'd probably go home.
Pretty exciting, right?
Is that in New Mexico?
I don't know.
Well, come on.
Tell me something
about yourself.
Well, there's not
much to tell.
I don't much like
talking about myself.
It's not easy for me.
Fine.
What about the boy?
His mother died.
And?
I'm taking him to live
with his grandparents.
Well, why go through
all that trouble?
Well, because
he's a good kid.
I don't mind
spending time with him.
Uh-huh.
What's in it for you?
There ain't nothing
in it for me.
You're lying.
You're a liar.
Is he yours?
Look at you.
I ain't no fucking liar.
You're way better.
I'm not even making...
Snap, snap, clap.
I can't snap.
Hey, you know we're not far
from my grandparents' house.
My mom said it snows there.
I've never seen snow.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You should come.
I mean, you know,
if you wanted.
It'd be cool.
Yeah. Sounds fun.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Hey, let me talk to George.
It's John.
John?
How's the head?
Oh, just fine.
How's your sister?
Hey, John.
Any luck in finding my money?
I've got the rest
of your $10,000.
So you're 10 short.
How about this?
I bring you what I have.
Or you can come
looking for the rest.
Maybe I'll go and look
for it in New Mexico.
Farmington, New Mexico.
Maybe I'll find
my money over there.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Of course you don't.
$20,000, John.
See you soon.
Our hometown ain't
far from here.
Y'all can stay with us
if you want.
Oh, yeah? How long?
As long as you want.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
I think that this little thing
has probably run its course.
So we should
probably get going.
Wow.
Well, fuck you, John.
Well, I think we've already
done that, haven't we?
Louis.
John tell you why
he's taking you home?
Yeah, he's taking me
to my grandparents.
No, baby.
Did he tell you why?
I think you should probably
quit while you're ahead.
Well, I think I'd like
to fill in the blanks, okay?
John strikes me as
the type of guy who's failed
at just about everything
he's ever done.
Am I right?
You always had luck with
the ladies, didn't you?
But that never lasted
and somewhere along the way,
all those big plans,
well, they fell apart
and you got desperate.
A little lonely.
That's why the idea
of dragging him around,
well, wasn't so bad,
was it?
Mom...
Don't worry, honey.
He ain't like us.
Men like him don't have the balls
to survive in the real world.
All right, listen, lady...
But the one who's got
the most to lose is you.
Do you even know
who he is, honey?
'Cause he's using you.
Just like he used me.
Just like he
uses everybody.
This is bullshit.
They always run.
John?
- John?
- Get back inside, Louis!
John, let's just leave.
We can find another ride.
Louis, get back inside.
John, she doesn't
know anything about you.
She's right, Louis.
I am afraid.
And I just can't take living
like everyone else, you know?
The problem is, there's
certain things about me
that I just can't
seem to change.
John.
John, stop.
John!
I knew there was
something wrong with him.
Come on, Louis.
We're gonna take you home.
It's not gonna
end well, honey.
Come on, get in.
Come on, it's okay.
Louis! What are you doing?
Get over!
Get down!
God damn it!
This is a lot of money.
We could fly to Farmington
if we wanted.
You know what she said
about you wasn't true.
I don't know, she split me
wide open, didn't she?
You know, when I was in jail,
everyone wanted
to blame everyone else
for who they
turned out to be.
Mom, dad, girlfriend, wife.
I made a lot
of mistakes in my life.
But they were my mistakes,
nobody else's.
They're mine.
You know, when you
get older, Louis,
all those mistakes start
piling up inside you.
Just a pile of mistakes.
Regrets, blame.
It's enough to make you
feel sick to your stomach.
Secrets make me
feel like that.
Yeah, secrets, too.
You got many secrets?
Yeah, plenty.
How about you?
Yeah.
I like that girl.
Shit, that ain't no secret.
Yeah.
Tell me one
of your secrets.
Maybe some other time.
John?
Hey!
Look at that.
Hey, we need some
food for the road.
All right.
I'm gonna go grab some gas.
Let's meet back
here in ten minutes.
All right,
you go first.
Watch out.
Go on!
Our APO here is 96309.
So drop us a line,
anytime, APO 96309
and we'll get it on.
Anything else?
Oh, that's it.
Thanks.
This is the 11:00 report
featuring John Marks
with the news and sports.
A brazen daytime robbery
of the Alpine Savings Bank
has state police looking
for an unidentified man
and his teenage accomplice.
They were last seen traveling
west on Farm Road 369
in a tan station wagon with
Texas license plates 74EJQ8.
Are we going to jail?
Nah, we ain't
going to jail.
You scared?
No.
I'm scared.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Oh, what a mess.
We should go to Mexico.
We could live there for
years with all this money.
We should get a car, but...
we could do that.
- Give me a rock.
- Oh, I got it.
I liked the
station wagon better.
Yeah, well, nobody's gonna
be missing this piece of shit.
I can tell you that much.
Be nice if we could
this thing up over 50.
I figure we'll drive
about halfway there
then find a quiet place
to camp for the night.
What's it gonna be like?
What?
Your grandparents' place?
Yep.
I don't know.
I imagine it'll be beautiful.
Think we'll be there tomorrow?
Oh, yeah.
We should be there by lunch.
First we have to make it
through the desert.
Then we'll cross
into the mountains.
We'll know we're getting close
when we can see the farmlands.
Green, as far as
the eye can see.
Just like
that picture?
Yeah, just like
the picture.
Let me get that for you.
There you go.
You're looking
good there, partner.
I want to make
a good impression, you know?
Let's go.
Fill it up, will you?
- Morning.
- Good morning.
He almost
finished out there?
Yeah, almost.
9-1-1.
What's your emergency?
Hello?
What's the address
of your emergency?
That'll be it.
Okay, it's $20 on pump, $24.
$24. That's a steal.
You have a good day.
Boy?
You're the one
from the paper.
I think you got me confused
with somebody else, all right?
No. I know who you are.
I know who he is too.
The truth, sir...
The truth is,
he's my son
and all I've ever done
is disappoint him.
I've abandoned him.
I've lied to him.
I found every
excuse that I can
just to make him another
mistake in my life.
A secret that
I keep to myself.
But he won't let me.
Please, just
let me make it right.
Just please
Come on.
Grab your bag!
Don't you hear that?
Do you remember
the address?
What?
Do you remember
what the place looks like?
Do you remember the address?
What's going on?
All right, I need
you to leave.
I'm not leaving you.
I promised this guy
in there I wouldn't run
'cause I can't run anymore.
I see myself as a person
that I'm supposed to be.
A good person, the kind
of person that you deserve.
I just...
I don't have the courage
to be that person.
to change.
Do you understand
what I'm trying to say?
Here, take this with you.
Take it with you, and go.
I need you to go, all right?
You're gonna be okay.
Hey, you're gonna
be all right.
Now go, go, go, go.
I don't want to leave, John.
I don't want to leave you.
You gotta go. Go.
I don't want to leave you, John.
Go! Run, god damn it!
Run!
Face the car!
Hands in the air!
What do you think it's going to be like?
I'd imagine it'd be beautiful.
Surrounded by farmland as
far as the eye can see.
Just like that picture?
Yeah, just like
the picture.
We're going to do
a quick line inspection here
in Farmington, New Mexico.
Line number seven.
You lost?
I need to get
to Farmington.
You are lost.
I'm not lost.
Oh, whatever you say.
Yeah, you're close.
It's up that road about
an hour or so.
An hour?
Yeah,
at least an hour.
But you're young.
You could give me a ride.
I could, yeah.
I'd be a lot more willing if
we was to bargain for it.
Kid with that kind of
silver ain't gonna have
a hard time finding
a ride home.
How about it, kid?
23 Farm Road. 23 Farm Road.
Louis?
Hey, Grandma.
Oh, thank you, Lord!
Oh, we thought
we'd lost you forever!
You were supposed
to be here days ago.
Just look at you.
How'd you get here?
I walked.
Oh, Lord.
Well, come on in the house.
Where'd you start from?
What do you mean,
you walked?
How do you boys
get so dirty?
It's good to have
you home, sweetheart.
I want this to feel
like home, okay?
This was your mother's room.
I kept so many of 'em.
I hope they
don't make you sad.
I like looking at 'em.
Makes me feel like
she's still here.
You were born in this bed.
This exact one.
Really?
See?
There's your mom and
your dad holding you.
You were just
a few months old.
Oh, you've grown
so much since then.
Oh, my sweet boy.