Evidence of
a cataclysmic event...
You can see
it here, that this event
took place.
Written accounts
describing lost cities...
Atlantis
had a great advanced
civilization.
And mythic tales
of gods punishing humanity...
They decided
that they would destroy all
these civilizations.
In ancient
cultures throughout
the world, there are numerous
stories of mankind nearly being
destroyed by a great flood.
But could such an event have
actually taken place?
And might it have been caused by
an otherworldly force?
One has to
ask the question: "What if Noah
was one of the
extraterrestrials?"
Millions of people
around the world believe
we have been visited in the past
by extraterrestrial beings.
What if it were true?
Did ancient aliens really help
to shape our history?
And if so, might we find
evidence in the stories of
"The Great Flood"?
It is one of the
best-known stories of the Bible,
and variations of this ancient
tale can be found in cultures
throughout the world.
From ancient Hindu teachings and
Mesopotamian legends to
Mesoamerican myths, it is
written that the gods sent a
powerful flood to wipe out all
of humanity...
God is angry at
human beings, because human
beings have not been behaving
properly; they have been
violating God's laws.
KATHLEEN McGOWAN COPPENS:
Certainly the most famous of
these is the legend of Noah.
In Genesis, God becomes so
disgusted with the behavior of
His creation that He says He
"repenteth of making them..."
...and He brings forth the
deluge.
In stories
much older than the story of
Noah, in the story of
Gilgamesh, the Sumerian legend,
the council of gods brought
the flood.
In Plato's writing,
Zeus brought the flood.
In
Hinduism, God had instructed
that, one day, the whole Earth
will be flooded.
When that happens, you build a
boat and you gather the people,
some animals, and then I will
save you.
The story of the
Great Flood is often considered
to be mythological.
But similar stories of a
cataclysmic flood can be found
in approximately 1,200 different
cultures around the world,
and many anthropologists say
that because these stories are
so numerous and date back
thousands of years, it is
unlikely that they originated
from a single source.
When we find
similar myths all over the
world, like the myth of the
flood, then we have to ask
ourselves are these things that
human beings came up with
independently, because let's say
there was a great flood in
ancient history, that has been
memorialized in people's
mythologies, because it was such
a cataclysmic event that people
looked for a religious
explanation for it.
The fact that
there are ancient stories that
speak of the same flood, it
almost leads into that
direction that, at some point,
some cataclysm happened that
not just affected one geographic
area of the world, but the
entire planet.
If a cataclysmic
flood really did occur, killing
most life on the planet,
what could have caused it?
And is there any
physical evidence to suggest
that it actually happened?
Scientists say answers to both
questions may be buried deep
beneath the sea.
The Indian Ocean.
According to the five scientists
who make up the Holocene Impact
Working Group, this area--
900 miles southeast of
Madagascar-is where an
enormous asteroid struck the
Earth, thousands of years ago.
This impact may have been so
large that it triggered enormous
tsunamis that flooded inland
areas across the region--
an event the local inhabitants
would have perceived as
a great flood.
Since so many
ancient cultures have a flood
story or a flood mythology,
this is probably based in some
sort of real event...
and an asteroid landing in
the ocean, in the right place,
triggering a tsunami, would then
lead to one of these
major floods.
The Holocene Group
says evidence for a
catastrophic asteroid strike
lies in what they believe is an
18-mile-wide crater on the
floor of the Indian Ocean,
just west of the island
of Madagascar.
Holocene Group scientists
believe further evidence
supporting their theory also
lies in what are called
"chevrons"-ancient deposits of
sediment and fossils in both
Madagascar and Australia.
What was so out
of place and unusual about the
chevrons was that they
weren't land-based debris.
But, rather, it was the
kind of debris you get from an
ocean sea bottom, things like
marine animals, marine fossils.
They've also found what's really
the smoking gun of any asteroid
or comet impact, and that's
micro-beads.
The only way they are formed
is by the extreme heat of an
impact melting the rock,
the rock being thrown into
the air, or water, and cooling
into these nice little spheres.
Similar marine
fossils have also been found on
the other side of the world,
at the ancient temple
complex of Puma Punku,
in modern-day Bolivia.
If the Holocene Group's initial
findings prove true, they could
be definitive evidence that
a cosmic strike caused
large-scale flooding thousands
of years ago.
But if an asteroid really was
responsible for a worldwide
flood, scientists say it would
have to have been as large as
the one that led to the
extinction of the dinosaurs,
which measured eight miles
wide and struck the Earth with a
force five billion times more
powerful than the bomb dropped
on Hiroshima.
There are many
ancient texts that tell us
that there wasn't just a flood,
but there was also a
conflagration, a period of fire,
when the Earth was bombarded
with firestorms, the gods
bringing them down, and that
this period was then
followed by a flood.
And it would seem that
fragments of this comet
vaporized the ice sheets that
had been covering large parts
of the northern hemisphere for
tens of thousands of years,
sending all of the water up
into the atmosphere,
which then rained down.
Perhaps even for 40 days,
40 nights, like the Bible
tells us.
According to those
scientists who subscribe to this
theory, the fires that might
have occurred just before the
flood would have left behind an
ash layer in the Earth, all over
the world.
This distinctive ash layer--
which scientists call the
Usselo Horizon-could be the
ultimate proof that the Great
Flood really occurred.
And researchers believe they may
have discovered it.
Just outside the small Belgian
town of Lommel, author and
researcher Andrew Collins
follows local archeologist
Ferdi Geerts to the site of a
mysterious black layer of soil
excavated by a mining company.
I can already see a
black layer, um, in the soil
here.
It's about just under a-a meter
down, um, three to four feet,
um, and, um, are we looking here
at the Usselo Horizon?
Yes.
Is this, is this it?
At the end of the
ditch we see, uh, a peat layer.
Yeah.
At the top of the
peat layer, there is, uh, some
charcoal.
Right. So, can-can
we go down and look at this?
Yes.
Collins and Geerts
get a closer look, which allows
them to determine that this dark
layer of soil seems to date to
the end of the last ice age,
about the same time the Usselo
Horizon is supposed to have
formed.
If we come down from
the, from the-the surface here,
which is obviously the modern
day, there is this accumulation
of sand over a period of around
13,000 years, that takes us back
to this point here.
The black is a layer,
eh?
Yeah.
And the-the white is
sand.
We call that a soil horizon.
Yeah. Okay.
According to
Geerts, this black layer dates
back to the time period when a
global flood may have devastated
Earth.
But what is it made of?
Collins and Geerts dig into the
soil and discover that it is,
indeed, charcoal.
This is the Usselo Horizon, and
to Collins, it's confirmation
that the catastrophe described
in the Bible was real.
This is physical
evidence of that flood,
of that conflagration.
This is your absolute evidence
that this event took place.
This is the evidence of the
cataclysm.
Could the Usselo
Horizon, a possible impact
crater in the Indian Ocean and
sea fossils at Puma Punku all be
proof that the ancient story
of a great flood is not a myth,
but that it is based on actual
events?
And if so, could the rest of the
story, in which God sent a
flood to annihilate the human
race, be true as well?
This suggests
that a great flood did, in fact,
happen; that it was real.
But then it also presents us
with an intriguing possibility.
It is entirely possible that
there is an extraterrestrial
origin to this terrible flood.
Could it be that
the Great Flood described in so
many ancient texts really did
occur at the end of the last
Ice Age?
And if so, could it have been
brought on by extraterrestrial
beings?
Ancient astronaut theorists say
yes, and claim that evidence of
this can be found at the top of
one of the world's most sacred
mountains.
Laurel, Maryland.
October 2014.
At Johns Hopkins University,
top scientists from all over the
world gather for the first
International Asteroid Impact
Deflection Assessment Workshop.
The focus of this event is to
demonstrate the latest
technology designed for
diverting the course of
asteroids headed for a collision
with Earth.
The proposed method involves
launching a spacecraft to
collide with the asteroid at a
velocity nine times faster than
the speed of a bullet fired from
an AK-47.
If we look at
the dinosaurs, for example,
65 million years ago-they were
wiped out due to the impact of a
giant rock that wiped out
everything on planet Earth at
the time.
And so, right now, scientists
around the globe are working
tirelessly to redirect asteroids
from possible collisions with Earth.
In addition to
using direct impact to knock an
asteroid off course, scientists
have also looked into the
possibility of creating a
gravity tractor that could
actually manipulate the
trajectory of the object.
But if we are close to
developing this kind of
technology today, is it possible
that extraterrestrials who
visited Earth in the distant
past already possessed the
ability to redirect asteroids?
And if so, might they have used
this technology not to deflect
an asteroid away from Earth...
but towards it?
We are talking
about technology that equals
ours today, or as some have
said, that it actually surpasses
whatever it is that we've
achieved so far in our modern
age.
And so, if we can control
the trajectories of asteroids,
to direct them away from Earth,
then it's certainly possible
that highly advanced
extraterrestrials could have had
the technology to direct an
asteroid towards Earth.
It's
interesting how the legends
described how the flood came.
It is stated that a great meteor
or comet or something was to
swing around from behind the
sun, and as such, rip the oceans
out of their bodies.
The flood was clearly contrived.
It was sent by higher powers to
correct things here on Earth.
They had an intent and a purpose
for Experiment Earth, which they
believe had become corrupted,
and therefore the flood was sent
as an attack, an assault upon
humanity.
If the Great Flood
was a real, historical event,
could it have been deliberately
caused by otherworldly beings
as ancient astronaut theorists
suggest?
But if so, why?
What might they have been trying
to destroy?
Mount Hermon, Lebanon.
1869.
Exploring the top of this
historic mountain range, British
archeologist General Sir Charles
Warren discovers the sacred
temple of Qasr Antar-believed
to be the highest place of
worship in the biblical world.
Sir Charles
Warren hiked up to the top of
Mount Hermon.
The ruins of this temple are
there.
And there he found an ancient
stele and he broke this stele
into two pieces and brought it
back to the British Museum.
When scholars
translated the Greek text, it
read: "According to the command
of the greatest and holy God,
those who take an oath proceed
from here."
The inscription's significance
was lost on archeologists for
more than a century, until
biblical scholar George
Nicklesburg connected it to an
oath mentioned in the ancient
Book of Enoch.
According to Enoch, Mount Hermon
is where a band of renegade
angels known as the Watchers
descended from the heavens in
the distant past and took an
oath before meeting with humans.
In the time before
time, the sons of God came down
to Earth.
They were the shining ones, the
Enohim, or fallen angels.
And they found the women very
attractive and they married the
women or bonded with the women.
The offspring of
these unnatural unions between
angels and humans were said to
produce giant hybrid beings
called the Nephilim, and God was
so disgusted by their existence
that he decided to send a great
flood to cleanse the Earth of
them.
But how is it that human women
were able to be impregnated by
angels?
Could it be, as ancient
astronaut theorists suggest,
that the Book of Enoch is not
actually describing angels, but
rather a different kind of
otherworldly being?
You've got to
wonder what was really going on
here?
Are extraterrestrials coming
and now breeding with humans,
which was somehow forbidden and
wrong, but they did it anyway?
So the other extraterrestrials
decided, "This is a big mistake. Now
we've got to destroy all these people."
Could the story of
the Great Flood actually be
describing extraterrestrials
coming to Earth long ago, and
interbreeding with human women
to create a mutant race of
giants?
Ancient astronaut theorists say
yes, and claim further evidence
can be found by examining ruins
that are believed to date back
thousands of years before our
earliest known civilizations.
The Gulf of
Khambhat, India. 2001.
Scientists working some 25 miles
from shore, and 125 feet below
the surface, stumble across
something extraordinary: what
appears to be the signs of an
ancient civilization.
Recently,
the marine archeologists of
India have discovered two cities
in the Bay of Khambhat.
They are still working on it,
uh, you know, going down there
and archiving it and taking
photographs and videos.
They think that
these cities were destroyed in
a geological change that
happened many thousands of years
ago.
But you have to wonder,
yourself, if there are not more
sunken cities all around India.
Their own legends and myths say
exactly that.
The ruins found
beneath the ocean in the Gulf
of Khambhat are thought to date
back at least 9,000 years, to
the time when some researchers
believe a comet struck the Earth
and caused a global deluge.
Could these submerged cities not
only be evidence that the Great
Flood really did occur, but also
that it wiped out an advanced
society that existed long before
the earliest known human
civilization?
Scientists say further evidence
can be found in archeological
sites around the world that date
back to end of the last ice age.
In southeastern Turkey lies
Gobekli Tepe, an extraordinary
series of circular stone
structures with intricately
carved pillars weighing as much
as 50 tons.
Radiocarbon dating indicates
parts of the complex were built
about 10,000 BC, and at least
one archeologist believes there
are signs it may have been
destroyed by a flood.
We have
evidence there of catastrophic
destruction; of pillars being
knocked over at the end of the
last ice age; that things were
very severe, people were trying
to rebuild it at the time.
Eventually, they effectively
gave up and covered over the
entire site, maybe to come back
later to uncover it, maybe to
simply bury it for posterity.
In the rain forests
of Indonesia is a series of
terraces, walls and steps on a
hill that the locals call Gunung
Padang.
When scientists drilled into the
Earth to determine its age, they
discovered the site dates back
to at least 9700 BC.
Very interestingly,
one of the layers of Gunung
Padang that's been exposed
seismically shows that there was
an entrance to a cave at about
9700 or so BC that was
subsequently covered over.
Again, I think this ties in with
the events at the end of the
last ice age.
People were going into caves,
they had to escape, and then
things were covered over after
that.
Are these ruins
that are found across the world
evidence of an advanced
civilization that existed before
a global deluge?
And if so, might we find mention
of it in ancient myths?
If we go back to
ancient Greece, one of the
myths, one of the sacred
narratives that Plato preserves
is the narrative that there used
to be a great continent, which
he calls Atlantis.
And Atlantis had a great,
advanced civilization.
Atlantis was one of the
continents that was destroyed by
the Great Flood.
When does he date
Atlantis?
To 9600 BC, which is very close
to the modern date of the end of
the last ice age.
So all this, I believe, ties
together that we had an earlier
cycle of civilization.
It was devastated at the end of
the last ice age by natural
catastrophes.
Humanity was driven into a dark
age that lasted thousands and
thousands of years, until
civilization reemerged about
5,000 years ago.
Is it possible that
the story of Atlantis is really
describing a civilization that
existed before 10,000 BC, when
the Great Flood and the end of
the ice age are said to have
happened?
Did Atlantis suffer the same
fate as Gobekli Tepe, Gunung
Padang and many other ancient
structures that appear to have
been hit by some catastrophic
event?
Ancient astronaut theorists say
yes, and suggest that the most
compelling evidence can be found
not with what was destroyed,
but with what survived.
Qumran, Palestine.
1946.
In the desert, ten miles east of
Jerusalem, a Bedouin shepherd
leaves his flock of sheep and
goats to look for a stray.
Walking along the cliffs, the
shepherd spots a cave in
the distance.
He threw
a stone into a cave and
he heard the crack of breaking
pottery...
so he went in to investigate,
and found jars that contained
ancient manuscripts.
McGOWAN COPPENS: The Bedouin
shepherd's find led to a
discovery of 11 caves
that contained the most
extraordinary cache of
literature, arguably, in human
history-the Dead Sea Scrolls.
There are 800 pieces of
literature found in these
11 caves and it tells us so much
about the ancient world.
One of the amazing revelations
is the story about Noah that we
don't see in the Old Testament,
and the story is that when Noah
is born, he's an extraordinary
baby with a strange complexion
and the ability to light up
the room with his eyes.
What's
interesting is that you
actually have Noah's father,
Lamech, questioning whether or
not Noah is his son.
And this is due to the fact that
we have this story about these
fallen angels that came down and
had sex with women.
Lamech confronts his wife,
Batenosh, "Is it my son or is
it, is it one of theirs?"
Noah's exterior
is described as very foreign.
His eyes are described to be
glowing like sunbeams; his skin
is glowing, as well.
Now that's a very bizarre
description, and so, one has to
ask the question: "What if
Noah was one of the
extraterrestrials?"
Could it be, as
ancient astronaut theorists
suggest, that the Biblical
figure of Noah was, in fact,
an alien being?
Is this the reason he is
described as having a strange
complexion and glowing eyes?
The key thing
that's going on with Noah is
that he is pure in God's sight,
and so is his family.
And this purity seems to
be genetic, as much as what you
might call spiritual.
And so, when God makes plans to
wipe out the rest of humanity,
what he's wiping out is the
extraterrestrial dimension of
humanity that has come about
through the pollution of human
genetics.
Could
extraterrestrials have sent
the Great Flood to cleanse
the Earth of genetic mistakes,
and make Noah the father of a
new version of humankind?
According to ancient stories,
the world that Noah's
descendants were born into was
very different from the one that
existed in pre-flood times,
when gods, giants, fairies, and
other creatures were said to
share the planet with humans.
The flood does seem
to serve as a demarcation point.
In the Bible, we read about how,
before the flood, people had
longer lives, but then, after
the flood, shorter lives.
We see the same thing in
Mesopotamian tradition,
with the Sumerian King List,
where, before the flood, we have
kings that ruled in Mesopotamia,
with extraordinarily long lives.
After the flood, the lengths of
reigns of these kings becomes
much shorter.
The other thing that
happened before this
Great Demarcation is that the
gods were present among us.
There was a close interaction
between the human and
the sacred.
The gods would guide us and
they would be tempted.
There would be interaction,
the god might marry a mortal
and then there would be
descendants of the gods.
Now the gods seem so far away.
So, there are these theories
that this was the big shifting
point in human history.
It is really
interesting to note that the
interaction with these higher
beings seems to only be located
in the past.
All these depictions of "there
were giants upon the Earth."
Or a time when man interacted
with the gods.
Where are the gods today?
We only seem to have subtle
interactions.
It's curious to
think why that might have been.
What was it about this
Great Flood, this dividing line
in history, that caused the
separation of god and man?
It could be that our evolution
depended upon a natural
upbringing, an upbringing that
was not contaminated by this
notion that we're not alone in
the universe.
It could be a necessary part of
the human development.
Uzengili, Turkey.
1997.
More than 7,000 feet up,
near the country's eastern
border, an American explorer
searching for Noah's Ark, named
David Allen Deal, stumbles upon
the ruins of an ancient
settlement.
McGOWAN COPPENS: There is an
extraordinary archaeological
site in the Anatolian plateau,
in Turkey, called Naxuan, and
Naxuan comes from an ancient
word that means "Noah's Zion,"
the city of God that Noah built.
Mount Ararat, which is the
legendary resting place of
Noah's Ark, is very close by,
so it makes a lot of sense
that this could have been
the landing site of the ark and
then this city would have been
built by Noah.
The ancient
Armenian historian Moses of
Choren called Naxuan,
"the place of first descent
where Noah and his family
emerged from the ark and built
the first city or town after
the flood."
Could this be the first
settlement in the post-flood
world, the place where Noah
lived and died?
Today, this remote area is
largely uninhabited, but
according to explorer David
Deal, a recent archeological dig
reportedly uncovered something
remarkable:
the region may contain as many
as a million graves.
McGOWAN COPPENS: There is
evidence that people came
from all over the world
to bury their dead here,
for 10,000 years.
The idea is that if you are
brought here to be buried in
the site of this extraordinary
prophet, this man who was chosen
by God to be the survivor of the
deluge, that you, too, would be
resurrected because you were in
such holy company.
According to some
researchers, if this is indeed
the place where Noah began the
repopulation of the Earth, then
the Ark must be nearby as well.
In the Book of
Genesis, we read about how God
commanded Noah to build an ark.
And the measurements of this ark
are quite large.
The dimensions usually given are
about 450 feet long by 75 feet
wide by about 45 feet high.
Such a boat of these dimensions
was never seen in the ancient
world, and in fact, not until
the 19th century was there ever
a boat of this size.
In 2009, a Dutchman
named Johan Huibers started
building a full-size version of
Noah's ark using the
instructions laid out in the
Bible.
It took him three years and more
than a million dollars
to complete the project.
But while the ship seems
perfectly designed to ride out a
torrential storm, many say it's
still far too small to literally
hold two of every animal species
on the planet.
It would seem pretty
clear that Noah did not scoop up
every form of life on Earth and
put it into the Ark.
And so as a means of saving all
life-forms on Earth, uh, this is
not possible, not believable.
But ancient
astronaut theorists suggest
there might be another way in
which the ark was able to
preserve two of every creature
on Earth, as stated in the
Bible.
Let's look at it
from a technological
perspective.
The only way that you can create
an ark like Noah created,
according to what we can read in
the Old Testament, is if you
collect DNA samples.
So, what if the ark was a
metaphor or a symbol for some
type of a DNA bank?
Did the ark
described in the story of Noah
really exist?
And if so, might it have been
not a vessel to carry two of
every animal species, but a DNA
bank, built to hold the genetic
information of all life on our planet?
What one might
read into this is that some kind
of special DNA bank was to be
created; that animal DNA, plant
DNA, and human DNA for that
matter, were all to be
preserved somehow in an ark that
was to float through the flood
and this catastrophe.
Is it possible that
all of humanity is descended
from Noah's genetic lineage-a
new species that replaced the
indigenous people who once
existed on Earth?
And all that remains of this
once great society are the giant
slabs of rock that were too big
to be washed away by the flood?
And if so, might we be destined
to suffer the same fate?
Perhaps further clues can be
found by looking at our own
modern-day version
of Noah's Ark.
Spitsbergen,
Norway.
On this remote archipelago, not
far from the Arctic Ocean, lies
the Svalbard Global Seed Vault.
Known as the "doomsday vault,"
this repository for the DNA of
plants, animals, and humans can
withstand nearly any cataclysm,
including a flood, an
earthquake, or a nuclear blast.
The Svalbard
Seed Bank is a structure or a
facility that's sunk into the
permafrost.
It's essentially an
international effort to deposit
as many seeds, and particularly
seeds of crop plant varieties, to
help to preserve genetic diversity.
With the doomsday
vault, are we creating our own
modern-day ark...
one that, instead of housing
two of every living creature on
Earth, will house the seeds of
every kind of plant life?
The Svalbard Seed
Vault has been designed with
some sort of cataclysm in mind.
The idea is that in the event of
some catastrophic event, it
would still stay cold and
preserve seeds for thousands of
years.
It's sort of this last hope.
The Svalbard is
just one of several biological
storehouses located around the
world.
England's Millennium Seed Bank
is even larger, while the U.S.
federal government has built a
similar facility in Fort
Collins, Colorado.
Scientists say one reason for
these repositories is that
another large asteroid-similar
to the one that is believed to
have caused the Great Flood--
will eventually strike Earth.
It's just a matter of time.
You always have the
risk, and of course we've seen
it here on Earth, of having
large asteroids or comets hit
the planet and cause tremendous
ecological damage.
Right now, all our genetic eggs
are in one basket.
Whether it's a comet or asteroid
hitting us, we are in jeopardy.
In February of
2013, an asteroid large enough
to take out all of New York City
came within 18,000 miles of
Earth.
Another has been predicted to
strike the Earth sometime in the
next 20 years.
But if a great flood or some
other global catastrophe were
to occur today, are we prepared
to survive it?
And if there really are
extraterrestrial beings watching
over the Earth, are they likely
to be the cause of such a
cataclysm?
Or will they simply be
observers, sitting quietly by
and letting nature take
its course?
If
extraterrestrial gods are there
watching us and, either aware of
future catastrophes or are
capable of making them
themselves, then perhaps we need
to be prepared for that.
We live in a precarious point
where, at any time, we could go
through another catastrophe.
And you have to ask yourself if
the extraterrestrials themselves
may not create that.
One of the
explanations for why
extraterrestrials might seek to
destroy humankind is because
they treat us as their property.
They treat us as their
offspring.
And they're able to make
decisions about humanity based
on their needs.
So perhaps their needs were
satisfied and they decided they
didn't want humankind around
anymore, so it's just as easy to
wipe them out as it is to
continue to perpetuate their
existence.
The
evolution of humans on this
planet has been completely and
totally an experiment on the
part of extraterrestrials.
If survival is the bottom line,
they are trying to get us over
some kind of a finish line when
we're still alive.
Our survival
was ensured by
extraterrestrials, way back in
the remote past, because we are
their direct offspring.
We are their product.
They, in fact, have a vested
interest in our survival.
Are we the
descendants of an
extraterrestrial ancestor named
Noah, who was sent to repopulate
the Earth after the Great
Flood?
And if so, are there
extraterrestrials watching over
us, even to this day?
Not to destroy us, but simply
to see if we can prevail over
the Earth's next great
cataclysm?
It is a question we may not have
much time to think about
except to consider how
much or how many will survive.
Captioning sponsored by
A&E TELEVISION NETWORKS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org