[ CLICKING ]
[ BEEPING ]
Woman: CHILDREN,
EXPERIENCE TELLS ME
THAT SOME OF YOU WILL FORGET
THE LESSONS I HAVE TAUGHT.
No.
THIS SUMMER,
TAKE TIME TO REFLECT
ON YOUR PAST YEAR
IN THE SECOND GRADE...
[ COMPUTER GAME BEEPS ]
YES!
...AND HOW YOU CAN MAKE
THIRD GRADE BETTER.
NO!
MR. O'MALLEY,
DO YOU DISAGREE WITH ME?
NO, SISTER LEONORA MARY.
I AGREE.
[ CHILDREN GIGGLE ]
Woman: PETE! BOYS!
COME ON, LET'S GO!
MOM...
YES, HONEY?
I TOLD THEM TO BE READY
BY 9:20,
BUT THEY JUST DON'T LISTEN.
ANOTHER COMEBACK STOPPED!
REGGIE JACKSON STINKS.
BOYS!
WE GOTTA GET GOING.
MOM'S GONNA FREAK.
GET DOWN HERE RIGHT NOW!
WELL, WHAT SHOULD WE
TELL HER?
YOU COULDN'T FIND
YOUR BELT.
HOLD ON!
WHY AREN'T YOU
GOING TO CHURCH?
WHAT ARE YOU,
A DETECTIVE?
WHY AREN'T YOU
IN THE CAR?
COME ON, LET'S GO!
GOD DOESN'T WAIT!
IT'S KILLING ME I CAN'T BE
WITH THEM AT CHURCH.
MY MOST CHERISHED MOMENTS
HAVE BEEN WITH YOU KIDS
AT CHURCH.
SCREAMING BRATS.
WHY ARE YOU LATE?
PETE COULDN'T FIND
HIS BELT.
MM-HMM.
WHY ARE YOU LATE?
SEAMUS LOST MY BELT.
[ BABY CRIES ]
HEY...
WHY DIDN'T YOU GUYS MAKE US
WAIT A LITTLE LONGER?
YOU KNOW HOW I HATE
BEING LATE FOR MASS.
KATIE, YOUR TOYS
ARE EVERYWHERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? GOD GIVES YOU
168 HOURS A WEEK.
YOU'D THINK YOU'D GIVE HIM
ONE BACK.
IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
[ SIGHS ]
I'VE BEEN READY
FOR THREE HOURS.
OH, SHUT UP,
YOU KISS ASS.
COME HERE.
NO.
COME HERE. HONEY,
I'M NOT GONNA HIT YOU.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU,
YOU SHOULDN'T TALK LIKE THAT.
WHY AM I THE ONLY ONE
THAT GETS HIT?
[ COMPUTER GAME BEEPS ]
TOUCHDOWN!
I'M CRUSHING YOU AGAIN.
[ BABY CRYING ]
HERE, THAT ONE, TOO.
MAYBE THE TEDDY BEAR
WILL SHUT HER UP.
I'M GONNA SHUT YOU UP,
TOO, YOU LITTLE JERK.
"C."
[ BEEPS ]
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
Pete:
GROWING UP IRISH-CATHOLIC,
HEAVEN AND HELL
ARE TALKED ABOUT
AS IF THEY'RE
MY NEXT-DOOR NEIGHBORS.
[ COMPUTER GAME BEEPS ]
TOUCHDOWN!
AND MY MOM'S JOB...
GODDAMN IT.
...IS TO LOVINGLY GUIDE US
TOWARDS THE RIGHT PATH.
LORD'S NAME IN VAIN.
COME HERE. COME HERE, MISTER.
AGH!
DON'T YOU TALK LIKE THAT,
YOU LITTLE SON OF A BITCH.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY TO A CHURCH,
FOR CHRIST'S SAKE.
MORNING.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
OKAY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[ SCREAMS, CRIES ]
ALL RIGHT.
HAPPY SUNDAY,
EVERYBODY.
MORNING, SON.
[ SCREAMING ]
OKAY.
Thank you, dear.
Watch him.
Get in there.
You're going to confession.
Right over here,
right here, right here.
Pete: UNFORTUNATELY,
NOBODY KNOWS
THE EXACT PATH TO HEAVEN.
MY MOM SAYS
THAT'S WHY WE GO TO CHURCH --
TO PRAY TO JESUS
FOR ANSWERS.
BUT HE JUST HANGS THERE
SILENTLY,
LOOKING DOWN AT ME,
SEEING EVERYTHING.
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
HEY, MOM...
YES, DEAR?
YOU THINK DOING MY CHORES
WILL BE ENOUGH TO KEEP ME
OUT OF HELL?
WHAT'D YOU BREAK?
PETER EDWARD O'MALLEY,
LOOK AT ME, HONEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THINK THAT
SISTER LEONORA MARY THINKS
THAT I'M GOING TO HELL.
AND WHY DO YOU THINK
SHE THINKS THIS?
WELL, SHE SORT OF SAID IT
A LOT THIS YEAR.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
MAYBE YOU CAN DO SOMETHING
TO PROVE TO SISTER MARY
THAT YOU'RE GOING STRAIGHT TO
HEAVEN -- DO SOMETHING GOOD.
HELLO?
OH, HI, JACKIE.
WELL, WHAT CAN I DO
TO PROVE IT TO HER?
HONEY, JUST BE YOURSELF,
OBEY THE NUNS,
AND YOU'LL BE FINE, OKAY?
YOU'RE A GOOD BOY.
HELLO.
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL.
IF YOU CAN'T SAY SOMETHING
GOOD, YOU JUST DON'T SAY
ANYTHING.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
SHE IS KIND OF LOOSE.
HMM, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF SISTER LEONORA MARY?
SISTER BIG BAGS?
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
A LOT EASIER
THAN SISTER GLORIA.
WHY?
SHE KEEPS TELLING ME
I'M GOING TO HELL.
YEAH.
SHE'S BIG ON HELL.
WELL, HOW CAN I PROVE TO HER
THAT I'M NOT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
TOMORROW'S THE LAST DAY
OF SCHOOL.
I KNOW, BUT LET'S SAY
I WANTED TO.
HOW WOULD I DO THAT?
WELL, IN RELIGION CLASS,
I DID THIS REPORT
ON ST. PAUL.
HE'S THIS GUY
THAT AFTER JESUS DIED,
HE KEPT GOING AROUND
TRYING TO CONVERT PEOPLE
INTO CHRISTIANITY.
HE WAS ON A QUEST.
CONVERT PEOPLE
THAT WEREN'T CATHOLIC?
YEAH, THERE WERE A LOT
BACK THEN,
LIKE THE JEWISH PEOPLE
AND THE ROMANS.
JEWISH PEOPLE?
YEAH, CONVERTING JEWISH PEOPLE
WAS MAJOR.
THE ROMANS...I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE EVEN THE GREEKS.
EVERYONE.
DID IT WORK?
THEY MADE HIM A SAINT.
YOU THINK THEY MIGHT
MAKE ME A SAINT?
[ Chuckling ] YEAH,
THAT'D KEEP YOU OUT OF HELL.
BUT THEY ALREADY GOT
A ST. PETER.
[ BELL RINGS ]
SEE YOU AT CHURCH...
AND NEXT YEAR
IN THE THIRD GRADE.
YOU MAY GO.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
MR. O'MALLEY, MAY I SPEAK
TO YOU FOR A MOMENT?
YES, SISTER LEONORA MARY?
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I HAD
TO PULL YOU BY YOUR EARS
TO THE FRONT OF THE CLASS
AND GIVE YOU THE RULER?
A LOT.
PROBABLY TOO MANY TIMES,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I DON'T ENJOY HAVING TO DO THAT,
YOU KNOW.
I THINK THIS IS
AN IMPORTANT SUMMER FOR YOU.
THIS IS THE SUMMER
WHERE YOU CAN CHOOSE TO KEEP
FOLLOWING THE DEVIL'S WAY
OR CREATE A NEW PATH
TOWARDS JESUS.
NOW, WHICH PATH
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE?
THE JESUS PATH.
GOOD.
I EXPECT TO SEE A DIFFERENCE
IN YOU NEXT YEAR.
OH, YOU WILL,
SISTER LEONORA MARY.
I'VE GOT A PLAN --
A QUEST.
GOOD. YOU MAY GO.
ENJOY YOUR SUMMER.
I KNOW YOU WILL.
OH, UM...DO YOU KNOW WHERE
I CAN FIND A TEMPLE?
FIRST GAME OF THE SUMMER,
PETE.
COME ON, SEAMUS,
I'M STARTING MY QUEST.
Boy: WHO'S GOT THE BALL?!
HEY, KEVIN!
SO YOU'RE ACTUALLY GOING
TO THE TEMPLE?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE THING'S
KIND OF WEIRD --
YOU GOING THERE...
THE QUEST.
YEAH.
WELL, AT LEAST
YOU KNOW IT'S WEIRD.
SEE YA.
Man: WELL, KEEP UP
THE GOOD WORK, JASON.
I WILL.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE YOUR PARENTS
VERY PROUD.
THANK YOU, RABBI JACOBSEN.
SEE YOU IN A COUPLE DAYS.
YES.
BYE-BYE, NOW.
HOW YOU DOING TODAY?
I'M GREAT. THANKS.
GOOD.
WHAT'S THAT THING
THAT YOU HAVE
ON THE TOP OF YOUR HEAD?
OH, IT'S, UH, CALLED
A YARMULKE.
IT DOESN'T REALLY
BLOCK THE SUN, DOES IT?
NO.
UH, BUT IT DOES BLOCK
BALD SPOTS.
WHOA.
IT CAN COVER BALD SPOTS.
MY OLD UNCLE JIM
COULD HAVE USED THAT.
[ Chuckling ] UH-HUH.
SO, YOU, UH...CASING THE JOINT
FOR A HEIST?
WHAT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR?
JEWISH PEOPLE GO HERE,
RIGHT?
UH-HUH.
I'M TRYING TO SEE
IF I CAN HELP JEWISH PEOPLE
GET TO HEAVEN.
AH, ONE NOBLE ENDEAVOR.
A QUEST.
A NOBLE QUEST.
HOW MAY I BE
OF ASSISTANCE?
I JUST WANTED TO CHECK OUT
THE TEMPLE,
BUT THERE'S NO BIKE RACK.
TELL YOU WHAT -- WHY DON'T YOU
LET ME HELP YOU
FIND A PLACE FOR THE BIKE,
AND I'LL SHOW YOU AROUND?
WELL, THANKS.
AND THAT WAY, WHEN YOU
AND THE REST OF THE GANG
GET TOGETHER,
YOU'LL KNOW
WHERE THE SAFE IS.
WHAT GANG AND WHAT SAFE?
YOU KNOW, FOR THE HEIST.
Pete: NO CROSS?
Rabbi:
UH, NO. NO CROSS.
I FIND THE CROSS
FUN TO LOOK AT.
SOMETIMES I THINK ABOUT
CLIMBING UP THE WALL
AND UNSCREWING THE SCREWS,
AND LETTING HIM GO.
MASS GOES FASTER THAT WAY.
UH-HUH.
YOU SHOULD REALLY THINK
ABOUT PUTTING ONE IN HERE.
I WILL GIVE THAT
SOME THOUGHT.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I'M THINKING THAT THIS IS
WHERE MY QUEST STARTS.
OKAY.
WELL, IF I CAN BE OF ANY
ASSISTANCE, DON'T HESITATE.
MY OFFICE IS RIGHT THROUGH
THOSE DOORS THERE.
I'D SHOW YOU AROUND
A LITTLE BIT MORE,
BUT I GOTTA GET BACK
TO MY FAMILY. I HAVE A --
YOU HAVE A FAMILY?
YEAH.
WELL, THEN WHAT DO THEY
CALL YOU?
WELL, MY SON CALLS ME DAD,
AND MY CONGREGATION
CALLS ME RABBI...
RABBI JACOBSEN.
PETE. PETE O'MALLEY.
NICE TO MEET YOU,
RABBI JACOBSEN.
PETE O'MALLEY.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
OH, LOOK AT
ALL THESE LITTLE...
STOP MAKING UP
THESE STORIES.
YOU'RE JUST LYING
THROUGH YOUR TEETH.
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
I WAS LIKE, "HI, JULIE,"
AND SHE WAS LIKE, "HI, EDDIE."
SHE DID NOT SAY THAT.
OH, SHE SAID,
"HI, EDDIE..."
HEY. HEY, GET YOUR ELBOWS
OFF THE TABLE.
EDDIE, WHAT'S --
WHAT'S WITH YOUR HAIR?
ALL MY FRIENDS LOVED IT.
YOU, MY FRIEND, ARE GOING TO
THE BARBER COLLEGE THIS WEEK.
CAN I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION,
PLEASE?
I GOT SOMETHING TO SAY!
WELL, I GUESS SO.
THIS BETTER BE GOOD,
KATIE.
SO, TODAY, I PEDALED MY BIKE
ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO O'CONNOR'S HOUSE.
THEN, I PEDALED BACK,
AND IT WAS SUNNY.
[ LAUGHS ]
SPEECH THERAPY FOR
THIS ONE -- MAYBE.
Margaret: HONEY...
[ Sarcastically ]
THAT'S GREAT.
MAKE FUN OF HER.
DOES ANYBODY KNOW
WHAT A YARMULKE IS?
YOU MEAN A BEANIE?
NO, IT'S NOT A BEANIE,
POP.
IT'S, UH -- JEWISH PEOPLE
WEAR THEM, PETE.
IT'S -- IT'S RELIGIOUS.
IT'S THEIR TRADITIONAL
HEAD WEAR.
IT'S LIKE FEATHERS
FOR INDIANS.
EXACTLY.
WELL, WHAT'S IT FOR?
TO HIDE THEIR HORNS.
THEY HAVE HORNS?
[ LAUGHS ]
JOSEPH!
NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT,
AND NOBODY REPEATS THAT
OUT OF THIS HOUSE.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
WHO WANTS ICE CREAM?
I DO.
CHOCOLATE, PLEASE.
COME ON,
I NEED HELPERS.
VANILLA.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE REQUESTING FLAVORS?
YOU'LL GET WHAT WE HAVE.
WE ALWAYS DO.
PETE, GET ME SOME --
SOME VANILLA.
SO, YOUR UNCLE CHARLIE
CAN GET YOU AN INTERVIEW
AT THE CITY PLANNER'S OFFICE.
YEAH, WELL, UH,
NO, THANKS.
WELL, PATRICK, WHAT ABOUT
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT?
NO, NO, NO,
FORGET ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S ALWAYS THERE
FOR HIM.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WELL, UH, YOU KNOW,
I'M STILL WAITING FOR THOSE
SCHOLARSHIPS TO COME THROUGH,
AND UNTIL THEN, I'M
LIFEGUARDING, YOU KNOW.
I'M MAKING MONEY
AND SAVING MONEY --
LIFEGUARDING?
[ LAUGHS ]
I RAISED A PROFESSIONAL
LIFEGUARDER IN CHICAGO.
WORKS THREE MONTHS A YEAR,
RIGHT?
DAD, IF YOU COULD SEE
SHEILA MORAN
IN A BATHING SUIT,
YOU'D BE A LIFEGUARDER,
TOO, I PROMISE.
"OH, PATRICK, SAVE ME.
HELP! SAVE ME!
OH, GIVE ME A LITTLE KISS
ON THE CHEEK, BABY."
PATRICK, FRANCIS DEMOS TOLD ME
SHEILA LIKES YOU.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS ASK HER OUT.
DON'T LET HER OLD MAN
CATCH YOU.
NO KIDDING.
DO WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT
MY PERSONAL LIFE
EVERY NIGHT AT DINNER?
[ LAUGHS ]
I THINK YOU LIKE HER,
SON.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING, CHILDREN
SHOUTING IN DISTANCE ]
COME IN.
HEY, RABBI JACOBSEN.
IT'S ME -- PETE O'MALLEY.
OH, YES, MR. O'MALLEY,
HAVE A SEAT. HOW ARE YOU?
I'M GREAT. THANKS.
I'M READY TO START
MY QUEST,
BUT I THOUGHT I MIGHT NEED
YOUR PERMISSION FIRST.
EXCELLENT IDEA.
WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
I WAS THINKING OF SETTING UP
THIS LEMONADE "FREE TRIP
TO HEAVEN" STAND.
OF COURSE!
THE OLD LEMONADE "FREE TRIP
TO HEAVEN" STAND.
VERY ENTERPRISING.
JEWISH PEOPLE LIKE
LEMONADE, RIGHT?
OH, SURE.
IN FACT, I THINK MOSES HAD
THE FIRST SETUP ON MOUNT SINAI.
I'M -- I'M JUST SETTING IT UP,
UH, AT THE FRONT DOOR.
OH, AND I'M NOT GONNA
CHARGE.
WELL, IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA
CHARGE ANYTHING,
PEOPLE WON'T TAKE YOU
SERIOUSLY.
HOW ABOUT A NICKEL?
ALL RIGHT.
FINE,
DON'T CHARGE ANYONE.
I'M SURE THAT'LL WORK.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
HOW EVERYTHING GOES.
APPRECIATE IT.
UH, PETE...
YEAH?
JEWISH PEOPLE DO BELIEVE
IN HEAVEN,
JUST NOT THE SAME WAY
CHRISTIANS DO.
OURS INVOLVES
A LITTLE MORE WAITING.
WELL, MAYBE I COULD GET THE
PEOPLE WHO DON'T WANT TO WAIT.
OKAY.
HERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
SEE YOU LATER.
[ BELL DINGS ]
[ DISTANT TALKING ]
AH, MR. O'MALLEY.
JUST REMEMBER ROME
WASN'T BUILT IN A DAY.
HOW DO YOU MAKE
ANY MONEY HERE?
I'M FREE,
AND I STILL HAVE NOBODY.
I ENVY YOUR YOUTH.
YOU'LL DO BETTER
TOMORROW.
WELL, IT'S LATE TODAY,
THOUGH,
SO WHY DON'T I HELP YOU STORE
YOUR OFFICE?
WE'LL PUT HER RIGHT INSIDE
THE SYNAGOGUE DOOR THERE --
FOR FREE, OF COURSE.
YOU KNOW, YOU AND I
SEEM TO BE THE ONLY TWO
ON THIS BLOCK
THAT CARE ABOUT
FREE STUFF.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
WE REALIZE
WHAT WE HAVE TO OFFER
YOU CAN'T BUY.
EITHER THAT OR
YOUR LEMONADE STINKS.
IS THAT A POSSIBILITY?
DON'T TELL MOM WE CHARGED CANDY
AT THE PHARMACY.
OKAY, I WON'T.
HEY, YOU WANT TO PLAY
SOME BALL TOMORROW?
NO, I DON'T THINK I CAN.
I'M GOING TO
THE SYNAGOGUE AGAIN.
[ VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES ]
DOOR-TO-DOOR SERVICE.
IT'S A LOT TO ASK
FROM A PART-TIME SECRETARY.
RABBI JACOBSEN,
YOU'VE RECEIVED SIX MESSAGES.
OH, YEAH?
LISTEN, WHATEVER WE'RE PAYING
YOU, IT'S NOT ENOUGH,
NOT IF YOU'RE GONNA INSIST
ON GIVING ME CURBSIDE SERVICE.
WHAT IS THIS?
MEMBERS OF THE CONGREGATION
DON'T SEEM TO THINK
THIS LEMONADE STAND
IS SUCH A LAUGHING MATTER.
IT'S AGAINST JUDAISM.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS CONGREGATION --
THEY BARELY NOTICE
THIS SYNAGOGUE IS HERE
UNLESS IT'S
THE HIGH HOLIDAYS.
ALL HE'S DOING IS
ASKING PEOPLE TO THINK.
AND YOU'LL NOTICE,
WHEN YOU ASK PEOPLE TO THINK,
THAT'S WHEN THEY START
COMPLAINING.
BUT HE'S ADVERTISING
CHRISTIANITY.
NO, HE'S ADVERTISING
THOUGHT.
HE'S ASKING PEOPLE TO HAVE
A FREE CUP OF LEMONADE
AND MAYBE GAIN SOME INSIGHT
ABOUT HOW TO GET INTO HEAVEN.
IF THAT GOES AGAINST
PEOPLE'S WISHES, SO BE IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I WISH?
I WISH THERE WERE
A THOUSAND PETES
SETTING UP STANDS
ALL UP AND DOWN THE STREET.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU LIKE STIRRING THINGS UP.
YEAH. MY GENERATION,
THEY'RE CRAZY.
LUCKILY, YOUR LOVELY WIFE
IS RAISING DANIEL.
THAT IS A GOOD THING,
ISN'T IT?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
Margaret:
SEAMUS, GET DOWN HERE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OUT OF THE TUB?
GET BACK IN THERE.
I DON'T THINK THIS QUEST THING
IS GONNA WORK.
YOU'RE MISSING
SOME GREAT BASEBALL.
MULDOON SAYS HE'LL TRADE ME
AN ERNIE BANKS FOR A PETE ROSE.
DO IT.
TRADE FOR A CUB?
IT'S NOT ABOUT
WHO YOU ROOT FOR.
IT'S BUSINESS.
BANKS IS GONNA BE
A HALL-OF-FAMER.
WHO KNOWS ABOUT PETE ROSE?
HEY, THERE'S THE RABBI
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
[ SIREN WAILING ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER,
TIRES SQUEAL ]
I WONDER WHERE THE FIRE IS.
LET'S GO.
[ SIREN APPROACHING ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
RIGHT HERE!
THE WATER!
OVER HERE!
TAKE IT EASY, SIR.
THAT'S MY HOUSE.
THAT'S MY HOUSE!
I'M SORRY.
YOU CAN'T GO IN THERE.
MY SON'S IN THERE!
WHERE IS HE AT?
UPSTAIRS IN THE BACK!
THERE'S A WOMAN, TOO!
DANNY!
COME ON, LET'S GO.
WHERE'S DANNY?!
DANNY!
HONEY.
HE'S IN THE BACK!
[ Crying ] DANNY! DANNY!
HE'S IN THE BACK.
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
THEY'RE GONNA GET HIM.
HE'S IN THE BACK.
[ CRYING ]
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE GONNA GET HIM.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT,
OKAY?
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
HIS LEGS ARE MOVING.
HE'S GOTTA BE OKAY.
DANNY! DANNY!
HE'S ALL RIGHT, YEAH?
GET SOME OXYGEN ON HIM!
OKAY, THERE'S A WOMAN INSIDE --
ESTHER -- UPSTAIRS!
SAME PLACE!
IT'S GOTTA BE THE SAME PLACE!
NO, WE'RE GOING BACK.
JOE, IT'S TOO HOT.
LET GO OF ME!
KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
OH!
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
I'M ALL RIGHT.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH, I'M FINE.
ALL RIGHT, WE GOTTA GET BACK
AT THIS.
THERE'S STILL A LADY
IN THERE, GUYS.
JOE, IT'S TOO HOT!
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
[ SIGHS ]
HOW'S THE KID DOING?
HE'S GOOD.
YEAH?
ALL RIGHT?
DAD! DAD!
SEAMUS.
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU
NOT TO CHASE FIRE ENGINES?
AND YOU BROUGHT
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER?
HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE I TOLD YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE, HUH?
GET YOUR CAN HOME
RIGHT NOW.
STAY THERE UNTIL
I GET BACK.
SORRY, MA'AM.
THE FIRE WAS HUGE.
IT WAS REALLY BIG.
MM-HMM.
I WONDER
WHO THAT KID WAS.
[ WHISTLES ]
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I TOLD
YOU BOYS, HUH?
YOU DON'T CHASE FIRES.
YOU RUN AWAY FROM THEM.
YOU KNOW A LADY DIED
IN THAT FIRE TODAY?
WHO?
AN OLDER LADY WHO WAS
BABYSITTING THE RABBI'S KID.
SHE DIED.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING
IN THAT NEIGHBORHOOD ANYWAY?
HUH?
WHAT, A COUPLE OF MUTES?
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
YOU'RE BOTH GROUNDED.
YOU DO NOT LEAVE
THIS BLOCK.
IF I FIND OUT EITHER ONE
OF YOU LEFT THIS BLOCK,
YOU WILL GET A SPANKIN'
THAT YOU WILL STILL FEEL
ON YOUR 16th BIRTHDAY.
BUT THE BASEBALL FIELD...
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]],
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING UP?
HUH?
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
DAD, SEAMUS WAS
ONLY IN THE AREA
BECAUSE HE WAS
CHECKING UP ON ME.
SEE, I'M -- I'M ON MY QUEST
TO MEET A JEWISH PERSON
AND HELP THEM GET TO HEAVEN.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
I DON'T EVEN THINK JEWISH PEOPLE
BELIEVE IN HEAVEN THE WAY
YOU AND I DO.
I ASKED MOM,
AND SHE SAID THEY COULD BE
CONVERTED THROUGH JESUS.
WELL, I ALSO ASKED
FATHER KELLY IN RELIGION CLASS.
HE SAID IT'S THE ROLE
OF A GOOD CHRISTIAN.
HE SAID THAT?
MM-HMM.
SO, ANYWAYS,
I'VE BEEN GOING OVER TO
THE SYNAGOGUE ON GREENWOOD.
YOU'VE BEEN GOING OVER
TO THAT SYNAGOGUE?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR JEWISH PEOPLE THERE.
YEAH, ANY JEWS OVER THERE?
YEAH, I MET RABBI JACOBSEN.
HE'S LIKE A PRIEST
BUT NOT AS SCARY.
HE'S REALLY NICE.
MM-HMM.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
8...AND 1/2.
YOU SHOULD BE WORRIED
ABOUT BASEBALL
AND GOING TO THE SWIMMING POOL
AND BEING ASLEEP AT 9:00.
THAT'S ALL YOU SHOULD BE
WORRIED ABOUT, ALL RIGHT?
DON'T GO OVER TO THAT SYNAGOGUE
ANYMORE, ALL RIGHT?
YOU GO TO CHURCH,
YOU LET THE JEWISH PEOPLE
TAKE CARE OF THEMSELVES.
BUT I'M ON MY QUEST.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
DON'T TRY TO CHANGE
THE WORLD AT 8 1/2,
ALL RIGHT?
HEY, LOOK AT ME.
GO TO BED.
HEY, PETE...
YEAH?
GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, DAD.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
YOU KNOW, JOE, I CAN'T RAISE
THESE KIDS ALONE.
[ SIGHS ]
I'VE GAINED TOO MUCH WEIGHT
TO FIND A NEW HUSBAND
AT THIS POINT.
SO YOU'RE MY OPTION.
IF YOU WERE SKINNIER
WHEN WE MET,
THEN I SURE AS HELL
DON'T REMEMBER.
AND NO WAY I LIKED IT.
I LIKE SOMETHING
TO HOLD ONTO.
[ GROANS ] WELL, THEN...
GO HOLD ONTO SOMETHING,
HONEY,
BECAUSE SEX IS
NOT A CONVERSATION.
DO YOU KNOW PETE IS GOING OVER
TO A SYNAGOGUE,
TRYING TO CONVERT
JEWISH PEOPLE?
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT? I'M NOT FINDING THAT
AS FUNNY.
HONEY, HE'S A LITTLE BOY.
HE'S SEARCHING FOR MEANING
IN HIS LIFE, WHATEVER.
WHAT MEANING?
BASEBALL SHOULD BE
THE ONLY MEANING
IN AN 8-YEAR-OLD'S LIFE.
SOME KIDS ARE JUST DESTINED
FOR GREATER THINGS.
SOUNDS LIKE HE'S LOOKING
TO GET HIS ASS KICKED.
I TOLD HIM NOT TO GO OVER THERE,
AND DON'T YOU LET HIM
GO OVER THERE EITHER.
"I DON'T WANT YOU
TO LET HIM GO OVER THERE."
HONEY, I CAN'T WATCH THEM
ALL DAY LONG, EVERY ONE OF THEM.
COME ON, MOLLY'S A BABY.
SHE NEEDS MY CONSTANT ATTENTION.
PETE GOES OUT IN THE MORNING,
HE COMES BACK, HE'S ALL CLEAN,
NOBODY EVER CALLS TO SAY
HE'S BEEN IN ANY TROUBLE,
I THINK I'M DOING ALL RIGHT.
OH, THAT'S PARENTING 101.
HE'S CLEAN, AND
NOBODY SAYS HE'S TROUBLE.
WHAT AM I GONNA HAVE TO DO,
RAISE THE KIDS AND WORK?
DON'T START, JOE.
THAT IS JUST THE TERRITORY
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET INTO.
HEY...
HMM?
OH, NO.
HEY, IF WE WERE TO MAKE
A CHILD --
LET'S SAY WE WERE TO BRING
ANOTHER CHILD INTO THE WORLD
RIGHT NOW --
I PROMISE YOU
HE'D BE CLEAN,
AND HE WOULDN'T BE
ANY TROUBLE.
HONEY, YOU CAN'T JUST CLIMB
ON TOP OF ME,
FOR GOODNESS' SAKE.
IF IT'S MY WOMB
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR,
CHECK THE BOTTOM OF THE BED,
'CAUSE I WAS DUSTING
AROUND THERE TODAY.
I THINK IT FELL OUT.
[ VEHICLE PASSES BY,
DOG BARKS ]
HEY, THAT'S GIN.
WHAT?
YOU SHOULD BE A GARBAGEMAN
THE WAY YOU PICK UP
EVERY CARD I THROW DOWN.
YOU DO THAT TO PISS ME OFF?
NO, I DO IT TO WIN.
WELL, AND TO PISS YOU OFF
A LITTLE.
NOW, LET'S SEE --
500 TO 220...
AT, UH, WHAT,
A NICKEL A POINT.
[ Irish accent ] THAT'S,
UH, 14 BUCKS YOU OWE ME,
LIEUTENANT O'MALLEY.
HEY.
GENTLEMEN.
MY, UH, WIFE, SON, AND I
WANTED TO THANK YOU FOR
YOUR BRAVERY AND KINDNESS.
THANK YOU.
UH, HEY, YOU'RE WELCOME.
RABBI, JOE O'MALLEY.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND ALL THE GUYS,
WE JUST WANT TO SAY WE'RE
REAL SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS.
THANK YOU.
UH, ESTHER LIVED
A VERY GOOD LIFE.
SHE RAN MY SYNAGOGUE
LIKE AN ARMY BATTALION.
OH, YEAH?
UH, MY WIFE BELIEVES
THE BEST WAY TO THANK SOMEONE
IS THROUGH THEIR STOMACH.
SO SHE'S MADE SOME LASAGNA
FOR ALL OF YOU.
IT'S REAL GOOD.
I'LL BET IT IS.
YOU KNOW,
SHE SHOULDN'T HAVE.
I MEAN, MY GUYS, UH,
THEY LOVE A GOOD MEAL,
ESPECIALLY THAT ONE,
BUT, UH, REALLY, HONESTLY,
WE'RE JUST DOING OUR JOB.
WELL, IT'S A HEROIC JOB
YOU DO,
AND SHE WANTED TO THANK YOU
PERSONALLY,
AND I'M SURE MY SYNAGOGUE'S
GONNA WANT TO THANK YOU
FORMALLY.
OH, YEAH.
Man: CHECK THIS OUT.
IT TAKES TWO GUYS TO HOLD
THIS THING TO FIRE.
IN THE JEWISH TRADITION,
WE, UH, SIT SHIVA.
IT'S FOR THE MOURNERS
OF THE DECEASED.
YEAH, YEAH, WE GOT SOMETHING
SIMILAR CALLED A WAKE.
RIGHT.
IT'S LIKE A WAKE.
SORT OF.
ANYWAYS,
I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY,
BUT I MENTION IT 'CAUSE
I'D BE HONORED IF YOU'D STOP BY
AND SIT WITH MY FAMILY AND
FRIENDS FOR A FEW MINUTES.
OH, YEAH, SURE, YOU JUST
LET ME KNOW WHERE IT IS, AND
I'LL TRY AND STOP BY, YEAH.
Man: OKAY, NOW CAREFUL.
[ GRUNTS ]
SHHHH!
YEAH! GET THAT FIRE.
ESTHER HAD ONE
LIVING RELATIVE.
THEY'RE FROM OUT OF TOWN, SO
WE'LL BE DOING IT AT MY PL--
WELL, MY IN-LAWS' PLACE.
OH, YEAH.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO LIVE
WITH YOUR IN-LAWS?
Danny: DAD! CHECK ME OUT!
THERE'S TROUBLE.
YEAH, GOOD JOB.
OVER THERE, OVER THERE!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE NOW?
[ LAUGHS ]
UH-OH.
AH, ALL KIDS LOVE
FIRE TRUCKS, HUH?
YEAH.
THEY CERTAINLY UNDERSTAND
THAT LIFE IS FOR LIVING, HUH?
HMM.
YOU HAVE CHILDREN?
OH, YEAH. I GOT EIGHT.
EIGHT?!
YEAH.
WOW, YOU'RE A BLESSED MAN.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE "CURSED" IS A BETTER WORD.
[ LAUGHS ]
BY ANY CHANCE, A, UH, YOUNG,
HANDSOME REDHEAD NAMED PETE
WOULDN'T BE IN THE O'MALLEY CLAN
OF YOURS, WOULD HE?
LISTEN, YOU SHOULD KNOW
YOUR BRAVERY'S BEEN PASSED ON.
HE MAY BE ONE OF
THE MORE EARNEST YOUNG MEN
I'VE EVER MET.
LISTEN,
I WANT TO TELL YOU,
I JUST FOUND OUT HE'S BEING
A NUISANCE OVER THERE
AT YOUR TEMPLE,
AND I'VE TALKED TO HIM,
REPRIMANDED HIM,
AND BELIEVE ME, HE'S NOT GONNA
BE BOTHERING YOU ANYMORE.
I RESPECT YOUR WISHES.
YOU SHOULD KNOW, THOUGH,
THAT HE'S WELCOME
AT MY TEMPLE ANYTIME.
YEAH.
NICE AND SHORT --
THE HAIR.
I GOTTA BATTLE WITH MY KIDS
TO KEEP THEIR HAIR SHORT.
THAT'S THE WAY A KID'S HAIR
SHOULD BE.
YEAH, HE'S, UH, HE'S ACTUALLY
TRYING TO GROW HIS OUT.
UH, HE UNDERWENT CHEMOTHERAPY
ABOUT SIX MONTHS AGO --
UH, LEUKEMIA.
LEUKEMIA?
YEAH.
HE'S IN REMISSION.
WE'RE ALL VERY HOPEFUL.
GOD HAS A PLAN...
ALBEIT A MYSTERIOUS ONE,
FOR MY FAMILY.
SO, LOOK, WHEN YOU GET
THE TIME,
UH, COME ON BY AND --
AND BRING PETE.
SURE.
I THINK IT WOULD DO
EVERYBODY'S SPIRIT'S GOOD
TO SEE A YOUNG MAN
SO FULL OF LIFE
THE WAY YOUR SON IS.
YEAH, YEAH, HE'S FULL OF
SOMETHING. [ CHUCKLES ]
Children on TV:
LEFT FOOT, RIGHT FOOT,
GO, GO, GO!
LEFT FOOT, RIGHT FOOT...
HEY, GETTING THE MAIL'S
MY JOB!
IT'S YOUR JOB?
YOU WANT THE MAIL?
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU WANT THE MAIL,
HUH? HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR?
BILLS...BILL...
BILLS.
NOTHING BUT BILLS.
...SPECIAL GUEST
IN THE CLUBHOUSE TODAY.
HE CAME ALL THE WAY
FROM THE LINCOLN PARK ZOO!
COME ON.
LET'S SAY A BIG HELLO
TO ZOOKEEPER ROB!
HEY, I DIDN'T SAY YOU COULD GO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Margaret:
PETER, SEAMUS -- NOW!
LET'S GO!
GET IN HERE!
OH, HONEY, PLEASE,
CAN I BE THE YELLER TODAY?
OKAY, IS THAT EVERYTHING?
YES.
NOTHING UNDER YOUR BEDS?
COME ON.
NOPE.
NOTHING IN THE CLOSET?
MNH-MNH. NOPE.
YOU DIDN'T HIDE ANYTHING
IN YOUR SISTER'S ROOM?
UNH-UNH.
IN THE BATHTUB?
MOM, IT'S ALL IN THERE.
NOTHING BEHIND THE DOORS?
YOU DON'T HAVE TWO PAIRS OF
PANTS ON RIGHT NOW, DO YOU?
'CAUSE I'M WASHING
EVERYTHING.
NO, IT'S ALL IN THERE.
ANYTHING IN THE SINK?
WHAT TIME --
NOTHING UNDER THE BEDS...
WHAT TIME DOES
THE BOYS' GAME START?
Seamus: 6:00, BUT IT'S
A DOUBLE-HEADER.
MM-HMM.
UNCLE ROGER'S COMING.
SO IS BILLY AND ROBERT JR.
YEAH...
DID YOU FINISH YOUR CHORES?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, YOU AND I ARE INVITED
TO A "CHIVAS" AT THE RABBI'S.
CHIVAS?
YEAH, IT'S KIND OF
LIKE A WAKE.
I TOLD THEM
WE'D TRY AND STOP BY.
WELL, HOW'S HE DOING?
WELL, I DON'T THINK
HE'S TOO HAPPY.
THAT LADY THAT DIED WAS HIS
SECRETARY FOR, LIKE, 40 YEARS
OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T THINK HE'S TOO HAPPY
RIGHT NOW.
HONEY, HE LOST SOMEBODY
HE LOVES VERY, VERY MUCH,
AND I'M SURE HE'LL BE SAD
FOR A WHILE.
HIS LITTLE BOY WAS SAVED,
AND THAT'S THE GOOD SIDE,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO, ANYWAY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, HUH?
TELL RABBI JACOBSEN
I'M SORRY.
CAN I HEAR
A "THANK YOU, DAD"?
THANK YOU, DAD!
THERE YOU GO.
SO WE'LL GO, AND THEN
WE'LL CATCH THE SECOND GAME,
ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT -- THE RABBI'S
SON IS YOUR AGE, HONEY.
SO WHEN YOU GO THERE,
YOU SAY TO HIM HOW SORRY
YOU ARE, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY, I WILL, MOM.
ALL RIGHT.
HE'S PROBABLY JEWISH,
RIGHT?
I WOULD THINK THERE'S
A HIGH LIKELIHOOD OF THAT.
I NEED YOU TO WASH UP, HONEY.
HERE, YOU CAN WEAR
THIS AND THIS.
HERE, PUT THOSE ON.
TUCK THE SHIRT IN,
WASH YOUR FACE.
OKAY, MOM, I WILL.
SOAP AND WATER.
I WILL, MOM.
OKAY.
YOU DO THE SAME THING.
GO WASH YOUR FACE.
I LOVE IT WHEN YOU TALK TO ME
LIKE I'M 9.
WELL, WHO ELSE DO I TALK TO
ALL DAY BUT --
COME HERE. HEY.
WHAT?
YOU WANT TO MAKE OUT?
WITH YOU?
[ CHUCKLES ]
I DON'T WANT TO GO
TO THE RABBI'S
OR WHEREVER THIS THING IS.
HONEY, YOU SAID YOU WOULD,
AND YOU'RE GONNA GO.
YEAH, SO, I CAN'T SAY NO TO HIM
RIGHT THERE.
I MEAN, JEEZ...
THE GUY LOSES THE LADY THAT HE'S
KNOWN ALL OF HIS LIFE.
HIS HOUSE IS IN ASHES.
BESIDES THAT,
HIS KID'S GOT LEUKEMIA.
WHAT?
YEAH.
I MEAN, HOW AM I GONNA SAY NO
TO THAT?
WHY, YOU DON'T.
IT'S THAT OLD
ELECTRICAL WIRING.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
HEY, MOM.
OH, HI, HONEY.
HOW YOU DOING?
YOUR DINNER'S WARM.
IT'S IN THE OVEN.
USE THAT TOWEL THERE.
DON'T BURN YOUR HAND.
YOU WANT SOMETHING TO DRINK
WITH THAT?
UH, NO. I'M ALL RIGHT.
WATER?
NO.
HEY, LIFESAVER.
YOUR MA SAYS YOU GOT
SOMETHING TO TELL ME.
UH...
I THINK I'M GONNA TAKE A LOOK
AT THAT JOB
AT THE CITY PLANNER'S
OFFICE.
THAT'S A GOOD JOB.
IT'S GOT NICE BENEFITS.
I'LL TALK TO ALDERMAN McMANUS
ABOUT IT.
WHAT?
WHAT'S THAT LOOK?
DON'T EVEN GO IN THERE
IF YOU'RE GONNA GO IN THERE
WITH THAT ATTITUDE, PAL.
ALL RIGHT?
THE ALDERMAN'S
DOING US A FAVOR, OKAY?
SO DON'T GO IN THERE ACTING
LIKE A PUNK.
A LOT OF KIDS YOUR AGE
DON'T HAVE A CHANCE LIKE THIS.
NO, ACTUALLY, A LOT OF KIDS
MY AGE GO TO COLLEGE.
AND THEY'RE FOUR YEARS BEHIND
EVERYONE ELSE IN THE WORKFORCE,
AND WHAT HAVE THEY LEARNED?
HOW TO SMOKE POT
AND HOW TO SLEEP ALL DAY.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT THE GOOD JOBS
REQUIRE, REQUIRE
A COLLEGE DEGREE TODAY?
A CITY JOB IS A GOOD JOB,
AND ALL IT REQUIRES
IS A LITTLE HARD WORK
AND THE RIGHT ATTITUDE.
THAT'S MY ONLY CHOICE, THEN --
THE IRISH WAY. THAT'S IT? HUH?
I GOTTA GET A CITY JOB, WORK
MY ASS OFF, HAVE 40 KIDS, HUH?
SO I CAN RETIRE
ON A CRAP PENSION
AND LIVE IN THE SAME HOUSE
I'VE LIVED IN MY WHOLE LIFE?!
HEY, YOU LOWER YOUR VOICE.
THAT'S OUR LIFE YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT, PAL.
WHAT, YOU WANT TO BE
A HOTSHOT DOCTOR,
HAVE 1.2 KIDS AND A BIG HOUSE
IN THE SUBURBS
WITH ENOUGH LOVE TO FILL
A CLOSET
SO THAT YOU CAN FINALLY RETIRE
TO FLORIDA
AND DIE LIKE A RAISIN?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
MAYBE I DO.
WHY CAN'T I JUST DO THAT?!
THEN GO AHEAD!
BE LIKE THE JEWS!
HAVE NO MORE THAN TWO KIDS
'CAUSE IT'S NOT ECONOMICAL
TO HAVE MORE!
RAISE YOUR KIDS TO BASE
THEIR LIFE
ON THE SIZE OF THEIR WALLET!
YEAH, THAT'S --
THAT'S RIGHT, POP. YEAH.
WHY IN THE WORLD SHOULD
I RAISE MY KIDS
TO BASE THEIR WORTH ON THE SIZE
OF THEIR WALLET?
THAT'S CRAZY!
YOU SHOULD BASE IT TO SEE HOW
MUCH BOOZE THEY CAN DRINK
WITHOUT PUKING, HUH?
IS THAT IT?
JOE! JOE!
HUH?! HUH?!
YOU UNGRATEFUL,
SMART-MOUTH PUNK.
YOU GOT ALL THE ANSWERS AT 18,
DON'T YOU?
HUH?
NO...I DON'T.
MAYBE IF I GO WORK AT THE CITY
PLANNER'S OFFICE,
I'LL GET THEM BY THE TIME
I TURN 40, LIKE YOU, HUH?
LET IT GO, JOE.
YOU BETTER GET OUT OF HERE
RIGHT NOW.
I'M LEAVING.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT KID?
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
GIVE THESE TO THAT MAN.
HI. I'M JEFFREY JACOBSEN,
RABBI KENNY'S BROTHER.
JOE O'MALLEY.
MY SON PETE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
OH, IT'S, UH --
I'LL GO PUT THESE
IN THE KITCHEN.
THANKS.
ESTHER LOVED FLOWERS.
OKAY, GOOD.
HEY.
HEY. HOW YOU DOING?
GOOD.
HEY, WANT TO CHECK OUT THE ROOM
THAT I'M STAYING IN?
SURE. CAN I?
SURE. YEAH. GO AHEAD.
CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING
TO DRINK?
UH, YEAH. I'LL JUST HAVE
A SCOTCH IF YOU GOT IT.
UH, I'LL HAVE TO CHECK TO SEE IF
I HAVE ANY SCOTCH. IF NOT...
OH, A BEER WOULD BE FINE.
OKAY, I'LL HAVE TO, UH,
I'LL HAVE TO CHECK TO SEE
IF I HAVE ANY BEER.
IF NOT, UM...
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M FINE.
YOU SURE?
NO, I'M ABSOLUTELY FINE.
THANK YOU.
OH, MRS. JACOBSEN.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
OH, I'M SORRY ABOUT...
WHAT HAPPENED.
YOUR SON LOOKS GOOD.
YEAH, HE DOES, DOESN'T HE?
YEAH, HE LOOKS GOOD.
RABBI, HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD, GOOD.
THANKS FOR COMING.
MY PLEASURE TO BE HERE.
APPRECIATE IT.
WELL, YEAH.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
CAN WE GET YOU ANYTHING?
UH, WATER WOULD BE FINE...
IF YOU GOT WATER.
DO YOU PLAY ON A TEAM?
NO. I COULDN'T THIS YEAR.
I GOT LEUKEMIA.
IT'S CANCER.
I TOOK THIS MEDICINE
THAT MADE ME LOSE MY HAIR,
BUT IT'S GROWING BACK.
DID IT HURT?
NO. JUST FELL OUT.
I DON'T REALLY FEEL IT,
BUT IT'S BEEN IN REMISSION
FOR SIX MONTHS.
REMISSION?
MEANS
IT'S STILL KIND OF THERE,
BUT IT'S NOT REALLY
BOTHERING ME.
I SWEAR, MY HAIR WASN'T THIS
LIGHT BEFORE.
WAS THE FIRE SCARY?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
I WAS UPSTAIRS PLAYING
IN MY ROOM,
AND THEN I SAW A LOT
OF SMOKE.
THEN YOUR DAD CAME IN
AND SAVED MY LIFE.
BUT IT'S NOTHING LIKE THE FIRE
DRILLS WE DO IN SCHOOL.
SPEAKING OF SCHOOL,
WHAT GRADE ARE YOU IN?
I'M GOING INTO SECOND OVER
AT BRIARWOOD.
I'M GOING INTO THIRD
OVER AT HOLY CROSS.
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO BE JEWISH?
I DON'T KNOW.
GOOD.
I'M CATHOLIC.
WHAT'S THAT LIKE?
NOISIER.
THINGS ARE USUALLY NOISIER
AROUND HERE,
BUT IT'S BEEN QUIETER BECAUSE
OF THE SHIVA.
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN
AT MY UNCLE JIM'S FUNERAL.
YOU WOULD'VE THOUGHT
IT WAS A BIRTHDAY PARTY.
MY MOM SAID THAT EVERYONE'S SAD
BECAUSE THE PERSON DIED,
BUT THEN AGAIN, THEY'RE HAPPY
BECAUSE HE GETS TO GO TO HEAVEN.
JEWISH PEOPLE CAN'T GO
TO HEAVEN.
WHY NOT?
'CAUSE THEY'RE JEWISH.
GOD DOESN'T LET JEWISH PEOPLE
INTO HEAVEN.
BUT IF YOU'RE INTERESTED,
MAYBE I COULD HELP
YOU GET TO HEAVEN.
YEAH?
YEP.
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS CONVERT YOU.
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY CONVERTED
ANYONE BEFORE.
SO WHAT CAN I DO IN HEAVEN?
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
THEY CALL IT PARADISE.
SOUNDS GOOD.
SO WHEN CAN WE START?
MEET ME AT YOUR SYNAGOGUE
TOMORROW.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT A RAIN DELAY?
Man: YEAH, 15 MINUTES, JOE.
OH, YEAH? ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE'LL STAY HERE.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
SO, DANNY'S A GOOD KID, HUH?
YEAH. HIS HAIR'S SHORT BECAUSE
OF THE MEDICINE,
BUT IT'S GROWING BACK.
YOU DIDN'T TRY
SAYING ANYTHING TO HIM
ABOUT WHAT WE, UH,
TALKED ABOUT, DID YOU?
BUT, DAD, DANNY WANTS
TO DO IT, ALSO.
WHAT DID I SAY?
HIS FAMILY IS JEWISH.
HE'S JEWISH.
THEY DON'T WANT TO BE
CHRISTIAN.
BUT IT'S A QUEST.
YOUR QUEST IS CALLED OFF,
MY FRIEND.
BUT I PROMISED DANNY.
WE'RE MEETING
AT THE SYNAGOGUE --
NO, YOU'RE NOT!
YOU DON'T GO TRYING TO CONVERT
JEWISH KIDS
THE SAME WAY THEY DON'T COME
OVER HERE TRYING TO CONVERT US!
BUT HE WANTS TO DO IT.
I SAID NO, AND I DON'T WANT TO
HEAR ANOTHER WORD FROM YOU!
YOU DO NOT GO TO THAT TEMPLE
ANYMORE.
YOU DO NOT BOTHER DANNY
OR HIS FAMILY ANYMORE.
AND, SO HELP ME, GOD,
IF I FIND OUT YOU'VE BEEN GOING
OVER THERE,
YOU'RE GONNA GET THE SPANKING
OF A LIFETIME,
AND YOU'RE GONNA BE GROUNDED
UNTIL YOU'RE 16,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?!
YES, SIR.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
MR. O'MALLEY.
YOU LOST?
HEY, FATHER.
NO, I'M NOT LOST.
I JUST HAVE A LOT MORE
QUESTIONS THAN ANSWERS.
AH.
[ SIGHS ]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M JUST GONNA CHECK OUT WHAT
THIS PLACE LOOKS LIKE
FROM YOUR SEAT.
THAT'S MY CHAIR.
DON'T BREAK IT.
DO YOU GET THE COLLECTION
MONEY?
[ Chuckles ] NO.
WHY,
DID SOMEONE TELL YOU I DID?
NO. BUT THEN,
HOW DO YOU GET PAID?
[ SIGHS ] DON'T YOU NEED TO GET
HOME, MR. O'MALLEY?
YOUR JOB IS TO HELP PEOPLE
GET TO HEAVEN, RIGHT?
YES.
BUT HAVE YOU EVER ACTUALLY SEEN
SOMEONE IN HEAVEN?
NO.
WELL, THEN, HOW DO YOU KNOW
IF THEY MADE IT TO HEAVEN?
FAITH.
FAITH?
YEP.
BELIEVING IN SOMETHING
COMPLETELY
WITHOUT ACTUALLY HAVING
ANY PROOF OF IT.
FAITH.
I-I DON'T HAVE ANY PROOF
OF HEAVEN,
BUT I HAVE FAITH IT EXISTS.
WHAT'S THE BEST WAY
TO GET TO HEAVEN?
BELIEVING IN JESUS.
LIVING THE WAY HE TAUGHT US
TO LIVE.
WELL, HOW DO WE KNOW
IF WE'RE DOING THAT?
IS THERE, LIKE,
SOME KIND OF TEST?
WELL, YOUR LIFE IS THE TEST.
SO, THEN, YOU HAVE TO DIE
TO FIND OUT HOW YOU DID
ON THE TEST.
I GUESS SO.
DON'T YOU JUST ONCE
WANT TO KNOW
IF ONE OF THE PEOPLE YOU PRAY
FOR MADE IT TO HEAVEN?
[ SIGHS ]
IN DUE TIME.
WHAT'S THE PURPOSE
OF COMMUNION?
TO MAKE A PART OF JESUS
A PART OF US.
WELL, THEN, WHY DO I HAVE TO
WAIT TILL THIRD GRADE?
I MEAN,
WOULDN'T IT HELP ME NOW?
THE CHURCH BELIEVES
THAT CATHOLICS
SHOULD FULFILL
A FEW REQUIREMENTS
BEFORE THEY EARN THE SACRAMENT
OF COMMUNION.
LIKE PASSING A FEW TESTS.
YES.
SO IF I PASS ALL THE TESTS,
I CAN GET COMMUNION?
YES.
THANKS, FATHER.
YOU CLEARED UP
QUITE A FEW THINGS FOR ME.
[ HORN HONKING, BIRDS CHIRPING ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OUR QUEST HAS TO BE DONE
IN SECRET.
OUR MISSION
IS NOW UNDERCOVER.
WHY?
JUST FOLLOW ME.
SO, THIS DOESN'T ACTUALLY REALLY
LOOK LIKE IT'S UNDERCOVER,
BUT WHY ARE WE UNDERCOVER?
WELL, 'CAUSE.
SO, WHAT'S OUR MISSION?
TO GET YOU TO HEAVEN.
RIGHT. SO, HOW AM I GONNA GET
TO HEAVEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU GOTTA HAVE SOME IDEAS.
WELL...
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO SET UP
SOME TESTS.
HAVE YOU TAKEN
ANY OF THESE TESTS?
NEXT YEAR, I HAVE TO COMPLETE
FIRST-COMMUNION TRAINING.
WHAT'S COMMUNION?
THIS PIECE OF BREAD
THAT'S JESUS.
AND YOU EAT IT?
YEAH.
GROSS!
SO I SHOULD DO THE
FIRST-COMMUNION TRAINING,
SHOULDN'T I?
WELL, I HAVEN'T DONE IT YET,
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE.
BUT WE CAN MAKE UP SOME TESTS
OF OUR OWN.
HOW ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE
A BRUCE JENNER?
WIN THE DECATHLON,
GO TO HEAVEN.
YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AND THEN WE SHOULD HAVE
A GOLD-MEDAL CEREMONY.
GOTTA HAVE A MEDAL.
COMMUNION CAN BE OUR MEDAL.
R-I-I-I-IGHT.
HEY, WAIT UP!
NO, I'M GONNA BEAT YOU!
[ TRAIN RUMBLING ]
DID YOU KNOW
THAT MY MOM AND DAD
DON'T LET ME ON THE EL
WITHOUT THEM?
YEAH, BUT FATHER KELLY
AT THE CHURCH,
HE ALWAYS TALKS ABOUT
THIS RISK REWARD.
SO YOU'LL BE OKAY IF YOUR
PARENTS FIND OUT.
YOU'LL JUST EXPLAIN TO THEM THAT
THE RISK IS WORTH THE REWARD.
OKAY, ANYWAYS, LISTEN.
I HEARD BRUCE JENNER SAY
THAT THE KEY TO WINNING THE
DECATHLON IS TO STAY FOCUSED.
YOU STAY FOCUSED ON
THE DECATHLON,
FORGET
ABOUT EVERYTHING ELSE,
AND THEN, UH, YOU CAN, UH,
GET TO THE COMMUNION PART
OF IT.
♪ IN THE SUMMERTIME
WHEN THE WEATHER IS HOT ♪
♪ YOU CAN STRETCH RIGHT UP
AND TOUCH THE SKY ♪
♪ WHEN THE WEATHER'S FINE ♪
♪ YOU GOT WOMEN, YOU GOT WOMEN
ON YOUR MIND ♪
♪ HAVE A DRINK,
HAVE A DRIVE... ♪
IF YOU SEE MY SISTER,
JUST START RUNNING.
BUT HOW WILL I KNOW
IT'S YOUR SISTER?
I'LL BE RUNNING.
RIGHT.
♪ ...IF HER DADDY'S POOR,
JUST DO WHAT YOU FEEL ♪
♪ SPEED ALONG THE LANE... ♪
OOF!
YOU GOTTA WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE GOIN'.
YOU OKAY?
THEY SEEM TO BE STARTING YOUNGER
AND YOUNGER THESE DAYS.
♪ ...WE'RE NOT DIRTY,
WE'RE NOT MEAN ♪
♪ WE LOVE EVERYBODY,
BUT WE DO AS WE PLEASE... ♪
COME ON.
LISTEN...
YOU HAVE TO GET SERIOUS.
BRUCE JENNER IS FASTER,
STRONGER,
AND CAN JUMP HIGHER
THAN ANYONE ELSE I KNOW.
SO I FIGURE THAT THAT'S HOW
WE SHOULD DO THE DECATHLON.
OKAY, I'M FAST.
WELL, FIRST YOU HAVE TO BE
BAPTIZED.
[ GIGGLING ]
AHH!
AMEN!
I THINK IT WOULD'VE BEEN EASIER
IF YOU WERE A BABY.
ON YOUR MARK...
GET SET...
GO!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
ALL RIGHT!
GOOD JOB!
THANKS.
ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE.
♪ ...WE'LL GO DRIVING
OR MAYBE WE'LL SETTLE DOWN ♪
TRY TO THROW PAST
THAT LINE.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA.
THAT WAS A GOOD THROW.
SO, WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
WELL, IN THE OLYMPICS,
I'VE SEEN THEM DO HURDLES.
BUT WHAT COULD WE HURDLE?
[ SIGHS ]
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
GO FOR IT.
HEY!
HEY, YOU!
WHOA!
[ LAUGHING ]
OH, SHOOT!
WHOA.
WE REALLY NEED THE RIGHT ROCK
TO DO THIS.
YOU WANT THE SURFACE TO BE FLAT
LIKE THIS.
MY RECORD'S, LIKE,
FIVE SKIPS.
OKAY, MAYBE THAT WAS
A LITTLE TOO HARD.
THIS ONE?
YEAH, YOU COULD TRY IT.
MIGHT NOT WORK,
BUT YOU COULD TRY IT.
THAT...
WAS A REALLY GOOD THROW.
I COULD BEAT IT,
I JUST NEED A REALLY GOOD ROCK.
NO. NO. NO.
THAT'S NO GOOD.
[ Chuckles ]
HEH HEH HEH.
YEAH, YEAH.
HOW YA DOIN'?
Danny: NO WONDER PEOPLE DIE
TRYING TO GET TO HEAVEN.
THE LAST ONE'S
GOTTA BE TOUGH.
I DON'T KNOW.
'CAUSE SOME OF THOSE
WERE REAL TOUGH.
YEAH, BUT THE LAST ONE'S GOTTA
BE REALLY, REALLY TOUGH.
SOMETHING THAT TAKES STRENGTH,
SPEED, AND COURAGE.
I DON'T KNOW.
SWIM OUT TO THE BUOY.
I CAN'T EVEN SEE THE BUOY.
I CAN'T GET THERE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO IF YOU WANT
TO WIN THE DECATHLON.
GO AHEAD.
[ GASPING ]
Danny: HELP! I NEED HELP!
YOU PASSED 9 OUT OF 10
TESTS.
GOD'S GOTTA BE HAPPY
WITH YOU.
YEAH, BUT I DON'T KNOW IF I'M
GONNA PASS THE LAST ONE.
THAT'S TOUGH.
I REALLY WANT TO PASS
THE DECATHLON.
I WANT TO GO TO HEAVEN.
Pete: DO KIDS DIE
FROM WHAT YOU HAVE?
WELL, I HEARD SOME ADULTS
WHISPERING ABOUT IT.
ADULTS ALWAYS GET QUIET WHEN
THEY TALK ABOUT DEATH.
SOMETIMES I HEAR MY PARENTS TALK
ABOUT IT LATE AT NIGHT.
SOMETIMES THEY START TO CRY.
I DON'T WANT THEM TO FEEL SAD
IF I DIE.
WELL,
THERE'S OUR LITTLE MAN.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
[ SPEAKING HEBREW ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THANKING GOD FOR THE FOOD.
YEAH, BUT WHAT WAS THAT YOU DID
AS I BEGAN THE PRAYER?
OH, YOU MEAN THIS?
YEAH.
WELL, IT'S LIKE PICKING UP
A PHONE AND CALLING GOD.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
HE WAS THERE TO HEAR YOU.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, THIS QUEST
FOR HEAVEN --
IT'S, UH, IT'S A GOOD THING,
OF COURSE,
BUT AS JEWISH PEOPLE, WE HAVE
OUR OWN RITUALS AND CUSTOMS...
DIFFERENT THAN PETE'S.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I TAUGHT PETE SOME OF THEM,
BUT I LIKE THIS ONE.
I SEE.
[ SPEAKING HEBREW RAPIDLY ]
BUT LET'S, UH...
LET'S MAYBE DO THIS LESS...
AS IN NOT AT ALL.
OKAY.
THANKS.
THERE YOU GO.
IT PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE GOOD
FOR BUSINESS
IF THE RABBI'S SON CONVERTS
TO CHRISTIANITY.
I WOULDN'T THINK SO.
NO.
KENNY, MAYBE THIS IS GOING
TOO FAR.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE ME DO,
TELL OUR SON HE CAN'T GO OUT
AND PLAY WITH PETE?
WOULD THAT MAKE YOU HAPPY?
I DON'T THINK IT'S ABOUT
MAKING ME HAPPY.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT YOU BENDING
OVER BACKWARDS
NOT TO MAKE WAVES
WITH YOUR SON.
MAKE WAVES.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA LET OUR
CHILDREN MAKE CHOICES IN LIFE,
THAT WE WERE GONNA TRY TO BE
A LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT
THAN OUR PARENTS WERE
WITH US.
LEAVE MY PARENTS
OUT OF THIS.
WAS I ALONE WHEN WE TALKED
ABOUT THIS?
NO, BUT I DON'T THINK
THIS IS THE TIME
FOR OUR CHILD
TO BE MAKING THESE CHOICES.
OR MAYBE
IT'S THE BEST TIME.
WHY? SO DANNY CAN COVER ALL
OF HIS BASES?
IT'S NOT ABOUT
COVERING BASES.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
OUR SON WENT OUT...
ENJOYING HIMSELF...
PLAYING...
LIKE A BOY?
NOT LIKE A SICK BOY, JUST...
A BOY.
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS. I'LL NEED IT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
HELP, PETE! HELP!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
IT, AND THEN YOU DON'T.
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, YOU MAKE IT BACK FINE
WITH ME.
I KNOW.
SO, THEN, WHAT'S WRONG?
WELL, I LOOK UP TO SEE
WHERE THE BUOY IS,
AND I CAN'T SEE IT.
AND THEN I REALIZE HOW FAR OUT
I AM, AND THEN, WELL...
WHAT IF I GO WITH YOU?
UM, NO.
I GOTTA DO IT ALONE.
MMM...
BUT WHAT IF YOU DON'T
LOOK UP?
BUT THEN I DON'T KNOW
WHERE I AM.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL FIGURE THIS OUT.
I CAN SEE FINE.
I CAN SEE IT FROM HERE,
BUT WHEN I GET IN THE WATER,
I CAN'T SEE IT,
AND THEN EVERYTHING STARTS
GETTING REALLY FAST,
AND I CAN'T GO
ANY FURTHER.
STAY RIGHT HERE AND WATCH ME
SWIM TO THE BUOY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
51...
52...
53...
54...
55.
LISTEN, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS COUNT YOUR STROKES.
IT TOOK ME 50 STROKES THERE
AND 55 STROKES BACK.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO LOOK UP.
CAN YOU COUNT TO 50?
YEAH.
I'M A LITTLE BIGGER,
SO IT MIGHT TAKE YOU
A FEW MORE STROKES.
CAN YOU COUNT TO 60?
YEP.
WELL, THEN JUST COUNT TO 60
STROKES, AND THEN SWIM BACK.
OKAY. I CAN DO THAT.
BUT LET'S DO IT TOMORROW.
MEET ME UNDER THE STAIRS
AT THE SYNAGOGUE.
RIGHT. TOMORROW.
TOMORROW YOU COMPLETE
THE DECATHLON.
DANNY SAID
I MIGHT FIND YOU HERE.
WELL, UH, I DON'T KNOW HOW HE
KNEW I WOULD BE HERE.
HE SAID TELL YOU HE COULDN'T
COMPLETE THE DECATHLON TODAY.
WELL, TELL HIM I CAN MEET HIM
TOMORROW.
TOMORROW'S NO GOOD,
EITHER.
HE'S GOT TO SEE THE DOCTOR
ABOUT HIS CANCER.
I THINK HE'S FINE.
I THINK SO, TOO.
ARE THEY GONNA GIVE HIM
ANY MORE OF THAT MEDICINE
THAT MAKES HIM
LOSE HIS HAIR?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT A DOCTOR.
MY OLDEST BROTHER WANTS TO
BECOME A DOCTOR.
YEAH?
COULD ALWAYS USE ANOTHER
GOOD DOCTOR.
MY DAD SAYS THEY PLAY
TOO MUCH GOLF,
AND THEY CHARGE
LIKE BASTARDS.
SEAMUS SAYS IT'S OKAY
TO SAY SWEAR WORDS
AS LONG AS YOU'RE SAYING WHAT
THE PERSON BEFORE YOU SAID.
SEAMUS SOUNDS LIKE HE'LL BE
A GOOD JOURNALIST SOMEDAY.
TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR OLDER BROTHER.
IS HE, UH, STUDYING MEDICINE
IN SCHOOL?
NO, HE CAN'T AFFORD IT.
MEDICINE'S VERY EXPENSIVE.
CERTAINLY WORTH IT, THOUGH,
IF YOU WORK HARD.
RABBI, WHEN DO YOU THINK DANNY
WILL BE BETTER?
[ SIGHS ]
I THINK THAT ONE'S
IN GOD'S HANDS.
WELL, YOU'RE CLOSE TO GOD.
HOPEFULLY THAT RUBS OFF
A LITTLE ON DANNY.
I REALLY HOPE HE GETS BETTER
SOON.
WE'VE GOT SOME UNFINISHED
BUSINESS TO HANDLE.
I CERTAINLY HOPE YOU GET TO TAKE
CARE OF THAT BUSINESS.
FOR NOW, WHAT DANNY NEEDS
IS OUR PRAYERS.
OKAY.
I'LL PRAY TO JESUS,
AND YOU PRAY TO GOD,
AND HOPEFULLY ONE OF THE TWO
WILL ANSWER.
THAT'S A DEAL.
SEE YOU LATER,
RABBI JACOBSEN.
OH, THAT WAS GOOD.
THANK YOU, DEAR.
YOU KNOW, UM,
THE RABBI CALLED
AND SAID HE WANTED TO STOP BY
AFTER DINNER,
AND I SAID IT WAS OKAY.
RABBI?
MM-HMM.
JEWISH PEOPLE GO OVERBOARD
WITH THIS GRATITUDE STUFF,
DON'T THEY?
HONEY, I DON'T THINK IT HAS
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH HIM BEING JEWISH.
HE'S JUST SAYING THANK YOU.
WHERE'S KNUCKLEHEAD?
MOM,
WHERE DOES THIS DISH GO?
HE CALLED,
HE SAID HE'D BE LATE.
HE CALLED, ALL RIGHT?
AT LEAST HE CALLED.
PROBABLY SITTING ON HIS CAN
IN THAT LIFEGUARD TOWER
READING A BOOK.
DIRTY BOOK.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
COME IN.
HE'S AT THE DOOR.
YOU DON'T YELL.
WHAT?
OH, HI.
HI. RABBI JACOBSEN.
MARGARET O'MALLEY.
HEY, RABBI.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT YOU.
NO, NO. WOULD YOU LIKE
SOMETHING TO EAT?
I CAN MAKE YOU A PLATE.
OH, THANKS, NO.
MY WIFE THINKS IF I EAT
ANOTHER WOMAN'S COOKING,
IT'S A FORM OF ADULTERY,
SO I SHOULDN'T.
BUT I BROUGHT SOMETHING
FOR AFTER THE MEAL.
OH. ALL RIGHTY.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME COFFEE?
THAT'D BE GREAT.
THAT'D BE GREAT, YEAH, THANKS.
SIT.
OKAY.
SO, HOW'S YOUR, UH,
HOW'S YOUR LITTLE BOY?
OH, HE'S GOOD. THANKS.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TOMORROW
FOR THE MONTHLY CHECKUP,
AND HOPEFULLY IT'LL BE
SIX MONTHS REMISSION.
OH, GOOD, GOOD.
WE HOPE SO, TOO.
OH, THANKS, THANKS.
HERE YOU GO.
OH, GREAT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, WELL, YOU PROBABLY REMEMBER
I MENTIONED TO YOU
THAT THE SYNAGOGUE WOULD LIKE
TO FORMALLY THANK YOU
FOR YOUR BRAVERY.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THERE'S NO NEED FOR THAT.
I TOLD YOU, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE JUST DOING OUR JOB.
AND I HAVE A STANDING ORDER
NOT TO DISAGREE WITH A MAN
UNDER HIS OWN ROOF,
BUT, UM, YOU RISKED YOUR LIFE
TO SAVE MY SON'S LIFE,
AND IF NOT FOR THE EXPLOSION,
YOU WOULD'VE MARCHED BACK
IN TO GET ESTHER --
AGAINST THE WISHES OF YOUR
PARTNERS, I SHOULD ADD.
OH, HONEY --
EXCUSE ME, RABBI.
THIS IS OUR OLDEST BOY
PATRICK.
THIS IS
RABBI JACOBSEN.
PATRICK.
PETE TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
YEAH,
I, UM, I HEARD ABOUT YOUR LOSS.
I'M VERY SORRY.
OH, THANKS, YEAH.
I WAS JUST TELLING
YOUR FATHER THAT --
IN FACT, YOU MAY WANT TO JOIN
US, IF THAT'S OKAY.
PETE TOLD ME ABOUT YOUR INTEREST
IN STUDYING MEDICINE IN COLLEGE,
AND OUR SYNAGOGUE GIVES
SCHOLARSHIPS EVERY YEAR
TO A FEW STUDENTS,
AND THIS YEAR,
IN HONOR OF ESTHER SIMON,
WE'RE GONNA GIVE A FULL
SCHOLARSHIP TO ONE STUDENT.
AND I RECOMMENDED TO THE BOARD,
AND THEY AGREED,
THAT PATRICK BE THE RECIPIENT
OF THE SCHOLARSHIP.
THANK YOU, RABBI.
HONEY?
RABBI, THAT IS AN EXTREMELY
KIND OFFER,
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY,
ONE THAT WE CANNOT ACCEPT.
OH, WELL, I --
ON BEHALF OF MY CONGREGATION
AND FAMILY,
I CERTAINLY HOPE YOU CAN
RECONSIDER ACCEPTING IT.
OTHER MEN RISKED THEIR LIVES
THAT DAY AT YOUR HOUSE.
IT WASN'T JUST ME.
UNDERSTOOD.
IT JUST SEEMED A BIT MORE
PERSONAL THAN OFFERING UP, SAY,
A STATUE TO THE ENTIRE
FIRE DEPARTMENT.
I SPOKE TO YOUR CHIEF.
HE APPROVED IT.
YOU SPOKE TO MY CHIEF?
WELL, YES.
I HAD TO MAKE SURE THAT IT
WAS WITHIN THE RULES.
[ SIGHS ] THE BOARD GIVES
ONE SCHOLARSHIP,
PETE MENTIONED PATRICK'S DESIRE,
AND I RECOMMENDED PATRICK.
I IMAGINE THEY WANT TO
GIVE IT TO HIM
IN A REAL PUBLIC CEREMONY.
I IMAGINE SO.
BE GOOD AS A PUBLIC SHOW,
YES.
FREE PUBLICITY FOR THE TEMPLE,
NO DOUBT.
Margaret: JOSEPH.
WHAT?
WELL, THAT'S TOTALLY
INAPPROPRIATE.
MR. O'MALLEY,
BOTH OF OUR RELIGIONS
ARE PRACTICED IN PUBLIC,
AND, YES, THERE ARE CEREMONIES
AND RITUALS.
THIS SCHOLARSHIP
ISN'T ABOUT FREE PUBLICITY.
IT'S ABOUT DOING GOOD, HONORING
GOOD, THANKING GOOD.
I DON'T MEAN TO DISRESPECT YOU
OR YOUR FAMILY
OR DISHONOR THE MEMORY
OF ESTHER SIMON.
OF COURSE NOT.
RABBI, THANK YOU
FOR STOPPING OVER.
MY SON PETE
HAS A BIG MOUTH,
AND MY FAMILY DOESN'T NEED
YOUR HANDOUTS.
WE THANK YOU
FOR YOUR KINDNESS.
JOE.
POP,
YOU CAN'T DO THAT TO ME.
YOU WILL SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
HEY...
WHERE THE HECK
DO YOU GET OFF
COMING INTO MY HOUSE
LIKE THAT, HUH?
I GOT MY SON ASKING ME,
"IS JESUS REALLY
THE SON OF GOD?"
HE'S 8!
WELL, THEN, IT SOUNDS LIKE
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
MY SON'S ASKING WHY HE CAN'T
MAKE THE SIGN OF THE CROSS
BEFORE HE PRAYS TO GOD.
MY CONGREGATION IS WONDERING
IF I'M TURNING INTO A RABBI
FOR JEWS FOR JESUS.
THE IRONY, OF COURSE, IS
THAT I DON'T THINK JESUS
WAS THE SON OF GOD!
YOU PREACH THAT TO YOUR
PEOPLE. YOU KEEP IT OUT
OF MY HOUSE, ALL RIGHT?
YOUR SON CAME TO ME, OKAY?
HE CAME TO ME TO ASK
IF HE COULD HELP JEWS --
HELP SAVE JEWS
FROM GOING TO HELL!
HE CAME TO ME!
YOU! GET BACK INSIDE!
IF SOMEONE COMES TO MY HOUSE
LIKE THAT,
I POLITELY THROW HIM OUT
ON HIS ASS!
GOOD, I'LL REMEMBER THAT.
"YOU DISAGREE WITH ME,
YOU'RE OUT ON YOUR ASS."
YOU KNOW, IT'S A GOOD THING
IT DIDN'T DETER YOUR ST. PAUL
WHEN THE ROMANS THREW HIM OUT
OR ST. PATRICK IN IRELAND
WITH THE SNAKES.
OH, DON'T START WITH THAT!
THROWING ST. PATRICK
BACK IN MY FACE!
THIS AIN'T
A BIBLE-STUDY GROUP, PAL!
[ SIGHS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
POP, ARE YOU TOO PROUD
TO LET ME ACCEPT IT?
FIRST OF ALL, YOU HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING TO DESERVE IT,
AND SECONDLY, I AM NOT
GETTING INVOLVED IN HIS
PUBLICITY STUNT, ALL RIGHT?
JOE, I DON'T THINK
IT'S A PUBLICITY STUNT.
I THINK IT'S AN ACT
OF KINDNESS IN RETURN
FOR AN ACT OF KINDNESS.
I TOLD YOU NOTHING
GOOD WOULD COME OF
HIM GOING OVER THERE.
PETE!
GET IN HERE RIGHT NOW!
HONEY, PLEASE DON'T START
YELLING AT HIM.
WHAT DID HE TELL
THE RABBI -- THAT WE DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH FOOD TO EAT?
WELL, THEN MAYBE THE RABBI CAN
START A FOOD DRIVE FOR THIS
FAMILY, HOW 'BOUT THAT?
WHAT'D I TELL YOU ABOUT
NOT GOING TO THAT TEMPLE? HUH?
I'M ON A QUEST
TO GET DANNY INTO HEAVEN.
AND I'M ALMOST THERE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE ON THE ROAD
TO HELL, MY FRIEND.
NOW GO TO YOUR ROOM
JOE...
AND DON'T COME OUT
UNTIL I TELL YOU TO.
WHAT?
DON'T TELL HIM
THINGS LIKE THAT.
I JUST WANTED
TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
THE RIGHT THING. YOU KNOW
WHAT THE RIGHT THING IS?
IS WHEN YOUR MOTHER
TELLS YOU SOMETHING
OR WHEN I TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU DON'T WORRY
ABOUT JEWS, YOU DON'T
WORRY ABOUT CATHOLICS.
YOU WORRY ABOUT ME.
NOW GO TO YOUR ROOM
AND GO THERE UNTIL
I TELL YOU TO COME OUT!
POP, I'M GONNA GO
SEE THAT RABBI MYSELF,
AND I'M GONNA
WORK OUT A DEAL, OKAY?
OVER MY DEAD BODY.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NOT ABOUT KINDNESS.
IT'S ABOUT THE JEWS
GETTING PUBLICITY
FOR HELPING OUT SOME POOR
IRISH CATHOLIC FAMILY
SO THEY CAN GET ON THE NEWS
AND EVERYBODY CAN SAY
HOW NICE IT IS OF THEM
THAT THEY SHARE THEIR MONEY
WITH THESE POOR SLOBS.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE
SO CYNICAL ABOUT THIS, HUH?
Y-Y-YOU HAVE TOO MUCH PRIDE
TO LET THIS MAN HELP ME OUT,
HELP YOUR SON OUT?
MAYBE IF YOU HAD
A LITTLE MORE PRIDE --
POP, I HAVE HEARD YOUR SPEECH
BEFORE, OKAY?
I KNOW WHAT IT IS --
YOU WORKED HARD, YOUR
FATHER WORKED HARD,
AND THEREFORE,
I HAVE TO WORK HARD.
OKAY.
I WANT TO WORK HARD, POP!
I WANT TO WORK HARD AT SCHOOL
TO GET A GOOD JOB.
ALL RIGHT!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT?
I DIDN'T SPEND MY DAY
AT THE BEACH, ALL RIGHT?
I'M TIRED.
I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT THIS ANYMORE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA --
WHAT DID I SAY?!
MOM?
MOM, PLEASE SAY SOMETHING
TO HIM.
MOM!
HUH?
Woman on P.A.: DR. FISCHBEIN,
PLEASE DIAL THE OPERATOR.
WHY DON'T WE GO
DISCUSS THIS IN PRIVATE?
Mrs. Jacobsen:
JUST TELL US.
HIS WHITE-BLOOD COUNT
IS HIGH.
AND MOST OF THE CELLS
THAT I CAN SEE IN HIS BLOOD
ARE LEUKEMIA CELLS.
I'M SO SORRY.
WHAT'S THE PROGNOSIS?
DANNY'S BEEN ON ARA-C
BEFORE,
BUT THIS TIME, WE'RE GIVING
HIM A MUCH HIGHER DOSAGE.
IT'S GOING TO ALLOW US
TO HAVE A FIGHTING CHANCE
TO GET HIM
BACK INTO REMISSION.
BUT...I WOULDN'T BE
COMPLETELY HONEST
IF I DIDN'T TELL YOU
THAT HIS CHANCES FOR SURVIVAL
ARE VERY LOW.
[ Deep voice ] ANOTHER STRIKEOUT
FOR SEAMUS'S TEAM.
PETE'S TEAM, TRYING TO BE
THE FIRST TEAM EVER
IN THE HISTORY OF BASEBALL
TO GO UNDEFEATED,
COMES TO BAT
WITH A 13-RUN LEAD.
[ Higher voice ] JACK,
THEY'RE NOT ONLY UNDEFEATED,
BUT THEY'VE 10-RUN-RULED
EVERY SINGLE TEAM
THEY'VE PLAYED.
[ Deep voice ]
GOOD POINT, CHARLIE.
[ SPINNER WHIRRING ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WE HAVE TO COMPLETE
THE DECATHLON.
WE CAN'T.
WE HAVE TO.
I KNOW I CAN DO IT.
LISTEN, I'M GROUNDED FOREVER
BECAUSE OF YOU.
IF MY DAD SAW ME WITH YOU,
I'D BE GROUNDED TO INFINITY.
NO, I'D BE GROUNDED
TO INFINITY
IF MY PARENTS KNEW
I WAS HERE.
THEY THINK I'M NAPPING.
LISTEN,
I...CAN'T...DO IT!
NO, YOU LISTEN.
THIS MIGHT BE MY LAST CHANCE
FOR A WHILE.
THEY MIGHT PUT ME ON CHEMO
RIGHT AWAY.
THE TESTS ARE BAD.
[ SIGHS ] I'M NOT GONNA
DISOBEY MY DAD AGAIN.
I GOTTA BE ABLE TO
TELL MY PARENTS THAT
I'M GOING TO HEAVEN.
YOU CAN'T GO TO HEAVEN.
IT'S OUT-OF-BOUNDS
AND OFF-LIMITS TO JEWS.
THERE'S NOTHING THAT
YOU OR I COULD DO ABOUT IT.
YOU SAID IF I FINISHED
THE DECATHLON,
I'M GOING TO HEAVEN!
WELL, I WAS WRONG.
YOU GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE.
I'M GONNA GET IN SO MUCH
TROUBLE BECAUSE OF YOU,
AND THEN I'M GOING TO HELL
FOR SURE.
Get outta here.
THAT WAS A BRIEF RAIN DELAY.
PETE'S TEAM COMES TO BAT.
[ DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE ]
HONEY...
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY,
AND FORGET IT.
MY DECISION ABOUT THIS
IS FINAL.
YOU KNOW, JOSEPH, WHEN
FATHER MURPHY MARRIED US --
OH, DON'T START
WITH THAT CRAP.
HE SAID --
FATHER MURPHY
WAS AN IDIOT.
CAN YOU STOP TALKING
FOR ONE SECOND, JOE?
I'VE JUST GOT SOMETHING
TO SAY, AND I DON'T WANT
YOU TO INTERRUPT ME, OKAY?
I'M NOT GONNA ALLOW YOU
TO TAKE AWAY PATRICK'S CHANCE.
HE'S GONNA PURSUE
THIS DREAM, JOE.
THE RABBI'S BEING GENEROUS,
AND I THINK THAT...
I THINK YOU THINK
IT REFLECTS POORLY ON YOU.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
HONEY, YES, IT IS.
IT --
YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO SEND
YOUR CHILDREN TO COLLEGE,
SO YOU'VE DECIDED
IT'S A BAD THING.
I'M NOT GONNA STAND BY
AND LET YOU SQUASH
PATRICK'S DREAMS.
IT'S JUST
NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
IT'S NOT ABOUT DREAMS.
WHAT'S IT ABOUT, JOE?
TELL ME WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
IT'S ABOUT WHAT'S RIGHT.
PATRICK KNEW THAT
IF HE WAS GONNA GO TO COLLEGE,
HE WAS GONNA EARN IT
BY GETTING GOOD GRADES
AND EARNING A SCHOLARSHIP.
OH, YOU WANTED HIM
TO TAKE SCHOOL SERIOUSLY?
YEAH.
IS THAT WHAT HE LEARNED
FROM YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
"OH, HE'S JUST GONNA
GO GET A CITY JOB.
"WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES COLLEGE MAKE?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF HE GETS A's OR C's."
BUT THAT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH
FOR HIM.
HE WOKE UP ONE DAY
AND SAID, "I HAVE TO BE
BETTER THAN THAT."
AND YOU KNOW, HE'S
GOTTEN STRAIGHT A's
EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
'CAUSE HE'S A CHIP
OFF THE OLD BLOCK,
AND HE WANTS TO DO HIS BEST
AT WHATEVER HE DOES.
AND THAT'S WHAT HE'S
GONNA DO -- IN COLLEGE,
WITH THE SCHOLARSHIP HE ACCEPTS
FROM RABBI JACOBSEN.
THAT'S RIGHT, JOE.
OR SO HELP ME GOD, WHEN
YOU COME AT HOME AT NIGHT,
THE ONLY THING COLDER THAN
YOUR FOOD WILL BE YOUR BED.
[ DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE ]
IS PATRICK GETTING
A NEW JOB?
[ LAUGHS ]
LISTEN TO YOU --
ALWAYS WORRIED ABOUT
EVERYONE ELSE'S BUSINESS.
YOU GET THAT FROM MY SIDE
OF THE FAMILY, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, DAD SAID I GOT
A LOT OF THINGS FROM
YOUR SIDE OF THE FAMILY.
OH, HE DID, DID HE?
YOU KNOW WHAT HE MEANS?
YOUR SWEETNESS, YOUR HUMOR,
AND DEFINITELY YOUR NOSE.
MOM, DO YOU THINK DAD
WILL END MY GROUNDING SOON?
WELL, THAT DEPENDS.
ARE YOU TRULY SORRY
FOR DISOBEYING HIM,
LYING TO ME?
MOM, I WAS ON A QUEST,
AND ON QUESTS, YOU
HAVE TO TAKE RISKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HONEY --
YOU KNOW THAT FEELING
YOU GET IN YOUR HEART,
THAT LITTLE VOICE
THAT TALKS TO YOU?
YOU KNOW WHY THAT'S THERE?
IT'S BECAUSE
I CAN'T ALWAYS BE WITH YOU
TO TELL YOU WHAT'S RIGHT
AND WHAT'S WRONG.
THAT'S YOUR CONSCIENCE.
WHAT DOES YOUR CONSCIENCE SAY
TO YOU ABOUT YOUR QUEST?
I THINK IT SAYS TO DO
WHAT YOU AND DAD TELL ME TO DO.
WELL, THAT AND...
YOU KNOW WHAT? I BELIEVE
YOUR QUEST IS GOOD.
BUT DAD SAID --
DADS DON'T ALWAYS KNOW...
EVERYTHING ALL THE TIME.
JUST SOMETIMES.
THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
HE CAN'T GROUND YOU.
MNH-MNH.
WELL...DON'T GIVE UP
YOUR QUEST, HONEY.
[ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
COME ON IN.
PATRICK.
HI.
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M ALL RIGHT.
GOOD, GOOD.
WHERE'S YOUR DAD?
UH, HE, UH, HE HAD TO GO
RUN SOME ERRANDS.
HE'LL PICK ME UP HERE
IN A FEW MINUTES.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
UH...LISTEN,
SINCE WE SPOKE ON THE PHONE,
I'VE RECEIVED A CALL
FROM THE HOSPITAL,
AND I'M NEEDED THERE.
MY WIFE...
[ SIGHS ] CALLED.
DANNY'S, UH, GOT AN INFECTION
FROM THE CHEMOTHERAPY,
SO I-I DON'T -- I DON'T HAVE
AS MUCH TIME TO...
TALK ABOUT THIS AS I, UH,
AS WE HAD PLANNED.
I, UM...
I HOPE EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
YEAH, WELL, ME TOO.
I, UH...I DON'T KNOW.
UH, HE'S HAD INFECTIONS
BEFORE, YOU KNOW?
I'M SORRY.
THANKS.
UH, UH,
REGARDING THE SCHOLARSHIP,
UH, I HOPE YOU REALIZE THAT
THIS IS...GONNA OPEN DOORS
THAT WOULD NEVER POSSIBLY
BE AVAILABLE TO YOU
WITHOUT A DEGREE.
YEAH, I KNOW IT WILL.
AND, UH...IF THE OFFER
IS STILL THERE,
I WOULD -- I WOULD
ABSOLUTELY LOVE A CHANCE --
OH, NO, NO, PATRICK,
THE SCHOLARSHIP IS YOURS.
ABSOLUTELY. YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE US ALL PROUD.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
ESTHER SIMON PROUD.
WOW. OHH.
AS I SAID, I JUST WISH
I HAD MORE TIME.
WE'LL WORK OUT ALL THE DETAILS
AT ANOTHER TIME.
UH, I WILL --
I WILL PRAY FOR DANNY.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, RABBI.
CONGRATULATIONS, PATRICK.
[ CRYING ]
SAVE MY SON.
Announcer:
...CHET LEMON, FIRST SWING.
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON.
STRIKE!
OH, YOU SPINELESS
ROOKIE BUM!
...THIRD TIME TODAY LOOKING,
AND PAUL RICHARDS HAS TO THINK
ABOUT SITTING YOUNG LEMON...
HEY, POP?
[ MUTTERING ]
POP?
WHAT?
IF I'M GONNA GO TO COLLEGE,
I'M GONNA WORK MY ASS OFF.
I'M -- REALLY, I'M NOT GONNA
BE A POT-SMOKING,
SLEEP-TILL-NOON
COLLEGE HIPPIE.
...FUNDAMENTAL BASEBALL GAME,
FOLKS...
I'M GONNA DO THIS
COLLEGE THING, AND
I'M GONNA DO IT RIGHT.
...LAMAR JOHNSON
COMING TO THE PLATE...
I KNOW.
...SOX ARE DOWN
BY THREE RUNS...
I KNOW YOU ARE.
RICHARDS JUST CAN'T SEEM
TO FIND A SPOT
IN THE EVERYDAY LINEUP
FOR HIM.
THE WHITE SOX'S YOUNG NUCLEUS
OF CHET LEMON,
LAMAR JOHNSON, JORGE ORTA...
HEY...
BUT BECK SEEMS TO THINK WITH
THESE YOUNG PLAYERS MATURING...
DON'T BE ACTING LIKE THIS
IS YOUR FIRST TIME DRINKING.
COME ON.
I DON'T KNOW.
SURE WOULD BE NICE...
AND I DIDN'T GIVE THAT
TO YOU.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
Joe: HEY. PEDRO.
HEY, DAD.
SEAMUS SAYS THERE'S
A BIG GAME OVER THERE
AT, UH, HOLY CROSS,
AND, UH, THEY COULD PROBABLY
USE ANOTHER PLAYER.
SO CAN I GO?
NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE GROUNDED, REMEMBER?
I'M GONNA GO PLAY,
AND I'M JUST LETTING YOU KNOW
WHERE I'M AT.
OH, WAIT --
Y-YOU WANT TO PLAY?
DO YOU WANT TO PLAY?
CAN I?
[ LAUGHS ]
GO ON, GET OUTTA HERE.
SORRY, DAD.
I WON'T DISOBEY YOU AGAIN.
OH, LISTEN, PATRICK SAW
RABBI JACOBSEN LAST NIGHT.
I GUESS DANNY'S
BACK IN THE HOSPITAL.
YEAH, HE SAID THAT
HE THOUGHT THEY MIGHT
PUT HIM BACK THERE.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
MM-HMM.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOUGH,
WHAT HE'S GOT.
IT'S TOUGH ON THE KID,
AND, UH...
IT'S GOTTA BE TOUGH
ON THE PARENTS, TOO.
WELL, I'LL PRAY FOR HIM.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S A NICE IDEA.
YEAH. GOOD.
OH, AND, UH...
HE ALSO TOLD PATRICK
TO TELL YOU THAT, UH...
DANNY FINISHED
THE DECATHLON.
71 STROKES THERE,
86 BACK.
NO WAY!
YES WAY.
I DID IT IN 55 STROKES.
OH, YOU DID, HUH?
YEAH, BUT FOR HIS AGE AND SIZE,
71 STROKES IS GREAT.
I MEAN, HE FINISHED
THE DECATHLON.
I CAN GIVE HIM HIS MEDAL
SO HE CAN GO TO HEAVEN.
YEAH.
SEE YOU LATER, DAD.
ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU, PETE.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ RUSTLING ]
MR. O'MALLEY.
STEALING COMMUNION?
FATHER KELLY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AND DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE HUNGRY.
NO, FATHER.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
I HEAR THIS STUFF
ISN'T GOOD, ANYWAYS.
WELL, I WISH WE COULD CHANGE
BREAD DISTRIBUTORS,
BUT THAT'S NEITHER HERE
NOR THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
MR. O'MALLEY?
I'VE GOT A FRIEND WHO
REALLY NEEDS A PIECE OF JESUS.
HE'S REALLY SICK,
AND HE'S IN THE HOSPITAL.
AHH.
WE HAVE PEOPLE WHO GIVE
COMMUNION TO THE SICK
IN THE HOSPITAL.
BUT...THEY CAN'T GIVE IT
TO HIM.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE HE'S NOT CATHOLIC,
AND HE'S ONLY 7.
YOUR FRIEND --
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
DANNY.
WELL, THAT POSES A BIT
OF A PROBLEM, MR. O'MALLEY.
COMMUNION IS FOR CHRISTIANS
WHO HAVE EARNED THE RIGHT
TO RECEIVE JESUS
AND WHO ARE OF AGE.
OH, HE'S EARNED THE RIGHT.
HE'S PASSED ALL THE TESTS.
TESTS? WHAT TESTS?
THE TESTS WE MADE UP TO SEE
IF HE'S WORTHY OF JESUS.
AND HE IS WORTHY,
ALL RIGHT.
HE'S AS WORTHY
AS ANY CATHOLIC I KNOW.
WELL, I-I BELIEVE YOU,
MR. O'MALLEY.
BUT WE'RE CATHOLICS.
WE -- WE HAVE
THESE TRADITIONS.
WELL, JUST BECAUSE
HE'S NOT OLD ENOUGH,
THAT TRADITION'S NOT FAIR,
BECAUSE HE MAY NOT LIVE
LONG ENOUGH TO BE OLD ENOUGH.
AND IF JESUS DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO HAVE A PART OF HIM JUST
BECAUSE HE'S NOT OLD ENOUGH,
WELL, THAT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
THE JESUS I KNOW.
THAT BREAD, UH...
IS UNCONSECRATED.
IT'S -- IT'S NOT
THE BODY OF CHRIST.
IT'S JUST BREAD.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
JESUS WON'T MIND.
GO AHEAD. TAKE THE HOST
TO YOUR FRIEND.
GO ON.
THANKS, FATHER.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
Woman on P.A.:
DR. DANNON TO PEDIATRICS.
DR. DANNON TO PEDIATRICS,
STAT.
[ SIGHS ]
SEE YOU LATER.
ALL RIGHT.
RABBI?
PETE.
RABBI,
I NEED TO SEE DANNY.
I NEED TO SEE HIM.
I'VE GOT HIS COMMUNION
RIGHT HERE.
SEE? HE EARNED IT.
HE PASSED THE DECATHLON.
LISTEN TO ME, PETE...
DANNY'S PASSED ON, OKAY?
NO!
NO! HE DIDN'T GET
HIS MEDAL!
NO!
Mrs. Jacobsen: PETE...
I PROMISED HIM!
I PROMISED HIM.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
[ CRYING ]
HE TOLD ME.
THE PRIZE FOR FINISHING
THE DECATHLON
WAS A PIECE OF JESUS,
SO HE COULD GO TO HEAVEN.
DANNY TOLD ME TO THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING YOU DID
AND -- AND TO TELL YOU
HE'S GONNA SEE YOU IN HEAVEN.
BUT HE CAN'T GO
WITHOUT EATING THIS, RABBI.
[ Crying ] HE CAN'T GO!
OH...PETE.
[ NO AUDIO ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
HEY, PETE.
DAD?
LET'S SEE THAT ARM.
[ DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE ]
GOOD. GOOD THROW.
THANKS.
WHAT'S GOING ON, PETE?
NOTHING MUCH.
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
I THINK I HURT
THE RABBI'S FEELINGS.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT,
SMART GUY?
IT WAS THE OTHER DAY,
AT THE HOSPITAL.
I TOLD HIM
DANNY WASN'T IN HEAVEN.
[ BARKING CONTINUES ]
SO, YOUR BROTHER PATRICK'S
GOING TO COLLEGE, HUH?
YEAH. HE'S SO EXCITED.
I NEVER WENT TO COLLEGE.
WHY NOT?
'CAUSE
I COULDN'T AFFORD IT.
GOT MARRIED, STARTED A FAMILY,
GOT A GOOD JOB
'CAUSE I HAD TO...
TAKE CARE OF MY FAMILY.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD REASON.
IT IS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I LEARNED?
WHAT?
THAT YOU TAKE CARE
OF YOUR FAMILY...
NO MATTER
WHAT YOUR DIFFERENCES ARE.
A DAD'S JOB IS TO TAKE CARE
OF HIS FAMILY.
THAT'S WHAT I LEARNED.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT I'M GETTING AT --
AND I'M JUST
THINKING ALOUD HERE --
BUT IF GOD
IS ANY KIND OF A FATHER,
YOU THINK HE WOULD TURN
HIS BACK ON HIS OWN FAMILY
AND NOT LET THEM
BACK INTO HIS HOUSE?
NO.
OF COURSE HE WOULDN'T.
JUST LIKE I WOULDN'T
TURN MY BACK ON YOU
OR YOUR BROTHERS
OR SISTERS.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
MAYBE DANNY IS IN HEAVEN,
EVEN THOUGH HE'S JEWISH,
ALL RIGHT?
I MEAN, AN ESKIMO
AT THE NORTH POLE
NEVER HEARD OF JESUS,
BUT IF HE'S BEEN
A GOOD PERSON ALL HIS LIFE,
SHOULDN'T HE BE ALLOWED
INTO HEAVEN?
WELL, YEAH...BUT...
BUT WHAT?
BUT THEN
THERE'S NO REASON
FOR ME TO LISTEN
TO THE NUNS AT SCHOOL ANYMORE.
[ LAUGHS ]
LISTEN, MY FRIEND,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET OUTTA
CATHOLIC SCHOOL THAT EASILY.
YOU STILL GOTTA LISTEN
TO THEM.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
RABBI JACOBSEN?
DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT
TO TALK?
SURE.
YOU KNOW HOW I HAD MY
QUEST TO HELP A JEWISH
PERSON GET TO HEAVEN?
OH, YES.
WELL, I LEARNED SOMETHING
ON MY QUEST THAT MIGHT
HELP YOU ON YOUR QUEST.
REALLY?
WHAT WOULD THAT BE?
THAT JUST SAYING
YOU BELIEVE
OR JUST PRAYING
TO JESUS --
WELL, THAT'S NOT
HOW YOU GET TO HEAVEN.
NO?
NOPE.
JESUS IS ONLY A SYMBOL.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHOSE NAME YOU USE.
YOU COULD USE
ANYONE'S NAME,
JUST AS LONG AS THEIR NAME
SYMBOLIZES BEING GOOD.
THAT IS INTERESTING.
I WAS THINKING --
IF THE JEWISH PEOPLE DON'T
WANT TO COPY THE CHRISTIANS
BY PRAYING TO JESUS
JUST BECAUSE THEY DON'T
LIKE THE NAME JESUS,
WELL, THEN,
THEY DON'T HAVE TO.
I MEAN, THEY CAN MAKE UP
THEIR OWN NAME TO PRAY TO.
IT'S NOT THAT WE DON'T LIKE
THE NAME JESUS.
UM...
WHAT NAME WOULD YOU SUGGEST
WE PRAY TO?
DANNY.
[ SIGHS ]
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT
HELP YOU IN YOUR JOB --
ON YOUR QUEST.
YEAH, I THINK
IT PROBABLY WILL.
THANKS.
SEE YOU LATER,
RABBI JACOBSEN.
TAKE CARE, PETE O'MALLEY.
OH, YEAH -- UH, I ALMOST
FORGOT TO TELL YOU THE
MOST IMPORTANT THING.
WHAT'S THAT?
THAT DANNY IS IN HEAVEN.
YEAH?
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
FAITH.
ALL RIGHT.
[ HORN HONKING IN DISTANCE ]
[ CAR DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ SLOW PIANO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MID-TEMPO
ACOUSTIC-GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ I HAVE A PICTURE
OF A CHILD ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH A FIELD
FREE AND WILD ♪
♪ CALL IT TIMING,
CALL IT FATE ♪
♪ THE SKY'S THE LIMIT,
TOO MUCH, TOO LATE ♪
♪ AND NO ONE
SHOULD HAVE TO GO WITHOUT ♪
♪ THE FRIEND I HAVE IN YOU,
I HAVE NO DOUBT ♪
♪ ONLY YOU COULD HELP ME
UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ WHY WE WON'T BE RUNNING
HAND IN HAND ♪
♪ NOTHING'S SIMPLE,
NOTHING'S FAIR ♪
♪ FAITH CAN BE LONELY,
MAKES IT HARD TO BEAR ♪
♪ AND NO ONE
SHOULD HAVE TO GO WITHOUT ♪
♪ THE FRIEND I HAVE IN YOU,
I HAVE NO DOUBT ♪
♪ AND NO ONE
SHOULD HAVE TO GO WITHOUT ♪
♪ THE FRIEND I HAVE IN YOU,
I HAVE NO DOUBT ♪
♪ AND NO ONE
SHOULD HAVE TO GO WITHOUT ♪
♪ THE FRIEND I HAVE IN YOU,
I HAVE NO DOUBT ♪
♪ AND NO ONE
SHOULD HAVE TO GO WITHOUT ♪
♪ THE FRIEND I HAVE IN YOU,
I HAVE NO DOUBT ♪
♪ I HAVE A PICTURE
OF A CHILD ♪