VARNA
VARNA BULGARIA
Ladies!
Baccarat.
Exquisite.
Tihomir.
Hang up.
Bradley Fine.
- I'm honored.
- Pleasure is all mine.
Tell me where the bomb is?
10 seconds or
you’re dead.
Interesting.
You see.
When my men
and I hid it.
I made sure to
erase any witnesses.
And then I erased
the erasers.
Which means.
I'm the only one who knows...
just where that
dangerously compact
and transportable nuke is.
So.
I'll say I have
more than 10 seconds.
Well then.
In that case.
I say you better start...
Ah-choo.
Oh.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
What...
Why did you do that?
I didn't do it on purpose.
There's like a ton of pollen in here.
Oh God. Christmas on a cracker.
Did you take your medicine.
- I forgot it on the plane.
- I told you this morning
I put extra in
all your jackets.
You did.
Great.
Shit.
- Thanks.
- No. You know what.
That's on me because I heard
you sniffled a while ago
and I did nothing with
that information. So.
It's-That's blood on my hands.
Really, okay.
You know what?
You got 3 coming in.
Get out the back door now.
Move.
Anybody in here?
Yeah, we got 1 coming
around the corner now.
Your 3 guests are coming out
of the door behind you right now.
Watch your 6.
- Yahtzee.
- Oh, zinger. Heh-heh
Should have brought
more bullets.
I thought they were chocolate sprinkles
which I would eat normally by the fistful.
But this tasted like, there's
no other way to say it really.
Like
a rat sauce.
Hey guys.
Can you please keep it down.
Look. Unfortunately there's
vermin in the ceiling again.
And I hate to say it but they-
well they pooped all over your cake.
- Am I going left?
- No.
Okay. I need you to go right.
and head down the tunnel.
You got 1 coming
around to your right,
and he's got a
swarm behind him.
- That's my girl.
- Oh, I don't know.
Watch your back.
Oh.
It's a close one, Fine.
- Whose the finest of them all?
- You are.
Oh, Bradley, you're so fine.
You're so fine, you blow my mind.
Hey, Bradley.
(Clap, clap)
Oh god!
Duck!
Nice moves, Fine.
Bodies has been
working out for you.
- You noticed?
- You just seemed looser (Are you kidding.)
in your hips.
I mean athletically...
speaking.
I don't know.
I guess you don't seem so awkward.
(Oh, shut up.)
- Going straight?
- No. Go right up the stairs.
You're going to find a little friend
on the first landing.
- Thanks for your help.
- Okay, you are clear to the top.
Get moving.
Oh my god.
The rats can fly!
Come on, you guys.
Alright, Fine.
Stop at the door.
Okay, you have a guard approaching.
I'll tell you when.
Wait for it, Fine.
3.
2.  1.
NOW!
Oh dear.
Did I forget to knock?
They're culling at my hair.
I can't see!
What do you mean
you can't see?
I'm good.
You got SUV approaching.
- Go to the dock!
- Dock.
Excellent idea.
Fine, there are boats
at the end.
Uh--
No keys, Coop
Panel is on the lower left,
under the steering wheel.
You can.
You can hot wire it.
I can't get to the wires.
Then stay down and
hold your ears.
And how will I
hear your beautiful voice.
Stop being adorable
and get down.
Lock on coordinates:
43.16547,  27.94654
Fire.
Now!
Ha ha.
Bonsoir!
Nice drone work, Coop.
- I can kiss you.
- Oh well.
Well I would
I would accept that
with an open mouth.
Ha ha. Soon as I'm back,
dinner's on me.
Great work, Coop.
Oh, hey.
Pick up my dry cleaning for me
would you.
Also get my car.
Oh sure.
No problem.
Oh, and I have to
fire my gardener.
He keeps running over the
sprinkler heads with the mower.
Could you cut him
loose for me.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Sure, you kidding.
I love it.
You're the best.
- Smell you later, pal.
- God.
Poor Jaime.
The thing is.
Jaime, that uh...
Oh.
These your-These your children.
- Children here.
- Yeah, I have children.
Just have to cover
the eyes.
They're looking right at me.
Please.
Don't fire me.
No.
I mean I would never...
This is... more of a
review.
Oh.
Jaime.
The... lawn... mower...
Oh.
Right to the lawn mower.
You're a killer, Susan.
Oh.
These look delicious!
I don't want to be critical,
but this is very chewy.
Coop.
You're eating a hand towel.
Just,
cleansing my palate.
Jes. You had to take me
to such a dump?
Come on, cheapskate.
- Burger King was booked up.
- Ha!
- Sorry.
- Hey, I've been thinking.
Yeah.
I couldn't do what I do
without you.
And I've been thinking about
doing something special for you.
So.
Good gravy, Fine.
Oh.
That's...
It's a crazy cupcake.
- You love cakes.
- Wow. That is wonderful.
Imagine, how
awkward it would've been.
If it had been a
diamond ring or something.
Not a diamond ring.
No.
Oh, I wouldn't had see it like that.
I wouldn't want to marry you.
I don't want your
musclely arms and hands,
rubbing my back with Nivea
for the rest of my life.
There are 3 kids running.
You know.
Karen, Tommy and Billy
and you said get out of here.
No, thank you.
I'll just... You know.
I'll just...
Giving me a little jewellery
I can actually wear.
Not going to wear it?
Yes.
- I was just saving it. I mean.
- Put it on.
- Look at that, wow. That's a...
- That's an adjustable toggle.
Adjustable toggle.
You don't.
You don't see that.
It's a lot of jewellery there.
- It's so you.
- Is it? Wow, perfect.
Seriously.
I-I couldn't do what I do
without you
in my earpiece.
I can never do what you do.
Can you imagine
me as a spy?
My god.
- Out in the field.
- Yeah.
- With a gun.
- What?
Elaine would
never let me be a spy.
I can't even
can't even dress like a spy.
I mean, you know. Look at you
and your tailor and your...
Everything is cut right,
and my, it's like a
lumpy, pumpkin
sag dress.
I...
It doesn't even have a label.
I think my mom made it.
No. Stop.
Enough.
No.
Good god.
- Go easy on yourself.
- Okay.
We're a perfect team.
That's why we work.
Yeah.
Come here.
Look close.
I think you're
getting a pinkeye.
- What?  No. No. No.
- Right there.
Did you like wiped your eye
after you cleaned out the cat box.
I don't have cats.
- Why did I think that?
- I don't-I don't know.
You should get some.
There's good company.
LANGLEY
- LANGLEY, VIRGINIA-
We intercepted a chatter that the
weapon is still being offered
to the highest bidder.
Someone other than Boyanov
knows where that nuke is.
It's probably
his daughter, Rayna.
She's really the only
person he trusted.
Jesus, Cooper.
Do you have pink eye?
Go home.
You're going to infect everybody.
- Told ya.
- No.
It's not pink eye, ma'am.
It's just... I'm having a bit
of a allergic reaction.
Well, I'm allergic to disgusting
childhood illness. So stay away from me.
Sorry.
Anyway, you are right.
After Boyanov's death,
Rayna went to a safety deposit
box of a DSK bank in Varna.
- The chatter picked up later that night.
- What do we know about her?
I can pull up her file.
Oh, that's stuck.
So warm in here.
I'll pull up my file.
Jesus, not on my keyboard,
with your pink eye infected fingers.
Why don't you just cry directly
into my mouth while you're at it.
It really is just
a allergic reaction.
Sit down.
I'll do it.
Okay.
I'm going to sit down.
Rayna Boyanov.
Major at international law at Oxford,
top of her class.
Been living in London
for the past 10 years.
Now, we know she has
been communicating
with the heads of several
terrorist organizations.
Most ominously,
Solsa Dudaev,
The Al Qaeda funded leader
of the Chechen Martyrs Brigade
We have compelling evidence that
he has the machinery in place
to get that nuke to New York.
In time for next week's
UN general assembly
I'm already packed.
One of sources was told she's taken
residence outside of Sofia.
Go get her.
Grab my things, Coop.
Jesus, Cooper. Go put on
some sunglasses or something.
Feel like you're a gypsy,
cursing me with it.
Yup.
I'm on it.
God.
My life is a disaster.
- No, it's not.
- I'm 40, I live by myself.
I've not been in a
real relationship since
- Jerry left me 3 years ago.
- Jerry was a jackass.
I mean, when I gave up
teaching to join the CIA
I thought everything is
going to be different.
I thought I was going
to be this amazing spy.
I'm just the same boring person
like I was before.
Well, for what it's worth.
I think you're brilliant as you are.
You're exciting.
You know what?
You played it too safe.
I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
I just.
I still- you know.
Hear my mom's voice.
Well behave woman,
often make history.
Yes, you do know the phrase.
"Well behaved women seldom...
make history."
Yeah that's, never heard she said it.
What about this.
Oh, just blend in.
Let somebody else win.
- Classic. Yup.
- I got that a lot in my schools.
And there was a
"Give up on your dreams, Susan."
She used to write that
in my lunch box.
Oh.
I mean, look.
Okay.
What's really so different
between us and Karen Walker.
I think-I think literally.
Everything.
No, hang on.
No.
Because you were just as
good as out in the Carvela.
She-She has more successful
missions than even Fine.
Oh.
She's the worse.
Look at her.
She's so perfect, isn't she?
Oh, hi. I'm Karen Walker,
Super spy. Heh-heh-heh.
Perfect hair.
Perfect face.
She probably cries herself
to sleep every night.
- I don't think she probably does.
- She probably does.
And not like
sort of cute little tears.
Like brilly.
Sort of you know.
Silent kind of thing.
I don' think that.
Like sort of upside
down kidney bean.
- This is what I look when I'm asleep.
- Shh shh, shut up. Be quiet.
She wouldn't know who we are
She's not in front of us now.
Hi. Hey Nancy.
Hi Susan.
- Hi.
Hey, you 2 cuties sitting here
being all cute.
- Uh.
- Ha-ha.
Can I have an
Old Fashioned, please.
- His service is really slow.
- Super slow.
You're not getting that
in the next hour.
- Here you go, Miss Walker.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
- Wow.
Alan and I go way back.
I come here all the time.
So do we.
Right Alan?
Hey, Alan.
How... Alan.
Big A.
Yoo-hoo, Al!
You got a hole.
Miss Walker.
These 2 bothering you?
- Oh no. Thank you, they're fine.
- Okay.
- Alan.
- He's the sweetest.
- He just pretends not to know.
- He's funny.
Yeah, well.
Anyway, I'm taking some time off.
So I'll see you guys
when I get back.
- Oh.
- Where're you going?
- Capri.
- Capri. - Capri.
I wished I could just
stick around here, you know.
Curl up with a good book.
- But, I have a yacht full of
friends waiting for me. - Wow.
Anywho.
I'll see you guys when I get back.
All freckle and tanned
- We're gonna see you.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
Oh, sorry.
Susan's ill.
It's her stomach
My god.
Thank you for that.
- Why would you do that?
- I'm sorry, I panicked.
What a great moment.
- Just looked a her.
- Oh, I know. That dress.
Look at her confidence.
They are even allowed
to smoke in here.
I'm gonna go home.
- No, come on.
- Yes.
Susan.
- Sorry.
- Feel better.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
- Fine. You good?
- Okay, Coop. Just pulling up.
Susan, you're killing it.
Oh good.
You know what, they are chicory.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Any sign of her in the house?
Heat sensors aren't
picking anything up.
There's some kind of interference.
I don't like this, Fine.
I'm up for the challenge.
Let's go in.
Shoot. There is something
wrong with your camera.
Can you switch out
for a new one.
Too late.
Oh.
No security.
Her father would never have
let himself this exposed.
Okay. Pull back, Fine.
This is too easy.
I like things that are easy
Oh my god, Fine.
I don't know how you
do things like that.
Hey.
Who's the finest of them all?
I don't know.
I'm guessing,
you?
Drop your weapon.
Fine, what's happening?
Let me guess, whoever is in your ear
wants to know what's happening?
He's about to die.
That's what.
Awfully big gun
for such a little girl.
God.
Don't say stuff like that.
Okay. There's a knife rack
directly to your right.
The way she's holding the gun,
she's not experienced.
If you jump and launch.
You get the knife and disarm her.
Did someone just suggested
you grabbed one of those knives.
No-no-no...!
Damn it!
Fine?
Can they see me right now?
Let me adjust
the angle a little bit.
Oh my god.
His name was Bradley Fine.
He worked for the CIA.
Other top agents include,
Matthew Wright, Timothy Cress,
Rick Ford and Karen Walker
Come on, Fine.
Come on.
I know who all
your active agents are.
So. Unless you like the
body count to grow.
I suggest you stay
far away from me.
Now grab some tissues,
because it's about
to get real sad.
No, don't.
No!
Oh my god.
Fine.
As Deputy Director.
I've never had
a more difficulty duty,
than to bid farewell
to colleagues taken from us.
From Dover,
to the family services.
To memorials like these.
It's tough to say goodbye.
There's nothing you could
have done, Susan.
Bradley Fine.
Was more than just
a co-worker and a friend.
He's a part of our family.
As family, even knowing that
the universe has a plan
for each human life.
It's hard to accept the
sudden lost of such a
good and decent person.
Okay. There's a knife rack
directly to your right.
Susan. I got your assessment
report on Rayna Boyanov.
I know you're probably feeling
a lot of emotion right now,
but please refrain from
using the term "thundercunt".
Oh my god.  I-I didn't realise
I wrote that, I'm sorry.
Nancy,
I'm sending you a photo.
It's in pretty bad shape.
Can you enhance it.
Paris.
How the fuck did this thwart,
find out our fucking names?
We don’t know.
And I've looked way back
where the 'T' word for.
You're not immune
from the HR department.
Grow up. The thwart means something
completely different in England.
Well, here it means vagina.
Anyway.
Obviously we're talking about a mole.
It could be a mole that
could've hacked our system.
It's anyone's guess.
The bottom line is.
Rayna Boyanov is about to sell
a small scale tactical nuclear weapon
to a terrorist organization.
And we don't know where
she or the bomb is.
And fortunately, our analyst,
Susan Cooper found the lead.
Rayna had the number
of Sergio De Luca.
We've long suspected
that De Luca of working
as an intermediate
with terrorist groups.
Rayna maybe using him
to find buyers for the nuke.
The number was to a office
he keeps in Paris.
I told you to send me
in there instead of Fine.
And you didn't.
And now Fine is dead.
I'm kind of fuck in.
You can't.
We need someone to follow De Luca
without being detected.
And I would hopefully
takes us to Rayna.
But it can't be
any of you.
Here's what we do.
I go into the
face-off machine.
Get a whole new face.
I turned up.
They'll never know it's me.
Do you have quarters?
'Cause it cost 50 cents.
What, I've got to pay?
No, because it doesn't exist.
Yes, it does!
I heard Chress and Wright
talked about it in the shitter.
I'm pretty sure that
they're pulling your leg.
You pair of fucking vaginas.
Seriously.
You got to cut that out.
Jesus. Look, one of us
has to go in.
Doesn't matter if
we've been exposed.
We've all gone deep before,
and we always gotten our guy.
Guys.
This is more than just a kill mission.
Now we get Rayna, De Luca
and some top terrorist leadership
and get the weapon back,
if we do this right.
We just need someone who could
shadow them without attracting attention.
- We need someone invisible.
- I'll do it.
Okay, thanks lunch lady.
I'm serious.
I...
I've never been
out in the field.
Exactly.
Stupid fucking idea.
My point is that
it's highly doubtful
I've ever been exposed
But you worked with Fine.
They may have a
record of you too.
Possibly.
But.
You know. The odds of them
knowing my face are very low.
Ms. Crocker,
I would really like to do this.
For Fine.
You're not seriously
considering this, are you?
If you think,
I'm going to sit by
and let you send in a fucking
secretary to do my work.
You might as well accept
my resignation now.
If I can jump in.
I'm
I'm technically,
classified as an agent.
Look.
Full.
Full agent, so.
Agent, agent, agent.
I'm agent.
Are you considering this?
For your safety and the safety
of those around this table.
I'm considering it.
Then consider this.
I quit.
And I know there is a
fucking face-off machine.
You're just keeping it
a secret from me.
That hasn't happened before.
It is quite a lovely office.
What's your deal, Cooper?
- What do you mean?
- You got a faery side?
I really did in that report
mean to write cunning.
I've been going over your files.
You're top of the class
at the academy
in all computer and support skills.
No surprise there.
But you have a certain tame
demeanor around the office that
says you've never even held a gun.
So imagine
my surprise when I saw footage
from this drill back at the farm.
Is that... kidding.
Is that me?
That can't really...
Stupid gun.
Eah!
- Somebody definitely sped this up.
- Son of a bitch.
Camera angle,
does not make...
- Cooper. Cooper. Stop it,
- Okay, uh.
Ouch.
Those contacts, that's a,
you know.
I must have watched
this 15 times now.
Because,
what the fuck.
- Well, I...
- I almost put it up on YouTube.
Well, I was, to say the least,
uncomfortable.
with the event.
But I would also like to say
it was over 10 years ago.
The instructor was not harmed.
- Fine, was your mentor. Right?
- Yes.
Why did you not
become a field agent?
Well, we're such a great fit
and a great team.
I mean Fine,
made some great points
You know, maybe I match
better with... just staying.
- In the Bureau.
- Well.
Yeah.
He sniped you.
All the top agents used to
do that before I got here.
I really thought he
made some great points.
Women.
Alright, have you any
field training since then.
- 10 years is a long time.
- No, ma'am.
Normally I would send
you back to the farm,
but there's no time and
I can't take a chance
of anyone leaking your name.
Am I-Am I going?
- You're going.
- Okay. (Jes...)
- But it's a track and report mission only.
- Got it.
We'll be giving you a new identity.
You will not longer be Susan Cooper.
- Oh, I have a few ideas for that.
- Your new name.
I was just spit-balling and I thought
Serafina, Mannix, Gisele.
Carol Jenkins.
Carol
Jenkins.
You know.
If I may, ma'am.
There was a 13 year old
girl name Carol,
that used to come take me
around the neighbourhood
and used my braid as a dog leash.
And made me begged for biscuits.
So.
- Carol Jenkins.
- Yes, Carol Jenkins.
Carol Jenkins is a
single mother of 4.
Temporarily relocated from Delaware
to increase sales for a software company.
Okay.
That is-That is.
a different occup....
Huh!
- Is there a problem?
- No!
Just wondering if
this is my family of 4,
taken hostages.
I'm just not sure
how De Luca is going to take me
seriously if I looked like this.
De Luca is not going
to take you anything.
In case you did not
hear me.
You're not to make direct
contact with any of the targets.
Track and report.
Now we're setting you
up in a surveillance office
across the street from De Luca's.
You'll be tapped into
the same telecom trunk
and have access to voice and
data coming into his office.
And that's as sexy
as it gets.
One mistake, and we got a
nuclear bomb in the hands of terrorists.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Go see Patrick.
He's got special equipment for you.
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
Oh, did you come up
with your spy name yet?
My would be
Amber Valentine.
That sounds like you're
an adult film star.
No,
I did this 'Find name formula'.
Amber was the name of my first pet
and I grew up on Valentine Street.
Did you come up
with your porn name?
- Oh, no. Amber is a spy name.
- Yes
- No.
- What was yours be?
Meatball Martin Luther King Junior Boulevard.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Oh my god.
I'm so excited.
- You're a spy.
- I know, I know. I guess you can say...
Oh, I got to get one of those.
You think you're going to get one of those!
No, I'm not.
Look at that.
That looks high tech.
It's like the future.
- Patrick.
- Susan.
- Hey, Patrick.
- Yes.
I was given specific
instructions by Elaine
to tailor these
gadgets to you.
Wow.
Look at them.
-These are not yours.
- Oh.
Is that a whistle
Elaine wanted you to
only be carrying items
of single woman traveling
through Europe would have.
But she can get that
from any pharmacy
Not this whistle.
When you blow
through this whistle.
A small poisonous dart flies out,
neutralizing your target.
Also, it needs your
finger prints on it to work.
Okay, that is-that is really neat.
That is really super cool.
This anti-fungi spray
can freeze and disable
any security system.
Wow.
That is
quite an image to be
carrying all over Europe.
It's also a pepper spray.
Why not,  just make it
look like pepper spray.
It's a...
It's a pretty good idea.
Alright. Well, next time.
Well, I can-I can wait
if you wanna print up
a new label.
No, I'll have to
turn the printer on again.
I don't really want to.
Each of these are
filled with chloroform.
Oh, that is and un...
settling amount of
hemorrhoid wipes.
Makes me kind of wonder
what exactly is
going on back there.
I wouldn't know.
I don't have that problem.
If you ever feel like
you've been poisoned.
- Chew one of these.
[Stool softener_LAXATIVE]
Have I-Have I done something
to you, to upset you or...
This is peculiar theme.
Finally.
Every agent gets a night vision scope
hidden in their watch.
Okay. I've read about this,
I've even looked it...
- Oh.
- Who's that?
That is Bette Midler
and Barbara Hershey.
- From Beaches.
- Mm-Hm.
How much am I
suppose to like Beaches.
I would imagine a lot
if you have the watch.
- Hey Pat, I'm flying!
- Anthony.
Don't wear out
the battery on that.
Am I-Am I getting that?
No. You are not going
to get that, alright.
I've already packed your bags.
Hurry up and get dressed.
Carol Jenkins has to get
to the airport immediately.
And may I say.
I think it's very brave of you
to sacrifice your life
for your country.
Oh, not sacri...
I'm-I'm coming back.
Let's see.
You look amazing.
I look like someone's
homophobic aunt.
PARIS
PARIS_FRANCE
Wow.
Hotel Modiere please.
This is so exciting.
Oh.
The Louvre.
Wow.
Oh, that's a beautiful hotel.
Not that one?
Oh. I hope it's that.
Is it that one?
No? Oh, no.
Maybe next time.
We're getting into
a-a little dicier of an area.
Oh.
It's a little unsavory.
I think we can probably
go back towards
my hotel.
No no. No no.
I hope it's-it's...
It's-I don't believe this could
be the Hotel Modiere.
- Don't you think.
-[HOTEL MODIERE]
Oh, this is.
Yes it is.
Oh man.
Keep it together,
Susan okay.
Nancy?
Please tell me you can hear me.
- I'm here, I'm here. I got you.
- Okay.
Okay. You'll be pleased to hear
that the bats are officially gone.
We have now vermin free.
Did you get your gun, Carol?
Yes.
And don't call me that.
Oh, my God. I cried.
Peed, I think.
Having a heart attack.
I can't do this, Nancy.
Fine was the real spy, not me.
Don't worry.
I'm here for you, okay.
Everything is going to be fine.
I'm gonna talk you through this, alright.
Put your camera in.
I want to see your room.
Ewf. No, you don't.
It's that bad.
Martha Stewart had a
breakdown kind of feel.
Ooh.
Wow.
Looks like they put you up
in a Shits Carlton.
Hey listen.
Try and get some sleep, okay.
And we'll get started
first thing in the morning.
I don't know what I'm going to do
when I see that Rayna woman.
I want her dead for
what she did to Fine.
Okay, deep breaths.
Listen to me.
You're not going to get anywhere near her,
so there's nothing to worry about.
Guys!
There's a mouse on my tits.
I think you're safe there.
- Alright, goodnight.
- Night.
You got this, Susan.
You're a warrior.
You're a weapon.
Okay.
Look, no sweat.
Looks like you're
sweating to me.
Jesus!
What are you doing in my room?
What? How did I get into
this shit box hotel room?
- Because I'm a real spy.
- I thought you quit?
We have to stop the sale
of a nuclear bomb.
And they send in someone who
looks likes Santa Claus' fucking wife.
Uh.
Did you forget I'm undercover.
Because you're not
suppose to be here?
Well. I make a habit of doing things
that people say I can't do.
Walk through fire.
Water ski blindfolded.
Take a piano at a late age.
And I'm gonna take down
De Luca and Rayna and Dudaev.
And I'm gonna
get that bomb back.
- Why do you even care what I do?
- You think you're ready for the field?
I once used the
defibrillators on myself.
I put shards of glass
in my fucking eye.
I jumped,
from a high rise building.
Using only a raincoat,
as a parachute.
I broke both legs upon landing.
And I still had to pretend
I was in a fucking
Cirque Du Soleil show.
I've swallowed enough microchips
and shit them back out again.
To make a computer.
This arm has been
ripped off completely.
And re-attached with
this fucking hand.
You know it's, that's impossible.
I mean medically.
During the threat of
an assassination attempt
I appeared convincingly,
in front of Congress,
as Barack Obama.
In black face?
That's not appropriate.
I watched the woman I loved,
get tossed from a plane.
And hit by another plane,
midair!
I drove a car off the freeway,
on top of a train,
while I was on fire.
Not the car!
I was on fire.
Jesus.
You're intense.
Took this from your mini-bar.
Well, that's not right.
You're going to ruin this mission.
No.
You are.
No, you're going to.
- You times infinity.
- Oh.
Could this hotel be more murdery.
Okay.
So my office is in here.
Which means that De Luke's is
right across the street at 39...
Oh God. Tell me that's not
De Luca's building?
De Luca must have known
we were coming.
What am I suppose to do now?
Okay, don't panic.
Lemonade out of lemons.
Stay focus.
We can do this.
Excuse me, please.
-Yes?
When this building burned down?
Last night.
It was a big fire.
See.
There.
- Can I?
- Here You Go.
Does this man
lives on this street?
No, no.
I don't know him.
Okay.
I got it. I got it.
I'll run it through the system.
It will take a few minutes.
Nothing's coming up.
Might just be a looky-loo.
Well. Keep looking.
I've got a feeling about this guy.
Well, I've got a feeling
you're about to fuck things up.
Oh. Bugger me with a fishfork.
It's Ford.
Sharon? Ford is in the field.
Did you know this?
Until he checks in,
there's nothing I can do.
You go make some friends
and stop stalking me.
Was it your mission
to tip off the target,
so he burns everything
in their butts?
It's so well done.
Phenomenal.
I'm sure they got suspicious because
they've been seeing you all over the place.
- You're going to get yourself killed.
- Nothing kills me.
I am immune to
179 different kinds of poison.
I know because I
ingested them all at once.
When I was deep undercover
in an underground,
- poison ingesting crime ring.
- Wow.
It was like dog fighting.
But instead of dogs fighting
It was humans ingesting poison and rich people
will bet whether we would live or die.
Yeah. I'm having a hard time
with this one.
I died for 5 minutes,
and then I came back to life.
Was it worth... He looks like
he's in the cast of Newsies.
Does Crocker even
know you're here?
I don't need anyone's permission
to save the country.
and avenge my dear friend,
Bradley Fine's death.
You've didn't ever liked him.
You used to call him Beverly Whine.
You had him as secret Santa
and you gave him tampons.
It's called the rivalry of men.
You wouldn't understand it.
Unless you got the dong
up underneath that skirt.
Okay. That's super rude and
don't say dong. Don't do that.
Nobody sees me when
I don't want them to.
I move like a fucking shadow.
Oh.
Excuse me, sir.
He's gone all sorts of rogue.
Sharon says he really did quit.
Elaine couldn’t stop him.
He's out for blood.
Yeah, a real tough guy and
his Louis Vuitton backpack.
Nancy, do you see that?
It's the man from the fire.
- I'm follow him.
- Oh, exciting.
And I'm follow you,
follow him.
So I'm having
quite a day here.
Do you think Ford is
leading him to a trap?
Idiot doesn't even know
he is being followed.
Okay. He is meeting with some woman.
I don't recognize her.
You have any idea who she is?
No, it's hard to make out.
Can you get any closer?
Nancy, our guys just switched
Rick Ford's backpack.
It's a setup.
I got to go warn him.
Ford! Ford! Look out!
I got to get through!
I left my baby in the shop.
Get out of the way!
Let me through, I'm sick!
Susan, tell them
you shat your pants.
That would get me
out of your way for sure.
I shat my pants!
Excuse me.
Ford!
He's got a friend.
Hello everyone!
Hands up!
Let's dance!
Ford!
I need your mic!
No... I need.
No!
I...
No no no.
Don't.
Susan, you're meant to be blending in.
What are you doing?
No!
Move!
Rick Ford!
Give me the mike!
What you're doing doesn't help!
Oh god.
Rick Ford!
They switched the bag!
Oh, fuck!
Get out of the fucking way!
Move!
Get out of his way!
Oh, no.
Nancy, I'm in pursuit on
one of the terrorists.
He took my picture,
he's going to blow my cover.
You're in pursuit.
What will you do if you catch him?
What in god's name are you
going to do when you catch him.
Knock him over with a hammer.
I don't know.
I'm still tracking and
reporting his location.
This all seem very
Rick Fordy to me.
I do not condone this sexy but
reckless action of yours, Susan.
Oh God.
He went into a building.
Okay, girl.
Well done, that's it.
Time to call it a day now.
Location is officially noted.
- I'm following him in.
- What?
I'm doing this for Fine.
He's at the top of the stairs.
Oh God.
Please be careful.
You are incredibly
out of your league.
Oh. This is just like when I
watched myself in a sex tape.
There is just a lot of philandering
and laughable moments.
Nancy, I need you to not talk,
until I ask you to.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I'm really nervous.
Be careful Susan.
Oh, hey.
Imagine, running into you up here.
I was just looking for my bird.
I..
just looking...
Hey, Mr. Beanbag!
You like birds?
Alright. Alright.
Let me give you a warning.
I don't want to see anymore of that
funny bomb stuff.
You know?
Alright, that's enough.
Drop the knife or I'll shoot.
I don't think you will.
You see. It works better when
you have the bullets inside the gun.
Oops.
I guess that CIA training
isn't what it used to be.
Guess you're right, asshole!
No, no, no!
Oh God.
Oh Susan, what did you do?
Oh God. Not on him.
Not on him!
Well. Rayna's people obviously
knew Ford was in Paris.
And getting footage of a CIA operative
setting off a bomb in a public
could be a PR qoof
for any terrorist group.
Do we have anything
on that woman he met?
Facial recognition isn't showing anything.
They were all over Ford.
Are you able to track him?
Oh, God damn Ford is
still off the grid in Paris.
I know, because he keeps trying
to hack into our system for Intel.
He's like a dog that gets
loose from his yard. And just.
keeps humping and shitting
his way through the neighborhood.
Okay, here's a video.
Make sure you got
everything on camera.
Phase out of the hotel
and go back after the attack.
I'll take Renaldo to Rome.
Renaldo. We have a record
of anyone with that name?
Not that I'm aware of.
Nicola.
Are you listening to me?
- I was just testing the camera.
- Stop it. Find Ford.
Hey, Nancy. Can you pull up Fine's
POV cam from Boyanov's office. And.
Look on the desk
there's some photos there
and see if you can find one
of him standing next to a car.
Renaldo is a Rolls Royce.
Hack into the Rolls tracking system.
That car's a Wraith so is has a
Satellite Aided Transmission.
And tap into Boyanov's feed
His GPS should tell you exactly
where De Luca is in Rome right now.
I'm gonna head to the airport.
Forget it Cooper.
You're coming back immediately.
Ma'am, I really think
I can do this.
And I'm not one to toot my own horn, but
you know what, I'm gonna toot.
And say that, I just
saved a lot of people.
We're so close in getting
Rayna and that bomb.
- Pull back that rug in the corner.
- Oh.
- You'll be given a new identity.
- Oh, thank God!
Oh!
No!
Your name is Penny Morgan.
You're a divorced housewife from Iowa.
You sold more Marry Kay products
than anyone else in your state.
You traded in a free car you won
to fund a trip through Europe.
My hobbies are decopatch
and needlepoint.  I collect
porcelain dolls. And I am the
Vice President of the Ames Garden Club.
I couldn't even be president?
Maybe I should just be married to one
of the dolls. Just to make it extra sad.
10 cats?
What do I have 10 cats?
Is that even legal?
You know Fine,
he got to be a businessman.
Once he was even
a race car driver.
Well, there's the 10 cats.
Just missing the shirt that says
I've never felt the touch of a man.
Oh Cooper, you're right.
You did good work back there.
That would had been a real mess.
Thank you ma'am.
You still
went with the cat lady.
It was already in the floor.
ROME
ROME_ITALY
Hi beautiful!
How are you?
Oh my god.
So pretty.
Great.
That's a real confidence builder.
- Did you find De Luca?
- He's been at the Majestic hotel,
but he's just left.
Heading south, okay.
I'll guide you to him.
I've sent a ally to drive you.
Elaine said nothing fancy,
so I
I've gone with earthy.
Woo.
Whoa.
- He stopped the car.
- Alo, Fuck off!
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Hi beauty.
- Oh.
- Welcome to Rome!
- Thank you. Oh.
Thank you.
Oh.
I am Aldo.
Like, the shoe store
found in American malls.
I'm Penny, like the penny.
Like a penny.
- I like penne alla vodka (pasta dish).
- Okay.
Did you just grab my butt?
Yes.
Come.
We need to get you to De Luke.
Gravity Christmas!
Oh, my God!
Don't worry, I have you.
Slow down!
Nancy, are you sure this guy is even an agent?
Absolutely.
No, he's the best.
He's-He. Oh. Though there had been
some complaints filed against him.
- Hey, watch the road! Watch the road!
- Hey, Mary! I love you!
Oh my god!
Watch the road!
Wow.
Aldo is making great time.
Awww!
Watch the cart!
Dead end!
This can't be right.
Oh my god.
- God!
- Intriguing lady, we're here.
Now.
You must go because I fear,
if I stare into your beautiful
green eyes a moment longer,
I will fall in love.
Oh.
Too late.
Might as if it ever worked?
- I will take that as...
- That's a no.
- I Know.
- Take that as a no.
God.
Hey, ma'am.
Ah, typing.
I admire your thumb.
You know.
You were just hitting on me.
- I like to play the odds.
- yeah.
Here is my phone number.
Memorize it, then burn it.
Do you have something for me?
Do I have something for you?
- Would you like something from me?
- I-Not that.
What do you want from me?
You're suppose to have an
envelope with my gun in it.
I don't have a gun.
I am just arouse
from looking you.
It was a joke.
There is no gun.
They said you would no longer
be needing one.
Good luck.
Bye.
Gravy.
Was Pepe Le Pew not available?
Oh.
Stop complaining, Susan.
You're getting more actions
than I had in days.
Months. Years.
3 years and 40 days.
Do you have an
update on De Luca?
Yes, yup. He should be
pulling up right about now.
[RENALDO]
Oh, wow.
He is hot.
I'm not going to lie to you.
I don't think I can be objective anymore.
I'm rooting for that guy.
I want him to win.
I'm joking Susan,
don't report me.
Ewk.
And he is handsy.
Let's set up camp in the
pastry shop behind you.
According to our data De Luca
spends all night at the casino.
- I'm going in, Nancy.
- Susan, you heard Elaine.
Track and report.
No contact.
I'll track De Luca inside,
and then I'll report.
And if he initiate contacts with me,
I'll just- I'll go with it.
Susan, your cat lady look is
not going to fit in, in there.
That's right. Penny Morgan is
gonna burn her cat T-shirt
and spend some of that
Mary Kay money.
This is full blown rogue.
Hey, beautiful looking!
You are so pretty! Beautiful!
You guys are terrible.
Awh.
I really hope De Luca is
still in there, for your sake.
And they're not going to
reimburse you for that.
You should've gone to
cheaper stores, Susan.
- Okay. I'm going offline, Nancy.
- Wait-wait. Wait-wait. Su...
Susan!
Well.
Bonjour now, boys.
If I'm not out in 10 minutes
it's because I won the place.
Let me just
rub that for luck.
Oh, that's an oily-
that's an oily scalp.
Enchanté. (Nice to meet you)
I'm sorry.
But I have to check you in.
- Your name, please.
- Penny Morgan.
I-I don't see you on the list.
I'm so sorry.
She's with me.
Darling.
You’re late.
The way you look,
I say it's more than
worth the wait.
- Come. Let's get a drink.
- Ow.
Such a gentleman.
You look absolutely stunning tonight.
And darling...
What the fuck
are you doing in here?
Well, that's quit a tone changes
and what are you doing in here?
You're completely
compromising me right now.
Oh, I'm compromising you?
Fucking hilarious.
You're about to cause a scene
trying to get into this fucking place.
Give me a little credit.
What do you think I'm going to do?
Run over and be like:
"Hey, I'm a crazy lady!
Where's the buffet?
I'm from the Midwest.
Where's Blue man group?"
Okay. I'm not an idiot, Ford!
You're an idiot!
You should not be in this casino,
because De Luca here.
- And I need to get close to him.
- Yeah. How are you going to do that?
How are you going
to do that, Cooper?
What. You're going to seduce him?
That your big fucking plan?
Yeah. What if it is?
Why is it so hard to believe?
Because you look like a flute
player in a wedding band.
That's fucking why!
I'm here to take De Luca out.
Oh, sounds romantic.
I hope you get lucky.
God damn it.
If I was trying to sound romantic,
you would be on another floor,
soaking wet and breathless.
Wondering what came over you.
But I'm not!
So get the fuck out of my way.
I need you to rein it in, buddy.
Okay.
If you take out De Luca,
we don't have a shot at getting Rayna.
So take it down like 5000 notches.
- Take it down. That's how you get
polonium 2000. In your drink
-Oh God.
I got 18 months in intensive care
for radiation poisoning.
I got 6 months without eyes,
While everyone I ever loved is gunned down.
Really. Everyone that you loved has been
gunned down, and just you survived.
Did you ever think that maybe
everybody you loved is not being killed,
but they're killing themselves because
they can't stand to be around you.
This shit is the real deal.
Life and death.
This, the field, is hell
a lot different than
sitting behind your fucking
monitor googling shit.
Stay away from me, Ford.
And do not let De Luca see you.
And by the way, I can see your gun
sticking out of your back pocket.
Unless you're so extreme,
you got a second dick
coming out of your hip!
Oh, Konichiwa. (good afternoon)
- Ma'am,
- Yes yes.
- Seats are reserved.
- Of course they are, yes.
I'm going to have to
ask you to wait outside.
Yes, absolutely.
No?
Another door?
I knew that.
Of course there's another door.
Probably happens all the time.
- It's never happened before.
- Okay.
- Ma'am?
-Yes.
Ma'am, right here is okay.
No more exploring, please.
Okay.
Lovely.
- Nancy?
- Susan?
Oh my god.
Hi.
I found her. I found Rayna.
She's with De Luca.
You did it.
Excellent trucking and reporting, madam.
Oh my god. Somebody just
put something in her drink.
- What is it? Is it poison?
- I don't think it's a fiber supplement.
She killed Fine, Nancy.
I could really enjoyed just
watching her die right now.
And she's the only one
who knows where the bomb is.
So Dudaev will never
get his hands on it.
Oh god, Susan.
What're you going to do?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am, hi.
Do you speak English?
Because I think somebody just
put a roofie in your cocktail.
- Are you sure it wasn't you?
- What?
No.
God, I wouldn't-I wouldn't never.
Could you point the man out?
Well, he just kind of
zipped out that door.
He's wearing a purple bow tie.
Thank you, Miss...?
Oh. Penny Morgan.
Oh, it's no trouble.
Really, I mean.
I think us ladies,
have to watch out for each other.
I mean these kind of thing
happens all the time.
And people often try to roofie... you?
Once, I asked someone for a Tylenol,
and they gave me a Tylenol PM.
I'm not sure what
their intentions were. But.
It seems they may have found him.
Would you come with me to identify him?
Yes, of course.
I'm...
happy to help.
Holy shit.
My friend here says she saw
you put something in my drink.
I don't know any of you people.
Okay, I'm just in Rome on business.
I was about to head back
to my hotel and go to sleep.
Perfect.
Just in time for a night cap.
- Apparently there's nothing wrong with it.
- I don't want your drink.
Fuck you, Rayna.
Mmm.
Scrumptious.
So.
Jokes on you.
Fuck you.
How long was I out?
You fainted just long enough
for us to laugh at you.
- What happened?
- It was all a dream.
I'm just kidding.
A man's throat dissolved.
Sorry, that wasn't my fault.
Oh, thank you.
That's...
surprisingly polite.
Sorry about that.
I just...
I mean I've seen a lot of things
in my days.  I just never
I have never
seen that, exactly.
Penny.
Do you feel the need to tell
anybody about what you just saw?
Am I going to tell anybody?
You know that
asshole got what he deserved.
I mean.
I knew the second I saw him,
I thought.
That guy doesn't deserve a throat.
So.
Good on you.
I would like to take you to dinner,
to say thank you.
And we must discuss
this hideous dress.
It's just hysterical.
Oh, ha ha.
Good.
That's-
That's what I was hoping... for.
Oh.
And by the way!
Christo is suppose to be
looking after me at the bar
making sure nobody would
put anything in my drinks.
Thought I give him a talking to.
Seems fair maybe
dock him a day's wage.
Or shoot him in the head.
That always works.
- You know, Rome is quite amazing.
- Rome is the worst.
- Yes.
- So boring and tacky.
I'm so glad one of us finally said it.
Eh-heh-heh
- You have lipstick on your teeth.
- Really?
Looks like you had
a box of crayons.
Damn it.
Here we are.
These should have been brought out
when we first sat down.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
So far I'm riddled with
disappointed at the service.
So sorry. You know, ma'am.
I apologize.
You know, I once saw someone
eat one of
these before
This is strange.
Do you always tear your
food up into little pieces?
You look like a squirrel.
I was just checking
for the consistency
- Mm.
- You eat like a baby.
Thank You.
So, would you like to have
a look at the wine list?
Yes.
Penny, you can order.
Okay. Oh.
Passum.
OK. I'm feeling-
I'm feeling a red
Kind of a red.
Like a lot of noise.
Like a little bit of
a-a barky finish.
I tend to like a white, with the grid
of a hamus
That’s, of course,
been thinned out.
Okay, here. I will have the
Sapori e Delicia.
Right. That is the
name of this restaurant.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
So.
Why don't you surprise us
with something we don't know?
Like a delicious bottle of wine.
Right, sorry.
I'll be back in 5 minutes, okay.
So hard to get good help
these days.
Don't you find that?
When I was a little girl
growing up in Bulgaria
which is the worse by the way.
Poor people everywhere and
cabbage is continuously cooking.
There was this woman who
was kicked out of her house.
And she lost all her money.
She couldn't even sell her body.
So she became a clown
on the streets.
She would performed all
her tricks standing in mud.
And just cry and cry.
You remind me of this woman.
Yo, thank you.
Come on!
We're going to Budapest.
- Bu-Budapest?
- I have some business to finish there.
And you can take my private jet
when we're done.
Anywhere you want to get home.
My way of repaying you
for saving my life.
Okay.
Is there a problem?
No, not at all.
Let's go.
Hey, what? What?
I'm just talking with the girl.
Okay okay.
Let's not make a scene.
You know what I need. Just get my room key
out and I'll grab a bag and pack my things.
It's Susan.
She's sending a code.
- No, they can collect you back later.
- Shut
And if the rest of your
clothes are like that dress
down
I can send someone
to burn them for you.
- the power.
- Quit a zinger.
Shut down the power
to the casino in Rome.
What?
Well, shut the entire
bloody grid down then. Now!
That would be great.
Everybody please remain calm.
Stay where you are.
Oh, no!
What's happening?
I have this.
What the fuck just happened?
- God damn it.
- Oh my god. Rayna.
Thank god your hair
broke your fall.
I don't know what happened.
The lights were going out.
And I thought it was a robbery.
Two of your guys slammed into me.
And took you down.
I think one of them touched my bottom.
Are they going to be okay?
I wouldn't be worried about them.
Their fate has just been sealed.
Sorry, oh.
I'll let you go. Let you go.
Shame on you!
Wow!
This is a really jetsy plane.
Is this yours?
- It is my father's.
- Oh.
You've never been
on a private jet before?
Oh no.
I did get upgraded to premium
economy once, which was pretty plush.
Premium economy.
Sounds like a pen
for dirty animals.
Yeah, probably.
But it was not quite like this.
Thank you.
Why are you being
so nice to me?
Can't just be because I remind
you of some sad Bulgarian clown.
You remind me of my mother.
Oh.
Really? You know that...
I mean, you and I are.
You know, pretty close in age.
You're funny.
It's the Bulgarian clown in you.
- Okay.
- She was marvelous.
But she was different.
Eccentric, like you are.
The moment I saw you standing
there in that abortion of a dress
- Oh, come on.
- It's as if to say
This is what I got, world.
It's hideous, but it's mine.
- This was her.
- Oh, wow!
Hey, how did you get that picture of me?
I look amazing.
Hello doppelganger.
She was the only person
I could ever trust.
- Well. Here's to your mom.
- To my mother.
- And to you.
- And here's to you.
You may never be
as wise as an owl,
but you'll always be
a hoot to me.
What a stupid fucking
retarded toast.
- You're delightful.
- As are you.
Now.
Where did you say we're headed?
Headed
Where did you say we're...
Oh God.
If you ever feel like
you've been poisoned
Chew one of these.
What happened?
I've never seen somebody
dive for stool softener before.
That's one thing that happened.
What did you do?
Did you drug me?
Of course I did.
I told you, I can't trust anybody.
I had to look through
your things. Anyway.
Tell me. Are you hemorrhoids
particularly large or just tenacious?
Stop texting!
I'm not texting
if you must know.
I'm playing Candy Crash.
And I just made level 95.
God, that is so rude.
Jesus, Colin,
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm sorry, Rayna but there's
been a change of plans.
Who paid you off, Colin?
Colin hasn't worked here for like 8 months.
I'm Frederick.
Is that why you are doing this? Because
I didn't remember your fucking name?
Let's just say there are people who
really want what you're selling.
You don't have to do this.
I can give you a very
comfortable life. Col...
- Mmm.
- You forgot my name again, didn't you?
- No. No, I didn't.
- Yeah.
It's...
Hmm.
Don't say fucking Colin.
Fuck. I don't give a shit what your
name is. You're the fucking help.
Nice try, Colin.
But Stan and I already se...
It's Frederick!
Frederick!
Sorry lady. But they
only paid me for one...
Aw!
Wha!
Come on!
Rayna, go to the cockpit
and level us out!
Like I know how to fly
a fucking aeroplane!
This was weird.
Blow that thing
all you want, lady.
Yeah.
Why don't you blow me, Colin.
Aww.
It's Frederick.
Ewk.
Eww.
Oh.
For fuck sake.
I got it.
I know what to do.
Oh, are you okay?
No! I got a dead
man's head up in my ass!
This one's for Fine.
Down draft!
Not again! Do you have any idea
what you are fucking doing!
Oh.
The controls are so sensitive.
God. One of these dead fuckers
just shit his pants.
Okay, wait a minute.
I got it.
I think I got, okay.
Okay.
Good thing I learned to use
that Flight Simulator app, huh.
Congratulations
Penny Morgan.
You just blew your cover.
Now put the plane on
autopilot and get up.
Any bullshit and I'll blow your
CIA brains all over that control panel.
I know what you're thinking.
And you're wrong.
My real name is
Did you come up with your spy name yet?
-No.
- My would be.
- Amber Valentine.
What are you?
A porn star?
You're fucking hilarious, huh?
I'm a private bodyguard, and your
father hired me to protect you.
Bodyguard.
You? Please.
That's funny. 'Causes the way I see it.
Without me.
You would currently be
crashed in the Alps right now.
Or you'll be laying in the morgue
with a hole burned in your throat.
You little spoiled piece of shit!
Why would my father
hired somebody like you?
Because he trusted me.
And for whatever fucking reason,
he loved you.
Didn't even want you to know
I'm watching you.
So...He's the one who made me come up with
this whole loser Penny Morgan bullshit.
Yeah, Oh, you looked like dead,
like my dead mama.
And fuck you for saying I look
anything like that fucking beast!
No wonder your father
never had the son he wanted.
You fuck that monster once and you just
dropped the fucking mic and walked out.
Fuck you!
Everything you said is a lie.
Oh, what happened?
Did I hit a little sore spot?
Yeah. He always wanted a son,
and you knew it.
Look. He wanted you to
take over the business.
He's just afraid
you'll get yourself killed.
So, if you want to live and
you want to load that bomb,
you stick with me.
And if you got
a problem with that...
Know what you can do, Rayna?
You and your bullshit accent
can land this fucking plane by yourselves.
Okay, bodyguard.
But if I find out you're lying
to me about of any of this,
I'll show you ways to die
you've never even dreamed of.
Now let's go to Budapest.
I need a fucking drink.
Yeah, I bet you fucking do.
Oh my God.
BUDAPEST
BUDAPEST_HUNGARY
FOUR SEASONS HOTEL
Welcome back to the
Four Seasons Budapest, Miss Boyanov.
Don't talk to me, you're not my friend.
Get away from me.
Okay, move.
Move! I got it!
So. What's the plan?
Who are we meeting?
You're my bodyguard,
not my business partner.
So just focus on
guarding my body.
So not knowing who we're meeting
tonight is going to make me
...extra effective.
That's okay, I get it.
I've got shit to do,
you'll probably be fine.
Why don't I go get you a nice dress
to be buried in. Dumb ass.
I'm meeting a potential bidder
if you must know.
If they don't top the current,
offered sale will happen tomorrow.
- Where?
- I don't know yet.
- Anton.
- Ouch!
Anton is part of my security team,
psycho.
Yeah. Well, guess what.
I don't like his face.
I don't like the looks
on your face!
And who the fuck are you?
I'm the person that's gonna cut your
dick off and glue it to your forehead
so you look like a limp dick unicorn.
That's who the fuck I am!
Your name should be
Mr. Bagofdicks, not Anton.
Okay, Jesus!
Let's just calm down, okay?
Does he not look
like a bag of dicks.
Enough! I can see why
my father like you now.
Amber is my
hired bodyguard.
Be more like her.
And your head had better
not broke my fucking phone.
Got a big night ahead of us.
Don't be afraid to clean
yourself up, Amber.
Take a shower,
that's what I'm saying.
Yeah? Don't be afraid
to hit water yourself.
You smell like a dead hooker
that washed up on the beach
and then roasted in the sun for a week
before they've even found her body.
Okay, you need to take it,
way down.
- I'm sorry, that's too much.
- I've told you.
- Okay. That was too much. Too much.
- Oh Jesus.
M.R. Sumon @subscene.com
What are you staring at?
- Give me your fucking coat.
- This is a man's coat. So.
Yeah, but I don't see a man,
do I?
I see a reject from
"The sound of Music."
Well, I won't give it to you.
I've been in this dress for
12 fucking hours. Give me your coat.
No.
- I'm gonna take that fucking coat.
- Aw.
I warned you. You Swedish
gummy fish motherfucker.
Ouch!
Oh my god.
- Nancy.
- Oh my god. Susan.
Hello. Hello?
Just say something to me, please.
Susan, anything.
I cannot handle this, Susan.
There is nothing in real life
that someone could do to a spy
that is filthier or more upsetting than
what my brain would cook up right now.
So save me from myself, Susan!
Because you know
what's gonna happen?
I'm gonna get chattier, aren't I.
Did you know that you can't have a change
having big thoughts
- or the brain...
- Oh my god, Nancy. You're driving me nuts.
I couldn't talk because I was
in an elevator filled with people.
Oh, you're alright.
Oh thank god.
You disappeared for 12 hours.
We didn't know what had happened.
Well, I had to take off my
earpiece and my camera.
Rayna is on to our agents. So she was going to
spot my equipment from a mile away.
You're with Rayna?
You're not suppose to be
within a mile away of her.
Nancy, I know. But I'm in deep
and I'm getting such good Intel.
Please, I just need to remain on
radio silence just a little bit longer.
Okay, don't worry. Because I'll be out
to keep a better eye on you now.
Why are you saying that?
How?
- Eh.
- Wait. Wh-What are you doing here?
Elaine wanted to know exactly what
you're up to, so I tracked your earpiece.
- They sent me here to find you.
- They sent you?
Well. I was as unknown as you are,
so they thought my cover was safe.
Did they give you an identity?
It's so cool. I said I wanted
to be Amber Valentine. And.
- What?
- And they let me use it.
Hey I don't know why you
get to pick your identity.
I had to go with
the freaking cat lady.
- Amber!
-Yes.
- Yes.
- Who is this?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know the
police were here.
This is my colleague.
Detective
The one I fucking
told you about.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did, Helen Keller!
So, you're both named Amber?
Whoa! What did I tell
you about talking to me?
Nothing. You just said
nothing about talking.
You know what. You want me to have
Cagney and fucking Lacey explain it to you.?
Cagney's coming down
your fucking throat.
Lacey, she's gonna
come up your ass
I'm gonna meet them
in the fucking middle
and play your heart
like a fucking accordion.
I'm gonna pump
that shit until it pops.
- You Swedish bitch!
- You wouldn't dare!
You gonna cry?
You little Swiss fucking pussy.
- I'm not going to cry.
- You're crying now!
I'm not.
It's so fucking hot.
Okay. You know. Just let's leave
Anton alone for now, please.
What's your name?
- Susan Cooper.
- What?
- Oh, sorry. It came out.
- What did I just...
Not suppose to fucking
say her real name.
She's one of my best.
She's highly fucking skill.
- Very skill.
- At what?
Getting things out of
a higher cupboard?
That's-That's very good.
Because I'm tall?
Really, I'm not very good
at reaching high things.
A doctor once said to me that
I had the muscles capacity of an infant.
- My arms are like 2 noodles...
- Get down!
Susan, get Rayna to safety.
Now!
- I've got her.
- Go!
Go away!
Who puts a roof on a scooter!
What are you, the pope?
Get out of the way!
Oh my god!
They're driving crazy,
I can't keep up with them.
Okay, wait a minute.
I got it.
Alright.
A little detour.
Oh god.
Let's do this.
I am so bad ass!
Got it.
I know what you're saying.
Do your project now!
Just get to work!
Where are we going?
Smells like cheese over here!
Stick with me,
you'll be safe.
Crawl with me. I must protect you.
Crawl with me.
Fucking ridiculous clown show.
This fuckery stops now.
- Excuse me. Do you know if there is a
Popeyes Chicken around here?
- What?
I saw a KFC down the way,
but I'm more of a Popeyes guy.
The food is really weird I...
Oh my God, I'll ask someone else!
Okay, enough!
Drop your weapon!
Oh my god. Karen.
Why aren't you at Capri?
I'm so sorry I shot you.
You must have not known
it was me either.  I changed my hair.
Oh, yeah. Looks really good.
Are those extensions?
No.
It's just-It's just my hair.
- You know, a few clips, colored.
- Okay, if you say so.
I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry about this too.
Oh, my God.
No no no...
Susan, my thighs are on fire.
I don't care.
Where is Rayna?
I don't know. She slipped off me,
I was very sweaty.
- Karen Walker is dead.
- What?
She's a double agent.
Somebody shot her right in front of me.
I don't know who did it.
I don't know how deep
this whole thing goes.
Oh my God.
Oh!
Oh.
Get your motherfucking
asses up here!
Now!
Shit!
People are trying to kill me, and all
that's left of my fucking security team
is you two defending me! You look like
somebody's demented aunts on vacation!
Do you have anyone on your team,
other than this asthmatic Big bird?
Yeah.
We usually just use her for
non-physical security resources.
I'm very non-physical resourceful.
I do a lot of reading.
I read palms and maps.
And I read all of
"The Hunger Games".
How is that helpful!
I don't know,
I'm panicking.
And you! You have to stop with
this stupid Penny Morgan outfit.
You have to dress like
an actual human!
Get me more security when I come
back out here, or you're both dead!
Suck on this, Rayna.
This mission is going to cost you,
you know.
The clothing allowance cut off
half way through the last...
Oh god. Could you please concentrate
on getting the new bodyguard.
- God damn me! Please.
- Alright. Alright.
Crappy.
I've already contacted the agency.
Oh.
Come on!
You, in this outfit.
Magnifico.
(Magnificent)
- You have anything yet?
- No one so far, Susan.
Slight intimidating crowd, however.
Hello.
You look nice.
Ah, just keep laughing.
Looks fade.
Just keep your eyes open.
God damn it.
I told you to dress up.
And take off those gloves.
You look like Darth fucking Vader.
You know the reason I'm wearing these
gloves is because I don't know what kind
of woodland creatures is
going to come crawling
out of that fucking nest
on top of your head.
Whatever.
Keep a eye out for this woman.
She's the one coming
to make the bid.
He's got a friend.
I need you to keep your eyes open.
I may need your help out there.
To close my eyes in the presence of
this beautiful body would be a crime.
Oh god.
Nancy. Okay, you know that women
I spotted in Paris, the bomber?
Well, she's coming tonight
to make the bid.
If she really works for De Luca so we know
some things up. I need you to keep an...
God.
Son of a beast thing.
Excuse me, he's mine.
Yeah.
I didn't mean to hit her that hard.
God. You look like a balloon animal.
Here, take those.
- Hi. What are you doing, Ford?
- I'm here to help you, Cooper.
You may have found Rayna,
but you cannot lose her.
- This isn't fucking play time, anymore.
- Yeah?
It's play time on your face
with your stupid mustache.
You look like a pervert
bus driver.
- Cooper?
- Yeah.
It helped.
Let go.
Yeah, who's dominating now?
You're putting this entire
operation in danger.
Your girlfriend, from the Paris bombing,
is on her way here to meet Rayna.
If she sees you, only my cover's blown.
And then we're both dead.
Just worry about yourself, Cooper.
Thank you for the beautiful ladies.
You guys okay?
Let's welcome
Mr. 50 Cent
What's up Budapest.
Oh, shit.
She's here.
Okay. We can't let Rayna see her.
So, you need to take out her
bodyguards, and I'll deal with her.
- Hey. Nobody orders me around.
- God. Do you have a better idea?
We'll release
a gas in the club
causing everybody to get
temporary amnesia.
- Get a 100 sticks of dynamite...
- Oh god.
Just go!
Nancy, I need you
to get in here now!
I'm coming, Susan.
I'm here, I'm here.
Pardon, excuse me.
Okay.
I'm here. I'm here.
Oh, wow!
50 Cent a piece.
Thanks for letting me know.
Do not let Rayna see that woman.
Create a diversion, now!
- What kind of diversion?
- A big one.
50, I love you!
Kiss me.
- Get her!
- Take me now!
Turn around.
- Get off!
- I'm coming in.
Nancy, I got her.
Meet me outside.
Okay, great. No, I'm fine now.
Thank you so much. Okay.
Now I got my wish.
And that was it.
For a hob, now I got to drop
Michael Bublé in Croatia. He wants me.
Okay, Cooper.
I got this under control.
You're coming with me.
Oh my god.
Susan!
Okay, bigger diversion!
Huge diversion!
Bitch!
I got to know who she's working for.
Get Rayna out of here.
That's not fair!
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
God damn it!
- Nancy, where are you?
- A bit indispose.
It turns out 50 Cent doesn't have
a great sense of humor or irony.
I need backup!
I lost my gun in the club!
Okay.
Aw! Why did I get
rid of my gloves?
Ah!
AW!
Ah-ha-ha...
Aw!
Motherbuttler!
You got a lot of rage
in that jumpsuit.
- Get up!
- Aw.
You are under arrest by Susan Cooper
and the government of the United States.
Rayna, how did you do that?
I didn’t.
He did.
Hello, Coop.
Fine.
Aw.
Hey.
Coop.
Wake up!
Did you have a nice nap?
You were snoring very loudly.
Well, this is really not the
most upsetting news right now.
My father used to
bring people here.
Did he also make you dressed
like a slutty dolphin trainer?
He starved them, tortured them.
You name it.
But he especially didn't like it
when people lied to him.
Not that I bought it.
- You knew?
- Of course I knew.
I told you you were better
off in the basement, Coop.
- You could have avoided all of this.
- And what, Fine?
Now you're a nuclear black marketer?
A terrorist?
No.
He's just fucking me.
You're a loud kisser.
- Excuse me?
- You're a loud kisser.
And it's gross and unappealing.
You look like some
old toothless woman
sucking the jelly out of a donut.
Hey. How's it like sleeping with
the man who killed your father?
Nice try Coop.
- She already know it was Cress.
- Ah. Okay.
You probably always been in love
with him, haven't you?
Talking in his ear,
hoping eventually one day
he'll fall in love with you.
Poor little pathetic Susan Coleman.
Reminisce my last name so truly
not much of a burden, is it?
- Coppin.
- No.
Cropon?
Are you-Are you thinking Groupon?
No, my name is not Groupon.
Croop?
Keep going.
- Kapalski.
- It's getting further from it.
Well.
Whatever the fuck it is,
Let's just call it Dead!
Hey, baby. I thought we were
gonna hang on to her till tonight?
I changed my mind!
Goodbye.
Like I waste a bullet on you.
Put her in the room.
Aw.
Eah!
Hey Aldo.
Hello captured lady.
I failed.
I failed the mission.
Fine's alive and
he's a traitor.
Don't be downhearted.
My mama,
said to me.
Aldo,
life is
full of sorrow
and surprises.
But a
magnificent
pair of bosoms
will...
Good story.
- Susan.
- Get away from me.
No, listen.
I haven't got much time.
Why did you do it, Fine?
This was my only way in.
I had to fake my death
to gain Rayna's trust.
I jammed the signal.
Popped out my lens. It was easy.
I hated to do it to you, Coop.
But I had to, I had to.
Rayna knew all about our agents,
'cause Karen Walker
sold her the names.
I just couldn't trust anyone at the
agency not to give me away.
Not even you.
How would I know
you're telling me the true?
Did Karen Walker
tried to kill you?
- You shot her?
- I'm deep undercover.
But not so deep that
I can't still protect you.
Alright.
Look me in the eye.
- Huh?
- Really. Look me in the eye.
One of your eyes is
bigger than the other.
- Really?
- No.
You're perfect.
God damn it.
Asshole.
- Ou!
- That hurt.
Good, it's suppose to.
- Bosom.
- Huh?
- Is he dangerous?
- Only if you have boobs.
So. Does Rayna really
know I was a spy?
No.
Not until you blew your cover
back at that kitchen.
I really thought she was
more experienced than that.
Thank God she's not.
Because if she was,
you would be dead now.
- I used your pretty good covers...
- I got to go.
We're heading to De Luca De villa
to meet with Dudaev.
Then we're taking him
to wherever the bomb is.
This thing is almost over.
Hang tight.
Hello, bound lady.
Not now, Aldo.
I think Mr. Fine
underestimated you.
You found your target,
you tracked them down.
You fought very hard.
Susan.
You're a good agent.
You'll get them next time, huh?
Unless we die here.
Maybe we'll not.
You know what?
I'm not going down like this.
I need you to untie me.
No. You heard Mr. Fine.
He's working a plan.
- We have to stay put.
- Untie me. Now!
That's my ass!
It is very difficult to see
or gauge my position.
You're just simply
grabbing my ass.
Let's roll to our side.
God! Oh!
Aye!
The knot is very tight,
but I am making progress.
You hand is
way up in there.
My right hand is restraint
from the weight of my body.
Okay.
I got an idea.
Oh my god.
- Oh Jesus.
- Don't move.
- Wait, wait. Wait.
- Stay still.
- No-no-no...
- Yes-yes-yes...
- Good god.
- Scusa. (Excuse me)
Can't be happening.
God damn it. I was having such an
empowering moment before you started.
My penis
may be gently kissing
the back of your head.
Just untie me before
I crush your nuts!
Oh, please!
If only we had time for
such pleasures.
God!
Oh, stop licking it!
- It is done.
- Thank you Aldo.
I don't want to know
why my neck is wet but
- you did excellent work.
- Prego. (Welcome)
Okay. Turn around.
Let me untie you
and let's get the
fuck out of here.
Stop!
I need you to alert
CIA and Interpol.
I'm going to De Luca's
and backup Fine.
You know where the villa is?
I know everything.
One day, Lady superspy.
Susan Cooper.
I will fuck you.
Love this new car smell.
Really nice.
Mmm.
Welcome to Lake Balaton.
I found this staircase and made
them built a house around it.
Our dear Mr. Dudaev
will be arriving shortly.
You.
are about to become
a very rich woman, Rayna.
Which means you'll have to be a little more
careful about the company you keep.
So many people have such
terrible agendas.
Like perhaps,
your friend here.
I can see his obvious
outer appeal.
You've terrific eyes.
Thanks.
But he also works for
the CIA, doesn't he?
Mr. De Luca, it's true.
I worked for the CIA.
But they think I'm dead.
You and Karen Walker,
both double agents.
What's going on in the CIA?
Drones taken all the cool assignments?
If we don't get rid
of him right now,
I'm calling off the deal.
Don't you fucking dare.
Yeah. Why don't you
listen to that, asshole.
Don't you fucking dare.
You're a bit outnumbered here.
Miss...
I'm sorry,
what the fuck is your name?
Susan Cooper.
I'm with the CIA.
Jesus. Rayna, did you invite
the entire agency here
or are they just having a
company retreat at
the villa next door.
God, you're funny.
Huh.
It's just me.
As could be in your best interest
to keep Fine and me alive.
I'm trying, but I not quite
following your logic.
You want me to slow it
down for you. Okay.
You're about to meet
with Solsa Dudaev.
A man I've been collecting
intelligence on for years.
And I'm guessing your boys here
are too busy manscaping
to tell you how
he does business.
It's about half the people
he deals with end up dead.
I'll tell you another thing.
Your little girlfriend,
one from the Paris bombing.
She's just using you
to get to Rayna.
If it hadn't for me last night,
she would have kidnapped her at the club.
And you would be standing
here with your dick in your hand,
because you'd never find that bomb.
So.
You need me, De Luca.
And I'm not going to help you
unless you keep Fine alive.
So.
Let me get this straight.
You work for the CIA.
Yet you're willing to help
me sell a nuclear bomb,
in order to save this man's life.
- Why would I believe that?
- Because she's in love with him.
Yeah, so what?
This idiot doesn't even know it.
Too dump to know
I'll do anything for him.
Look.
Fuck the CIA, right.
What did they
ever done for me?
Took 10 years of my life,
give me shitty pay.
Put me in the basement
with a ceiling full of bats.
Pretty sure give me a pink eye
or at least an allergy.
Something got fuck up in my eye.
I would have mal a long time ago
if it hadn't been for Fine.
So, yeah.
I'll do anything it takes
to keep him alive.
That's pretty pathetic, right?
Extremely pathetic.
God, you're an asshole.
When this is over,
I'm gonna shave that fucking head.
Alright, Miss Hair Vision.
I'll take you up on your offer.
But if you try anything,
I mean anything.
I'll make your dream come true and
send you and your boyfriend to heaven.
Let's go.
Mr. Dudaev.
Welcome to Hungary.
Like Chechnya,
only easier to pronounce.
Enough with the bullshit.
Where is the package?
Once my client sees the payment.
She'll take us all to
it's very secure hiding spot.
Wherever that may be.
I got it, handsome.
100 million euros doesn't buy
what it used to, does it?
Nice ice, Solsa.
Right.
It's all yours.
Gentlemen.
If you would follow me.
- Here it is.
- What is this bullshit?
Bullshit?
Solsa, I'll have you know.
It's the nuke.
Clever girl.
Huh.
A lead lined compartment.
Correct. The lead lining is said
to mask any radiation detection.
My father was extremely
good at his job.
Unbelievable! You know.
You could have warned me, Rayna.
I have been throwing my gym clothes
in that uh-uh thing for a week.
It is beautiful, huh?
Yes, it is.
What the fuck are you doing?
Conducting business.
Uh-uh-uh...
Put it in the helicopter.
Don't forget my diamonds.
What the fuck is going on?
De Luca played you, Rayna.
And you lead him right to it.
You didn't expect me to
let him have it, did you?
I mean. Like giving a
strafe of areas to a hillbilly.
I have a buyer who is willing to
pay me 500 million euros for it.
And Dudaev would've never be able
to get that bomb onto American soil.
My buyer will have it in the middle
of New York city and use it next week.
So, you know.
If you haven't seen "Phantom" yet...
So what?
Does this me you're going
to kill me too, Sergio?
I'm afraid so.
Sorry Rayna. It's just cleaner
that way, you understand.
Explain it to me, De Luca!
Oh God.
He-He means well.
At this stage,
it keeps getting better and better.
Thank for the performance folks.
But. Sorry, Rayna, the show's over.
Go!
Holy shit!
- Where's De Luca?
- Susan!
Get down!
No!
I should have killed
when I had the chance.
- Rayna.
- What?
Under the car.
Push it over.
Seriously?
Can't you just fucking
burn arms and push it.
Ha-ha-ha...
Aw!
What happened?
Did I get him?
De Luke has got the bomb
to the helicopter.  Get up!
Ah, fuck me.
I got this.
No!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Kill her.
I got this.
I've done this before!
I bet you're gonna
fuck this up!
Shut up and help!
Are you kidding me?
Ford, what the hell
are you doing?
I'm gonna crawl up you
and take out De Luca.
Get your hands off my boobs!
I'm saving you!
Oh my god.
Those do not belong on those!
I can't get a good grip.
Your pants are too slippery.
Hold on tight! I'm gonna swing
like I'm on a trapeze.
And leap my way up
to the COCKPIT!
Awww!
I told you you're gonna
fuck this up, Cooper!
Oh, I split.
Woo, that's high!
Ohh!
God damn it.
Fucking new suit.
This shit ends now!
- Freeze!
- Oh my god!
I'm not in the fucking mood
for your bullshit!
Oh yeah?
Then you'll love this!
I'm not in the mood
for your bullshit!
Back off.
Sorry, spy.
Play time's over.
Yeah, it is.
Say goodbye to your toy.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Do not you dare!
Oh my god!
The stones!
No!
Oh my god!
Die.
Woo-hoo.
I just shot a man!
Is it wrong?
It felt so right.
It's so me!
Hey, heroic lady!
In my country there is a saying
about women like you.
Hot as fuck!
Oh god.
Not now, Aldo!
Go Susan!
Oh!
That was not a part of my plan!
Just like a women.
To wear jewelry into battle.
Although this is the ugliest
fucking necklace I've ever seen.
Yes, it is.
And it's all yours.
With an adjustable toggle!
Okay, here we go.
No problem.
Come on!
Okay, okay.
I got it. I got it.
Nice copter.
Where did you get it?
It's 50 Cent's.
I had to deputize him
to let us use it.
He is so afraid of me.
I'm a motherfucking spy.
Let's go shoot somebody else.
Oh, zip it up, 50 Cent
or I'll mouth you again!
This day is just getting
better and better.
He wants me!
I think we should land!
I dropped a nuke in the water.
Good job guys.
Sorry about the lake.
Alright, muscle.
Don't push.
You'll get your pictures.
There's enough 50 to go around.
You know I just help
because of terrorist, right?
You ever seen Kanye
do some shit like that.
He never.
Well.
Isn't this wonderful?
I was hoping to spend
the rest of my life in jail.
Give me some quality time
to deal with the fact
that I was sleeping with the man
who killed my father.
Anyway, call my lawyer.
Get the turf from the hotel.
- I need everything on time...
- Do you think I still work for you?
Whatever.
Fuck you.
I knew you really like me.
Hey.
Fuck you too.
Don't touch my fucking hair.
Watch it.
Oh god, Aldo.
I'm-I'm too tired to fend
you off your groping.
Please.
I understand completely.
Look.
My real name is Albert.
MI6.
Look. I'm sorry if my
disguise was a bit much.
I just like to really
get into character.
Although I fear I may have become
over excited at certain points.
- A little bit.
- By way of apology.
Should your work ever
bring you to London
I would love
to take you for dinner.
Okay. Yeah.
I...
That would be nice.
Wonderful.
God!
How do you like my
English accent? Huh?
I learned it from
the Downton Abbey.
No, I'm only joking.
- Or am I.
- My god.
Coop.
Great work.
What a job!
SuperCooper.
- Really, amazing.
- Thanks.
Yes, it was.
You really came through.
Thank you ma'am.
I like to keep you out
in the field for now.
Wow.
We need you to fly
to Prague tomorrow
to infiltrate an international
drug smuggling ring.
Here's your new identity.
You in, Cooper?
Agent, Susan Cooper.
Reporting for duty, ma'am.
Yeah. Nobody says or
does that but great.
Okay.
Thank you.
Francis Mays is an
unemployed telemarketer
living off her disability cheques.
Oh, sweet Jesus!
Any who wears reading glasses
in their passport photo?
She's only kidding.
She got you.
Oh my god.
It was a good one.
Yeah, actually I'm not.
I don't have a sense of humor.
- No, you don't.
- We'll talk soon.
Got the pink eyes under control.
But...
It was actually an allergy, ma'am.
Okay.
Got it.
So.
You're a spy now, Coop.
Yeah.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
I don't think I'll ever find anyone
as good as you in the basement.
Well.
I think you will. There's a lot
of good people down there.
So, hey.
The thing is.
I know a great little restaurant
right near here.  Maybe
you and I
could go for a nice long
dinner.
You know what.
I just
got a feeling like a
a girl's night.
- You understand, right?
- Yeah, sure.
I'll catch you later.
You go have a great time.
Thank you.
Hey.
Coop.
All those things you said
about me to De Luca.
Did you mean that?
You're a lot furrier than
I thought you'd be.
- Yeah.
Smell you later, pal.
Glad you're still alive
Beverly.
- You silly fucking girly wanker.
- Aw! God!
Nice work, Cooper.
Wow.
Is that a compliment?
That's not easy
for you to do.
Ah fuck it.
Look, you did a good job.
Probably just beginner's luck though.
Ah, there we go.
- Where did you get that suit?
- I fucking made it, didn't I.
It's nice.
You're still out of the CIA?
Probably not.
They need me.
I think I need to spend some
time on my own first, though.
Clear my head.
I'm going to take
this down the coast.
Maybe, spend some time in Italy.
Travel to Greece.
Sometimes a man
needs to go to sea.
Sounds good, Ford.
Good for you.
Take care.
Bye.
Arrivederci !
- Do you think he knows that's a lake?
- No. I don't.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I can't let anybody see
how sore I am.
- I got you.
- Okay.
- Come here.
- Oh, my glutes are really season up
If you're sore,
I'll tell you what.
Take a hot bath and then
we get to celebrate.
- I hope you like champagne and beef jerky.
- Well. Oh, that's a...
You have to.
Because I stole a case of it.
- I don't know if I like them together.
- Out of 50 Cent's helicopter.
Oh.
Slower. Slower.
Come on!
Is this a fucking lake?
How the fuck do I get to Italy?
Oh, stop screaming.
You loved it.
Oh god.
Edited by M.R. Sumon
Thanx "Freesub"