[ PROJECTOR WHIRRING ]
[ MOTOR REVVING ]
[ MOTOR STOPS ]
>> [ PANTING ]
[ DEVICE CRACKLING ]
WE GOT A SURVIVOR!
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
[ MID-TEMPO DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> SO, TELL ME ABOUT
GEORGE MARSH.
>> UM...
GEORGE MARSH IS A GREAT MINER.
HE'S ONE OF THE FINEST MEN
WORKING UNDERGROUND.
IT'S A REAL LOSS.
HOW WAS THAT?
>> THAT WAS GREAT.
>> HEY, OVER THERE, PRETTY LADY!
>> HI, MR. MUNDY.
>> OH, SAM, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> OH, GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT MY DAD?
>> OH.
IS THIS THE PART WHERE I STRIP
FOR THE CAMERA?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
NO, KEEP YOUR CLOTHES ON.
MY MOM IS GONNA SEE THIS.
>> OH, WELL, THEN, IN THAT CASE,
JUDITH, THIS IS FOR YOU.
[ HUMMING "THE STRIPPER" ]
>> OH, WAIT. I GOT A $10 BILL.
>> OH, PUT ONE RIGHT HERE, BABE.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
WHOO-OOH!
OKAY, ONE MORE TIME.
>> YOU KNOW, GEORGE, I'VE ONLY
KNOWN YOU A FEW MONTHS, BUT,
MAN, I REALLY ADMIRE YOU, AND I
HOPE I CAN MAKE IT AS LONG AS
YOU HAVE.
>> HEY, ROOKIE, I THINK IT'S A
LITTLE BIT TOO LATE --
>> MAN, BENNETT, YOU FUCKING
RUINED IT.
I HAD IT AWESOME GOOD JUST THEN.
>> RANDY BENNETT.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> AM I DONE?
>> I HEARD YOU WERE IN TOWN.
>> ALL RIGHT. I'M GONNA GO.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
>> IT'S BEEN A WHILE I GUESS,
HUH?
>> WOW.
>> YOU'VE BEEN GOOD?
>> I'M -- YEAH, I'M GREAT.
>> NICE.
>> HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> I'M GOOD, YOU KNOW.
JUST WORKING -- WORKING WITH
YOUR DAD.
>> THAT'S SO CRAZY.
>> WHY?
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S YOU AND MY
DAD.
>> YEAH, I GUESS.
NO, IT'S GOOD. HE'S A GOOD GUY.
>> YEAH.
>> SORRY TO SEE HIM GO.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> THANKS. YOU DO, TOO.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, SO...
OH, YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING TO
MY DAD?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> [ CLEARS THROAT ]
>> THERE YOU GO.
JUST LOOK INTO THE LITTLE LENS
THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT. NOW?
>> YEP.
>> GEORGE, YOU ARE A GRUMPY,
ORNERY SON OF A BITCH, BUT I
JUST WANT TO SAY THANKS FOR ALL
THE ADVICE YOU'VE GIVEN ME OVER
THE PAST COUPLE YEARS.
NOT A LOT OF GUYS WOULD HAVE
DONE THAT, AND I REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
IS THAT GOOD?
>> YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
>> SO, NEW YORK, HUH?
HOW'S THAT GOING?
>> YES. IT'S GOING.
IT GOES...REAL FAST.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DO THAT.
TOO MANY PEOPLE FOR ME.
>> YEAH, IT'S GOOD, THOUGH.
>> WHAT KIND OF, LIKE, LAW DO
YOU DO SPECIFICALLY?
>> OH, YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
TRUST ME.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE I DO.
WHAT KIND IS IT?
>> WELL, IT'S ENVIRONMENTAL LAW.
>> ARE YOU SHITTING ME?
>> YEAH. YEAH, I KNOW.
>> DOES YOUR DAD KNOW?
>> OF COURSE HE DOES.
[ MICROPHONE FEEDBACK ]
>> WHOO!
>> CHECK.
>> WHO ORDERED THE STRIPPER?!
>> CHECK, CHECK, CHECK.
CALM DOWN. QUIET DOWN.
GEORGE, WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> HE'S NOT HERE.
>> OH, RIGHT. I HEAR YOU.
I'LL MAKE THIS QUICK.
LOOK.
I JUST WANT EVERYBODY TO KNOW
THAT A GOOD MAN IS LEAVING THIS
OUTFIT, A GREAT MAN, AND WHILE
WE'RE SAD TO SEE THAT YOU'RE
MOVING ON A LITTLE SOONER THAN
WE THOUGHT YOU'D BE, WELL, WE'RE
BLESSED TO HAVE KNOWN YOU FOR
WELL, WHAT?
SINCE BRACKETT OPENED THE MINE
BACK IN '81, MAN?
THAT'S OVER 30 YEARS.
>> DAMN, THAT'S A LONG TIME.
>> TO GEORGE MARSH.
WE LOVE YOU.
TOMORROW'S YOUR LAST DAY, SO
LET'S MAKE TONIGHT COUNT.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> [ COUGHS ]
>> HAS HE BEEN BACK TO THAT
DOCTOR?
>> HE WON'T GO.
[ COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> HEY, COME ON.
>> STAND BACK.
>>  WON'T YOU BE MINE?
HEY, NOW, MISS FANNY
HEY, NOW
WON'T YOU PLEASE BE MINE?
HEY, MISS FANNY,
PLEASE, WON'T YOU BE MINE?
>> SO, I WENT TO THE STORE, GOT
SOME EX-LAX, AND PUT IT IN THE
BROWNIE.
>> OH!
>> AND I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
MIDSHIFT, I KNEW EXACTLY WHO WAS
STEALING MY BROWNIES EVERY DAY.
>> YOU'RE A SHIT DETECTIVE.
>> TORRES!
>> AH!
>> MORE SHOTS.
>> GO AND GET HER ONE.
THANKS.
>> HE'S A LAZY SON OF A BITCH.
>> UH-OH.
>> KEEP IT DOWN!
KEEP IT DOWN!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> OKAY, TO FINISH MY POINT, AND
THEN I'M DONE -- I WASN'T SAYING
IT'S Y'ALL'S FAULT, OKAY?
IT IS CORPORATE GREED.
IT'S UNSAFE.
IT'S UNCLEAN ON EVERY LEVEL.
>> NO DISRESPECT, BUT IT'S
BULLSHIT.
NO, NO, NO.
I'M NOT TRYING TO MAKE YOU FEEL
BAD.
IT'S JUST REGULAR PEOPLE, THEY
DON'T CARE WHERE THE POWER COMES
FROM.
THEY JUST CARE IF SOME FUCKING
BIRD GOES EXTINCT.
>> [ Chuckling ] YOU TELL THEM.
>> HAVE THEM WORK UNDERGROUND
FOR A DAY.
>> YEAH.
>> I KNOW IT'S HARD WORK.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> I BROKE A NAIL!
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> I CAN'T GET ON MY FACEBOOK.
>> I SEE WHERE THIS IS GOING,
ALL YOU MEN WITH YOUR MOANING
AND GROANING AND CHEST-THUMPING.
>> I'D LIKE TO MAKE A TOAST!
TO THE UNCLEAN INDUSTRY THAT
PAID FOR YOUR LAW SCHOOL.
>> AH!
>> HEAR, HEAR!
>> FINE.
I'LL GO WITH Y'ALL TOMORROW.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT?
I'M SERIOUS!
NO, I WILL GO INTO THAT MINE,
I'LL SHOVEL THAT COAL, AND I'LL
GET TWO CUTS ALL ON MY OWN.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S NOT GET
CARRIED AWAY HERE.
>> COME ON, GEORGE.
YOU AFRAID YOUR LITTLE GIRL'S
GONNA SHOW YOU UP?
>> OH, YOU KNOW, WE COULD
REPLACE ONE MARSH FOR ANOTHER.
WE WOULDN'T HAVE TO CHANGE THE
NAME ON THE HELMET.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, MUNDY?
>> OH, I'D SAY THAT'S GEORGE'S
CALL.
>> HELL, NO, MUNDY.
MINE AIN'T NO PLACE FOR A WOMAN.
>> WELL, I THINK IT'D BE ALL
RIGHT IF MY LITTLE GIRL CAME
DOWN THERE FOR A COUPLE HOURS,
CHECKED OUT WHAT HER OLD MAN'S
BEEN DOING FOR 35 YEARS.
I THINK THAT'D BE JUST FINE.
I CAN'T BE LOOKING AFTER YOU.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THAT.
>> I'LL KEEP AN EYE ON HER,
GEORGE.
>> ALL RIGHT. IT'S DONE.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> I'M GOING!
>> WHOO!
>> I CAN DO IT!
>> LOOK AT THEM GUNS!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT FOR ME.
I GOT TO GET SOME SLEEP.
>> OH!
>> COME ON!
>> DAD!
IT'S YOUR PARTY!
>> I'M AN OLD MAN!
>> MUNDY'S AN OLD MAN!
>> YEAH. I TOOK A NAP.
[ ALL LAUGH ]
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU, GEORGE.
>> THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
LITTLE GIRL?
THAT'S YOUR LAST DRINK.
IT'S AN EARLY MORNING.
>> OOH!
>> 'NIGHT, YOU ALL.
>> 'NIGHT, GEORGE!
>> All: GEORGE!
[ ALARM RINGING ]
>> [ GROANS ]
I REMEMBER YOU GETTING UP EARLY,
BUT THIS IS EARLY.
>> YEAH.
GOT YOURSELF A LITTLE HEADACHE
THERE, DO YOU?
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE REALLY GONNA DO THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
>> IT'S THE LAST CHANCE TO SEE
YOU IN ACTION.
>> HMM.
ALL RIGHT.
WRITE A NOTE FOR YOUR MOTHER.
>> DAD, IT'S ONE DAY.
>> LITTLE GIRL, IF YOU'RE GONNA
DO THIS, YOU'RE GONNA DO IT
RIGHT.
NOW, LEAVE A NOTE FOR YOUR
MOTHER.
>> IN 35 YEARS, YOU NEVER MISSED
ONE DAY?
NOT ONE?
>> NOT ONCE.
WRITE SOMETHING.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU WRITE A POEM
OR JUST ONE WORD.
WRITE SOMETHING.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU IN THE TRUCK.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ MAN TALKING ON RADIO ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
>> MORNING, WILLIAM.
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
THE COAL MINER'S DAUGHTER.
YOU ACTUALLY SHOWED UP, HUH?
>> I THINK I'M STILL DRUNK.
>> OH, THEN, YOU'LL FIT RIGHT
IN.
>> YOU SERIOUSLY DIDN'T THINK I
WAS COMING?
>> NO.
ACTUALLY, SOME OF THE GUYS HAVE
A BET.
LOOKS LIKE I LOST.
>> RANDY, TAKE SAM TO THE
OFFICE.
>> YES, SIR.
>> [ SIGHS ]
YOU REALLY GONNA MISS THAT
SUNSHINE EVERY MORNING?
>> OH, IT'S JUST HOW HE IS.
>> YEAH.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW,
MAN.
IT IS BAD LUCK TO HAVE HER GO
DOWN THERE.
>> WHAT THE HELL YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
SHUT UP.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DIDN'T
SPEAK UP LAST NIGHT WHEN I SAID
IT.
>> I DID!
>> SEE HOW PRETTY MY FACE IS?
MAN, I LOOK PRETTY RIGHT HERE.
>> MASEK, YOU GET CROWDED FROM
THAT THREESOME LAST NIGHT?
>> OH, YOU KNOW IT, BOY.
>> I DON'T MIND SLOPPY SECONDS
IF YOU WANT TO PASS ONE OF THEM
MY WAY.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU REMEMBER WHAT I TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE BREATHING APPARATUS,
RIGHT?
>> YES.
FIRST SIGN OF TROUBLE, POP THE
SEAL, TAKE THE UNIT OUT,
MOUTHPIECE IN, NOSECLIPS UP,
AND...
>> Both: BREATHE NORMALLY.
>> YEAH.
ANYTHING GOES WRONG DOWN THERE,
YOU GET HER OUT.
THE FANS SHUT DOWN, POWER GOES
OUT, YOU GET HER OUT.
>> I GOT IT. IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> YOU READY?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I'LL SEE YOU OUT THERE,
THEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> COME ON, FELLAS.
STEP IT UP.
>> I HEARD A LITTLE RUMOR ABOUT
YOU AND SHEILA BAXTER.
>> YOU CHECKING UP ON ME?
>> NO.
MY MOM LIKES TO KEEP ME
INFORMED.
>> OH, IS YOUR MOM CHECKING UP
ON ME?
>> YOU MIGHT HAVE BEEN HER
FAVORITE.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE TO BACK
OUT.
>> IT'S JUST A COUPLE HOURS.
>> JUST SAYING.
I'VE SEEN EVEN A LOT OF TOUGH
GUYS LOSE IT DOWN THERE.
SAM?
>> HUH.
>> YOU AFRAID?
>> NO.
>> HOLD UP.
LET ME CHECK THIS.
YOU GOT YOUR BREATHER?
>> YEP.
>> IS IT SNUG?
>> YEAH.
>> COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
SAY GOODBYE TO THE DAYLIGHT.
>> WHAT DO THEY WANT?
THEY WANT A FEW THINGS TO MAKE
YOU SMILE.
>> MORNING.
>> OH, WELL, HERE WE GO.
SAM, YOU KNOW MOST OF THESE
JOKERS FROM LAST NIGHT.
GENTLEMEN, WE GOT A LADY WITH
US.
LET'S BE NICE TODAY.
>> OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S "TAKE YOUR DAUGHTER TO
WORK" DAY.
>> SHUT UP.
>> ALL RIGHT, SAM, GET
COMFORTABLE.
IT'S A LONG RIDE TO THE BOTTOM.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> CAREFUL.
>> WELCOME TO WORK, Y'ALL.
[ HORN HONKS ]
>> MOVE YOUR ASS.
>> QUIT IT, MASEK.
>> GET OUT OF THE WAY, SIR.
>> HERE BOY. GOING TO SHOVEL.
>> ALL RIGHT, SAM.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE GRAND TOUR.
THIS IS WHERE WE GET FRESH AIR.
FANS SUCK OXYGEN IN FROM
OUTSIDE, AND THE METHANE GETS
PUMPED OUT.
[ WHIRRING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
>> WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
>> OH, WELL -- WELL, THAT'S JUST
THE WEIGHT OF THE MOUNTAIN
PRESSING DOWN AROUND US.
BUT YOU GET USED TO IT.
AND OVER HERE IS WHERE WE DIG
OUT THE COAL.
AND THE ONLY THING HOLDING UP
THE ROOF IS THESE PILLARS OF
COAL RIGHT HERE.
HMM.
NO WONDER PEOPLE THINK WE'RE
NUTS.
>> WELL, HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN
YOU DIG THEM TOO THIN?
>> OH, WELL, WE GOT ENGINEERS UP
TOP FOR THAT.
THEY TELL US WHAT'S SAFE,
STRUCTURALLY SOUND, ALL THAT.
YOU KNOW, IF RANDY DOESN'T FLUNK
OUT OF NIGHT SCHOOL, WE ALL
MIGHT BE ASKING HIM IN A FEW
YEARS.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SAVE YOUR LIGHT.
>> AND THIS?
THIS IS THE DINNER HOLE.
NOW, IF ANYTHING GOES WRONG DOWN
HERE, THE FIRST THING WE DO IS
WE GET OUT OF THE MINE, BUT IF
THE SHIT REALLY HITS THE FAN, WE
PARK OUR ASSES IN THIS LUXURY
CONDO HERE UNTIL SOMEONE CAN DIG
US OUT.
[ MUFFLED CONVERSATION ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
COME ON, RED HAT.
KEEP UP.
[ HORN BLARES ]
>> WELCOME TO THE FACE!
NOW, THIS IS THE CONTINUOUS
MINER.
THAT STEEL DRUM THERE IS FITTED
WITH OVER A HUNDRED TUNGSTEN
CARBIDE TEETH.
IT'S PULLED OUT OF THE MOUNTAIN.
THEN, WE SHOVEL IT ON TO
CONVEYOR BELTS, AND UP AND OUT
IT GOES.
IT'S JUST AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
WELL, THAT'S THE END OF THE
TOUR.
READY TO GO TO WORK?
>> SURE.
>> WELL, GOOD. I GOT SHIT TO DO.
RANDY, SET HER UP.
>> COME ON.
I GOT A SHOVEL WITH YOUR NAME ON
IT.
>> KEEP IT UP, FELLAS!
>> SO, JUST GET A REAL GOOD
SCOOP AND THEN LIFT WITH YOUR
LEGS ONTO THE BELT.
>> [ GROANS ]
HOW'S THAT?
>> JESUS, THAT'S TERRIBLE.
THE CONCEPT IS TO GET IT OFF THE
GROUND AND ONTO THE BELT.
>> [ GROANS ]
I GOT SKINNY ARMS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ Straining ] OKAY.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU, ON YOUR LUNCH
BREAK?
>> AH, COME ON.
>> SHIT.
>> What the hell's going on down
there?!
>> NOTHING.
JUST HIT A ROUGH PATCH.
>> Well, be careful!
Don't break another bit on me.
>> OH, MY RADIO'S BREAKING UP.
I CAN'T HEAR YOU, MUNDY.
OH!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
IT'S COOL, MAN. KEEP GOING.
I NEED MY QUOTA.
>> I'M GOING.
[ HORN BLARES ]
[ MACHINE WHIRRING ]
OH! WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
>> SHUT IT DOWN! SHUT IT DOWN!
>> GOD DAMN, MAN.
OH, MAN.
>> YOU BROKE SOMETHING.
>> I DIDN'T BREAK NOTHING.
>> YOU BROKE A HOLE IN THERE.
>> OH, AIN'T THAT SOME SHIT?
[ COUGHS ]
YOU SEEING THAT?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
OH, SHIT!
>> YEAH.
>> YOU REALLY DONE IT THIS TIME.
>> OH, I DID IT.
>> YOU BROKE THE MOUNTAIN.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> I DIDN'T BREAK THE MOUNTAIN,
MAN.
SHUT UP.
LOOK HOW DEEP THAT SHIT IS.
>> WHOA!
>> WHAT IS THAT?
[ RUMBLING ]
>> OH!
>> AAH!
GET DOWN!
>> GET DOWN!
>> RANDY!
[ FAN STOPS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ MEN YELLING IN DISTANCE ]
DAD?
DAD?!
[ SIREN BLARING ]
>> SAM?
>> RANDY?!
D-DAD?!
RANDY?!
[ CRYING ]
>> SAM?!
>> RANDY?
>> RANDY.
>> BREATHE.
[ MAN GROANING IN DISTANCE ]
SAM, HELP ME!
>> GET THIS OFF ME!
OW!
>> SAM!
>> JESUS.
>> OH, GOD.
>> [ GROANS ]
OH, GOD!
>> HERE! HERE!
>> HELP ME OUT OF HERE, GUYS!
SOMEBODY!
OH, GOD!
>> PULL IT OUT!
PULL IT OUT!
OH, JESUS!
>> COME ON. WE GOT TO GO.
>> GET HIM UP.
LIFT HIM UP! LIFT HIM UP!
WATCH HIS LEG!
>> [ GROANING ]
AH-HA-HA-HA-HA!
>> LOOK AT ME. LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT ME.
I KNOW IT HURTS.
I KNOW IT HURTS, BUT WE'RE GONNA
GET YOU OUT OF HERE.
>> WE GOT TO GO.
>> OH, GOD.
>> GET HIM OUT.
>> AAAHHHH! IT HURTS!
>> COME ON.
>> DAD?!
>> OW, OW, OW, OW!
>> COME ON. KEEP IT GOING.
>> I KNOW IT HURTS.
>> GOD, IT HURTS!
>> SETTLE DOWN!
>> AAH-OW!
>> COME ON NOW.
SET HIM OVER THERE.
>> I CAN'T MAKE IT.
AAH!
>> SAM?!
>> DAD?!
>> DAD! DAD!
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU GUYS ALL RIGHT?
>> HOW BAD IS IT, RANDY?
>> I'M CHECKING.
COME ON. GET OUT OF HERE.
>> I GOT HIM. I GOT HIM.
>> EASY, EASY, EASY.
EASY NOW.
>> GODDAMN IT!
IT'S BAD, GEORGE.
>> I GOT YOU.
>> I TOLD THEM THIS COULD
HAPPEN.
>> WHAT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, RANDY?
>> IT MEANS WE'RE FUCKED, HONEY!
I TOLD YOU ALL IT WAS BAD LUCK.
I TOLD YOU!
>> STRODE!
LEAVE HER ALONE, GODDAMN IT!
HEY, HEY, HEY.
BACK UP. BACK UP.
BACK UP.
>> WHAT?!
>> LUCK HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
IT.
>> [ COUGHING ]
>> OH, JESUS.
>> [ GROANS ]
[ SIRENS BLARING IN DISTANCE ]
>> I'M TELLING YOU, JACK, IT
HAPPENED IN A MATTER OF SECONDS.
THERE'S THREE DEAD, ANOTHER FIVE
OR SIX MISSING.
[ PANTING ]
MUNDY'S BANGED UP PRETTY BAD.
HIS LEG...
>> MUNDY, MUNDY, I'VE GOT TO SET
IT IF YOU WANT ME TO BANDAGE IT.
>> JACK, I JUST NEED AN
ESTIMATE.
>> WHAT?
>> I SAID I'VE GOT TO SET IT.
IF I DON'T SET IT, IT'S GONNA
GET INFECTED.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO SET A
LEG.
YOU WANT HIM TO LOSE THE DAMN
THING?
>> LOOK. YOU WANT HIM TO DIE?
>> NO, GOD!
>> I WAS JUST KIDDING, MUNDY.
YOU AIN'T GONNA DIE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW HOLD HIM NOW.
YOU READY, MUNDY?
>> OH, NO, NO.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
>> LISTEN TO ME.
LOOK AT ME. LOOK AT ME.
IF I DON'T SET IT, I CAN'T
BANDAGE IT, ALL RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN MAKE IT
QUICK, DAMN IT!
>> GRUBBS, HOLD HIS ARM.
>> OH, GOD!
>> GRUBBS?
I SAID, SNAP OUT OF IT, BOY!
HOLD HIS ARM, GRUBBS!
GODDAMN IT!
ALL RIGHT, STRODE, YOU READY?
ON "THREE."
ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
>> AAH-AAH! OH, MY GOD!
>> [ VOMITS ]
>> AAHHH!
OH, GOD!
[ BONE SNAPS ]
>> OH, THERE WE GO.
>> OH, GOD!
>> LOOK AT ME.
I GOT YOU, ALL RIGHT?
WE'LL GET YOU OUT.
>> [ PANTING ]
>> YOU ALL RIGHT THERE, ROOK?
>> NO.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, DRINK SOME
WATER.
MAKE SURE AND STAY HYDRATED.
>> WE'RE GONNA BE OKAY, RIGHT?
TH-THEY KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING?
>> YEAH.
THEY GOT PROCEDURES FOR THIS
KIND OF THING.
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> SO, THIS HAS HAPPENED BEFORE?
>> NO, NOT TO ME.
>> YOU KNOW SOMEONE THAT IT'S
HAPPENED TO.
>> WHO WE MISSING?
>> RIGHT?
I SAID, WHO WE MISSING?!
>> YEAH, WE CAN GET IN THERE.
>> WHEELER, TASS.
>> AUGIE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN AUGIE.
>> WHAT ABOUT VAN HORN?
TORRES?
ANYBODY SEEN THEM?
>> NO.
>> NO?
THOSE GUYS WERE WORKING THE
MINER, RIGHT?
FARTHEST FROM THE COLLAPSE.
>> YEAH, THEY WERE ON THE MINER.
>> YEAH, SO?
>> YEAH, SO, WELL, IF THEY
DIDN'T GET COVERED UP, WHERE THE
HELL ARE THEY?
>> YEAH, I UNDERSTAND, JACK.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
[ COUGHS ]
>> WHAT'D THEY SAY, GEORGE?
>> IT'S GONNA TAKE THEM 72 HOURS
TO GET TO US.
>> WHAT?
>> Oh, shit!
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE WE GONNA
DO?
>> WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
NO NEED TO PANIC.
RESCUE CHAMBER -- GOT PLENTY OF
OXYGEN, PLENTY OF SUPPLIES,
ENOUGH TO LAST US FOR FIVE, SIX
DAYS.
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO WAY.
NO WAY!
HA!
WHAT ABOUT THE MINER, HUH?
FIRE THAT THING UP.
DIG OUR WAY OUT.
>> DIG OUR WAY OUT.
>> NO, YOU DIG INTO THAT RUBBLE,
THE WHOLE ROOF WILL COME DOWN ON
TOP OF US.
>> WE'RE GONNA LOCK OURSELVES IN
THAT THING?
>> NO, FUCK THAT.
I SAY WE RUN THE MINER, GEORGE.
>> THE COLLAPSE HAPPENED THIS
SIDE OF THE VENTILATION FAN.
WE ALL KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
>> I'M NOT WAITING FOR THEM!
>> WE AIN'T GETTING NO MORE
FRESH AIR COMING IN.
AND THE AIR WE GOT AIN'T GONNA
BE BREATHABLE.
WITH THE METHANE AND CO2 LEAKING
IN, WE GOT TO GET OUR ASSES IN
THE RESCUE CHAMBER.
>> LET ME RUN IT, GEORGE.
>> IT'S OUR ONLY OPTION.
COME ON, SAM, RANDY.
AND GET MUNDY AND GET HIM ON IN
HERE.
LET'S GET SETTLED IN.
72 HOURS -- THEY'LL GET TO US.
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
>> ALL RIGHT. I GOT YOU.
[ FAN WHIRRING ]
>> [ GROANS ]
>> WE GOT FOOD AND WATER.
AIN'T NOTHING FANCY, BUT IT'S
OUR HOME FOR THE NEXT THREE
DAYS.
[ MUNDY COUGHING ]
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
>> I WAS SUPPOSED TO E-MAIL MY
BOSS A BRIEF TONIGHT.
SHE'S GONNA BE PISSED.
>> I'M SURE SHE'LL UNDERSTAND.
[ MAN PACING ]
MASEK, MAN, SIT DOWN.
>> [ UNZIPS ]
EXCUSE ME.
[ AIR HISSING ]
[ BLOOD SQUISHING ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY GET SOME
SLEEP.
[ GEORGE COUGHING ]
HERE YOU GO.
>> THANK YOU.
[ COUGHING CONTINUES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> SHH!
[ CLATTERING IN DISTANCE ]
>> What is that?
>> DON'T KNOW. JUST STARTED.
[ CLATTERING CONTINUES ]
>> A RESCUE TEAM?
>> THAT CAN'T BE. IT'S TOO SOON.
>> WELL, I HEARD SOMEBODY.
>> YOU DIDN'T LEAVE ANYBODY OUT
THERE, DID YOU?
>> NO, NO, WE LOOKED EVERYWHERE.
EVERYONE WE SAW WAS DEAD.
>> COULD BE MORE RUBBLE...
THE ROOF SETTLING.
[ MAN SCREAMS IN DISTANCE ]
>> YOU HEAR THAT?
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
>> STAY INSIDE.
KEEP THE DOOR SHUT.
[ BEEPING STOPS ]
>> I DON'T HEAR IT ANYMORE.
>> SHH!
I HEARD SOMETHING.
>> MAN, WE DON'T KNOW WHAT WE
HEARD.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN A BIRD
TRAPPED IN THE VENTS.
>> THAT AIN'T A FUCKING BIRD!
THAT'S ONE OF OUR BOYS TRAPPED
OUT THERE.
>> IF THERE'S SOMEBODY OUT
THERE, WE GOT TO GO FIND HIM.
>> I SAY WE WAIT FOR THE RESCUE
TEAM.
EVEN IF THE GUYS ARE COVERED, WE
GOT NO GEAR TO PULL THEM OUT.
>> RESCUE TEAM?
THEY AIN'T COMING FOR ANOTHER
TWO DAYS, IF THEY'RE COMING AT
ALL.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE IT IF I LEFT
YOUR LITTLE, SORRY ASS OUT THERE
WITH NO AIR, HUH, YOU LITTLE
CHICKENSHIT?
>> EASY, MASEK.
>> I GOT KIDS, MAN.
I AIN'T GONNA RISK MY LIFE FOR
SOMETHING I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
IT IS.
>> AND HE DON'T?
>> MAN, THAT'S ONE OF OUR GUYS
OUT THERE.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> WHAT, YOU BEEN UNDERGROUND
ALL OF SIX MONTHS, AND YOU THINK
YOU'RE A FUCKING EXPERT?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, STRODE?
FUCK YOU, MAN!
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY!
COME ON.
>> KNOCK IT OFF, GODDAMN IT!
>> GET READY. WE'RE GOING OUT.
[ ALARM BLARES ]
>> COME ON.
[ BEEPING ]
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
LITTLE CHICKENSHIT.
>> WHAT WAS IT?
[ BEEPING STOPS ]
>> RANDY GOES WITH ME.
WE'LL TAKE ENTRY "A."
MASEK, YOU AND THE BOYS TAKE
"H."
WE'LL WORK OUR WAY BACK HERE.
I WANT YOU ALL TO BE THOROUGH,
BUT DON'T BE STUPID.
STICK TOGETHER AND KEEP THOSE
RADIOS ON.
>> HOW MANY OF THEM BREATHERS
WE GOT LEFT?
>> WE GOT A FEW.
>> AIR'S STILL GOOD.
WE BETTER NOT USE THEM TILL WE
REALLY NEED THEM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M GOING WITH YOU.
>> HELL, NO, GEORGE.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
>> YOU STAY AND TAKE CARE OF
BOB.
>> WELL, BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
WE ALL GOT FAMILY TO GET BACK
TO.
>> YOU GOT THAT RIGHT, BOSS.
HERE WE GO.
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
[ BEEPING STOPS ]
>> THEY'LL BE FINE.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> YO, VAN HORN?!
WHEELER?
[ MAN SPEAKING OVER
WALKIE-TALKIE ]
>> Copy. Out.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I THINK IT NEEDS TO BE
ELEVATED.
>> OKAY.
LET ME SEE.
OKAY.
UM...
ALL RIGHT.
UH...
IT'S ON THE COUNT OF THREE.
>> OKAY.
>> ONE...
TWO...
>> [ INHALES, GROANS ]
>> THREE.
>> AAH!
>> IS THAT OKAY?
>> [ GROANS ]
[ BOTH YELL ]
>> [ GASPS ]
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ PANTING ]
OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY.
[ PANTING ]
>> VAN HORN?!
TORRES?!
>> [ PANTING ]
>> VAN HORN?
>> THIS IS BULLSHIT!
TORRES?
>> I'M TIRED OF YOU CRYING,
STRODE.
IF YOU'RE SO GODDAMN SCARED,
THEN WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK WITH
MUNDY DOWN TO RESCUE, ALL RIGHT?
>> COME ON.
>> VAN HORN?
>> COME ON, MEN!
[ CRACKLING ]
>> YOU HEAR THAT?
>> YEAH.
[ CRACKLING CONTINUES ]
IS THAT YOU GUYS COMING DOWN
ENTRY "A"?
>> No, boss.
>> WHO'S THERE?
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> IT'S SAM.
>> FUCK.
SHIT.
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
I TOLD YOU STAY IN THE CHAMBER.
>> [ PANTING ]
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> NO. UM, I SAW SOMETHING.
>> GO ON BACK.
IT AIN'T SAFE HERE.
>> YOU WANT ME TO WALK BACK ON
MY OWN?
>> WE'RE ALMOST AT THE END,
ANYWAY.
>> STAY CLOSE.
>> Okay.
>> TAKE THE LIGHT.
>> WE'RE HEADED TO THE FACE
RIGHT NOW.
>> Copy that. Be careful.
>> YO, COME ON. LET'S GO.
>> HELLO?
[ GASPS ]
>> SAM?
>> JESUS.
>> WHOA, WHOA, SAM.
>> [ PANTING ]
>> GODDAMN IT, SAM!
I TOLD YOU, STAY CLOSE!
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> CONTINUOUS MINER'S STILL ALL
RIGHT.
>> NOT A SCRATCH.
>> SO, WHERE ARE VAN HORN AND
TORRES?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HEY, LOOK.
LOOKED LIKE THEY BROKE THROUGH
TO SOMETHING.
>> YOU THINK MAYBE THEY WENT IN
THERE?
GOT STUCK?
>> MAYBE.
COME ON. LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> FUCK THAT.
I'M NOT GOING IN THERE.
>> HEY, THEY COULD BE TRAPPED.
>> THEN, YOU GO.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
HEH.
>> FUCK HIM. I'LL GO.
[ COUGHS ]
>> WE'RE AT THE END OF "A."
AIN'T NO SIGN OF NOBODY.
WE'LL HEAD BACK TO THE CHAMBER.
[ SIGHS ]
MASEK?
>> WHERE THE FUCK IS HE?
Masek?!
Hey, Masek?!
[ HORN BLARES ]
>> OH, SHIT. LET'S GO.
GO, GO, GO!
>> RANDY, WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
>> [ PANTING ]
[ GEORGE COUGHING ]
>> RANDY?
[ BLARING CONTINUES ]
[ ALL YELLING ]
>> GET DOWN! GET DOWN!
>> AAH! AAH!
AAH!
>> OH, GOD.
>> HUSH UP.
>> WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED HERE?
MASEK?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
GEORGE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, YOU DON'T
KNOW?
>> I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
>> WHERE'S GRUBBS?
>> GRUBBS? HE'S GONE.
HE'S SPOOKED.
>> YOU DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING?
WHO TURNED THIS GODDAMN MACHINE
ON?
>> NO ONE TURNED IT ON!
THERE WAS A GODDAMN CRACK IN THE
FACE.
IT LOOKED LIKE VAN HORN AND
TORRES MAYBE DUCKED IN THERE
WHEN THE CEILING FELL.
I TOLD THEM TO SIT TIGHT.
I WAS ONLY 50 FEET IN WHEN I
HEARD THE --
>> GODDAMN IT!
I TOLD YOU ALL TO STICK
TOGETHER?!
DIDN'T I TELL YOU THAT?!
>> I WAS ONLY GONE FIVE MINUTES!
WHEN I LOOKED, THERE WAS NO SIGN
OF TROUBLE.
>> BUT WE SEARCHED THAT --
>> SO, WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO
SAY?!
DON'T YOU GET IN MY FACE!
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
HEY, COME ON NOW. EASY, EASY.
>> [ COUGHS ]
>> WHAT, NOW YOU GOT YOUR
DAUGHTER AND HER BOYFRIEND HERE
TO PROTECT YOU?
>> What's going on down there?
>> BOB? YEAH.
WE GOT SOME...WE GOT SOME REAL
TROUBLE HERE.
>> WHAT THE HELL'S HAPPENING,
RANDY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
AIR'S GETTING REAL BAD.
THESE GUYS MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN
CONFUSED.
TURNED ON THE MINER.
>> I'M TALKING ABOUT EVERYONE.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN MY DAD ACT
LIKE THAT.
>> Jesus Christ.
[ MAN WAILING IN DISTANCE ]
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> THAT SOUNDS LIKE GRUBBS.
>> WHAT, THROUGH THERE?
>> YEAH, THERE'S ANOTHER TUNNEL
BACK THERE.
GRUBBS?!
>> WHAT DID YOU SEE IN THERE?
>> I BARELY GOT TO THE OTHER
SIDE BEFORE I HEARD THE
SCREAMING.
>> COME ON.
>> COULD BE A WAY OUT.
>> [ PANTING ]
Oh, God.
OH, SHI--
Shit!
NO.
SHIT! OH, GOD!
>> SAM, WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I CAN'T MOVE.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY.
>> I'M STUCK. OH, GOD.
>> ALL RIGHT. CALM DOWN.
>> SAM, STOP MOVING.
STOP MOVING.
SAM, YOU HAVE TO STOP.
>> [ PANTING ]
>> LOOK AT ME. LOOK AT ME.
Shh! IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE A DEEP
BREATH...
>> OKAY.
>> ...AND PULL, ALL RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT, ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
>> OH, GOD!
OH, GOD.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
COME ON.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
ALMOST THERE.
COME ON.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
[ RUMBLING IN DISTANCE ]
[ METAL CLATTERING ]
>> GRUBBS?
>> HOLY SHIT.
>> PART OF OUR OLD MINING
OPERATION.
PROBABLY FROM THE '20s.
>> DON'T.
THE STUFF'S NEARLY A HUNDRED
YEARS OLD.
YOU COULD SET IT OFF JUST BY
BREATHING ON IT.
>> RIGHT.
AND THANKS FOR THE TIP.
>> LOOK AT THIS.
>> JESUS, THAT'S ONE OF THE 19.
>> NO.
>> YEAH!
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> CARNAHAN.
I REMEMBER THE NAMES ON A PLAQUE
HANGING IN MY OLD HIGH SCHOOL.
>> WHAT'S THE 19?
>> BACK IN '27, 19 WERE COVERED
UP, AND BACK THEN, ALL THEY HAD
WERE MULES AND PICKAXES TO DIG
THEM OUT.
>> SO, THEY JUST LEFT THEM DOWN
HERE?
>> WELL, THAT'S THE WAY IT WAS.
THEY NEVER DID FIND THE REMAINS.
>> THE STORY GOES THAT THEY ALL
WENT CRAZY DOWN HERE.
ENDED UP KILLING EACH OTHER.
>> WELL, THAT'S STUPID.
HOW IN THE HELL WOULD THEY KNOW
THAT IF THEY NEVER FOUND THEM?
>> IT'S JUST STORIES, MASEK.
>> COME ON. WE'RE WASTING TIME.
LET'S FIND GRUBBS.
HEY, GRUBBS?!
>> YO, ROOKIE?
>> GRUBBS?!
GRUBBS?!
>> YO, ROOKIE?
[ MUNDY TALKING
OVER WALKIE-TALKIE ]
>> HOLD ON, MASEK!
WE'RE HERE.
>> Outside the chamber right
now?
>> NO, WE FOUND AN OLD TUNNEL
OFF ENTRY "H."
>> Then, who's outside right
now?
>> OUTSIDE WHERE?
>> Someone is outside the rescue
chamber banging to get in!
>> WE'RE ON OUR WAY BACK.
>> GRUBBS?!
>> BOBBY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
>> SOMEBODY WAS OUT THERE.
>> WHO?
>> SOMEBODY WAS JUST OUT THERE.
YOU DIDN'T SEE SOMEBODY COMING
IN HERE?
>> WHO WAS IT? VAN HORN? TORRES?
>> WE DIDN'T SEE ANYBODY.
>> SOMEBODY WAS BANGING ON THE
SIDES HERE.
>> AIN'T NOBODY OUT THERE.
>> WHO'D THEY SOUND LIKE?
>> WHY YOU WASTING OUR TIME?!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO IT WAS, BUT
YOU HAD TO SEE THEM.
>> WE GOT BOYS DOWN THERE!
WHY YOU WASTING OUR TIME,
MUNDY?!
>> WE DIDN'T SEE ANYBODY, ALL
RIGHT?
>> THERE'S NOBODY OUTSIDE.
>> YOU SIT DOWN AND CALM DOWN
RIGHT NOW!
NOW LISTEN. I'M NOT LYING!
>> I KNOW YOU'RE NOT.
>> STRODE IS DEAD.
GRUBBS IS MISSING.
WHEELER, TOO.
SO IS VAN HORN AND TORRES,
ALL RIGHT?
>> THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
THIS RIGHT NOW.
THAT WAS NOT THEM.
I HOLLERED.
THEY DIDN'T ANSWER.
>> YOU DONE LOST YOUR MIND,
MUNDY.
>> [ COUGHS ]
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
PLEASE.
PLEASE STOP RIGHT THERE.
COME ON. I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
>> WORRIED ABOUT ME?
GOD DAMN.
YOU NEVER DID BEFORE.
WHY THE HELL WOULD YOU START
NOW?
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
I WORKED MY ASS OFF ALL THESE
YEARS TO GIVE YOU A GOOD LIFE,
AND WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU JUST...YOU JUST GO.
DON'T THINK THAT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU AND YOUR MOTHER ARE
DOING.
GANGING UP ON ME.
THAT'S WHY YOU TOOK THAT
BULLSHIT JOB.
GET ME RETIRED.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
>> JESUS, DAD.
I DID IT 'CAUSE I CARE ABOUT
YOU.
>> I DON'T NEED YOU TO CARE
ABOUT ME!
NOW GET!
>> THIS JOB IS KILLING YOU!
>> THIS GODDAMN JOB IS THE ONLY
THING I GOT LEFT, AND YOU JUST
TOOK IT AWAY FROM ME!
GODDAMN YOU TO HELL, WOMAN!
>> [ Voice breaking ] FINE.
JUST...
STAY OUT HERE AND DIE, FOR ALL I
CARE.
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
[ DOOR CLOSES, BEEPING STOPS ]
>> WELL, HOW DOES THAT MAKE ANY
SENSE?
WE'VE BEEN MINING BOTH SIDES OF
THAT SEAM FOR MONTHS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
JUST SEEMED LIKE IT KEPT GOING.
>> WELL, IT HAD TO HAVE AN ENTRY
SOMEWHERE.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOUR MAP, GEORGE?
>> NO, THEY WERE TRAPPED.
THEY'D HAVE FOUND A WAY OUT.
>> WHAT ABOUT THOSE ENTRIES WE
DUG BACK IN '83?
>> THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
MOUNTAIN?
>> YEAH.
IF THE TUNNEL YOU FOUND GOES
BACK AS FAR AS YOU SAY IT DID,
THEN --
>> MAYBE THEY INTERSECT.
>> YEAH.
IF WE DUG HERE BACK IN '83, AND
WE WOULD HAVE HAD TO COME THIS
WAY.
AND THIS IS THE ONE THAT THE 19
DUG.
PUT THEM SIDE BY SIDE HERE.
>> IT COULD BE CLOSE.
>> NO, BUT THEY NEVER INTERSECT.
WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO SIT AND
WAIT FOR RESCUE.
[ THUD ]
>> WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT?
>> [ COUGHS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> AAH!
>> LOCK THE DOOR!
>> [ COUGHS ]
>> THAT CAN'T BE OUR GUYS, CAN
IT?
>> [ COUGHING ]
[ CLATTERING ]
>> [ GASPS ]
[ AIR HISSING ]
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, RANDY?
>> WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?!
DAMN.
WE'RE LOSING OXYGEN.
I GOT TO GO OUT THERE.
>> WHAT?!
>> I GOT TO CHECK THE TANKS.
>> I'M GOING WITH HIM.
>> RANDY?
WHAT IF THEY'RE STILL OUT THERE?
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
[ DOOR CLOSES, BEEPING STOPS ]
>> ALL RIGHT, TRY TO GET
SOMEBODY ON THE PHONE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Shit.
Oh, fuck.
[ GASPS ]
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> OH, GOD. OH, GOD.
>> GET BACK INSIDE.
COME ON. COME ON.
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
JESUS FUCKING CHRIST!
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON OUT
THERE, RANDY?
>> I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT THE HELL WAS OUT THERE?
>> VAN HORN.
>> WHAT?
>> VAN HORN'S DEAD!
SOMEBODY STUCK A PICKAXE IN HIS
GODDAMN STOMACH!
>> WHAT?!
>> SOMEONE...
SOMEONE...
>> SOMEONE STUCK A PICKAXE IN
HIS GODDAMN STOMACH!
GUTTED HIM LIKE A GODDAMN FISH!
NOW HIS GUTS ARE ALL OVER THE
GODDAMN FLOOR!
[ SAM PANTING ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED, RANDY?
>> I DON'T KNOW, GEORGE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHO WOULD DO SOMETHING LIKE
THAT?
>> WHO'S STILL MISSING?
GRUBBS?
>> NO, NOT GRUBBS.
MAYBE TORRES.
>> LOOK.
NOBODY'S GOING BACK OUT THERE.
WE STAY IN HERE!
>> NO, WE CAN'T.
THERE'S...THERE'S NO MORE
OXYGEN.
>> WHAT?
>> SOMEONE BROKE THE CONNECTORS
AND TOOK THE TANKS.
>> SO, HOW MUCH AIR DO WE HAVE
LEFT?
>> WHATEVER'S IN THOSE TANKS.
>> FUCKING EMPTY.
>> TWO HOURS...MAYBE LESS.
>> [ STAMMERING ]
THERE'S ANOTHER RESCUE
CHAMBER -- THE INFLATABLE.
>> WHERE?
>> IN STORAGE.
ENTRY "C."
>> THAT WAS FLOODED MONTHS AGO.
>> YEAH, BUT IT'S THERE, AND
IT'S GOT TANKS, MAYBE TWO.
THEY'RE IN THE CAGE.
>> LET'S DO THAT.
RANDY AND I WILL GO GET THE
TANKS.
>> I'LL GO WITH YOU.
>> HELL, NO, GEORGE.
YOU AIN'T IN NO SHAPE TO HELP.
>> I SHOULD STAY HERE, FIX THE
CONNECTORS.
>> HEY, GEORGE, YOU CAN'T CARRY
NO TANK.
>> OKAY, THEN, I'LL GO.
I'LL HELP.
>> OKAY.
>> AIR'S GETTING WORSE OUT
THERE.
YOU GUYS NEED TO HURRY.
[ ALARM BLARES ]
[ BEEPING ]
>> LOOK OUT FOR EACH OTHER.
>> I GOT IT.
[ BEEPING STOPS ]
MOVE OUT OF THE WAY.
WATCH YOUR FINGERS.
READY?
[ GROANS ]
COME ON.
LET'S GET THIS THING OVER WITH.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ COUGHING ]
[ COUGHING ]
>> WHERE THE HELL IS THIS THING,
MAN?
>> UP AROUND THIS BEND.
NOW WATCH YOUR STEP HERE.
>> STINKS BAD.
[ COUGHS ]
>> [ EXHALES ]
>> DAD?!
>> WHO MOVES OUT HERE?
>> [ PANTING ]
I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> I GOT YOU.
GIVE HIM OXYGEN.
>> I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> WE GOT YOU. IT'S OKAY.
BREATHE.
COME ON. YEAH.
OKAY, JUST BREATHE. BREATHE.
BREATHE.
[ MAN WAILING IN DISTANCE ]
>> COME ON.
WE GOT TO GO. LET'S GO.
COME ON. COME ON. GET HIM UP.
GOT TO GO. LET'S GO.
COME ON UP.
>> GENTLE.
>> LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
WE GOT TO GO! WATCH YOUR HEAD.
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
JESUS. SOMEONE'S BEEN HERE.
WHOEVER IT WAS, THEY'RE GONE.
>> TANK'S OVER HERE.
>> THERE ARE SOME SMALLER TANKS
INSIDE.
CHECK THEM OUT.
>> Shit!
[ GASPS ]
DAD?
MASEK?
DAD, ARE YOU THERE?
AAH!
[ AIR HISSING ]
OH, GOD.
[ PANTING ]
OH, GOD! OH, GOD!
AAH!
[ PANTING ]
COME ON. COME ON!
Fuck!
[ GROANS ]
OKAY.
AAH!
[ Straining ] OKAY.
OKAY.
OH, GOD!
COME ON!
[ PANTING ]
[ BOTH YELLING ]
[ PANTING, CRYING ]
AAHHH!
>> HEY, HEY. SHH-SHH!
I GOT YOU.
HEY.
SAM, SAM, IT'S ME.
IT'S OKAY. SHH!
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> AAH!
NO!
>> HEY, HEY.
HEY, HEY, HEY, SAM.
CALM DOWN. CALM DOWN.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT? WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> I KEEP SEEING THINGS.
>> SAM, CALM DOWN.
YOU'RE GONNA HYPERVENTILATE, ALL
RIGHT?
NOT ENOUGH OXYGEN TO BREATHE
LIKE THAT, ALL RIGHT?
>> OKAY.
>> SAM.
WHERE'S YOUR DAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LET'S GO FIND HIM, ALL RIGHT?
>> DAD?
>> GEORGE?
>> IS IT DYING?
[ RANDY RAPS FLASHLIGHT ]
>> SHIT.
HANG ON.
HANG ON. HANG ON.
HERE.
THIS SHOULD LAST US A LITTLE
BIT.
>> DAD?!
HE'S GOT TO BE HERE SOMEWHERE.
>> George?
>> Dad?!
WHERE'S THE OXYGEN?
IT WAS RIGHT THERE.
YES!
WILL THESE WORK?
>> SHIT.
>> WHAT?
>> THESE ARE THE EMPTIES.
>> No!
[ MAN WHISTLES IN DISTANCE ]
>> WHO'S THAT?
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
MASEK?
IS THAT YOU?
>> [ GROANS ]
>> JESUS, MAN, WHERE YOU BEEN?
>>  OFF TO HELL...
WE GO
>> AAH!
[ GROANS ]
>> [ INHALES SHARPLY ]
>> [ GROANS ]
>> [ PANTING ]
>> [ COUGHING ]
[ ALL GROANING, PANTING ]
RANDY, HELP ME GET HIM IN THE
CAGE BEFORE HE WAKES UP.
HURRY.
>> I GOT HIM.
>> GET HIS LEGS.
>> WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT?!
>> THERE'S JUST SOMETHING --
SOMETHING IN THE AIR.
>> IT'S NOT THE FUCKING AIR.
>> SAM, THERE'S NOT ENOUGH
OXYGEN.
>> SOMETHING IS HAPPENING.
HIS EYES -- FUCK!
GRUBBS, TOO.
>> WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN GRUBBS?
>> GRUBBS -- HIS EYES.
I SAW -- I SAW THEM.
NOW MASEK -- IT'S THE 19.
>> WHAT DO YOU -- 19?
>> SAM, I FOUND ONE TANK.
WE HAVE ENOUGH FOR FOUR MORE
HOURS.
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
>> WE GOT TO GO.
HE CAN'T BREATHE.
>> WHAT ABOUT MASEK?
>> FUCK MASEK! WE GOT TO GO!
>> WE'RE NOT LEAVING HIM!
>> FUCK HIM!
>> WE ARE NOT TAKING --
>> GEORGE, WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
GEORGE, YOU'RE NOT THINKING.
IT'S MASEK.
NONE OF US ARE THINKING RIGHT
RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE NOT LEAVING MASEK!
>> HE'S GOT TO BREATHE!
WE NEED TO GO NOW!
>> HEY.
>> COME ON.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS TALKING
ABOUT?
WHAT THE FUCK AM I DOING IN THIS
CAGE, HUH?
>> RANDY.
>> WHY DON'T YOU OPEN THE GATE
AND LET ME OUT?
>> RANDY.
>> MASEK.
>> HEY, RANDY, BOY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> MASEK...ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
MAN?
>> NO, MAN, MY FUCKING HEAD
HURTS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> RANDY, WE GOT TO GO!
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
MASEK...
WHY'D YOU DO THAT, MAN?
>> DO WHAT, BOY? WHAT I DO?
>> YOU ATTACKED US.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
NO, NO.
NO, I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
>> [ GROANS ]
RANDY, COME ON!
>> SAM, JUST WAIT A MINUTE!
AAH!
MASEK.
>> I'LL DIE WITH NO AIR DOWN
HERE.
DON'T YOU LEAVE ME.
WE DON'T LEAVE NO MAN BEHIND,
RIGHT?
>> MASEK...
[ GROANS ]
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
>> I'M GOOD.
MY HEAD HURTS.
>> WE'LL COME BACK FOR YOU, MAN.
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
I SWEAR.
>> RANDY.
>> RANDY?!
>> WE'LL BE BACK.
BENNETT?!
>> SAM?
>> BENNETT, GET YOUR ASS BACK
HERE!
FUCK!
[ MASEK YELLING IN DISTANCE ]
>> HERE, HERE.
LET ME HELP.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT IT.
>> WE HAVE TO SLOW DOWN.
>> IF WE STOP, WE DIE.
COME ON.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
[ CRACKLING CONTINUES ]
[ MOTOR WHIRRING, DYING ]
>> WE GOT TO CONNECT THE OXYGEN.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
>> WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DID I DO?
>> WHAT DID YOU DO TO MUNDY?
>> I WASN'T EVEN HERE.
>> WHY DID YOU LEAVE?
>> TO SAVE YOUR DAUGHTER...AND
TO SAVE YOU.
>> YOU DIDN'T SAVE NOBODY!
>> DAMN MOTHERFUCKER!
>> GET HER OFF!
>> [ COUGHING ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
I ALWAYS WANTED TO SPEND THE
REST OF MY LIFE WITH YOU.
IT'S FUNNY HOW THINGS WORK OUT.
>> [ PANTING ]
>> SO, THAT'S IT?
NO.
WHAT...WHAT ABOUT THE OLD MINE?
>> WHAT ABOUT IT?
>> DAD...
DIDN'T YOU SAY IT MIGHT
INTERSECT WITH THOSE TUNNELS
THAT YOU DUG WAY BACK?
>> IT'S CLOSE, BUT THEY DON'T
MEET.
>> WELL, HOW CLOSE?
>> CLOSE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE DYNAMITE?
WHAT IF WE...BLOW A HOLE IN THE
WALL AND GET THE FUCK OUT
THROUGH ONE OF THOSE TUNNELS?
>> IF WE DON'T BLOW OURSELVES UP
FIRST.
>> WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
>> BE CAREFUL.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS WAY.
>> [ GASPS ]
>> WHAT IS IT?
[ MAN YELLS IN DISTANCE ]
>> WE GOT TO GO.
>> WHAT?
[ ALL PANTING ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'LL GO FIRST.
>> WAIT. SAM.
>> I'M THE LIGHTEST.
>> HOW FAR DOWN IS IT?
>> [ PANTING ]
IT'S FAR.
[ BOTH YELLING ]
>> SAM?!
>> [ COUGHING ]
>> SAM?
>> [ Straining ] Oh, God.
>> SA-A-M!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> OH, GOD.
>> SAM, TALK TO ME!
SAM?!
SAM, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
>> YEAH.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> THE LADDER'S FUCKED UP.
WE GOT TO FIND ANOTHER WAY DOWN.
>> [ PANTING ]
Shit!
Jesus!
Oh, God!
[ MAN GROANING ]
>> AAH!
>> SAM?
>> [ GASPS ]
HOW'D YOU GET DOWN HERE?
Y-YOUR LEG.
>> I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW.
>> STAY BACK.
I SAID, STAY BACK!
STAY BACK!
>> OH!
>> [ GASPS ]
Oh, my God.
I'M SORRY.
[ PANTING ]
NO.
S-SHIT.
NO, NO.
[ PANTING ]
[ MAN YELLING IN DISTANCE ]
OH, MY GOD.
DAD?
HELL!
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
SAM?!
>> RANDY.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
>> SAM.
>> DAD.
>> [ WHEEZING ]
HELP ME.
>> I GOT YOU.
>> GEORGE?
[ COUGHING ]
WHICH WALL?
>> RANDY.
THROUGH THERE.
[ GEORGE COUGHING ]
[ LIGHTER FLICKERING ]
>> COME ON.
I can't breathe!
I can't...
>> RANDY?
RANDY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
COME ON!
>> I can't breathe.
>> HURRY!
RANDY!
COME ON!
NO.
AAH!
GET OFF ME!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
[ PANTING ]
NO!
[ Crying ] NO!
NO!!
NO!! IT DIDN'T FUCKING WORK!
[ CRYING ]
WE'RE GONNA DIE.
>> [ Weakly ] Sam.
>> I'M SORRY.
[ SOBBING ]
>> Sam.
It's okay.
They heard the explosion.
They'll find us.
>> NO, NO!
NO, DAD, NO!
OH, NO!
NO!!
[ CRYING ]
NO, PLEASE!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
AAH!
[ SHOVEL STRIKING ]
[ STRIKING CONTINUES,
BLOOD GUSHING ]
[ MOTOR WHIRRING ]
[ DEVICE CRACKLING ]
>> WE GOT A SURVIVOR!
[ HELICOPTER WHIRRING ]
>> AT THIS POINT, WE'RE STILL
GETTING VERY FEW DETAILS.
WE KNOW THAT...
WE CAN SEE IT IS...
>> THANK GOD.
[ SIREN WAILING ]
OUR BABY GIRL.
RANDY?
>> He tried to kill me.
>> WE ALSO DON'T KNOW IF THERE
ARE ANY POTENTIAL SURVIVORS.
>> GENTLEMEN, PLEASE.
PLEASE.
>>  WHAT AN AWFUL DAY
>>  WHEN THE JUDGMENT COMES
>>  AND THE SINNERS HEAR
>>  THEIR ETERNAL DOOM
>>  AT THE SAD DECREE
>>  THEY'LL DEPART FOR AYE
>>  INTO ENDLESS WOE
AND GLOOMLESS WOE AND GLOOM
>>  I'M PAYING NOW
>>  THE PENALTY
>>  THE UNREDEEMED
>>  THAT THE UNREDEEMED
>>  MUST EVER PAY
>>  THOUGH FOR HELP I CRY
>>  IT'S NOW IN VAIN
>>  IT'S ALL IN VAIN
>>  FOR ALAS I'M DOOMED
FOR AYE
I'M DOOMED FOR AYE
>>  IF I COULD RECALL
>>  ALL THE YEARS NOW GONE
>>  FOR MY SAVIOR'S CAUSE
>>  I WOULD SPEND EACH ONE
>>  BUT THEY NEVER AGAIN
>>  CAN TO ME RETURN
>>  AND THE TASK IS LEFT
UNDONE
IT'S LEFT UNDONE
>>  I'M PAYING NOW
>>  THE PENALTY
>>  THE UNREDEEMED
>>  MUST EVER PAY
>>  THOUGH FOR HELP I CRY
>>  IT'S NOW IN VAIN
>>  IT'S ALL IN VAIN
>>  FOR ALAS I'M DOOMED
FOR AYE
I'M DOOMED FOR AYE
>>  OH, I REALIZE
>>  BUT ALAS TOO LATE
>>  WHAT A DARK MISTAKE
>>  ALL MY LIFE HAS BEEN
>>  I REFUSED THIS LOVE
>>  WITH A VARIOUS HEART
>>  AND I MUST PAY THE PRICE
OF SIN
THE PRICE OF SIN
>>  I'M PAYING NOW
>>  THE PENALTY
>>  THE UNREDEEMED
>>  THAT THE UNREDEEMED
>>  MUST EVER PAY
>>  THOUGH FOR HELP I CRY
>>  IT'S NOW IN VAIN
>>  IT'S ALL IN VAIN
>>  FOR ALAS I'M DOOMED
FOR AYE
I'M DOOMED FOR AYE