Tonight, we'll go behind the walls.
I'm going into the walls tonight.
Dig beneath the lies.
I didn't kill that man, Michael.
The evidence says you did.
And the treachery.
You tell me now.
Not gonna happen, John.
All to uncover the facts and secrets
behind TV's most exciting new show.
I'm getting you out of here.
From a man who will go to any length
5 years at Fox River State Penitentiary.
To save a brother about to die
for a crime he may not have committed.
To the brutality and violence of one
of the world's most notorious prisons.
From a mysterious trail
of cover-ups and muggers
Move on the younger brother before
anything bites any of us in the ass.
To a sinister plot that reaches
to the highest levels
and darkest corners
of the US government.
The man killed
the Vice-President's brother.
All tonight, as we present
May 11th, that's the day, pal.
That's the day they...
you know... execute me.
I know.
I didn't kill that man, Michael.
The evidence says you did.
I don't care what the evidence says.
I didn't kill him.
Swear to me.
I swear to you, Michael.
I play a man whose older brother
is on death row
framed for a crime that he may
or may not have committed.
What is it about this case
that the Secret Services
are so interested in?
The man killed
the Vice-President's brother.
I've exhausted all legal options
trying to clear his name.
So I decide to take matters
into my own hands.
The character that I'm playing
is a structural engineer
and I've got this brilliant
detailed plan
that covers everything
from certain individuals' backgrounds
in the prison itself,
the warden of the prison,
the mob boss inside
the guy who is running
the black market.
Open it.
I hold up a bank...
Put down your weapon!
...in order to get thrown
into the same prison
where he's being held
so I can help him escape.
I've known you my entire life.
You don't have a violent bone
in your body.
I play Veronica Donovan.
I'm an attorney.
And Michael calls on me
to represent him
basically because he wants
to get thrown in jail.
I'm not a criminal attorney.
I'm like a real estate attorney.
It's a kind I've no idea what I'm doing
and I'm completely in over my head.
Rarely in a case of armed robbery
do we hear a plea of no contest.
Are you sure of this Mr. Scofield?
I'm sure Your Honor.
Your Honor,
we'd like to recess if we could,
my client's a bit confused
at the moment.
- I'm not your Honor.
- He is your Honor.
I guarantee him being thrown in jail.
You discharged a deadly weapon
during the commission of the crime
suggests malice to me.
The closest level 1 facility
would be Fox River State Penitenciary.
Sentence to be carried out immediately.
Michael?
Why?
I'm getting you out of here.
It's impossible.
Not if you designed the place, it isn't.
It's a thriller but it's also
a family... drama.
The show explores
the extremities of love
and what some people are willing to do
in order to save a loved one's life.
My brother and I have a very complicated
relationship where he... has...
taken care of me from an early age
when both of our parents
were no longer on the scene.
- It's not gonna be the same.
- Oh we're gonna figure it out.
And no matter what,
It's still gonna be me and you.
Okay, but...
What if something happens to you?
You just... have a little faith.
Made a lot of sacrifices so that
I would not have to suffer
the way that he did,
His life took a couple of wrong turns.
Lincoln was the kind of guy
that chose the wrong side of life,
but made sure that Michael
didn't follow in his footsteps.
I went off to college and grand school,
enjoyed the degree of success
that he never knew,
so when he goes to prison,
I really feel as I owe him,
for having made all these sacrifices,
and now I can use all of
the expertise I've gotten
as a structural engineer
in order to save him.
You know, I've made my peace
with what is coming
and you show up and
give me the one thing
a man in my situation shouldn't have:
Hope.
Just have a little faith.
I've got the most meticulous plan
you can imagine.
I've done extensive researches as far as
across the layout of the prison
what screws they use,
what bolts they use.
Getting outside these walls
is just the beginning.
We gonna need money.
I'll have it.
And people in the outside.
People that can help you disappear.
I've already got them.
They just don't know it yet.
Michael has gone about
making contact with all his inmates
in the prison, because every inmate
is serving a function
for the break, once they do breakout
so he needs everyone of these guys
to make this thing happen.
The very cool twist,
is that I have the blueprints
to this prison
hidden in a tattoo that covers
my entire upper body and arms.
- You've seen the blueprints?
- Better than that.
I've got them on me.
Am I supposed to be
seeing something here?
When I first saw the tattoo,
my question was: "Well...
where are the blueprints?", because
they're not visible to the naked eye.
Look closer.
They are woven into the artwork itself.
They said there was gonna be
a prison map, hidden
within a tattoo.
The Art Department e-mailed me a map,
and I took the map,
threw it over onto a light table,
threw a piece of vellum on top of that,
then just incorporated some cracks
and contour lines and stuff like that.
I knew they were in these visual effects
but I wanted it to be there
as much as possible.
Now the front
contains all the underground
passageways.
The back is the
overview shot like it's from
helicopter point of view
of the actual prison.
It's not just drawings but there are
words written backwards and upside down,
various symbols that mean
certain things and references to
people, to street names
to chemical formulas, and a lot of it
only I can see when I hold up a mirror
so I can read the writing
in the correct way.
As the episodes come about,
they called me up
and told me: "Okay,"
"we need this specific design,
we need it to say this..."
They're constantly being
procreative on thinking up
different ways
to incorporate the tattooer.
I've only had the entire tattoo on once,
so far.
Kind of like 30 decals
that they put together like...
pieces of puzzle.
It's 2 or 3 pieces for each arm,
and a back and a front in one piece,
and there's some top of the shoulders
and... there is the rib cage
that has a several pieces.
That's impressive.
I have no idea what most of that stuff
actually signifies.
But the writers have
this entire series planned out
through the second season,
so each episode is a surprise.
When we return, you'll come face to face
with the villains of Prison Break.
Three!
How's the foot?
And the men who will play a key role
in the escape.
See these hands?
They're digging machines.
Are you going to China,
I'll get you there!
Plus, we'll uncover the conspiracy
that put an innocent man behind bars.
Anyone that's a threat
to what we're doing is expendable.
All when Prison Break Behind the Walls
returns.
No one's ever broken out Fox River.
Underscene steps
have already been mapped out.
- Every contengency.
- Every contengency!
You may have the blueprints
of this place
but there's one thing those plans
can't show you: people.
As soon as you look at these cats
the wrong way, they'll cut you off.
All every good story needs a...
a villain.
Or in our case, many villains.
And we have villains that you hate,
and villains that you love to hate.
Wrong piece of real estate, Fish.
It belongs to T-Bag.
Who?
You best pick a respect, Fish.
Man kidnapped half dozen
boys and girls down in Belmer.
Raped them, killed them.
Wasn't always in that order either.
Does T-Bag has a real name?
That is my real name.
No, no, no, please.
Sit.
So you're the new one I've been hearing
all of River Views about?
Scofield.
What I loved about T-Bag
was that on paper, he was saying things
that are very menacing and dangerous.
And, obviously,
he's a leader of the pack.
- Ragheads got you scared, do they?
- Sorry?
Assume that's why you're over here.
Few days on the inside,
any God-fearing white man realizes
the correctional system's
got a serious lean
towards the African-American persuasion.
I hadn't noticed.
But, I wanted to...
try to make it charming... and sweet.
"You have to do
what I want you to do", but...
it was also a very protective
kind of thing.
We'll protect you. I'll protect you.
All you gotta do is...
take this pocket right here,
and your life'll be
all peaches and cream.
Looks to me you already got
a girlfriend.
I got a whole another pocket
over here.
Well, I'll pass.
Then you best move then.
Now.
T- Bag is a huge conflict for Michael.
The great thing about T-Bag
is that he is always in his face
saying: Hey!
First I want you...
Okay, you don't want me?
I'm gonna make your life miserable,
and by making your life miserable,
I'm gonna mess up your plans,
whatever they are.
Got an issue with our little friend
over there?
Don't gotta come to you,
you don't give the green light.
Everythin' in here runs through me,
you know that?
My name is John Abruzzi,
and I'm a mobster, I'm a hitman.
I'm not a Don.
But for my family,
I took the dive to go to prison.
Say you were able
to get outside those walls...
Would you have the people in place
to make sure you disappeared forever?
Why do you care?
Just curious.
What I say to Abruzzi is:
"I've discovered the man who"
"pointed the finger at you
and put you behind bars."
This individual who is off
on witness protection somewhere,
I found out where he is.
Word is there's someone in here
who knows where Fibonacci is,
and you're not doing anything about it.
I'm working on it.
Well, you're not working on it
fast enough.
Apparently, Fibonacci's
coming up for air again.
Next month, a congressional hearing.
Now, if he testifies in that hearing,
a lot of people are going down.
Including me.
And I've known you a long time,
our wives are friends,
our kids go to the same catholic school.
Now, it would be a shame,
if anything would happen to your kids.
One of my
mobster friends
has my two kids
and he's gonna hurt the kids if I don't
follow his new rules.
Abruzzi decides to break me
and simply get the information out of me
by force.
Now I'm gonna count to 3.
- One...
- I give you that information,
I'm a dead man.
You know it, and I know it.
Two.
I'll tell you the name
from outside those walls,
not a second before.
You tell me now!
Not gonna happen, John.
Three!
I call it "Sicilian pedicure."
We do that in Sicily all the time.
- I'm gonna kill that scum!
- You won't!
You kill him, you kill our express
to get out of here.
Look what he did to you.
You're not gonna last
a second in this place
unless I do something about it.
You ever hear of Top-Flight Charters?
Yeah.
They're run by a shell corporation
Abruzzi owns.
We get him on board,
there's gonna be a midnight flight
waiting for us the night
we get outside those walls.
It's important to remember
that he's not
a super hero.
He doesn't have martial art skills and
when he goes behind bars
to save his brother,
...he's very much in jeopardy.
24/7.
How's the foot?
Officer Bellick.
He's in charge of the prisoners,
the guards,
he knows everything.
So he kind of...
in a strange way, kind of underhandedly
runs the show.
You're talking out of the side
of your neck.
Just trying to fly low
over the radar, boss.
There isn't any flying under my radar.
Bellick's first impression with Michael,
is that he is... cocky upstart.
And Bellick enjoys
people like that 'cause
he loves to mess with them.
Under the table, cohoño!
What the hell is this?
It's insurance, white boy!
Now dump it!
So... Tooling up for the race riot,
aren't we?
I try to find out
what Michael's up to.
He's up to something.
This guy shouldn't be in here.
So I think that's
a quandary for Bellick
that he enjoys, you know,
trying to put that puzzle together.
I'm telling you the guards are
the dirtiest gang in this whole place.
The only difference between us and them,
it's the badge.
There are a number of characters
that he encounters in prison
who he probably would not choose
to engage with
on the outside
because he would look at them
as convicts,
people who'd committed
...crimes,
but what he comes to understand is that
they are good people.
They may have made certain mistakes,
but they do still have value and worth,
not only to Michael's plan as a whole
but to his development as...
a man, as a person.
Sucre?
You can't be serious.
The guy's a thief Michael,
he can't be trusted.
Gonna have to trust him,
because he's my cellmate.
We don't hire him, there won't be
any digging in that cell.
And if there's no digging
in that cell...
then there's no escape.
Fernando Sucre is an amazing character.
One of the things I love about him,
he's not just a thug.
I'm not saying he's a good guy, but
he's got a good side,
he... he loves his girl,
What's another word for love?
What's the context?
Oh you know...
The "l love you so much,
I'm never knocking over
a liquor store again" context.
Except, you know, classy.
He's got a girlfriend on the outside,
Marie-Cruz, with whom he's in love,
Marie-Cruz has
another suitor who's actually
Sucre's cousin,
so there's another man on the scene.
What are you doing here?
Where's Marie-Cruz?
She's not gonna come around here
any more.
Is she hurt?
Oh no no, she's fine, she's fine.
She's just...
She's with me now.
Sucre feels threatened,
and wants to get in on the plan,
simply to
get out so he can stop the wedding.
I want back in.
- Too late.
- I'll do what you want.
See these hands?
They're digging machine.
Are you going to China,
I'll get you there!
I'll dig like a psychotic rodent
if I have to...
Fish!
I gotta be back in.
Fernando/Michael...
how awesome these two guys.
They think differently,
they're brought up differently
and somehow,
their chemistry just sparks
this thing that
makes it placid to watch.
- Good to be back, mate!
- Good to have you back.
So...
When do we get started?
They have their own
agenda, but they care each other
and they...
and they support each other.
Is this yours?
You're not a good liar.
Come on, Sucre, you go to the SHU.
Move along, Deputy.
I'm not done checking the cell,
down here.
I said move along.
Prison wardens are usually very tough,
hard nosed,
preachers who have been moulded
that way by the...
by the prison system.
He's not your...
traditional expected warden bad-ass type
but instead, a warm...
paternal figure.
I can't help wondering what someone
with your credentials
is doing in a place like this?
Took a wrong turn
a few months back, I guess.
You make it sound
like a trafic infraction.
Like all you did was turn the wrong way
up a one way street.
Everyone turns up once sooner or later.
Almost 21 years ago,
I did little time myself in England.
And the warden, or the governor,
they call him there,
his all philosophy about...
prison and prisoners,
was very similar
to Henry Pops' in that he's...
he believed in rehabilitation.
I know you're a structural engineer,
Scofield.
Shah Jahan built the Taj Mahal as a
monument to his undying love
for his wife.
My wife is quite fan of the story.
It appeals to the romantic in her.
What's odd? This is truly unique
to discover that he has a wife
for forty years, and...
well, he loves her,
wants to do something for her.
I build any more...
you talking it'd come down
like a house of cards.
That's where I was hoping
you could be of assistance.
And for the favour, I can offer you
3 days of work a week in here,
and that will keep you off the yard.
What you see in my relationship
with the warden,
is that he does become a...
surrogate father figure.
And that complicates our relationship
because I need to manipulate him
in certain ways,
to do what I need done.
But the more I become
attached to him emotionally,
the more guilt I feel about
manipulating him.
And that's a very interesting dynamic
in Michael's journey.
Who's the pet lover?
He'll deny it but he's D. B. Cooper.
Parachute out of a plane 30 years ago
with a million and a half in cash.
Doesn't look like the type.
Much like the warden character,
I think D. B. Cooper
eventually represents
some kind of surrogate father to me.
I heard you were D. B. Cooper.
You want a Cooper story?
I can't give it to you.
'Cause I'm not him.
It's too bad.
Sort of wished it was true.
Man's a legend.
Nowhere near as much as I wish
it were true, friend.
I'd have a million five
waiting for me on the outside.
What D. B. Cooper represents to me,
initially,
is simply a man with a lot of cash
on the outside,
which we'll need
once we break out of prison.
So I try to enlist him in the...
escape plan.
Do you ever think about Boston?
Sure.
Think you'll ever see it again?
I'm a 60 year old man,
and there're 60 years left on my ticket.
What do you think?
I'm thinking about going.
Ah there's going and there's... going.
Which one do you mean?
The one you think I mean.
The character that I'm playing
plays other characters.
With the warden,
he's kind of a surrogate son,
with the mob boss,
he's an antagonist who
has something in his possession that
that mob boss desperately needs.
He is a brilliant chess player,
but discovers as he goes along that...
they aren't partners, they're people.
And...
it's... it really makes for some
very complicated
and engaging drama.
Coming up,
we'll unravel the web of cover-ups
and conspiracy
that could reach to
the highest levels of government.
What is it about this case
the Secret Services
are so interested in?
And the mysterious woman behind it.
Move on the younger brother
before anything bite
any of us in the ass.
Plus, we'll join the cast
inside the notorious
real life penitenciary
that is the home for Prison Break.
And hear their terrifying stories.
It's a bit spooky here,
maybe haunted would be a better word.
When Prison Break Behind the Walls
continues.
It's time we stop
beating around the bush gentlemen,
and go after the damn bush!
Burrows.
4100.
Take the only thing Burrows has left:
time.
After all, the chair isn't the only way
to take a man's life in prison.
There is a large government conspiracy
that put my brother behind bars
in the first place.
And what you...
ultimately learn is that
forces larger than all of us
are at work here,
to make him look guilty.
The evidence was there.
The evidence was cooked.
They're introduced
to two Secret Service agents.
They're not sure who exactly
they're working for,
who are committed to making sure
that this frame up
is carried through
to the end of a boy and of...
my brother being executed for a crime
that he did not commit.
The closer it gets,
the more I'm worrying that the bottom
is gonna fall out of this whole thing.
In one month,
it'll all be over.
My character's name is
Special Agent Kellerman, Secret Services
and what I like most
about playing him is that...
he's extremely effective and efficient,
and streamlined.
He's kind of Michael's
doppelgänger really,
on the outside of the prison.
Kellerman is also clever,
and obsessed and committed.
But he's committed to...
foiling Michael's plan.
It's our understanding that you have
great influence with the governor.
We're friends.
It's also our understanding
that you're opposed to death penalty.
I'm a man of God, how could I not?
In this case, we're hoping
you'll suspend that position.
If the inmate appeals to me
for intervention,
how can I turn my back on him?
Are you saying you won't do it?
I'm not a man to equivocate.
Admirable.
What's important about Kellerman,
in a character like Kellerman, is that
you might look at him as the bad guy.
But, he has a mission,
and he is gonna get
the mission
that has been assigned to him done,
any way possible.
He fully believes that what he is doing
is for the good of the country.
This guy does not...
think he is a bad man at all.
He can think in fact, he is doing
absolutely the good thing
for a higher cause.
All right, Scofield had no priors
and a full time job as an engineer.
Correct.
Obviously, something's up.
Move on the younger brother.
What I love about the mysterious woman
is that
the setting seems so domestic.
and tranquil and...
"Martha Stewart Asks",
and yet, directing
the Secret Service Agents to carry out
...their nefarious schemes...
It's representative of a conspiracy
at the highest levels!
Hello?
We have a small complication.
There's a lawyer poking around.
Veronica Donovan.
Yes.
Anyone that's a threat
to what we're doing is expendable.
Anyone.
Understood.
The Secret Services are terrified
that she's gonna... uncover the plot.
I deserve to know.
I loved him as much as you did.
Lincoln and I were romantically
involved.
And basically,
before Michael gets himself thrown in,
I had pretty much written off Lincoln
and believed that he is guilty.
When he got thrown into prison...
she was at the point of...
She believed like many
that he did commit the crime and she...
basically... you know,
left him there.
Michael's in here because he thinks
you're innocent.
What's he told you?
He isn't telling me anything
but I know, Lincoln.
I know what he is planning.
Call him off.
If you love him, call him off.
I saw the tape.
I haven't done what you saw.
I know what I saw.
Through Michael's actions,
she's been forced
to reevaluate the sentence
and as a result of that,
she started to find...
you know, holes in the case.
On your risk what I'm talking to you
'cause they'll kill your boy
like they killed mine.
Coroner's report says
what killed your boyfriend,
Leticia, was an overdose.
No, they killed him.
'Cause he knew things.
Things they didn't want to get out.
Like what?
Like who is really behind that hit
that night.
Sure as hell wasn't Lincoln.
None of them knew
what they were getting into,
they were just pawns in a big game.
I'd get as far away from him
as you can girl.
'Cause there's nobody they can't get to.
Uncovering what exactly
is going on trying to find evidence
to exonerate Lincoln,
I'm starting to realize
this is bigger than anybody thought.
You see anything? Definitive cuts
any place that proves the tape
might have been cooked?
The thing's clean! No footprints.
Here's the audio track from the tape.
Sound pretty true, right?
Yeah.
But noise is a lie.
It doesn't just die like that.
What does that mean?
The sound of the gunshot.
It wasn't recorded in that room.
I start to realize that Lincoln
wasn't guilty.
And I commit my time
to sort of uncovering
this conspiracy that's going on.
And I'm dedicating all my time
to Lincoln.
Coming up...
we'll take a closer look
at the intricate plan
that is at the center of Prison Break.
We got a runner!
And the beginning of a romance
that could sabotage the entire escape.
I'll take you to dinner.
Lunch?
Cup of coffee?
Plus the cast reveals
some surprising secrets...
of what lies ahead.
Well, I'll say that you shouldn't
get attached to anyone.
I mean, anyone.
All when Prison Break Behind the Walls
returns.
I'm Michael, by the way.
Scofield. I've read your report.
And you are?
Doctor Tancredi will do.
Tancredi like the governor?
By coming to my relationship with
Dr. Sandra Tancredi,
I need to be in the infirmary
where she works
because there is a certain grate there
that I need access to which is going
to figure into our plans later on,
And to that end, I'm
prentendig to be a diabetic,
so I can go in and get an insuline shot
on a regular basis.
Tattoo? It's fresh!
Hold up.
I guess being a diabetic,
you don't mind needles.
Gotta launch into that relationship
simply hoping to manipulate her.
To use her to accomplish
what I need to accomplish.
But find, slowly but surely,
that there may, in fact,
be a relationship there.
Be up a change
you wanna see in the world.
I think they're people
who are surprisingly...
similar to one another.
What?
Nothing, that was just my senior quote.
That was you?
This whole time,
I was thinking it was Gandhi!
You're very funny.
And were he on the other side
of the bars...
He's someone...
with whom she could at least
have a profound friendship
and potentially, have
the kind of unique
consonant understanding that
happens very very rarely in life.
You know you're gonna get killed
in here, right?
If you're not careful?
I'm like you I bet.
When I get out of here, alive,
I'll take you to dinner.
Lunch?
A cup of coffee?
Michael, this...
this charm act...
could be exactly what's getting you
into trouble out in the yard.
I think what constantly surprises me
about it is...
it's a show that tries to...
change a pattern
as soon as it's established.
Just as soon as you see
Michael's mask,
perfectly applied, day after day,
it cracks.
Those twists and turns every week...
Oh my God, the hero, the hero!
The hero is in trouble! How is he... oh!
Look, he's gonna make it! Oh, no!
There's another wall
he's getting out through.
There is another conflict here.
It's just basic good story-telling.
You're a dead man Scofield!
You hear me?!
You're just dead!
Don't let the hero off the hook.
Just don't let him off the hook.
If you do:
end of the story.
It's a roller coaster.
It's really one of those things that...
It takes you from left to right,
right to left,
It just keeps you... on your toes.
I think one of the most clever part
of the show
is that there's a little puzzle
for the audience to solve
in each and every episode.
They're given a set of facts
or information
that you immediately assume in one thing
and at the end of the episode,
you find out they mean something
entirely different.
One episode...
deals with what you think
is another inmate named
Allen Schweitzer, name that you hear
referenced a couple of times.
Allen Schweitzer.
The name mean anything to you?
- Should it?
- I don't know, you tell me.
Never heard of the guy.
It's actually a reference to Schweitzer,
which is the name of the company
that made the toilet in my prison cell
that we're actually going to dismantle
and get behind
to break through that wall.
And Allen is a reference to huh...
an Allen wrench,
which is what I need to get my hands on
in order to dismantle the toilet.
And they've got reference to...
what you think of individuals' names
English, Fitz and Percy.
We have a decision to make.
- Yeah.
- English,
Fitz or Percy.
If we're gonna pull this off,
we need to single one of them out.
And this being prison,
you assume that I mean that
they're guards or other inmates
that we have to...
execute but they're actually...
street names.
There are three streets
on the exterior of the prison
English, Fitz and Percy.
And one of them will be the street
that we'll take out of the prison.
So I break out of my cell,
head off to the roof of the prison,
and intentionally set off an alarm.
We got a runner!
Once an inmate escapes,
obviously, a lot of
law enforcement parties
are set into motion.
So I can see from which direction
the State Troopers
and helicopters will be coming,
and so, when I see the cop cars
coming down English,
and I see the cop cars
coming down Percy,
and Fitz remains open, I know, Okay.
When we finally escape,
Fitz is the road to take.
Coming up, the family drama
that is at the heart of Prison Break.
Love you.
Always loved you.
And we'll go inside the real life
Prison Break penitenciary
that has been the final stop
for some of the world's
most notorious criminals.
John Wayne Gacy was in a cell here,
my effect's that's Lincoln's cell.
When Prison Break Behind the Walls
continues.
5 years. Sentence to be carried out
immediately.
Uncle Mike?
I didn't want you to come.
Go home L.J.
I didn't want you to see this.
The show is a family drama.
It's about brothers...
and especially fathers and sons.
Two pounds of pot?
What were you trying to do?
Set a record?
It's not funny, L.J.,
you could be going to jail.
Last semester, you were getting almost
all As and now...
It's your father, isn't it?
I don't have a father.
Life thrusts on him a role
that he's not ready to play,
which is being a man at 15.
And, when that happens,
you get rebellion.
I'm not asking you to love me.
I... already screwed up the chance
long ago.
I'm asking you to love yourself.
So that's what fatherly advice is like?
They're putting me to death, L.J.
In a month time, I'll be dead.
You get that?
You're already dead to me.
One of the things that surprised me
is the depth to this story.
Give me your hand.
What are you doing?
He reaches out to his son
and says... "I wanna go to my grave"...
"resolving the inner conflict"
that they both have towards one another.
"I may achieve that."
I want you to be here.
I want you to be there
the day before I die.
So I can see you.
So I can hold you.
I love you.
I've always loved you.
The center of it is like just family,
you know,
It's not about the crime,
it's not about, you know, the jail.
I mean that's just the symptom
of a family, 'cause what more
would you go and commit a crime for
than you would for family?
What more would you do anything?
There's nothing more meaningful
really on the Earth
that I could think of.
Not money, not huh... anything,
but it's their love, you know?
And if that love doesn't...
exist then...
then why do we...
why do we do anything for it?
To create the realistic
and terrifying world of Prison Break,
the producers decided to film
not on a Hollywood sound stage,
but in an actual prison,
the State Penitenciary in Joliet,
Illinois.
Ready in... Action!
...all those nights...
in California?
For over 150 years,
Joliet was one of the world's
most notorious
maximum security prisons,
home to such infamous
and cold-blooded criminals
as public enemy number 1:
Baby Face Nelson,
teenage thrill slayers Leopold and Loeb.
and more recently,
one of the most
shocking murderers of all,
John Wayne Gacy.
I'm not gonna pretend
that I have any idea what it's like
to be in an actual prison.
I feel very fortunate
that we're here at Joliet
because it's an incredible place
with an incredible history in the news.
150 years of pain and
violence and fear
are soaked into these walls and
I like to think of Joliet
as another character
in the story,
adding a certain authenticity and
essence that we couldn't duplicate
on a sound stage somewhere.
Be mark!
Action!
Being here at Joliet, being here
in an actual prison gives you
a sure middle taste
of what it's like to be there.
These 40 feet walls,
with the razor wire on the top,
these watchtowers on every corner,
it's imposing.
It's an incredible place
in that it...
just captures you know, the...
the intensity of the darkness
of human nature.
You just come in here
and you feel that kind of...
it's like a...
creepy muzzy kind of feeling.
Apparently, some of the boys
are saying they felt like the ghost of
John Wayne Gacy touching them.
I don't know if they're making it up,
but I personally,
have not been in the cell
where people are feeling
John Wayne Gacy's touch
I don't necessarily believe in... the...
supernatural or ghosts, whatever but
the crew have noticed
a few things
and you don't wanna hang out here
all by yourself too much,
it gets pretty... pretty tense.
Just a few years ago,
Joliet State Penitenciary was declared
no longer suitable to house prisoners
and was decommissionned.
But it has become the perfect home
for Prison Break.
They have deemed this place
uninhabitable for criminals,
they deserve better.
But let's get some actors
and some crew people,
throw them in there,
they'll do anything.
Welcome to Prisony Land, Fish!
There were ever a several things
I didn't understand but, you know
I talked to these buddies,
that I called up that had been in prison
and said: "What's this world out?
I don't know what it is!
Yo Fish?! What you lookin' at?!
You look kind of pretty
to be up in here, man!
What d'you know about this fish?
He's my new celly.
I totally misjudged you, Scofield.
I didn't think you were
the agitating type.
90 days in the SHU!
That ought to be enough time
to convince you of that fact.
Trey Street Deuces got the hoops.
Norteños got the bleachers.
Woods got the weight pile.
The C.O.'s got the rest.
And a lot... you know,
some have been here in this prison,
and I said:
" Does that sound real to you,
does that sound..."
"Does the world sound right to you,
is the language right?",
they say: "Yeah".
"Yeah, you're right on,
keep going, keep going."
Coming up,
we'll reveal
some of the cast's predictions
of the shocking twists and turns
that lie ahead.
Something serious
potentially lethal
can happen to any of us.
Like it could shank in any time!
When Prison Break Behind the Walls
continues.
In just the first 7 episodes
of Prison Break,
Michael Scofield has put in motion
an elaborate and dangerous plan
to save his brother from death row.
- I'm getting you out of here.
- It's impossible.
Not if you designed the place, it isn't.
His plan involves
getting himself arrested
and thrown into the same prison,
an intricate tattoo
that hides the map of the jail
- You've seen the blueprints?
- Better than that.
I've got them on me.
and the mysterious details
required for the escape.
He's aligned himself with prisonners...
those good...
When do we get started?
...and bad...
...will be instrumentaled to his plan.
As well as prison officials
who will be his unwilling accomplices.
It's better for me
to owe you one in here
than it is for you to owe me one,
I can promise you that.
Outside the prison,
we've learned Michael's brother
may have been framed
in a conspiracy
that could reach to the highest levels
of the US government.
- There's a lawyer poking around.
- Anyone that's a threat is expendable.
And nonetheless for Michael,
a full scale prison riot
had not only threatened the lives
of those he cares about...
Come on! Get my hand!
...it had threatened
to expose his plan...
I'm breaking out.
and guarantee
his brother's execution...
So what twist and turns
lie ahead in Prison Break?
Well, I'd say
that you shouldn't get attached
to anyone.
I mean... anyone.
Like it could shank in any time!
Something serious
potentially lethal can happen
to any of us at any time.
I'm not allowed to say, I don't know!
Makes me nervous
just talking about it.
See? They're watching me!
I predict I'm gonna go
through some crazy stuff.
There might be another one joining us.
I can probably say that.
Can I? Maybe, I don't know...
I personally think it'd be kind of funny
if they killed my brother,
and I'm stuck in prison,
and I still have to get out!
The biggest surprise would be
if he was actually the killer.
I mean there were shows that
I watched as a kid, growing up
that I loved and they'd end
and I'd go: "God"!
What happens next?!
It's so exciting that people walk up to:
"I have to know!".
What I liked to make me...
liked to make myself feel better about
my place in the world... I say...
You know, I can't tell you.
But generally, I really don't know.
If we ever break out,
and I'm assuming that we do,
we're on the run, so that it takes on
a fugitive kind of... field.
There'll be a large number of us,
and we'll probably split up each of us
to accomplish whatever it is
that we need to accomplish.
Then, it's all about uncovering
the conspiracy that puts Lincoln in jail
in the first place.
And I would imagine
the audience at that point
rooting for me
and my brother to...
solve the goverment conspiracy.
Rooting for Sucre
to stop his girlfriend's wedding
to the wrong man.
But hoping and praying
that T-Bag is caught
by the authorities.
And I'm guessing that he will continue
to elude them.
I kind of have fantasies of Lincoln
heading off to Hawaï and...
surfing and drinking beer...
But I'm hoping for Monica sins
with all the hot guys,
like that's what I'm hoping
that the future will bring.
Steamy Monica'd sin, so,
I'm looking forward to some of those.
They come up with these fascinating
twist and turns,
that only ratchets the suspense
and the tension up, higher and higher.
And every episode is better
than the one before.
No matter what the future holds
in the intricate story of Prison Break,
one thing is certain...
The roller coaster ride
of thrills and danger,
treachery and betrayal
has only just begun.
And on October, 24...
1 hour before the story resumes
with a brand new episode,
You'll have a chance
to see a special anchor
of the episode leading up to it.
So make you own plans
to break into TV's
hardest new drama: