The war between the Humans and
the Cyborgs began 73 years ago.
Back in the year 2027.
10 years later the war was won by the Cyborgs.
They control the Earth and
the Humans became their slaves.
There were a scientist who
created a super-DNA gene...
...which would produce a man
with extraordinary powers.
A woman, Zana, was chosen to give birth
for this mutant human.
Zana knew where a special craft was hiden.
A craft stolen from the Cyborgs
that can travel throught time.
Scch, Alex! You have to be quiet,
until we know where we are.
Alex, I have to leave you my love,
I am sorry.
Please try to undestand. Some day
you will return to our world.
You have Powers, Alex.
When you are ready this neckless
will explain everything.
Goodbye my love.
They baby was called Alex after
her famous ancestor.
And thou she was born in the year 2077 -
the destiny of her life was forged
in the late 20th century.
in grimm Wootan, East Africa.
What's wrong....  whats happened, ....
News: A collection of goldcoins has been
stolen from the museum in Mosar.
Three American student worker are
suspected to have fled in an ultralight....
The government wants an evacuation
of all villages  between Karu and Mosar.
The Wootan rebels started a new offensive.
And groups of American mercenaries
has been hired by the rebel leadership.
They start to win the skirmishies and have already
taken over the old uranium mine in Dabar.
Because of your accent.
My accent. I've learn English
from mine workers.
You never had to learn English.
You came to us already knowing English.
What the hell are you, lass?
Such large muscles!
I pray that you're foreigner we can ransome.
You touch me and you're sick son of a bich!
Ooo... nasty talk for a yank
we are going to eat.
- You are sick!
- Want to see something really sick, yank?
No, not me!
I told you to wait for me!
Lucky day.
I've got a captive.
The Americans pay dearly
for their children.
I thought you were the one fighting for freedom.
Everyone has their home use.
Mine is to make the imperialists pay...
...in gold.
Look at all these muscles!
My god.
Come on, cut us free before
the rebel show.
Come on.
I can help with that!... Please.
Hey, don't leave us, please!
Please, don't leave us!
- I'll take you to my plane.
- What plane?
I fly through to Mosar.
From there we return to the States.
My sister and I are really sick of this country
and civil war, we just wanna go home.
My dad was an engineer,
and he is dead.
- Who pilots?
- Me. It was my dads plane ...
He hid it before the rebels got us.
- Come on.
- OK. Fly me away from here.
Its a deal.
This cloths are hard to come under hat .
Whats the idea, hah?
It will help us get past the Rebels.
You pretend to be my prisoners.
Just remember, its a cover.
What is it?
Follow me.
Stupid idiot! You deserved to die.
My bulletproof vest is ruined!
You are really something.
Been here a long time, huh?
The old mining plant?
Yeah, we needed a fuel pump.
My father was forced to land the plane.
We were looking for a pump,
when the rebels found us.
Dad was killed.
We run, we ended up up here.
You know the outpost is really close by.
Find the pump?
Yeah I can install it,
when we get to the plane.
Only we had to do the first time. its was just
to much for her, killing of our dad and everything
The mining plant is controlled
by Wootan bandits. Too risky.
- It is our only chance?
- Yes.
My dad worked for the goverment.
What brought you to Africa?
My mother. Murdered by rebels.
Sorry.
It was a long time ago. I realy don't
remember her. I grew up in a tribe.
- You sound like an American.
- Holy Cross missionary were Americans.
- So your village were is close by?
- It's gone. Everyone dead.
.... rebels.
- No ... devil.
- So whats the story of your life?
- What do you mean?
Well, you are pretty muscular
aren't you, for a girl.
Its like you been here a long time.
Wait! Quick.
What ...... What? Come.
This is the only way to mine.
- I can not see anything.
- Now look. - Wait.
Find the girls.
- Try to escape and I kill you and your sister.
- She is not my sister.
- And I can make a deal worth more than a rent.
- How is that?
There is a treasure and a plane.
You take me to it and I split the looth with you.
What about her?
I do not need any more partners. Do you?
Give me the gun.
Shoot her.
Noo!
Drop your weapons.
Your bullets can't hurt me..
- Shitta.
- Shut up!
.... here. Find the white woman
and terminate her.
She is in sector 17.
Concentrate patrol in there.
- What do you want?
An American. A rebel has her.
Information costs money.
Yes, yes something I want.
- Don't hurt me, please.
- Please?
- Come on you want the information or what?
- You know, we usually kill girls down here.
- Here you are.
- Where are they?
- There, up on the ridge.
Make in a hurry. Someone is gone a find us.
I sent scout to make sure we are safe.
Enyoy your life, we are going to be rich.
Until he is back we have
time to change that!
- You saved me.
- Did I?
What do you think I liked it?
Just trying to stay alive.
I don't trust you.
but I need with the plane.
Frame me, I'll kill you.
I just want out of here alive.
What, what is it?
What?
Get down, get down.
Do you want another one of your friends to die?
No! Oh!
You would be vaporized if you resist.
Remain in place.
Drop your weapon.
Why do you want me?
Because you are wanted by
my superiors for your genetics.
Your mother brought you
from our time to hide you.
My mother was from your world?
My world is a 100 years into the future.
It has takes me 20 years to locate you.
Now I scan you again
to confirm your genetic code.
After I receive confirmation,
you will acompany me back to my time.
- Can you still fly? I get you to
the plane, can you still fly?
- What was  it?
- Now wait here.
Get it back. Put it down.
Put it down! Now!
That gold is mine!
Step away from the plane. Go on.
Mine alone!
I deserve all of it!
Emily!
Emily.
Noo.
Aaaah.....