( wind blowing )
- ( fire crackling )
- ( alarm bell ringing )
( man screams )
( building creaking )
( man screaming )
( crashes )
( tribal music playing )
( ululating )
( thunder rumbling )
( eerie music playing )
( thunder crashes )
( thunder crashing )
( growls )
( bangs )
( high-pitched tone )
( banging )
( pitch increasing )
Man's voice:
YOU ASK ME TO EXPLAIN
WHY I'M AFRAID
OF A DRAFT OF COOL AIR...
WHY I SHIVER
MORE THAN OTHERS
WHEN I ENTER A COLD ROOM...
WHY I SEEM SICK AND SCARED
WHEN THE CHILL OF EVENING
CREEPS THROUGH THE HEAT
OF A MILD AUTUMN DAY.
THERE ARE THOSE WHO SAY
I RESPOND TO COLD
LIKE SOME DO A BAD SMELL.
AND I'M THE LAST
TO DENY THE IMPRESSION.
WHAT I'LL DO IS TO RELATE
THE MOST HORRIBLE CIRCUMSTANCE
I'VE EVER EXPERIENCED
AND LEAVE IT TO YOU TO JUDGE
WHETHER OR NOT THIS FORMS
A SUITABLE EXPLANATION
OF MY STRANGE BEHAVIOR.
IT IS A MISTAKE TO FANCY
THAT HORROR IS ASSOCIATED
INEXTRICABLY WITH DARKNESS,
SILENCE AND SOLITUDE.
I FOUND IT IN THE GLARE
OF A MID-AFTERNOON,
IN THE DARK CANYONS
THAT LACE THE MALIBU COAST
AND IN THE TEEMING MIDST
OF FADED AND BACKWATER ESTATES.
A BIG HOUSE
BUILT BY BIG DREAMS
THAT HAVE LONG GONE
TO REAL-LIFE SHIT,
A HOLLOW PALACE
NOW FORCED TO RENT ROOMS.
-  ( gear shift clicks )
-  THIS ONLY-IN-L.A.
BOARDING HOUSE
WAS RUN BY A LONG-AGO
TROPHY-WIFE LANDLADY,
HER AUTISTIC DAUGHTER
AND TWO FELLOW BORDERS
WHOSE STAY HERE WAS
SIMPLY A BRIEF SOJOURN
OF RESPECTABILITY
ON THEIR WAY TO THE STREETS.
( clicks, whirring )
( car door opens )
( gear shift clicks )
THE PLACE WAS
A FOUR-STORY MANSION
OF CHEAP PLASTER
AND CHEAPER ROOF TILE,
DATING APPARENTLY
FROM THE MID-'80s
AND FITTED WITH MULTI-LEVELS
AND SPLIT-LEVELS
WHOSE STAINED AND SULLIED
SPLENDOR ARGUED A DESCENT
FROM HIGH LEVELS
OF PLENTIFUL CASH AND CREDIT
-  AND A NEW MARRIAGE.
-  ( gear shift clicks )
THE RESULT 20 YEARS LATER
STUNK OF A MESSY DIVORCE.
-  AT LEAST THE AIR WAS CLEAN..
-  ( crows cawing )
...AND THERE WAS NO ONE
TO SEE HOW FAR I'VE FALLEN.
IN THE SPRING
I HAD SECURED
SOME DREARY AND UNPROFITABLE
REWRITE WORK
FOR SOME GUTTER-SCUM
PRODUCTION COMPANY.
AFTER THAT WENT BAD--
LIKELY BECAUSE I TOLD
THE PRODUCER
WHAT I REALLY THOUGHT
OF HIS WORK...
Woman:
CHARLIE BAXTER.
- Charlie: MRS. HAYWARD.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
-  ...AND BEING UNABLE TO PAY
ANY SUBSTANTIAL RENT...
- KEEP GOING AROUND.
- OKAY.
- ...I BEGAN DRIFTING FROM ONE
CHEAP APARTMENT TO ANOTHER
UNTIL I WAS DOWN
TO LOOKING FOR A ROOM.
I HAD HOPED TO FIND SOMEPLACE
WHERE I COULD PUSH THROUGH
MY WRITER'S BLOCK
- AND FINISH
MY OWN GREAT SCREENPLAY.
- WAS IT EASY TO FIND?
Charlie's voice:
BUT RIGHT THEN, I NEEDED
A PLACE THAT WAS CHEAP...
PLEASE, COME ON IN.
...BUT CLEAN AND QUIET.
- Charlie: NICE PLACE.
-  ( door closes )
Charlie's voice:
IN THE ROOMS, LARGE AND LOFTY
AND DECORATED
WITH SCHIZOPHRENIC TASTE
AND RIDICULOUS KITSCH,
THERE LINGERED
A DEPRESSING MUSTINESS
AND A HINT OF OBSCURE...
SOMETHING.
SOMETHING I COULDN'T
QUITE PLACE AT THAT MOMENT.
Mrs. Hayward:
IT'S SO BIG.
HARD TO KEEP UP
WITH JUST MYSELF
AND MY DAUGHTER.
STILL, YOU'VE DONE WONDERS.
- I LIKE THE ANIMALS.
- AREN'T THEY PRECIOUS?
THEY WANDERED
ONTO THE PROPERTY ONE DAY.
FIRST THE GOATS,
THEN THE SHEEP.
YOU'RE TRYING
TO GET THEM TO EAT
SOME OF THAT TALL GRASS.
THAT WAS THE HOPE.
I'M A LITTLE BRITTLE
TO BE WEED WHACKING
THE PROPERTY.
- HAVE TO, YOU KNOW.
- WILD FIRES, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
BIG FINE IF YOU DON'T.
WELL, MAYBE I CAN
HELP YOU THERE.
YOU WIELD
A MEAN WHACKER, CHARLIE?
I LOVE THE FLOORS.
Charlie's voice:
THE WOOD WAS NOT
EXACTLY SPECIAL,
BUT THE FLOORS WERE CLEAN.
Mrs. Hayward:
IF YOU DON'T REQUIRE
A CERTAIN MEAL,
I'D APPRECIATE THE NOTICE
SO I DON'T OVER-PREPARE.
THE FAMILY ROOM IS
A COMMON ROOM.
WE DO HAVE SATELLITE.
WOW.  SATELLITE.
I DATE THE GUY
AT THE LOCAL RADIO SHACK.
HE GIVES ME
THE PROGRAMS FOR FREE.
- GREAT.
- ANYTHING WE CAN DO
TO MAKE ENDS MEET.
- IT ALL HELPS.
- EXACTLY.
YOU UNDERSTAND.
YOU ARE
IN THE BUSINESS.
UH, WHAT ABOUT LAUNDRY?
IT'S $10 EXTRA PER LOAD,
AND I DON'T DO
ANYTHING EXOTIC.
POCKETS HAVE TO BE CLEAR.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
THERE'S A LAUNDROMAT IN MALIBU
IF THAT'S TOO STEEP.
( smacks lips )
SOUNDS REASONABLE.
- I THINK SO.
- Charlie's voice:
THE TOUR CONTINUED.
AS IT TURNED OUT,
THE LINEN CHANGE WAS
TOLERABLY REGULAR
AND THE HOT WATER
NOT TOO OFTEN COLD
OR TURNED OFF,
SO THAT I CAME
TO REGARD IT
AS AT LEAST
A BEARABLE PLACE
TO HUNKER DOWN
UNTIL I MIGHT
REALLY LIVE AGAIN.
YOU WILL SHARE
THIS BATHROOM.
DON'T GO UP THERE,
ALL RIGHT?
AND IF YOU NEED
MORE TOWELS,
THEY'RE RIGHT
IN HERE, OKAY?
AND, WELL,
HERE'S YOUR ROOM.
Charlie's voice:
AS FOR MRS. HAYWARD,
SHE DIDN'T ANNOY ME
WITH THE GOSSIP
OR WITH CRITICISMS
OF EXCESSIVE ELECTRIC USE
IN MY THIRD-FLOOR ROOM.
YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
( chatting continues )
- DO YOU NEED
SOME HELP OR--
- NO NO NO, I'M OKAY.
-  OKAY, GREAT.
- THANK YOU. ( mutters )
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO--
-  NO NO NO.
- THANK YOU.
- ( floor creaking )
( woman coughing )
Charlie's voice:
AND MY FELLOW LODGERS WERE
AS QUIET AND UNCOMMUNICATIVE
AS ONE MIGHT DESIRE...
BEING MOSTLY DOWN-ON-THEIR-LUCK
INDUSTRY TYPES
A LITTLE ABOVE THE COARSEST
AND CRUDEST GRADE
OF STUDIO PRODUCER
OR DIRECTOR.
ONLY THE DIN
OF GOATS BAAA-ING
BELOW MY WINDOW PROVED
A SERIOUS ANNOYANCE.
I'D BEEN THERE TWO DAYS
WHEN THE FIRST
ODD INCIDENT OCCURRED.
ONE MORNING
AT ABOUT 7:00,
I HEARD SOMETHING SPILL
ON THE FLOOR...
( clattering )
...KIND OF
A SPLATTERING SOUND,
AND BECAME SUDDENLY AWARE
THAT I'D BEEN SMELLING
THE PUNGENT ODOR
OF SOMETHING FOUL
FOR A WHILE.
- ( faint whirring )
- ( sniffing )
( thrumming )
THE WALL WAS WET,
LIKE CONDENSATION...
AND COOL--
UNNATURALLY COOL.
A CHILL REACHED DEEP
TO MY BONES.
( crows cawing )
( birds chirping )
I HADN'T MET EITHER
OF MY FELLOW LODGERS
AS THEY KEPT ODD HOURS
AND ONE NEVER SEEMED
TO LEAVE HIS OR HER ROOM.
IF THEY TOOK MEALS,
IT WAS AT PROBABLY
AT FIRST CALL,
SINCE I WAS FINDING MYSELF
JUST MAKING IT
BEFORE THE KITCHEN CLOSED.
I KNEW THE NEIGHBOR
TO MY LEFT WAS
- A MAN NAMED ARNOLD DELTOID.
- ( whirring, hissing )
MRS. HAYWARD SAID
DELTOID HAD BEEN
AN ANIMATOR AT DISNEY
DURING THE STUDIO'S GOLDEN AGE
BACK IN THE '50s...
THERE'S SOMETHING LEAKING
IN MY ROOM FROM--
...BEFORE EVERYTHING
BECAME DIGITAL,
BEFORE HE GOT
FORCIBLY RETIRED.
NOW HE WAS HOLED UP HERE,
-  DESPERATELY TRYING
TO LEARN SOFTWARE...
- HELLO?
...THAT WOULD ALLOW
HIM TO EARN A LIVING
IN THE 21st CENTURY.
THE OTHER LODGER
WAS A MYSTERY.
MRS. HAYWARD HAD DEFLECTED
ALL MY QUESTIONS,
WHICH JUST JACKED UP
MY CURIOSITY.
THE LODGER NEVER LEFT
THE ROOM, AS FAR AS I KNEW.
MRS. HAYWARD DELIVERED
THREE SQUARES TO HIM DAILY.
A COUPLE TIMES I HEARD
WHAT SOUNDED LIKE A COUGH.
SOMETHING LIKE
AN AIR CONDITIONER
GOING FULL BLAST.
BUT MORE...
( mechanical hissing )
( silverware clinks )
- OUTSIDE
BY SIDE OF THE HOUSE.
- ( thrumming continues )
Charlie's voice:
ANXIOUS TO ALERT MRS. HAYWARD
ABOUT WHAT WAS
GOING ON IN THE ROOM
AT THE END OF THE HALL,
AND, TO BE HONEST,
TO LEARN A LITTLE MORE
ABOUT THIS MYSTERY LODGER...
( birds chirping, cawing )
...PUSHED BY MY CURIOSITY,
I HURRIED OUTSIDE
TO FIND THE LANDLADY.
- OH! ( gasps )
- JEEZ!
OH, GOOD MORNING,
CHARLIE.
HAD BREAKFAST YET?
IT ENDS IN 10 MINUTES.
YEAH, THANKS, MRS. HAYWARD,
I'LL GET RIGHT ON THAT.
THERE'S BEEN A LITTLE ACCIDENT.
NOT TO WORRY, CHARLIE.
WE'RE TAKING
CARE OF IT RIGHT NOW.
SORRY IF IT DISTURBED YOU.
OH!  JEEZ!
( exhales deeply )
HI.
( door opens )
( thrumming continues )
IT'S GETTING WORSE.
- Charlie: WHAT?
- THE DOCTOR'S ACCIDENTS.
- ( footsteps overhead )
- WHAT KIND OF ACCIDENTS?
SPILLS,
BROKEN BOTTLES.
I ONLY HEAR IT.
NEVER ACTUALLY SEEN THE DOCTOR
OR THE INSIDE
OF HIS... ROOM.
MUST PAY
A HEALTHY RENT TO GET
- THAT KIND OF SERVICE.
- ( chuckles )
WHAT'S RENT MONEY
TO A DOCTOR, ANYWAY?
EXACTLY.  WHY WOULD
A DOCTOR RENT A ROOM?
DON'T KNOW
AND FRANKLY, DON'T CARE.
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
THE DOCTOR WAS ALREADY HERE
BEFORE I ARRIVED.
- MRS. HAYWARD EVER
TALK ABOUT HIM?
- NOPE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF IT'S A HIM OR A HER.
SHE SAID YOU WERE
A SCREENWRITER?
YEAH, I USED
TO SAY THAT...
BUT NOT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU NOW?
WANNABE.
( laughs )
AT LEAST YOU'RE HONEST.
- ( glass shatters )
- ( bangs )
( clatters )
( woman coughing )
Arnold:
YOU'LL GET USED TO IT.
WHAT'S THE STORY
ON THE GIRL?
AUTISTIC,
BUT IT SEEMS
TO COME AND GO.
AUTISM DOESN'T
COME AND GO.
( humphs )
THE EGGS SEEM
A LITTLE RUNNY TODAY.
( squishes )
( breathing deeply )
( mechanical hissing )
( thrumming )
- ( keys jingling )
- HEY.
- LEAVING?
- ( lock clicks )
- CHARLIE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND YOU'RE ESTELLA.
CHAR-LEE.  CHAR-LEEE.
( sighs )
THE DOCTOR SPILLED
SOME CHEMICALS.
THE ODOR WILL
BE GONE SHORTLY.
I CAN DIG UP
SOME DEODORIZER FOR YOU.
- NO, IT'S FINE.
- I'M SO SORRY.
THE DOCTOR HAS BEEN ILL,
YET THE WORK CONTINUES,
SO THERE ARE ACCIDENTS.
- ( sighs deeply )
- HE WORKS IN HIS ROOM?
THE DOCTOR IS
BEDBOUND NOW.
WELL, WOULDN'T THE DOCTOR
BE BETTER OFF--
IN A HOSPITAL?
WELL, YES, BUT THE DOCTOR
WON'T HEAR OF IT.
THE DOCTOR KEEPS SAYING
THAT'S WHERE PEOPLE
GO TO DIE.
THE DOCTOR BELIEVES IN
AN EXPERIMENTAL TREATMENT--
QUITE RADICAL,
SELF-ADMINISTERED
AROUND THE CLOCK.
THE DOCTOR'S ROOM HAS
TO BE HAS TO BE KEPT
BELOW 55째
AT ALL TIMES.
-  WHAT'S THE TREATMENT?
- ( sighs )
I ONLY KNOW THAT IT
INVOLVES KEEPING
THE TEMPERATURE LOW
AND INJECTIONS.
MANY INJECTIONS.
THE DOCTOR WAS A FAMOUS
NEUROSURGEON AT U.C.L.A.
THE DOCTOR IS
DOING IT ALONE?
THE DOCTOR ALLOWS ESTELLA
TO ASSIST, NO ONE ELSE.
ESTELLA?
BUT SHE'S AUTISTIC.
THAT'S RIGHT.
Charlie's voice:
MRS. HAYWARD DISAPPEARED
AND ALL WAS QUIET AGAIN.
I RETURNED
TO MY ROOM.
( thrumming continues )
THE LIQUID
HAD CEASED TO DRIP.
I HEARD THE LANDLADY'S
HEAVY FOOTSTEPS
ON THE FLOOR ABOVE ME,
ALONG WITH
HER ISSUING COMMANDS
TO HER MOSTLY
AUTISTIC DAUGHTER.
A DAUGHTER I FOUND
TO HAVE A CERTAIN
FASCINATION AND APPEAL.
( fly buzzing )
HMM.  AUTISTIC HOTTIE.
WOULD THAT BE
AN OXYMORON?
SUDDENLY I WAS
AWARE OF A FEELING
I HAD LONG MISSED.
I WAS DRAWN
TO THE PAGE.
( crows cawing )
- ( heart beating )
- ( exhales )
ESTELLA FASCINATED ME.
SHE WAS LIKE A DREAM THAT
ONE COULDN'T QUITE TOUCH.
DAMN THAT AUTISM.
( birds chirping )
STOP.
- STOP!
- I'M SORRY.  I--
( laughing )
CHAR-LEE.  CHARL-EE.
- I-I-- I--
I LIKE THE SOUND.
- ( goat bleats )
CHAR-LEE.
I LIKE IT TOO...
COMING FROM YOU.
( laughs )
ESTELLA!
I NEED YOU, HONEY!
STAY AWAY
FROM MY DAUGHTER,
MR. BAXTER.
WE MAY BE DESPERATE,
BUT NOT EVERYTHING
- OR OTHERWISE.
- ( stammers )
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
- LIKE HELL YOU DIDN'T.
- LOOK--
MAYBE I DON'T DO
THE BACKGROUND CHECKING
I SHOULD
AND I KNOW THE TYPE
THAT NEEDS WHAT I GOT,
BUT YOU ARE
WAY OUT OF LINE.
- PLEASE, MRS. HAYWARD--
- I WANT YOU OUT OF HERE
IN AN HOUR.
YOU'VE GOT ONE HOUR
BEFORE I CALL THE POLICE.
- IS THAT CLEAR TO YOU?
- YES.
I'M SORRY,
MRS. HAYWARD.
ESTELLA'S AUTISM
INTERESTED ME.  I--
IT'S THE WAY THAT
SOMETIMES SHE'S AFFECTED
AND SOMETIMES--
THANKS TO DR. SHOCKNER.
YOU'VE GOT ONE HOUR.
( heart beating )
( static )
Charlie's voice:
DR. SHOCKNER I HAD
NEVER HEARD,
EXCEPT FOR CERTAIN SOUNDS LIKE
AN AIR-CONDITIONER MECHANISM
AND WHAT SOUNDED LIKE A PUMP.
( hissing, whirring )
I WONDERED FOR A MOMENT
ABOUT WHAT STRANGE ILLNESS
THIS DOCTOR MIGHT HAVE,
AND WHETHER SHOCKNER'S
STUBBORN REFUSAL
OF OUTSIDE AID WERE
THE RESULT OF A RATHER
INSANE ECCENTRICITY.
( heartbeat continues )
THERE IS, I REFLECTED,
AN INFINITE AMOUNT
OF MADNESS IN THE MIND
OF A ONCE POWERFUL
AND WEALTHY PERSON
WHO HAS FALLEN DOWN
IN THE WORLD.
I MIGHT NEVER
HAVE MET DR. SHOCKNER
EXCEPT FOR THE HEART ATTACK
THAT SUDDENLY STRUCK ME
THAT AFTERNOON AS I PREPARED
TO VACATE MY ROOM.
( heartbeat continues )
( thuds )
I KNEW I WAS
IN TROUBLE,
AND I KNEW THERE WAS
NO TIME TO WASTE.
( thuds )
MY BRAIN WAS FRYING.
MY CHEST WAS EXPLODING.
( heartbeat continues )
I REALIZED
I WAS HAVING A STROKE
- AS A COMPANION
TO MY HEART FAILURE.
- ( distorted breathing )
( heartbeat continues )
I REMEMBER THINKING
HOW SURREAL IT ALL WAS.
I THINK,
BUT I CAN'T BE POSITIVE,
THAT I HEARD
HUMMING AS I SAW
THE WHITE LIGHT OF HEAVEN.
OR WAS IT THE GLOW
FROM THE FURNACES OF HELL?
IN THAT MOMENT
IT DIDN'T MATTER.
CHARLIE BAXTER HAD FOUND
HIS MOMENT OF GRACE
AND IT WAS SCORED
BY THE MOST BEAUTIFUL HUMMING
HE HAD EVER HEARD.
( hissing )
AFTER A MOMENT,
I COULD HEAR
WHAT I THINK WAS
THE SOUND OF A FOOTFALL,
THEN THERE CAME AN OPENING
OF THE DOOR IN FRONT OF ME.
( creaking )
A RUSH OF COOL AIR
GREETED ME,
AND THOUGH THE DAY
WAS ONE OF THE HOTTEST
OF THAT SUMMER...
- ( distorted footsteps )
- ...I SHIVERED.
I NOW SAW A TABLE OF BOTTLES
AND MACHINES AND SYRINGES
WHICH MRS. HAYWARD
HAD MENTIONED.
THIS WAS THE LABORATORY
OF THE DOCTOR.
DR. SHOCKNER
MOST CERTAINLY WAS
A PERSON OF EDUCATION,
TASTE AND WEALTH.
( woman speaks )
THEN A FIGURE
APPEARED OVER ME.
THE FIGURE WAS SHORT
BUT EXQUISITELY PROPORTIONED
AND WORE A SOMEWHAT FORMAL
RODEO DRIVE WARDROBE
OF PERFECT CUT AND FIT.
NEVERTHELESS,
AS I SAW DR. SHOCKNER
IN THAT BLAST OF COOL AIR,
I FELT A REPUGNANCE
WHICH NOTHING
IN THE DOCTOR'S LOOK
COULD JUSTIFY.
ONLY SHOCKNER'S
FLAT ALABASTER COMPLEXION
AND COLDNESS OF TOUCH
COULD HAVE EXPLAINED
WHAT I WAS FEELING.
AND EVEN THESE THINGS SHOULD
HAVE BEEN EXPLAINED AWAY,
BUT MY LOGIC WOULDN'T.
IT COULDN'T.
AND MY FEAR CUT RIGHT
THROUGH THE PAIN OF DYING.
MY REPUGNANCE
WAS SOON FORGOTTEN
AS I WAS SWALLOWED
INTO A PEACEFUL BLACKNESS.
( electricity crackling )
HONESTLY,
DESPITE MY IRRATIONAL FEAR,
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
IN ADMIRATION
OF THE SURGEON'S GREAT SKILL.
WHAT ARE YOU NOW?
Mrs. Hayward:
STAY AWAY FROM MY
DAUGHTER, MR. BAXTER.
Charlie:
WHO AM I?
( distorted humming )
THE DOCTOR CLEARLY
UNDERSTOOD MY NEED
AND ADMINISTERED TREATMENT
WITH A MASTER'S TOUCH,
ALL THE WHILE REASSURING ME
IN A FINELY MODULATED
THOUGH ODDLY DEAD
AND TONELESS VOICE
THAT THE DOCTOR WAS
THE SWORN ENEMY OF DEATH.
AND HORRORS ASIDE,
MY LIFE WAS SAVED.
( soft whirring )
WHEN I AWOKE
NINE HOURS LATER,
I FOUND MYSELF
IN MY ROOM...
WITH DR. SHOCKNER.
( weakly )
DOCTOR.
( groans )
( hoarsely )
I LIKED YOUR SCRIPT...
ESPECIALLY ABOUT
THE MAD DOCTOR.
IT'S JUST A SCRIPT.
IT'S TRUE.
( clicks tongue )
I AM CONSIDERED
QUITE MAD BY MOST...
( whispers )
ESPECIALLY OTHER DOCTORS.
WELL...
I'LL VOUCH FOR YOU.
( crows cawing )
HOW DOES IT END,
YOUR SCRIPT?
I DON'T KNOW.
HAVE ANY IDEAS?
ANY IDEAS?
I AM ONE OF THOSE
WITH A COLD, CLINICAL MIND.
NO SENTIMENTALITY.
SOUNDS LIKE AN AGENT.
( chuckling )
DO YOU MIND GETTING
IDEAS FROM OTHERS?
NOT WHEN THEY'VE
SAVED MY LIFE.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
I THINK YOUR VILLAIN
NEEDS MORE HISTORY.
THE DOCTOR'S
NOT A VILLAIN.
REALLY?
IT READS
THAT WAY TO ME.
MISUNDERSTOOD.
ANYWAY, IT'S JUST
A FIRST DRAFT.
THERE'S ROOM
FOR CHANGE THEN?
FOR THE STORY
OF THIS MAD DOCTOR
TO GO IN ANOTHER
DIRECTION?
SURE.
REWRITES.
( chuckles )
FUN.
( exhales )
WHAT DID YOU HAVE
IN MIND, DOCTOR?
AS I WAS SAYING,
THE DOCTOR NEEDS
MORE HISTORY.
SAY THIS DOCTOR,
WHO WAS BRILLIANT
BEYOND WORDS,
WAS SUDDENLY STRICKEN
WITH A RARE FATAL DISEASE.
SHE COULDN'T ACCEPT
IMPENDING DEATH SO--
"SHE"?
MY MAD DOCTOR IS MALE.
DID I SAY "SHE"?
I'M SORRY.
I MEANT "HE."
BUT I LIKE
THE SEX CHANGE.
- DO YOU?
- VERY MUCH.
AS I SAID,
SHE COULDN'T ACCEPT DEATH.
SHE WAS
A GREAT SURGEON,
A BRILLIANT SURGEON.
SHE WAS A LIFE-GIVER
WHEN THERE WAS NO HOPE.
SHE HAD THE SKILLS
AND THE TALENTS OF GOD.
SO SHE WAS...
BIG INTO HER EGO AND...
SHE COULDN'T ACCEPT
NOT BEING ABLE
TO SAVE HER OWN LIFE,
HER OWN WORTHY LIFE,
WHEN SHE HAD SAVED
SO MANY LESS VALUABLE,
MY OWN INCLUDED.
IN A SENSE, YES.
I LIKE IT.
SO THIS BRILLIANT DOCTOR
HAD TO SAVE HERSELF.
SHE KNEW SHE COULD DO IT
BEFORE TIME WAS OUT.
SHE SOON HAD SUNK
HER FORTUNE
AND LOST ALL HER FRIENDS
IN A YEAR
OF BIZARRE EXPERIMENTS
DEVOTED TO CHEATING DEATH.
Charlie's voice:
SOMETHING OF THE BENEVOLENT
FANATIC
SEEMED TO RESIDE
WITHIN HER,
AND SHE RAMBLED ON
ALMOST GARRULOUSLY.
EVIDENTLY SHE FOUND
THE SOCIETY OF A WELL-BORN,
WELL-EDUCATED WOMAN
A RARE NOVELTY
IN THIS SHALLOW WORLD
CALLED MALIBU,
AND WAS MOVED TO MEMORIES
OF BETTER DAYS
AT GRAND UNIVERSITIES
AND WORLD-RENOWNED
MEDICAL CLINICS.
HER VOICE, IF QUEER,
WAS AT LEAST SOOTHING.
SHE SOUGHT TO DISTRACT MY MIND
FROM MY OWN BRUSH WITH DEATH
BY SPEAKING OF HER THEORIES
AND EXPERIMENTS.
AND I REMEMBER
HER TACTFULLY CONSOLING ME
ABOUT MY WEAK HEART
BY INSISTING THAT
WILL AND CONSCIOUSNESS
ARE STRONGER
THAN ORGANIC LIFE ITSELF,
SO THAT IF A BODY IS
ESSENTIALLY HEALTHY
EXCEPT IN THE AREA
OF DISEASE,
AND THAT THE HEALTHY ORGANS
AND BONE AND TISSUE
ARE CAREFULLY PRESERVED,
IT MAY, THROUGH SCIENTIFIC
ENHANCEMENT,
RETAIN A KIND OF ANIMATION
DESPITE THE MOST SERIOUS
IMPAIRMENTS, DEFECTS,
OR EVEN ABSENCES
OF MAJOR ORGANS.
( heart beating )
SHE MIGHT,
SHE HALF-JOKED,
SOME DAY
TEACH ME TO LIVE--
OR AT LEAST TO POSSESS
SOME KIND OF CONSCIOUS
EXISTENCE
WITHOUT ANY HEART AT ALL.
WHAT?
NO HEART AT ALL?
YOU MEAN...
WITH AN ARTIFICIAL HEART
OR SOME KIND
OF A MACHINE?
NO.
WITHOUT ANY PUMP.
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE,
ISN'T IT?
DEFYING THE LAWS
OF PHYSICS
OR GOD OR SOMETHING.
OR SOMETHING, YES.
THAT WOULD BE IT.
IS THIS TOO MUCH
FOR YOUR SCREENPLAY?
I DON'T KNOW
IF THE AUDIENCE CAN
SUSPEND THEIR DISBELIEF.
I'M NOT SURE I CAN.
I KNOW THE STUDIOS
WOULDN'T.
( guffaws )
REALLY?
I WASN'T AWARE THAT
"NIGHT OF THE LIVING DEAD"
WAS A DOCUMENTARY.
TELL ME ALL OF IT.
I'M SORRY
I INTERRUPTED.
Charlie's voice:
FOR HER PART, SHE WAS AFFLICTED
WITH A COMPLICATION
OF DISEASES
REQUIRING
A VERY EXACT REGIMEN,
WHICH INCLUDED
CONSTANT COLD.
IT WAS THEN I NOTICED
THE TEMPERATURE IN MY ROOM.
IT WAS COLD.
I NOTICED THE AIR CONDITIONER
IN MY ROOM GOING FULL POWER.
FUNNY, I HADN'T
NOTICED IT BEFORE.
SHE SAID ANY MARKED RISE
IN TEMPERATURE MIGHT,
IF PROLONGED,
AFFECT HER FATALLY;
AND THE COLDNESS
OF HER ROOM--
SOME 55째
OR 56째 FAHRENHEIT--
- HER AIR CONDITIONER HAD
ADDITIONAL BATTERIES...
- ( Shockner coughing )
...AND AN AIR-CLEANING PUMP.
THAT WAS THE SOUND
I HAD HEARD IN MY OWN ROOM.
( wheezes )
( coughing continues )
( weakly )
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I JUST NEED TO REST...
( whispers )
IN MY ROOM.
( inhales sharply, thuds )
- ( inhales sharply )
- AM I ALL RIGHT?
( sighs )
YOU MEAN, SHOULD YOU
GO TO THE HOSPITAL?
- ( inhales sharply )
- YES.
ONLY IF YOU WANT TO DIE.
THEN I'M OKAY?
( swallows )
FOR REAL?
YOU'RE FINE.
JUST REST.
STAY IN BED.
DO NOT LET
THE SUNLIGHT IN.
( exhales )
I'LL COME TO SEE YOU
IN THE AFTERNOON.
OKAY.
YOU'RE THE DOCTOR.
I MEAN IT, CHARLIE.
DO NOT LEAVE THIS ROOM.
ALL RIGHT,
BUT MRS. HAYWARD IS
GONNA BE PISSED.
SHE EVICTED ME.
I'VE ADDRESSED IT.
YOU'RE FREE TO STAY
UNTIL YOU'RE FULLY RECOVERED.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
I JUST REMINDED HER
OF THE HIGH COST
OF LIABILITY LAWSUITS.
GOOD NIGHT, CHARLIE.
GOOD NIGHT.
THANK YOU.
( whispers )
OH, IT'S MY PLEASURE.
NICE TO HAVE
A COMPANION.
( pump hissing )
( ascending footsteps )
Charlie's voice:
RELIEVED OF MY HEART FAILURE
IN AN INCREDIBLY SHORT TIME,
I FELL ASLEEP,
A DISCIPLE AND DEVOTEE
OF THE GIFTED RECLUSE.
( knocks on door )
COME IN.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
I'VE BEEN BETTER,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
THANKS FOR
LETTING ME STAY.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU.
THE DOCTOR SAID
THAT YOU'LL BE WEAK
FOR A FEW MORE WEEKS.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN
RUN OVER BY A TRUCK.
SHE SAID TO MAKE SURE THAT
YOU HAVE PLENTY OF REST,
THAT YOU EAT A GOOD MEAL.
SHE MADE THIS HERSELF.
YEAH, REST.
REST-- REST AND,
UH, FOOD.  YEAH.
( stammers )
THE... DOCTOR--
DOCTOR KNOWS.
YEAH, THE DOCTOR KNOWS.
DOCTOR KNOWS.  DOCTOR KNOWS.
THAT-- THAT'S RIGHT.
YES, THE DOCTOR KNOWS.
THANKS.
WELL, IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU WANT, LET US KNOW.
- COME ON, ESTELLA.
- OH YEAH, MAMA, YEAH.
I CAN-- I CAN--
I CAN, UH--
I CAN FEED HIM, YEAH.
'CAUSE-'CAUSE--
YEAH, HE-- HE MUST EAT.
YEAH, AND I CAN-- I CAN--
I CAN FEED HIM, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.  SLOWLY.
MR. BAXTER'S SYSTEM
MAY NOT BE QUITE RIGHT YET.
OH YEAH, MAMA,
I-- I KNOW, I KNOW.
I-- I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I KNOW.
- ( whispers )
I KNOW.  I-- YEAH.
- I'LL BE BACK IN A BIT...
- ( mutters )
- ...TO SEE ON YOU.
( whirring, clicking )
WHAT'S ON THE MENU?
IT SMELLS.
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
UH, YEAH.
UH, THE, UH...
DOCTOR'S, UH, YEAH,
RECIPE.  YEAH.
YOU MEAN THE DOCTOR'S
A GOURMET COOK TOO?
- YEAH.
- ( grunts )
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
MMM.
( chuckling )
HOSPITAL FOOD.
- ( gags )
- OH OH OH NO.  OH NO.
( coughing )
OH NO.
YEAH, YOU MUST--
YOU MUST DRINK IT ALL.
- YEAH, UH UH,
DRINK IT ALL.
- MMM.
- YEAH.
- I CAN'T.
NO.
PLEASE?
LET'S TRY SOME
OF THE PASTE FIRST
THEN I'LL
CHASE IT WITH A SIP.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
( mutters )
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
YEAH.
I'LL TAKE THE SPOON.
( gags )
( spits, coughing )
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.  OKAY.
I'M SORRY,
BUT THAT'S NASTY.
- ( moans )
- ( muttering )
AAAAAAAH.
( moans )
I CAN'T.
( sighs ) I CAN'T.
Y-Y-Y-YOU MUST.
YOU MUST, OR-- OR YOU'LL--
YOU'LL GET SICKER--
SICKER,
CHAR-LEE, CHAR-LEE.
YEAH, SICKER.
SICKER, CHAR-LEE.
OKAY.  OKAY.
YOU ANSWER ONE
OF MY QUESTIONS,
I'LL TAKE A BITE
AND THEN A SIP.
OKAY?
I ASK A QUESTION.
AND THEN YOU ANSWER
AND THEN I TAKE A BITE.
- OKAY?
- IT'S A GAME SHOW!
ALL RIGHT,
A GAME SHOW!
- YEAH, OKAY.
A GAME SHOW, YEAH.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
Charlie's voice:
ESTELLA, AS BEST SHE COULD
AND COLORED BY HER DEEPLY
INNER STATE OF REALITY,
ANSWERED MY QUESTIONS.
WHAT I PIECED TOGETHER
WAS SHOCKNER CAME TO LIVE
IN THE HOUSE
TWO YEARS EARLIER.
THOUGH LOW ON FUNDS,
THE DOCTOR PAID
FOR "SPECIAL SERVICES"
WHICH INVOLVED INSTALLING
THE CUSTOM AIR CONDITIONING
AND THE RUNNING OF ERRANDS
TO PURCHASE HER NEEDS.
SHE WAS A QUIET
IF ODD TENANT,
BUT SHE PAID WELL
AND ON TIME.
EVERYTHING WAS GOOD
UNTIL ONE DAY LAST AUGUST.
THE HORROR
OF HORRORS CAME
WITH SURPRISING
SUDDENNESS.
ON THAT HOT SUMMER DAY,
THE AIR CONDITIONER
BROKE DOWN,
SO THAT WITHIN MINUTES
THE DOCTOR'S ROOM
HAD WARMED TO ABOVE 55째.
( no dialogue )
ESTELLA AND HER MOTHER
WERE OUTSIDE.
DR. SHOCKNER STAGGERED
DOWN THE STAIRS.
( crows cawing )
MRS. HAYWARD WORKED
DESPERATELY TO HELP HER UP,
BUT SHE INSTEAD
PLEADED FOR ICE.
MRS. HAYWARD DID
AS SHE WAS TOLD,
RUNNING INTO THE KITCHEN
TO GET ALL THE ICE
IN THE FREEZER.
IT WAS THEN
THAT ESTELLA FOUND
SOMETHING ON THE FLOOR.
( thunder crashes )
THE GOOD DOCTOR'S
INDEX FINGER.
IT HAD ROTTED AND FALLEN OFF
IN THE STRUGGLE.
AS ESTELLA
CONTINUED HER TALE,
IT'S CREEPY HORROR
WAS BEYOND BELIEF.
ESTELLA TOOK
THE FINGER OUT TO THE GARDEN
AND BURIED IT THERE.
SHE SAID SHE DID IT
BECAUSE A NEW ONE WOULD GROW
AND SHE WOULD SURPRISE
THE DOCTOR WITH HER CROP.
( fly buzzes )
( whirring )
DRINK.
ONE MORE QUESTION.
THOSE CUTS ON YOUR NECK,
- THERE.
- UH, THE...
THE DOCTOR.
YEAH, THE DOCTOR.  THE DOCTOR.
WHY DID SHE DO IT?
YEAH, UH, MAMA MADE HER.
YEAH, MAMA MADE HER.  YEAH.
MADE HER?  HOW?
UH, MAMA SAID--
UH, MAMA SAID IF-IF--
IF SHE DIDN'T FIX ME--
YEAH, IF SHE DIDN'T FIX ME,
THAT-- UH, THAT-THAT--
THAT SHE'D TELL ON HER.
THE FIXING,
SHE DID GOOD?
YEAH, UH, UH,
MAMA WANTS
MORE FIXING, YEAH.
MAMA WANTS MORE FIXING.
YEAH, SHE WANTS
MORE FIXING.
- BUT-BUT-- BUT THE-- BUT--
- BUT WHAT?
UH, BUT THE, UH--
THE DOCTOR--
THE DOCTOR SAYS IT'S, UH--
IT'S-IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
YEAH, IT'S JUST TOO--
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.  YEAH.
SO THE FIXING STOPPED?
YEAH.  NO NO.
MAMA'S SAID--
MAMA SAID THAT--
THAT-- THAT--
THAT IF-IF--
IF THE FIXING
DIDN'T KEEP ON, THEN--
THEN SHE WOULD...
SHE WOULD DESTROY
HER MACHINE AND-AND--
AND THAT SHE WOULD--
SHE WOULD BURN IN HELL.
YEAH, BURN IN HELL.
BURN IN HELL.
YEAH, LET HER
JUST BURN IN HELL.
( stammers )
AND THAT SHE KNEW
WHAT SHE WAS.  YEAH.
AND THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT SHE--
SHE WAS VERY MAD.
SHE WAS-- SHE VERY MAD.
YEAH, UH-HUH.
- YEAH, SHE WAS MAD
WHEN SHE SAID THAT.
- SO IS SHE STILL FIXING?
YEAH...
OH YEAH.
( grunts )
MY COMPLIMENTS
TO THE CHEF.
PICK UP THE TRAY,
ESTELLA.
LET'S GO.
I-- I-- I--
I LIKED
THE QUESTION-ANSWER GAME.
- ESTELLA!
- YEAH, OKAY.
- ( grunting )
- ( knocks on door )
YOU-- YOU OKAY?
( chair clatters )
I HEARD YOU WERE SICK.
DID THE DOCTOR
TREAT YOU?
( breathing heavily )
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
( crying )
I WAS PROMISED.
I PAID MY... DEPOSIT.
- DEPOSIT FOR WHAT?
- I WAS PATIENT.
- IT WAS MY TURN.
- TURN FOR WHAT?
THE DOCTOR'S METHOD!
YOU--
LOOK...
I KEPT HER PRESERVED
DOWN IN THE STORAGE ROOM,
IN THE FREEZER.
SHE'S THERE, WAITING.
I'M NOT INVOLVED.
I PAID
EVERY LAST PENNY I HAD
TO MRS. HAYWARD AND THE DOCTOR
TO BRING HER BACK!
- BRING WHO BACK?
- MY WIFE.
- WIFE?
- YES, MY WIFE!
SHE LIVED HERE WITH ME...
BEFORE I KILLED HER.
I WAS DRUNK.
WE WEREN'T GETTING ALONG.
( cries )
I KILLED HER.
I STABBED HER
TO DEATH.
BUT I LOVED HER.
I STILL DO.
AND I MISS HER
AND I WANT HER BACK.
( sobbing )
BUT SHE'S DEAD.
SHE'S FROZEN...
IN MRS. HAYWARD'S FREEZER.
Charlie's voice:
DELTOID SPUN A TALE
MORE HORRIBLE
WITH EACH SENTENCE.
HE AND HIS WIFE HAD
MOVED IN SIX MONTHS AGO.
THEIR LIVES HAD TAKEN
A DEEP, DARK DIVE.
THERE WAS BLAMING
AND FIGHTING.
THERE WAS LIQUOR.
THEN IT ALL
BLEW UP ONE NIGHT
AND DELTOID TOOK
HIS DRAWING PEN
AND DROVE IT
INTO HIS WIFE'S THROAT.
HE RAN TO MRS. HAYWARD
AND WANTED HER
TO CALL THE POLICE.
TO HIS SURPRISE,
MRS. HAYWARD OFFERED
AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT
COURSE OF ACTION.
IF DELTOID WOULD
PAY HER DOUBLE HIS RENT
AND KEEP HIS MOUTH SHUT,
SHE WOULD SEE
IF THE DOCTOR WOULD BRING
HIS WIFE BACK TO LIFE.
SHE EXPLAINED
TO THIS DESPERATE
AND DISTRAUGHT MAN
THAT THE DOCTOR HAD
DONE THIS ONCE BEFORE
AND SHE HAD GREAT SKILL.
MRS. HAYWARD SAID THIS
TO A BROKEN MAN,
A MAN THAT WAS EASY PREY
FOR HER WILD SCHEME.
SO BOLSTERED BY
THIS HOPE OF UNDOING
HIS HEINOUS ATROCITY,
SHE AND DELTOID PUT
HIS WIFE IN THE FREEZER,
BESIDE THE OTHER
FROZEN MEAT.
SHE TOLD DELTOID
HE HAD TO BE PATIENT,
THAT THE DOCTOR WOULD GET
TO HIS WIFE IN TIME.
SHE WOULD BE NEXT.
WHAT DO I DO?
HOPE.
HOPE?
( laughing )
HOPE.
NOW THERE'S A GOOD WORD.
Charlie's voice:
NO ONE EVER SAW
ARNOLD DELTOID ALIVE AGAIN.
WHEN HE CAME TO BE MISSED--
AND THIS WOULD TAKE WEEKS--
ESTELLA WOULD FIND HIM
LYING IN THE FREEZER
WITH HIS DEAD WIFE.
HE SLIT HIS WRISTS
AND WRAPPED HIS BLOODY PAWS
AROUND HIS LOVING WIFE.
THERE WAS AN INCREASING
AND UNEXPLAINED ATMOSPHERE
OF EVIL AND HORROR
THAT SEEMED TO RISE
AROUND THE HAYWARD HOUSE.
THE WHOLE HOUSE,
AS I'VE SAID,
HAD A MUSTY ODOR.
BUT THE SMELL
THIS DAY WAS WORSE.
AND IN SPITE OF ALL
THE DEODORIZER AND INCENSE,
AND THE PUNGENT
CLEANING CHEMICALS,
IT WOULD BE A SMELL
THAT WOULD NEVER BE MASKED.
FIENDISH THINGS WERE
IN THE AIR.
SO STRONG WAS
THE PUNGENT PRESENCE OF EVIL
THAT BELIEVERS
WOULD BE REACHING WILDLY
FOR THE BEADS
OF THEIR ROSARIES.
A LESS ADVENTURESOME SOUL
WOULD HAVE LONG FLED,
SCREAMING AND MAD-EYED.
THERE WAS NO SOUND
WITHIN THE GREAT HOUSE,
EXCEPT A NAMELESS
SORT OF SLOW, THICK DRIPPING.
( door opens )
THE SOUNDS WERE
OF UTTER TURMOIL.
AND ABOVE THE CLATTERING
AND SLAMMING OF ODD VOICES,
I HEARD A WOMAN PRAYING
IN A DESPERATE PLEA.
IT WAS THE DOCTOR.
WE COULD HEAR
A WILD THRASHING
WITHIN THE DOCTOR'S ROOM
AND A HYSTERICAL VOICE
CROAKING,
"THE COLD.  THE COLD."
- ( Shockner moaning )
- HER AIR CONDITIONING FAILED.
SHE NEEDS HELP!
LISTEN TO HER!
IT'S A PITY.
Charlie's voice:
AS I TRIED TO WALK,
I WAS SUDDENLY AWARE
OF HOW WARM IT WAS
IN THE HALL.
IT MADE ME DIZZY AND WEAK
AND SICK TO MY STOMACH.
I NEEDED THE COLD.
THE DOCTOR'S
RAGE AND FEAR,
SWELLING
TO GROTESQUE PROPORTIONS,
SEEMED LIKELY
TO SHATTER WHAT REMAINED
OF HER FAILING PHYSIQUE.
AND ONCE A SPASM CAUSED HER
TO CLAP HER HANDS
TO HER EYES
TO SHIELD THEM...
OR KEEP THEM
FROM FALLING OUT.
SHE GROPED HER WAY
DOWN THE HALL TOWARD ME
AS IF BLIND
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THE DOCTOR'S STENCH
WAS OVER-POWERING.
IT WAS SO STRONG
AS TO SUCK THE OXYGEN
OUT OF THE AIR.
I FELT SUFFOCATED
AND SMOTHERED BY IT.
AGAINST ALL
MY SCREAMING INSTINCTS,
I REACHED OUT
TO THIS POOR WOMAN.
( labored breathing )
AS THE MINUTES PASSED
I OBSERVED WITH REGRET
THAT MY NEW FRIEND
WAS INDEED SLOWLY,
BUT UNMISTAKABLY
LOOSING GROUND
PHYSICALLY.
THE LIVID ASPECT
OF HER BEING WAS INTENSIFIED.
HER VOICE BECAME
MORE HOLLOW AND INDISTINCT.
HER GRACEFUL MOTIONS WERE
LESS PERFECTLY COORDINATED.
AND HER MIND AND WILL
DISPLAYED LESS RESILIENCE
AND INITIATIVE.
( hoarsely )
DO I DISGUST YOU?
- NO.
- SHE WAS AWARE
OF THIS SAD CHANGE
AND LITTLE BY LITTLE
HER EXPRESSION AND CONVERSATION
BOTH TOOK ON A GRUESOME IRONY
WHICH RESTORED IN ME...
NOT EXACTLY.
...SOMETHING
OF THE SUBTLE REPULSION
I HAD ORIGINALLY FELT.
MMM.  IT'S THE SMELL.
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT.
I WAS BEAUTIFUL.
I CAN SEE THAT.
- ( sizzling )
- ( labored breathing )
IT'S...
IT'S TIME FOR--
FOR YOU TO TAKE
YOUR MEDS.
YOU HAVE A CHOICE,
CHARLIE.
A CHOICE?
A CHOICE.
ONE I DID NOT HAVE.
TELL ME
ABOUT MY CHOICE...
AND YOURS.
Charlie's voice:
I LISTENED, ADDICTED
TO HER EVERY WORD.
( Shockner speaking )
Charlie's voice:
SHE TOLD OF SECRET RESEARCHES
AND ALMOST GHASTLY RESULTS.
IT SEEMS THAT SHE DID NOT
SCORN THE INCANTATIONS
OF THE WITCHES
AND THE BLACK ARTS
WITH REGARD
TO LIFE AND DEATH,
SINCE SHE BELIEVED
THESE CRYPTIC ARTS
CONTAINED RARE
PSYCHOLOGICAL STIMULI
WHICH MIGHT CONCEIVABLY
HAVE HEALING EFFECTS
ON THE NERVOUS SYSTEM
IN WHICH ORGANIC LIFE HAD DIED.
I WAS MOVED BY HER ACCOUNT
OF THE AGED DR. TORRES
OF VALENCIA, SPAIN,
WHO HAD SHARED
HIS EARLIER EXPERIMENTS
AND NURSED DR. SHOCKNER
THROUGH A GREAT ILLNESS
18 YEARS BEFORE,
AND WHERE HER
PRESENT DISORDERS BEGAN.
...BEYOND MY TIME...
NO SOONER HAD
DR. TORRES SAVE HIS COLLEAGUE
THAT HE HIMSELF DIED
A GRIM DEATH IN A FIRE.
THE DOCTOR MADE IT
WHISPERINGLY CLEAR--
THOUGH NOT IN DETAIL--
THAT THE METHODS
TORRES USED TO HEAL
HAD EXTRAORDINARY
INVOLVING TECHNIQUES
AND PROCESSES NOT WELCOMED
BY THE CONSERVATIVE WORLD
OF MODERN MEDICINE.
( coughing )
- MRS. HAYWARD!  HELP!
- ...FOR HER TO CALL
THE PARAMEDICS.
-  AS I LISTENED AT THE DOOR...
- WE NEED HELP!
...I COULD HEAR
THE LANDLADY HUMMING
LIKE A CRAZY LOON.
- ( coughing continues )
- WE NEED HELP!
A KIND OF GROWING HORROR
SEEMED TO POSSESS HER.
CHARLIE!
SHE TALKED
ABOUT DEATH INCESSANTLY,
BUT LAUGHED HOLLOWLY
AT SUCH THINGS AS BURIAL
OR FUNERAL ARRANGEMENTS.
- YOU NEED HELP.
- ( labored breathing )
YOU NEED HELP.
LET ME CALL THE PARAMEDICS.
THERE WAS SOME BITTER IRONY
IN THOSE MATTERS.
ALL IN ALL,
SHE BECAME A DISCONCERTING
- AND EVEN GRUESOME
COMPANION.
- PLEASE.
YET MY GRATITUDE
FOR HER SAVING MY LIFE
MADE IT IMPOSSIBLE
TO ABANDON HER.
OKAY.
BUT FIRST, I NEED
TO WRITE SOMETHING.
OKAY, TAKE--
TAKE YOUR TABLET NOW.
( labored breathing )
( coughing )
SHE HAD WRAPPED
THE SCARF IN A WAY
THAT HER EYES WERE HIDDEN
FROM MY VIEW.
I NEVER SAW
HER EYES AGAIN.
THE FIRST THING I NOTICED
WAS THE COLDNESS
OF THE ROOM WAS GONE.
THE SECOND THING I NOTICED
WAS IT WAS QUIET.
THE AIR HAD
BEEN TURNED OFF.
WHAT WAS, OR HAD BEEN,
ON THE BED I CAN'T
AND DARE NOT SAY HERE.
IT WAS HIDEOUS AND IT
WOULD HAUNT ME FOREVER.
A CLAW-LIKE FINGER
POINTED ME TO THE TABLET.
SOMETHING WAS
SCRAWLED IN PEN,
IN AN AWFUL,
FRANTIC HANDWRITING
ON A PIECE OF PAPER
HIDEOUSLY SMEARED
WITH OOZING ROT
AS THOUGH BY THE VERY CLAW
THAT TRACED
THE HURRIED LAST WORDS.
IT WAS THE UTTER END
OF DR. SHOCKNER.
Shockner's voice:
"THE END IS HERE.
NO MORE THE SMELL
OF AMMONIA
AND THE DESPERATE NEED
OF UNUSUALLY COOL AIR.
IT'S GROWING WARMER
EVERY MINUTE
AND THE TISSUES CAN'T LAST.
THERE WAS AND IS
A GRADUAL, INEVITABLE
DETERIORATION.
DR. TORRES KNEW THIS.
HE COULDN'T STAND
WHAT HE HAD CREATED IN ME.
FOR YOU SEE,
I DIED THAT TIME,
127 YEARS AGO."
- ( engine revs )
- ( gate rattles )
( rattles )
( gate rattles )
Shockner's voice:
"NOW IT PASSES TO YOU, CHARLIE.
THE SECRETS.
HOW FAR WOULD YOU GO
TO REMAIN
AMONG THE LIVING?"
( bangs )
Charlie's voice:
YOU ASKED ME TO EXPLAIN
WHY I'M AFRAID
OF A DRAFT OF COOL AIR,
WHY I SHIVER MORE THAN OTHERS
WHEN I ENTER A COLD ROOM,
WHY I SEEM SICK AND SCARED
WHEN THE CHILL OF EVENING
CREEPS THROUGH THE HEAT
OF A MILD AUTUMN DAY.
THERE ARE THOSE WHO SAY
I RESPOND TO COLD
LIKE SOME DO
TO A BAD SMELL,
AND I'M THE LAST
TO DENY THE IMPRESSION.
MORE AND MORE I FEEL DRAWN
TO THE COOLNESS.
MORE AND MORE I FEAR
I WILL NEED THE COOL AIR.
A HAUNTING REMINDER
OF MY VULNERABILITY.
WHAT I WILL DO IS TO RELATE
THE MOST HORRIBLE CIRCUMSTANCES
I HAVE EVER EXPERIENCED
AND LEAVE IT TO YOU
TO JUDGE WHETHER OR NOT
THIS FORMS A SUITABLE
EXPLANATION OF MY WEIRDNESS
AND MY RECENT MOVIE SUCCESS.
IT WAS A CIRCUMSTANCE
THAT BROKE MY WRITER'S BLOCK.
IT MADE ME UNDERSTAND
I HAD TO DIE
TO LIVE AGAIN.
( eerie music playing )
- ( girl screams )
- ( gunshot )
( gunshot )
( growls )
( thunder crashes )
( high-pitched tone,
increasing )