#Free Blood - Never Hear Surf Music Again#
# There must be some fucking chemical
# Chemical in your brain
# That makes us different
from animals
# Makes us all the same
# Take it if it makes you numb
# Take it if it makes you come
# Take it if it makes you make it...
- Hello?
- Are you coming to the party tonight?
- Yeah, totally. Where is that?
- 20 miles outside to the lake.
- Just for the...
- What?
I can't... I can't hear you.
- It's a really big...
- I'm gonna... fucking iPhones!
# Take it if it makes you numb
# Take it if it makes you come
# Take it if it makes you...
127 Seconds... 126 Seconds...
This is insane!
Think... think...
Useless!
Help!... Help!
Kristi!
#Bill Withers - Lovely Day#
# When I wake up in the morning, love
# And the sunlight hurts my eyes
# And something without warning, love
# Bears heavy on my mind
# Then I look at you
# And the world's alright with me
# Just one look at you
# And I know it's gonna be
# A lovely day
Lovely day, lovely day, lovely...
Good afternoon.
We have Darren Golston, here...
...he tells about his crappy
cellphone reception.
Yeah, ever since i get the iPhone,
i can never seem get service anymore.
AT&T or Verizon?
AT&T.
I love this guy.
Hey, can I say "hi"
to my mom and dad?
Mom and dad?
Mustn't forget mom and dad, right Darren?
I love you with all my heart.
I'm sorry, i'm always in a deadzone.
Can you hear me now?
I love you.
Help me!
This video was produced
for parody purposes only...
...in no way did the filmmakers
intend to make light of...
...Aron Ralston's struggle in
Blue John Canyon.