There is no darkness without light,
and yet there is light
without darkness.
I have both within me.
Flyby to Ghost,
you're about 20 miles
out from target.
There are no bogies
visible from above.
Roger that, Flyby.
So tell me, is there any good
restaurants around here?
Nobody told me Movie
Star can't cook.
Yeah, that's a negative on
the restaurants, Ghost.
Ghost, this is Director Styles.
Reaper-1 is now online.
We're maintaining a safe and
invisible distance to target.
We're getting a good image of
what's going on down there.
Ready to bring Hellfire
down on your command.
Look, I'm sorry about
cutting your team.
This is a mission we
need to keep quiet.
You're operating as
a two-man team now.
Target name: Abu Alwaki Khan.
The ground-branch comedians
called him Abu Normal.
Your primary target
remains Abdul Normal.
We have new information
on the secondary target,
an arms dealer.
Hey, Ghost.
We gotta go.
Our secondary target is
a Chicom arms dealer,
an Islamic fundamentalist who
finances terrorist activities.
We go by call signs.
We never know a team
member's real name.
You're now five miles out, Ghost.
Switching to radio silence.
Over and out.
I don't feel good about
them splintering our team.
We a 12-man team, minimum of six.
We down to fucking two
'cause they had to go kill
some fucking high-value
target up in the north
50 minutes from here.
What the fuck is that?
Well, it's a small camp.
VICD confirmed target's
there, that right?
UAV followed him in there
about 45 minutes ago.
He's got a protection
detail of three shooters.
We've had eyes on that
target ever since,
and there's been nobody
in and nobody out.
Since when a guy like that
got three security detail?
He got 15 motherfuckers in there
with guns and you know it.
This intel is fucked up.
Well, we don't know
how many shooters
he could have already
in that building.
Look, before we stick
our dick in anything,
we're gonna sneak up and take
a good look before we commit.
Here's to dead enemies
and live friends
and all y'all
motherfuckers going home.
Roger that.
Let me tack up.
How it look out there?
Looks good. Good conditions, bro.
- Nice and quiet?
- Yeah, I like it.
I wonder how much pussy he get.
Do you think he get
more than, like,
Osama bin Laden got?
I'm... I'm gonna be
sorry to kill his ass.
A lot of virgins are
gonna be happy though.
- That's true, once he go up there.
- Yeah.
Okay. Take a look at this here.
That's our route in.
Let's get positioned in this building
here, but we gotta clear this first
before we get into the
hornets' nest over here.
Try to figure out...
we make a decision in here.
Oh, fuck me, man.
What you got?
Ghost to nest, ghost to nest,
you're getting too
close, man, back off.
You're gonna give my position away.
Roger that, Ghost.
Once Abu Normal is
confirmed to be in there,
you can take him out,
but wait for my word.
Standing by. Over and out.
We got the chickenshit
sandwich now, boy.
Well, let's go get this bastard.
Come on.
Clear.
Whoa. Thank you, bro.
Looks good. Compound clear.
Okay, Ghost, got
eyes on, settled in.
You're good to go.
Oh. Check that. We got a rover.
Be advised: one rover.
Okay, that rover... he is up.
He's on top.
Looks like he's walking
off into the woods, bro.
You're clear. Go
ahead, make your move.
Looking good. Six is clear.
Movie Star, can you see
anything inside the hooch?
Negative. Hang on.
I see four.
Four Haj... check that,
check that, six...
six Hajis, all got AKs.
Ghost, a man in a white coat...
could be our second target.
Okay, confirmation
on target, stand by.
Ghost to nest, visual
confirmation on the target.
They're using human
shields. No joy, no joy.
This is Nest. We have a
lock on your position.
We have orders to initiate
Hellfire now. Stand down.
I repeat, they're
using human shields.
No joy, no joy!
Okay, be advised, our
rover is returning.
He's 30 yards out.
You're gonna have to
take this guy out.
I can't crack him there.
He'll create a hornets' nest.
You've got him. He's 10 yards out.
10 yards. He's on your six.
Five, four,
three, two...
two steps. He's there.
I'm going in now,
repeat, going in now.
On my way to you.
I'm on my way to you.
Move.
Call off the strike. Abu Normal's
on the move. Call off the strike.
- We've got women and children in here.
- Papa! Papi!
Target locked, sequence initiated.
Direct hit on Abu Normal.
No joy on the secondary target.
Call off the air-strike!
We've got kids in here!
Negative, Ghost.
Hellfire is initiated.
Come with me! We gotta
get out of here!
Flyby, this is command.
We have a direct hit.
Ghost! Ghost, how you doing?
It's my right... right side.
Check the girl.
- Nothing's broke.
- Check the girl.
Hey. You okay?
She's not moving.
Some things never change.
Mya, do you have the keys?
You hungry? Come here.
Don't tell me I lost them again.
- Hey.
- What's happening? Are you locked out?
- You want some help?
- This would be great.
The second time I've lost my keys.
I think I can fix that.
- My name's Lena...
- Nice to meet you.
and she's my sister, Mya.
- What's happening?
- What's his name?
You know, I just never named him.
You can name him.
Roman.
- Roman.
- Roman?
Roman it is.
Come on, doggy.
Pretty.
Good boy.
- Okay, there you go.
- Thank you. Wow.
That was easy.
- Thanks.
- Alexander.
Thanks, Alexander.
Mya.
Go inside and say goodbye.
- Bye.
- Bye, Roman.
Go, go, go, go.
I'll come by later and
drop off a new lock.
Any time.
Nice to finally meet you, neighbor.
Nice to meet you.
Come here, boy.
Where do you think you're going?!
Catch him!
Pick him up.
Let's go.
I have already paid!
I swear it.
Hey, Amerikansky.
He says he already paid.
When you speak to me
you speak in English.
You know that.
This is not fair.
I work hard for this money.
I understand. We work hard...
to provide you protection.
But it comes at a price.
I think I need protection
from Mr. Vladimir.
Hey!
You don't pay up next week,
I'm taking your fucking tongue.
Don't!
Okay okay. Okay.
Just give me a second.
How much are you short?
Watch the door.
Don't mistake this act of kindness
as weakness.
Are we clear?
- Are we clear?
- Yeah.
He's square. I'm gonna grab a bite.
Da?
Da. Wait.
Vladimir says there's a problem.
He wants you to check it out.
Same as others?
Da, sliced and diced.
Identical MO.
Gangs killing rival gangs I guess?
But why leave incense?
It's Chinese.
They believe incense to be associated
with the "yin" energies of the dead.
Burning joss sticks
attracts ghosts,
who consume the smoke and destroy
the fortunes of the family.
It's symbolic.
Googled it.
These guys... look very Russian.
Yeah. The cross
signifies prison time
and the ring finger indicates rank.
This arm belongs to a lieutenant.
Okay. So...
let's find out which Russian gangs
are missing a lieutenant...
and has a beef with the
Chinaman assassins.
Hey, Sasha, I don't suppose
you'd know anything about
this mess, would you?
You know me better
than that, Constable.
I'm just getting a bite.
Afternoon, Father.
Alexander. I've seen you
pass by many many times.
First time you
actually came inside.
Yeah, just looking around.
Of course. Feel free.
Thanks.
You must be Mya's brother.
- Yeah, how'd you know?
- Hey, where's your dog?
You mean Roman.
He's at my apartment.
I'll bring him by later.
That's the man I've been
telling you about...
our new neighbor with the dog.
Okay. I gotta get out of here.
Just in case...
you get hungry, here's a little...
whoa. Hey. No, you
can't have all that.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
You're coming by tonight?
I can't. I gotta work,
but I'll call.
- You still have it?
- Have what?
The key.
What key?
I give you... on the neck.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The neck.
- Yeah. Yeah!
- This key. This key.
- Yeah.
- Of course I have.
I never leave home without it.
- Good.
- All right.
I'll see you later.
No. But whoever it was
left joss sticks on
the bodies again.
Yeah, he's sending a message.
And the money?
One last thing. Vladimir...
who is she?
Just a girl.
Feels light.
It's all in there, sir.
If you like, I could...
at least you and your men
made it here alive tonight.
Let's keep it that way.
I can't afford to do business
with some Chinese
ninja out hunting us.
Give this to Chen... clean.
And before you go, enjoy the girls.
Tonight, it's on the house.
Hey!
Try Lena, the girl behind the bar.
Leave the girl alone.
It's all there.
My sister working here was
not part of our deal.
You are telling me what to do now?
Your sister is here so I
can keep an eye on her,
- to keep her safe.
- If she works here,
I say she's for sale,
like the rest of the bitches.
You promised my
family protection...
if I came here to work
off my father's debt.
I am upholding my part of the deal.
Yes, and you are very
good at what you do.
That makes you valuable to me.
You want out, no?
That's why you are here...
to rescue your family.
Noble, truly.
But Lena is beautiful.
She could make me a lot of money.
But Aleksey is right.
Lena here is nothing more
to me than a pretty girl
behind the bar, and
until the debt is paid,
she is my girl, not yours.
Remember that.
- Who is it?
- Alexander.
Wait a minute.
I brought you a new lock,
unless you and your sister want
to keep using a screwdriver.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
Hi, Roman. Come on.
Come on.
Okay, so you're an American.
What are you doing here?
Sasha's an American.
What's he doing here?
He's... kind of over there
with a guy who's not a
very good human being.
- What's your relation to him?
- Vladimir?
In business with him?
Yes, you could say that.
I only come here to drink.
This is kind of a bad neighborhood
you're walking through.
I thought I'd walk you home.
Hey, bitch.
Are you work here or what?
Hey, where are you going, honey?
I want a lap dance.
You know, it takes the IQ
of a mature caterpillar
to know the difference
between the staff and the dancers.
- You understand?
- I want that bar bitch to dance for me,
so fuck you.
- Shall we go?
- Are you for real?
Not really. It's all fake.
Well, Mya was worried.
Yeah, poor thing.
She's alone so much.
It was worse... a lot worse
before Sasha came back.
- And...?
- And...
Our father owed money
to the Russian mob,
he died and the debt fell
onto me and my sister.
And how is it you got
mixed up with Vladimir?
With Vladimir.
Sasha... Sasha is my half-brother.
He grew up in the states.
He was in the military
and was stationed over here.
So when he heard about our problem,
he came to help us out.
Hey, asshole, do you know
who that ho belongs to?
Yeah, she belongs to me.
Why? Vladimir sent you?
Tell Vladimir Piteras if he has
something to say, say it to me.
Take this. I'm gonna
talk to these guys.
- Okay.
- Can you do that for me?
Lock yourself out again?
No, just worried about you.
Why don't you come in?
Thanks.
I can't believe those assholes.
Thanks for helping me...
- again.
- I didn't do nothing, ma'am.
I'm just a handyman.
I work with saws,
and screwdrivers,
and hammers, and...
simple stuff like that.
They were Vladimir's men.
You said earlier that Sasha was
working with some dangerous men.
You know all about them, don't you?
I do.
Then you know once there is a debt,
there's no getting away.
So, as long as Vladimir
needs Sasha, here we are.
But it will come a day when
Vladimir doesn't need him anymore,
- and when that day come...
- When that day comes,
you go away to a nice, safe place
and you have to never think
about them again. You hear?
I'm glad you made it home safe.
So am I.
Ooh, the rate this guy's going,
we're going to be out
of Russians soon.
Again with the incense.
And the Chinese
writing... Gwai Lo...
it means "white ghost."
But not a derogatory
sense, you know?
Like he sa... he's
saying it with pride.
You know?
A vendetta. So he's not Chinese.
Maybe.
Ah... okay.
Oh, I googled the tats.
You were right about
the last victims.
These guys...
have the same ink.
Yeah, but they're low level,
- Foot soldiers.
- So?
- Messengers?
- Bag men.
They were transporting something.
Something our assailant has
taken, probably money.
The way they are cut up...
the killer obviously is
very skilled with a knife.
Short sword. I'm guessing our
man is sending a message.
- A warning?
- Yeah.
But the question is,
a warning to whom?
Keep your mouth shut
and do what I do.
My buyer,
a very good customer...
he likes big weapons,
dangerous weapons,
expensive weapons.
All you had to do was launder
this money through your club.
Now the money's gone missing.
I cannot honor my
deal with my buyer.
Mr. Chen, I would never...
never... steal from you.
But these murders, they
are disrupting my ability
- to do bus...
- Oh.
You were short last month.
This is your way of saying
you're short yet again?
No, Mr. Chen, I just
need more time.
Li Wei just confirmed that you have
this Russian girl at your club.
You are very fortunate...
that my buyer has this proclivity
for beautiful Russian girls.
The younger, the better.
Maybe I can... repair the situation
with the help of
your Russian beauty.
You know, I am reminded
of this old proverb
that if you stand by the
river's edge long enough,
eventually...
you will see your dead
enemy's body floating past.
the money or...
Your choice.
Why didn't you call me?
I told you, Alexander
took care of it.
- It wasn't any problem.
- It wasn't a problem?
- No.
- Right.
Lena, do you have any idea
what's going on right now?
You don't. You call me.
- Alexander?
- How can I help you?
Replacing the lock.
Oh, yeah.
What do you think I am,
man? Put that away.
And I also wanted to say thanks for
what you did for my sister last night.
I didn't do nothing.
Look, I do the best that I can
to take care of my family,
but I can't be all
places all the time.
So what you did last night...
I appreciate it.
Look, man, I have a
rope around here...
on the Russians, with the Chinese.
There's bad guys that live by a
code of ethics and follow the rules
and there are those who don't.
You're running with
those who don't.
You're right.
It's still none of your business.
- Keep that in mind.
- My family, my business.
All right.
We're not gonna be here
much longer, anyway.
You can count on that.
I gotta go.
Oh, and I sincerely hope that you didn't
have anything to do with what happened
to Vladimir's men last night.
Not me.
Hello.
Amerikansky.
Hey, Why'd you call
me at a payphone?
I was downstairs at the club.
So I would be able
to speak with you,
Knowing that our conversation
will remain in private.
Sasha...
I'm afraid we suspect
one of our own stealing
from Mr. Chen.
Are you talking about the murders?
Yes, Sasha, the murders.
Okay. Just wait a second.
Vladimir, I would never
steal from you or Mr. Chen,
let alone kill one of our own.
I may believe that, Sasha,
But Mr. Chen is not the
sort that is comforted
by panicked assurances.
But if it makes you
feel any better,
he will continue to care
for your lovely sister
long after you are dead and buried.
I didn't kill anyone!
I swear to you! You
have to tell him that!
Wait! Andrei!
and try your call again.
Please hang up.
Oh... fuck!
Mya?
What's going on?
Where is Sasha?
Did something happen to him?
- Yes, something happened to Sasha.
- What?
Your brother was a thief,
so he had to pay with
his life, I'm afraid.
- No, that's impossible.
- I'm afraid it's possible and finished.
But this is not the
reason I'm here.
I'm here for you.
You're a smart and
very attractive girl.
Now I can see why
Mr. Chen had decided
to keep you for himself.
Don't touch me!
Now be smart and watch your tongue.
I don't want to mess up
that lovely mouth of yours.
- No.
- Go in that room.
Mya.
Keep her quiet.
Mya!
Lena.
Mr. Chen is willing to
take her over money.
I'd be a fool to turn
her over so easily.
Okay.
Slight change of plans.
- Keep her safe. Let's go.
- Mya! No.
Stop!
Mya!
No!
Do that again and
your sister is dead.
Do you understand me?
Now be a good girl
and get in the car.
Oh Shit.
Quit staring at me, bitch.
Go on. Test me.
I dare you.
Give us a minute.
- What's going on?
- We got trouble.
Come on.
Stay here.
Go back to your room.
Back to my room?
Uh-huh.
You want some?
You're gonna die, motherfucker.
Alexander.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
They took Mya. Sasha's dead.
- This can't be happening.
- Well, he... he's not dead.
That's for sure.
Why do you think Vladimir took Mya?
He said he was taking
her to Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen wanted me,
but he took Mya instead.
I don't even know who Mr. Chen is.
Well, I do. Come on.
Sir, I know who took your money.
I don't care who took my money.
We made a deal.
The cash, the girl
or I'll kill you and
your entire family.
This is the thief's sister.
I brought her to you
for collateral.
Are you gaming me?
Or do you have the biggest
pair of balls on earth?
You're running out of time
and excuses, Vladimir.
Hi.
What is your name?
Mya.
Oh, your name is Mya.
She's the little sister
of the one you asked for.
I will have her soon
again, but until then...
I am Mr. Chen.
Take her to the safe house.
The money is one thing,
but when people start
to die around me
with frequency and ferocity,
it usually means that
someone is trying to take
what is rightfully mine.
Is this what you're trying to do?
Mr. Chen, please, I'm
getting your money.
I just thought...
no. No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no! No!
No!
No! No!
You think too much, Vladimir.
I'm gonna keep the girl.
I would start going if I were you.
- Where are we going?
- To see your brother.
My friend told me
he's hiding out here.
Follow me.
Sasha.
Are you trying to kill me?
Okay, okay, it's good
to see you, too. Yeah.
Thank God you're alive.
Vladimir said that you're dead
- and I thought you were.
- Sorry to disappoint you.
Sasha, Vladimir and Aleksey took
Mya to someone called Mr. Chen.
- What?
- Yeah.
So I know you don't trust me,
but you're gonna have to trust me.
Otherwise, I can't help you.
You know, there is an old
adage from Sun Tzu that says,
"When one first sets out for war,
first dig two graves."
And I'm hoping that you feel
that way about your family.
I'm hoping you're willing to die
in order to save your family.
How you feel about that?
Whatever it takes.
This I call...
It means "the Devil's
Butcher Knife."
I use it a lot. It's
the perfect weapon.
Very quiet.
Why'd you kill Vladimir's men?
Two years ago I was
given an assignment
to terminate a couple terrorists.
One in particular, he was
working with am arms dealer,
and...
I got the terrorist and
the arms dealer got away.
- Mr. Chen.
- That's right.
So the last two years
I've been tracking Chen
through Asia, and went
to Hong Kong and...
killed all of his men, triad style,
just to flush out Chen.
- What's in it?
- I wanted him to think
that it was inside-the-family job,
so I get in there and kill
the bad guys with a sword
and leave joss sticks on the body.
You drew the w... the writing
on the wall. Gwai Lo.
I'm the one that's gonna
save your sister,
and I'm the one that's
gonna kill Chen.
Good. Let me help.
Open it.
It's the money from the drops.
It's... it's Vladimir's money.
All right, let me tell
you what you can do.
You go to Vladimir and
find out how much money
it's gonna take to buy her back.
So you just want me to stroll in
and talk to the guy
that tried to kill me?
Well, he's not gonna kill you,
'cause he knows you're a part of
how he's gonna get the money.
You wait for me here.
You said you were
just a regular man.
Yeah, that's true...
I'm a regular man who does
bad things to bad people.
If Vladimir sees you
here, he will kill you.
- You know that, right?
- Yeah.
Just let him know I'm here.
Hi, Sasha.
I'm supposed to give you a dance.
Of course you are.
So why did he send you and
not one of his goons?
I don't ask questions, Sasha.
You know that.
I just do as I'm told.
Look, why don't you just sit back
and enjoy the dance?
Okay. Passion?
I need to speak with Vladimir.
Thank you, Passion. That's enough.
I didn't think I would
see you again, Sasha.
Easy.
I'll give you whatever
you want for Mya.
The price is 300,000.
This is what I owe to Mr. Chen.
Pay it and you can
have your sister back.
Sounds reasonable?
300,000?
Yeah, reasonable as hell.
Finally.
Hey, look, there's our friend.
Think he might talk either?
I don't know. Let's find out.
Hey, Sasha!
- Yo, man!
- Let's have a word.
Come. Come, come.
No no!
What? No, no, no, no, no!
No!
Just a second.
Yeah.
I got it under control.
He said he would be back soon.
Best to relax
and not to work yourself up
any more than you are, Lena.
I know Sasha would do anything
for me and my sister,
- but Alexander...
- Is just like your brother.
- A military man.
- A good man.
Mr. Wei.
Yes, our buyer will be
arriving tomorrow morning.
He'll be terribly disappointed
when I tell him there's
problems with our deal.
Won't the little one be enough?
Scratch Roberta's itch?
I'm not sure if his
interest would dip so low.
Perhaps not, but... if they do?
We'll decide in the morning.
Okay. So...
I'll bring her in the morning.
Yes.
Tell me the truth and
I won't hurt you.
Where is Mya?
I don't know.
You don't know.
You want to take me to her?
Okay, where can I find Chen?
I can't tell you.
If he finds out I sent you
to him, he'll kill me.
Okay, well, I'll kill you
a lot fucking worse.
And I'm a lot better
at it than he is.
If I'm dead, you're dead!
Those girls are dead!
I don't mind.
I don't mind if everybody dies,
but I will kill you really slowly.
Now where is Mya?
I guess it's gonna be a
long, painful night.
This is a very very
special compound,
but it's gonna be slow
and fucking painful.
There will be no more
fucking around with you.
You want to tell me,
or you wanna die?
Either way is fine
with me at this point.
I really don't give a fuck.
Okay, I'll talk, I'll
talk, I'll talk.
Talk.
I'll bring you there.
- I'll bring you to Mr. Chen.
- You'll bring me there? Perfect.
Get ready. We're going now.
Hey.
Dude, what do you want?
I already said everything
I gotta say to the cops.
Am I under arrest?
My friend...
what for?
Chess?
- What is your name?
- Alexander.
And you're here for
the little girl?
Yeah.
What is your business?
When you say, "what
is my business,"
you mean, what do I
do for a living?
- Yes.
- I'm a handyman.
A handyman?
Well, Mr. Handyman,
I have good news and bad news.
The good news is I
do have the girl.
The bad news is I need her
for another business transaction.
Well, that's a shame, because...
I came here to make
a deal with you,
and any good businessman
would always hear
what another man has to say.
I'm prepared to throw money down.
How much money are
we talking about?
- How much you want?
- How about a million?
A million? How about
300,000 cash, right now?
That's a good number.
I tell you what: you
come back tomorrow,
bring your money and we
can do some business.
What happened?
They took her.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
'Cause now...
I will snatch every
motherfucker birthday.
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
Camera 4 is not working.
I don't get a signal too.
No signal.
Reboot the system.
Three men...
two getting out of a limo,
one guarding the gate
that's in the driveway.
Looks like your tip might
actually be worth the trip.
Still down.
Pavel will be pissed
if something's wrong.
Okay, let me hear
your theory again,
'cause you're drawing a
lot of conclusions here.
Okay, so what do we know so far?
Chinese guy with a sword.
"Gwai Lo." "White ghost."
Maybe not.
Dead Russians.
And who's the big dog
in town these days?
Mr. Chen, the Chinese arms dealer.
Okay.
And we got nothing connecting
Mr. Chen to the murders.
Hear me out. What if
Vladimir is laundering money
- for a deal for Mr. Chen?
- No. No.
You have nothing to prove that.
What if our killer is
taking out Vladimir's men?
Okay. Why?
In order to prevent Mister...
to prevent Vladimir
from paying Mr. Chen?
Lena?
Sasha.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Did they hurt you?
- No.
- Okay.
Come on.
- This way, this way.
- Let's go.
Easy.
Easy easy.
You really didn't give me
a choice, you know?
- Pavel?
- I tried to steer you away,
but you wouldn't listen.
Talking all the time.
- Talking all the time.
- You work for Vladimir?
Are you kidding me? Huh?
I work for Mr. Chen.
- What?
- No, they're cops.
Look, stay here until I come
back and get you, all right?
- Okay.
- Don't move.
Okay.
Partner, you are...
a real pain in the ass,
but not anymore. Not anymore.
No!
Watch out!
Li Wei, go! Warn Mr. Chen!
Sasha!
Go, go, go. I'm okay, I'm okay.
Go, I'm good, I'm good.
Too bad you are unarmed now.
I am, too. Come on. Come here.
You know what? Let's
make this a fair fight.
Roberto. See, unteachable.
You're early, my friend.
Bongiorno, Mr. Chen.
You have caused me much
trouble, Sasha. Much trouble.
I guess that's the cost
of doing business.
You should have never come back.
Sasha, be careful.
Shoot him!
Okay. Okay. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Stop, stop, stop.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Lena. Lena. Come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I've got you. I've got you.
My squad car is over there.
I'll call it in, make
sure she's safe.
Go. Finish this.
- I'll be back.
- No.
I'm gonna finish this.
I'll be back.
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay, I'll take her.
I'll find another
to clean my money.
Excellent.
Not very spirited.
Roberto, she's still young.
Ah. This is true.
Make her a Shirley Temple.
What do you want?
I have an appointment with Chen.
I got some stuff in here for him.
Show me.
He's clean. Mr. Chen
is expecting him.
Alexander, I've got Lena.
She's safe.
Stay on the perimeter.
Wait for my signal.
All right, copy that.
Well, Mr. Alexander.
Oh, you could just
call me "Alexander."
As you wish.
But addressing someone
in the formal
is much more...
polite. Don't you think?
Yeah, it's impressive. Yeah.
Listen, the deal was $300,000,
and I brought the money.
You know, it astounds me
how a handyman got $300,000.
How did you get so much?
Well, that's kind of
none of your business,
but the fact of the
matter is I got it,
and we have a deal...
$300,000 for Mya.
She's right there.
I'm here to take you home.
Oh, about that...
I changed my mind.
I thought you were a man of honor.
I thought you were
gonna keep your word.
I thought we had a deal.
No, no, no, no, no, we had
business... not yet a deal.
But it's time to make a deal.
I already told you she's
for another buyer,
but her sister, however...
how much would you pay for her?
Let's say 300,000 maybe?
But you see, the deal was for Mya.
Then I guess we have no deal.
Yeah, well, I got all
this money here.
What you want me to do
with all this money?
$300,000, all right here.
You know, may I say
either you are very brave
or very naive for you
to come back here.
Now, you didn't bring no firepower.
If you did, we would've
honored our word.
But you're nothing but a handyman.
It'd be stupid for us
just not to take that
money and kill you.
I'm gonna give you one last chance
to keep your word.
You're gonna give
me one last chance?
- That's what I said.
- In my house?
With my people and my guns?
Yeah.
I lied, but that's what I do.
I lie for a living.
I got some bad news for you.
See, I lie for a living, too.
And guess what?
I'm not a handyman.
I'm a professional killer.
I came here to kill you.
You're Gwai Lo?
That's the way it is.
Sasha!
Is this how you wanna go out?
A man of war?
A son of Guan Gong?
Like this?
Killing a child? This is not you.
You look at the total summation
of your whole life...
and see your last breath.
Is this it?
Well said.
All my life, I try to take
care of my han dais,
honor Guan Gong,
amassed wealth and power,
but no one close would tell me
it's by trickery and deceit.
It took an adversary
to show me the significance
of life and death.
If we can resolve this
by the code of Gong...
as han dai...
men of honor...
by the sword...
would you?
Come here, come here.
Mya, Mya, get over here.
Come here.
Now I can die in peace...
Yes.
Come here.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
Are you sure this is what you want?
There's nothing here
for her anymore.
I don't want to lose you again.
I don't want to lose
you either, squirt.
I'm gonna give you this dog.
He's a good dope dog.
That's where I got him.
Are you sure you don't
wanna come with?
Yeah, I'm sure. I'm retired.
And if you're retired, you're
gonna need some company.
You got any ideas?
Yes.
It's finally over. Hear me, kiddo?
Don't forget to call me, yes?
Yes.
It's good to see you.
Take care, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Talk to you soon.
- Thanks for coming home.
- Of course.
Oh, let me give this to you.
It's good luck... from Mya.
Never leave home without it.
Okay. Thank you.
Bye.
All right.
Help me walk him.
Buckle up.