MARIANNE: Come on Zack!
Here. Now maybe you'll
stop bugging me.
Sierra Drivers!
Yes! Mom.
Thank you.
I wanted these so bad.
You are the coolest mom in the world.
- Don't wear them when you're playing.
- Duh.
Look, I can't, I promised Emily
I'd go to the movies with her.
God, you're so pussy-whipped!
Fuck you, Chris.
I'm not whipped!
- That's so ridiculous.
- Right,
like you're not the most pussy-whipped
guy on the planet fucking Earth.
Just 'cause
I'm not a Neanderthal like you.
I can actually be friends with a girl.
Whipped!
Like everyone doesn't know.
Give me a break.
Man, lately every time
I ask you something,
- it's always Emily this, Emily that...
- Come on, grow up.
You just hate girls.
You probably still run up...
- ...to them with dead frogs.
- Hate girls?
No! I don't hate girls. I love girls!
I just don't like them when
they're standing up.
Now I know why I hang out with you.
- 'Cause I got such a great line of shit?
- No,
'cause you make me feel so superior.
Face each other.
Chris says
I'm totally pussy-whipped.
That's a disgusting expression, Zack.
Well, you know what I mean.
People say I let Emily push me around.
Bullshit! Emily is such a sweet thing.
She adores you.
What are you talking about?
Well, people say I'm not the boss
in the relationship.
Like I'm not manly enough.
I don't know.
Chris Briggs is a total chauvinist.
I know, but you know I'm not like that.
Everyone says I'm too...
...politically correct.
Whatever that actually means.
That means you're a sensitive kid and you
treat women with respect and as equals.
And to me that's a real man.
Thanks, Cindy.
Let's go blue! Go! Come on Zack!
Yes!
You know, that's a terrible habit.
Smoking gives you...
Gary! Don't be
King of the Nerds for a change.
Jerking off is a terrible habit too
but that doesn't seem to stop you.
Emily, I don't understand why you
hang around here while we're playing.
Well it's more peaceful.
And I get stuff done;
so I have more time later.
Study, study, study...
College, college, college...
College ain't all that
it's cracked up to be, ya know.
Oh really?
Look I know you think I'm stupid,
but lots of people become successful
without a college diploma.
Just look at that computer guy...
- What computer guy?
- That computer guy...
The Microsoft guy.
Dropped out of Harvard.
Made billions.
Think about it.
Bill Gates.
You know college doesn't hurt.
Yeah Em's right.
It gives you more options.
And...
I don't want to
hear a word from you!
Maybe for brainiacs like you guys.
Travis and me...
...we'll make it big our own way.
Yeah, speak for yourself, Dude.
Two kings, two twos.
Beat that, suckers!
Sorry, Charlie, three eights.
Fucking shit!
I think you better plan on
going to college, Chris;
'cause you're not going to make it
as a gambler.
You've got a kickback scheme
going on with your parents, don't you?
They leave town, and you
take all our money.
He's got enough now to buy you that
little bracelet with the diamonds in it.
Really!
Oh shit!
Well, you know I would have no problem
with that whatsoever...
Yeah, I bet. When is the last time
you bought me something shiny?
That's not part of the deal, silly.
Men buy the nice things for ladies.
That's the deal.
Oh, that's the deal?
I'd like to see that in writing some day.
Men. Ha! I guess that
leaves you out, Zack.
Unless Emily knows
something we don't.
Alright, I'm gonna head out.
I think I've lost
enough money for one night.
Change your mind?
Nah, I've got to be
up early tomorrow.
More training?
I run in the morning.
Fuckin' Rocky Balboa over here!
Training for
the state fuckin' championship!
Too bad, it's gonna be some bash.
- Who's going over Chet's?
- Nah, I'm hanging here.
No you're not.
You're coming with me, dirtbag.
- Why?
- Zack is here with his squeeze, schmuck!
We're trying to give them a little room.
You brain-dead squirrel.
I'll see you guys.
Maybe we'll hook up tomorrow.
Bye.
So, you've thought about it?
Of course, I've thought about it!
Zack, I've dreamed about it.
So what are we waiting for?
Look stop! Stop!
Come on, we talked about this.
You said you'd never play
that game with me.
I'm not playing with you.
I'm not ready.
I told you, Zack.
I'm just...
I'm not ready,
that's all.
But hey,
come on.
When I am...
...there'll be no one but you.
You know that.
Get in the car!
Listen lady you have me mistaken
with someone else.
Lady this is some kind of mistake.
You must have me mixed up
with somebody else.
Not if your name is
Zachary Alan Butterfield.
And don't call me lady.
My name is April.
I don't get it!
Did I do something wrong?
Just shut up,
I'm not going to hurt you.
You already did.
Didn't I just tell you to shut up!
I'm just worried.
Maybe he's just hanging
with his friends.
Let's give it until one.
Please tell me what this is about?
If it's money,
my dad is just a professor at a college.
He's not rich or anything.
I don't want your dad's money.
Tell me what you want
maybe I can help.
Just keep walking.
This here's the kitchen.
I cook a lot.
I'm very good at it.
This is the office.
This is the library.
This is the guest room.
My bathroom.
My bedroom.
And this is your room.
For now, you'll have to stay in bed.
Be good and you'll be free to roam
around the house.
Wouldn't want you
wandering off by yourself.
These woods are kinda of isolated;
people die in them all the time.
I have a present for you.
This is a very special necklace.
Hold still.
Whose room was this?
No one's. I made it for you.
Looks great!
I might get one for myself.
Hey, I want to show you something.
So, you're free to walk around.
Well sort of...
There's an electronic perimeter fence.
Little transmitters in the ground
send off low frequency pulses...
...on the same frequency
as your necklace.
Oh, if you get to the perimeters edge,
it'll detonate your necklace.
Check out his necklace.
It's C-4.
Plastic explosive.
You can shape it into anything.
It's soft, like clay.
Each one of your beads
is stuffed with it.
This is the manual override.
Oh, yeah I forgot.
It's dead-switched.
Try and take it off...
...it'll break the circuit
and it'll explode by itself.
So, you're free to walk around.
Well sort of...
There's an electronic perimeter fence.
Oh, if you get to the perimeters
edge, it'll detonate your necklace.
Morning Sheriff.
Any news?
Morning.
No, sorry to say.
Can I come in for a minute?
Come on inside.
Thank you.
Sheriff are you still investigating us?
Look, I'm sorry about that polygraph
stuff this morning,
- that's just standard procedure.
- Well it was horrible!
It was horrible to think,
you could think that...
- ...anyone could think that we...
- Honey.
Parents are always the first suspects.
We can't take any of this too personal.
Your husband is right.
We always look at the parents first.
We just wanted to eliminate you folks
as suspects so we could get on with it.
Our only interest is finding your son.
Now we're going to have to
take a look at his computer...
...that might hold the key
to this whole thing.
We've got guys,
- we call them computer forensic...
- No. Zack doesn't have a computer.
No, he doesn't.
We do, but...
Zack, he didn't have time for
any of that stuff, he was an athlete.
Doesn't he talk to his friends
on your computer?
No, listen, you take the computer.
Look at it. Look all you want.
But he didn't talk to
anybody on that thing.
No, he never did.
He said he didn't like to...
...he said he didn't type very well.
He didn't type "too good"
is what he said.
We encouraged him to use it -
and he would say that -
and I would correct him,
"Not very well," I would say.
Zack, you don't type very well.
I'll send a deputy around
for it this afternoon.
Any way we can help, Sheriff.
Yeah well, I'll keep you posted.
One thing:
we talked to his teachers,
his friends, his coaches.
Was there anybody?
Was there a new man in his life?
- Somebody we didn't know about?
- A man?
Well yeah like...
...a casual acquaintance,
a truck driver,
- a karate buddy, something like that?
- No, he's a star athlete.
He's always training or playing.
He's busy, popular.
There a lot of girls buzzing around.
He has a lot of friends.
Yeah, Zack didn't know anybody that
we wouldn't have known about.
Well, I gotta ask about
drugs and alcohol.
I'm sure Zack has had a beer,
just like any guys his age,
maybe even took a hit off a joint...
- ...or something...
- No, Peter!
Listen, honey, this is no time...
...to start worrying about maintaining
some sort of social image.
No, Zack wouldn't pollute
his body with that garbage.
You know he's a fitness freak!
- I don't want him to think that...
- I know, all I'm saying...
...is that there's no way that
we could know what he did once...
...much less what he did
every second of his life...
Folks, folks. Take it easy.
Alright, I only meant...
...did he have a problem with that stuff?
Seems like he didn't.
I'm just covering all the bases here.
We...
We actually don't have
a clue of what's going on here.
The last time you saw him, he was out
running on Reynolds Road, you said.
Well, we've been up and down that road.
We've covered every inch of it.
There were no signs of violence.
Master Kwan, his Karate instructor,
told me he was a ferocious competitor.
Top of his class.
Right.
It's not likely anyone could take him
without a fight on their hands, right?
- That's right.
- Well,
there's no evidence of that.
I think we have a walk-away here.
Mom? Dad?
Fuck!
If you're awake in there
that was the sound of...
...your loud and obnoxious cell phone
being blown to pieces.
It's C-4.
Plastic explosive.
You can shape it into anything.
It's soft, like clay.
Each one of your beads
is stuffed with it.
It's dead-switched.
Try and take it off...
...it'll break the circuit
and it'll explode all by itself.
How did you know all my sizes?
I know a lot about you Zack.
I've had my eye on you
for some time now.
I was watching you back when you
were kicking ass as a freshman forward.
Open it.
It's part of an Indian costume
for when we play Cowboys and Indians.
Do you like it?
This...
You're gonna love this.
This is something special.
You sit tight.
And I...
Forgive me Father
for I have sinned.
I haven't been to confession
in two weeks.
And my soul is black with sin.
And I have been a naughty girl.
Hey!
I'm going to do that
with someone else,
not with you.
It's time to earn your keep.
There's your uniform.
Go put it on.
Go put it on!
Pretty funny outfit?
It's to prevent you
from concealing anything from me.
I wouldn't want you transporting
any contraband into your room.
Come on.
You're going to scrub the bathroom
until it shines.
It's done.
Gleaming?
Like a beacon to passing aircraft.
What the hell?
It's a drink.
You ever had one?
No,
but I've thought about it.
So smart.
So witty.
Such a cute little thing!
Come here.
Little son of a bitch.
I get the picture. What, I disgust you!
Is that it? Get the fuck out of here!
Go to your room!
You want to play this game?
You know we
should really talk about how...
Zack?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Did something break?
I didn't beat you up that badly.
What am I going to do?
Got it.
Let's see.
Shock. Fast but weak pulse?
Nope.
Feeling weak or nauseous?
Maybe you're depressed.
You better listen
and you better listen good.
I am the boss around here.
You better damn well answer me
when I'm talking to you!
I'll let it slide this time.
Don't expect me to be so lenient
in the future if you don't shape up.
Glory glory
hallelujah,
when I lay my
burden down.
Glory glory
hallelujah,
when I lay my
burden down.
Thank you.
- Professor.
- Sheriff.
This is Agent Quincannon,
Agent Harnett with the FBI.
- The Bureau is helping us out.
- Thank God.
We don't have any leads
as to Zack's whereabouts.
There's no evidence of any kind.
There were no witnesses.
The State Police have canceled
the search,
and the Town Police have decided
to close the case.
I on the other hand have decided to
hold it open as "unresolved."
That way if anything new comes in,
I can reinstitute the search
for Zack right away.
Folks, I have to be honest with you,
the chances of us finding him
at this point are pretty slim.
I'm not sure I understand
what you're saying.
Stranger abductions don't usually occur
with kids this old.
You guys are good people,
I wouldn't want
this to hijack your life.
This can be
very destructive to families.
My best advice to you...
...is to move on.
He'll get it touch eventually.
Agent Quincannon, do you have kids?
No.
No, I didn't think so.
Let me tell you something.
Your child is not just a responsibility,
like a pet.
Loving your child with all your heart...
...is not a choice.
It's not a decision.
It's a truck that hits you
the day they're born...
...and stays parked on your heart
for the rest of your life!
Honey...
No! If you think for one minute...
...that I'm going to just let this go,
than you've got another think coming.
You're really beautiful.
You're drop-dead gorgeous,
you know that?
I'm flattered.
That's flattering.
You know, you can be really nice.
I think you're growing on me.
This is fabulous.
Well, I make it from scratch.
I bet you could make money
selling this stuff.
Well, I could show
you how to make it.
Would you?
Well, no time like the present.
It's never easy with kids.
No, but personally I think
some pedophile has got him.
And if he does, those guys are really...
Maybe you shouldn't assume it's a guy.
What?
Could be a woman.
I hate you fuckin' FBI guys.
You think you know everything.
But...
...we do.
Remember, 6 tablespoons of salt
in every gallon of boiling water.
Then you let the water cool.
Then you add
the warm water to the cheese curds.
And then you mash the cheese curds up.
And then you can add
a little bit more water...
...until you have a well-formed ball.
Where did you learn all this?
My mother was a great cook
that evil bitch.
At least she took
the time to teach you all...
She never taught me shit!
I learned from watching.
I watched her prepare meals
for my dad and for Smiling Jack.
She never taught me shit.
This was Dad's favorite room.
He used to come in here and escape.
Mom was this tyrannical bitch.
She used to spew her venomous crap
at anyone around her.
One day he just upped and left.
No note, no goodbye,
no fight.
I was nine, and...
...'poof' no more dad.
But soon mom had a new boyfriend,
Smiling Jack.
- Was he a good guy?
- Yes.
He was a career Army guy,
a Captain.
He was the one who taught me
how to hunt and shoot, ride and fish.
He was the one that got me
started in martial arts.
He loved my mom, though...
...he used to put on
that old record "Irene, Goodnight"...
...when he was drunk
and sing along to it.
He was like a real dad to me.
A good dad.
- She wasn't mean to him?
- No,
she watched her step around Jack.
She knew she had a good thing.
What she like about him?
She liked his disability checks.
He got wounded in the first Iraq war.
He was much older than her.
I want to show you someting.
You're the first person
to be in this room since he died.
One day,
my mom had had enough of both of us.
She just took off.
Said she was going to buy cigarettes...
...never came back.
Gone just like my dad.
But Jack, though...
...he never stopped loving her,
even after she left us.
As he got older and sicker,
I...
...spent most of my time
taking care of him.
Letting my...
...entire girlhood years...
...pass me by.
No proms, no boyfriends...
...no girlfriends, no sleepovers...
...nobody.
My God.
Maybe that is not entirely true.
Smiling Jack loved me...
...in his own way.
I'm flattered you
shared that with me.
Right.
Where was I?
It took some time to get over him.
What happened to him?
He died.
Alcohol I think.
Liver. Kidneys.
It was bad.
By the end, he wasn't too coherent.
Want to know the kicker?
I took care of him for ten years,
day in and day out.
I was devoted.
His last words were "Irene."
Irene.
Irene?
My mom.
Damn!
One day I just I said,
"Fuck it! I'm out of here."
I took off.
Next thing I know I enlist in the Army,
and I am on my way to Afghanistan.
It was totally cool.
I loved it.
I had a lot of fun.
They kept giving me
more training.
I got along with the guys.
Before I knew it I was in Iraq.
You did the war over there?
Yeah, I did the war.
The war did me.
They recruited me. I signed on and...
...I was in Iraq having more
fun and games with the Arabs.
Holy shit. Dangerous.
Yeah, it was pretty wild.
So you were with mostly guys?
Mostly.
Did any of them become,
like your boyfriend?
What do you mean?
They must have noticed
how beautiful you were.
I mean they're guys.
You said when you were growing up you
had no boyfriend.
I'm just wondering,
if that changed in the Army.
You're a very smart boy, Zack.
How am I smart?
You're trying to get into my head.
You've been paying attention.
Aren't you something.
My first time was
on the hood of a Humvee,
in an olive grove outside of Kabul.
He was an 18 year old corporal
from Oklahoma.
I woke up in the morning alone,
hungover, blood dripping down my leg.
What would you wish for if a genie
offered you three wishes?
I'd wish for all those years back...
...all my teenage years.
All of them.
I'd wish for a mom and a dad and a...
...high school prom.
What's with the bald walls?
No pictures or paintings?
Acoustics, it's the music room.
Oh.
Why are we here?
Just a hunch.
Good morning! Thought I let
you sleep in for a change.
Thanks.
Food is on the stove.
It might be warm.
Well you wake up in the morning,
hear the work bell ring;
you go marching to the table,
you see the same damn thing.
All on one table,
a fork, knife and a pan.
And if you say a word about it,
you're in trouble with the Man.
Let the midnight special
shine it's light on me,
let the midnight special
shine it's light on me.
Now if you ever go to Houston,
boy you better do right.
You better not stagger,
and you better not fight.
Sheriff, he'll arrest you.
He'll carry you down,
and if the jury finds you guilty,
you're penitentiary bound.
Let the midnight special
shine it's light on me.
shine it's ever loving light on me.
You're so good!
Full of surprises this morning.
You ain't seen nothing.
Since you've been such a good boy.
I have enough of this
to keep us well-fed forever.
Can I ask you a personal question?
I think we're
on sufficiently intimate terms.
What?
Yes, you may.
Ask away.
You're a beautiful woman.
You know that, right?
Don't try to play me, sonny boy,
it ain't gonna work.
I've been played by the best.
You think I'm playing you?
You should try trusting
somebody sometime.
Do you think I was
playing you last night?
You played me like a fiddle.
Only you didn't know it.
OK, point taken.
What's your question?
You do know, you're
drop-dead gorgeous, right?
- This is your personal question?
- No,
what I mean is...
...you could have
any man you want.
Why would you pick a kid like me?
- Men suck.
- Than why don't you go lesbian?
- Because, I like men.
- But you just said they suck.
That's the problem.
I like men, but they suck.
Hence you.
You lost me again.
I figured teachers you see on the news.
They're on to something.
You know find themselves a boy
before they become a man...
...and your make your own man.
And here you are,
you're a man,
and you don't suck.
- I'm a man now?
- Yeah. How does it feel?
I don't feel any different.
Actually, I guess I do.
More mature, more grown up,
maybe more confident.
But I think I was
happier when I was a boy.
So no matter how much gas I
put in it;
the fuel gauge reads empty.
Well Richard taking a look at it now,
but it's probably the sending unit
that's no good on it.
- Could you to do me a big favor.
- What's that?
Can you move all the furniture
out of here and wax the floors?
OK.
Thank you.
- Do you mind if I put a poster up?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Jimmy on that Honda,
it's a sending unit.
Mike on your car
the sending unit is no good...
...and it's probably going
to take a day or so...
...before we could get the part in.
That does me no good.
I've got to be in Boston tonight.
I've got to drive straight through.
Alright, what I suggest is keep
the gas tank full...
...and just watch the odometer
and have a safe trip.
- What do I owe you?
- Forget about it.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Morning Professor Butterfield.
Peter, please.
Peter, I see that the heat
doesn't slow you down.
It might be time to stop now.
How is your wife holding up?
As well as could be expected, I guess.
She is out putting up those posters.
Come on inside.
This sure is
a scorcher out there.
I got to tell you, Peter.
I've been doing this for 30 years,
this one really got me stumped.
I've never been
as clueless as I am now.
The other day, you guys said that you
didn't believe there was any foul play.
Impossible. I know my son...
...not with rose-colored glasses
or anything.
We were guys together.
We talked about everything.
I know him as well
as you know an old friend.
You're saying he had no secrets?
Not from me. I'll bet on that.
All parents think
they know their kid,
it's practically a cliché.
No offense.
We talked about intimate stuff. Sex,
masturbation, STDs, drugs, booze.
We talked about that
stuff anywhere, anytime.
We were friends.
That's great that you and your wife
have this candid...
My wife was not involved in any...
- ...of those conversations.
- It was a guy thing.
Yeah, and Marianne
respected that.
Do you have any suspicions?
- Could there be a problem with the girl?
- No.
A previous boyfriend?
A jealous ex...
No. We interviewed the hell out of her
and Chris Briggs.
Let me ask you, you said that you
talked about to Zack drugs and booze.
Why would you talk to Zack about
drugs and booze, if he didn't do them?
He didn't, so he had lots of questions.
Me being a child of the eighties
I had lots of answers.
I know he tried to smoke my cigars
once in a while.
Had a beer. He is a
real boy, after all.
That's harmless shit.
You're right about one thing though.
It wouldn't have been easy to take him.
What all that karate stuff?
Yeah.
Whoever took him had a real fight
on their hands.
You did a wonderful job, Zack!
- I'm impressed.
- I surprise myself sometimes.
Well let's get you cleaned up,
tonight is a very special night.
You look so handsome
like a leading man in a classic film.
I never had one of these on before.
Follow my lead my Prince.
Good you're awake.
I brought you some yum yums.
- This looks really good.
- You know everything I've said to you...
...these past couple of days
has come from the bottom of my heart.
Same here.
Good, I just wanted to get that out.
Well I'll let you eat.
I have some things I need to attend to.
I have breaking news from,
I da' ho'. You da' ho'?
I don't know where the fuck I am!
I have an exclusive interview with Zack,
an extraordinary boy who escaped
from the clutches of a kidnapper.
Zack, how did you escape?
I pimped my way into her good favor.
Then, I sprang my escape plan on her ass.
I can see that, can you describe her?
Yeah, tall, crazy...
...psycho bitch lady.
- Why'd she do it?
- She wanted my ample package.
- Where did she keep you?
- She kept me locked up in a bedroom...
...with a chain long enough
to clean the bathrooms.
Did you know this lady from anywhere?
No, she came out of nowhere
and did a drive-by kidnapping.
What become of
this crazy psycho killer bitch?
She is over there
being put in chains by the police.
She's going to the big house.
- Can I say something?
- Go right ahead.
I want to say hi to my mom and dad,
and whut-up to my shorty, Emily. Yo, Em!
Shit, I'm never going to
get out of here alive.
Dinner is ready.
Good. I am famished.
Zack, dinner is ready!
Honey.
Do you think we were too lenient?
Gave him too much space?
No way.
If Zack ran away,
it had nothing to do with us.
There has got to be somebody.
Lady this is some kind of mistake.
You must have me mixed up
with somebody else.
Not if your name is
Zachary Alan Butterfield.
You're going to scrub the bathroom
until it shines.
when I lay my
burden down.
Little son of a bitch!
I get the picture! What, I disgust you!
Is that it? Get the fuck out of here!
Go to your room!
Right. Where was I?
This is the manual override.
When you get a chance,
my sink is leaking.
Really?
- It is going to rot everything below it.
- How bad is it?
It only happens when I use the faucet.
Then it can wait.
Where were we?
- Thank you, I really appreciate it.
- It's the least I can do.
- I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
- Bye
- Hello
- Hi
Well, hello.
Hey Mrs. Butterfield.
- What is this?
- It's quiche lorraine.
- Want to come in?
- Yeah, thanks.
Great.
We love quiche. That was so thoughful!
And you made it yourself?
Yeah, it's only the scond time
I ever did.
So, I hope it's OK.
I'm sure it is. It is beautiful.
Would you like some cookies and milk?
Yeah, sure.
Peter, cookies and milk?
Sure.
- Hi Em.
- Hi Mr. Butterfieild.
Now, I can't believe...
...they expelled Chris Briggs
just for talking back to his teacher.
I know. Talk about strict.
He was going to graduate in a few months.
You know Mandy told me about it, 'cause
she was there when it happened.
Ms. Bennett told Chris
in front of the whole class that...
...she wasn't surpriised...
...that he couldn't answer
a question about women's suffrage.
"After all, what do men care
about the toils of women?" she said.
And then he said,
"Well, I care deeply for women, just
as long as they're not standing up."
He said that?
Yeah.
- My God.
- As you can imagine she blew her top.
She told him to get out of her class and
down to the Principal's office.
Then she decides she's gonna leave the
teaching assistant to finish class,
- and escorted him there herself.
- You don't say.
I know.
No one stood up for Chris...
...that surprised me, because...
...she was always persecuting the boys.
Everyone knew it.
She is like this feminist fanatic.
All the kids are afraid
to stand up to her.
The great Lady Hildegarde Bitch-Bennett.
- Her name is Hildegarde?
- No, we just call her that.
Lady Hildegarde Bitch-Bennett.
That is really quite imaginative.
Yeah, but...
if Zack had been there, I know he...
You know what, I better get going.
I hope you like the quiche.
Stop by any time,
I do enjoy catching up with you.
Are you OK to walk home?
I can give you a ride?
No, don't worry about it,
I'll be fine.
See you guys around.
As promised, I've come
to save the day.
Did you know plumbers get
200 dollars an hour.
You know that amazes me.
You're all set.
This is my upper body
strength force-multiplier.
This gave me the leverage to remove...
...and install every kind
of pipe in this house.
Having the right tool is everything.
Whoever said,
"Never send a woman to do
a man's job." Never met me.
You're welcome?
Oh, it was nothing!
You never appreciate anything I
do around here.
God! You fucking little shit.
The next time you want
something done, you do it yourself.
Don't come crying to me about it.
Thank you.
You changed
my whole outlook on plumbing.
Fuck plumbing! You need to change
your whole outlook on women.
If you're all that
why didn't you install the fucking...
...pipe right in the first place.
Discipline would be easy,
if he wasn't so talented.
Sit down.
You've never had a steak
like this in your whole life.
And these are my very
special garlic basil mashed potatoes.
Well?
What?
How is it?
Good.
Good. Yeah. Really. Real, good.
You want to try a new song?
What? After lunch?
Yes, that's what I meant.
Yeah, OK.
Who could that be?
- Hello there.
- Can I help you?
I'm sorry to bother you.
My car broke down.
I mean it ran out of gas
way down the road.
My phone won't work.
I got no signal.
Do you have a phone
that I could use?
No.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
- I know, I'm some random guy.
- There's a store 5 miles away.
You can hitch.
Let me ask you something,
is that your kid brother?
Just now...
You know what, I'll be OK.
Never mind.
You really fucked up on this one.
What did I do?
We'll talk about it later. Now,
I have to go for a ride
and do some heavy lifting.
This is so you can think about what you
did, and what happened because of it.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah!
So, the drunken asshole passed out
behind the wheel.
He drove his car straight
into Lake Cornwall.
He wasn't wearing his seat belt so...
...when the air bag deployed,
it broke his neck.
It'll do that if you're not wearing
your seatbelt, you know.
April, I didn't do anything.
He had it on cruise control.
It went in at full speed.
Nobody goes to that lake.
It's very deep. There's no fish.
And if they do go there,
it'll be a very long time from now.
Please let me go?
I'm going to let you stay here all night
and contemplate the error of your ways.
I suppose I have to feed you.
- You killed that guy.
- It's what I do best.
Killing people?
The Army spent a lot of money teaching
me how to do that.
I got real good.
They reward soldiers for killing.
Medals, promotions, pats on the back.
But this isn't the war,
you're home now.
Well, you don't just turn it off.
It becomes easy, efficient.
It becomes second nature.
Is this that
"post-trauma" war thing?
What post-traumatic stress disorder.
Please. I served with a lot of men who...
...loved every second of it.
That is just bullshit shrinks think of...
...so they don't have to deal
with the essential nature of mankind.
What's
"the essential nature of mankind?"
They are killers.
They're the most successful predators...
...in the history of life
on this planet.
And you can't figure out why I
have trouble sleeping at night.
What?
Nothing.
Get up you little twerp.
We're going to have this discussion now.
That was a lame stunt you pulled today.
Jesus Christ! What now?
What stunt?
You were signalling your presence
to that stranger.
I thought we were through with that.
I thought we had bonded -
that we were a team.
We laughed. We loved.
We sang together. We were great!
- What went wrong?
- Nothing.
Nothing went wrong.
You're just suspecting it. We're good.
We better be fucking good.
April, what can I do
to make you feel better about...
You can sit back down!
- Do you know what this is?
- It's a shotgun.
It's a twelve gauge shotgun.
This can blow
a good-sized hole in a man.
It's by far
the best method of home defense.
Best kept by your bed.
Loaded.
It is quite primitive.
And this...
This is innovation.
You don't even have to be
anywhere near your target.
I mean all you have to do is press
this little button and boom!
There're a hundred ways
to kill a man.
But by remote
just kinda takes all the fun out of it.
Do you want to live?
Yes.
Good.
Just keep me happy.
Well, I've had just about
enough excitement for one night.
Let's go to bed.
I hate it when we fight.
- I don't want to fight with you.
Well, will you promise
never to hurt me again?
I promise.
- Thank you.
- For what?
For making me happy for
the first time in my life.
For loving me.
I have a surprise for you.
You know, that's a good idea.
- You almost ready in there?
- Just a sec.
Oh! Zack. I think we should...
What did you go and do that for?
I lied.
I would've never hurt you.
Hello.
Yeah, my name is Zack Butterfield.
I'm 15. You guys are looking for me.
Yeah.
Yes, but I don't know where I am.
You can trace it?
Yes, it's a cell phone.
OK, I won't hang up.
Yeah, I'll wait right here.