- What's up?
- I'm looking for Giovanni?
- Where's Giovanni?
- Over there. He's expecting you.
It should appear any minute no.
Come.
It's the only one of the seven islands
darker than the night.
I wouldn't miss it for anything.
Can you see it? There!
- Ginostra.
- It's the Sciarra del Fuoco.
The last eruption
was 600 years back.
If you come from the south part,
it looks like a pregnant woman,
but from the north, it looks like
an old man ith a long beard.
600 years, that's young,
for a volcano anyway.
The first two months,
he lost the use of his legs.
The X-rays showed nothing organic.
It as the trauma.
- And now?
- He's fine.
He spends his days here.
How about his mental condition?
He's a very secretive child.
That's him.
He speaks English.
His father taught him.
Ettore, you have visitors.
Get up.
I'm Matt Benson.
Come and get dressed. Excuse us,
we'll be right back. Let's go.
I prefer to question the boy
in my house.
I want to start tomorrow.
We ask Rome,
but we decide in Lipari.
Sicilians are a polite,
but proud people.
My wife prepared this for you.
It's mozzarella,
tomato and prosciutto.
- Is it mozzarella di buffa?
- Yes, I think it is.
It's not buffa.
Stop the car!
I'm gonna be sick.
You okay?
Yes. We can go.
Let's see. Milk, coffee, cereal.
- These should last a few days.
- One more trip and it's done.
- Do you want me to help you?
- No, thank you, it's okay.
Did you sleep well?
Don't just stand there, come help.
I found peanut butter.
It's amazing, in this tiny store.
Tina would have killed me
if I hadn't found it.
Paola, where is the phone?
Ah, I found it.
Hello?
Mom, hi.
Can you hold on a second?
Ettore, go down to the cove
and try this out.
I got you twelve gauges,
I hope it's okay.
No, mom, they're hooks for fishing.
I was talking to Ettore,
the boy that Matt's working with,
he's going to be staying here.
This island is the end of the world!
There's no water.
They bring all the water by boat.
I just bought 200 bottles.
Can I call you back mom,
I'm really busy? I love you.
So the lady is letting you have
half of the house?
- Is everything okay?
- Just one more bag.
Do you mind hiding the bike?
I don't want Tina to see it.
- I'll give it to her when Matt comes.
- Okay.
She's going to love it. Thank you.
What's going on?
Excuse us. Let me speak.
Sorry.
- You all okay?
- We must go no.
Thank you for your help.
We live at Santa Ginostra,
you can come and visit us
on Sundays and Thursdays.
You'll be welcome.
Thank you. I will.
Ettore,
grab a chair.
For what?
We're going to ork.
- Why not inside?
- Inside is my home.
This is our office. Over here.
Come here.
In front of Ginostra.
Ho do you like it here?
No problem?
My wife, my daughter?
No.
Here, take a look.
What is it?
- Smell.
- I don't know.
- Coke?
- It's not a game, come on.
I'm not a dog.
- Doesn't it ring any bells?
- I don't know what it is, okay?
It's Semtex.
Joe Manzella used this
to kill your family.
Ho often did your dad
go to New York?
- Leave my dad out of this.
- Twice a month on average.
I have his passport here.
You can have it.
All I can do is put Joe Manzella
and his buddies away for a while.
That's not enough for me.
- You knew your dad was Cosa Nostra?
- No he wasn't. Never!
He as the personal chef
of Frank and Joe Manzella.
The mafia bosses of Ginostra.
When Frank was forced to move
to New York, he sent for your father
twice a month, to cook for him
and his family. They were real close.
They were like
your family too, right?
Mister, I am eleven years old,
you asked me about my father.
I loved him,
he loved me, and he's dead.
Ettore, come up here.
What are you doing here?
I can't take my eyes off you.
You don't like the fish?
This fish is up against
some merciless critic.
Ettore's dad
was one of the best local chefs.
Paola is a wonderful cook as well.
- Yeah but his fish had...
- Fennel instead of lemon!
I used hat I had.
So, how long
are you going to stay?
One week. Tina has to start school
on the twelfth.
In one week, you'll have time
to see every beautiful sight.
And no matter
how long you stay,
you won't have time
to see all the ugly ones.
Well, we'll be back
in three months, for Christmas.
Four months.
Too long away from your husband.
I am planning a long week-end
in New York, next month.
I'm trying to learn
all the names of the volcanoes.
I know there's Lipari,
and Vulcano, and...
- Allicudi...
- Allicudi.
- Your turn.
- No, your turn.
She's allergic to volcanoes.
Are you afraid?
No, more like impatient.
Wondering everyday
if it's going to erupt,
when we know we have one chance
in a million to see it wake up.
It's like having a ticket for a show
that may never open.
Isn't that better?
Actually,
I would like to see it blow up.
No, here boredom
catches up with you
and it won't let go.
It grows on you.
Enough!
He loves this country
more than I do.
And maybe
more than he loves me.
- What are you talking about?
- I thank volcanoes for one thing.
The "Santa Ginostra".
- Who makes this wine?
- The nuns.
Taste before investigating,
Mr. FBI Man.
In Sicily, do as Sicilians do.
Elena and Giovanni
make quite a pair.
- He was a little pushy.
- That didn't seem to bother you.
Tina feels right at home here,
nothing phases her.
She really likes Ettore.
I'm sure your work with him
will go fine. Children sense things.
Oh, I love this place.
- Do you know how owns the house?
- No, I don't.
It's going to be too big for you
when we're gone.
I'm glad you've come.
We have to be careful
with Tina here.
Giovanni says it goes down 500 feet.
You could have died up there.
I took the night ferry
and lost my way.
I thought the convent as higher up.
Santa Ginostra is a sanctuary,
protected from all, even the FBI.
I was told anyone could come here
on Thursdays.
I'm just an ordinary visitor.
And a neighbor now too.
Follow me.
- Do you know our wine?
- Yes.
- And our perfumes?
- No I don't.
We banished Rome's God.
We worship the abyss.
Sister Chiara.
Take this visitor to our shop.
You may find something for your wife.
I'll make you a deal...
as a neighbor.
This is where
the flowers are pressed.
We mix jasmine, mimosa,
local roses and many others.
Our composition is a...
a secret.
Those wild flowers remind us that
before the lava flow, Ginostra
was covered with trees and meadows.
Here you are.
The choice is yours.
Tell Joe Manzella
I'm here to get him.
Did you sleep well?
- I went back to bed.
- I missed the ferry.
Why didn't you take the helicopter?
It wasn't available.
What are we going to
talk about today?
How about, you.
Why have you brought your family?
It could be dangerous, if I talk.
Don't you worry about that.
Okay. Paola!
- Paola!
- I'm here.
- Look at the shells we found!
- Ah, ho beautiful!
His specialties?
I can't talk about it.
You can.
I blacked out just after.
I don't remember a thing
until the hospital.
Before the explosion.
Tell me.
- I'd rather give you names.
- I'm not interested in names now.
I didn't think of my mother,
I looked for my father.
I heard him shouting,
he was shouting to my sisters
to get out.
The flames didn't seem
to touch him,
he was holding my sisters
in his arms.
They were like two balls of fire
in his hands.
The flames of hell.
Then, all of a sudden,
he weakened and fell forward
over the wheel
and that's all I saw.
The explosion hurt me, here.
And I blacked out.
What happened that morning?
What?
They left me alive
to kill the bastards who did it.
Come over here.
What makes you think
Joe Manzella wasn't alone?
He is the boss of seven islands.
Everyone works for him.
Did your father ever mention anybody
special, he might have met here
that stands out, maybe someone
outside the Cosa Nostra,
maybe from the police?
Marty Del Piero?
No.
Give me some names of the people
who were closest to Manzella.
Two names.
Beppe Puglisi.
Santo Ragusa.
Okay.
That'll be all for today.
I'll check them out
with the D.A.
Ginostra is the most
beautiful island in the world.
Ettore was born here,
like the Manzellas,
and he was a happy child.
But the Manzellas forced the people
into silence and submission.
Look, can you see there?
That's Ettore's house.
It's an old mill.
His uncles and cousins live there.
They washed every stone
to purify it,
to erase memories of Ettore's father
after he betrayed the Mafia.
Now, do you want to fly over
to see the convent on the other side?
No, later.
I have to get to the D.A.
to check out some names.
What do you know about me?
Well... your name, your age...
Not much.
And... the accident.
It wasn't an accident.
Doesn't your husband
tell you nothing? Never?
About his job? Not really.
Only what you'll tell me.
- Why did Matt come here?
- I don't know exactly,
- to investigate.
- He came from New York just for me?
Yes, I guess.
Are you impressed?
My dad went to cook in New York
lots of times,
but I'm sure
that's not the only reason.
Don't you think
you should ask Matt?
I'm going to bed.
I put some blankets in your room
in case it gets cold.
Sweet dreams.
- Who is it?
- The names you gave me were bullshit.
Turn on the light!
Those two guys are doing
two hundred years apiece.
And you knew it, didn't you?
- If you touch me, I'm gone.
- And you still protect them.
- You can't say that.
- Your mother,
your two sisters
and your father...
You're hurting me,
you're hurting me on purpose!
What are you protecting kid?
What?
- Listen to me.
- Don't' touch me...
What are you protecting?
Do you wanna let your mother and
father and your sisters' go this way?
Or do you wanna get those people
who took them away?
Don't talk to me like that.
I can get people to hurt you.
Make up your mind kid because
I'm on a plane back to America.
You wanna stop, we stop now,
right fuckin' now!
You're only a kid, I understand.
But now's the time to grow up.
It's too soon for you,
but that's the way it is.
You wanna go on
or do you wanna stop?
Let's go on.
Alright.
Now I believe you.
Okay.
She hasn't changed much
since New York.
I followed her for two months
while she was with Frank.
Manzella.
That's his territory.
- Why don't you take him?
- Naples is off limits.
Okay, let's wait until he gets back
to Ginostra, to get him.
Ettore, here are you?
Here.
Aren't you interested in history?
It's our ancestors!
Nobody is here.
Fontanella's closed to the public.
Today, it's all ours.
No, the Celts, my ancestors,
came here in the 4th Century AD.
- Are you listening?
- Yeah, I know that,
- you already told me.
- For once, it wasn't in war.
They offered your ancestors,
their Gods in thanks.
And that's how come the Celtic Gods
have the bodies of Apollo or Diana.
"Lose ten pounds in two weeks",
are you interested?
Are you saying I'm a little...
No, it's just that I can
get you tapes, very cheap.
I know a man in Catane
who has hundreds of them.
If you call him, use my name,
Matt doesn't get involved.
I wouldn't expect this
from the son of a great cook.
Please don't talk about my father.
My dad and I were like that.
I'll put it near the pond.
I'd love to take it to New York.
Maybe I can bring it for you.
- Where did it go?
- What?
The escort, where are they?
I can't believe it.
Look out! Jessie!
Are you okay?
- He wants to kill me.
- Who is he?
- Start the car!
- Get down, get down!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Shut up!
It was an accident.
It's a small road!
I'll pay for the car,
I'm sorry, please!
Ettore!
God damn, God damn!
Etorre!
Help! Somebody!
Help!
Jessie,
- I'm here.
- Where did he go?
Help me, I'm stuck!
That's it!
You're coming with me.
Don't move! Freeze!
Get back.
Drop the knife or I'll shoot.
Drop it!
Get in the pick-up.
Start it.
Don't move! I mean it.
Start this fuckin' pick-up!
I'll kill you.
I'm not joking.
I'll shoot you.
Get back!
Get back you son of a bitch!
Wait.
Give me the gun.
- Yeah?
- What the fuck's going on?
The escort left them at Rapallo.
- Ten minutes from the villa!
- I don't know. I'll check it out.
If you guys
can't guarantee our security,
I'm gonna ask the FBI
to get us back to the States,
Shit, Shit!
I've got my wife and kid here!
It won't happen again!
I'll get you more cars
in front of the house.
But Jessie should not go out
too much, especially with the kid.
Calm down. I'll take care of this.
It won't happen again, okay?
Okay keep me posted.
Why didn't you tell him
about the pick-up?
Our security is his concern,
the pick-up's ours.
I swear that man
wanted to hurt Ettore.
Look, the perfume from Santa Ginostra.
Excuse me. I rang.
Oh, I couldn't hear you,
because of the waves.
Okay.
- Is Matt home?
- No, he'll be back at five.
If you can wait
I'll get you a drink on the terrace.
- Sure, okay.
- It's up here.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
- What does Manzella want now?
- He was with a colleague.
Why he does come here?
Hello!
It looks better like this.
- And I can see her from my bed.
- Thanks for bringing her back to me.
It's her all right.
I'd recognize her anyhere.
I'm staying longer.
I called the office, and they said
I could stay another week.
You don't look happy.
I am, but Giovanni
will never agree to it.
It makes things
much more complicated for him.
- He said it wasn't a problem.
- And Tina, she has to give...
- You called Giovanni?
- He came by this afternoon.
- Why didn't you tell me.
- I forgot. Look at her face,
- What did he want?
- it's so serene.
So we can go back
on the eleventh.
That's plenty of time for me
to get things for Tina for school.
Be happy I'm staying.
Come on, please.
I don't want to see those bastards.
- They're your family.
- I have no family.
Well, seems you have to.
The court allows them one visit
every four months. It's the law.
Whose law?
They disowned my father.
They didn't even come to his funeral.
They took my house.
What do you want? They're bastards.
I'll take care of them.
It'll go quickly.
You can just come in
for five minutes, and it'll be over.
It'll be okay, I promise.
Come on.
Uncle Gino's already killed,
and not only once.
I'll go in first.
You can leave us, thank you.
- How nice meet you.
- Hi, I'm Jessie.
Here is my family.
Rosa,
- Nice to meet you.
- Maria,
- Bambini,
- Vicenzo, her husband.
- Rosa speak very well English.
- Oh good.
Matt's gone to get Ettore.
Please, come in.
- Fine. How is Ettore?
- Ettore is fine, thank you.
Please have a seat.
Stefano was my baby brother.
Yes a tragedy.
My baby bother.
I'm sorry.
We haven't seen Ettore
in four months. How is he?
He plays a lot, outside...
- I hope he's not too difficult.
- Oh no, not at all,
he's a lovely boy, I adore him,
he's very strong, very courageous.
Courageous?
He is saying he is worried
about Ettore's courage.
We loves Ettore.
We love Ettore very much.
Oh, here they are.
- Matt Benson?
- Mr. Greco. How are you?
- My family.
- Vincenzo.
Ettore, would you like to go to
the kitchen and get them a drink?
There's orange juice in the fridge
for the children.
It has been very difficult for him.
He hates everybody.
He wants everybody to pay.
This family visit
has been allowed by the court,
under condition Ettore suffers
no pressures of any kind,
no threats and no intimidation.
He is here under my protection
and my responsibility.
If I see any coercion,
I will ask you to leave
and no further visit
will be allowed.
Matt!
I repeat. We cannot land.
We must hurry.
There are too many. We'll go back.
We are in position.
We await instructions. Over.
Benson? Benson?
What's your position?
Matt, do you read me?
Alpha 43. We're in position.
- We must go no.
- Wait.
Matt, where are you?
Okay.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Giovanni, we're coming.
- It's too late.
Go, go, go!
Matt, it's too late,
he's getting away!
Giovanni, we're here.
Manzella has escaped.
...in Sicily.
In the last fifteen years,
I have worked as a cook
for Joey and Frank Manzella,
in their houses
in Ginostra and Brooklyn.
I have witnessed many dealings
of the Cosa Nostra
and I request to be put
in the Witness Protection Program.
Before I agree to testify, I demand
that my family be protected
and brought to America.
I entrust the safety of my family
to Matt Benson of the FBI.
The commitment to the truth
is a brave decision, Mr. Greco.
But what guarantee do I have
that my family will be safe?
Elena warned us, it's easy
to fall in love with Santa Ginostra.
I'm the agent
in charge of your case.
What the?
You have my word...
- What is it?
- It's a tape I left in.
- Put Tina to bed, I'll be right up.
- I'll help. I'm not ready for bed.
I'll clean up,
I'll be up in a minute.
You can't get out.
Give me the keys,
give me the fucking keys!
You lied to me.
I'm going to tell you the truth.
You said you didn't know
my father.
I knew him. He came to see me
in Brooklyn. To talk.
What about?
- The Cosa Nostra.
- You're lying!
My dad never talked!
You forced him,
you're a fucking cop!
My dad is not a traitor!
Listen to me.
Frank Manzella sent his mistress
to Santa Ginostra
where his brother Joe
could protect her.
But Joe fell in love with the girl.
He asked your father
to poison Frank and he refused,
and refusing Joe meant
signing your death warrant.
Your father wanted
to take care of his family
and the only way he could do it
as to become a federal witness.
And in return,
I promised
to protect his family and bring you
all to America to start a new life.
And we're all dead!
You killed us!
- You're the one who killed us!
- Stop it!
I screwed up.
Someone in the justice department
warned Manzella
and your father
became a sitting duck.
I came here to find that bastard
that betrayed me.
It's your revenge you're after.
You don't care about me or my family.
I'll bring you Manzella!
And you'll help me
find who betrayed me.
No! Keep away from me,
you fucking cop!
Hold your voice down!
You'll wake everybody up.
I don't care! I'm going to
tell Jessie what's between us.
What are you talking about, kid?
That you didn't protect my family?
That you got us killed!
You're scared she'll leave you
if she knew what kind of man you are?
- Maybe I'll just tell her...
- Matt!
I don't want my wife to know
anything about this.
I'll tell her what a shit you are!
Let go of me! You're choking me.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
If my wife or anybody
finds about this,
you won't get what you want.
You won't get what you want.
Listen to me.
I'm the only one here who can
help you get Manzella!
I'm the only one!
I'll help you get what you want.
We'll get him.
I promise you.
Go to sleep.
- You rang?
- Giovanni is not home?
No.
- I was going to number 18.
- Oh. Okay.
Will you come on Sunday?
We're having a party by the islands.
Thanks.
- Matt. I wanted to tell you...
- Yes?
We can help you.
Tischka! Cut it out!
Come in.
- Bring the mower back up!
- No!
Who the hell's going to steal it?
My wife... Susanna...
for forty years now.
- Matt Benson.
- Nice to meet you.
- Here, have a seat.
- Thanks.
Elena told me about you yesterday.
- What will you have to drink?
- Same as you.
Honey, could you bring us
a couple of whiskeys!
So...
You see... Retirement.
I met him for the first time...
thirty-five years ago?
- Thirty.
- Thirty. On Malcolm Street.
When I was tailing
Giuseppe D'Alba.
Honey, could you leave us?
It wasn't me who betrayed you, Matt.
You believe me?
I received your request to protect
Ettore's family,
when his father decided to enter
the federal witness program.
But you know how slowly
things move here.
Before we could do anything, it had
all blown up in our faces, literally.
Two months later,
I was due for retirement,
I didn't speed up the investigation,
and understand... in Lipari,
we already have
too much on our plates.
I've lost a son
in this dirty fucking war
and, on his grave,
I tell you it wasn't me.
Do you believe me?
Yeah, I believe you.
They love sugar.
You're making a big mistake
having that kid at your house.
You're an American,
an easy prey.
They'll trap you in that den of yours
and choke you on their own soil.
It always rains for re-enactments.
They were all against me
coming here.
All of them, except Giovanni.
I don't know why he's here. He could
have had a great career in New York.
His father as a cop in Gela.
Got killed when Giovanni was eight.
It always rains for re-enactments.
This sucks!
I'll have two cops in the car
with you, to play your family.
Don't try to remember
what happened,
just do what comes naturally.
- Did you come by my house Saturday?
- Yeah, I wanted to talk to you.
What about?
Well, I'll tell you later.
When I give that signal,
send the car okay.
The virgins from Santa Ginostra
aren't here yet.
The nuns ere the first to arrive
after the explosion.
Go on, I wanna see the kid.
I'll catch up.
Okay, We'll start without them.
Alright, go!
What is it now?
- Nothing. Close your window.
- It was open. It was sunny that day.
Dino, Leonardo,
the boy's cold. What do I do?
Is everybody ready?
Yes.
Okay, start the car moving.
- Manzella's here.
- Where?
On Ginostra. We are planning
to set him up again.
You are supposed to keep out
of the operation.
It's a request from the D.A.
Hey, hold on!
Oh fuck, the kid's jumped out.
Come here!
Who was watching him?
- He went that way.
- Where?
It's all right.
We'll get them,
believe me.
On my daughter's head.
I'd prefer you to go back sooner.
I've had a great time
with you and Tina here,
but things are getting
more difficult.
But I told you, Giovanni
said it was safe...
Of course Giovanni
would be delighted if you stayed.
Don't tell me you're jealous!
Something's going on.
You don't work with Ettore anymore.
- You don't pay attention to him now.
- I want to give him some time.
It's not easy for him,
hat he has to tell me.
I feel like you're
keeping things from me.
- Important things, between you two.
- What do you mean? There's nothing.
So, you were happy
that I was here
- and no you want me to leave.
- Yes,
I want you to go home!
Oh, Lord,
Bless and sanctify this act
for the purification of my body
and soul.
Take it, it's yours.
Look how nice it is.
It's an angel.
I give you an angel.
Give it life and tenderness.
Keep it.
So that it may always eat.
So that it will always be free.
- I want to go home!
- You don't like it here?
My home is over there, not here.
- We have to give them time to forget.
- Forget what?
Time for you to forget
what they have done again.
They don't want me
to go to Ginostra.
What do you want to do there.
There is nothing to see.
The Manzellas' father was the richest
building contractor in Sicily.
But that wasn't enough for him,
he wanted to conquer Naples.
He got involved in politics. He even
tried to get elected mayor,
but the Neapolitans sent him
back home to his island.
After that,
he decided to build a bridge,
so he would never have to
set foot in it again.
When he had to drive from the airport
to get a boat for Ginostra,
he would throw his garbage
out of the window,
as if the city was
just one big dump.
What do we do about that pretty
little nun from Santa Ginostra?
Let her run free. Soon, I'll be
able to arrest her for complicity.
Why haven't you arrested her yet?
- I mean her complicity with you.
- With me?
Well, at the station they're saying
that you instructed the pilot
to fly over the Ginostra convent
to sabotage Manzella's arrest.
That's the "unofficial" version.
You're investigating me?
If you keep missing Manzella,
you'll have more time
to investigate us.
I'll climb down, I love it.
How do you make "Bucatini"?
A la matriciana,
Al pesto, with seafood...
And with sunfloer seeds?
With sunflower seeds?
Only in Milano they can eat that.
The dinner when they decided
to kill Greco, they served bucatini
with sunflower seeds.
The earth on volcanoes
is too black for sunflowers to grow.
Fourth floor!
Hey! Fourth floor!
Fourth!
Hey! Where's Giovanni,
is he alright?
- Where?
- He's there. He's okay.
Why did you scream?
You screamed.
- I heard you scream.
- Let go of me! You're crazy!
I fell.
Yes operator. Can you get me
the District Attorney?
District Attorney.
Hello? Is Matt Benson there?
What name?
It's very urgent.
This is Jessie, his wife.
And I need to talk to him.
It's really important.
One moment.
Thank you. You see,
he hasn't come back.
And I'm very frightened.
It's just that...
Hold on, please.
It's just not like him to not call.
So can you tell me anything?
Matt Benson has been
taken off the case. Good-Bye Ma'am.
I hate you.
Your dog's not barking anymore.
Maybe you killed him.
You would.
The Grecos' killing
has really hurt me,
it has hurt me bad.
The kid's my responsibility now.
I don't care about the kid.
I would like the two of you
to meet.
What for?
You could say
he's both our responsibility now.
I want to be alone.
Go away.
Ettore's family's tickets.
They were supposed to leave
three days after the car bomb.
Nobody's used them.
I had an affair with a woman
in New York, twenty years ago.
She had a baby.
A baby I didn't want
and I didn't want to see.
It was a girl,
and she grew up alone,
between Brooklyn and Queens.
My wife would have died
if I had told her.
I didn't say anything
but I only accepted the missions
that would keep me here, to forget.
The girl's mother
never held it against me.
We hadn't planned anything,
it just happened
and the girl,
I never knew,
but I think
she must have hated me.
Then, when she turned seventeen
she became beautiful
and she met Franck Manzella.
My daughter became
Franck Manzella's mistress.
Then his brother Joe's mistress,
and they used her
in their business.
When you called me
to protect the Grecos,
because the father
as going to talk,
I knew he would denounce
Joe and my daughter.
I didn't hesitate.
You see...
she is my daughter.
Lie down.
Tomorrow,
I'm going to have you arrested.
Where's the lizard?
Where is it?
Maybe he'd like some toast
and butter,
what do you think,
scrambled eggs?
Okay. Here,
you sit over here darling.
Get your tush up
don't fall off.
Okay, put a little milk in the bowl,
okay let's see, okay lambsky,
here we go. Breakfast.
There's a plane tomorrow at 9:00.
We're taking it.
- Wait...
- We're taking it!
I'll call Giovanni.
- Do it now.
- Nice milk...
Lamby.
- Come on lamby.
- I'm leaving.
- You're imagining things.
- I'm afraid here, of everything,
- even afraid of you.
- He doesn't want any milk.
I don't know what's happening
but its...
How far will you go?
Forgive me.
The sea is getting rough. If we
don't go we could be stuck here.
What about Ettore?
You wanted all this.
There is nothing I can do for him.
Don't use him now.
Call Giovanni.
Giovanni. Matt.
Del Piero's dead.
What?
He poisoned himself.
He was found
at the edge of the swimming pool.
He poisoned himself?
Was there a note?
No.
Who found him?
Susanna. I've got to go.
I'm there now.
Okay, okay.
Did you call Giovanni?
I lost a friend,
in Boscoreale.
Marty Del Piero.
We worked together in New York,
a long time ago.
I'm through here.
I want to go home.
Tomorrow, after the funeral.
You little prick!
Are you fuckin' trying to kill me?
Are you crazy?
Mommy, I can't find Ettore.
Ettore! Ettore!
Where's Ettore?
Tina.
- Love, did you see Ettore leave?
- No.
Ettore!
Giovanni, it's Jessie.
I can't find Ettore anywhere.
I don't know what's happened.
Do you know where Matt is?
Could you come over right away?
Yes, right away. Thank you.
Matt!
Ettore has disappeared,
Giovanni thinks
he might have gone to Ginostra.
Jessie, Jessie.
Is there any news of Ettore?
Calm down.
We'll find him. I promise you.
Don't worry. He just needed
to get away, okay?
Where's Matt?
Is the funeral over?
He's probably with the magistrates.
All the officials were there.
People want to get to know Matt.
Especially his methods.
I need to find Matt.
I need to tell him about Ettore.
You will. I am going to Ginostra.
Ettore must have gone back there.
I called the helicopter,
it's arriving.
But, I need the car.
But... Matt has mine.
I need to be able to leave.
I can't just be left stranded here.
Matt will be back soon.
Don't worry.
You have to stay here anyay.
In case Ettore comes back.
I need the car.
Thank you.
Let's go. Quickly.
Go, go.
Ettore!
Ettore! Stop!
- What you doing? Are you alright?
- Let go of me.
I killed Manzella.
I'm free now.
You took my gun.
It's starting to wake up.
We need to evacuate. Call the base.
Icarus to base,
Icarus to base...
The volcano is erupting
we must evacuate the island.
I repeat.
We must evacuate the island.
I see a car.
It's Manzella's car.
You see the body?
I see a body by the car. Lower!
I can't. There's a side wind.
That's Benson's car.
Lower!
The body is Manzella.
Get out of here. Now!
Ettore!
What's happening?
- We're getting out of here.
- What about Ettore?
What about him?
- I'm letting him go.
- But I thought...
- It's all over.
- Matt...
- He's Giovanni's problem now.
- Tell me what's happening!
Start packing!
My car slipped into the crater
and crashed into Manzella's pick-up.
They will accuse me of his murder
when they find the two cars.
I'll say it was me,
it's the truth.
I am a criminal because
I'm keeping a criminal in my house.
Get the hell out of here.
- You're free.
- Where do you want me to go?
- They want to kill me.
- I'll tell them you ran away.
It's Giovanni.
They've come to arrest him.
What did you do?
I'm not a murderer.
A revenge is not a murder.
Matt, stop them!
Don't let them land.
Bastard!
I can't. I can't get it down.
Elena!
Elena! Elena!
What are you doing?
We must leave. They're evacuating.
No, I've been waiting for years.
I've got to get Matt.
He killed Manzella.
The volcano is going to fuck me.
I have to get a picture of the cars.
- Elena, come on!
- No, no.
Come on lamb, come on.
Come on lamby.
Come on lamby, let's play.
If the lave covers the evidence,
I'm screwed.
Where's your damn camera?
He didn't do it.
What?
I was with Matt. He was here,
at the time Manzella disappeared.
What are you talking about?
You heard me.
You fucked him?
I didn't say that. I said he didn't
kill Manzella. He is innocent.
What about you?
Are you innocent too?
- Bitch!
- If you insist, I'll testify.
You fucking bitch!
We're safe here.
Even if there is a tidal wave.
We're on high ground.
The guards have left!
- They obey Giovanni.
- Come on lamby, come on.
Come and play with me.
Come on lamby, come on.
Come on lamby,
Mommy, mommy, come and see,
the lamby's sick.
Maybe you played with it too much.
It's not a toy.
- It's a bomb.
- What?
They've put a bomb in it.
Get away!
What?
It's all right.
Mommy, what's happening?
I'm scared.
Jessie!
It's all over. Sweetheart.
You alright?
Okay, okay, sweetheart?
You okay? It's alright.
It's all over.
It's all over now.
It's done.
This is Benson. Tell him to come
and get us at the Villa Massina.
The boy's back.
He's okay.
Tell him to hurry.
Fucking weather.
Ginostra wakes up
and everything goes to hell.
I know what you did.
What did I do?
Forget it.
I've come for the boy.
Manzella's dead.
I'm responsible for him.
You can't keep him here any longer.
- I'll bring him back tomorrow.
- No, no. I'll take him.
Let him get his things.
Someone is going to
come and get his stuff tomorrow.
- I'll get his coat.
- What?
Matt, what are you doing?
Matt!
Giovanni!
Give me the boy!
- Give me the boy.
- What?
- Come on. I'll bring him tomorrow!
- What are you talking about?
Matt, Matt!
Matt! Help me!
Matt!
He's chained me. Help!
Matt, help me!
They are coming to get me.
What are you doing? Stop it!
Ettore! Brake the light!
The stones in your pocket!
Break the light!
- Bastard!
- Matt.
Take his gun!
Wash your hands.
Wash them good.
Giovanni is coming!
It's not Giovanni.
It's for us.
- We have to go right now.
- Where are we going?
- Back to New York.
- What about Ettore?
He's coming with us.