MAN: Kate, you come here right now!
(WHIMPERING)
- Oh, God. Oh, my God.
- Kate!
Daddy, please, just listen to me.
- Just listen to me, please.
- Katherine, you stop.
You don't understand.
No, please, daddy, no!
Get away from there.
No, no, please.
Ooh! Ugh!
Bitch!
Come back here.
Katherine, come here.
You get out of there.
Come back here.
So why do you need a surrogate?
Well, four years ago I miscarried,
and shortly after I was
diagnosed with ovarian cancer.
I always knew that I
wanted to have children,
so I had my eggs frozen and...
Then they took out the ovaries and
the tubes and... you name it.
And then just last month I was told
that I have one viable
embryo left in the fridge,
so this is my last shot.
Are you married?
Yeah, he's... he's excited
about doing this.
- What's his name? What does he do?
- Jacob. He's a writer and a teacher.
Jacob, Jacob Kelly? Jacob
Kelly, the novelist?
That's my guy.
So like we talked about
in last semester's class,
what your character does,
particularly at the end of the story,
spells out the meaning
of the story.
Ms. McKendrick, your ending,
who does what to whom
with which and why?
Well, she kills the bad girl,
but that's so cliche.
My story sucks.
Not so fast. What
does your villain do?
Remember, everyone, your villain is more
important to the plot than your hero.
So keep an eye on the bad
girl. What else you got?
Well, it's about this little boy...
And it's about their relationship.
There's a scene where the
girl's in love with the guy.
- Yeah.
- Right, okay?
So how do you show it?
Well, I don't want to be obvious.
No, it's okay. Please, be obvious.
You all know Kate, right?
Works in the front office.
So let's say your character
does something like...
And you can just help me demonstrate
here, something like...
Oh, Professor Kelly.
Oh, my gosh.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
I seriously think this
semester more than any other
the kids seem really,
really engaged.
You should hear some
of the stories...
- Hi, Jacob.
- Hi. Hey.
I wanted to tell you that
everybody in the office
thinks that you are one of
the best teachers on campus.
Thank you.
- Would you sign this?
- Sure.
I'm excited to start reading it.
If only you knew how much I
needed to hear that right now.
Are you working on anything now?
Yeah, I'm working on a
new outline right now.
So, um, uh...
Truthfully, I have sort of been
blocked for a while lately.
But I'll get back to it someday.
Well, I'm sure whichever novel
you do next will be amazing.
Thanks.
- Hey, sweetie. Sorry, I'm late.
- Hey, hi.
I was showing a house on the west
side and the buyer was late.
Oh, man. Kate, you
remember my wife, Allison.
Yes, hi, from the Christmas party.
Yes, hi, Kate. Good. How are you?
Good. How's the real es...?
- Hey, can I talk to you real quick?
- Sure, yeah.
I don't know if I could do it.
What?
Forgive a man after
he cheated on me.
Jacob Kelly had an affair?
Oh, you didn't know?
Yeah, he talked about it on TV.
Happened about five years ago.
With who?
Some old girlfriend from college.
You know, maybe I
could forgive him.
Good-looking man like that?
ALLISON: So the cost is a
little more than we thought.
JACOB: What are we talking about?
All in, about 90.
$90,000?
I thought it was
going to be like 15.
Well, 15 is the surrogate's fee,
and then there's the
fertility drugs and the IVF,
and they've got to transfer the
embryo and... there's a lot.
I mean, you know, we talked
about this a year ago.
Yeah, I know we
suggested this before,
but why don't we just
get a friend to do it?
Okay, who? I mean,
do you know someone?
Well, no.
Look, I really like this girl.
Her name is Remy.
We have a meeting with her
tomorrow morning at 10.00 A.M.
At the carrier's clinic.
Okay.
Please don't worry. I've got time.
WOMAN: I was a surrogate for
my older sister three years ago,
and, well, I really loved
being pregnant, you know?
And the feeling of having a
life growing inside you it's...
It's just indescribable.
And... and I would want every
woman to experience that.
And my heart goes out
to women who can't,
and, you know, that's the
main reason why I do this.
And what guarantee
do we have, that...
And, no offense, that Remy won't be
out drinking and partying all night?
Well, all of our surrogates
are tested regularly.
- That won't be an issue.
- Okay.
Besides, Remy has never been
a party animal, correct?
That's right. I'm pretty boring.
Now, why don't the two of you
go away, think about it,
and when you've reached a decision,
come back and we'll talk about it?
Actually, we are ready to do this.
Well, good, great.
Here you go.
Where do we sign?
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah, that was quick.
That was very fast.
Well, all right, so
we're gonna do this.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Well, that was... That was quick.
And, uh, and I guess this is it.
Hey, listen, we can
give you a ride.
Oh, no, the metro's really close.
- Thank you, though.
- Sure.
And I guess we'll see you
at the hospital next week.
Okay, great.
Well, I look forward to...
Having our baby.
There it is. Put it
right out there.
Yeah. Yeah, okay, well
it was nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you.
- Bye.
Okay, bye.
Oh, come on, don't do this.
I'm sorry.
How... how am I supposed be
excited about the thought of you
carrying someone else's
fetus inside of you?
We need the money, Matt.
I'm doing this for us.
I know.
So what do they do for a living?
Well, she is a real estate agent,
and he's a famous novelist.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What's his name?
Jacob Kelly.
I have never heard of him.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm going to shower.
Oh. Oh.
- Ooh!
- What?
Nancy just texted me.
She's back in town.
She got a new cell phone
and she wants to do
something later tonight.
"See you at 9:00."
(CAR ALARM WAILS)
Ugh. Man.
Can I help you?
Hi.
I'm such a klutz sometimes.
I'm Susan.
- Remy.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you so much.
- No problem, no problem.
- Do you come here a lot?
- Hi.
- Hey.
Are you waiting for someone?
Yeah, a friend of mine.
She's late. What about you?
I just got a call.
He changed his mind.
Oh, no.
Yeah, online dating.
That's what I get.
What are you drinking?
Uh, juice mix.
Really? Slow down, girl.
Well, can I get you another one?
We can celebrate my
getting stood up.
That's all right.
No, come on. I insist.
Okay.
All right, okay. I'll be back.
What can I get you?
Uh, two juice mixes.
Two? All right.
All right, there you
go. Two juice mixes.
- That'll be...
- Keep the change.
- Thank you so much.
- Thanks.
- Juice mix.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
To girl's night out.
- To getting stood up.
- Yeah.
I think those guys over there
want to dance with us.
(LAUGHS) Oh, no.
- What?
- I don't... don't dance.
- Oh, come on. You're at a club.
- No.
- You have to dance at a club.
- No, really. Thank you, but no.
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC)
Whoo!
Yeah! Whoo!
Hey, Remy. You okay?
Yeah, we gotta go get Nancy,
cause I think she's down there.
No, Nancy's not here.
No, Nancy's down...
Come with me upstairs.
We'll get some fresh air.
Okay, well...
No, it's this way. Come on.
Come on. Oh, you okay?
Yeah. That's... If we
bring her upstair...
I don't want to leave
her out there.
Oh, no, she's not...
Nancy's not coming.
Come on.
Oh, come on. We're almost there.
Where we going?
Where you going? Come on.
Oh. Come on.
Look at the view.
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna call my
boyfriend. I need to go.
Here, I'll do it. Let me help you.
Let me do it. I got it.
Here. I got it.
Give me your purse.
- You're going to fall.
- Thank you.
Oh, come on. Come up here. Come on.
No, I'm not going over there.
- No, I want to call my boyfriend.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- No.
- It's totally safe.
- Look at this view.
- Whoa.
No, this is... This is nuts.
Hey, are you going to call
my boyfriend or not? I don't...
(BOTH GRUNTING)
What are you doing? Are
you crazy? Get off of me.
- Get back here.
- Get off of me!
Who the hell are you?
Aah!
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Get off of me! No!
Please don't!
Aah!
(BODY THUDS)
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
Hey, Susan. You're like me. You
park half a mile from the club.
Hey, let me buy you a
coffee or something, huh?
There's this wonderful little
cafe right around the corner.
- I have to work tomorrow.
- At Whittendale?
Yeah. How did you know?
Come on, one coffee, huh? You
said you didn't have a boyfriend.
I don't, but I am in
love with someone.
Does he know how lucky he is?
Ow.
He will soon.
JACOB'S VOICE:
Why do kids like it? I don't know.
Maybe it's because the
story is about something
that I went through
when I was a kid.
You see, high school, college,
things that we do at
that time in our life
that sort of define who
we are later on in life.
I believe that...
BOTH: That everyone has a story to tell,
everyone, some event from their past
that they feel the need to
convey to another person.
- Why?
- Loneliness.
Loneliness.
We all want someone to
understand who we are.
I love you, Jacob Kelly.
As soon as I received the news, I
called you immediately. I'm so sorry.
- Was it suicide?
- The police don't think so.
Preliminary toxicology report...
found ecstasy in her system.
Ecstasy? What kind of operation
are you running here?
Your girls are supposed
to be completely sober.
I can assure you that we did
a complete background check,
drug testing, everything. I would
never have given you her profile
if I had seen anything
in there that was wrong.
Since we've already
started this process,
I think it's important that we find
another surrogate that you both like.
I have a few candidates
here I'd like you to see.
No, thank you. We're done here.
- I'll take my check back.
- Well, no, Mr. Kelly,
please just take a couple of
more days to think about this.
You give us our $10,000, or you're
going to be hearing from our lawyer.
I think it's best that
you find another match.
Just come on. Let's go.
You didn't have to
blow up like that.
I'm sorry.
(PHONE RINGS)
Hi, Matt.
Why are you so happy?
It's good to see you.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Nancy.
Um... Remy's dead.
What?
Last night after the club,
she went to the roof
and somehow she fell.
The police said that
she took ecstasy.
I think somebody forced it on her.
Did you see anything?
Did I... did I see anything?
What do you mean?
Yeah, you were with
her last night. Did...
No, Matt, I'm in San Francisco.
(CABLE CAR BELL RINGS)
I haven't seen Remy.
I haven't been to L.A.
in over two years.
Matt? Matt?
I really thought that we had this
whole thing figured out, you know?
It makes you wonder if any of these
agencies can be trusted at all.
Have you thought about, I don't
know, asking a friend to do it?
Yeah, yeah, but Allison doesn't
think we'll find anybody.
Oh, sure you can.
She just has to have had
a baby before, right?
Yes. Beth, you have a kid.
What are you doing for
the next nine months?
Oh, no. I'm not going
through that again.
Exactly.
Thanks, though. I'll see you.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Do you have a second?
Um, yeah, sure.
I had a baby when I was 20.
I could do it. If you wanted me to.
Uh, when Jacob told me you
were willing to do this,
I was quite surprised.
Oh, I'm happy to help.
So, we did a background
check, no criminal record.
I called all three of the
references you gave us,
and everyone had really great
things to say about you.
Well, that's good.
But when I checked
your credit history,
I noticed something
kind of strange.
Really?
Kate, you have a credit line
of close to a million dollars,
which means you're worth
a great deal of money.
That's pretty unusual
for someone your age.
Yeah, that... that is
because of my inheritance.
My father passed away
a few years ago.
Look, I know that you
don't know me very well,
but when Jacob told me
the story about what
you've been through,
losing your baby and
then the cancer,
I just... I felt like helping you
is the right thing to do.
Would you just give us a second?
Oh. Of course.
We barely know her.
We know her better than
we knew the last girl,
and I'm not going back to
one of those agencies.
I don't know.
I like the fact that she gave
her baby up for adoption.
That shows me that she wants
what's best for the child.
Listen, I know how badly
you want this baby.
And I do too.
ALLISON: All right.
I need to be straight with you.
We've put 12 embryos
in the freezer.
11 of them didn't make it.
We have one viable embryo,
one chance to make this work.
You've got to promise me
you won't let us down.
I won't.
All right. Let's make a baby.
Oh, my gosh.
Uh, we drew up this contract.
You can just take it home and
take a look, okay? Just give it a...
Let's take a picture
of all three of us.
- Yes.
Oh, my, gosh, okay.
- Can you do it?
- Do you want...
- Yeah. Yeah, right there.
- Okay.
All right, like that?
Okay, Kate, now I'm going
to extend the catheter
through your cervix to
the top of your uterus.
JACOB: Now it might be a
little bit uncomfortable,
but it should only take a minute.
Take as much time as you want.
I want to enjoy this.
She was with some chick.
Can you... Can you describe her?
Brunette, short hair, hot body.
I don't know. I can't get
more specific than that.
I get 20 or 30 of her
in here every night.
Was she with anybody else?
Not really, no.
But her friend, though,
short hair brunette girl,
there was this one guy
hitting on her pretty hard.
He comes in here
every now and then.
He's, like, an Iranian guy.
So did you find a cure
for your writer's block?
Actually, I'll be taking on
more classes next semester,
so there just isn't time
to write another book.
- Come on, sweetie.
- Hey, why don't you leave that...
and why don't you go show
Kate the nursery upstairs?
Oh, Kate, wait till you
see it. It's so cute.
You should never stop writing.
That's your gift to the world.
You should be able to write
all day long if you want to.
I'm sorry.
I just, I really, really
enjoyed your book.
That's all.
Oh, wow.
Oh, this is so cute.
Yeah, we put it together a couple
of years ago before I miscarried.
Oh.
Look at this.
And these.
Jacob actually built this crib.
Well, do you want a boy or a girl?
Well, hopefully just
someone who likes pink.
Have you guys picked a name?
Oh.
It's my grandma's name.
My mom actually made this.
Oh, Allison, you have no idea
how happy it makes me
to see you so excited.
Well, you are literally making
our dreams come true, so...
So, what's it like knowing
pretty soon you're
going to be a mom?
It's, um, it's as if...
I already have this...
Connection to her
even though I haven't even met her.
I lay in bed at night
dreaming about what it'll
feel like to hold her.
I've been waiting for years.
But I know in my heart that
everything is going to be...
wonderful.
- Okay, ready? Okay.
- Yes.
- Smile. Gorgeous.
- I'm smiling.
Your turn.
- I... I don't really... I don't...
- Just do it.
- Smile, okay?
- Okay.
Okay, perfect. Give me two secs.
- Weird.
- Quirky.
All right, dessert.
Okay, let's check this out.
What are you having?
- Okay, ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay, look.
- What?
Oh, you got to check this out.
It's cool right?
Look.
It's an app. I downloaded it.
It's "make your baby's face.com".
Oh, my God. It's amazing, Kate.
- I can e-mail you a copy if you want.
- Yeah.
Do you mind if I use the restroom?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thanks.
It's incredible.
- Special delivery.
- Thank you.
- Who are these from?
- I have no idea.
Hey.
No abnormalities that I can see.
Bloodflow is good.
Everything looks normal.
Matt, couple months waiting
around paid off, buddy.
That's your guy. Right
down there, black shirt.
So this girl that she was with, the
bartender said she had dark hair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Her name was Susan.
She was gorgeous, man.
But she blew me off.
I was about to drive home when
I saw her walking to her car.
What kind of car?
It's a blue Mazda Hatchback.
You know what?
She did have one of those employee
parking stickers on her car.
It was... it was for a college.
Whitmore?
Whittendale?
Yeah, that was it. That was it.
(RINGS DOORBELL)
Hey, Kate. What are you doing here?
- Can I come in?
- Sure.
What is it? What's the matter?
- Nothing. You're not going to understand.
- Something's wrong. You can tell me.
- You can talk to me.
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
Okay, why don't you sit down?
- No.
- I'll get you a glass of water.
Water is fine. Water is good.
- Okay. All right.
- Okay.
Okay. Here you go. Take a sip.
Okay. Now tell me what's the matter.
You're starting to scare me a little bit.
It's... you're not going to
understand if I tell you.
- I got to go.
- Kate what... wait a second.
- No!
- Kate.
- Don't touch me!
- Kate. Kate.
- No!
- Kate.
Leave me alone!
Jacob, what's wrong with her?
Where is she... Where is she going?
I...I have no idea. She
came over here all upset.
- Is she all right? I mean...
- I don't know.
- What did you do to her?
- Nothing. Nothing.
I asked her what was the matter,
but she wouldn't tell me.
- Well, did you touch her?
- No.
Why was she screaming "don't
touch me" if you didn't touch her?
I wasn't touching her,
okay? I don't know.
I kept asking her and she wouldn't tell
me what was going on. I don't know.
God, I'll talk to her.
The last thing that I
wanted to do was upset you.
That's why I haven't said
anything about this.
Tell me what happened.
I want to know everything.
Um, well, it started my
first week on the job.
The things that he would say.
I thought it was harmless,
but then when I had the
embryo transferred,
he started e-mailing me.
I see his e-mails. He
hasn't been writing you.
From his faculty address,
not his personal.
Well, what did he say?
Just chatting about the baby,
how happy you are.
And then he started
getting romantic.
I told him I didn't think it was
appropriate for him to write those things.
So he stopped. And
then a few weeks ago
I got a huge bouquet of red
roses delivered to me.
And you're sure they're from him?
The card said, "from Jacob."
And this.
He even asked me to meet
him at a hotel last weekend.
I want to see the e-mails.
(BEEP)
Hi, this message is for Jennifer.
My name is Jacob Kelly,
and I'm calling regarding a
letter of recommendation
that you wrote for Kate Randall.
He wrote me about 10 times.
I told him if he didn't knock
it off I was going to tell you.
What were you doing
at the house today?
This morning at school
he asked me to come by.
Allison, I swear he said
that you would be there.
And when I got to your
house, you weren't there.
And that is when he
tried to kiss me.
I didn't do any of that.
She is out of her mind.
Then how do you explain this?
Your credit card
statement, roses, $300.
I didn't buy anybody flowers.
Lingerie, 450.
You spent more on that hotel than
you spent on our entire honeymoon.
Okay, look, she got ahold
of my credit card number.
Oh, God, come on. Don't
treat me like an idiot.
- I read the e-mails.
- What e-mails?
From the school website, back
and forth between you and Kate.
What? I don't even use that.
Nobody uses that website.
Okay? I haven't even checked
my profile in months.
- Kate says all of the teachers use it.
- Okay, well I don't use it.
When I want to talk to my
students, I do it in class.
I...I didn't write any of those.
Yeah, you did. I know
your writing style.
A lot of people know
my writing style.
Do you know how easy it is for a school
employee to hack into my faculty e-mail?
Is that what happened?
I don't know, she's trying to
make me look bad for some reason,
and I had a feeling that I was
wrong about her, but now I'm sure.
I called back her references.
I'm going to talk to somebody
that knows this woman.
Just admit it. You're scared
of being a father, are you?
What? That's... That's ridiculous.
So you thought you'd treat yourself
to one final personal
bachelor party
before getting serious
and raising a child.
Would you please just listen
to yourself right now?
This is just like you and that old college
girlfriend of yours from five years ago.
First of all, it was
seven years ago,
and she wasn't my
girlfriend in college.
You'll never change. It's my fault.
It's my fault for trusting you,
but I want you out of this house.
- Ali, wait a second.
- You go stay in a hotel.
- Apparently you can afford it.
- Ali, come on.
(RINGS DOORBELL)
REMY: He's a famous novelist.
Really? What's his name?
Jacob Kelly.
I have never heard of him.
(GATE CREAKING)
Ugh! Ugh!
You're hurting the baby!
Shut up!
You're in love with that
novelist aren't you?
You want to have his baby so bad,
you killed my girlfriend.
Just to get the job.
Isn't that right?
(WHIMPERS)
Hey, you don't want
to talk, that's fine.
Just call Jacob Kelly and see what
he has to say about this, huh?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
This is Jacob.
Mr. Kelly, my name is Matt.
I'm Remy's boyfriend.
I got some information
about your surrogate.
Agh!
(COUGHS)
Hello, are you there?
(LINE RINGING OUT)
Hey, it's Matt. Leave
a message, thanks.
(BEEP)
Hi, this is Jacob Kelly.
I guess we got disconnected.
Call me back when you
can please. Thanks.
I got a call from Matt.
Do you know him,
by any chance, Kate?
Remy's boyfriend?
He called to tell me he had
information about my surrogate.
What do you think he
was talking about, Kate?
Leave me alone.
Why did you hack into
my e-mail at school?
Why... why did you write all
of those things in my name?
If you don't leave right now,
I'm calling the police.
You stole my credit card
number and you went shopping.
If anybody's going to call the
police here, it's going to be me.
Kate, you're pregnant with my
kid. What are you thinking?
What are... are you trying
to ruin my marriage?
Is that what's going on? Because I
don't get it. I don't get any of it.
I don't get why you'd
want to hurt my wife,
who by the way, thinks you two are
pretty much best friends right now.
Look, just tell me why
you're doing this.
What have I done to hurt you?
Let go of me. Don't touch me.
No, we're not done,
Kate. We're not done.
I am going to do whatever
I have to do to...
Jacob, get out of here!
Stop it! Just get out of my house.
What the hell you looking at?
It's in excellent condition.
It's 2500 square feet. It's
four bedrooms, three baths.
(PHONE RINGS)
Oh, excuse me one second.
It's open. You can go on in.
I'll meet you inside.
Hey, Kate. What's up?
Jacob came to my house
and attacked me.
He did what?
(PHONE BUZZES)
Let me guess. Kate called you.
How could you do this?
Well, it was easy. She deserved it.
Have you lost your mind?
Jacob, no one deserves to
be beaten half to death.
What?
She just called me from
the hospital, Jacob.
13 stitches and, God, you
could have hurt the baby.
What the hell are
you talking about?
You go to her house
and beat her up?
You've always had
a temper, but I...
Okay, wait. Stop. Ali, she's lying.
Don't deny it, okay?
The neighbors saw you.
I did not hit her.
Look, not only is this woman
insane, she's dangerous.
What hospital is she in?
You stay away from Kate, all right?
And you know what? You stay away
from me too, you son of a bitch.
Ali, are you...?
Ali, are you there?
Yeah, that's good.
Kate?
- Oh, my God. Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- I am so sorry that this happened.
- No, no, it's not your fault.
How's the baby?
Oh, they just did an ultrasound.
Everything is good.
Oh, thank God.
I can't even believe that he
would do something like this.
It's my fault.
I never should have told you that
Jacob was infatuated with me.
No, no, nothing is
your fault, okay?
We just...
We both need to stay away
from him until the baby's born.
I know that he's sorry
for what he did.
Don't worry.
I told them that I
fell down the stairs.
I'm not going to press
charges or anything.
Oh, I forgot.
Um... it's a boy.
It's a boy?
It's a little baby boy.
We... we have to
buy some blue paint.
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah.
Store these at campus security for
me. He can pick them up there.
And I need you to shut down the following...
His access card to the building,
his parking pass, and
the faculty e-mail.
- Beth.
- Then call maintenance.
- What's going on?
- Hey, Professor Kelly,
I was wondering if you
could read my short story.
You're fired.
What? Is that a joke?
I mean, you can't
possibly be serious.
What did you tell them, Kate?
What did you tell them?
Wow, you're good.
Let me ask you something, did you get
somebody to punch you in the face,
or were you able to do
that all by yourself?
You can leave now, Mr. Kelly.
Beth, she's a liar, okay?
She's doing this to frame me.
Beth, come on.
You know what, Shawn?
Go ahead and put that under my desk,
because I'm going to be right back.
And, Valerie, yes, I would be very
happy to read your short story.
Yeah, I left you a message regarding a
reference that you wrote for Kate Randall.
Uh-huh.
Yes, I need to talk to one
of Kate's family members
or anybody that's known
Kate her whole life.
I'd start with her dad's business.
- Okay, her father's name is Edward?
- Yes.
Edward Randall. And, I'm sorry,
what was the name of his company?
It was a shipping company.
I was Ed Randall's
secretary for ten years.
When he died, new
management took over.
I was the first person they let go.
Luckily I found another job.
Did you by any chance
know his daughter, Kate?
You mean, Katherine? Of course.
Ed talked about her
all the time. Why?
Well, my wife and I hired
her to be our surrogate,
and now she's just causing all sorts of
trouble, and I want to go to the police,
but I don't have... I don't have
anything concrete to tell them.
Sounds familiar. Katherine
was a nightmare.
She made her father so angry he quit
communicating with her entirely.
Why?
Why? Are you kidding?
The baby.
Because she gave the
baby up for adoption?
Adoption? Is that
what she's saying?
Her baby died.
She said it was crib death.
But I could tell that the way Edward
talked about it he didn't believe her.
And then there was all that
business with the will
and his estate and the lawyers.
She screwed over
everybody, me included.
Would you be willing to
tell this story to my wife?
All right, yes. Thank you.
- So you believe me now?
- No, she's just bitter.
I mean, Kate got all of
her father's inheritance,
and this secretary lady
didn't get anything.
What do I have to do
to convince you, Ali?
Why would Kate kill her own baby?
It just... It doesn't
make any sense.
Why would she beat herself
up to get me fired?
None of what she's
doing makes any sense.
And that's not the
only thing, okay?
Last night I got a phone
call from a guy named Matt,
said he was Remy's boyfriend.
Said he had information
about our surrogate,
and then the line went dead.
I called him back and
there was no answer.
So go to the police.
And tell them what?
What proof do I have?
I have nothing.
Ali, just look at me please.
Just look at me.
I'm your husband, okay?
I'm the guy that you fell
in love with 16 years ago.
I'm the guy that still
loves you right now
no matter how much you
hate me in this moment.
Why won't you believe me?
JACOB: Congratulations.
You took away most
of it, didn't you?
My wife, my job.
I suppose what's next
is you call the cops
and you take away
my freedom, but...
Before you do that, I just
have one little request.
I want to know why.
Please. Why?
Please.
I read BlackBerry Winter
over a hundred times.
It changed my life.
Jacob, it changed everything.
And the first time I
saw you on television,
I knew you were my soul mate.
Alexandria.
Yes. That's my pen name.
I'm going to show you something.
KATE: I have been waiting
for this moment for so long.
I knew that one day you would come
and you would be
standing right there.
I love you.
I wrote you every two days
for six years straight.
Even when the letters came back,
I didn't lose hope that some day...
Some day you would write me back.
When my father died,
I had to find you.
I got a job at Whittendale
just so I could be close to you.
I'm sorry I had to get
you in so much trouble,
but it was the only way
for us to be together.
Jacob, you're free.
Allison left you. Besides,
she can't give you babies.
I can.
And you don't have
to teach anymore.
I liberated you from
that awful job.
We can live together in
my father's mansion.
It's up in the mountains.
It's so far away,
nobody will bother us.
Jacob, we can have this
baby that I'm carrying,
and then at night we
can make our own.
ALLISON: Hi, Kate.
I'd punch you in the nose,
but I'm afraid you'd enjoy it.
What actually happened to Remy?
Why did her boyfriend call Jacob?
Maybe she didn't accidentally
fall from that building?
I think we need to
talk to the cops.
No.
If you call the police,
I will kill this baby.
Okay. Okay.
If you try to trick me
or have me arrested,
I don't care. I'll
drink rat poison.
I'll take a coat hanger to it.
- Kate.
- I don't care.
I will do whatever it takes,
but I will not let this baby live.
You would actually kill
yourself and my child?
If I can't get Jacob
Kelly to love me,
what is the point of living?
Oh, Kate, honey, you need help.
I don't need anyone's help!
Okay.
Get out of my house.
Leave!
Go!
Well, what happens if we
turn her into the police?
Well, they'll take
her into custody,
but they can't watch
her 24 hours a day.
She can still make good on
her threat to harm the baby,
even in jail.
Are you saying there's
nothing that we can do?
Look, definitely gather as much
of a paper trail as you can,
credit card statements,
e-mails, all of that.
It'll help us if we decide
to sue her later.
I'm sorry.
But I think the only
options you have
are to go to the police and
accept the consequences,
or you can try to work
something out with her.
You okay?
We could just do what she wants.
Hmm?
She's in love with you, so...
We could just play along with it.
Until she delivers.
Ali, it's, like, three
in the morning.
No, listen to me. You could...
You could go live with her
and I could follow you
and stay in a camper or
rent a cabin or something
and... and then when
she gives birth
we could take the
baby from her and...
And we turn her in to the cops.
Right?
You expect me to go live with her?
Because a couple of days ago
you were ready to divorce me
because you thought I
was cheating on you.
I don't like the idea,
but I'm willing to, I don't know,
make the sacrifice in
order to save our child.
Your sacrifice?
I hate this woman.
We cannot let her kill our baby.
We have to keep tabs on her.
One of us has to be
watching her 24/7.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
What are you doing here?
I'm yours.
I don't believe you.
Allison is done with me.
She blames me for bringing
you into our lives.
Oh, yeah?
You're carrying the
only viable embryo,
taking away her last chance of becoming
a mother, and I let you do it.
She's never going to forgive me.
You're lying.
I'm here, aren't I?
Do you think that you could love
me after everything I've done?
I'll try.
Try now.
There'll be plenty of
time for that later.
Can I borrow your cell phone?
What for?
Please, baby?
We only need mine.
I've prepared a nursery and a playroom
for the baby. It's just down the hall.
The Internet and landline
have been disconnected too,
so you can concentrate on your
writing and we can be left alone.
Sometimes I need the
Internet to do research.
My father has a huge
library. You can use that.
You've certainly
thought of everything.
There's something else
I want to show you.
This is for you.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
How's the writing going?
Good.
Can I read some pages?
Sure.
I think the woman should live.
Oh, oh, I like that she dies.
Yeah, but this scene is so violent.
I like that it's violent.
In fact, I was going to make her death
even more violent on my next pass.
Well...
I don't believe your
main character.
Okay.
What don't you believe?
What if...
she were 17 years old,
senior in high school.
No, she's 21.
She's 17. She's
practically a child.
Come here, sweetheart.
What if her father's friend,
a business partner, let's say,
wanted her to be his lover?
And this is Tony.
Heard so much about you, Katherine.
KATE: One day her dad leaves
her alone with this friend
and the friend forces her
to have sex with him.
- No, Tony stop.
- So he rapes her.
Yeah, he rapes her.
Good girl.
Gets her pregnant.
She wants an abortion,
but daddy says no.
He says that if she
gets an abortion,
he will write her out
of the family fortune.
- You can't do that to me.
- I'm doing it.
So she carries the baby.
For nine incredibly painful months,
thinking, of course,
that she could just
give the baby up for adoption
and be done with all this.
But, no.
Daddy wants her to keep the baby,
wants her to live
with his best friend.
Look, this is not the
end of the world.
It is for me.
KATE:
You see, it's a business deal.
In her father's eyes, she's
just a piece of property
to be traded for a majority
share in a competing company.
So she kills the baby.
She has to.
It's the only thing that she can do
to get herself out of the
situation, to be free.
When daddy looks into the crib,
he sees his grandchild dead.
He freaks out.
Kate, you come here right now.
He tries to kill the
main character.
Ooh!
But she gets away.
Daddy cuts her out of the
will, but she's smart.
On the night of his death,
she gets a hold of the one
executed copy of the new will.
And she shreds it.
Daddy's lawyers have to
resort to the old will,
where she gets it all.
In the end, she wins.
Big.
That, Mr. Kelly, is a great story.
And I want you to write it.
"My dearest Allison, I can't
tell you how much I miss you."
"Knowing that you're nearby
helps me get through this.
"I think of you every
waking moment,
"and I can't wait
until this is over.
"I adore you so much,
"even this writer
can't find the words.
Love, Jacob."
ALLISON: "Dear sexy world-famous
author whom I love so very much,
'we are so close to this
whole thing being over.
"Been watching the calendar,
"and she's in her final two weeks.
"As for me, I'm doing okay.
"I'm mostly worried about you.
Just be careful. I love you. Ali."
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
KATE:
Jacob, come out of there. Jacob.
Where is it?
JACOB: Where's what?
The story I told you, about
the 17-year-old girl?
I told you to write it, and
you haven't even started.
I will. Relax.
What's wrong?
You don't think it's a good story?
I think it's a sad story.
Then why haven't you
started to write it?
Why haven't you started writing it?
Answer me.
Because it's not my story.
It's your story, and
it's true, isn't it?
No, I made it up.
I talked to your dad's
secretary, Kate.
You killed your baby.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
You know you did.
Why?
Why did you do it?
Because that man raped me.
And my father forced
me to keep the baby.
You could have walked away, Kate.
You didn't have to kill that child.
But you did because you
hated your father,
and now you're feeling guilty about it,
so you want me to write your story
and make you look like a hero,
but I'm not going to do that!
Because you're not a hero.
You're a coward, and
you're a murderer!
Please wait. I need you.
I need you to write my story.
No one will listen to me.
But they'll listen to you.
They will listen to Jacob Kelly.
Do what I say,
or you know exactly what I will do.
Ah, yes, that's the girl I love.
What are you doing?
Making you famous.
Where are you going?
I'm just taking out the trash.
It's not very full. Can't
it wait until tomorrow?
Well it's such a nice house.
- I'm just trying to keep it clean.
- Okay, well, I'll come with you.
It's beautiful weather.
Let me grab my shoes.
No, it's just going to take a second. And
I finished the first chapter, so I want...
- I want to come back and show you.
- Okay, great.
Okay, I finished the first chapter.
You want to read it?
I made the changes
that you suggested,
and I actually think that
you're really going to love it.
Kate, you've got to
unlock this right now.
Why?
(SCREAMS)
You... are you okay?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
So you can write her
more love letters?
"My dearest Allison,
"the longer I am away from you,
the more I realize how
much you mean to me."
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
This is the worst thing
you have ever written.
- Okay.
- You know why?
'Cause it's a lie.
She's still controlling you, Jacob.
She's forcing you to write these letters
and hide them out in the wall, isn't she?
You need to calm down.
You need to realize you
don't love her anymore.
You love me.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I'm so... I'm so sorry.
She is the problem here, not you.
Okay.
You're going to just
relax, stay here,
and when I get back,
this little problem of ours
will be dead and gone.
Kate... Kate! Kate, no!
Kate, wait, come back! Kate!
Kate!
Aah!
(GROANS)
Okay. Okay.
Allison!
Oh, God.
(GROANS)
(RIFLE FIRES)
JACOB: Allison!
(SCREAMS)
This is it.
No! No!
Get your hands off of me.
This baby is coming right now.
No, it's not.
- Kate, you need to push.
- No, I won't.
- Kate, you have to push.
- Go to hell.
Push!
You can't make me.
If you don't push,
you will kill this child.
I don't care.
I'm getting this baby, Kate.
You need me.
You do what I say, or you are going
to die right now. You understand?
Now push! Push!
(SCREAMS)
Yes. Yes, harder.
Harder, Kate.
(BABY CRYING)
Kate, no. Kate, you need to rest.
Kate, don't do anything...
The sheriff will be
here any minute.
Kate.
Kate, it's over. Kate.
(WHIMPERS)
(SIREN WAILS)
That's her. That's Kate Randall.
ALLISON: She needs help.
Miss Randall.
Miss Randall, can you hear me?
Okay.
Come on.
You all right?
Yeah.
You want to tell me what happened?
You tell it.