You want food?
Uh, no thanks.
Just a little more coffee.
Thanks.
Two bucks for the coffee.
I have to go to work.
What?
I gotta go to work.
So go to work.
You think I care?
Good.
Go to work.
I'm going.
Get out of my way.
I'm here.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
I had something else to do.
Your shift started at 9:00.
I'm aware.
Hey.
Essentially, about,
a few years back
when Denver had--
That man will go broke
he's not more careful.
Stu?
I took money to the bank
this morning
and account's almost empty.
I told you years ago he'd run
this place into the ground.
No one's talking to you,
old man.
He'll pull it together.
Here you go--okay.
I'll be back.
All right.
Warm you up there?
Sure.
Thanks.
Mm hm.
Are you new in town?
Uh, just new to this route.
You're a truck driver.
You probably get a lot
of us through here, huh?
Yeah, I've seen my fair share.
Probably doesn't hurt that
you're the only town
for 50 miles.
A good point.
I'll leave you
to read your book.
I can change those for you.
I hate that machine.
Yeah, it's sensitive.
It's horrible.
Sorry, I said.
There you go.
Where's the closest
shower to here?
Uh, motel around the corner.
It's kinda gross though.
Yeah?
Why can't I use yours?
Heh, uh, you want anything else?
I can think of a few things.
Yeah, okay.
Hello there.
Hello, darling.
Would you like something to eat?
Oh my God.
Good job.
I'm amazing.
Yes, waitress, please,
thank you.
I, um, would love
to start with your...
oatmeal with milk
and sugar, please.
All right.
Levi?
Oatmeal, milk.
You think that's free 'cause we
put it on all the tables?
Uh.
Is, uh, is salt expensive?
We pay for it.
That means it's expensive enough
for you not to spill
it all over the place.
Yes, sir,
yes, sir.
I hear ya there, sir.
You two should learn
some respect.
What did I do?
So you got a break coming up?
Not really.
Levi, I have to go
to the bathroom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's two of us.
Does nobody work here no more?
This yours?
Ain't mine, babe.
I thought you were
getting back tomorrow.
You left the light on.
You have a bedroom,
you know.
Did you bring home any food?
Nuh-uh.
You wanna play?
Sure.
You wanna go first?
Yeah.
Too bad.
Oh.
Fran sucker!
How is that new bar?
It's a shit hole.
Did you get laid?
Yeah, kinda.
Where's the lucky lady?
I'm not bringing
those girls back here.
You can bring girls
here if you want.
Why you acting all weird?
I'm not acting weird.
Why aren't you trying
to piss me off then?
Francine?
Huh?
What're you doing?
Going to sleep.
All right, well...
What do you want?
Like, why did you wake me up?
I thought you might
wanna sleep in your bed.
Ow.
Do you wanna go get breakfast?
No.
Uh, there's shit to eat,
Francine.
Well, go to the store.
Give me some money
and I'll go shopping.
Why don't you get a job?
What's wrong with unemployment?
Um, it barely pays.
It pays a dickload considering
it's for doing nothing.
You ever thought that maybe
I have more important things
to do than pay your rent?
Not really.
Well, I do.
Last time I was working,
when you fucked your boss
and ruined his marriage,
you just sat around here
and listened
to sad vagina music.
That the kinda stuff
you wanna get back
to doing that's so important?
You know, I don't throw
your shit in your face.
Yeah, you do.
Like when?
I'm not having this
conversation right now.
The fucking sun's
not even up yet.
I'm going to bed.
You suck.
Fuck you.
Morning.
Good morning.
Want a grilled cheese?
Sure, thanks.
John called.
Yeah, I know.
It's good money.
You really wanna be married
to that guy again?
The guy who came home
at 6:00 every night
and who worked
on the house all weekend
and who got up before noon?
I thought you really liked my,
uh, flannel trucker look.
Sexier than the bank look.
Hey, Ben, Eliza,
your lunch is ready.
Hey, the kids get
the hats that I got 'em?
Yeah.
Yeah, they got the hats.
Yummy, yummy in my tummy.
Oh, come here!
Let me see you.
What is this?
What is this face?
I like your hat.
-Thanks.
-It looks good.
They're never leaving
the house in those.
Did you leave the house with it?
Yeah.
What did the neighbors say?
They said, "Time to move."
-They liked it?
-Uh huh.
-That's pretty cool.
-And they liked the way
I put mine backwards.
How'd you get so much more?
They call you "hip"?
You're hip?
No.
They called me awesome.
Really? Yeah.
Of course they did.
Why you look good?
I guess I got
a good night's sleep.
Wanna come in?
No.
Not today.
Well, what about tomorrow?
Tomorrow's my birthday, Dad.
Yeah, I know.
Okay, I know
you need to go, but--
You know what we discussed
about cell phones.
No, not until you're 16.
Jenny, why don't you
go start the car?
What, I can't even
give her a gift now?
I'm never gonna hear
the end of this.
You've made me
the bad guy, you know.
Well, let her keep the phone.
Stu, I really don't
wanna fight right now.
You know, I haven't seen
her in over two months.
I took the night off.
She's 15.
She wants to spend her birthday
with her friends
instead of her dad.
She'll grow out of it.
You look good.
You still doing okay?
Of course, Danielle.
I wanna make this work.
Look, I'll call you next week
and we'll find a time
for you to take her
out to dinner, okay?
Call me if you need me.
I think I got it.
How much longer
you have on the dryers?
Ten minutes.
You have a son, right?
Not no more.
There you go.
Thank you.
What're you guys
up to tonight?
You going out?
Just over to the mill.
Yeah, Jim's gonna find
us some strippers.
Easy, Frank.
I may have to find
that Russian girl later.
She's not Russian.
She's Serbian.
Is she around?
Do you need change for this?
It's all yours.
What's she so pissy about?
Bye, guys.
Mm-hm.
Yup.
So what's your deal?
You just drive in the northwest?
Yeah, I try to.
I try to stay near my family.
Got some time
to play cards with me?
Or you gotta go?
Depends on the game.
Depends on what you know.
Ah, Go Fish, Old Maid.
I might remember a little poker.
Ah, a cardshark, huh?
Let's play Go Fish.
All right.
You must have kids.
Seven and Five.
Hey.
Frank was looking for you.
See ya.
She's friendly.
She has her moments.
All right, you have any kings?
Oh man.
I...do.
I was gonna lie.
Don't lie.
Thank you.
So she's a friend of yours?
I mean, I like her.
That's half of it.
How about threes,
you got any threes?
Mm-mm, go fish.
She was a mail order bride.
-Really?
-Yup.
Hm, I have one of those.
No you don't.
For real?
No.
Nope, my wife and I, we met
the more traditional route.
So you guys
are still together?
Yeah, just had
our 10 year anniversary.
Well, congratulations.
Thanks.
Me or you?
Um...I don't know.
Where are all
the God damn customers?
I told 'em to go home so I can
play cards with this gentleman.
Wouldn't surprise me.
You go.
How about...
twos?
Yeah.
I got another one, too.
Oh, you were holding out.
That's not cool.
Thanks for the company.
I better go.
Move up.
Freckles On My Chin.
For a band?
I think that sucks.
What about Tiger Cock?
Bold.
It's got a ring.
It does.
No, get your own.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yours tastes better.
Mm, mm.
Oh, that's good.
Thank you.
You gotta go to the right.
Don't do that--
don't, no I don't like it.
-I wasn't gonna do that.
-I don't like it.
-I don't like being tickled.
I was not even tickling.
I don't--please don't.
Cut the fucking shit out, man.
Oh-oh, come on, come on.
If you think that's flirting,
then no wonder you're single.
Francine, just 'cause you bang
anyone that looks at you.
Shut up.
Then stop looking at me.
Fuck you, fuck you.
Corey said you went home
with some slut the other night.
So, when did you start taking
such an interest
in my nightlife?
I didn't.
Come here.
Do you like playing
with those guys?
Those guys out there?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's fun.
What if you guys
don't go anywhere?
Where are we gonna go, I mean,
we're not going anywhere, honey.
Corey thinks you will.
Yeah.
Corey.
Bless his heart, bless his
little--little thumper.
Come here.
Come here, please.
There, oh yes, see.
You're right,
we should make out.
That's a good idea.
No, I don't wanna make out.
I'll start.
You know, Corey can fucking
mind his own business.
I mean, what is he, your dad?
No.
He's not even
your brother, right?
Yeah, I know.
Right.
So what the fuck?
I guess we could make--
make love.
No, I don't want to.
Try that--have you
ever tried that?
No, I've never tried that.
I heard it's fun.
Hi, Jenny,
it's your dad again...
calling to see when
would be a good time
to get together
for your birthday dinner.
Better late than never, right?
Give me a call when you can.
Love you.
Hello.
Hi.
Hey.
Why are you here?
'Cause I was hungry.
How was your drive?
It was pretty standard.
Do you mind that I'm--
Uh, no, go ahead,
go right ahead, here.
Thanks.
So what's the attraction?
Of?
Truck driving.
I don't know.
Is that your rig?
My rig?
That's what they call it,
right?
Yeah.
Can I check it out?
How long you been
workin' at the diner?
Mm...12 years,
on and off.
Wow.
Gonna stay working there?
Mm...I don't know.
You wanna give it a go?
Okay.
A drive.
-Yeah.
-Come on.
All right,
here's your lesson, ready?
Mm-hm.
Hat on.
Thank you.
See that key right there?
-Mm-hm.
-That's your ignition.
-Yep.
-Engine.
Start right there.
Clutch, brake,
accelerator.
You know what this is.
-My stick.
-Yeah.
All right, so you're gonna
put in the clutch.
Okay.
And turn the ignition,
turn the key.
Yeah, it sticks
a little bit,
just wiggle it.
There you go,
hit the start.
Like that.
And release the brake.
-How do I do that?
-Just punch it in.
Okay.
All right.
So what you're gonna do
is you're gonna
put the clutch in,
and let it out slowly.
I'm going backwards.
Gonna go forward.
-Okay.
-All right.
There you go.
Got it?
I think so.
Okay.
Just give it
a little gas.
Start turning your wheel.
I feel like
it's gonna tip over.
Mm-mm, just keep going,
give it a little more gas.
-Okay.
-Good.
Straighten.
You wanna stop?
Yeah, I need to.
Put the clutch in,
all right?
And you're just gonna
hit the brake real lightly.
Ooh, sorry!
That's it,
hit the ignition.
-Hit the key.
-Uh-huh.
Pull out your brake.
That's it.
Nice job.
You're hired.
So...
...how much does one of these
bad boys cost?
That depends.
I got this one used,
so...
-It's a sleeper?
-Yeah.
It's fancy.
It's not that fancy.
It gets it done, though.
Hm.
It's bigger than
what I thought it would be.
-More books.
Boring.
I could sleep here.
Do you wanna come back here
with me?
It's probably not
a good idea.
You sure?
No.
I'm sorry.
Um...I'm sorry.
You shouldn't be sorry.
Wanna play
with the broken radio?
You saw me looking at it,
didn't you?
Yeah.
It's more wishing it worked
so I could call for help.
Breaker, breaker.
I, uh, am feelin'
a little lonely out here.
Yeah.
It's really not the same
when you know
no one can hear you.
You still early.
I didn't get to eat.
What you want?
Mm...apple pie.
Is good dinner.
Want me to warm it up?
No, I like it cold.
Here is.
So dreamy just
for a truck driver?
Shut up.
It's me!
The machine by the back door,
it don't spin.
I'll fix it.
And you owe.
For before
and for this.
Is your little girl coming?
No.
I don't have any cash,
can I pay you tomorrow?
You know...
if you're happy,
your little girl
like you better.
Thanks for the tip.
-I'm on a break.
-I didn't say anything.
All the storage units
have a number, right?
So you have to, like,
remember which number
goes to which one,
you know what I'm saying?
I know, what's the point
of the story?
I'm just saying, there's
this one that's been locked
for like a while.
-Probably just someone's junk.
-Maybe there's something
in there we can sell,
I don't know.
It's probably not that valuable
if they're keepin' it there.
They'd probably keep it
at their house.
I don't know, man.
Can't you just go
look at the record
and see who rented
the damn unit?
Well, yeah, I mean--
-Not workin'?
-Not yet.
Um, I was gonna go for a walk,
do you wanna go?
Yeah.
-Hey, man.
-Hey.
How you doin'?
-Great.
-Right on.
-Who is that?
-Holy shit.
Ohh...
Yolanda.
Jelena.
It's almost like
you live here.
Do you ever go home?
I been pullin'
some extra runs lately.
-You cold?
-A little bit.
-Here.
-No!
You don't have
to do that.
Come on.
I'm gonna take it.
Got it.
So those guys back there,
they, uh, friends of yours?
Uh...
that's my brother
and his friend.
Seem like the type
that had a brother.
I don't--
is that good or bad?
No, it's good.
You seem just like
you can hold your own.
Mm-hm.
That's my foster brother.
There were four boys
and me.
So, is this
your dream come true,
bein' a trucker?
No.
I was actually
a banker for 10 years.
D'you get fired?
No, my branch closed,
and, I don't know.
I was looking
for another job,
I just realized
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life
behind a desk, so...
just thought
this would be a good way
to get some perspective.
Huh.
Oh, the jacket.
Very nice move,
the gentleman.
Who's that?
What?
Who is that guy?
No one.
Aww, don't give me that shit.
You sleep with every
single girl at that bar.
It's true.
Tell me about him.
-Nuh-uh.
-Tell me,
tell me about him,
he from here?
He from here?
-No.
-No?
Mm-mm.
Where did you meet him?
Here.
He's a truck driver.
Figures.
You got something
to say, Corey?
No.
I mean, I saw his truck,
I figured he was
a fuckin' truck driver.
Wow, that's great.
So you're...cozyin' up
with truckers now?
That's fuckin' great.
Why don't you keep
your nose on your face, huh?
-Mind your own business.
-That's so amazing,
it's amazing--I mean,
as long as I, you know,
long as I get my turn
once in a while,
I'm fine with that.
You are such an asshole, Ty.
-Hey, Francine.
-What?
Could you grab me
some of that toilet paper
-and bring it home?
-Get your own toilet paper.
All right.
Thought you had
a handle on this.
You told Danielle you quit.
What difference
does it make?
I always thought
it was a good thing
when a father wanted
to spend time with his daughter.
Well, my dad barely stuck around
after conception, so...
I'm not really
the person to ask about that.
But...it counts for something
that you're trying.
-You all right, Stu?
-Yeah.
Has Jenny seen this?
Nuh-uh.
Why are you here
in this shitty town,
running a diner?
What should I do?
Sell your paintings.
To who?
There's people
that buy artwork, right?
Not here.
Well, then move.
Can't move.
Yeah.
You should go to sleep.
It's been a long time
since you've been here.
Yeah.
Wanna stay?
You know...
you were the only one
that ever treated me
like a decent guy.
Well, you are a decent guy.
You're just really drunk.
When did you get so sad?
I gotta go.
Okay.
You like good tea?
Mm-hm, thank you.
Did your kid draw these?
Yeah.
How old is he now?
He just turned 20.
What?
You do not look old enough
to have a 20-year-old.
I am plenty old.
Don't you miss him?
I mean, why didn't you
go back after Carl died?
My son with
mama.
She don't want me come home.
He's fine.
Did you sleep
with the trucker yet?
I want to.
But we both know
how that ends up, don't we?
Stu is lonely man.
Don't matter who's with him,
he's just...
...lonely.
He'll never change.
Thank you.
You lonely now.
But won't always be for you.
Hello?
D.A.?
Now?
I'm sorry it's such
short notice.
-It's okay.
-I've tried everyone else.
No, don't worry, it's great.
Um, I'll have my cell,
so call me,
for any reason at all,
and I'll be back tomorrow
by 5:30.
Okay.
Have you been painting?
Nah.
All right. Be good.
Both of you.
Corey?
Get in here
and clean up.
Can I talk to you?
Really?
Well, I'm sorry, Francine.
Can I do something for you,
can I get you something?
Ohh, what is up with you?
Me?
You're the one with cuntitis.
Look, you can have
your dickhead friends come over,
but you've gotta
clean up after 'em,
it's really fucking annoying.
-I didn't order that.
-You always have a beer.
Trent.
Fuck off.
I'm so tired
of bitching at you, Corey.
Yeah, well,
that makes two of us.
Look, can we just get drunk?
I have to work at...no.
What are you talkin' about,
you don't have to work
for like seven hours.
You can get drunk and sober
in seven hours,
it's a known fact.
-Oh, is it?
-It is.
Oh...
I don't know,
you would know, wouldn't you?
Come on, just do
one shot with me.
Francine, we never
drink together anymore.
One fuckin' shot.
Okay, fine. One shot.
Trent!
What?
Trent, I'm sorry.
Can we have
two whiskeys?
Yes.
Is that me?
Yep.
Painting a picture
that did not exist, my friend.
-I have no idea--
-She was studying.
That's a very redeeming
quality about someone,
-when you're 16.
-That's true.
That's what Ty says
to me all the time.
Fuck Ty.
Fuck.
What?
Oh my God, I need coffee.
I'm gonna be so drunk
at work.
Who gives a shit?
Your boss comes to work
drunk all the time.
He does!
I know.
I'm such a failure.
Shut the fuck up, Francine.
I'm the failure, remember?
No, you're not.
You have goals and you have
things you like doing.
You have lots of guys
you like to do, Francine.
That's so mean.
I like this trucker.
Come on, Francine.
I know.
'Cause that works out.
Yeah, but he's different.
He's like--
He's like actually interested
in my pathetic life.
I'm interested
in your pathetic life.
You don't count.
What the fuck does that mean?
No, you're not.
Yes, I do.
I'm, like--
You're like one of the--
You're one of the only
people I care about.
Really.
What?
Corey.
It's the last thing
I need right now.
What, you're leaving?
Yeah, I gotta go to work.
Francine, come on, don't leave.
Corey, some people
have to fucking work.
Oh fuck.
Are we gonna get dinner
or something?
Oh sorry, um...
my schedule's kinda strange.
I usually eat dinner
in the morning.
So we're not eating.
No, of course we are.
Um...
What do you want?
Order a pizza?
What am I talking about;
It's your birthday, we should--
We should go out.
Where do you wanna go?
How about Chinese?
Eh, it's a drive.
You have a car, right?
Yeah.
So let's go.
Okay.
Oh.
And I think that is something
that people need to know.
People need to know about this
because we're talking
about the president
that has an oath
to Skull and Bones before--
that, you know, supersedes
the oath to the country
and to our interests.
What?
First, you know you.
I'm fine.
Drink some coffee.
Some of them got, uh,
into the depths
of the organization.
Why are you so tired?
I was up really late.
Oh yeah, because you work
the night shift at the diner.
Yeah.
When do you normally sleep?
Oh, usually in the mornings.
I'm sorry I messed up
your schedule.
Oh no no, don't worry
about that.
Are you done with that?
-Yeah.
You guys want dessert?
I think my dad's too tired.
Do you have any birthday cake?
Um, I can see if we have
something like that.
What do you want,
like, chocolate?
Yeah.
I'll see what we have.
Thanks.
Thanks for letting me drive too.
Mom never lets me.
Well, here's to my driver.
Dad.
Dad!
How is he?
We're monitoring him.
He's stable right now,
but he still hasn't
regained consciousness.
Doing everything we can.
Hey.
How are you doing?
You okay?
Mm-hm.
You drunk, Francine?
Yeah.
You all right?
Mm-hm.
Are you taking me out?
I don't know.
So now what?
What were you like as a kid?
Where'd that come from?
I bet you were pretty bossy.
Maybe a little, yeah.
Probably really good
at everything.
Not at all.
Come on.
Can I--Can I come
sit next to you?
Hey, there's somebody here.
Hey, Danielle.
You're up early.
Late actually.
Do you want some coffee?
I assume the hospital
called here about Stu?
He was in a car accident.
Oh my God,
did he hit somebody?
No, Jenny was driving.
Oh my God.
Is she okay?
He's been drinking, hasn't he?
On and off, yeah.
Is he gonna be okay?
Hey.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I don't know.
It's okay.
Hey.
She wanted to be here
when you woke up
but I made her go home
and go to sleep.
She wanted to be here?
She's never even
had a driving lesson.
I thought it would be
safer if she drove.
She actually talked
to me at dinner.
It's been a long time.
I'm glad you had fun...
before you passed out,
and let our daughter
crash your car into a guardrail.
Once she sees you're awake,
and gets into her head that
she didn't actually kill you...
That's it, Stu.
You're out of chances.
You going home?
Yeah.
I bet you're a really good dad.
I can be.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
Hey!
Corey.
Yeah, I know, Francine.
I'm an asshole.
Yeah, you are.
You know, why don't you
tell me why it is
that I'm such an asshole.
I don't know.
I just--
I was just--
I have to stop doing things I'm
going to regret later, you know?
No.
Come on.
You're my brother.
I'm not your brother, Francine.
We lived in
the same foster home
for two years.
We're roommates.
And yeah, you walk around here
in your underwear
and you're always leaning
on me and touching me.
I don't touch you.
We're not related.
It's not like it's illegal.
And you act like you've
never considered it.
We had sex your
first night at the house.
I was 16.
I had sex with anyone
that looked at me.
Well, some things never change.
You're really important to me.
Am I?
I don't--I don't
have anyone else.
I know.
Neither do I.
Then can't you just be
my brother?
Ah, fuck it.
I thought you were sleeping.
Well, this fucking sucks.
I'll come back and visit you.
You're not coming back
to this shithole.
Shut up.
You know I'm gonna miss you.
All right.
So do I have to worry
about a little poke
if I give you a hug.
Shut up--
Ah, come on!
I'm going back to bed.
You have someone
coming for you?
Nope.
You need someone
to pick you up.
I'll manage, thanks.
--drizzling with an increased
chance of rain this afternoon
with thunderstorms the rest
of tonight and for the week.
47 degrees right now,
low tonight is 42.
I know you're standing there,
I can hear ya breathing.
I came to say goodbye.
That's right, you're leaving.
Well, be good.
There's a first time
for everything, right?
Yeah.