(car horns)
(sirens chirping)
(tires screeching)
- Whoa!
- (driver): Watch it, buddy!
- Here you go.
- Ah! Cavalry.
What is this?
- Coffee?
- What's in it?
- Uh--
- It isn't stevia.
- No, they were out.
- Rob, if you're gonna do
something nice, get it right.
- Yes, Captain.
- It's "Major" to you.
I've been promoted.
- Nice. Very seasonal.
- Now not one person's
put a tip in there all day.
- There you go, Major.
- As you were.
- Trick or treat, Sam.
Morning, Enid.
- Hi, Mr. Carelli!
- Let me guess, you're late
because you stopped
to buy Sam coffee again?
You can stop now. I've already
awarded you the "nicest guy
in the office" award.
- I like him.
- Why?
- He's honest.
- Oh, my!
- Emmett!
- Mm?
- Elyse Samford is coming in
next week to discuss
a trademark infringement
suit. That's the file.
I want precedents cited,
t's crossed, i's dotted.
- Who's Elyse Sanford?
- Samford! With an "m".
The new CEO of Samford Candy!
One of our biggest clients.
I don't care if you have
to work on that all weekend.
Put 150% into that.
- Absolutely, Dad. I will
dedicate myself entirely to this
all weekend long and cancel
all my other plans. You got it!
All over it!
Sanford... Samford.
- Yes!
- Andrew.
- Hey.
- Dad wants precedents cited
on these by Monday.
Make sure you cross
the i's and dot the t's.
- This weekend? No, no, no.
I'm playing golf with--
- I don't care if you're golfing
with all four living
ex-presidents. Handle this.
(frustrated sigh)
Chin up, Rob.
- So, Rob, how's it going?
- Busy.
- Busy, yeah.
- And yet your billable hours
aren't even near the goal we set
at your last year-end review.
- I sort of felt the number
you set wasn't realistic
given the actual number
of hours in a day.
- Oh, Rob, Rob, Rob...
I see I'm going to have to help
you succeed despite yourself.
There you go!
- Let me guess.
Covering for Emmett and Andrew?
- Can you get me everything
you have on Samford Candy?
- You want me
to stay late with you?
- No reason for your evening
to be ruined, too.
- Hang in there.
Maybe one day
you'll get to live
the dream, too.
You never know.
(both laughing)
(phone ringing)
- Ruby!
- [Hey, Uncle Rob!]
- Hey, sweetie.
- [Ready for some bowling?]
- Well, that's um,
kinda the thing...
I can't make it tonight.
- [Don't stand me up!]
[You're my only uncle.]
- Uh-huh, I realize
I'm your only uncle.
- [I'm not taking
no for an answer.]
- Okay, okay! I'll come.
You ever think about
being a lawyer yourself
or has hanging around me
totally turned you off of it?
- Oh-oh! Ruby Cole in the house!
You owe me pizza!
With sausage and mushrooms.
- Girls your age
don't eat mushrooms.
- I'm precocious.
- I'm well aware of that.
Just because you got a strike
doesn't mean you're
gonna beat me.
- Just 'cause you're a guy
doesn't mean you're
gonna beat me.
Kelly Kulick--
- Won the PBA Tour title
against a man
in 2010, I know.
- Your feet got
ahead of your swing.
- Really, Dad?
'Cause I think I've beaten you
two games to one today.
- It's called a head start.
(both laughing)
- Excellent bowler!
- You know what? They say
the strength in the wrist
diminishes with age. I think
I'm gonna get you a wrist guard
for your next birthday.
(laughter)
- Highly unlikely, my dear.
Highly unlikely.
- Want me to go talk you up
to her? She's with her dad.
- You've got to stop trying
to fix me up. I'm doing fine.
- Ah! La-la-la-la...
- You're killing me, dad!
Give me a break!
No, seriously, I need a break.
Do you want a snack?
- No, I think I'm just
gonna stay here and gloat.
- You haven't had a date
since that lawyer lady
closed the file on you.
- I'm good. I've just been busy.
I'll meet someone
when I meet someone.
- Hey, can I get a candy bar?
Thanks.
- Hi.
- Hey. Buying some candy?
- Yep.
- Which one are you gonna get?
- My favorites.
(chuckles)
- Ruby!
- Just so you know,
he's single
and a lawyer. Very successful.
- Impressive. You must
be very proud.
- I am.
- Hey.
- Hi!
Nice kid you've got here, Ray.
- She sure is, but that's not--
- Got great taste in candy.
- What?
- Come on!
You had such an opportunity
and you just wasted it!
- Really?
- It's always good to get
you out of the office.
Those two guys at work still
giving you a hard time?
- Their daddy's the boss.
- I wish I could
cast a spell on them.
- Excellent idea!
- But I mean,
you're a cool guy,
so why do they have
to treat you like that?
- When you're the low man
on the totem pole,
everyone else gets to
stand on top of your head.
- You're too nice.
- You can't be too nice.
- Yeah, you can.
(insects chirping)
- Hi!
- Here she is.
Safe and sound.
- Can Uncle Rob
hang out with us, Mom?
- Sorry, gotta get back to work.
- You know it's very important
I spend time with appropriate
male role models.
- That's why I just
took you bowling, buddy.
- I'm almost finished
with your Halloween costume.
Do you want to come try it on?
- See you next week, Uncle Rob.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- My God, it's just so awesome!
(sigh)
(groaning)
- Stevia.
- Attaboy!
Worked all weekend again?
- No.
- Really?
What did you do?
- For one thing, I went bowling.
- Ah, impetuous youth!
(chuckling)
You, sign in.
- Are you kidding me?
You see me every day!
- Sign in.
- Do you have any idea what
dealing with you is like?
- Disturbing and frustrating?
- Yeah, on a good day.
- Thank you.
- Make sure to have the
restrooms cleaned, spotless.
Yes, get to work. Send those
to the third cubicle.
- What's going on?
- Uh, Samford Candy.
Something about some trademark
infringement lawsuit.
- Oh, that explains
my weekend...
or lack thereof.
Any inside info?
- Howard Samford is retiring
and handing the company over
to his daughter Elyse.
She's a Princeton grad.
No dummy, but not a lot
of practical experience.
- Merry, you are
a fount of information.
- Awesome! Good work,
people! Nice!
Hi.
Did you put 150% into that?
- Always do.
- Excellent.
Well, this is a major client.
You should feel very pleased
that I trust you enough
to allow you to work on this.
- Just spending time with him
is privilege enough.
- Carelli!
Look, when Ms. Samford gets
here I want you to join us
in the conference room,
okay? Just me and the boys
looks a little too
nepotistic. You can talk,
just not much.
- Yes, sir.
(phone ringing
in the background)
- Samford...
Elyse Samford...
Ooh!
- Ms. Samford!
- Hey.
- Mr. Samford!
- Hi.
- Mr. Higgins is waiting for
you, but can I get you anything
before I take you back?
- I'm okay.
- Nothing for me, thank you.
- Alright, please have a seat.
It will just be a moment.
The Samfords are here. Yes.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I never had to wear heels
when I was working in the field.
I'm only good for about an hour.
- Alright.
(beeping)
Yes? Alright, thank you.
Alright, we'll be meeting
in conference room one,
if you'll follow me.
- Hello, Elyse.
Nice to see you!
How are you? Howard,
this is a surprise!
- Carter, always.
- Please sit down.
- Nice to meet you, Ms. Samford.
- You know, you
look familiar.
- Really?
- Wait a minute.
It was last week, at the
Sustainable Harvest conference,
right?
- Oh!
Yes, yes, absolutely! Are you
into organic gardening too?
- Yeah, I am up to my elbows.
(chuckling)
- Wonderful.
- (Rob): Sorry I'm late.
- Oh my gosh, small world! Um...
Ray, right?
With the adorable daughter?
- We sort of met already.
Rob, not Ray.
- No, but your shirt--
- Vintage.
And she's my niece. Not married.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you as well.
- Before we get started, I just
want to take this opportunity
to officially
introduce you to Elyse.
She's been working with Samford
Candy since high school,
has her MBA at Princeton.
I feel very confident
that she's going to be
picking up where I'm leaving off
and taking the company
to new heights.
It's time for a generational
change at Samford Candy.
Meet the new boss.
(chuckling)
- Well, I will be looking
to Higgins and Sons for the same
wise guidance you've given
my father over the years.
And trust me, I know
that everybody thinks
that I just got this job because
I'm the old man's daughter...
Which would be exactly right.
But that's what happens in
a family-owned company, right,
"and Sons"?
(all laughing)
So I just want to make it clear.
I'm a collaborative person
and I look forward to us working
together. So let's get started.
- It looks as though
you're being greeted
with trial by fire.
What we have on the table here
is a trademark infringement
on Samford Candy
by the Kraus Candy Company.
- They've changed their name
to Sanford. Emmett?
- Now, by using
the name Samford,
with an "m" like Uncle Sam,
it has a distinct similarity
to Sanford, with an "n".
- The other way around.
- Right, whatever.
They're about the same thing.
- Which would be the point
of the suit.
- Yes. By using the name Sanford
and similar packaging,
the consumer is being led to
believe that they are purchasing
a product made by Samford.
Now, on the left,
Samford, as you know.
On the right, Sanford.
- This seems like a potential
profit opportunity for us.
How much are we looking at?
- They don't stand a chance.
- Yeah, we'll need
to seek an injunction.
- An injunction, damages,
punitive damages,
costs and fees.
That could be a lot of money.
- How much are we talking?
- Before we get ahead of
ourselves, there is potentially
a much larger problem.
Sanford has been cybersquatting.
This needs
to be addressed immediately.
- As I pointed out to you
before the meeting,
thanks for bringing that up.
- No one has registered
samfordcandy.com. You should
jump on that right away.
- Dot everything,
sir. I am on it.
- By the way, Emmett,
nice piece of work there.
- Our clients deserve
our full attention.
if that means me missing out on
a weekend or a bunch of sleep,
so be it.
- Andrew will be
taking point on this.
- Of course, dad.
- Wonderful. Well, thank you all
for your hard work.
I fell Samford
is well taken care of.
And Rob, good job
jumping on the cybersquatting.
- My pleasure.
- This case is our
top priority, Ms. Samford.
- That's good to
hear. We do have
the annual Halloween Ball
coming up, as you may know.
It would be a shame to have
this hanging over our heads.
- Just leave it with us.
- Terrific. Well
done, as always.
- Nice to see ya, Howard.
- Thanks, Carter. Thank you.
- (Howard): Gentlemen.
- Pleasure as always, sir.
- She's amazing.
Smart, beautiful, funny.
- Rich!
- She sounds perfect. When
are you asking her out?
- Not sure how ethical that
would be while representing her.
- I think that only applies
in divorce cases.
(phone ringing)
Who are you texting?
- Boss' son. He's dropping
some work off for me.
- Again?
- Yeah.
- Are you... Another round,
darling, please.
- Coming up.
- Do you want us to
verbally lacerate him?
- I would love
you to. But don't.
- Okay, so when
you ask her out,
tell her to bring a
rich friend of hers
so that I can...
Please set me up
with a rich...
- I wouldn't think you have time
to be sitting around here, Rob.
- My plate was totally clear
when I left the office.
- Look, Rob...
You want to succeed
with our firm?
You gotta come in earlier
and stay later than
everybody else. Alright?
You gotta clean out your plate,
and then you take a look around
and say, "What else can I do?
What can I take off
of Andrew's plate? What can
I take off of Emmett's plate?"
You don't just want
to be adequate, alright?
You want to be
exceptional.
- When do you need this?
- Bright and early.
As a matter of fact, you are not
gonna have time to finish this.
Mmm!
See you in the morning.
- Oops!
(glass shattering)
- Rob!
- I'm so sorry.
- He is so sorry.
- You shut up.
- You are mean.
- Can I just ask one question?
- Massive student loans,
bad economy,
and no one's hiring.
Bye, guys.
- Thanks, Rob.
That's too much!
- Morning, Sam.
- FYI, your boss is a tool.
- Which one? I have three
and they're all tools.
- Tall. Dark. Skinny.
- Emmett. What did he do?
- Asked me to find
a new job because the
sight of me depresses him.
- He actually said that to you?
Sam, I'm really sorry.
- Are you kidding?
It made my day!
(chuckling)
- Energy drink
in your coffee?
- Attention,
everyone! Attention!
Ms. Samford here has
a very exciting announcement
for the office.
- Hey, everyone!
As new CEO of Samford Candy,
this year I have decided
to invite the entire firm
to our annual
Halloween Ball!
(cheering)
So please come.
Wear a costume,
but none of this wearing a suit
and saying you're
dressed as a lawyer.
(laughter)
I'll see you all at the ball!
(indistinct chatter)
(birds chirping)
Hey, Dad!
- Hi there! Nice to see you.
Crazy day!
- So do you think you can handle
slumming it for a while?
- Well, it beats plaster dust
and power tools,
banging and crashing.
(sighing)
- You're lucky that you have a
daughter with a spare bedroom
to help you with your
renovation habit.
- I sure am!
- (laughing): Coffee?
- Crazy not to.
- Do you want to know who
I'm gonna be for Halloween?
- Who?
- Kelly Kulick.
- No one's gonna
know who that is.
- People aren't gonna know
one of the greatest bowlers
of all time?
- I'm thinking no.
- Well, I'll know
and it will be cool.
Only trick or treating all night
with a heavy bowling ball
might be tough.
- You could make one out
of Styrofoam and paint it.
- My mom can make me one.
What about you?
Are you gonna do that
"I'm not wearing a costume
because adults
should dress like adults
on Halloween" thing again?
- Actually, I'm wearing
a costume this year.
- Truth?
- Yeah.
I'm going to a Halloween ball
given by Samford Candy
and I hear they have
some pretty amazing things
in their gift bags,
some of which
might even go to you.
- You are getting in a costume
and going to a Halloween party?
What the heck
happened to you?
- Man to man?
Man to girl...
- I'll never tell.
Mom!
Uncle Rob is in love!
- That's not what I said!
- He's going to this big
fancy ball she's throwing
and he asked for a costume.
- Don't you know my kid has
the biggest mouth in town?
- I do not!
- Mm-hmm...
- Give me a break!
I just told my mom!
- Are you really gonna wear
a costume? I haven't seen you
get dressed for Halloween
since you were about ten.
- I know. I was a vampire cowboy
three years running
before I decided
I hated costumes.
What am I gonna wear
and not feel like an idiot?
- I will make something for you.
Let's get you measured.
- I can't believe you!
- What?
- Alright...
- You don't have to do
this. I can buy something.
- When your sister makes
costume suits for a living,
I don't think so. 32.
So... What is going on?
How serious are you
with this girl?
17.
- Ruby's a little premature.
I haven't even asked her
on a date yet.
- Oh. Well, what do you
want to go as?
Pirate? Gangster?
- How about the prince
of the uncles?
- (laughing): 40.
I don't know what kind
of prince that would be,
but what about
a regular prince?
Rob, stop moving.
- Okay.
- I'm speechless!
- Dad, I was thinking...
We should try and move the
company forward by making it
more environmentally friendly.
- I'm listening.
- So if we use plant protein
instead of animal whey protein,
it's better for
the environment
and it makes our candy
safe for vegetarians.
- It might raise costs.
- But I was thinking,
if we publicize our company
as a family-run company
who cares about the world,
who cares about our consumers,
we might be able
to step up profits
and offset those increased
costs. What do you think?
- I think you're going to be
the most beautiful woman
at that ball.
- I mean about my idea.
- The smartest, with
the most beautiful ideas.
- It's not gonna be the same
at the ball without you.
- This ball is going
to be your night.
My being there would
just detract from that.
(chuckling)
(sighing)
- Okay, let me clean up
and then we're going dancing.
- Dancing?
Why?
- Because you're going to a ball
and as I recall from your prom,
you're a terrible dancer.
- It's Sunday night. Doesn't
she have school tomorrow?
- It's 7 o'clock. What time
do you think I go to bed?
- Homework?
- Let's go.
You need to have some fun.
- I went bowling.
I had food that doesn't come in
a paper bag. I already had fun.
- You are going
as the last male figurehead
of the Carelli family.
You need to represent.
♪♪♪
- Is this the waltz?
- Yes. What else could it be?
Alright... Lift your hand.
Like that. Okay?
Let's see what you've got,
little bro.
(both laughing)
Sorry!
You are worse
than I remember.
- Can we go now?
- If you can walk,
you can dance.
The waltz starts
with the box step, okay?
You know the box step?
- Uh...
- Okay. Ruby, come and show
your uncle the box step.
I will be you, but better.
(chuckling)
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- You never said anything
about turning.
(both laughing)
- Are you gonna let
a 12-year-old show you up?
Come on! Come here!
Alright, thanks. Basic...
box step.
- (both): One, two, three...
One, two, three...
- Now look up.
And stop moving your lips.
- Okay.
(laughter)
You're doing a lot better!
You haven't stepped on my feet
in a couple of minutes.
(both laughing)
Well, here's the secret.
Dance like you're one person.
- Sure, yeah!
One person with three left feet;
two of them mine.
I am going to have
blisters on my feet.
- Toughen up, buttercup.
- Do you want some tea?
- I gotta get home. It's late.
- Who are you, Cinderella?
- Yes, and you're my
fairy godmother.
I still have work to do.
Can you wave your magic
wand and make it disappear?
- Sure thing.
(chuckling)
- Practice.
(humming)
- Ladies.
(sighing)
- A lot.
- Yeah.
- Eight o'clock! Oh no!
Okay...
- Hey, pal!
- Sorry.
- (woman): Taxi!
- No coffee today, sorry.
- You look terrible.
They're taking
advantage of you, pal.
You need to start
standing up for yourself.
- What I need is
to keep my job.
(video game sounds)
- Andrew! Where's the
trademark infringement filing?
- The...?
- The Samford
trademark infringement.
- I gave it to Rob.
- I assigned it to you.
- I just gave it to him to cross
the t's and dot the i's.
Dad, he doesn't earn
his money around here.
He sits around all day
doing nothing!
Definitely not
putting in 150% like I am.
- Carelli!
Carelli?
- I think he just stepped out.
- Sir?
- What does your
watch say, Carelli?
- 10:15.
- 10,000.
- I don't understand.
- That's how many attorneys
lost their jobs at
major firms this year.
Did you know that?
- I... I didn't.
- How would you like
to make it 10,001?
- No, sir.
- Mr. Carter,
Mr. Carelli is always here
before everyone else.
I'm sure he had a good reason.
- A lot of legal secretaries
out of work too.
- She had nothing
to do with this.
- My sons can't be expected
to do everything themselves.
Someone has to help
with the heavy lifting.
- I realize that.
- Pattern yourself after them.
- I will. Thanks for
your understanding.
- I think you should stay
until 10:15 tonight.
Maybe dot some i's,
cross some t's.
- Want me to stay with you?
- No, I got it.
- Yeah...
I think I'm gonna stay with you.
- Still working?
- I'm just going over the
quarterly projections.
What do you think
about if we go into gum
or breath mints?
- I think you're in charge
of the company now.
It's your baby.
(small laugh)
- Right.
- Hey, I wouldn't have
put you in charge, CEO,
if I didn't think
you could handle it.
You're worried about
this trademark business?
- No. No, I know
we're in the right.
- When was the last time
you had some fun?
- I have fun.
- It's a very evasive answer.
- Okay, every time
we go bowling, I have fun.
(sighing)
(small laugh)
- Beautiful night,
isn't it?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- That fall snap is in the air
and the leaves are turning.
Wouldn't you rather be taking
a walk with your guy
than sitting here buried
behind your computer?
- Dad,
you've entrusted me
with a huge responsibility
and I just want
to live up to it.
- You know, when your
mother was alive,
I tried as best
as I could to manage
both the company
and a life with her.
And after she died,
I kind of lost myself
in the work. No fun,
no friends...
I never fell in love again.
Now that I'm retired,
I intend to change all that.
- Good.
- Lysie,
don't make the
same mistake I did.
When you're old and it's cold,
you're gonna want company.
Not a company.
(sighing)
- Hey, Rob!
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, looks good.
How many billable hours
would you say this represents?
- 25, minimum.
- Wow! That's great!
- Thanks.
- Of course, as lead attorney,
I'll be billing those.
You really need to get your
client base broadened, Rob.
This firm needs
more rainmakers!
Maybe work up a business
development pitch
and I'll take
a look at it. Chin up!
(groaning)
- What happened? Are you okay?
- I just dropped something.
All good.
- Sanford's entire concept
was based on appropriating
the worldwide recognition,
good will and success
of Samford Candy, in a...
In a, um...
In an intentional effort
to cause confusion
in the general public
between Sanford
and Samford candies.
Defendant's actions constitute
trademark infringement
in violation of
Lanham Act, 15 U.S.C.,
section 1114.
- Anything else?
- Uh, yes, Your Honor.
We'd like to ask for
a temporary injunction
until the time that this
matter is adjudicated.
- So ordered.
Nicely prepared, young man.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
No point in doing something
unless you're gonna do it right.
Right?
- Good morning.
- Boom! Crushed it!
- Yeah, sure did.
- Oh, wait till I tell
Elyse how I dominated!
- You're meeting with Elyse?
- Yeah. She asked for a full
report on the court appearance,
so I'm gonna explain to her
in detail everything I did.
- That should be interesting.
- Yeah, maybe you
should... You know,
come to the meeting too; just
to take notes or whatever.
(sighing)
(whistling)
- What's going on?
- I'm meeting with
Elyse Samford.
- You've got it bad!
- That obvious?
(chuckling)
- Mm-hmm!
- And then I filed for
trademark infringement
and got a temporary
injunction to stop Sanford
until the case can be heard.
- What about the domain name?
- Uh... Rob,
why don't you read
from your notes what
I told you about that?
- Um... That is covered
under the Anticybersquatting
Consumer Protection Act,
which need to be taken up
in Federal Court.
We filed on that as well.
- Exactly.
We've got you covered.
- Okay, great.
Well, Andrew, thank you.
I feel like I'm in great hands.
And thank you, Rob not Ray.
- You're good with names.
- I'm sure Ms. Sanford
has better things
to do with her time than to make
chitchat with you, Carelli.
- Samford.
- You're good with names, too.
- Uh, let me
walk you to your car.
- Sure.
- Bye, Ms. Samford.
- Oh, call me Elyse.
- So what do you drive?
I got an M3 convertible.
- Oh, I have a chauffeur.
- Fabulous!
- See you tomorrow, Sam.
- What's wrong with you?
You look like your
best friend just died.
Which would be me
and I'm still alive and kicking.
- You ever feel
like what's the point?
- No. No, I am constantly clear
on the meaning
and gift of life, my friend.
I'm what you'd call
a committed optimist.
- I guess I'm just tired. Sorry.
- Well, take a load off,
then. Come on, sit down.
And quit apologizing
all the time.
I'm the guy with
the meaningless job.
Too many hours,
not enough overtime.
But if you want to feel
sorry for yourself,
go right ahead.
- So what's your dream, Sam?
- What?
- What would make you happy?
- Alright, I'll tell you.
But if you're only asking me
just to get me to
ask you, forget it.
(small laugh)
- You don't have to ask me.
Do you ever think
about a woman?
- No, not since '98.
- What happened in '98?
- I became a realist.
- 'Cause there's this woman--
- No, no, not listening. No, no.
- She--
- I'm not listening.
- Fine.
- Man, you give up easily!
No wonder you're striking out
in the romance department.
Alright, here. I'll
get you started, okay?
She's absolutely
beautiful, right?
- Beautiful, smart.
- And?
- Powerful.
She's the CEO of Samford Candy.
- And?
- And she seems kind
and sort of vulnerable.
- So what's the problem?
- The problem is that
she's way above my level.
- So what? You want to be
on her level? Grow.
- She's the head of a
mega corporation, Sam.
I'm a lawyer. It's
a lot of growing.
- Nothing you can't overcome.
All you gotta do--
- Carelli! What do you
think you're doing?
- Um...
- Young man,
you represent this firm.
I don't ever want to see you
lounging like this again.
- That's my friend
you're talking to!
- I beg your pardon?
Stay out of it.
Step it up, Carelli.
- Thanks for trying.
- Forget it.
Hey, Rob.
I know these guys are working
you like a dog around here,
but you gotta make time to
interact with the outside world.
That's where the new
clients come from.
And that is what's gonna
make you a rainmaker, my friend.
It will also get these
other clowns off your back.
- So you're a lawyer now?
- Used to be.
You get one question.
- How did you get
from there to here?
- A woman named Lois.
(clears throat)
The love of my life.
We were partners
at the same firm,
until she "fell out"
of love with me
and fell into love
with the senior partner.
- That's harsh.
- Well, let's just call it
a "disincentive"
to continue practicing.
It's a nest of vipers.
- Do you ever think--
- No. No.
(indistinct chatter)
- Are you gonna ask
the candy lady out?
- Not until I make partner.
- Oh, come on!
Then I think you should go
to the speed dating thing.
- I'm not doing it!
- You're always complaining
about how you don't have
enough time to date. So this
is perfect. Speed dating...
Get it? For people who
don't have a lot of time.
- Ruby, I've had
plenty of girlfriends.
I honestly don't need your help.
- How about online dating?
I think you should
take a whack at that.
- Why do I have children
and security guards
giving me life advice?
- 'Cause you need it.
- Gee, thanks. Why do you care
so much if I have a girlfriend?
- I'm twelve. How interesting
do you think my life is?
(insects chirping)
- Look.
- Wow!
(small laugh)
- I keep telling you:
I'm gifted.
- You are going to kill!
- Helen, this is incredible!
I don't know how to thank you.
- Oh, come on.
Free baby-sitting is plenty.
- He isn't baby-sitting.
He enjoys my company.
- Yes.
- She's right!
So I'll be over at 6 o'clock
tomorrow. Ms. Kulick and I
are gonna go trick or treating
for a couple of hours
and then I'm off to the ball!
- As you command, my prince.
(chuckling)
- Good morning, Sam!
- Happy Halloween, Rob!
- Happy Halloween to you!
- I'm thinking of
going as a clown.
- You like clowns?
- No, I'm terrified of them.
I thought this would be
cheaper than therapy.
(both laughing)
Think this will get me a raise?
- Alright, guys
and girls! Attention!
We're letting you all go
fifteen minutes early
so you can go and get ready
for the Samford Halloween Ball!
Really? Nothing?
(soft cheering)
Hey, yeah!
- How did Sanford get the
domain name samfordcandy.com?
I thought you were on that!
- I was. I did. I registered it,
Dad. I swear I did!
- Well, you better get this
straightened out right away!
I don't care if
it takes all night!
- The ball is tonight!
I delegated this job to Rob.
This is not my fault.
- Then get him to do it!
Someone's got to handle it!
- Yes, Dad.
- You registered
sanfordcandy.com.
- So?
- So it's Samford,
with an "m".
Which means that Sanford, the
company we're fighting against,
can still buy domain names
Samford Candy needs.
- This is your fault, right.
You're gonna fix it.
- Wait, how is this my fault?
- I asked you to register it.
You must have misspelled it.
- No, that isn't true. You never
asked me to register anything.
- Are you calling me a liar?
- No, you said you'd handle it.
- You have to write
a motion to set aside.
It's gonna take all night. You
might as well forget the party.
- Listen, Emmett--
- If I see you at
the ball, you're fired.
- You're not serious?
- Try me.
- I'm sorry, Ruby. There's no
way I can leave and take you
trick or treating.
- [You're going to the ball--]
- I can't go to the ball either.
- [What about the costume?]
[It's gorgeous!]
- I'm stuck in the office.
Tell your mom I'll wear
her costume next year,
if I can.
- [It's not gonna be the same]
[without you.]
- Have fun.
- [Bye.]
(typing on keyboard)
- Sorry, sweetheart. No can do.
- Just let me go up
for a minute.
- No trick or treating in the
building. There's nobody here.
- What about Rob Carelli?
He's my uncle.
- You're Ruby! His Ruby!
Yeah, he talks about
you all the time.
Just go on up.
- You don't even
have a door on your office?
- It's a step up from the
cubicle I used to have.
- Dreaming big, uncle Rob?
- What are you doing here?
- You gotta go
to this ball, man.
- I can't. I haven't even
finished up Emmett's mess
and if he sees at the ball,
I'm fired.
- Has he seen your costume?
Then you're going to the ball!
- I really can't, buddy.
- You really can.
- I have tons of work
and they lock
the building down at midnight.
- So? No problem. You just
gotta be back here by midnight.
- Or what?
I turn into a pumpkin?
(animated chatter)
(people laughing)
Merry, it's Rob.
- You're not
supposed to be here.
- I'm well aware of that.
I'm just going to avoid
Higgins senior and juniors.
- Did you get the motion done?
- Almost. I'm going to go back
before midnight and finish up.
- Don't forget to cross
those i's and dot those t's.
You go over there!
Look, tonight, you're
not an associate.
You're a prince!
Go act like one!
- Good evening, my princess.
- Strange coincidence!
- Maybe it's not a coincidence.
Maybe it's synchronicity.
- I'm Elyse Samford.
- Yeah, I know.
- Okay, this is usually
where you tell me
what your name is.
- Remember that old
board game, Mystery Date?
Tonight, I'm your mystery date.
- I kinda like that.
Okay, so what do you do
when you're not princing?
- I can't tell you that either.
- Okay, so what
can we talk about?
- You, the night...
Bowling.
- Bowling?
- It's one possibility.
We don't have to.
I know a lot of
people find it lame.
- No! I'm a big
Kelly Kulick fan.
I mean, you've got
to love a woman who took
a PBA title away from a man.
I have a custom Storm. I have
bowled one perfect game
in my life, have a slight right
hook, but I'm working on it.
And I love bowling with my dad.
- I'm a big
Kelly Kulick fan, too.
♪♪♪
May I have this dance, my lady?
- Oh!
I can barely walk in these,
let alone dance.
I haven't waltzed in ages.
- Don't worry. I'll lead.
♪♪♪
- I never knew that waltz
could be so romantic.
- Me neither. I learned from
my sister and a 12-year-old.
(laughing)
Let's not forget these.
- (Elyse): Beautiful moon.
- Sure is.
Your glass slippers, my lady.
- Actually,
they're Lucite.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- Little trick I learned from
my grandfather, the shoemaker.
(chuckling)
- Thank you.
This has turned out
to be a magical night.
- It has.
- (Carter): May I have
a Cuba Libre, please?
- Give me a VRB.
(clears throat)
Two to one ratio energy drink
to vodka. Don't mess it up.
- Emmett, I'm gonna need you
to go by the office and
bring me the Sheehy brief
so I can look at it tonight.
- Are you okay?
- But the building will
be closed by the time I get
there. It's almost midnight.
- (Carter): You'd better hurry.
- Let me get you a drink.
- Yes.
- Okay.
(contented sigh)
- Are you gonna read it here?
- I'll read it tonight, at home.
- Your gift bag, sir.
- Ow!
- So you want me to go
to the office right now?
- That's exactly
what I want you to do.
(insects chirping)
- Taxi! Taxi!
- Your gift bag, sir.
- 54, Gaily Avenue. Go, go, go!
- Have you seen a masked prince?
- No, I'm sorry.
- No? Okay, thank you.
- Hey, fetch the car.
Come on!
Get this.
Thanks.
(frustrated groan)
(indistinct chatter)
- Sam, Emmett's right behind me!
I need you to slow him down.
- My pleasure. Nice suit!
(panting)
(elevator bell ringing)
Yeah? Help ya?
- Open it up. I need to get
in the office. Open the door!
- Oh, right! I didn't recognize
you in your getup there.
This should do it.
(grunting)
No, no.
(small laugh)
Drive you crazy, uh?
I'm pretty sure that's it.
Yeah, there you go.
(nervous sigh)
- Come on, get in!
- (Sam): There you go.
They should have
a turnstile on that.
You could get a can opener
for that thing!
I will let it
slide this time.
(panting)
- Oh!
You've been busy, Carelli?
You're only missing out on the
greatest party ever. Chin up.
- I had the most
incredible night.
- Tell me about it.
- I met someone.
- Tell me about him.
- That's the problem.
I can't.
- Well, what does he do?
- Don't know.
- What does he look like?
- Couldn't tell ya.
- How in the world can you not
know what somebody looks like?
- Oh, he was wearing a mask.
- Oh right, yeah.
The costume ball.
But you seem to have felt
a strong connection
with this fella.
And you weren't able
to catch his name
or a phone number?
- Well, it didn't come up.
He offered to get me a drink,
the clock struck twelve,
and then I never saw him again.
- Hey, Uncle Rob.
- [Ruby!]
- So how was it?
- The ball? Or her?
- You know.
- [She's amazing.]
- What?
- SHE'S AMAZING!
She's amazing. Thank you,
Ruby, for making me go.
- No problem.
- I can't imagine what going
from being a lawyer to this
is like.
- No. You cannot.
- But we're turning
things back around.
I signed you up for
a continuing education class.
All you need is 25 hours,
unless you've been arrested.
- Great.
- You haven't been
arrested, have you?
- No. But who says I want
to be a lawyer again?
- You can say a lot of bad
things about being an attorney,
but it's got to beat working
as a security guard for
twelve bucks an hour.
- Debatable.
- Look,
here's a list of the classes
you need to go to.
- Not gonna happen.
- Sam--
- Thanks for the attempt,
all right?
- Sam?
- What?
- You can do this.
(scoffing)
- Maybe we could get some DNA
off of this crown
and put it in some
sort of database.
- Ooh, do--
Oh, you're kidding.
- A little.
Not that I'm not
taking this seriously.
I am. Very seriously.
- Okay, look.
I've crossed off the name of all
the people I know and then all
the people I can eliminate.
Those are the ones
that are left.
- I think most of these people
work for Carter Higgins.
- Really? Are you sure?
- Seems that way. I think
we should call Higgins.
- Okay.
- [Higgins and Sons,
good morning.]
- Carter Higgins, please.
It's Elyse Samford.
- What did I do?
- Did you talk to Elyse Samford
at the Ball?
- No. Why? Did she say I did?
- Does she know what costume
you were wearing?
- No, nobody does. You saw me.
I was totally incognito
so I could spy on the staff.
Good idea, huh?
- I'm having a brainstorm.
I'm going to need
150% from you on this.
- You got it.
- Elyse? Hi,
Emmett Higgins here.
I understand
you're looking for me.
A prince costume, yes.
Yep, that was me.
Where did I go?
Well, there was
an emergency
back at the office,
my dad needed me.
You know how it is when your
father needs you, you gotta go.
I've been meaning
to call you, I just...
I didn't know if you felt
the same way that I did.
Well, so...
when can we get together?
Excellent.
It's a date.
See ya.
- Hey, Dad,
I think I found him.
- See you tomorrow.
- Uh, yeah. See ya.
(soft music)
- So...
we have a lot in common,
don't we? We both work
for our fathers...
- It's great being part of
a family-owned business, huh?
- Mm-hmm. It is.
Oh man, it really is.
But it must be great being
handed over the reins.
- It's a mixed blessing. I mean,
I would have happily been
willing to wait
if my father hadn't been
ready to retire.
- Our dads were great
in their day, but...
fresh ideas can really infuse a
business with new life, right?
Survival
of the fittest,
know what I mean?
Would you like to start
with some wine?
- Sure.
- I spent my junior
year in France
studying with one of the top
vintners in the world.
I will handle this.
- You seem so different
than the other night.
- Well, like wine,
I improve with time.
Ahem!
We'll have a bottle of the
Lafite Rothschild 2000.
- Oh no, no, I...
That's over a thousand
dollars a bottle!
- I know. And you...
you're worth every penny.
I feel a real...
connection, don't you?
- Did I seem tipsy
to you at the Ball?
- No.
- No?
You sure you were wearing
a prince's costume?
- 150%.
- Okay...
Sorry, I just... hand cramp.
Hey, Dad.
- You're home early.
- Yeah,
kind of a letdown, actually.
He wasn't really
what I expected.
- Expectations, huh?
Is this fellow worth
a second chance?
- I don't know.
He was kind of a jerk.
- In that case, you made
the right choice in
cutting him loose.
Be patient. As they say,
if it's meant to be,
I'm sure you two
will connect.
- Night, Dad.
- Had her eating out
of the palm of my hand.
- Perfect. Then help me convince
her to sell to Sanford.
- Sanford wants
to take over Samford?
Wait, did I say
that right?
- Sounds fantastic, doesn't it?
- Well, it doesn't sound
fantastic for Samford.
- Maybe not, but it does
for the Higgins. If we can
talk her into this,
well, you know, I'll have
positioned myself
so we can make a fortune.
This goes through,
I buy a little island somewhere
and you boys take over
the business.
You like that?
- Yeah.
- Ah! Elyse, how are you?
Nice to see you.
- Good to see you.
- Did you get a beverage?
Can I get you something?
- Oh no, I'm fine.
- Well, have a seat.
- So what's going on?
You said it was important.
- Yeah.
An absolutely amazing business
proposal has come in.
- Fantastic. Let's hear it.
- I have to tell you it's
a tremendous piece of news.
Are you ready?
- I'm as ready as I'm gonna be.
- We have an offer
on the table
to buy
Samford Candy.
- Sell Samford?
I'm not interested
in selling Samford.
- Just hear me out.
- It's been in my family
for generations.
- There are major advantages
to considering this offer.
How much time you'll
have for more travel,
your charitable
activities...
You could remain
on the board of Samford
and continue to have a say
in the matters that
are important to you.
- What's important to me
is growing my family's business.
- Elyse,
don't dismiss this
out of hand.
This is an extremely
generous offer.
- Really? Who's making it?
- Sanford.
We're talking the kind of money
that would allow you
to devote the rest of your life
to making a real difference.
Promise me you'll think about
it. I'll send you the offer.
Remember, you and Sanford
are the major players
in this industry.
Together,
you'll be a behemoth.
Unstoppable.
- Well,
I will consult
with my father about it.
- Thank you.
As your advisor
and friend of the family,
I highly recommend
this deal.
The economy is shaky,
the future uncertain.
Samford may never be worth
this much money again.
- Thank you.
I'll see myself out.
- Have a good day.
Send Andrew in.
- Hey.
- Possible buyout of Samford.
Go through it.
- Samford
is incredibly successful. Why in
the world would they wanna sell?
- You're not being paid
to ask questions. Just
look it over, okay?
- The question is,
why is Higgins pushing this?
Samford gets bought out,
he loses his biggest client.
How is that to his advantage?
- Unless he's representing
Sanford, too.
- He can't be. That's a blatant
conflict of interest.
- Too obvious.
- Well, the whole thing
sounds shady.
- So what are you
going to do about it?
- I'm going to try to find out
what's really going on.
- Anything we can do?
- Maybe. Let me get back to you.
Just, uh...
forgot something.
"Dottsandcrossis".
Hmm...
"EmmettandAndrew".
"150%".
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Gotta find something
to help Elyse.
Come on, show me something.
Samford with an "m".
Nothing.
(vacuuming sound)
Caught you.
- I just wanted to see
how much I remembered.
- Come on, Sam, admit it,
this is helping you.
It'll be the only good thing
happening in my life.
- Why? What's wrong?
- My boss is trying
to talk Elyse Samford
into selling her company and I
know something dirty's going on.
I thought maybe he had a big
position in Samford stock
and was going to cash in,
but he doesn't.
- Higgins isn't stupid enough to
hold a huge position in his own
name, it's too obvious.
Plus he's her counsel; it's
a conflict of interest.
- Yeah, I know.
- Unless he's buying
Samford stock
under somebody else's name.
Ever hear of a stealth takeover?
You might wanna check
the stockholders.
- How--
- Used to specialize
in mergers and acquisitions.
- Of course. Thanks.
Okay, so we need
to identify the names
of the major stockholders
of Samford candy.
- 30% of
Samford stock
is institutionally owned,
pension funds, things like that.
It's hard to find
individual names.
I got Joseph Burns,
Alexandra Teller,
Haro Sinanian,
RiGlo Holdings....
- Fantastic.
Are there any more dumplings?
- Now what do we do?
- Search Higgins with each
of these names.
- That's my girl!
Anything?
- Nothing. We can't
connect Higgins
with any of
the shareholders.
- There's a Glogau.
- What's a Glogau?
- Somebody's name.
It's a picture of Higgins'
graduating class.
Yep, Rick Glogau.
See, just like the others,
his name doesn't show up
as a shareholder.
- What's the name
of that company again?
- RiGlo Holdings?
- RiGlo Holdings! Rick Glogau!
I found him!
- So maybe Higgins had
his old college buddy
buy a large position for him
and is pushing Elyse
into selling Samford
so the stock goes up
and he makes a killing.
- RiGlo Holdings has been buying
Samford stock for the last
couple of months.
- Great day!
- Not again.
- Sam, we found somebody
who's been buying big positions
in Samford stock.
- Can you prove Higgins
is behind it?
- You know, you should really
consider a law career.
I need to get more information,
but there isn't a lot of time.
- Pair of shoes.
- What are you doing?
- That's her.
- Who?
- The candy lady.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah, she's the lady
we were talking to by the candy
machine at Plaza Bowl.
- She's the one from the ball.
- Ohh!
- Wait.
Wait!
- Hi.
I'm Ruby.
- Yeah, I remember you.
Hi, "Rob not Ray".
- Hi.
- Do you want to bowl with us?
- You don't have to.
We don't want to intrude.
- That would be great.
I just came here to take
my mind off some things.
- I know what you mean.
- You want
to play for cash?
A little friendly bet?
(chuckling)
- Don't listen to her.
We usually just play for pizza.
- Ooh. Anchovy and pineapple?
- Ew.
- I'm just kidding!
Don't choke now.
- I'm waaaay beyond
reverse psychology.
See?
- Ohh!
Okay.
- Hey, you dropped your wallet!
- Ha, ha, ha!
Boom! Did you think I was gonna
fall for that tired old line?
Go, Ruby!
- She bowls to the right,
she bowls to the left,
watch out now 'cause
Ruby's the best!
- (both chanting):
Ruby! Ruby! Ruby! Ruby!
- Maybe I should
find a new sport.
- Are you kidding?
You are absolutely the best
twelve-year-old bowler I know!
- Rob is the best uncle
in the world. He spends
tons of time with me.
Not many single guys
out there like that, right?
- Yeah, you guys are lucky
to have each other.
- Yeah, it's great he has me,
but what he really needs
is a girlfriend.
(chuckling)
- Don't mind her,
she just thinks
I can't function on my own.
- Well, you guys,
I've had a great time, but I am
gonna have to hit the road.
- What about the pizza?
- I'm gonna have to take
a rain check. Rob,
you know where to find me.
- Hey...
Is that
a custom Storm?
- Yeah. How did you
know that?
- A friend of mine had one once.
- Yeah, but
it's not marked.
- Yeah, well...
Don't wanna keep ya!
- Okay.
See you guys.
- I can't believe you didn't
tell her you were the prince.
- Thanks for keeping my secret.
- Why didn't you tell her
that your boss is trying
to cheat her?
- I wanted to.
- Then why didn't you?
- I can't really prove it.
Plus I could tell her and
she could not believe me.
Or I could tell her and
start a huge fire storm
and it could turn out she wasn't
going to take the deal, anyway.
And then I'd get fired
for nothing.
- Don't you always tell me to do
the right thing no matter what?
- It isn't that simple.
You ready for pizza?
- Not hungry.
- Come on, you're always hungry.
- Well, I'm not hungry.
- Come on, Ruby.
Morning.
- If you want to know
how the class is going,
it's filled with arrogant
young shysters.
- So you're still going?
- For lack of anything
better to do.
- By the way, I paid all your
dues, so all you have to do
is finish the classes and
you can practicing law again.
- You're a good guy,
you know that?
- Not exactly.
- Rob, I'm telling you
you're a good guy.
Me. Sam. The guy
who hates everybody?
Hey, Rob.
- Yeah?
- (under his breath): Thanks.
- Did you actually
just say "thanks?"
- I may have. No, no, no,
I don't do the hug.
Hey, hey! Ah!
Okay, we're good. We're good.
- Thanks. Thank you.
- Did you go
through the offer?
- Why are we pushing her to sell
a hugely successful company?
I mean, if they sell,
we could lose--
- Did you go through it or not?
- I did.
But Elyse Samford
just took over as CEO.
If they wanted to sell,
shouldn't they have done it
before her father stepped down?
- Tick, tick, tick. That's the
sound of you wasting my time.
- I'm just thinking that--
- You're not being paid
to think.
- I'm not being paid
to ask questions, I'm not
being paid to think.
Then what am I being paid for?
- To cross the t's
and dot the i's.
- Do you even read, or did you
think you'd get a promotion
if it looks like you can?
- I passed the bar my first try.
Unlike yourself, who still
hold the state record
for number of times failed.
But I guess when Daddy's
the boss, it doesn't
matter, does it?
- The cloud ate my calendar.
- I'll take a look at it later.
Do you have
Elyse Samford's number?
- If it didn't eat
my contacts, I do.
- [Hello?]
- Elyse? It's Rob Carelli.
I've got to come talk to you.
- [Okay.]
- Right away.
I struggled over whether
to come to you with this,
but I had to tell you
about my suspicions.
- If you're concerned
there's something going on,
I'd like to hear about it.
Have a seat.
- It looks to me like Higgins
is buying stock in your company
in someone else's name, betting
on the takeover going through.
- What makes you think
that's the case?
- Why else would he
be pushing this?
- Do you have anything
to prove that allegation?
- One of the major stockholders
is an old college friend
of Carter's.
He's buying the shares
through a holding company.
- Can you prove the connection
to Higgins?
- No.
- Carter Higgins has been
Samford's legal counsel
for decades.
And I barely know you.
So tell me why
I should believe you.
- No reason in the world
other than the fact that
I have nothing to gain
by coming to you with this
and everything to lose.
But Higgins, if I'm right,
stands to make a fortune
if you go through with this.
- But I don't know if you're
right. You don't even know
if you're right.
- I know this is a big leap,
but if you could just
look into it further.
- You realize if I confront
Carter about this,
I'm going to have
to cite you as my source.
Otherwise nothing I say
will seem credible.
- I understand that.
- You'll probably lose your job.
- No probably about it.
- Then why are you doing this?
Why do you care if my family
business gets bought out?
- I...
The night of the...
- Yes?
- I just can't stand around
watching you get swindled.
- Well, thank you
for coming to me.
I appreciate you
risking your job.
I'm going to have
to think it over.
(whimsical music)
- I'm glad you told her
about the takeover.
- Thanks.
- I'm proud of you.
Is she going to stop it?
- I don't know. I'm not
sure if she believed me.
- Is there anything else
you can do?
- I'm out of options.
My hands are tied.
- What if you told her
you're the prince?
- It's complicated.
Things don't always go
the way we want them to.
Life isn't a fairy tale.
Everyone doesn't always
live happily ever after.
- Ruby! Hey, what
are you doing here?
Are you alone?
- We need to talk.
- Okay, come on.
- Ms. Samford.
- Hey, Peter.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Peter.
We won't be long.
- Furthermore,
the plaintiff in the case--
What's going on?
- Carelli was absolutely
not at the Ball.
He was here working all night.
Emmett saw him.
- My mom made the costume
just for him.
Rob was the prince at the Ball.
Rob is the one who fell in love
with this lady.
- He did?
- He really did.
- Well, that's ridiculous.
The kid's obviously lying.
My son Emmett wore
that prince's costume.
- You're the one lying.
- Let's just get Rob
and Emmett in here.
Now.
- [Emmett? Get Andrew
and come into my office.]
(knocking)
- Andrew,
Dad's office. Now.
- [Carelli, get into my office.]
- I swear, Dad, I came back from
the Ball and I saw him here.
You were working
all night, right?
- I snuck out
and went to the Ball.
When I overheard your father
telling you to come back here,
I took off and
just beat you back.
- That's impossible! You'll have
to take his word or ours, Elyse.
There's simply
no proof. No proof!
- Little trick
my grandfather taught me.
- Ew.
- Your favorite bowler
is Kelly Kulick.
You've bowled one perfect game
and you have the softest
lips in the world.
- Hey! You're fired!
- I don't think you're
in the right pay grade
to do that, little brother.
- Dad, fire him!
- You can assume that
if he was lying to you
about who the prince at the Ball
was, then he's also lying
about his involvement
in the Sanford buyout.
- That's it! Carelli,
get your things!
- Why did I have
to find out from Rob
that Sanford was cybersquatting
our domain name?
It seems to me if you were
looking out for my best
interests,
you would have been aware
of that a long time ago.
Unless of course you didn't
want me to know about it
because you knew Sanford
was planning to try and buy us.
- I'm absolutely appalled at
those accusations, young lady.
- Carter,
I am firing your firm
as counsel to Samford Candy Co.
I will have my new lawyer,
Mr. Carelli,
send over a termination letter
and collect all files today.
- Oh, and Mr. Higgins,
you can expect a call
from the SEC about this.
- Score!
- You do not get to talk
to my father like that!
You'll be sorry!
- Emmett?
- Yeah?
- Shut up.
- Yes, Dad.
- Hi, Rob.
- Hey, Sally.
(knocking)
Sam,
you are looking good.
- Stop.
- How's the new apartment?
- It's more like a closet
but I'll do for starters.
- Alright,
"and associates." Ready to go?
- Absolutely.
Shall we?
- We shall.
- By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
(applause)
- Ha! We got married.