I'm sure
we're not far off.
I'm glad you're
sure of it, George.
Oh, shit!
Hold on! Hold on!
Oh, sweetie.
Everyone all right?
You okay?
Okay?
Everyone okay?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Sit back, sit back.
Fuck, I think we're stuck.
Oh, shit.
How're you doing?
Hey--
you mind just
putting that down?
- Sorry.
- Thank you.
Where's the buck?
Will you guys cool it in front
of my kid, for fuck's sake?
- Kim, Kim.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
We've been after that buck
for 18 hours.
- I don't fucking care!
- Kim, Kim, Kim.
We just had an accident,
and you fire your gun
- 15 feet in front of my fucking car!
- Kim, cool out.
- Yeah, Kim, cool out.
- Hey, listen, look!
We're a little shook up.
Kim, just cool out for a minute.
- Can you tell me--
- Goddamn it!
Kim, cool out,
sit in the car.
Check on Miles.
Can you tell me who I can
call in town to get a tow?
Nobody open
this time of night.
That's just not true.
Can you tell me
the next big town?
Is there anywhere
closer than Danbury?
Hey, one of these antlers
is cracked, Otis.
That guy's a real treat.
Did they tell you
who to call?
No.
Let me see the map.
Fuck!
This is a bummer, right?
Yeah.
Were you scared
when we hit that deer?
- Yeah.
- You okay though?
- Some people out here
hunt the deer
and they catch the weaker ones
who wouldn't survive
the winter, that's the idea.
But it's sad.
- Poor deer.
- Yeah.
Shit.
I'm about 20 miles
south of Danbury.
Um, I just passed a bridge,
Shadow Ridge? Shadow Creek?
Something--
Shadow Creek.
Your daddy's gonna-- daddy's gonna
get us a tow out of here.
Right, Dad?
I said it was a mile
after that bridge
- on Shadow Ridge, right?
- Yeah, sounds right.
They said half an hour.
Okay. Then I'm going
to make us all dinner.
Right?
Yeah?
The antler on that deer
is busted because of you.
I'm sorry for that.
I wish it hadn't happened that way.
That all you got to say?
I think we should
just leave it at that.
Is that right?
Excuse me,
can I...
Excuse me, excus e me.
Can you step away
from the car, please?
Can I ask you your name?
- Otis.
- Otis?
My name is George,
and I'd like you to please
stay away from the car,
if you don't mind.
My family's very upset.
We want to wait here for our ride.
Now, I'm sorry
about the deer.
But it was an accident,
there's nothing we can do about it.
I don't know how
I can be any clearer.
Rack of antlers like that
worth a lot of money.
Hey, Otis,
I'm gonna go get the truck.
- Otis.
- I'm going to get the truck.
Otis, what do you say?
I say it's my deer
and this guy busted an antler!
Otis, that ain't right.
We got to talk about this.
Billy made the first hit,
so I don't know if it's yours.
The fuck with that.
I had the fatal shot.
Billy wounded him.
This guy took him out.
And you did the mercy killing.
Mercy killing.
Excuse me.
Guy's a piece of work.
Good shot, man.
That guy's got a problem.
Goddamn.
Are you dead or alive?
Alive.
Are you famous?
Yes.
Are you...
in showbiz?
Yes.
- It's like a farewell butt, right?
- Yeah.
- Madonna?
- No.
Courtney Love?
No, you have to keep
asking me questions.
Spice Girls?
Don't just assume
I'm a woman.
I think this is
our ride.
What's he up to now?
Could have saved you
some trouble. We got this.
- You the one that called?
- I called. What are you doing?
I'm getting you out of that ditch.
You could've asked.
No, no, no.
Looks like you got yourself
a friend for life.
Are you going up
to the Stooky place?
I guess you were right, Otis.
You all from the city?
You want to give
it a go, Billy?
Wait. Just wait.
Wait a minute. Wait.
- Stand back.
- Relax.
Here we go.
Okay, okay. Thank you.
There it is.
Ha ha ha.
Whoo!
It's $40
just for coming up here.
- I won't charge you for the tow.
- Thank you.
I'll only charge you $20.
I'm not paying you
anything.
Look who's got a bug
up his ass.
Listen, I didn't ask
for your help.
I'd already called for the tow.
You knew that.
I knew what?
I'm not doing this.
I'm not! This is ridiculous.
I don't think I understand
what your problem is, George.
- I really don't.
- Here.
- Somebody's got some manners.
- George, let's go.
Thank you, Kim.
I make a point of pissing in
your drinking water once a week.
New York City reservoir
just a mile from here.
- That's nice.
- Don't say anything, just drive.
I drink bottled water anyway.
What a prick.
Whoo!
It should be to the left.
There's a bridge.
Bridge?
Only Richard would have a bridge.
Here we go, Miles,
over the moat.
The moat to the castle.
Richard and Annie's mansion.
Yeah. It's a tan house,
isn't it?
Oh, it's beautiful.
Well, of course,
it's Richard
and Annie's house.
Whoo-oo...
Richard and Annie's house.
George, shush.
See, babe, not even a dent.
Built to last.
Lap of luxury, George.
Hey, Miles,
look at that.
- Huh?
- Hmm.
Looks pretty old, Dad.
Come on.
Let's go, Miles.
Whew, it's cold.
It shouldn't be so cold.
- There's a draft. You feel it?
- Yeah.
I'll turn the heat on.
Okay.
Want to unpack your bag?
Dad?
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah, I just found--
What?
The window was broken.
Go find some cardboard
and some tape.
Ask your mother.
Oh... okay.
Dad?
Yeah?
Were you scared before?
Maybe I was more shook up than I
thought by that thing on the road.
That's better, right?
Hey, Miles, why don't you
go get the cards?
- Dad!
- Get them, we'll have a quick round.
All right.
So...
Pick a card, any card.
Ha! Da-dum-dum-dum.
Da-dum-dum-dum.
All right.
''Together.''
Hmm. T-o...
g-e-t-h...
- I don't know.
- Come on, try.
Hmm, e-r?
Good, yeah, good.
Remember, it's basically ''To get her.''
See what I mean?
Let's see what's next.
It's ''Separate.''
This is a tough one.
I can't even spell
this one Every time.
In fact, if you get this,
you'll be top of your class.
You'll rule.
You will rule.
Come on, try.
S-e...
- p...
- Uh-huh?
- H mm?
- Where are you going, buddy?
- a-r...?
- Yeah?
a-t-e.
Good for you.
Nice one. Well done.
All right-- Ooh-hoo-hoo.
Toughy, toughy.
''Onomatopoeia.''
- I don't think so.
- All right, all right, all right.
''L'chaim.''
- Dad!
- All right, all right, all right.
''Appetite, appetite.''
- ''Appetite.''
- Come on, Dad. We did two.
Come on, try ''Appetite.''
What's wrong with that?
- You can do that.
- Dad!
All right, all right.
Go on.
You're no fun.
Nice going, kiddo.
What if you're sitting
in your living room
and a bullet
flies through the window?
Who do you call?
I'm just so glad we don't
have Star anymore.
She looked just like a deer.
She wouldn't have lasted
10 seconds out here.
- I miss Star.
- There's no TV.
You've got those
cool books there, Miles.
There are videos,
aren't there?
Nothing good.
Nothing you've heard of.
Let's build a fire.
Cool!
Richard said there'd be some wood
in the shed out back.
Miles,
- let's go get us some wood.
- Yeah!
Come on, bud.
Okay, help me
find some kindling.
Do you know how
to use an ax?
- Huh?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, first you've got
to get it balanced.
Get it right there
in the hole.
Holy moly!
Careful, Miles!
I-yi-yi.
They let me use this road
to pass through.
Dad?
- Is that him?
- Shh, shh.
He didn't get to keep the deer.
Go to your mom.
So he just drove across?
Just drove right by.
I don't understand why Richard
would let anyone
drive across the property.
Maybe Richard,
or maybe Annie,
wanted to seem neighborly
so they let him.
I don't know.
I think Annie and Richard
never come up here.
That's why they're
so generous with their keys.
It was Annie's thing anyway.
I knew Richard's interest
would fade.
He needs to be
in the center of it all.
Who wants to retire
to the country when you're young?
It's called an inner life,
George.
Just 'cause you don't approve
of my inner life
doesn't mean
I don't have one.
Ooh.
Besides, didn't he have
some weird incident up here,
and he just stopped
coming up for a while?
I don't remember that.
Maybe he just
told me about it.
What was it?
Some incident.
I guess I don't remember.
Probably had to do with that guy
driving across the property.
Annie would've told me
about something like that.
How you doing, Miles?
You liking the pasta?
Mmm, it's okay.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Come on, what is it?
That man knows
where we live.
Miles, don't worry,
sweetie.
I know I got angry
with him
outside the car,
but he was very excited
because he was chasing that deer.
It's really okay to hunt if you're
getting in tune with nature.
Don't feed him
that sack of shit, Kim.
- That guy was demented.
- George.
Your father exaggerates,
you know that.
It's nothing
to worry about, Miles.
Your mom can be very fair
and even-headed,
which is cool, right?
Except you don't want
to be a softy, either.
You got to be wary
of people like that guy.
They can be bad news.
No, queen!
King! King, king!
- Okay, okay.
- Jack.
Oh, five!
Five, six, seven, six--
no, no, eight!
Wait, wait, wait.
- Nine, five, five, three...
- Jack, Jack.
- Victory!
- No, no. You!
- Dad cheated!
- I did not.
- We have to let your father win.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, you.
Okay, Miles, come on.
- To bed.
- To bed, to bed, to bed.
One more game, please?
- No, come on. Up you go.
- To bed, to bed.
What'd you draw?
Oh, nothing.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
No one there.
No one there?
Okay...
And no one there.
You're safe.
- Mom?
- Yeah?
Do you think that deer
had a little family?
Oh, Miles...
don't think
about that, sweetie.
That's just sad stuff
that happens sometimes.
But you know, in nature
things like that happen,
and all the animals,
they adjust.
There's a balance.
Think about that, okay?
- Dad--!
- Dad!
It's not funny.
Good night, kid.
Night, Dad.
- Leave it open.
- I will, I will.
- Leave the hall light on.
- Shh-- go to sleep.
Can you tell me a little more
about ''sack of shit''?
What?
Talking to Miles
like that at dinner?
Oh.
- It was a bit harsh, I guess.
- What's the matter, George?
I don't know,
I can't put my finger on it.
Is it the reshoot?
Are you pissed off you're here?
No, no, babe.
That's not it at all.
Huh-uh.
This is nice.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
Yeah...?
Hmm?
- Those fucking guys.
- Out on the road?
- Yeah.
- What about them?
I just felt
the abyss between us--
me and that guy
with his shotgun.
That wasn't a shotgun,
but anyway...
And he had a pistol.
Did that threaten
your manhood?
Yeah, I guess it did,
Dr. McLaren.
Well, it's very
archetypical
for the civilized man
to feel threatened
by the man of the country.
That one guy,
he just seemed like--
how do you get through
to someone like that?
- George.
- Aaah.
- George?
- What?
We have ways of restoring
confidence in men with...
With emasculation problems?
Really?
Perhaps you should show me?
Exactly.
- Perhaps you could show me, doctor?
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
- This could take a while.
- Ooh, I hope so.
We'd like to start...
with a full checkup.
Hey, you.
Ho, ho, ho.
Wow, is this
to impress your clients?
No, my clients aren't
privy to this information.
Oh, really? 'cause I think
this one would cure them all.
Shhh.
- Is Miles in bed?
- He's fine.
Miles?
Are you there?
Mom?
I'm s cared.
Shh.
It's okay, honey.
Dad and I are right here.
Try to go back to sleep.
Anyway, Stefan's going
to stick to the prenup,
and he's not going
to budge.
He's got a right to be pissed.
She slept with his best friend,
who happens to be
his accountant too.
She's not going to ask for money,
she just wants out.
She's going to take him
for all he's worth.
You're sweet to be naive
on this one, but no.
All right,
maybe you're right.
It's pretty tacky.
If there's any justice,
she'll be hit by a bus.
Doesn't work that way,
George.
Here we go.
Outstanding.
Who wants to go into town
with me after breakfast?
- I do.
- Me, too.
I need curry if I'm
going to make that cass erole.
We must have curry.
Is very very important.
- Must have the curry.
- Dad.
I like the curry.
I cook the meanest curry
this side of Delhi.
Gotcha!
One,
two!
Think that guy
really pees in the reservoir?
Shush, George.
You're going to get Miles
all excited talking about pee pee.
We're going to go in this store,
you want to come?
No, I'm going to go
get the milk and curry.
What'd you say,
olive oil?
Something for Miles
to drink, too.
What should I get him?
Something he'd like,
George.
Okay, okay.
Cool it, baby.
Fruit juice or something.
All right.
I'll pull the car around.
- I'll meet you right here.
- Okay.
You like that?
It's okay,
you can talk to me.
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you know what it is?
Wendigo.
- Wendigo?
- Wendigo.
- What's a Wendigo?
- A Wendigo is a mighty,
powerful spirit.
What's it look like?
It can take on
many forms.
Part wind, part tree,
part man,
part beast.
Shapeshifting between them.
Shapeshifting?
Shapeshifting.
Can it fly?
It can fly at you like
a sudden storm, without warning,
from nowhere...
and de vour you--
consume you with its
ferocious appetite.
Appetite?
The Wendigo is hungry--
always hungry.
And its hunger
is never satisfied.
The more it eats,
the bigger it gets.
And the bigger it gets,
the hungrier it gets.
And we are hopeless
in the face of it.
We are devoured.
Is the Wendigo bad?
Nothing between
the earth and sky is bad.
But there are spirits
that should be feared.
'Cause why?
Because there are spirits
that are angry.
Angry?
Do you believe me?
I guess.
Go ahead and take it.
Nobody believes
in spirits anymore.
Doesn't mean
they're not there.
He who hears
the cry of the Wendigo
is never the same again.
Miles?
Miles, let's go.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa.
You've got to be careful in here.
What have you got?
The man gave it to me.
What man?
Behind the counter back there.
Excuse me.
My son said the man up there
gave him this little figure.
- Is that okay?
- What's he got?
That's... $5.
$5? Come on, Miles,
who said you could have that?
The Indian guy
behind the counter back there.
Is that possible
someone gave it to him?
Nobody works here but me.
Nobody's been in here
but me.
Oh, okay.
Come on, Miles.
Let's give it back.
He's kind of cool.
Will you take $3?
Four.
Okay.
You just blew
our budget, Miles.
There was a guy, mom.
- He gave it to me.
- What kind of a guy?
Hey, Dad.
- What?
- Later.
Come on.
- Mom?
- Yeah?
Didn't you see
the man?
I didn't see him.
Doesn't mean he wasn't there,
but you shouldn't
make stuff up that isn't true.
He was there.
I believe you, sweetie.
If it's true.
Mom.
Wendigo.
It can grow as tall
as the trees
and still it aches
with hunger.
The Wendigo is hungry--
always hungry.
And it's hunger
is never satisfied.
The more it eats,
the bigger it gets.
And the bigger it gets,
the hungrier it gets.
And we are hopeless
in the face of it.
We are devoured.
It can fly at you like a sudden storm,
without warning,
from nowhere...
and devour you--
consume you
with its ferocious appetite.
There are spirits
that should be feared...
because there are spirits
that are angry.
- Jesus.
- What?
I can't take this guy.
Seriously, he's like Boo Radley
the way he's always around.
George, Boo Radley
was a good guy.
Right, Miles?
Did you realize how close
we are to those guys?
Those are some
nice neighbors to have.
George, shush.
Look, Dad.
Look what I got from the man
at the thrift store.
- It's magic.
- That's cool.
Why don't you go show that guy
to your transformers?
They're not transformers.
What? What?
You got to show
more interest.
Last week it was transformers.
What can I say?
You don't see it, George,
but he lies and makes stuff up
to get attention.
It's because you got
to be there for him.
If we're going to do these weekends,
you got to be engaged.
You put these ideas in his head that
I'm not interested. It's not fair.
Come on, I don't
discuss this with Miles.
You've got all this anger
you carry around from work
or I don't know where,
and he feels it.
- He thinks it's directed at him.
- Oh--
He doesn't know what it is,
I don't know.
- Everyone's got anger.
- Oh, George.
I don't want to be
analyzed right now.
Miles sees this stuff.
He sees.
I got to make this phone call
to Charles in the city.
I told him I'd call.
I'll take Miles out afterwards.
We'll go sledding.
Okay.
I'll cook.
I got the curry.
Thank you, dear.
Come on, baby.
Hey, hey, hey.
We never even looked around
the whole house together.
No, go ahead.
Go on, make your call.
No, no, no.
Let's look upstairs. Come on.
I guess they're
still fixing it up.
I'd love to have the time
to acquire all this stuff.
Yup.
Annie has a good eye.
Mmm.
Aaah!
She really has this whole
stag thing going here.
I mean, look at this.
Aah.
Poor deer.
I took this funny picture
of the sheriff in town today.
Yeah?
He shot me this look.
It must piss
the locals off,
all these outsiders
coming up here.
It's really great
you brought your camera.
Get some pictures
for yourself.
- Yeah. Hey, look at this.
- What?
- You know that reservoir?
- Yeah.
This whole town's
buried under there.
- Hmm.
- 10,000 acres.
They flooded the valley
in 1907
to make drinking water
for New York City.
- Wow.
- That's a lot of displaced people.
We'd already displaced
the Indians.
Now Annie and Richard
live here.
Displacing Everybody.
A lot of Indian stuff
in the area.
Yeah, it's
the Catskills, George.
''Yeah, it's the Catskills, George.''
''It's the Catskills.''
Miles: No!
Miles?
Are you okay, sweetie?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just got sad.
- Are you cold out here?
- I'm okay.
What made you sad?
- I don't know.
- What do you think it is?
You can tell mommy.
Maybe he's just moody
like his dad, right, tiger?
Sometimes it helps to talk
about things when you're sad.
You've got to watch for those moods.
They'll get the best of you.
You'll end up taking soulful
pictures of corporate logos.
Oh, you shush.
Don't listen to him.
Your father complains
about his work,
but a lot of people
would kill for his job.
Don't listen to her.
Feeling sorry for yourself
is very unattractive.
Miles, remember,
boys against girls.
Hey.
Hey, tiger.
I think your dad wants
to take you sledding.
- Right, Dad?
- Yeah! What do you say?
Um, okay.
All right, I'm going to make
this call and we'll go out.
So you get ready.
I'll be right back.
- Yeah, man?
- Yeah.
Yeah, man.
You okay, sweetie?
- Don't worry, mom.
- '' Don't worry, mom''?
You're growing up
so fast.
Now come here.
Hey, Chas,
it's George.
So what's the verdict?
Are they serious about this reshoot?
Really? Fuck!
I'm up here, so...
It's nice.
Yeah, it's pretty cold.
Well, we had this--
this weird thing happen.
Yeah, we hit this deer.
It came right at the windshield,
so that was bad enough,
but then there was
this one guy, man.
I'm telling you, Chas,
this guy was bad news.
It scared me, yeah.
I was afraid
for Kim and the kid.
So what do they say
the problem is?
It's too dark?
In terms of light or tone--
like content, know what I mean?
Do they know what they mean?
Maybe it's just
a question of contrast.
No, I mean visual contrast.
I could bring out
the highlights.
Anyway, I'm not fighting
for anything anymore.
Just tell them to tell us
what they want,
I'll deal with it on Tuesday.
I'm taking Monday off like I planned.
They don't own me.
Okay, they don't
own me till Tuesday, okay?
All right, Chas.
Thanks, man.
Okay, I'll see you.
Hey, hey.
I'm going
to take Miles out.
We're going sledding.
You better believe it.
Hey, Miles, help!
Aaah!
Dad.
I know.
Ha ha ha.
Aaah!
No, aah!
Come on, kiddo.
Are you ready?
So, what happened?
They want to do it,
fuck them.
What are you going to do?
You need to go back?
No, baby, I want
to do this for us.
Charles can
take care of it.
We could go back
early Monday.
It's beautiful, it's perfect.
Come on, kiddo, let's go.
Ha ha ha!
We're off, we're off,
we're off!
Here you go, buddy.
Take my hand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah!
Sledding, sledding,
sledding.
You guys be careful.
- Oh, Mom.
Andy? Hi.
It's Dr. McLaren.
Is Everything all right?
I thought we weren't going
to call on the weekends?
Okay, okay.
What happened?
Okay.
How do you feel
about that?
Right.
You were intimidated, but...
What did you tell him?
Sorry, Andy,
but that's good.
It's right, because
you don't have the money.
So-- wait a minute, Andy,
I think they have call waiting here.
Hello?
Hey, Richard,
thanks for getting back to us.
Listen--
Oh, yeah?
You getting a tan down there?
Listen, we called because--
Shit.
I'm sorry,
can you wait a minute?
I have someone
on the other line.
Hold on.
Andy? Hi.
I have to take this.
But listen-- you did well.
You asserted yourself.
Try to experience that on your own.
After you've thought about it,
we'll talk on Wednesday.
Okay? It's important to keep
some boundaries between us.
You're trying to get
to be more independent, right?
Andy?
Okay, bye bye.
Richard.
Richard, are you there?
Hello?
Hel--
Shit.
''Whose woods these are
I think I know.
His house is in
the village though;
He will not see me
stopping here
To watch his woods
fill up with snow...
The woods are lovely,
dark and deep.
But I have promises
to keep,
And miles to go
before I sleep,
before I sleep.''
- Miles!
- That's right.
The poet's name
was Robert Frost.
He was writing
about the cold.
- What do you think about that?
- Oh, Dad.
Now Frost could take a simple image
and make it seem deep.
That's his rap.
Hey, what's the matter?
- Dad?
- Yeah?
- What's a Wendigo?
- A Wendigo?
I don't know. I never heard of that.
What's a Wendigo?
I don't know.
Where'd you hear
about it?
- This man.
- What man?
- In the thrift store.
- In town?
He told me the Wendigo
is this man
who's part animal,
always hungry,
and he eats people.
The Wendigo only goes
after bad guys, Miles.
You're safe.
You're a good kid.
- Hey, Miles?
- Yeah?
A lot of people
make up stories
to make sense
of the world.
It's a big world
after all,
and nobody really understands
how it all works.
Maybe for that guy
it's comforting to think
that the Wendigo is responsible
for all the bad stuff
out there.
That's okay.
That's what myths are.
They help us
talk about stuff.
Like Mr. Freeze
and Dr. Evil.
Dr. Evil.
There are good myths guys too,
like Superman and Yoda.
- Hmm.
- It's important to know
that they're just myths,
just stories.
You'll end up being
very disappointed
when things don't come true
that you're wishing.
Like when you didn't get
your big show in Soho?
Soho?
You little monster.
You are a dead man.
Oh, Dad.
You--
I've had enough of you.
You little--
you're a dead man.
- No!
- You're a dead man.
Truce! Truce.
Truce!
Truce?
Yeah.
- Okay.
- Dad.
Come here, buddy.
Hey.
Come on, let's sit.
It's good you feel bad about
that deer we hit, you know?
But things like that happen.
And you have to go through
a period of mourning.
Like where you're sad,
and then you put it behind you.$(where czy when)
You get it?
Where even
the worst thing
can be seen
in another way.
'Cause you got to be flexible
to make it in this old world.
Hmmm.
You sure you're not just stalling
'cause that hill looks steep?
No way!
Okay, buddy,
let's get that ride
so we can go home
and bother your mother.
Yeah!
Come on, buddy!
Dad?
Miles?
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Can you get up,
sweetie?
Here.
Careful, careful.
Honey,
you hit your head.
You're okay.
You're okay?
Huh?
Where's your father?
Where? Huh?
Where?
I don't understand,
Miles.
What happened?
- Daddy fell off the sled.
- How did he fall off the sled?
I don't know.
Hold my hand tight.
- Oh my God.
- He was here, mom.
He was here.
He wouldn't move.
Oh, God.
It's okay.
Come on.
Oh, God.
Hold on.
Oh, my God.
Miles...
did you hear anything when dad
fell off the sled?
- I don't remember.
- It's okay, sweetie.
Come on,
hold my hand tight.
Come on-- wait, wait.
We've got a whole deer
to cut up!
Where are you going?
- Hey!
- Oh.
Can I help you
with something?
I'm-- I'm trying
to find my husband.
Husband?!
- There's been an accident.
- What kind of accident?
- Have you seen my husband?
- What's he look like?
What was the name
of the guy who left?
He pulled out in his truck
just before I got here?
Otis?
Brandon, put those
on the bench.
It was you that was out
in the road last night, right?
You're staying at
the Stooky place this weekend?
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I saw a light on,
I-I needed to check.
- Come on, Miles.
- Just a minute.
Did you have some kind of accident?
- You want a tow or something?
- What happened?
No, I-I'm--
I'm sorry,
I-I was wrong. I--
I-I'm sorry.
I have to run.
Come on, sweetie, come on.
Hold on.
- Jesus Christ.
- Just let her go.
- Dad, where do you want these?
- Put them in the freezer.
- Spooky, man.
- Yeah.
- What was that about?
- They're just excitable city people.
Hey, man, what'd you do
with the beer?
We drank
all the last stuff I bought.
- What do you want to do with these?
- Put them in the freezer.
Unless you want
to eat them tonight.
Okay, Miles,
sweetie, you're gonna
have to walk.
Daddy's probably
gone home.
George!
Oh, my God!
Miles,
he did go home!
Come on. George!
George!
- George!
- Dad!
George.
Oh, my God.
Kim-- Kim.
What--
Oh, my God!
Miles, get a blanket.
Daddy's going to be all right.
We just want to keep him warm.
And a scotch--
Aargh!
- What happened?
- This is bad.
Who would believe it--
I'd swear I've been shot.
Those fucking guys!
- They shot me!
- Can we get you inside?
No, baby, no, no, no.
We've got to get to Danbury.
There's a hospital there.
We-- just get in the car.
- I'll call an ambulance.
- No, baby, no, no, no.
I got to know
we're on our way.
George, are you sure?
I don't know.
Let's do it!
Let's do it, Kimmy!
Oh God, oh!
Kim!
Miles!
Miles, help me!
Okay, push me,
push my back.
- Let me do it, let me do it!
- Can you get up?
- Let me do it!
- Okay. Okay.
Oh God, George...
Oh God.
Hand me the blanket,
sweetie.
Okay... Let's go,
let's go.
Hey, you okay?
- You okay, Miles?
- Yeah, Dad.
Yeah, you see me
fall off that sled?
- Yeah.
- How about that, huh?
I ran into a tree
looking for you.
Aww, good for you.
Atta boy.
Shh, shh,
stop talking.
Get the door.
It can fly at you
like a sudden storm,
without warning,
from nowhere...
and devour you--
consume you with
his ferocious appetite.
The Wendigo is hungry,
always hungry.
Its hunger
is never satisfied.
Do you want this?
I don't believe it.
Miles, seatbelt.
I fell back off the sled.
I didn't know what had happened
for the longest time.
I couldn't even feel the pain.
I didn't know if it was
hot or cold.
But then I saw the blood,
I must have fainted.
When I woke up,
it was like I'd been drowning
and this was
my last breath of air.
Like if I didn't
take this breath, I'd--
I'd slip away
for good...
into some euphoria.
I was tempted,
but I made myself get up.
I found the house,
it was easy.
It was like I was
carried by a big wind
and dropped at the door.
This is it,
I can feel it.
I'm only half here, Kim.
Daddy's gonna be all right, Miles.
Daddy's gonna
be all right.
This is an emergency.
My husband...
has been shot.
I need to know where
the hospital is in Danbury.
Fuck.
I'm heading west
on Route 19.
Okay.
I need you to call
the sheriff
and have him
meet us there.
And-- are you serious?
What's the number?
What's the fucking number?!
-
- What's the fucking number?
Don't be scared,
kiddo.
Don't be scared.
It's going to be okay.
Hey, hey, hey!
Listen to me--
remember that little thing
you got from the store?
What was it--
yeah, there it is!
Yeah, it's got
magic powers, right?
Huh? Isn't that
what you told me?
Right? Huh?
I was listening,
Miles.
Miles, I was
listening to you.
Don't be scared,
kiddo.
Don't be scared.
It's going
to be okay, huh?
Oh, Kim, oh baby.
What a fucking waste.
Give me your hand, Miles.
Give me your hand, buddy.
Yeah...
Watch the door.
Okay, somebody get
his feet!
One, two, three.
It's his abdomen.
Right in here.
Yeah.
Just a second.
I want you to tell Charles I'm
definitely not doing that reshoot.
- Shut up, George.
- What are you going to do...
when you got no one to shush?
I love you. Hang in there.
I got separation issues, you know?
Yeah, I know.
S-s-- s-e-p--
a-r-a-t-i-o-n.
- Dad?
- Hey, Miles.
Miles,
listen to me,
I want you to take care
of your mom.
- All right?
- Dad, what happened?
I don't know, kiddo.
Kimmy, Kim.
Ohhh, Kimmy!
Oh, such a beautiful day.
God, I remember
so much about today.
Those eggs and--
a drive, and--
we went sledding,
Miles and me.
You're my family,
my family, my family.
Oh, Kim, Kim.
Kim, you remember--
do you remember?
Do you remember
his first week home?
Do you remember he kept us up
for two nights screaming?
Yeah, I thought we'd
never make it through.
Listen, I'm always going
to be with you.
Come on, sweetie,
it's going to be okay.
Take my hand-- my hand.
Second down and 9
at the 35...
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Um, excuse me.
Mrs. McLaren?
- Yes.
- Hi, I'm Tom Hale.
Hey, there,
buckaroo.
I'm the sheriff.
Do you mind telling me
what happened?
My husband--
my husband was shot.
I think he was,
by this man
who we saw at--
at Braintree Road.
His name was Otis.
- Otis?
- Do you know who he is?
Mmm, yeah, well--
I'd seen him before.
He was--
he seemed capable of--
Now, Mrs. McLaren,
we don't know for certain
that your husband
was shot.
Mrs. McLaren?
Your husband was shot
once in the side
with a high-powered rifle.
The bullet grazed his liver
and the doctors
are recommending
emergency surgery-- immediately.
There'll be some papers
for you to sign,
so if you'll
wait right here...
Well, do you
know him or not?!
Yeah, Otis Stooky.
- What?
- Pardon?
That's the place
we're staying,
- the Stooky house.
- Really?
That's where Otis
grew up.
- What?
- Yeah, his mother died,
and then she left it
to Otis' sister.
Sister sold the place
and moved down to Florida.
Christ.
You mind telling me exactly
what happened, Mrs. McLaren?
Last night we--
we hit a deer with our car.
It was a fluke.
These men came out of the woods
and one of them was named Otis.
Oh, I can't believe this!
Wrong place,
wrong time.
Mrs. McLaren?
With your permission,
the y'll get started right away.
Oh, God!
I cannot fucking believe this.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Miles, help me.
Jack,
this is Tom Hale.
I want you to meet me
up at Battle Creek Road.
Otis Stooky's place.
I need backup.
Do you copy? Over.
Hey! Otis, you in there?
Tom Hale.
Hey!
It's the sheriff.
You in there, Otis?
What do you want,
Sheriff?
I want you to step outside
for just a moment, Otis.
What is it, Tom Hale?
Those people staying
up at the Stooky place,
they filed a complaint.
I just want
to ask you some questions.
You come down
to the station with me?
What kind of complaint?
Ah, come on, Otis.
Do me a favor.
They're from the city.
I've just got to go through
all the formalities.
What'd they say happened?
Oh, I don't know.
Just something about
them hitting a deer
and you was there,
and I got to--
I just got to get a statement
from you, that's all.
- Aw, shit, Tom!
- Yeah, I know what you mean.
These people come up
from the city,
they act like they own
the damn place.
Look, I get it every day.
That fucking Ben Stratton,
you know.
Raising our taxes,
kissing these people's ass.
Yeah, that's right.
You come with me now, huh?
I got Jack stopping by
in a moment.
I'd like you to come down
with me now, just to-- you know--
just to keep it
simple, huh?
Well...
okay, Tom.
Right, so we can say
we did it, okay?
Okay. Sure.
Damn.
I was just going
to watch the ballgame.
Yeah, I know, sorry
to put you out and all.
That game was
just getting started
when I stopped by
the hospital earlier--
What you doing
at the hospital, Tom?
Routine stuff.
You know...
I don't think I'm gonna go down
to the station there, Tom.
- What's that?
- I think you know what I'm saying.
Otis, I know it's been
you shooting up
the walls at
the Stooky place.
- Why do you say that?
- People see you there.
I spend time at Everett's,
you know that.
He's got that
shooting range.
Listen, Otis, I know you
got dealt a bad hand
with that house and all,
but a lot of people got problems.
City guy lets me take
the shortcut through the property.
Yeah.
You know, Otis,
I was gonna let you off
shooting up that place
and all, but...
I want you to come down
to the station with me now.
That really
what it is, Tom?
What do you mean?
You come all the way
out here over that?
Yeah, they're mad as hell.
Look, I got Jack
stopping by.
You coming with me
or not?
Okay. I'm coming.
I don't want to slap
the cuffs on you,
just to take you down
and give you a $30 fine.
- Coat.
- Right.
Don't lie, Tom.
Give me my liver.
What--?
Hey...
You'll be okay.
You fainted, sweetie.
You'll be okay, Miles.
Wha--
what are you?!
The devil?
Fuck you!
I'm sorry, Mrs. McLaren,
there was nothing
we could do.
So you get ready.
I'll be right back.
- Yeah, man?
- Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Sledding, sledding,
sledding.
Where even the worst thing
can be seen in another way.
Nobody believes
in spirits anymore.
Doesn't mean
the y're not there.
I'm getting you out of that ditch.
- You could have asked.
- No, no, no.
If I fall down
I'll try to get
back up
I'll catch you rain
In this paper cup
And you can
call my name
And I will come
I won't be far away
No matter what,
And you can hold out
Hold out, hold out
Hold out, hold out...
And if you lose
your way
I will steer
you straight
And if you lie awake
I'll sing you to sleep
And you can call my name
And I will come
I won't be far away
No matter what
And you can hold out
Hold out, hold out
Hold out, hold out...
If I fall down
I'll try to get
back up
I'll catch you rain
In this paper cup
And you can call
my name
And I will come
I won't be far away
No matter what
And you can hold out
Hold out, hold out
Hold out, hold out.