You can see your sister
in a moment.
Hello, I need to speak with Mr. Drake.
I'm Samantha Winston.
- Samantha Winston?
- Yes.
Here you go take a seat,
and I'll see if he has time.
Ms. Johansen, you can go in now.
Ms. Winston.
Ms. Winston!
- Yes.
- Mr Drake can see you now. Follow me.
I can poor believe my eyes.
Samantha Winston.
Hello.
Come in. Sit down.
Think that you remember me.
- How are you?
- I feel good.
- Where do you live?
- At a motel.
You know, I've tried to find you
over the years.
But you said you were moved
to Minnesota with your aunt.
Yes ...
What are you doing here?
- I need a job.
- A job?
- Harriet?
- Yes.
Want to ask a desk
to Ms. Winston outside my office.
She will be responsible for new customers.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Can you start tomorrow?
- Yes. Thank you.
Well, Harriet shows you
what to do.
There is a lot of paperwork.
You need not worry about other sides
of the business.
I hate to sound morbid,
but it goes well, we have 31 offices.
- It's great, Mr. Drake.
- My father was Mr. Drake.
I'm Lucas. Call me Lucas.
Mom, this is gonna Jack get paid.
Sheep.
Sheep!
Who are you?
What will you?
Is it ...
Is Samantha?
Samantha!
My God, Sammy, is that you?
I've been looking for you.
I ... no, sorry.
I ... I searched for you.
When Patricia died ...
- Why did not you tell me?
- You were eight ...
And lived far from here.
You stayed with a family ...
It was better than an alcoholic,
like me.
Come on, honey, let's go inside.
We can not talk here.
Please.
Come in, I have milk and cookies.
Here, sit down.
Look around the house,
if you like.
You can look at the pictures,
or go upstairs if you want.
It's beautiful photos.
Your mother was a beautiful woman.
I'm sorry, she passed away.
She loved you dearly.
How.
Just look.
Yes.
Here ...
Sit down, sit down and eat.
Mother would kill me if I did not
you food, she was so worried.
Here.
We have so much to talk about.
I wish you could be.
I do not drink anymore.
I try to do something good
for people.
I would like to make amends,
if you let me do it.
- How's your health that?
- I'm sober.
I have not drunk for years,
I will not even smell it.
What about you?
Where have you been all this time?
I stayed with some foster families,
for Aunt Patricia died.
They did not like me,
so it did not.
I ran away when I was 16,
and now I'm here.
- I'm tired.
- Let me show you your room.
Your room, my friend,
exactly as you left it.
- It's late, I have to go.
- Are you going already?
- I just wanted to see the house.
- How about a cup of tea?
Well.
- Do you like oranges?
- Not really.
Should I make some eggs for you?
I just bought a new frying pan.
Like them on TV.
I ...
I try to say that I will
be happy if you will.
Although it is only a few days.
I do not want any food.
I will be some day.
I have a clean pajamas for you.
My stuff is at the motel,
I do not need a pajama.
Are you telling me about mom tomorrow?
I do not remember much.
Your mother loved you dearly,
we're talking about it, I promise.
I put the key in the door
underneath.
Should I turn off the light in the hallway?
- No, that's fine, goodnight.
- Well, good night.
Jack?
Jack, is that you?
- Hello.
- What do you think about your first day?
- It's fine.
Well, you know, I have a guest house,
you can stay in.
- It's probably nicer to live in.
- I'm staying with Jack.
- Jack?
- He saw me looking in through the window.
- I will be there some day.
​​ - I see.
Do you want to come and eat with us tonight,
I can help you remember Jen.
- It will be great.
- Good. I have something for you.
Your first working mobile phone.
​​Use it wisely.
- I enjoyed meeting your kids.
- They liked you.
I know this because Tatiana never
invite anyone into his room.
- Where is your wife? She coming soon?
- No, we're divorced.
She lives in France with his new
billionaire husband.
The children are adopted. We love them
both like mad.
But ... they speak French now,
for they live in both places.
- Great.
- Yes, it is good for them.
Let me ask you something,
promise me not to get angry.
Do you really stay in your old house?
I do not think it's good for you.
It is fine.
It's alright.
You remember it enough not know you were little,
but I knew your mother well.
We were really close friends.
And I loved her.
She was an unhappy man.
But she lived for you.
She adored you.
I remember how she smiled,
when you were with us.
- I have never forgotten you.
- Is it true?
This I must say.
Can you hear Tatiana?
She is something of a musician.
Let me play something for you,
we wrote together.
We are still working on it.
She found the song,
the text is mine.
And I whistles.
It is a lullaby.
- Should I stop?
- Can I say goodnight to Tatiana?
Yes, do it, otherwise fall she never
asleep.
- I really enjoyed myself with you.
- I'm with.
Will you come and live here?
I have to go home.
I like your bear,
it's cute.
- Do you live here with your mother and father?
- I live with my father for the time.
- And your mother?
- No.
Where is your mother?
She is ...
She is in heaven.
- Do you miss her?
- Every day.
Have you invited Samantha to my
birthday?
It would be fine if you can
come.
- Sounds great, how old are you?
-14.
I have to go home, look now to get some rest.
- Come and see us soon again.
- I'll.
You're a good father.
- They are happy kids.
- I hope so.
What about you? Are you happy?
Hyggede you feel at least tonight?
I think he killed her.
Jack.
I think he killed my mother.
I came to find the truth,
I was looking on the net, there's nothing.
Honestly, I have sometimes been wanting
to beat Jack to death.
But I did not have any evidence.
So I let go of it.
- We must let go of it.
- Let go?
I can not even sleep.
And when I do,
I dream things.
I see her, and I'm trying
to reach for her.
- And she's gone.
​​- Breathe, you must breathe.
I'll get a little cold water to you.
Take it easy.
Hey, calm down.
Come on, I have some water for you.
Sit there and drink some water.
Here, drink a little.
How deep breath.
- Is that better?
- Yes, fine, thank you.
Sorry, I get a little nervous
sometimes.
- I do not know why.
- It does not matter.
Want to talk about your aunt Patricia?
I did not know her.
Yes. She was beautiful.
She had no other.
She also missed mother.
She was the only one who understood me.
It was a car accident. The police came
to pick me up at school.
They drove me to the hospital.
I was with her,
I begged her not to die.
But ... she did.
It felt like my life was taken
from me again.
But she hated my father.
Jack is much older than your mother.
He was never good enough for her.
But I have always seen him as a harmless,
it was just talk.
I have never believed that he was
involved in her so-called accident.
Accident?
It is said that she hit her head
against the bathtub.
Sam, honey.
Dr. Kaplan came and tried to revive
her.
No one knew the details.
But your aunt, Patricia,
was sure that it was your father.
- She was cremated soon after.
- Was she cremated?
Yes, people came and saw her,
and then she was cremated soon after.
- You knew that appear not.
- No, I did not.
Where can I find dr. Kaplan?
Last I heard something about him,
he was in a nursing home.
He suffers from dementia.
Sam ... Sam!
What if the doctor knows the truth?
What if he knows something was wrong?
He declared her dead in the bathtub.
He was court physician in this town for 30 years
and highly respected.
He was quite sure that your mother
had been dead long.
- And?
- And Jack was full all the time.
He was full that night.
So nobody knows what the hell happened.
- Did she in the bath?
- Yes.
No ... No, I can remember ...
Mother was lying in bed when she died.
- I was little, but I remember ...
- No, you're wrong.
You do not know anything about that night.
I mean it.
You do not.
Jack?
I thought I heard you coming.
I made dinner for you, I was hoping
that you came home.
I ate with my boss and his
family. Are the windows closed?
Now I see.
I did not know you had a job.
I work for Lucas Drake.
Lucas Drake?
Our competitor, our enemy.
Oh, dear, my goodness, the bandit.
He is an impostor, he asked even
up to the Senate.
You sold funeral firm for ten years
ago and I needed a job.
Yes of course.
Of course, honey.
What a beautiful pajamas.
I was just worried about you.
Because you were out so late.
I am tired, I want to sleep.
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Good night.
Sleep well.
I love you.
Hello?
- Can I help?
- Yes, we must talk with Mr. Drake.
- He knows we are coming.
- What is the name?
Good morning, I'm Benny Dawson,
this is my nephew Liam, and you are?
- I'm Samantha.
- Samantha. Nice to meet you.
- I'll give him the message that you are here.
- Do it. He's waiting for us.
Gentlemen. Good morning.
And good morning to you.
I do not run.
- I love lunch.
- You have an appointment in 20 minutes.
- It is doing you.
I am sorry if we ruined
planning.
- Maybe Samantha with?
- No, she is busy.
- Come on, I'm hungry.
- Well, next time.
Benny, come on.
I never lost faith that a
day would come and find me.
And you did.
What happened to the mother?
Do not you remember anything?
Only her beautiful soft skin
and her stuff.
Now that I'm here,
I feel sometimes her scent.
That's all.
How did she die?
The doctor said the mother had stomach cramps
and high fever.
It ... It was like an abortion.
- Was the mother pregnant?
- Yes, she was.
- How far along was she?
- I do not know.
How can you avoid knowing it?
I was different then.
You can ask me anything,
what you want about your mother.
But I beg you, do not talk with others
about it.
There were some bad complications
with pregnancy.
I was too drunk to help.
You destroy this family!
Was it dr. Kaplan, who told you
about complications?
I do not feel so good,
I must to bed.
Of course not.
Mr Drake is not here today.
I came to talk to you.
- Me?
- Yes, you will eat an early dinner?
It is just down the street.
- I'm sorry, what was your name again?
- Liam Dawson.
Well then ...
Yes, Mr. Dawson, let me take my coat.
They serve good Italian food
of Irishmen to be.
Tell me why you're such
a depressing place.
- I have a job.
- A task?
My mother was Jennifer Winston.
She died here 14 years ago.
- I want to know how.
- It sounds pretty heavy.
- Have you found anything yet, some clues?
- No, not really.
- Have you met my mother?
- No, I did not live here then.
- Everyone has their perception of it.
- I lived out west.
Salute. On your task.
If you need help
with no matter what, so to.
- I mean, I know people.
- Do you know people?
- What do you mean? What are you doing?
- What would you have done?
I joke, I am a lawyer. I make
paperwork and take phones.
I may need your help,
if you can keep a secret.
Just say, I will be happy.
- Why would you help me?
- Because I like you.
Are you at home, Sammy?
I come down.
- How did it in the church tonight?
- It was fine, really fine.
I wish you came by one day.
- Maybe you'd feel better.
- I'm fine.
I would just like to have you take with.
So we can spend some quality time
together.
And talk after all these years.
- I'm tired, I go to bed.
- I'm too tired.
Good night.
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me, Jen.
- Forgive me!
- What does he do?
My Goodness!
- Who are you?
- I know you, you must travel from here.
They kill you, fugitive!
My tax.
Thank you, Mr. Lopez. Goodbye.
It's a shame. Mayor Lopez
made the city what it is today.
- How does Lucas all this sorrow?
- He is incredible.
I have worked here for over 20 years.
He's a hero.
He has always been a good boy.
Did you know my mother?
Yes, your mother was wonderful.
- How did you know her?
- She came here very often.
And sometimes we ate lunch together
and chatted.
- You never mentioned.
- I did not think it was necessary.
- Did you not think it was necessary?
- Your mother had major issues.
The parents were dead, her sister lived
far away, his brother could not help.
Brother?
My mother had no brother.
- Yes, Thomas was her younger brother.
- Thomas?
- Where is he now?
- In a nursing home somewhere.
He did not come to your mother's funeral,
my friend.
He had mental problems.
She visited him almost every day.
- What do you know about the day she died?
- It's a long time ago.
I remember, she called it.
She sounded upset.
She did not feel well and wanted
to Lucas passed.
I said that I would say ...
Sometimes it happens that bad things
to good people.
Ladies ... Am I interrupting?
I was just getting ready
for the meeting.
- Is everything all right, Sam?
- I have the papers on your desk ...
That's fine, just go, Harriet,
we talk later.
She has not been herself in the
last thing she is old and we have you.
- She's afraid of losing his job.
- I'm not Harriet's job.
I do not even know if I will.
Have you spoken with Mr. Lopez about the flowers?
Why have you never mentioned that
I have an uncle?
I did not know if he was your mother's
brother.
Your mother used to take stragglers,
she had a warm heart.
- Forget it.
- Forget it?
Honestly so broke your mother is not
to talk about him.
She had you and your father to make sure.
It was plenty.
Yes, but I asked you to be honest.
Yes ...
- I heard that you ate with Liam Dawson.
- Yes, he is nice.
No, no, you must not have anything with them
to do, it is not good for you.
- Why?
- None of them.
- It was Liam, not his uncle.
- Trust me.
No, I do not need.
You forgot to say that my mother had
a brother.
And now you want to decide who I should
eat with?
- My little girl ...
- I made soup.
- You're always tired.
- Come on, baby, we go.
- No, Jen! I ask you, sorry.
- Stop now.
Well, listen here.
You're upset.
Sorry, I did not mention Thomas.
I did not believe ...
I would not want you to ...
Let's start over.
I promise to be honest.
Can you forgive me?
If we start now?
Where is Thomas?
And he's really my uncle?
I do not know, let's go for a walk.
Come on, it will do you good.
- You freeze to.
- No, I'm fine.
I know you are an adult and such,
but it makes no sense to freeze.
First of all ... Thomas.
I really think that he is dead.
Approximately one week after your mother passed except
- I heard that he took his own life.
He could not see any sense
to continue.
He held in a way just up
to exist.
My Goodness.
It's okay, I miss her too.
Yes, we miss her all along.
We all do together.
Thank you for telling me about Thomas.
But ... Liam is very nice to me.
Liam is cute, and I'm sure
that he is completely fine.
He Uncle Benny is my
partner.
His services have always a price.
And I will not see you in the end.
Alright?
- It's getting late.
- Wait. you eat with us?
I can not,
I have something I need.
- Do you need me tomorrow?
- It's Saturday. No, mom you well.
- I want to eat another day.
​​ - You are always welcome.
Feel better now?
Smut home with you.
Mother ...
I thought I could figure it out
here.
I really did.
I need answers.
Here is nothing.
I am coming.
Hello?
Liam?
- How did you get in?
- The door was open.
Thanks, I did not wait for anyone.
- Will you sit down? A cup of coffee?
- Sure.
- Milk and sugar?
- Black, thanks.
Here you go.
I look like I do not know what,
let me just fix me a little.
Sam, I like you.
Maybe too much.
How can you like someone too much?
I have big plans and have always believed
that a relationship would come across.
I also have big plans.
What are they?
We're together.
Together? I know you bad enough.
I only know that you and Benny Lucas'
business partners.
What are all the questions about?
What are you doing for them?
My father died when I was nine.
He left almost nothing to me
and my mother.
My mother had to clean for people
to get it to stick together.
Uncle Benny was father's youngest brother,
he paid the funeral.
He kept calling
and offer financial help.
Mother was saying no. I worked
hard to pay for college.
When I got my exam,
stood Uncle Benny there.
He offered to pay
for legal training, I said yes.
He continued to send money
to my mother, she lives in Manhattan now.
I would not have anything
if it was not for him.
I am sure that you have done much
more for your mom than Benny.
- You are a good guy.
- Maybe.
Has your uncle ever said anything
about my mother?
What? No.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Oh no, my father comes.
Hurry.
Go.
Oh, hello.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I was asleep.
- Has anyone been here?
- No.
I'm tired, I go to bed.
Are you feeling well?
Yes, the door was jammed.
I'm sorry I woke you.
I have not slept in the past.
Why have you not been able to sleep?
I do not know this place, this town.
I constantly think about Mom.
I think about her all the time.
She was a wonderful woman.
This is something else,
I can see her.
I dream about her,
but the dreams are nightmares.
You should not have nightmares.
It is I who should have nightmares.
Not you, you should not have bad
memories at all about your mother.
I do not know if it's memories
or fantasier-
- But they all end up in the same
manner.
Mother is always ...
You can tell me.
Mom is always on you.
I even have a nightmare about the day,
she died.
The doctor was there.
He said she was dead.
She was just dead.
I could not save your mother.
I lost you once,
I will not lose you again.
Before I became an alcoholic, I was a
successful man.
I bought wedding ring here
to your mother. I ventet-
- And hoped that you would find me,
so I could give it to you.
Honey, I was lost.
Just like you.
But I found the Lord.
I wish it was that easy.
That some beans could handle it.
Is it really the best thing
you can do?
Everyone must find their own way.
You will find your.
Honey, I love you.
Good night.
Hello? Hello, Liam.
No, I can not,
I'm going to church with my father.
I have to work tomorrow.
I have to run, bye.
- Can I help you?
- I have to visit Thomas Burton.
I am his niece.
Hello, I'm dr. Rockwell.
Your uncle is my patient.
He's not well enough to get a visit.
I just want to see him briefly.
He's out on the terrace.
How are you today, Thomas?
You have a guest.
Your niece, Samantha Winston,
have come to visit you.
Hello.
Jen!
Jen! Oh God ...
Jen.
I'm Samantha, Jennifer's daughter.
Oh, sweetheart.
Little girl.
I must know what happened to the mother.
Do you know how she died?
They killed her.
Who?
The dræbte-
- My sweet-
- Sister.
And you know what?
They kill you.
They do.
They will cut you off.
- Who wants to kill me?
- Calm down, Thomas.
He does not feel well.
You can visit him a second time.
- I come back, I promise.
- No! Listen to me!
Listen to me, I beg you.
- Thomas.
- Do not trust anyone.
Listen to me, especially not Lucas.
Do you understand me?
- Ms. Winston ...
- I'm coming back.
I come again, I promise.
No, come on, sit down.
I hate to sound like a father,
but are you sure you're okay?
- I do not know.
- What actually happens?
I told Jack about my dreams,
and I was worried about them.
- And?
- Ha told me to go to church.
I do not think helps dreams
is getting worse, I can not even sleep.
It is time that you talk
with a doctor.
Maybe, but how to be a doctor could
help me?
- I do not think anything helps.
- I know exactly who to talk to.
- I have a deal for you on Monday.
​​ - What kind of doctor?
A psychiatrist.
What?
You think I'm crazy?
- Wait!
- No, let me be. Liam believe me.
Liam can not help you.
Come here.
Sit on the couch, listen to me.
You are safe here, I'm on your side.
We'll find out here.
You can relax,
remember that you are comfortable here.
I'm on your side.
I am your friend.
I'll be here shortly.
Breathe deep, it'll go all
together.
I'm right here.
Well.
Lovely cold.
Nothing is happening.
Well.
Sync and relax.
You are quite excited.
You can relax a little.
Lie here a moment.
How, my friend.
Here, kick off your shoes.
How.
Well.
Relax completely,
you must not think of anything.
You look beautiful.
You look like your mother on a bullet.
You look like her completely.
Relax.
I love you so much, Jen.
I love you so much.
Jen, I have always loved you.
I am not my mother.
Sorry, I'm sorry,
I know.
Rest now just,
I have to go for a moment.
I go, you just stay here
and relax, you are in security here.
I'll be back.
- Hello.
- What do you do?
- You know why I'm here.
- No, I do not.
- Why she works for you?
- She needed a job.
Do you think it is wise to have her
here?
It is impressive Lucas.
You get all the jewels.
Last year it was a movie star.
This year it is our dear mayor
Maria Lopez.
You are a kind of king of the dead.
You ...
You make her beautiful for the big day?
You should never have lost the election.
It was a golden opportunity. I bet
great on your seat in the Senate.
You cost me a lot of money.
I know you do not hear so well.
So I ask again.
- Why she works for you?
- I'll keep an eye on her.
You learn it apparently never.
What is it with you and the family?
You knew this was risky.
If she wants answers,
I should maybe even give her them.
No, you stay away from her.
You've always got it with me
and Jennifer.
Never forget who made you
to the king.
Why do you live in a palace, and why
your innocent children go to private school.
- I never asked.
- Yes, you have.
Had you done that you should,
everything had been in order.
But you should definitely fall in love
in your little whore.
She was no whore.
It reiterates you never more.
You are emotional, how often should I
say that it is not personal.
It's just business.
- What can I do for you?
- Drill dr. Kaplan here?
- Yes, he does.
- I'm Samantha Winston.
- Can I talk to him for a moment?
- He has suffered a stroke.
- I ask ...
- He can not see anyone.
What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong?
- I'm bored, I came after some beers.
- How was your date?
- It was not much of a date.
We went here, ate, drank some wine.
- So it was weird.
- What do you mean?
We had to learn each other
to know.
But before I knew a word of it ...
- Everything was fine.
​​- It does not sound weird.
She asked if you have ever
mentioned her mother.
- She said what?
- Yes, I know.
And then she pushed me out
through the back door.
I called in the morning and ...
- She pretended she did not know me.
- Did you bring her mother up?
No, that was what made it
so weird.
- Do me a favor.
- All for you, Uncle Benny.
There's something you should know. Things that
never get outside these walls.
I never repeat anything you say.
The girl you see, the trouble.
- Samantha?
- I say this only once.
I can not express it differently.
She can destroy the entire city.
How could she do it?
Can you remember when you came to visit
after high school?
It is 13 to 14 years ago.
This started back then,
and now it's starting all over again.
- I do not understand.
- They cast a spell over the city.
Years ago asked Lucas up
to the Senate for my money.
He had a promising political career,
but then came the whore ...
But I fixed it,
because that's what I do.
- Fixed it?
- Yes, what is it you do not understand?
She poses a threat to all,
your nice home, your house home, everything.
- I do not understand.
- You do not understand it.
You just listen. And you need to find out
of everything, I mean everything, she has discovered.
Get it planted in your head,
and drink so out while you're at it.
My friend.
- My little treasure.
- What?
My little treasure, your little darling.
What?
- Good morning.
Want some eggs?
I have to run some errands.
And later in the day there are funerals.
All come well for prayers
for mayor Lopez.
I'll just have coffee.
The cookies look good.
You always have to be happy
for cookies with chocolate pieces.
And you have always been happy
for clamchowder.
I have to go,
but I will come back later.
Jack, the least I could do was,
to take care of the funeral. Lucas.
Mother?
- Not too close to the altar.
- Yes, there are two devotions to Mary Lopez.
Yes, we expect a large turnout.
You look good. Come on.
Too late. You should be happy,
you have a job here!
- Pick up the phone!
- You've been at it since Jennifer.
I saved you Jennifer,
I do not do it again with Samantha.
You do not take care of Samantha
and Thomas, your play is over soon.
Benny aligned second
Listen, I can not do this now.
No, you stay away from her.
I'll fix it here.
David, I need to visit Thomas Burton.
- Here is no Thomas.
- I was here after all yesterday.
- A doctor showed me over to him.
- I've never seen you before.
We have only 20 residents, I would know
what if one of them called Thomas.
I spoke to you yesterday.
Doctor, I was here yesterday.
I need to talk to my uncle
Thomas.
- We have no Thomas.
- He was here yesterday, I spoke with him.
- There are no Thomas.
- I saw him yesterday.
Are you feeling well?
- Please follow.
- What is this?
I saw him, he was here yesterday.
- The queue goes around the entire area.
- It was expected.
How beautiful that there are so many.
This is her cousins.
- May I offer my condolences.
- Thank you.
- Lucas had to go.
- Is something wrong?
He takes care of a personal matter,
we must ensure this.
Mr Benny, everything seems to be
in order.
You look nice, new suit,
and you lost you.
- No, I must talk to you alone.
​​- Liam is good enough.
I just explained that I had to
do things for you 14 years ago.
That I do not want to discuss now,
our girl needs help.
Precisely, I said no,
it would not work?
How subordinates you?
Should I tell him?
I had no choice, because she was
pregnant, and Lucas career was in danger.
- Did you kill her?
- Take and become adult.
Are you 11? Dr. Kaplan performed
a cesarean a little too early.
The cub is alive. He is yours.
- How old are you?
-14.
Jennifer did not do well, and your
dear Harriet rang, so I helped.
Shut up! Shut up!
I will not hear it here now!
Harriet, is Lucas who?
Well, ask him to come.
Benny.
Kaplan called it 'Placenta Abruptio'.
A fascinating process, they stand
placenta from the uterine wall.
The important thing is that everyone, including Jack,
thought that pregnancy killed her.
You have supplanted it here for 14 years, right?
But ... It tastes good!
It was a nice cremation until the
bitch, Patricia asked questions.
What are you talking about?
I did not help with anything, it was you!
I had stopped you if I could.
You may not dare to kill anyone,
but nothing to curb your career.
Well, listen to me. Make you the girl
something beating I'll kill you.
I do.
You can not hurt a fly.
There's something you must understand.
I did it for your sake
and the family.
I took care of Kaplan
and your mother.
They were a danger to the city.
It is not personally.
It's always, always about business.
- Jack!
- Stay there! I'll fix it.
Sam!
Jack!
Sheep! Sheep!
Sheep!
I told you she gave trouble.
Dad, where are you?
I can not believe Lucas.
I can not take care of the cops now,
I have to find the girl.
Think of all the possibilities
I have given him.
He screw up themselves every time.
This is not good.
She heard the whole conversation.
Is it her?
Why do not you phone?
Why can not I get hold of you,
Jack?
Dig a hole.
After everything I've done for you
and your family ...
You are a pathetic man.
Move, Liam.
- Please.
- Liam, move.
You killed my mother!
Liam ...
Liam!
Oh, Liam.
Do not, I beg you.
Sheep?
- I love you, Sam.
- Dad.
I love you so much.
It'll go all together.
- Where are you going?
- It'll go all together.
I beg you ...
- Where are you going?
- I love you.
- Sam!
- Dad.
The orders themselves.
- Dad!
- Sam, listen to me.
He's not there.
Jack has passed away.
Jack is dead.
He died long ago.
- He's not here.
- No, he's alive.
No, he died long ago.
- It was you who killed your father.
- Shut up! It was an accident.
It was an accident, do not listen to him.
You can not even take care of your wife
and child!
I would never make my family
something! Get out of my house!
Enough is enough, go away!
No, Daddy!
Sheep?
Samantha, you have been in hospital
for a long time.
I would see if you could clear up
themselves.
Sheep? Sheep?
It can, I promise you.
It'll go all together.
I will help you.
It's been more than seven hours,
and she has not said a word.
We must drive her back,
so that treatment can be resumed.
Do you understand me?
Yes. Yes I understand.
In memory of