*
Brooklyn: This is a story
about the guy I fell for.
But to really
understand why,
You have to know
a little bit about
the game he loves.
The game has been played
by native Americans
For centuries.
It requires speed
and agility,
Teamwork, strategy,
And a bit of violence.
You may know it
as lacrosse,
But native Americans
know it as baaga'adowe...
The little brother of war.
Their matches took days
And were played
over Miles of terrain.
The winners got land,
wives, and sometimes glory.
There's a lot
that's different
about the game now.
But the thing
a player needs most
hasn't changed at all.
And if you find
someone who has it,
I'd tell you
to never let go.
(Whistle blows,
crowd cheers)
(Overlapping shouts)
Get it over there!
Center it!
Swing it!
Watch his pass!
(Shouting continues)
(Whistle blows)
Who's Jimmy's back-up?
Hanson.
We're in trouble.
(Whistle blows)
(Sportscast playing
on radio)
Hey, coach says he's
having second thoughts.
*
You ready for this?
I was born ready,
bro.
Whoa.
A moment with
my player, ref?
Hansen's the backup,
and I don't want to
hear any arguments.
I thought I was getting
a second chance.
You're arguing.
There's a delay of game
penalty with your name on it
If I don't get
a resolution A.S.A.P.
I can win this.
What's it gonna be,
coach?
(Whistle blows)
We'll run a switchblade
first, coach says.
Yeah, sure.
I mean it, man...
Switchblade!
Trying to win the
game by yourself.
My play is called
"the iceman".
I'm not talking
about your play.
Do it... switchblade.
Bring us all in.
You got no time
for one shot,
And I know wherever
you're going.
15 seconds?
All I need is 10.
(Whistle blows)
All right, go! Go! Go!
Come on, Conor!
Switchblade!
Run switchblade!
Conor, pass! Sullivan,
that's not switchblade!
(Cheering)
Good job out there.
Hey, Riggins.
Hey, did that go in?
I didn't see.
Conor, man, let it go.
Come on, fighting
means suspension.
That was wonderful.
Yeah, nice, man.
You should call
your father.
The only time
he won't pick up
Is when he's
on patrol.
He's okay.
Dad calls that
"being in the shit".
Hey, Keegan!
Top-key mushrooms.
Maybe he didn't
pick up
Because his phone
is turned off.
Or maybe dad flew back
early from Iraq
To surprise his family.
Dad, you're home!
Ha ha ha!
You're looking
rather dashing,
colonel Sullivan.
As are you,
Mrs. Sullivan.
Perhaps I could escort you
home after this.
Perhaps you should.
Heh!
Aww.
Perhaps I could
escort you home
right now.
Easy, marine.
Get a room.
Ahh.
So, how come
you're home?
I'm wondering
the same thing.
Can't a guy just
slip away from the war
Without his family
thinking something's up?
No.
(Laughter)
I got some news.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
30 minutes, Conor.
Conor:
I can win this.
Dad: Other than the fact
that you let 14 get
inside your head,
I thought you were
ten tons of awesome.
Why are we
doing this, dad?
You know why.
We're gonna
move again.
Then they'll
call you back,
And it'll all
be for what?
Sorry, pal, that's
the military life.
Sometimes you gotta
just suck it up, son.
(Sighs)
Conor... It's
very important
That you tone your
attitude down here
on and off the field.
I had to pull some
strings to get you
in here.
I want you to promise me
that you'll show humility.
Conor, you listening
to me?
Not really, dad.
(Chuckles) Come on.
He's really cute.
Brooklyn: It's funny
what you notice
The first time
you see someone...
Confidence, a nice smile,
A little connection.
What you don't see...
What's impossible to know
at first glance...
Is everything else.
At least everything
that counts.
Hey, dad, how many
of those are yours?
That one.
And my name
is on that one.
And that was taken
right after the state
championship.
How many of those
did you win?
Four in a row.
Four?
Heh heh.
All right.
Hey, who's that
one guy you always...
Dave Milligan.
You're about
to meet him.
Straighten your tie.
He played on
one of the best
west coast teams ever.
The kid scored
70 goals last year.
Look, nobody
plays varsity
their first year.
I can't bench somebody
who's paid their dues.
It wouldn't be fair.
Since when are you
a stickler for propriety?
Why'd you
bring him here?
Because, despite our
considerable differences,
I know your reputation
as a coach,
And you turn out
a hell of a lacrosse player.
We play real lacrosse
here, not that west
coast field hockey.
Just play him,
see how he does.
I'm not asking
for favors.
I'm doing you
a favor just by
giving him a look,
And right now,
that's all I can
give you.
Fair enough.
(Indistinct chatter)
Can I help you?
Thanks,
but I'm pretty good
at dressing myself.
No, varsity only here.
Scrubs dress in there.
So, you're what passes
as varsity around here?
Yeah.
Heh. Awesome.
Yo, skip,
toss me a ball.
Watch the ball.
Sticks up, sticks up.
Watch that throw.
Watch the ball!
Let's go!
Great, guys.
Keep the pace up.
Stay focused.
Really well done.
Good, keep
the ball moving.
Oh, you're late,
west coast.
It's 4:00.
If you're not early,
you're late.
You owe me a lap.
Let's go,
cradle it out.
Sticks up. Keep your
feet moving.
Nice. Nicely done.
Watch the ball.
Get the energy up.
Sticks up.
You okay?
Cradle it out.
Sticks up.
Sticks up! Sticks up!
(Overlapping shouts)
Come on,
you can take him!
(Grunting)
(Laughs)
You think you can
do better, Sullivan?
Only one way
to find out.
Switch up your Jersey
to white.
Coach,
give me a whistle.
You got it, coach.
(Blows whistle)
Braveheart, give me
Bryant! Let's go
(Overlapping shouts)
Bryant, Sullivan,
let's go!
Anytime today, Sullivan!
Here we go!
Joe's gonna crush you.
One-on-one,
go on my whistle.
First one to score wins.
It's that simple. Got it?
Down. Keep it clean.
Good luck, brother.
I'm not your brother.
Oh, we're all brothers
in lacrosse, west coast.
(Whistle blows)
Come on!
Come on, west coast!
(Grunting)
No, no, no, no!
Hey!
Yeah!
(Cheering)
You should've
shot when you
had the chance.
Yeah, I guess so.
Welcome to Briarfield,
Sullivan.
Conor.
Hey, come on, wake up.
Dad? Is the house
on fire?
No, it's morning.
No, it isn't.
It's close enough.
Let's go.
(Laughing and grunting)
Not bad, not bad.
(Cell phone rings)
Hang on a sec.
I gotta take this call.
Sullivan.
Morning, general.
Yes, sir.
Right. Okay.
Thank you, sir.
What was that about?
Nothing.
Just some advisory work
they want me to do.
That it?
Yeah, that's it.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go.
Okay.
Keep your arms
extended, this side.
Let's see
what you got. Go.
(Grunting)
Oh, nice, nice.
Except you gotta
learn how to shoot.
Who's gonna pick up
a guy who shoots
like a drunk woman?
Huh? Come on.
*
Brooklyn:
There are a bunch of ways
to find out about someone.
You can watch them
around other people,
Find out what
their interests are,
How they react
to new circumstances.
Sometimes, if you
really want to know,
It's easiest to just
talk to them yourself.
Hey.
Hey yourself,
newbie.
Name's Conor Sullivan.
Brooklyn...
Milligan.
Ahem.
(Mutters)
Coach's daughter. Ahem.
(Laughs)
So, my dad says
you come out here
To practice
every day at 5 A.M.
Oh, does he?
He does.
Does that make you wonder
how your dad knows that?
Because it sure
makes me wonder.
(Laughs)
Hey, Joe, think fast!
Ha ha! Hey, babe.
Hey.
Hey, this is
my girlfriend Charlie.
Hey.
Um...
We should probably
get back to practice.
Yeah.
See you later.
Bye.
Nothing's hotter than
chicks with sticks.
Nothing.
Just doesn't sound right.
I didn't mean it
that way.
(Overlapping shouts)
Gotta watch the pick!
Ohh.
(Grunts)
This kid can play.
He most definitely
can play.
So, what do you think?
You want to move him up?
We'll see where he is
in a week.
Hey.
Nice practice.
Thanks.
You're not
taking my spot.
Do you play
right-side attack?
Damn straight.
Then I'm definitely
taking your spot.
Let it go.
(Chuckles) Ahh.
(Knock on door)
You wanted to see me?
Yeah, take a seat.
So, uh, you've been
practicing with us...
For, what,
about a week now?
What do you think?
Uh...
Well, I think you've
got a good system
going on...
Thanks, kid,
but I don't need you
to kiss my butt.
I'm asking if you can
play with them.
Not a one-man dance
out there,
But actually working
with them as a unit.
I thought you weren't
gonna play me.
Well, that may change.
May?
May.
You're not the God's gift
you think you are,
But you're better
than I expected.
Yes... I can play
with them.
Good. You'll suit up
on Friday.
It's our last game
before the playoffs.
Impress me.
(Overlapping shouts)
Why isn't he
playing Conor?
Relax, he knows
what he's doing.
I don't think Dave's
gonna give him a fair shot.
You know
us Sullivans, huh?
We always a way
to get it done.
(Laughs)
Move your feet!
Let's have some
pressure, defense!
All right, Dupree out!
Sullivan!
Eh-eh.
Remember what
I told you?
You got it?
Got it, coach.
Dad: Okay,
here we go.
It's about time.
He just wanted to show
Conor who's boss.
You think that taught
Conor anything?
Heh! Doubt it.
(Shouting)
Let's go, baby!
Nice goin'!
You gotta get your body
between the ball
and the goal, son.
What is this,
girls' volleyball?
(Cell phone ringing)
Good scrimmage!
First team, come off!
I'll be right back.
Dave: Nice job,
first team, good work.
Good work today. Nice.
Good effort.
Let's go, second team!
Let's see some pressure,
let's hear some talk!
That's what I'm talk...
come on, let's hear
some talk!
(Shouting)
Come on, let's go!
Keep it moving!
Keep that ball high!
(Shouting continues)
(Whistle blows)
End of the day.
Hit the showers.
Good work today.
Good work today,
everybody.
You didn't
have to wait.
Well, I think
we should talk.
All right.
So, who was that
on the phone?
They need me
back in Iraq.
Well,
mom needs you here.
So does Keegan.
Under six months.
That's it.
That's just
another surge.
We could've just
stayed in California.
At least then
I'd have some friends
to hang out with...
I know it wasn't
part of the plan.
Then this is where
you need to be.
This is your future.
Six months.
Come on.
*
Conor?
I've got something
for you.
What is it?
A box of roses.
Just open it.
That's what you said
they called you, right?
Captain America?
Hope you score
a lot of goals
with that, son.
But it's important
how you score.
Never put yourself
above the game.
Now, give your
old man a hug.
Come on.
I'll have my
right hand shot down
when you get back.
Can't wait.
Keep your head down
over there.
You just keep your
head up over here.
(Alarm ringing)
*
He's here.
You're late,
west coast.
Late to my own practice
that you're intruding on.
Intruding, huh?
We could leave.
You can stay.
My work here is done.
At least try
to play hard-to-get.
Shut up.
You ready?
Let's do it.
(Grunting)
You okay?
Yeah. Fine.
I can't shoot
with this thing.
Shooting strings
are a mess.
Ahh.
Much better.
Maybe if you didn't
shoot so hard.
I heard
about your dad.
Yeah?
How long
is he gone for?
Six months.
Hmm.
(Car horn honks)
(Sighs)
Same time tomorrow?
Well, I'd hate
to intrude.
(Chuckles)
Uhh!
Morning.
(Sighs)
It's fine.
When your daughter
leaves the house
before dawn,
It's not spying,
it's parenting.
(Scoffs)
I'm not sure
it's a good idea
To hang around
that Sullivan kid,
though.
Dad, I barely
even know him.
Right.
Everybody gather up!
Whole team, gather!
Let's go!
Everyone, bring it in!
I've just been informed
That Briarfield has been
selected as the location
For the first ever east-west
championship game.
Gentlemen,
it is my intention
That we're not only
hosting that game,
But we're playing in it.
Hands in, men.
Warriors on three.
(Cheering)
One, two, three.
All: Warriors!
Let's go out
and show 'em who we are!
Come on!
(Overlapping shouts)
(Whistle blows)
Sullivan, get in there
for Dupree.
Uhh!
(Overlapping shouts)
Bounce back up.
Let's go.
(Whistle blows)
We got number 9...
unsportsmanlike
conduct.
Two minutes.
That was a stupid play.
He pushed me,
I pushed back.
Come on Briarfield!
Man down!
Let's go!
(Indistinct shouts)
Nice game, Conor.
Except for the penalty.
Dad would've been proud.
Thanks, mom.
There's some mail
for you.
(Laughs)
What is it?
Dad signed me up
for some old-school
lacrosse camp.
Looks good,
doesn't it?
Run by native American
players.
Your dad used to
love it up there.
"Ha ha, dad.
Indian lacrosse camp.
Hooray east coast."
Your dad knows
how to text?
Uh, yeah.
He said he made
his private show him.
(Coughs)
* then we went up
* we are much older
* you wait like an angel
* and I pine
like a soldier *
* but I remember love
* love don't remember me
* it's been a long
* long time
* since I've been on
* your mind
* but I cannot
* decline
* anything for you
* I'll drink the whiskey
* you'll drink
gin and tonic *
* you got
much more strong *
* I got more neurotic
* but I remember love
* but love
don't remember me *
* now that I've been
replaced *
* I have the guts
to face *
(Lyrics indistinct)
Mother: Thank you
for coming.
Is it cold in here?
(Indistinct chatter)
Hey. With all
due respect, son,
I think your mom
needs you here.
I can't stay.
I just can't.
A warrior doesn't
run from pain.
Do the right thing
by your family
And stick around.
I'm sorry,
but I just really need
to get out of here.
(Indistinct chatter)
Hey, you mind
if I, um...
I'm...
I'm so...
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
I can't go back
in there right now.
Let's...
Let's get out of here.
Okay?
I'll drive.
Yeah.
(Grunting)
Arms extended.
Are you better?
A little.
As good as I can be.
Hey, Brookie.
Come on,
we gotta go.
(Sighs)
See you tomorrow?
You know the time.
I thought I asked you
to stay away from him.
What is your problem?
He just buried
his dad.
He's not real stable
right now.
I just don't want
to see you get hurt.
*
Uhh!
What was that?
What?
(Overlapping shouts)
Hey! Hey!
Settle down!
Dupree, you're done.
Back off, back off.
Sullivan, get out.
Go, go.
Get out of here.
Let's go, everybody
back to work.
Come on. Get back
to your stations.
Let's go.
Mom: Is this
about what happened?
Dave: Believe me,
it's not about that.
I have
a responsibility to...
Hello, Conor.
Coach.
I was just talking
with your mother
About whether
to let you play again.
It's been a month
since...
I thought you'd be
a little less
hotheaded by now,
But after today, I...
I need this.
Otherwise, I can't play
at the naval academy.
I know. But I need you
to be a player,
not a liability.
I'm trying to get
this team
In the national
championship game.
We could use you.
But if you fight again,
That's it...
You are off my team.
So, what you're
saying is,
I have to let them
beat on me
and just take it?
If you want to come back
as a player, you're welcome.
Otherwise,
don't come back at all.
But what you're doing
out there now
Is not lacrosse.
Brooklyn: You think
you know someone.
You have
a nice connection.
But before they can
let you in,
They've got to
let themselves in.
They have to learn
their own heart.
Come on,
you're gonna be late.
you said yourself
you needed to play.
Don't waste
this opportunity.
I'm not going.
You've been given
a second chance.
Just leave me alone.
Honey, I know
this is hard for you.
Do you?!
Come on.
You need to
suck it up, mom.
That's what this is?
You're sucking it up?
Since you've got
it all figured out,
Why don't you
step up and be a man?
Get yourself
to school on time.
Maybe you can spend
a little time
with Keegan.
Because you know what?
He's not sucking it up.
He's gotta learn.
Hey.
Where were you
this morning?
I was up late.
Okay.
I thought you wanted
to be the best.
What's the point?
You know your dad's
never liked me.
Doesn't even want you
around me.
Oh, come on.
We both know
My dad cares more
about winning the
championship game.
But it isn't enough
to be good, Conor.
Maybe if you were
more of a team player,
He would find a way
to use you.
Wow. So, you're
taking his side now?
Are you serious
right now?
I have been on your
side since day one.
Frankly,
I don't know what
your side is anymore.
(Whistle blows)
Sullivan, Douglas
is banged up.
Get in there.
Left side attack. Yes.
All right,
Briarfield, let's go!
Come on!
Hey, Sullivan!
How you liking
that left side?
(Whistle blows)
(Overlapping shouts)
Here, here, here!
Come on!
(Shouting continues)
Ref, come on!
(Cheering)
Conor, no!
(Whistle blows)
You're done.
Get out of my sight.
You all right?
(Indistinct chatter)
*
(Yells)
What is wrong with you?
Hey! Stop right there!
(Sighs) Heck of a way
to start spring break.
Any idea who
might've done this?
Um, it all happened
so fast.
I didn't...
* in the light of the sun
* is there anyone?
* oh, it has begun
* oh, dear,
you look so lost... *
No.
* your eyes are red,
your tears are shed *
* this world you must
have crossed, you said *
* you don't know me
* and you don't even care
* oh, yeah
* you said
* you don't know me
* and you don't
wear my chains *
* oh, yeah
Conor.
I'm going to bed.
You're not going
anywhere, Conor Sullivan.
* essential, yet appealed
* you carry
all your thoughts *
* across an open field
* where flowers gaze at you
* they're not the only ones
* who cry when they see you,
you said *
* you don't know me
* and you don't even care
* no, no, no,
Sullivan!
He doesn't deserve
that name.
The kid has no idea.
You wear glasses?
No.
Any prescription
medication
I need to know of?
What? No.
Do you have
a cell phone?
No.
From this point on,
you do not speak
unless spoken to.
Am I clear?
You're coming with me.
Like hell I am.
Fine. Spend another
night in jail.
Okay, okay.
So, where are we going?
The six nations
work camp.
It's where we send
all the reservation kids
Who can't get
their life together...
Kids like you.
Work camp?
Like picking up
litter and shit?
Get out.
(Both speak
native language)
Court papers?
Didn't get that far.
Weapons?
Drugs?
Pornography?
What? No.
I'm gonna frisk you
just the same.
And this will turn
into a court case
if you're lying.
Hands on the counter.
Spread your feet.
And your cheeks.
Sit.
I'll grab
your counselor.
I am
his counselor.
Yeah?
Okay.
Missionary Ridge.
Think you can find
your way back in the dark?
Shitfaced and blind.
(Both speak
native language)
(Thunder)
Not that it matters,
But would you mind
explaining to me
this whole thing?
Do not speak
unless spoken to.
Well,
where are we going?
What are we
supposed to eat?
You gotta be
kidding me.
(Thunder)
Jeez!
You need to build
a shelter
If you plan on
getting some sleep.
It's impossible.
(Thunder)
Duke! Duke!
Duke!
* If heaven would
fall down from the sky *
* and I'd walk right in
* I wouldn't know
where to begin, no *
(Lyrics indistinct)
* what did I ever do
* to deserve
to be kicked out? *
* oh, oh
* can you remind me?
* or can we write
the songs... *
Who are you texting?
Joe?
Yeah.
Any news
from your felon?
I can't stop
thinking about him.
But how do you
know if someone's
right for you?
Obviously, I can't
ask my dad about Conor,
And my mom's been gone
for so long.
I just don't know.
I guess you just have
to trust yourself,
And if he's right
for you, you'll know it.
Mm-hmm.
(Coughs)
Hey, home slice.
How come you slept
out in the rain
last night?
I got a great
shelter here.
Why didn't you
come get me?
Is it noon yet?
I don't know.
Aren't you an Indian?
Can't you look up
at the sun or something?
Well, it's gotta be
noon somewhere.
Well, you'd better
get started.
Started on what?
Knocking it down.
Why would I want
to knock down
A perfectly good shed?
Don't you live
in this place?
I've got my reasons.
I don't even know how
to use one of those.
This is gonna be
harder than I thought.
Which is
your chicken-choker?
My what?
Answer the question.
Are you really
asking me that?
You could've
killed me, man!
Lefty. Interesting.
One hand on the bottom,
one on the top.
Swing over
your shoulder,
extend your arms.
You get a lot more
power that way.
This place is
a freakin' mansion.
How am I supposed
to knock it all down?
Board by board.
Board by
ever-loving board.
Am ambidextrous.
*
* you feel like a candle
* in a hurricane
* just like a picture...
Be sure to extend
your arm.
* alone and helpless
* like you've lost
your fight *
* but you'll be all right
* you'll be all right
* 'cause when push
comes to shove *
* you taste what
you're made of *
* you might bend
till you break *
* 'cause it's all
you can take *
* on your knees,
you look up *
* decide you've
had enough *
* you get mad,
you get strong *
* wipe your hands,
shake it off *
* then you stand
* whoo, ooh
* 'cause when push
comes to shove *
* you taste what
you're made of *
* you might bend
till you break *
* 'cause it's all
you can take *
* on your knees,
you look up *
* decide you've
had enough... *
(Man screaming)
Get working.
I have blisters.
(Laughs)
There's gotta be
a purpose.
Crazy Indians got me
knocking down
a stupid shed
'cause it represents me
breaking myself down.
Yeah.
So stupid.
Why am I doing this?
You tell me.
You're the one
who screwed up.
When do I get
to go home?
When you learn
your lesson.
When's that
gonna be?
When I'm finished
knocking down your
palace here?
Kid, there's dozens of
buildings just like this
Waiting for you
and that sledgehammer.
What, Sully's
little boy
Want to come out here
and take a swing?
Temper is good.
It's how you use it
that matters.
When you fight,
you quit. Right?
In life, in lacrosse...
You know you failed.
You know you're not
gonna win.
So, you throw a punch.
And you quit.
Get back to work,
you little jerk-off.
(Squawking)
Is it 12:00 yet?
Crazy Indian.
Where's your sundial?
Save it.
You work,
I'll talk.
You know,
I'm a full-blooded
Iroquois.
This may sound
antiquated to you,
But the Iroquois
banded with five
other tribes
To form
the six nations...
A participatory
democracy
That lasts
to this day.
I have no idea what
any of that means.
A participatory
democracy
Means that my people
got the vote
100 years before
Thomas Jefferson
Decided all men
were created equal.
So?
So, you couldn't be
more authentically
And originally American
than that.
So, the next time
you call me
a crazy Indian,
I will personally
tattoo those words
to your forehead.
Do I have to
remind you again?
Do not speak unless
you're spoken to!
I was talking
to myself.
What?
I'm pretty sure
this is illegal.
So is destroying
a trophy case.
Now, work!
(Man shouting
in the distance)
(Shouting continues)
(Shouting)
Heh.
Permission to speak.
Define "warrior".
Someone who spills blood
on the field of battle.
What about...
I know what
you're gonna say.
But don't waste
your breath asking.
Turf burns do not now
and never will count
As spilling blood.
I'm sure your dad
taught you all this.
My dad was never
really around
to teach me much.
Well, that's
too bad for you.
'Cause my colonel
was there for me
in a big way.
Let me tell you
a story.
I left the F.O.B.
In a re-supply convoy
To the other side
of Fallujah.
You know what
we were carrying?
Ammo?
Energy drinks.
Gatorade and red bull.
The bare necessities,
right?
Then, all of a sudden,
we come to a traffic jam.
Before I know it,
I'm hit.
And the corpsman
takes one in the head
As he runs to save me.
And, I mean...
We can't move.
All of a sudden,
we're surrounded.
End of story.
Then your dad just
comes out of nowhere,
Like the cavalry.
You know what
he says to me?
"I'll never drink
another Gatorade
As long as I live."
And somehow he gets
the medevac.
He gets me out.
He gets everybody out.
I never knew a warrior
better than him.
Duke: Well,
you're up early.
Can't sleep.
I could swear
I'm hearing things.
Well, all right.
Let's go find them.
Find what?
The noises.
(Men shouting and whooping)
Conor: So, that's
what I've been hearing?
(Shouting)
Some of those guys
are the counselors
From the six nations
lacrosse camp
Your dad signed
you up for.
They come down here
To play the counselors
from the work camp.
Who are
the other players?
It's just them.
It's real lacrosse.
And, brother,
let me tell you... real.
Your dad played here.
He was a counselor?
Just a camper.
Hand-picked...
For his love of
the game was pure.
(Overlapping shouts)
You know,
Milligan played at
this game, too.
You didn't know that,
did you?
He and your dad
played together at Navy
after that.
They were cool until
a woman came between them.
Milligan fell hard
for her.
Your dad just
stole her away.
My mom?
My dad did that?
To a friend?
You know, every great man
has a weakness,
And Sully's...
It was Claire.
I'm giving up
lacrosse.
Why? Just because
your old man
wasn't a Saint?
You don't get it.
Every time
I pick up a stick,
Every time I hear
the word "lacrosse",
I think of my dad.
You know, if I could
say something...
Let him run
in your veins.
Let him
make you better.
He was proud of you.
Don't forget that.
Let's go.
(Shouts and laughter)
West coast.
Duke,
how you doing, sir?
What are you
doing here?
Spring break.
This is where
I learned to play.
Briarfield made
the championship.
Good for you guys.
Thanks.
Come on,
be on my team.
Let's go.
Here we go! Go!
(Cheering)
All right, guys,
I found a couple more.
This game's faster.
Looks the same
to me.
Heh. Ready?
Game on!
Trash talk out here...
You lose a few teeth.
(Overlapping shouts)
Ha ha ha!
You see that?
Were you watching
the roll dodge
Or were you watching
Joe getting burned?
I was watching Joe
get schooled.
Iron sharpens iron.
All right?
Joe's getting awfully
sharp today.
Two points down!
(Shouting continues)
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
Ha ha ha!
Ha!
Yeah!
(Shouting continues)
What the hell, man?
Joe! Joe! Joe!
Come on, man!
(Shouting continues)
Here we go, here we go.
Really?!
(Grunting)
Get off me!
Nighty night.
Let's go!
Play on. Here we go.
It's more than
a game, west coast.
When are you
gonna learn that?
Brooklyn: It's hard to say
if warriors are born
Or if they're made
by circumstances.
I know everyone faces
hardship in life.
It just seems like
some people
Are actually
made stronger by it.
Brooklyn:
I thought you wanted
to be the best.
Dad: Sometimes in life,
you just gotta
suck it up, son.
What you're doing
out there now
is not lacrosse.
When I was your age,
I could go for hours.
Conor:
Think I don't do that?
I never see it.
Brooklyn: What is
wrong with you?!
Mom: Why don't you
step up and be a man?
Hey.
This place is
starting to bore me.
Let's head back.
So, I still
don't get it.
Was this supposed
to be a metaphor?
Was I knocking down
the walls of my anger?
I mean, what was I
doing up there?
You think too much.
It's a simple
question.
How do you feel
right now?
Pissed that you
kicked my butt.
Other than that.
Honestly?
Confused.
It's about time.
What?
I spent a week...
Knocking down
a house...
So I could feel
confused?
You spent a week
knocking down a house
So you could feel
at all.
Look, you're
on your own now.
I'm not gonna be
able to be there
To rein in
that temper
Or whisper words
of sweet wisdom
in your ear.
You gotta
hold it together.
Can you do that?
Yeah. Sure.
Well... That's
a resounding hoorah.
You know, if I was
a betting man...
which I am...
I wouldn't put a single
George Washington
On your self-importance.
Ahh...
that's just
the way I am.
Now, your old man...
He would've probably
done things differently.
You asked me for the
definition of a warrior.
A warrior
gets the job done.
That's all I got.
Now get out
of my truck.
Yes, sir.
Hey, kid.
For the record,
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you.
(Starts engine)
Whoa. What's up, buddy?
Man, you need
a shower.
I try.
Mom... Is it okay
if I go see Brooklyn?
Here.
Wish me luck.
(Sighs)
(Playing classical music)
(Stops playing)
(Doorbell rings)
(Resumes playing)
Help you?
I'm here
to see Brooklyn.
I'm not so different
from you.
You're never playing
for me again.
But I'll play.
Anywhere there's
a couple of goals
and a field,
I can find a game.
I'm a lacrosse player.
And that's one thing
no one can ever take
away from me.
And, with all
due respect,
Tell Brooklyn
I stopped by.
Hey.
*
Brooklyn: The heart's
a funny thing.
It can break,
it can beat a little faster.
But the most important thing
it can do is heal.
And if you follow it,
It'll lead you
where you need to go.
(Beeps)
*
(Beeping)
Get up.
(Laughs)
Where'd you come from?
(Indistinct chatter)
Oh.
(Laughs)
I can do that, too.
Aah! Ha ha!
Goal.
That was cheating.
(Beeps)
All right.
Oh!
(Indistinct chatter)
Here, take it. Oh!
(Beeps)
(Laughs)
* will you feel
anything at all? *
* if I kiss you
where it's sore *
* will you feel better,
better, better? *
* will you feel
anything at all? *
(Beeps)
* will you feel
anything at all? *
Joe: Good, Sullivan.
Nice to see you,
east coast.
Nice to be seen,
west coast.
Performing
your penance?
How'd you know
I was here?
Word gets out.
If you don't mind,
I invited some friends.
Let's go, guys!
Whoa!
There he is!
The boys took
a little vote,
And we decided
we could use your help
this next game.
In case you didn't hear,
we're, uh...
We're playing
your old school
for the championship.
Thanks, Dupree.
I won't let
you guys down.
What's up, boys?
Let's go, guys.
Let's throw some
balls around, huh?
Brooklyn: The beauty
of finding yourself
And really knowing
who you are
Is that it allows
the possibility
For others to be a part
of your world as well.
Hey.
Heh.
* do you
* want to get to
* know me?
* every little thing that
* makes me me
* if you want
the best I've got *
* it'll cost you
a little honesty *
* take a deep breath
* and tell me what
you're feeling... *
(Sighs)
Hey.
What the hell is this?
We need west coast.
Out of the question.
We aren't asking,
coach.
This isn't a democracy.
He knows Sierra
better than any of us.
Come on, you guys.
Get back to class.
Brooklyn?
You need to find
a way, coach.
This is a team issue,
Brookie.
No. No,
it's personal, daddy.
So find a way.
Either Conor plays,
or none of us play.
There's a national
title on the line.
We're a team.
Remember?
Sullivan's a good kid,
and he's been
through a lot,
But he's not up to this.
And he'll take you all
down with him.
Then we all go down
together.
Big game today, dad.
I'm sure you'd have something
inspirational to say.
Well, guess what?
I met a girl.
She's beautiful, dad.
And the best part is...
She's Milligan's daughter.
I'm sure you got
a kick out of that.
You should see
my right-handed shot.
I miss you, dad.
I'm gonna get it done.
I promise you.
(Cheering)
(Overlapping shouts)
Look sharp,
west coast.
Respect the game,
east coast.
You ready
to win this?
How cute is he?
He looks
like his father.
(Whistle blows)
Let's go!
Sideline, everybody!
Gather up, gentlemen.
This is it.
The national championship
is on the line.
It's yours to win.
Hands in, gentlemen.
Do or die.
"Warriors" on three.
One, two, three!
All: Warriors!
Let's go, baby!
To the national high school
lacrosse championship,
Courtesy of lacrosse-x.Com.
This will be the first ever
national high school
lacrosse championship,
Featuring the best
of the east...
the Briarfield warriors...
Versus the best of the west...
The Sierra lions.
Shake hands.
The captains shake
as we get ready
For the national championship
high school match-up.
Dude. Midfield,
new team.
Fresh start,
green hornet.
What's Riggins
doing here?
Late-season transfer.
How sweet is that?
You hear me, Sullivan?
Did you say
something?
Both teams at midfield
as we get underway.
We'll have a chance to see
If west coast lacrosse
is ready
For the national stage,
And whether they can overcome
the transfer
Of their former
star player...
Number 9, Conor Sullivan.
All right, all right!
(Shouting continues)
Shot, and a goal!
Briarfield goes
on the board first.
Possession Sierra,
to number 14...
That's Riggins moving
the ball up the field.
Unchallenged
on the outside.
And a nice save
by the Briarfield goalie,
And the ball's out
the other way.
These east coast teams
can move the ball well,
And Briarfield's "d"
is doing just that
With a diagonal
up the field.
(Shouting continues)
Go to 3!
And a shot!
Goal, Briarfield.
Late in the second quarter,
With a 3-1
Briarfield advantage.
Shot Sierra... score!
All right, good finish!
Let's do it!
Goal, Briarfield!
Yes!
Number 9... Sullivan...
Doing it all by himself.
Sullivan scores!
This could be
a different game tonight
If 9 were still wearing
the purple of Sierra.
(Shouting continues)
Sierra just needs one
to take the lead,
And the later in the game
we go, the more the momentum
seems to shift to Sierra.
Oh, and a huge hit
by number 77!
Next time,
take his head off!
And Sierra's gonna
have a shot here.
We're under a minute,
tied at 9.
(Shouting continues)
Sierra working it around,
controlling the pace.
They swing it back up top.
Riggins,
stick somebody!
They've got time
to set something up.
And a goal! Sierra has
scored the go-ahead goal!
Sierra has just silenced
this home crowd.
28 seconds.
This is embarrassing.
We gotta tie this up.
What you got in mind?
You're captain America.
Nah, they know
my moves.
That's why we
gotta change it up.
Hey, offense, get in.
Come on, guys.
Briarfield needs
a big play
If they hope
to pull this out.
All: Break!
Let's go, white!
Nice play, white!
Come on, guys.
Come on, Briarfield!
Here we go.
National title on the line.
10-9, advantage Sierra.
Captain America!
Sullivan! Find Sullivan!
The ball's down.
The ball's up.
Oh! Possession Briarfield!
That's Joe Bryant.
The long stick is going
across midfield.
He's looking to pass inside.
Finds Sullivan.
Sullivan with a great dodge.
He cuts to the middle,
looking for his big left.
Needs a shot.
No, he dishes back!
Goal Briarfield!
There's no time on the clock.
But we are not done yet.
Hey, we've got overtime.
Don't get kicked out of this.
You east coast guys, man.
Talk about overrated.
Did Riggins just
call me east coast?
You are, aren't you?
That's not captain America.
It is over here.
Announcer:
Ladies and gentlemen,
by coaches' choice,
There will be no overtime.
We're still in there.
The game will be decided
by braveheart.
Why are we doing
braveheart?
Before the game,
the officials asked,
"do you want to do
overtime or braveheart?"
You agreed
without asking me?
I didn't know
a west coast team
would be that good.
Let's go!
This is our game!
All right, guys.
Settle down, it's not over.
Come on, settle down.
Gentlemen, the game is gonna
be decided by braveheart.
Dupree, that's you.
Not me, coach.
Bryant's hurt.
But Conor's not.
You know these guys
better than Dupree.
It has to be you.
Sullivan,
you up for this?
Okay, we know Sullivan's
looking for a fight.
Find it for him.
Hit him, and hit him hard.
Sooner or later,
he'll lose it.
All right, let's do it.
Let's do it!
Let's go! Let's go!
The nets will be brought
to center field.
This is sudden death.
No time on the clock,
no time outs.
Simple rules. The first
to score wins the game.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please join us on the field
for braveheart.
Oh, I can't take this.
We have to go.
(Laughs)
Braveheart may be
a new development
for organized lacrosse,
But its pedigree comes straight
out of the sport's history
As a true test
of a warrior.
No rest, nowhere to hide...
Just man-on-man
sudden death.
Who has the heart to
battle it out to the finish?
Down.
Too bad your dad's
not here to see
you lose.
Don't worry.
There's more than enough
of him here.
(Whistle blows)
Possession Riggins.
Driving Sullivan
up the field.
Left hand hold.
No clean opportunity.
Come on, Conor.
Fires. Blocked.
First chance for Sierra
comes up short.
And now to Sullivan.
Come on, Sullivan.
Sullivan looks
for an opportunity.
And he's down. Riggins...
Going back the other way.
Sullivan holding ground.
Riggins lowers
his left shoulder,
Tries to spin.
No movement.
Sullivan denies.
You can take him.
Come on, Conor!
Come on, get him!
Riggins fires
from the outside,
And shot blocked.
Easy save.
Back the other way.
Let's go, Sullivan.
Ohh!
Riggins lays into him.
Get used to that,
Sullivan.
This contest
is a bit chippier
As time goes on
and tempers flare.
Sullivan looks fired up
by the contact.
Come on, come on!
Sullivan hunting
for the game-winner.
Working the right side now.
Come on!
Come on, Sullivan.
Lining up for his big left.
Fires it!
A clutch save!
You can't let him
take that, Riggins!
(Shouting)
Riggins gets past Sullivan.
He's driving.
Take him down!
Get him!
A shot!
Crowd: Ohh!
His stick got tangled up
in Sullivan's facemask.
The shot was wide,
but Briarfield may be
in trouble here anyway.
You all right, son?
Dad: Conor...
Hope you score a lot
of goals tonight, son.
But it's important
how you score.
Never put yourself
above the game.
Conor: I have to let them
beat on me and just take it?
Duke: Temper's good.
It's how you use it
that matters.
Dave: If you fight again,
you are off my team.
Dad: Promise me that
you'll show humility.
Duke: When you fight,
you quit.
It's more than
a game, west coast.
When are you
gonna learn that?
Duke: A warrior
doesn't run from pain.
A warrior
gets the job done.
9, you okay?
If you can't continue,
I'm gonna have to
call a forfeit.
Nah.
We've got business.
All right,
play on!
(Blows whistle)
Come on, boy!
Sullivan attacks, powers.
Come on, Sullivan!
(Grunting)
Ride him, Sullivan!
Push him out!
Riggins giving nothing away.
Come on, come on.
Take the shot!
Sullivan spins,
he's got an opening.
It's in! It's in!
Briarfield wins!
The first national high school
lacrosse championship
Will go to the east coast
Briarfield warriors.
Thanks for being part of
a great championship game.
Congratulations
on the game, Conor.
Coach, thanks again
for the second chance.
I could say
the same to you.
Great job.
Good job, Conor.
Coach,
congratulations.
Thanks. You played
a hell of a game.
Impressive...
Captain America.
Nice right-handed shot.
Yeah? Well, now I'm
ambidextrous, too.
Way to go.
Your boys played well.
Thank you, honey.
Congratulations.
Go ahead.
You heading back?
Unfinished business.
Sergeant major.
Hey.
I gotta ask you...
Hammering down
the house...
Metaphor or not?
Hey. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Well done, honey.
Thanks, mom.
Hey, Sullivan.
You got a minute?
With all due respect, sir,
I need a few minutes
with my family.
All right. Nice job.
Brooklyn: It isn't easy
watching people you love
get hurt,
And it's impossible
to replace
Some things in life
that are lost.
But everything I look for
in a person...
Someone who stands up
when they're knocked down,
Can work with a team,
And has strength
and humility...
Can be found
through this game.
Maybe that's why lacrosse...
Or baaga'adowe...
Is known by another
even older name...
The creator's game.
Native Americans
believe they play
For the pleasure
of their creator.
Sometimes I think that's
why we do anything at all.
(Cheering)
Announcer:
Ladies and gentlemen,
please rise
As we honor the memory
of lieutenant colonel
Sully Sullivan
With a missing man
formation.
You do your dad
a great honor.
Respect the game.
Hey, Sullivan,
give me your stick.
You know what?
Today you're gonna
carry this.
Lead us out.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Let's get it
done, men.
*
(Cheering)
* I hope
* I can get to
* know you
* all your little secrets
* all the tiny pieces
* do you
* want to get to
* know me?
* every little thing that
* makes me me
* if you want the best
I've got *
* it'll cost you
a little honesty *
* take a deep breath
* tell me what
you're feeling *
* and feel love
* take a deep breath
* and let your kiss say
everything you mean to say *
* everybody thinks
we're too young *
* we should just
be friends now *
* don't complicate
* they don't
* have the magic we do
* they have never ever
* felt this way
* I can't get my mind off you
* do you feel
the same way I do? *
* take a deep breath
* tell me what
you're feeling *
* and feel love
* take a deep breath
* let your kiss say
everything you mean to say *
* we'll run away together
* and be alone forever
* we'll make our way
* just you and me
* take a deep breath
* tell me what
you're feeling *
* and feel love
* take a deep breath
* let your kiss say
everything you mean to say *
* I know
* I can get to
* know you
* all your little secrets
* all the tiny pieces