? Don't you know
that I love you ?
Ha ha ha!
It's gold, just like they said.
Yes, sir!
Gold, gold! Ha ha!
Really, really fine.
Well, I must admit,
you boys got a lot of nerve...
pulling a mining robbery
like that.
In broad daylight, no less!
Yeah, shooting up
all them good white folks.
Well, it comes with
the territory.
Ha ha! Well, gentlemen...
I'm prepared to go
10,000 apiece.
- What?
- What you talking, $10,000?
No, we agreed.
$200,000 on delivery.
It seems to me
things have changed.
Right now, this ore is hotter
than Memphis in July.
Now, you boys got to
turn it into cold cash.
There's only two people
who can do that...
and I'm one of them.
I suggest you take my offer.
Lester, you trying to cheat us,
you cheap bastard.
Hush up, baby girl.
I'll handle this.
You're trying to cheat us,
you dirty bastard...
and I'm very disappointed
in you.
Well, boy, I'll tell you,
take it or leave it.
? Hold you I love you ?
It ain't gonna go
this way, Lester.
You think about it again.
Drop your hands!
Drop your damn hands!
- Get your hands down!
- Move over! Move over!
That's right.
I don't do business with niggers
who pull guns on me.
Lester, baby...
you gone and picked
the wrong niggers...
to call niggers.
What the hell is
that thing on your nose?
It's distracting.
Ought to be removed.
My man Jodie here,
he's an expert cosmic surgeon.
- Ha ha ha!
- Yeah!
Ain't you, Jodie?
Oh, yeah! I-I-let me
have a look-see, Slim.
Oh, that's dog ugly.
- Ugly!
- Ugly, mm-hmm!
- Lester, it's gotta go.
- Gotta go.
Nurse...
No killing, Slim.
Who's the other fence, Lester?
Uh...
Pop go the weasel.
Aah!
You niggers rot in hell!
Doctor, I think you ought
to sterilize that wound.
Don't use that acid, Slim!
Go on around.
No! No! It's Easy Money
up in Harlem!
Easy Money?
The dude that own the Royale?
That's him! I swear!
Get that acid away from my face!
Bo! Get our shit
and get the hell outta here.
Come on, y'all, let's go.
- Slim...
- What?
You're gonna kill him,
ain't you?
Go help Bo.
You promised me no more killing!
Get the hell outta here.
Always got to run your mouth!
Come on, Hank.
Let's see if we can fry him
like a pork chop.
- Burn him!
- Ha ha ha!
Lester, you're gonna
look like sloppy chitlins.
Jodie!
- It's the sheriff!
- You set us up!
Y'all got ten seconds
to get your ass out here!
Fire!
God damn it, it's Lester!
Shoot the bastards!
Aah!
Imabelle!
Fuck you, nigger!
- Aaah!
- Back up!
Stop her! No!
Don't let her get away!
? Give to the blind ?
Help me, somebody. Mmm!
Christy, you forgot
your Hula-Hoop!
Young and tender inspiration!
Dirty old man.
Damn shame.
? Give to the blind ?
Lord...
thank you for letting me
wake up in my right mind.
Lord...
last night
after depositing $4.25..
Of my hard-earned money
into my bank account...
I passed the $1,500 mark...
my new balance
now being $1,500.25.
Thank you for
making me provident...
and for not putting
obstacles in my way.
Such as... women.
Amen.
And they snatched her purse
right off her arm.
Lord have mercy.
I don't know what's wrong
with these children today.
Nothing that a good ass-kicking
wouldn't help.
You go right ahead.
Thank you, honey.
You got manners to spare.
His mama
really raised him right.
Well, I hope he enjoyed himself.
She probably the only woman
he'll ever have.
Sorry. All full up.
As salaam alaikum, my brother.
What are you
saying to me, Claude X?
You speak English to me.
You just say hello.
Hell is low, brother man.
That's much better,
and very true.
Rodney, meet me over on 110!
- Jackson!
- You're late!
I'm sorry.
- Jackson!
- Yes, sir?
- You're late!
- I'm sorry. I just-
I know, I know.
Next time get on the bus,
no matter what!
We got dead people
to tend to here.
You think
they gonna wait on you?
Oh, no, sir.
? Ooh, ooh, ooh ?
Shake it!
I'm ready to go!
- Ohh...
- Hey, Goldy.
Say, Goldy!
? Just yesterday
skies were cloudy and gray ?
You must be some kind of
mathematical genius...
keeping all those numbers
in your head.
Well, you know how it is.
Notepads look too much
like evidence.
Yeah, well,
I'm very disturbed...
that one of your people
hit for ten grand.
It ruined my weekend, Goldy.
What can I say?
Old man Dixon's
been playing for years.
- He never won a dime.
- Yeah.
Suppose we just say
you remembered wrong.
You see, I hear he's due...
to take a little fall
down a flight of stairs.
You want to chump on the rest
of your people, you do that...
but anybody bets with me
gets paid.
You understand what I'm saying?
What's the matter
with this guy?
How come you always
looking to try me?
I'm gonna try you again.
You ain't gonna try me now.
Goldy, Goldy...
Hey, my friend...
I'll let Dixon off this time.
But it's the principle
of the thing.
I got one rule in life...
don't give nothing to nobody.
Take it easy, my man.
Drive. Come on.
Mm-mmm!
Yum yum yum yum yum.
Yum Yum Yum yum!
Mmm! Pow!
Put it in for me, honey.
Whenever, wherever, and however.
- Uhh!
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, Charlie!
- Yeah?
- Give me a hand, huh?
- Oh, all right.
Yaah! Jackson!
Ha ha ha!
You boys quit messing
with the corpses!
I ain't joking around,
you know!
Yes, Mr. Clay.
You getting ready for
the Undertaker's Ball tonight?
We'll find you a woman.
I ain't got no time
for no women, Louis.
We'll fix you up
with Mr. Clay's wife.
The one with the big ass
like two glazed hams.
Philistines!
She got big feet.
Cover a lot of ground.
Blaspheming philistines!
Two big, luscious titties,
like two cassava melons.
Blaspheming
philistine heathens!
Man, I'm not from Philly!
Who you talking to?
- I told you that!
- Hey, come on, man!
Blaspheming philistine
sinning heathens.
Sorry, Mr. Clay.
I'm separated!
Up in a man's business!
Would you look at me?
$5.00 an hour,
20 for the night.
What is this, the Ritz?
This is New York City, honey.
People don't come here
to sleep.
Hour's usually all they need.
All I got
is $4.00 to my name.
Oh, yeah?
What's that shit on your finger?
This is my grandmama's ring.
It's going with me to my grave.
All right,
you can keep your $4.00.
I got a room opening up.
Go on up and take a shower.
You know your best bet?
You should go on over...
to the Undertaker's Ball
at the Royale.
Royale? That's where
I was going anyway.
Well, good.
If anybody can raise the dead...
and make 'em pay their rent,
it's you.
Things don't work out,
you come on back home.
Ooh, yeah! Yeah!
Turn me, baby! Ooh!
? Elevator operator ?
? Up and down, up and down ?
? When my day is done ?
? I got to show you around ?
? Elevator operator ?
? Up and down, up and down ?
? Whoo, elevator operator ?
- What'd she say?
- Yeah!
I tell you
what she said, right?
She says, "Smitty,
Smitty, come on over."
So I go over there, right?
Soon as I get to the house,
she got 12 kids, man!
- What?!
- Twelve ugly kids!
Every last one of 'em
looked like Dracula.
All right now!
? Elevator operator ?
? Up and down, up and down ?
? Whoo, elevator operator ?
? When my day is done ?
? I got to show you around ?
? Owww! ?
Now, I take the 12 kids
that look like Dracula...
and put 'em in a room, right?
Let 'em watch some
of that "Andy 'n' Amos."
No, no. "Amos 'n' Andy."
Yeah, whatever it is.
Amos and... and... right.
So, I tip over
to her bedroom, right?
Man, I'm riding that coochie
like the Lone Ranger.
I got that Trigger thing
happening down there.
Smitty, I don't got time...
for all your blaspheming
and your evil ways.
I'm looking for Easy Money.
- Smitty...
- Ohh!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Get your goddamn hands
off me, chump.
Trying to clean you off.
Excuse me, but...
- Do we know you?
- Not in this lifetime.
- Oh!
- Whoo!
Hot damn!
I know that hurt you.
It hurt you.
No, can't hurt nobody
who look like Nat Cole.
Shit.
You better get rid
of them shaving bumps.
Man, shut up,
you old bug-eyed...
Yeah. Heh.
That's gold, all right.
Mmm. Mmm. That's good.
But you're gonna have
to show me the rest of it...
before I show you the money.
Now, honey, a whole lot
of people was killed...
playing around with this stuff.
My partners,
white folks, police.
I ain't just
flashing it around...
and ending up the way they did.
You know, I do believe...
you and I were cut out
to do business together.
But first...
Yeah, baby?
- Straighten up!
- Count off!
Act calm.
Take it easy, baby.
Their bark is bigger
than their bite.
So, what you trying
to pin on me now?
Familiar with an old man
named Julius Dixon?
Hit for 10 grand on a number
Goldy sold him.
It warms my head
when I can do some good...
for the old folks
of the community.
Yeah? Too bad he fell
down a flight of stairs...
before you could pay him!
You don't think
we could do this later...
like in the morning?
- Hell no!
Don't worry, baby.
They just do this shit
to keep themselves busy.
But, uh...
I got no place to stay.
Stay in a hotel.
But I got no money.
? The people quit the scene ?
? Like the devil was loose ?
? The clouds turned green ?
? And letdown lemon juice ?
? What walks on two feet ?
? And looks like a goat? ?
? That crazy Screaming Jay
in a bright yellow coat ?
? Hey, now ?
? Stick With it ?
? Baby, baby,
don't you quit it ?
? Ohh, you're bound to get it ?
? Yes, sir ?
? Made outta goat skin,
foreskin ?
? And laying out
in milk and gin ?
? Lord, lord, lordy ?
? I took a plane out Midwest ?
? To see my Uncle Joe ?
? We ran into
some real bad weather ?
? Ice, rain, and snow ?
? Fifty million bulldogs ?
? Twenty mountain goats... ?
Are you ready for me, daddy?
Oh, I'm sorry that
I spilled that water on you.
He spills a drink on me...
and now he won't even ask me
for a dance.
Boy ain't got no manners.
Well, honey,
you're just gonna have...
to make it up to me
on the dance floor, huh?
Would you hold
this for me, please?
Thank you.
I'm gonna hold this
for you, yeah.
Uh...
You're not an undertaker.
? I put a spell on you ?
I'm Jackson.
? Because you're mine ?
That's my toe, Jackson.
Sorry. I told you,
I don't know how to dance.
Baby, it's easy.
Just wrap your arms
around me...
? Ha ha ha, watch out ?
And squeeze.
? I ain't lying ?
? Yeah ?
I know who it is.
See, that's his cousin.
- Uh-uh.
- No, no.
Then that's...
Mr. Clay's in on this...
that's his wife's
sister's daughter...
- Uh-uh.
- No, no.
Then I do not know
who that woman is.
But...
? Because ?
? You're mine ?
Sorry.
And don't this feel good?
- Whoo!
- Oh!
Jackson, would you like
to go outside?
Because it's kinda hot in here.
Um, no. Uh...
Heh. I'm doing
just fine here, really.
Would you like to go home?
Really, don't worry about me.
I'm great.
Honey,
I ain't worried about you.
I'm worried about me.
See, I'm tired,
my feet are killing me...
and I just want to sit down.
Now, do you live nearby?
I'm sorry?
? And I love you anyhow ?
? I don't care
if you don't want me ?
? I'm yours ?
? Right now ?
? I put a spell on you ?
Let's go.
? Because you're mine ?
? Mine, mine ?
? Ow, whoo ?
? Ooh, you're mine ?
This is it.
Upstairs.
Jackson, I told you
never to leave...
your ham-greased stuff
in my kitchen.
Who is that?
Well, you ain't been
fornicating all these years.
I don't see how come
you want to start now.
If Christ knew
what kind of Christians...
he had up here in Harlem...
he'd climb back up
on the cross and start over.
Who's that?
Why, that's Jesus.
Now, honey,
I know who Jesus is.
The other one.
Oh. That's my mom.
She's dead now.
Sorry to hear that, Jackson.
I'm so tired.
I feel like I walked
all the way from Mississippi.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Would you like me
to rub your feet for you?
I could do that for you.
Sure, honey, that'd be fine.
Gotta take these off.
I've seen a lot of feet before.
I don't think
I've seen one... so small.
That's mighty sweet of you,
Jackson.
So, where is it
you seen all them feet?
Dead people.
Jackson.
Oh, you know...
being an undertaker
and everything.
It's not that
I work with the deceased...
or anything like that,
personally.
It's just... the job.
You get accustomed
to the sight of bodies.
What I mean is...
Looking at bodies ain't so bad.
That's not what
I'm trying to say, either.
What I'm trying to say...
is...
You probably
ain't never seen a body.
Mm-mm.
Oh, they ain't so bad.
Actually, it's
a very exciting line of work.
Police! Get the hell
out of the way, suckers!
Don't make me kill nobody!
- Straighten up!
- Count off!
Goldy, my boy.
What's a nice guy like you
doing in a place like this?
I live here, Grave Digger.
Now get the fuck out!
Two sluts cut up
a white cop last night.
So what? What?
So the word is,
they come outta here.
You wouldn't
know nothing about that?
I don't know
nothing about nothing.
I suppose you don't know
nothing about some boys...
in Mississippi that shot up
a bunch of white folks...
and stole a trunk of gold?
What's that got to do with me?
Sooner or later,
it'll end up in Harlem.
Between you and Easy Money...
knowing everything
that comes in and out of here...
Gentlemen, you wouldn't
happen to have...
a search warrant, would you?
We don't need
a goddamn search warrant.
OK! All right!
We said we don't know
nothing about nothing.
Yeah!
You better watch
your ass, fruitcake.
Or we'll shut
this motherfucker down!
Let's go.
Someday, though.
Yeah, someday...
I'm gonna kick your ass.
Try not to break
anything on the way out.
Bastards.
Could've been worse.
Ha ha! OK, girls.
The fun is over.
Let's clean up this mess.
Come on, come on!
Did you hear what they said?
There's gold in Harlem!
Don't even think about it.
Shit, Kathy,
this could be it for me.
I get my hands on that gold...
- Be careful.
- Yeah.
I'll be careful.
Yes! I'll be careful!
Ladies!
I'm coming back, ladies!
Hey! I done told you...
a million times to keep
your behind off my stoop!
What you doing?
Staring at you.
You've been there all night,
haven't you?
You covered me up?
Yeah, it gets
so cold around here...
I didn't want you
to get sick or nothing.
It's just that most men
would've uncovered me.
All of 'em, in fact.
What kind of man would do
something like that to you?
That's not very nice.
Where you staying, anyway?
Do you have family around here?
I sure had a fine time
last night, Jackson.
Me, too.
Thank you...
for covering me up and all.
Rubbing my feet and all.
Oh, it's no problem.
Really, it's no problem.
You a virgin, Jackson?
What you want to ask me
a question like that for?
I'll take that as a yes.
I ain't no virgin.
Heh.
I could teach you.
I don't know.
You already taught me to dance
and all that stuff.
Wow.
Come here, baby.
Turn around.
Oh. That's OK.
I can do that.
Lay down, baby.
- Up here.
- Oh.
Do you mind if I take
these pictures off the wall?
- OK.
Mm. What you trying
to do, baby?
I'm just... just...
taking my shoes off.
I'm sorry.
I'm so stupid. I don't...
I don't know how to do nothing.
Jackson.
It don't matter.
It really don't matter.
It don't? Really?
Mm-mm. No.
? Please, please,
please, please ?
? Please, please, don't go ?
? Please, please, please ?
? Honey, please ?
? Don't ?
? Ohh ?
? Oh, yeah ?
? Whoa, I love you so ?
? Please, please, don't go ?
? Baby, you did me wrong ?
? You know you done me wrong ?
? Whoa, whoa ?
? You done me wrong ?
? You know you done me wrong ?
? You know you done,
done me wrong ?
? Whoa ?
? Oh, yeah ?
? Took my love,
and now you're gone ?
? Please, please, don't go ?
? Please ?
? Please, please, please ?
? Please, please ?
? Please ?
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Mmm.
Will you marry me?
Marry me. Marry me.
Jackson...
don't you think that's
rushing things a little bit?
I mean...
Maybe we should just
try this out, you know?
Like for the weekend, huh?
Huh?
You mean, live together in sin?
Yeah. Why not? Hmm?
One, two... Uhh!!
Jackson, your decision
to liberate your hair from...
the influence of the white devil
is most encouraging.
Does that mean you're going
to liberate your mind as well?
No. It just means I'm going
to wear my hair natural now.
Woman sure has changed
you a lot in one week.
Morning, Mrs. Canfield.
This trunk is so heavy!
Stop complaining, Jackson.
If you knew anything
about women...
you'd know
you was getting off light.
- Hi, Mrs. Canfield.
- Huh!
I-I don't want
to complain or nothing...
Last night, you trying
to act like Samson.
Now I give you a chance to
prove it, and look how you act.
My good brother,
can you make it from here?
For I must prepare for mass.
As salaam alaikum.
Hey! I told you to just
say good-bye to me.
Just say good-bye.
It was awful nice
of him to help.
What kind of last name is "X"?
Oh, God, you're so innocent.
Ha ha ha!
It just fills my head with joy.
It's refreshing,
that's what it is.
His last name ain't
His last name is Taylor.
- Claude Taylor...
- Maybe that's why he changed it.
Oh... oh, baby!
They cut your throat!
And the trunk busted, and your
blood was all over the gold!
What gold?
It was just a dream.
I been wanting
to give you something.
Belonged to my mother.
And I figure,
if you wear this...
it'll chase all of them
bad dreams away.
Ohh...
I can't take it.
It's yours.
? May the Lord God
bless you real good ?
? Woke me up this morning ?
? Got me on my way ?
? May the Lord God
bless you real good ?
Hallelujah!
? Praise God on high ?
? It was a hot day
in Harlem, New York City ?
? City ?
? When Cain
went into the fields ?
? With his brother Abel ?
? Abel ?
? All right, and while Abel ?
? I said, while Abel ?
? Was tilling the soil ?
? Cain rose up ?
? He rose up
against his brother ?
? Oh, yes, he did ?
? He picked up that rock ?
? It was not
the rock of Jesus ?
? Jesus ?
? It was the rock of jealousy ?
? And Cain,
Cain took that rock ?
? He took that rock... ?
? Praise God, praise God ?
Have a blessed week now.
God bless you now.
Have a blessed week.
- Jackson!
- Reverend Gaines...
I'd like to introduce you
to Sister Imabelle...
a good, decent,
God-fearing woman.
Well, God bless your head,
my sister.
Now, Jackson, I hope you took
my sermon to head.
You still ain't talking
to your stepbrother?
No.
Forget your differences,
Jackson.
Life is too short
for all of this pettiness.
- Yes, sir.
- Now, remember, Jackson...
you promised to look over
the church accounts.
- Um, we'll be right back.
- All right.
You just go on home.
I'll be there shortly, OK?
- OK.
- Bye.
Yes, sir!
What's the matter, baby?
Ain't you glad to see me?
Oh, baby! Oh, baby!
I thought you was dead.
When I saw you at church...
I was so happy to see you,
I just wanted to cry.
I come over here
as quickly as I could...
just hoping you'd be here.
Oh, baby, here you are.
I think she's sweet on this lame
she's shacked up with.
And I think you don't know what
the fuck you talking about!
I needed some place to lay low,
so fuck you!
- No, fuck you!
Oh, man, this is bullshit!
She and him was gonna
cut and run with the gold!
She come back to get the trunk!
Now, Slim...
would I go
for a chump like him...
after I been with
a man like you?
An undertaker? Ha ha ha!
Jodie, you don't know
what you're talking about.
This here's my Imabelle.
This our Imabelle.
Besides, all Imabelle done
is to set up our first city boy.
Mm-hmm.
You want to scam Jackson?
Well, the boy look like
a born sucker to me.
We gonna take him
for everything he got, or...
Pop go the weasel.
OK, baby, what you want to do?
I think we ought
to bake some money.
That'll be perfect.
Say, baby girl,
who's that on the wall?
Why, that's Jesus.
I know who the fuck Jesus is.
I'm talking about
the other dude.
That's his mama.
That's Jesus's mama?
Jackson's mama, fool!
His mama?
That is one ugly bitch!
Ha ha ha!
Jodie, she got a gorilla
in her past.
Ha ha ha! And just think...
if you and Jackson
were to make babies...
Ha ha ha ha!
Y'all wait in the car.
I'll be right there.
Oh, baby girl...
Now, let me take a look at you.
Come on, let me take
a good look at you.
Mm-hmm. Now you take off
that jacket.
Sure miss looking at you.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm mmm mmm!
Come here, baby.
- Come here.
- Ha ha ha!
Um!
You stretching
this boy's jeans?
What, baby?
That sucker?
Well, he be a dead sucker
if he don't profit me.
You understand?
Babe, I don't know about this.
Sounds like a hoax to me.
Baby, it ain't no hoax.
I have something for you.
Hmm?
Oh, God.
You're gonna look fine
when you take me out...
with all that money
we gonna make.
Where'd you get it?
Did you sell
your grandmother's ring?
Oh, God.
What's wrong, baby?
I think you're the answer
to all my prayers.
You're every dream
I ever had come true.
Jackson...
What? What?
I never meant you no harm.
That's right.
This is
my life savings... $1,500.
And you want me to raise it
to 15 Gs, right?
Right.
Uh, are you gonna
change mine, too?
He did it for me last week.
It's a miracle. A miracle!
- Really?
- Mm-hmm! This man's a genius!
He's gonna make us rich.
We gonna be rich, god damn it!
Now, I'm gonna have me
some water while it's baking.
Uh, yeah.
Let me get some of that.
Why don't you sit down, daddy?
Your knees are shaking.
Thank you.
You know, if this works,
we can take the 15,000...
turn it into 150,000. 150,000,
turn it into 1.5 million.
1.5 million
into 150 million...
150 million
into 1.5 billion dollars.
We'll be rich.
We'll be really rich!
- Oh!
- Look out, honey!
Open in the name of the law!
I'm a United States marshal...
and I'll shoot the first
son of a bitch that moves!
- Aah!
- Run, daddy, run!
Don't you move, boy!
I don't want to have to put
a bullet in your ass!
I ain't moving!
I ain't moving! Look!
Man, put your hands down.
This ain't no goddamn movie.
Now, you stand up here and take
your punishment like a man.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
What, your woman
put you up to this?
Oh, no.
She's a law-abiding woman.
She ain't mine, neither.
No, no.
I don't want to be rude
or nothing...
but would it be OK...
if I gave you $20G...
would you let me go?
Oh, Lord, ashes to ashes
and dusk to dusk.
All he left me was his debts.
It's OK,
my little chocolate bunny.
You see,
we're better off without him.
See, y-your husband's
in a better place, and so am I.
Please forgive me.
I know how you feel.
Mmm! That you, Louis?
No, sir. It's me, Jackson.
I thought you took
the afternoon off.
Yes, sir.
But there were some numbers
that didn't add up...
and I thought they might
have overcharged us...
on that embalming fluid.
I ain't gonna give you no raise,
son, so don't overdo it.
Yes, sir.
I'll sop you like a biscuit
on some gravy.
Just think of me as smooth
as a piece of okra.
I'd suck you like a neck bone.
Here's the money.
You stay away from that woman.
Please...
Uhh!
You're lucky.
I don't want
to see you no more.
Imabelle?
Don't let her be gone, God.
Don't let her be gone.
She took the cross!
Sure took your time
getting here.
We do the best we can, ma'am.
Now, this is his room.
And this is him.
Don't surprise me none.
I don't know why old man Clay
trusted him in the first place.
You said he had
a woman up here.
Some southern gal.
She's a thief, too.
Oh! Evil, evil woman!
The same detectives
what arrested Jackson...
came back with two more
and arrested her.
Said they wasn't
no regular detectives...
said they was
some special agents.
And they took her trunk
as evidence.
- Oh, yeah? What was in it?
- I don't know.
Whatever it was, it certainly
must have been important...
the way they was carrying on.
Those could be the Mississippi
boys we been looking for.
Yeah! The ones
with the trunk of gold!
Maybe the gal's
trunk was full of her panties.
Gold!
- Maybe it wasn't.
Well, maybe it was,
and maybe it wasn't.
But somebody don't come up
with my $175.95 for my stove...
I'm gonna raise some hell,
you hear me?
I'm really gonna raise hell!
- Yes, ma'am.
- Mm-hmm.
- Who's that?
- Oh, that's Jesus.
I know that's Jesus.
I mean the other guy.
That's his mama.
- Jesus!
- God damn!
Thank you, ma'am.
Y'all welcome.
Wake up, my brothers and
sisters, for the time has come!
For we do not wish
amalgamating...
with the pale-skinned nation
of the Europeans.
Blacks should quit bothering
with his religion!
Quit bothering with hot combs
and skin-bleaching!
Man is made of haste,
my brother!
I ask you to let me
show you my portion!
I haven't got time for you
right now, Claude X.
Listen, you just slow down.
I'm gonna tell you something.
You're looking for your woman.
She's nowhere to be found.
I saw her leaving
with some serious black devils.
Now, it may do you well
to seek a brother's help.
You talking about
my stepbrother?
Uh-uh. We ain't been talking
for five years.
Well, you better sta? now.
I don't want
to talk to my brother.
I wanna talk to Reverend Gaines.
He'll know what I should do.
If you want to find God,
you talk to a preacher.
If you want to find devils,
you talk to a demon.
These will take
your uncle Inell...
straight to the bosom
of the Lord.
For I have seen heaven open
and beheld the white horse.
That'll be $5.00.
I told you...
No, no. There he his.
Oh, my God!
Brother Gabriel's
got your ticket.
I can't believe my own brother's
out here on the street corner...
impersonating a man of God!
What are you think...
Don't call me Sherman in public,
you hear what I'm saying?
That's your Christian name.
Claude X, why you bring
this square around here?
Brothers, brothers.
Goldy, your brother
needs your help.
He has been robbed
of his woman...
and the Prophet says
lower thy wings in kindness...
- to thy tribe of near-kin.
- Tribe, my ass!
Just because...
What's the daily word,
Reverend?
And the Savior said
to his disciples...
said, "He that loveth
his brother more than me...
"is not worthy of me."
The man is a demon.
- What?
- Run.
- That's not true.
- Run away from him!
- Blind man...
- I don't need no bean pie!
What you need
is a divine message!
Awaken, my people!
The so-called Negroes...
So, what happened, bros?
That gold-digger you met at
the Royale take all your money?
She didn't have
nothing to do with it.
Just 'cause the only kind
of woman you associate with...
is prostitutes and lowlifes-
Put that back!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Put that back!
Just because you abandoned
me and Mama...
and then broke her head
with all your evil ways...
don't mean that everybody
in the world is just like you!
Come here talking
that holier-than-thou shit...
looking for me to help you?
Fuck you, man!
You ain't said five decent words
to me in five years...
and now just 'cause
you need something...
That's right! I need you to
help me find my woman, Sherman!
- I need your help!
- Help yourself, man!
Here-here's some tickets
to heaven.
Move your preaching ass!
You want to run me down?
A man of the cloth?
Com flake-eating motherfucker!
Get out of the way!
Help me, Sherman!
You're my brother!
- Forget it!
- We're blood!
- No!
- There's gold.
There's a trunk full of gold.
Gold.
You say there's a trunk
full of gold?
You ain't never gonna change.
No. I ain't never gonna change.
Come here for a second. Shit.
And then they put
the money in the stove...
And the stove blew up,
and the marshal ran in...
- and blip blop de blam.
- How you know that?
My very own brother
taken in by the bluff.
But there was a hundred dollars
came outta that stove.
What's the matter with you?
Where's your fucking brain, huh?
You been drinking
embalming fluid or some shit?
You been suckered...
and your gal run off with
the stud that took your money.
She didn't run off.
They took her, Sherman!
She's in trouble, too.
I know. I can feel her.
She's in trouble?
You the one's in trouble...
Mr. Churchgoing Man.
Heh heh. Shit,
you just robbed your own boss.
You motherfuckers
got a cigarette?
No, we ain't got no cigarette.
Listen, I'll help you
get your woman back.
First, we call Kathy,
then we go see Blind.
But I keep the gold,
you understand?
You get the woman,
I get the gold.
Woman, gold. Strictly business.
- Got it?
- Got it.
All right.
You motherfuckers is in my way!
Give me your money...
and don't think
I wouldn't cut you, Reverend!
Have mercy, son.
You lucky I got
my reverend shit on...
otherwise I'd blow
your fucking lips off.
- Get the fuck outta here.
- I'm going!
I can't believe that. Man tried
to stick up a preacher!
So we got a deal, bros?
I just want
to get her back, Sherman.
I don't care nothing
about no gold.
Come with me, chump.
And stop calling me Sherman.
- Where you taking me, Sherman?
- Shh!
Will Kill, what you been doing?
Not a goddamn thing.
- Blind Man here?
- He's back there.
Shit.
That's him!
Coming to get it!
Sherman! There are
half-dressed women in here.
You know my stepbrother?
I'm Jackson.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Jackson, uh...
why don't you check out
the crap table?
Go ahead. Good.
Stepbrother?
Yeah. Listen,
I need some information.
It's that Jackson, ain't it?
You're jerking that lame.
Oh, come on, baby.
What you talking about?
What is it?
You got religion, baby?
Huh? Is that what it is?
Or is there something wrong?
do this tonight.
I want you
to stop treating me...
like I got nothing
to say in this.
Look, I haven't got time
to explain everything to you.
Like I said, just trust me.
That's not something
we're used to doing with you.
We? Who's we?
The family! You know,
the people you forgot about?
Oh, get off my back!
You really don't care,
do you? You really don't care!
You didn't even come
to your mama's funeral!
Hey! You don't know what
the fuck you're talking about!
And it ain't none of
your fucking business...
what I did or didn't do!
What are you gonna do?
Shoot me with your gun next?
Just forget it.
Just forget it and stick with
the business deal. All right?
I ain't never gonna own you
as my brother.
And that goes double for me,
man. That's double for me!
You ain't got no feeling.
I got feelings! I got...
Who are you to tell me
I ain't got no feelings?!
I'm a fool for talking to you.
Come on!
Oh!
? And I'm saving all my loving
just for you ?
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Didn't tell me you were
taking me to a whorehouse.
Shut up, man. Any luck?
Yeah, I think so.
Who's the 'john'?
My name's not John. My name
is Jackson. Thank you, ma'am.
Jackson?
You two are stepbrothers?
You made up or something?
No, no. Just got a little
business deal going, that's all.
I think it ain't like that.
Come on, sit down.
Sit down, Jackson.
I'll stand.
Thank you very much.
Where's he at?
Ah, Teena's got his lap staked.
Here.
Father, lead us not
into temptation...
but deliver us from evil!
- Ooh, is that them?
- Yeah, I think so.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
It just ain't right.
Just ain't right.
I'll handle this!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
- What's that lame doing?
- Oh, shit!
- Shit!
- Wait! I'll get him!
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, you!
Ooh!
Just throw his ass down there!
That is your brother?
Yes! And you should have
hit him twice!
You should have shot him!
All right!
I gotta go wee-wee.
Ain't you a little old
to be talking that way?
I talk that way,
I stay that way, honey.
I'll be right back.
- Goldy, listen! I got it.
- What?
He's been telling me about this
gold mine he's representing...
and he's been going all over the
United States selling shares.
How do you know
he's not scamming you?
Because he's got two partners,
plus a contact man...
named Gus Parsons
working the Braddock Bar.
And he said he's gonna show me
a trunk full of gold...
that they're using as bait.
But listen. They're pulling out
tomorrow night.
- You did great, baby.
- Thanks.
Keep him talking!
You gotta help me.
Son, you've gotta know
when you've had enough.
I got nothing. This is my chance
to get something.
Now, either help me
or I'm gonna do it alone.
Not this time.
Did you hit me?
Sherman!
What are you thinking about,
slugging your own brother?
I didn't hit you.
But I should've hit you!
He hit you!
He?
Oh, God.
Now, let's just go over this
one more time.
It's very important.
There are three things...
I do not want you to do tonight.
One... don't drink.
Don't drink? Why would I drink?
I don't drink.
That's your problem. But just
stick with that tonight.
OK? Two...
don't flash this roll..
In front of anybody
but Gus parsons.
- Don't flash this roll.
- Right.
All right, number thr...
What is that shit on your face?
It's my disguise.
All right. Three...
should you meet up
with Gus persons...
and he wants to take you
to the gold, you go by cab.
Go by cab.
Does he always have
to repeat everything?
Go get him.
I'm right behind you.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Good evening.
Evening.
Hello.
Good evening.
I bet he fucks it up.
I bet he pulls it off.
$20 he'll miss.
Twenty.
I'll have a glass of milk.
We don't serve no goddamn milk.
No milk. Right.
Well, how about some water?
We don't serve
no goddamn water.
No water. Right.
Well, you know, I'll just have
whatever you suggest.
Thank you very much.
Why is he drinking?
Ha ha ha!
'Cause you owe me $20.
What... is this stuff?
Rye goddamn whiskey.
It's good. Heh.
I can't... I can't believe this.
Yes, except that's two drinks
at $20... that's $40.
Thank you, that is
very hospitable of you!
It ain't goddamn free.
No, no.
I meant hospitable in spirit.
I got plenty of money.
Plenty of money!
Payday.
Out comes the roll.
What's wrong with you?
You trying
to get your throat cut?
You said it ain't free.
I'm just paying for my drinks,
thank you very much!
I don't want no trouble.
You're so unreasonable!
That's 'cause he knows
you paid him with my money.
What are you talking about?
This here's my money.
I know my money when I see it.
You done picked my pocket.
- Don't let him scare you, honey.
- Me? Scared? Ha ha.
That will be the day.
I'll have another rye whiskey.
Can't nobody tell me
I don't know my own money.
Now, wait a minute.
What is the difference
between...
Uhh!
He's got a gun!
I don't know how much money
you owe me now.
You're the punk who robbed me
last night, ain't you?
I got a good notion
to blow your fucking brains out!
I wouldn't rob you, boss.
Swear for the cross
it wasn't me.
Maybe it was that man
what robbed you.
'Cause he's sporting
a big roll from somewhere.
Don't you put that on me.
I hit the numbers last night.
I can prove that.
Oh, I know
it wasn't you, friend.
And maybe it wasn't you,
either...
but you sure as hell robbed
somebody in your lifetime...
so you're just getting
what's owed to you!
Get your ass outta here!
I was robbed of $700
last night!
Man tried to hit me.
But you know something?
That really don't
matter now, friend...
because I have tucked into
something that's nice...
something that's solid gold.
Gold?
Gus Parsons, real estate.
Coleman Jackson,
burial services.
Jackson, huh?
Hey, listen, Jackson.
How would you like to meet some
very successful businessmen...
- men just like yourself?
- Like me?
- Let's get out of here.
- Let's go this way.
This is the luckiest night
of your life.
Jackson, come here.
What is he...
I gonna have
to blindfold you, friend.
Blindfold me? For what?
My partners have $100,000 worth
of gold ore in their possession.
Now, they can't be
taking no chances.
Yeah, but I ain't...
Hey, Jackson.
I understand completely.
You don't know me
from the man in the moon...
SO...
I'm gonna give you my gun.
Thank you very much.
Would you lean over, please,
Mr. Jackson?
Get that door, baby girl.
Mmm.
There you are.
What, do y'all know each other?
I've been in jail two weeks...
and I ain't seen a woman
in all that time.
Maybe, uh...
I just dreamed about you.
First, you... you drain
the blood.
Ha! And then...
and then you shoot 'em up
with embalming fluid.
Damn!
How do you keep their faces
from turning all blue and shit?
Make-up.
Jesus.
Shit!
Look, whatever you do,
don't lose him.
This guy's playing whip-ass.
Since when are you worried
about your brother's ass?
Since he started shitting gold.
Hold on!
- Whoa!
- Get out of the way!
What's wrong with the street?!
Ooh! Somebody almost had
an accident or something.
Yeah, an accident.
Are we almost there?
Heh heh heh heh.
Yeah, we're almost there.
In this dream...
a woman almost as fine
as her...
is relaxing on the sofa with...
trying to interest me
in a box of, uh...
A box of what?
Let me see. I think it was...
candy. Heh heh heh.
Come over here, baby.
Come over here. Heh heh heh.
Ah, don't you love it
when dreams come true?
Damn, man.
Slim.
If your gold is as good
as your taste in women...
y'all got a deal.
Did you bring the money?
It'll be at my place
later tonight.
A sweet...
chocolate box of...
candy.
Heh heh heh.
Yeah.
You know, Jackson,
I really trusted you...
but you are
a big disappointment to me.
Disappointment?
What are you talking about?
Give me the money, Jackson.
I got the gun.
- Ha ha ha!
- Where's Imabelle?
Oh, so you're the fool.
If you don't tell me
where Imabelle is...
I will shoot you dead.
Be my guest.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
The money, Jackson.
What the fuck is this?
It's play money.
Now, ain't that a dirty trick?
Get your ass outta this car.
Get outta this car!
Now I'm gonna let you hear
what a real gun sounds like.
'Cause guess what? It's gonna be
the last thing you ever hear.
Next time you try
to duck somebody...
take your big-ass foot
off the brake light.
Look, if you guys are the cops,
I want my lawyer, understand?
You want a lawyer? Big Kathy,
didn't you used to be a lawyer?
Ah, shit! You son of a bitch!
That will be $500.
Take us where
you take the marks.
Ah-ah-ah! Stay in the car.
- Where are they?
- Top floor.
Hurry up!
You ever seen such
a sorry-looking bunch...
of cotton-picking farmers
in your whole life?
Mmm mmm mmm!
- Operator.
- Get me the police.
I can smell it like
biscuits and gravy.
Heh heh heh.
You ain't gonna eat
no more supper now?
Yeah.
It's me... Gus. I brought
investors for the gold mine.
Go ahead.
Here we go again.
It's the police, asshole.
Everybody freeze!
Damn you, Gus!
Freeze right there and shut up!
Imabelle.
Hey! It's that thieving undertaker!
Hey! Come back here! Come here!
Ooh, lordy, lordy!
Where are they?
- Fifth floor!
- Got it!
- What's the matter?
- My little baby toe!
Come on, they're getting away!
Let 'em go!
Come on!
I'm gonna kill somebody now!
What the fuck you looking at?
I'm gonna shoot you first...
anybody makes a strange move,
you got that?
- Eat shit.
- Shut up!
All right, come on, now.
Cooperate,
and we'll go easy on you.
Coffin Ed and Grave Digger
are here!
- Mm-mm!
- Jackson!
- Baby!
- Police! Everybody freeze!
- Hank, acid!
- Aah!
Aaah!
Jackson! Where are you,
so I can shoot you?
- Come on!
- Let's go!
Let's get outta here!
You all right?
Jackson, I told you
to wait in the car!
Back up!
- Hands up!
- Back up!
That's right, Goldy, run!
Straight on up!
Go get the car!
Imabelle!
Shut up, man.
Someday, Goldy! Someday...
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Jackson.
Imabelle!
Show your hands now, sucker!
Jackson!
Imabelle!
Imabelle! I'm coming
to get you, baby!
I love you!
- Jackson!
- I love you, baby!
Jackson, don't jump!
Ohm
Imabelle!
Oh, my God! He made it!
OK! OK! All right!
Imabelle! Imabelle! Imabelle!
Oh, bless you, Jesus!
Ha! I made it!
Jackson! Stop jumping!
Ed! Ed! No, no, no, no, no!
I'm crazy,
but I ain't no damn fool.
Someday, Goldy!
Someday!
Imabelle!
Jackson! Jackson!
What are you trying to do,
kill yourself?
I love her.
All right. But you got anything
against taking the stairs?
Shit!
- Taxi!
- Hey!
Taxi!
All right, get your ass out!
Imabelle!
- Imabelle!
- Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, Jackson!
I'm gonna leave you!
Hurry up!
Follow that red gypsy cab!
Don't lose 'em!
This way!
There's nobody here. Huh?
- She went this way. I know it.
- You know it?!
What are you listening
to him for?
He's in love.
That way!
This is unbelievable.
- There she is.
- This is unbe...
Let's just go in there
and get her.
Just wait a minute now.
Gotta do this thing right.
See, what we really need
is something big enough...
to carry the gold in.
The hearse.
Your boss's hearse.
I don't care nothing
about the gold.
Hey, we got a deal, remember?
The girl for the gold.
Or you can go up there
by yourself.
All right.
Just give me bullets
for my gun first.
- I'll give you one bullet.
- One bullet?
That's right. One bullet.
Deal?
Deal.
- It's gonna be OK.
- What you saying, baby girl?
I got a hole in my chest.
I need a fucking doctor!
That's too damn bad.
You got us hot as hell
as it is.
Jodie, you call Easy Money...
see if he can make that meeting
a little earlier.
Imabelle will stay
with the gold.
- Imabelle?
Well, she can't do nothing
with it by herself.
What about Gus?
Fuck Gus.
Hey, man,
what you talking about?
Pop go the weasel.
Don't you kill him, Slim.
Get the fuck outta the way.
Move!
Ah. Now, let's be kind to Gus.
He is our friend.
Hank, don't kill me, man.
I got no choice, man.
I don't want to die!
We'll take care
of your wife in Jersey.
Gus, baby,
you're giving dying a bad name.
- Come on, Hank, get him!
- I'm doing the best I can, man!
What do you want? Hold him.
- Hold his head down.
- Come on, Hank!
Come on, Gus, die!
Come on, hold him, Jodie!
Everybody happy?
You're just in time.
That's everyone
except Gus and the girl.
Parsons-number six.
Don't make no noise.
This guy is dangerous.
No noise.
Yes?
Shh.
Is that you, Imabelle?!
It's me... Jackson, baby!
I've come here to rescue you!
Daddy!
Yeah, you be Daddy.
I'm gonna check the gold!
We gotta go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
I didn't do it, officer.
Jackson!
That ain't no officer.
This is my stepbrother Sherman.
Oh, good.
Then you're just in time...
to help me get
that trunk outta here.
That's just what
we was intending on doing.
And then what was you intending
on doing with it?
Don't worry
about that right now!
I got him under control.
I just want you...
to get outta here
before they come back in.
You go downstairs
and you wait in the hearse.
You take this trunk down,
and we'll be right behind you.
Heh heh heh heh.
What do you mean,
you got me under control?
You ain't got me under control.
You gotta get her
under control. Come on.
Hey, baby girl!
Where you think you going?
Oh, God! Oh, God!
You come here!
Please! No! Aah!
Hold her, Jodie!
You know you hurt me, girl,
when you do this kind of shit.
You hurt me deep.
Aah!
Here, here, here.
Let me help you.
Where is she?
- She took off.
- What, she go back in?
Here. I don't...
I don't think so.
Well, she got to be around here
somewhere. Where is she?
She took off up the street.
How about we come back for her?
I ain't going nowhere.
I ain't leaving her.
I came here to get her.
Jackson. Shit!
Did you see that?
- We're not leaving him.
- No, no, no.
You think I'm going
to leave my stepbrother?
I told you we were going
to get that gold, didn't I?
Yeah. Just hurry up
so we can keep it, eh?
I'll get him.
We'll be right back.
- Jackson!
- Jesus.
Jackson, what are you doing?
She's gone... and I love her.
I know that, I know that,
but the gold is back there...
and it's just begging
for trouble.
You don't get the gold
unless I found Imabelle!
I did find you Imabelle.
Well, where is she?
Come on, man.
She don't want to stay found.
Shit, she ran away.
Get that into your head, man.
She don't want to be with you.
You don't know nothing
about love!
All you know is whores.
Don't you tell me...
about my head.
You know, Jackson,
you're just like Mama.
Don't talk about Ma!
You do not talk
about my mother.
Hey, fuck you!
She was my mama, too!
And I loved her
just as much as you did!
You didn't even go
to the funeral.
I'll bet you ain't
even been to the...
to the grave site once.
I've been...
I've been to the grave site.
I've been there!
Is that our gold
in the back of that hearse?
Damn straight, it is.
You got to hold me
so tight, Jodie?
Hope your lips don't give me
no shit, big mouth.
Uhh! Uhh!
Ima, get out of here!
Bitch, I'm gonna fuck you up!
Come here, shorty,
I'll show you something.
Come here, come here.
You want to see this, huh?
Yo.
Think about this, brother.
Just think about this.
You think about this right now.
Take your best shot, sucker.
Ohm
Oh, no, no.
You get up here, boy.
Stand up there.
Uhh!
Hit him again.
Ohh.
I thought I recognized
that voice.
This the bitch who run
the cathouse we were at.
- Nah.
- Yeah.
Last time I saw you,
you was dressed as a woman.
- Disgusting.
- Ain't that right, bitch?
Jackson, look...
I'm sorry, Jackson. I'm sorry.
I should've gone
to the funeral.
I didn't go. I didn't want
to embarrass everybody.
I know how everybody
in the family feels about me.
I should've been there.
I'm sorry.
Jackson!
- I thought you were gone.
- Oh, Jackson! Jackson!
They're trying to kill
your friend, Jackson.
your friend!
Kathy!
Wait a minute.
It's your last time, punk.
You talk to me, or I'm going
to let him fuck you up.
Where's Jackson
and the other phony cop?
Fuck you.
Hmm. Pop go the weasel.
No...
fuck you.
Uhh.
Kathy! Kathy!
God!
Kathy.
- It's me.
- Boss...
- it's Goldy.
- Uhh.
Come on, man.
Come on, Kathy. Don't die.
You hear what I'm saying?
Don't die, OK?
Kathy...
OK. OK. I'm going
to close your eyes.
Sherman.
I want those murdering
bastard friends of yours...
and you're going to take me
to them right now!
No, don't. Sherman, don't.
Jackson, Jackson,
you all right?
Baby, you all right?
- Get your hands off of me!
- Don't hurt her.
Take it easy.
Take it easy?!
I took it easy back there
jerking around with you...
when I should've been watching
out for my real family.
Yeah, man, make a move...
so I can blow her fucking brains
out on the sidewalk.
Make a fucking move!
I'm sorry.
Sherman!
You know, you take
that gun off my head...
I'll have an easier time
driving.
I mean,
it's kind of distracting...
Shut up, bitch!
The only person I ever cared
about in this whole world...
just died because of
your worthless ass!
I don't like what they did
any more than you...
but what do I get out of this?
We're gonna play a game,
you and me.
I don't know how many bullets
in this fucking gun...
but we're gonna play a game,
you and me.
You wanna play?
- Yeah!
- Let's play!
Don't fuck with me!
Um!
Fuck!
You kill me,
you don't get nothing.
Not even revenge.
What do you want?
I want a fifty-fifty split.
- Uh-uh.
- I planned that robbery.
Pad of that money's mine.
You tell me where they are,
it's a deal.
No. I go with you all the way.
All right.
All right, it's a deal.
But you fuck with me...
and I'm gonna do to you what
your boyfriend did to Big Kathy.
152 grand. Ha ha!
Too bad you didn't
bring your lady friend.
I had another dream about her.
Ahh... hoo, shit!
I can't tell you about it.
You were in it,
weren't you, baby?
Yeah, you were.
Listen...
I'm quite fed up with you...
Diddling with your
little rat dog there...
And running your mouth
all over my woman.
You stop that shit.
God damn it, Slim. Calm down.
You stop that shit!
Come on, Slim.
We done come too far.
You better get
some etiquette classes...
before you try and do business
in the big city, boy.
Boy?
You see a boy?
Grave Digger Jones here.
- It's Goldy.
- Goldy! Where the fuck are you?
Bastards killed Big Kathy,
and I'm gonna pay 'em back.
If you and Coffin Ed
can stop thinking...
about shooting my ass,
I think I can do you a favor.
All right, go on.
Some people are gonna have
to die on this one.
As long as it ain't me or Ed...
I don't give a shit.
Just pan of the job.
No sense in getting our heads
worked up over business.
That's right! Ha ha ha!
Eh, your friend Imabelle...
already got another pan
of me worked up...
and it ain't my head.
Ha ha ha!
- That's it!
- That's what?
- What?
I done told you.
Jodie, talk to him!
Pop go the weasel!
- What you talking about, Slim?
- Pop go the weasel!
- We come too far for this!
- No! Pop go the weasel!
Save that nursery school shit
for Mississippi, chump.
- Chump?!
- Yeah! Chump. Pussy!
You don't know me that well.
- He didn't mean nothing by that.
- Aw, pussy, get outta here!
- That's it!
- It can't be it! Come on, y'all!
Pop go the weasel!
Pop go the motherfucking weasel!
Slim! Aah!
Damn it!
Uhh! Baby! Not the dog.
Don't touch the dog.
Don't worry, baby.
Ain't nobody gonna hurt you.
Don't shoot my dog, man.
That's where I draw the line.
That just ain't right.
I'll give you
the motherfucking money...
you can walk out of here...
just don't let me see you
shooting no dog.
I want the money
and I want the gold.
Now, you know I can't do that.
Fine. Then I'm gonna
kill your rat.
All right! All right!
All right!
Take the money and the gold
and get out of town.
Now, just put my dog down.
- Put your gun down.
- I'll put the gun down.
Step away from it!
All right, I put my gun down.
Please put my dog down.
Here, baby.
No!
- Goldy, you all right?
- Imabelle!
Imabelle, come here!
You want this?
You want me?
- Baby...
- Motherfucker!
- You want some more? Here!
- Forgive me, baby.
Imabelle! God damn it! Shit!
God damn it! Shit!
You still carry this? Ha ha!
- Let her go, god damn it!
- Fuck you!
Let her go!
I'll kill her, I swear!
You kill her!
Ain't that your woman?
Huh? I'll kill her!
Go on and kill her!
You killed him, didn't you?
Who, your girlfriend?
You killed Big Kathy.
You cut his throat,
you bastard!
What, you grieving
'cause that he-bitch is dead?
I'm gonna put you
out your misery.
Slim!
Hey, baby, there he is,
Simple Simon.
You let him be!
It's me you want.
That's right. It's you I want.
Jackson,
shoot this motherfucker!
I don't need this
to do what I got to do.
Jackson, you need that!
Shoot this bastard!
You put the razor down.
I'll put the gun down.
I'll fight you for her...
like a man.
For as God is my judge...
I love you
more than life itself.
- Oh, Jackson...
- Shut up, bitch!
Like a good dog,
you stay right there.
Huh! Uhh!
You ain't no man.
I ain't even armed.
I can't believe you'd say
no funky shit like that.
Ha ha ha!
- Jackson, run! Run outta here!
- You stay outta this!
? All around
the mulberry bush ?
Yea, though I walk
through the valley...
I The monkey
chased the weasel ?
Aah!
This dance for you, baby girl!
Uhh!
Aah!
I will fear no evil...
The monkey thought
it was all in fun.
In the house of the Lord.
We ain't gotta do this.
- No.
- Ain't gotta do this.
Uhh!
All fall down!
Pop!
Uhh!
That'll be Grave Digger
and Coffin Ed.
I made a deal with them.
Told them about the gold...
but I didn't tell them nothing
about no money.
You take this
and get on outta here!
Listen to me. I want you
to stay behind this bar.
I'm gonna go out there
and make sure...
these cops
don't hurt my brother.
Here, take this.
Keep this safe.
No, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
You can't trust her!
Take that money
and get on outta here!
Sherman, why you always
gotta assume...
that everybody
is untrustworthy?
What are you doing?
- Straighten up!
- Count off!
Can't you see
that this man is injured?
Damn that man!
Where's the damn gold, sucker?
It's in Easy Money's office.
Let's go! Let's go!
Move 'em out!
Let's go, Goldy!
You got blood, whatever!
Get on in there!
What did I tell you, huh?
She's inside.
She is gone.
Must have gotten delayed.
She's permanently delayed.
She skated with the money.
I gotta see a doctor.
- Straighten up!
- Count off!
We were admiring
the body count back there.
And what a nice day's
work you did.
And how happy some undertaker
was gonna be...
when we remembered you was
wanted for robbing your boss.
It was not part
of Goldy's deal.
- Come on, we're taking you in.
- Wait a minute!
Are you resisting arrest?
I'm sorry, bros.
I'll do what I can.
Don't matter.
Nothing matters no more.
Someday, Goldy, someday!
I want my phone call!
Son of a bitch!
Get your ass up, sucker.
Who brought me these clothes,
made bail for me... a woman?
Hell, no.
Mr. Clay.
Well, well, well...
here's the big,
bad man himself.
Time you put
your six-shooter away...
and take out
your adding machine.
You drummed us up some work.
Two of them boys that was killed
was carrying eight grand apiece.
That money was just contributed
towards their funeral.
Oh, by the way, a lovely,
lovely young lady...
came by the office
and asked me to give you...
The cross.
Train station!
Where you think you going,
Jackson?
I just made your bail!
Train 55,
bound for Mississippi...
Here they are, Goldy.
leaving from platform 9.
AH aboard.
Oh.
Sherman,
what are you doing here?
Goddamn fool oughta be
getting some rest.
After you get shot,
it's always a good idea...
to spend a few days in bed!
Good God Almighty!
It's payday, man!
There's about
$50,000 here, man!
Count yours.
She says I'm too good for her.
She's right!
But count the money, man!
Hey, have you seen a woman...
With the sweetest ass
God ever made?
I just took her to platform 9,
train bound for Mississippi.
Jackson! Jackson!
Jackson, this is fifty... oh!
Jackson! Jackson! Jackson!
Take this money now.
Big Kathy wants you to have it.
- I don't want it!
- Wait a minute!
Good luck, brother.
You're gonna need it.
I love you.
God bless you.
God bless you, Goldy.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
He called me Goldy.
Look at him. Look at him run!
In all the years
I know that chump...
I never seen him run so fast.
If I had somebody like her...
- Goldy!
- I'd run fast, too.
Yeah, he'll be back.
Jackson in Mississippi?
It's like getting change
from a penny.
You getting sentimental
on me, Goldy?
Yeah, a little bit.
But I'm recovering.
I'm recovering rapidly!
Money! There's a lot
of money here, ladies.
I'm a very rich man.
Look at those ladies.
Look at them!
Yes! Money!
Excuse me.
Does this belong to you?
Only you can answer that.
You know, Jackson...
you really don't know me.
Yes, I know...
but it's a long ride
to Mississippi.
Tell me. You know anybody
in Mississippi...
who does a good foot rubbing?
Ahem. You know,
as a matter of fact...
I don't.
Mmm.
That's too bad.
'Cause my feet are killing me.
? In your darkest of hours ?
? Don't you despair ?
? You can feel his power ?
? It's everywhere ?
? If you're looking
for something ?
? Don't look too far ?
? 'Cause the answer
is right where you are ?
? 'Cause heaven ?
? Oh, heaven ?
? ls in your heart ?
? Yes, it is ?
? Heaven ?
? Oh, heaven ?
? Is in your heart,
mm-hmm ?
? In the heat of temptation ?
? It's worth the fight ?
? You can find your salvation ?
? And see the light ?
? If your soul needs healing ?
? Here's what I say ?
? Just fall on your knees
and pray ?
? 'Cause heaven ?
? Oh, heaven ?
? Is in your heart ?
? Yes, it is ?
? Heaven ?
? Oh, heaven ?
? ls in your heart ?
? Yes, it is ?
? Heaven ?
? Oh, heaven
is in your hear! ?
? If your world's in question ?
? Then set it free ?
? Give your heart
some attention ?
? Eternally ?
? If your soul needs healing ?
? Hear what I say ?
? 'Cause the answer you need
is not so far away ?
? It's in your heart ?
? Heaven ?
? Oh, heaven
is in your hear! ?
? Going to New York City ?
? Where them Broadway lights
so bright ?
? Well, I'm going
to New York City ?
? Where them Broadway lights
so bright ?
? Got an uptown woman ?
? She'll make me
feel so good tonight ?
? There's a rage up in Harlem ?
? Fighting for my girl ?
? Gonna get that woman ?
? Before I leave this world ?
? So I'm going
to New York City ?
? Where the Broadway lights
so bright ?
? When that uptown woman
love me ?
? She'll make me feel
so good tonight ?