Are you alive?
Yes.
Prove it.
It has begun.
- Make a hole!
As I was saying,
form follows function.
Nowhere is this axiom of design
more readily apparent...
than on board the world-famous
Battlestar Galactica.
This ship, the last of her kind
still in service...
was constructed over 50 years ago
during the early days of the Cylon War.
Originally there were 1 2 Battlestars, each
representing one of Kobol's 1 2 colonies.
Galactica represented Caprica and was
first commanded by Commander Nash--
"The Cylon war is long over, yet we
must not forget the reasons why--"
- Commander Adama, if I may?
- Captain.
I just wanted to say what a pleasure it's
been serving with you in your command.
Captain Kelly, it's been my honour.
Good luck in your next assignment.
Thank you, sir.
- "The Cylon war is long over, yet--"
- Good morning, sir.
Good morning, Starbuck.
What do you hear?
Nothing but the rain.
- Grab your gun and bring in the cat.
- Boom, boom, boom.
Attention. Honour guard detail...
report to star board hangar bay
for ceremonial brief in grand rehearsal.
Let's go, guys.
Chief's gonna have our ass.
Yeah, well, you're the one that
was supposed to wrap that yesterday.
Shh. It's the old man.
Too late. What's up?
Nothing, sir.Just another leak
in that "frakkin"' window.
Pardon me, sir.
It's supposed to be a Battlestar,
not a museum.
Sorry for saying so, sir.
Couldn't agree with you more.
Be careful out there, all right?
"The Cylon War is long over,
yet we cannot forget the reasons why--"
- Morning, sir.
- Good morning.
- Com traffic from the Midwatch.
- Hmm. Anything interesting?
Mostly housekeeping. Uh, there was
one odd message we were copied on.
The one from
Fleet Headquarters there, sir.
Courier officers overdue
coming back from Armistice Station.
They've asked for a full status report
on all F.T.L.-capable ships...
just in case they need somebody
to jump out there today--
see if his ship
has any mechanical problems.
I think we're a little bit busy today.
Wouldn't you say so, Lieutenant?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm glad we agree.
And may I take this opportunity
to say that it's been both a pleasure...
and an honour to serve under you
these past three years.
It's my honour, Lieutenant Gaeta.
"The Cylon War is long over--"
Colonel?
You'll see things here that look odd
or even antiquated--
Hello.
Antiquated to modern eyes.
Phones with cords,
awkward manual valves...
computers that barely
deserve the name.
It was all designed to operate
against an enemy...
who could infiltrate and disrupt
even the most basic computer systems.
Galactica is a reminder of a time when
we were so frightened by our enemies...
that we literally looked backward
for protection.
Attention all hands--
Morning.
Attention on deck!
- Chief. At ease.
- Sir.
This way.
A Mark Two.
Haven't seen one of these
in about 20 years.
If the commander will take
a closer look... at the tail numbering.
Nebula 7242 Constellation.
Oh, my God.
Where did you find her?
Rusting out in a salvage yard
on Sagittarian.
We had hoped the commander
would allow her to participate
in the decommissioning ceremony.
- She'll fly?
- Oh, yes, sir.
- Ah.
- We've restored the engines...
patched the guidance system,
replaced much of the flight control--
- You guys are amazing.
- She's fuelled, armed...
- ready for launch, sir.
- Commander.
- What? More?
- Mm-hmm.
Somebody's bucking
for a promotion around here.
I believe that would be
Prosna, sir.
He found this in the fleet archives.
He was doing some research
for the museum.
Thank you. Thank you all.
It's an honour.
You're welcome, sir.
Fall out.
All right. You heard the man.
Let's get number three up.
Attention.
Prior to 2300 hours.
Uh-oh.
- Here we go.
- If you're gonna play with the big dogs--
- No fear.
- l'm in. Bet's to you, X. O.
- l'm in.
- I'm not scared of you.
Oh, Helo. When are you gonna learn?
First you're flying with rooks, and then--
- Hey!
- Ow!
And then you're betting
against Starbuck.
"Starbuck. "
Now there's a callsign.
Starbuck. Starbuck, buck, buck, buck,
buck, buck, buck, buck.
Where'd you get
that nickname, anyway?
Was that before you were thrown
in the brink as a cadet for drunk
and disorderly or after?
- After.
- After. That's right. It was after.
I'm in.
Bet's to you, X.O.
- l'm in.
- Stay.
How's the wife?
Too early for that kind of money.
Hey, did you hear about
that Pyramid game on Geminon?
What were you doing on Geminon?
- This girl there I know.
- What girl don't you know?
The wife is just fine.
- Talk to her lately?
- Bet's to you, Lieutenant.
All right.
- Thirty to me.
And it looks like I'm gonna bring
this lovely little game to a close...
because... full colours!
Ha-ha!Ah-whoo!
- Ow! Ow!
- Stop!
- Okay, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Okay.
- Hey.
You have finally gone too far...
and now you're done.
Lieutenant, consider yourself
under arrest, pending charges.
Report to the brig.
- Gentlemen.
Are you really gonna press
charges against Kara?
For striking a superior officer?
You're damned right I am.
Heard you started the day off
pretty early.
I wasn't on duty.
Now, where did you get this?
Tyrol's deck gang scrounged it up.
- I couldn't talk you out of it, could I?
- Not a chance.
She is insubordinate, undisciplined.
Probably one of the finest fighter
pilots I've ever seen in my life.
- Yeah.
- She's better than I am.
- Twice as good as you.
- Like hell.
Jesus.
Listen, I'm not gonna defend
what she did.
That's because of the cracks
about your marital problems.
But you did kick over the table first.
I did not.
Unless I did.
You did.
So what do you say
we just drop the formal charges...
throw her in the brig,
cool her heels off until we get home?
You always did have
a soft spot for her.
Yeah, I guess I'm just
a crazy old man.
I'm afraid the tests are positive.
The mass is malignant.
- It's advanced well beyond the--
So I also sent
the president a copy of your speech
for Galactica's retirement.
Hopefully, he'll have
a chance to review it...
but there is a 30-minute time delay
between the Galactica and--
- Excuse me.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain. Welcome aboard.
We are en route to Galactica...
and our estimated flight time
is approximately five and a half hours.
Please sit back and relax
and enjoy your flight.
I'll take two!
All right.
- How small they are.
- I know.
- But they grow up so fast.
- May I?
Sure.
There.
- So light.
- So fragile.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
There, there. It's okay.
You're not gonna have to cry
much longer.
We really should be going.
- Of course.
It's amazing how the neck
can support that much weight.
Chantara. Honey. Let's go.
I gotta show you something.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Come on.
Give me a moment.
Just a second.
I'll go with you.
My God! He's not breathing!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
He's not breathing!
My baby!
For those of you just joining us
from the Pyramid game on Geminon...
welcome to The Spotlight...
our weekly interview programme devoted
to people making news on Caprica.
Today we're talking
with Dr Gaius Baltar...
winner of three Magnate Awards
over the course of his career.
A media cult figure and
a personal friend of President Adar's...
he is currently working as a top
consultant for the Ministry of Defence...
on computer issues.
But he's perhaps best known
for his controversial views...
on advancing computer technology.
Dr Baltar, again, welcome.
Thank you, Kellan. Firstly, may I say
how lovely you're looking...
and secondly, what an absolute
pleasure it is to be on the show.
Well, we're delighted
to have you with us.
Could you summarise your views
for our audience?
Yes, I'd be happy to.
My position is very simple.
The ban on research and development
into artificial intelligence...
is, as we all know,
a holdover from the Cylon Wars.
Quite frankly, I find this
to be an outmoded concept.
It serves no useful purpose
except to impede our efforts--
Miss me?
Can't you tell?
Your body misses me,
but what about your heart, your soul?
Yeah, those too.
- Do you love me, Gaius?
- What?
- Do you love me?
- Are you serious?
You had me worried there
for a minute.
- I'm hot, Gaius.
I'm so hot!
Viper 450, this is
Galactica. Approach port landing bay.
Hands-on, speed 105.
Checkers red. Call the ball.
Galactica, this is Viper 450.
Check that.
Did you say hands-on approach?
Viper 450, that's affirmative.
Hands-on approach.
Copy that, Galactica.
Port landing bay, hands-on approach.
Speed 105.
I have the ball.
Skids down. Mag-lock secure.
On behalf of Galactica,
I'd like to welcome you aboard, Apollo.
It's an honour to have you with us.
Morning, sir. Chief Tyrol.
I'll be your crew chief
while you're aboard.
Morning, Chief.
Captain Lee Adama.
It's a real pleasure to...
meet you, sir.
I'm sure you've heard this before.
I'm a great admirer of your father's.
The service is gonna miss him
when he retires.
Well, I'm sure someone will.
Is your auto-landing system down?
I was hands-on for the whole approach.
It's all hands-on here, Captain.
There are no auto-landings
on the Galactica.
Commander Adama's orders.
Is that right?
Attention in the port hangarbay.
Raptor touching down.
Clear. Projector is ready.
Nice flying, Lieutenant. I think
they heard that clear up to the bridge.
Yeah. I'm gonna catch hell from the
L.S.O., but it wasn't entirely my fault.
- Primary gimbal's acting up again.
- Oh, it's the gimbal's fault again?
- Helo, am I lying?
- Gimbal looked bad to me.
I've pulled that gimbal three times
and stripped it twice.
- The gimbal's not the problem, sir.
- You're not listening to me, Chief.
I listen very closely to what each
and every one of my pilots has to say.
You're not the one out there
trying to bring in 50 tons of Raptor...
onto a moving hangar deck
with a bad gimbal.
- I've got 1 0 years experience...
- Here we go.
breaking down and stripping
every component and every system--
That's ever been installed
in every spacecraft on my hangar deck.
- The gimbal is broken.
- Shut up, sir.
- Morning.
- Morning, sir!
All right.
Today is the main event.
We have a formation demonstration,
fly-by manoeuvres...
in conjunction with
the decommissioning ceremony.
I've got a few changes
to the flight plan.
Lieutenant Thrace is being replaced
in the slot by Lieutenant Anders.
Also, we have Captain Lee Adama
joining us...
and he's gonna be flying lead during
the fly-by, so please welcome Captain.
- Good to have you.
- Welcome, Apollo.
- Welcome aboard, Captain.
- Great.
- Welcome.
Thanks to Chief Tyrol
and his deck gang, Captain...
you're gonna have the honour
of flying the actual Viper...
that your father flew
almost 40 years ago.
Great. That's, um--
That's quite an honour.
Yes, it is, Captain.
And personally I can't think of a better
way to send this ship into retirement.
It may interest you to know that
the final results for the C.N.P. project are:
Working close to 95% efficiency
throughout the fleet.
- Hold your applause, please.
- No applause for me?
I doubt you would've ever
completed the project without me.
- Yes, well, you helped a bit.
- I rewrote half your algorithms.
All right, you were extremely helpful.
But let's not forget
you got something out of it.
All that poking around
inside the Defence main frame.
Should give you a huge advantage
bidding for the contract next year.
- You know that's not really why I did it.
- No, you did it 'cause you love me.
That, and God wanted me
to help you.
Right. He spoke to you, did he?
You had a chat?
He didn't speak to me
in a literal voice.
And you don't
have to mock my faith.
Sorry. I'm just not very religious.
Does it bother you that I am?
It puzzles me that an intelligent,
attractive woman such as yourself...
should be taken in by all that
mysticism and superstition.
But I'm willing to overlook it
on account of your other attributes.
I have to go.
I'm meeting someone.
Really? Who is he?
I'm insanely jealous.
I doubt that.
So touchy today.
Well, as a matter of fact,
I'm meeting someone too. Business.
A new project at Defence I might do.
So, uh...
you'll call me later, right?
It's about time.
I wondered when you'd get here.
- Secretary Roslin.
- Yes.
- Mr "Kickay. "
- Keikeya.
- Oh, sorry. Hi.
- Hi.
My name's Aaron Doral.
I'm from Public Relations.
- I'd like to welcome you
aboard Galactica.
- Thank you.
If you'll follow me,
I'll show you to your quarters.
Attention all hands.
At this time, Galactica
would like to welcome aboard...
the secretary of education,
Laura Roslin.
The secretary is a member
of the president's cabinet.
We're honoured by her presence
aboard our ship...
and her participation this afternoon in
Galactica's decommissioning ceremony.
Madam Secretary?
Yes, that's exactly what I would think.
Attention all hands.
E.V.A. activity on hull.
Do not radiate any electrical equipment
while E.V.A. is in progress.
Thank you.
In or out.
- Excuse me?
- Get in or get out.
- Shut the hatch.
- Sorry.
Where are you trying to be?
Uh, visitor's quarters.
I'm a visitor.
Yeah. Never would've guessed.
It tells people things
like where the restroom is.
It's an integrated computer network,
and I will not have it aboard this ship.
I heard you're one of those people.
You're actually afraid of computers.
No. There are many computers
on this ship, but they're not networked.
A computerised network would
simply make it faster and easier
for the teachers to be able to teach--
Let me explain something to you.
Many good men and women
lost their lives aboard this ship...
because someone wanted a faster
computer to make life easier.
I'm sorry that I'm inconveniencing
you or the teachers...
but I will not allow
a network computerised system...
to be placed on this ship
while I'm in command.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
Thank you. Excuse me.
This seems familiar.
Captain Adama, sir.
Sorry I wasn't there to greet you
with the rest of the squadron.
Did they kiss your ass
to your satisfaction?
So, what's the charge this time?
Striking a superior asshole.
Ah. I bet you've been waiting
all day to say that one.
- Most of the afternoon, yeah.
- Right.
So, how long's it been?
- Two years.
- Two years. We must be getting old.
Seems like the funeral
was just a couple months ago.
Yeah.
Your old man's doin' fine.
We don't talk about it much.
Maybe two or three times a year.
He still struggles with it, though.
- I haven't seen him.
- Why not?
- Kara, don't even start.
- How long are you gonna do this?
- I'm not doing anything.
- He lost his son, Lee.
And who's responsible for that?
Same old Lee.
You haven't changed either.
Zak was my brother.
What was he to me? Nothin'?
That's not what I meant.
And you know what--
You know what?
You should go.
I'm gettin' the urge to hit
another superior asshole.
Gaius.
Gaius!
- What are you doing here?
- Who the hell are you?
Get out.
Gaius, who is this woman?
Uh, she's a friend. Well, more
than a friend. When I say friend--
Get out.
This is just great.
Bye.
Look, it's, uh--
It's me, all right?
lt-lt-lt's totally me.
I screwed up.
I am screwed up.
I always have been.
It's a, uh-- It's a flaw
in my character that I have.
- I've always hated it and I've tried--
- Spare me your feigned...
self-awareness and remorse.
I came here because
I have something to tell you.
Oh, here he is.
If you'd just like to--
A little space.
Captain, thank you for joining us.
Hi. Aaron Doral.
If you'd just like to stand up there,
we'll get a few shots of you...
and the commander.
Thanks.
Hello, Captain.
Great. Okay, gentlemen,
could you maybe stand a bit closer?
Fantastic. Um, Commander...
could you put your arm
around your son?
Great. Perfect.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Um, see you at the ceremony.
We'll just be leaving this--
through this door way and to our right.
Attention, honour guard detail,
report to starboard hangarbay.
You want some, uh, coffee?
No, sir. Thank you, sir.
Why don't you sit down?
Congratulations on making captain.
Sorry I wasn't there.
Thank you, sir.
- How's your mother?
- Getting married.
Good for her.
We spoke about a year ago.
Had a real heart-to-heart. It was good.
I'm glad to hear that, sir.
Will that be all?
- Why don't you talk to me, Lee?
- What do you want to talk about?
- Anything. You've been here for an hour.
- Well, I don't have anything to say.
My orders said report here
and participate in the ceremony.
So I'm-I'm here, and I'm gonna
participate in the ceremony.
There wasn't anything in my orders
about having any heart-to-heart
chats with the old man.
Accidents happen in the service.
Dad, listen, I--
- You know all the things that you
talked to me about at the funeral--
- I really don't want to do this!
- They still ring in my ears after two years.
- Good!
Good. 'Cause-- 'Cause you know what?
They were meant to.
Zak had a choice. You both did.
"A man isn't a man until he wears
the wings of a Viper pilot."
Doesn't that sound
at all familiar to you?
That's not fair, son.
No, it's not fair.
Because one of us wasn't cut out
to wear the uniform.
- He earned his wings,
just like we all did.
- One of us wasn't cut out to be a pilot.
One of us wouldn't
have made it into flight school...
if his old man, his daddy,
hadn't pulled the strings!
That's an exaggeration.
I did nothing for him that
I wouldn't have done for anyone else.
You're not even listening to me.
Wh-Why can't you get this
through your head?
Zak did not belong in that plane!
He shouldn't have been there.
He-He was only doing it for you.
Face it. You killed him.
That'll be all, Captain.
So now you're telling me, um--
Now you're telling me you're a machine.
- I'm a woman.
- You're a machine.
You're a synthetic woman.
A robot.
- I've said it three times now.
- Well, forgive me.
I'm having the tiniest little
bit of trouble believing that.
The last time anybody saw the Cylons,
they looked like walking chrome toasters.
Those models are still around.
They have their uses.
Prove it.
If you're a Cylon,
prove it to me right now.
I don't have to.
You know I'm telling the truth.
See, stating something as the truth
doesn't necessarily make it so...
'cause the truth of the matter is
I don't believe a word of this.
You believe me because deep down
you've always known there was
something different about me--
something that didn't quite add up
in the usual way.
And you believe me
because it flatters your ego...
to believe that alone,
among all the billions of people...
of the Twelve Colonies,
you were chosen for my mission.
Your mission? What mission?
You knew I wanted access
to the Defence mainframe.
The-- Wait a minute.
The Defence mainframe?
What exactly are you saying?
Come on, Gaius.
The communications frequencies?
Deployment schedules?
Unlimited access to every database?
Oh, my God.
I had nothing to do with this.
You know I had nothing
to do with this.
You have an amazing capacity
for self-deception.
How do you do that?
How many people know about me,
specifically? That I'm involved?
And even now, as the fate of your
entire world hangs in the balance...
all you can think about
is how this affects you.
Do you have any idea what
they will do to me if they find out?
They'd probably
charge you with treason.
Treason is punishable
by the death penalty.
- This is unbelievable.
- What are you doing?
- Phoning my attorney.
- That won't be necessary.
He'll know what to do. He'll sort this out.
He's the best in the business.
It won't be necessary,
because in a few hours...
no one will be left
to charge you with anything.
What exactly are you saying?
Humanity's children
are returning home... today.
I'd like to thank
you all again for being here.
And, Elosha, thank you very much
for those wonderful words.
Next is a ceremonial fly-by
by the last Galactica squadron...
led by Captain Lee Adama.
And now it is my great pleasure
to introduce the last commander...
of the Battlestar Galactica,
Commander Adama.
Thank you very much.
The Cylon War is long over...
yet we must not forget the reasons
why so many sacrificed so much...
in the cause of freedom.
The cost of wearing the uniform
can be high...
but--
Sometimes it's too high.
You know, when we fought
the Cylons...
we did it to save ourselves
from extinction.
But we never answered
the question, why?
Why are we as a people
worth saving?
We still commit murder because
of greed, spite, jealousy.
And we still visit all of our sins
upon our children.
We refuse to accept the responsibility
for anything that we've done.
Like we did with the Cylons.
We decided to play God...
create life.
When that life turned against us...
we comforted ourselves
in the knowledge...
that it really wasn't our fault,
not really.
You cannot play God then wash your
hands of the things that you've created.
Sooner or later, the day comes...
when you can't hide from
the things that you've done any more.
You are one surprising son of a bitch.
Colonial Heavy 798, this is Viper 7242.
My callsign is Apollo, and
I'll be your escort back to Caprica.
Copy that, Viper 4272.
Glad to have you with us, Apollo.
Viper 7242, Raptor 31 2.
This is Boomer.Just wanted to say
it was an honour to fly with you, Apollo.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are now en route back to Caprica.
lf you look out the, uh,
starboard window...
you might be able to see one
of Galactica's old Mark Two Vipers...
which will be escorting us back home.
We don't have
any further information yet.
There are no
remaining ships able to leave Caprica.
But no actual enemy
has been sighted yet.
Officials are saying
there doesn't seem any doubt--
What have I done?
What am I gonna do?
There's no way out.
- I know.
- I'm sure you know.
That's your doing, isn't it?
Wait. Wait. There has to be
another way out of here.
I mean-- I mean,
you must have an escape plan.
You're not about to be destroyed
by your own bombs, are you?
How are you leaving?
Gaius, I can't die.
When this body is destroyed,
my memory, my consciousness...
will be transmitted to a new one.
I'll just wake up somewhere else
in an identical body.
You mean there's
more out there like you?
There are 1 2 models.
I'm Number Six.
- I don't want to die. I don't--
- Get down.
C.I.C. to commanding officer.
- Go ahead.
- I'm sorry to disturb you, sir...
but we have a priority one alert
message from Fleet Headquarters.
It was transmitted in the clear.
In the clear?
What does it say?
"Attention all colonial units.
"Cylon attack underway.
This is no drill."
I'll be right there.
Action stations, action stations.
Set condition one throughout the ship.
This is not a drill.
Repeat.
Action stations, action stations.
Set condition one throughout the ship.
This is not a drill.
Repeat.
Action stations, action stations.
Set condition one throughout the ship.
This is not a drill.
- Not a drill? They can't be serious.
- Sounds like it to me.
What are we gonna shoot with?
The ship's got no ammunition.
All right, people, let's go.
Let's get this hangar bay ready
for possible incoming.
What have we got?
Shipping accident?
Combat?
Understood.
Condition one is set.
All decks report ready for action, sir.
Very well.
This is a joke.
The fleet's playing a joke on you.
- It's a retirement prank. Come on.
- I don't think so.
This is the commander.
Moments ago this ship received word of
a Cylon attack against our home worlds...
is under way.
We do not know the size
or the disposition or the strength
of the enemy forces.
But all indications point...
to a massive assault
against Colonial defences.
Admiral Nagala has taken
personal command of the fleet...
aboard the Battlestar Atlantia...
following complete destruction
of Picon Fleet Headquarters...
in the first wave of the attacks.
How, why...
doesn't really matter now.
What does matter is that,
as of this moment, we are at war.
You've trained for this.
You're ready for this.
Stand to your duties,
trust your fellow ship mates...
and we'll all get through this.
Further updates as we get them.
Thank you.
War with the Cylons.
All right, people,
this is what we do.
We're the best, so let's get the old girl
ready to roll and kick some Cylon ass!
Come on! Let's go! Move!
This better be for real.
- Tactical.
- Sir?
Begin a plot of all military units in
the solar system, friendly or otherwise.
- X.O.
- Sir?
We're in a shooting war.
We need something to shoot.
I'll start checking munitions depots.
D., send a signal
to our fighter squadron.
I want positions and tactical status
immediately.
- Yes, sir.
- And get Kara Thrace out of the brig.
Boomer, acknowledge Galactica's
signals and send 'em our position.
Tell them we've detected a formation
of Cylon fighters directly ahead,
and I intend to attack.
Boomer, do you copy?
- Copy that.
- Ease up there, Boomer.
Take a deep breath.
Stand by. Helo?
I show 1 0.
No, no, make that five Cylon raiders
on course 324-mark-1 1 0.
Speed, 7.1 .
Time to intercept,
seven minutes.
- You don't sound too sure.
- A lot of jamming going on.
Cylons are using a lot of sensor decoys.
Sorting through them, but--
Understood.Just take your time,
guide us in. We'll do the rest.
Yes, sir.
So that would put our squadron
about here.
Now, looks like the main fight is
shaping up over here near Virgon's orbit.
But even at top speed,
they're still over an hour away.
Plot a course along this axis.
If we can keep Virgon
between us and the battle...
- we might be able to get pretty close
before the Cylons are even aware.
- At least, sir.
- Commander, ready for duty, sir.
- Good.
Where the hell
did the Cylons come from?
All we know for sure is
they achieved complete surprise
and we're taking heavy losses.
We lost 30 Battlestars
in the opening attack.
- That's a quarter of the fleet.
- I need pilots, and I need fighters.
Pilots you got.
There's 20 of us climbing the walls
down in the ready room.
But fighters--
I think I seem to remember
an entire squadron of fighters...
down on the starboard
hangar deck yesterday.
Yes, sir.
You sure they'll fly?
The reactor's still hot, so all we have to do
is pull the rad buffers from the engine...
refuel it, load the ordnance,
and you're ready to go.
The biggest problem is getting 'em
over to the port launch bay.
- Why can't we use the starboard launch?
- It's a gift shop now.
- Frak me.
- All right, let's go!
Everybody pick a bird!
We're going to the port launch bay!
- What's the latest, D.?
- A lot of confusion.
I keep getting these weird reports
about equipment malfunctions.
- Why is that weird?
- It's the number of malfunctions.
One report said an entire battlestar
lost power...
just before it came in contact
with the enemy.
They said it was like someone
just turned off a switch.
Cylon formation ahead. We're down
to two confirmed Cylons now.
Approaching visual range.
Okay, Boomer, we'll take it from here.
You back way off.
Roger that.
All right, boys and girls,
you break into attack formation.
There might only be two of them, but
I want you to stick with your wingman
and do not get overconfident.
Anybody know
what these things look like?
Pictures I've seen
of the old Cylon fighters were
sort of like a big flying wing.
Those pictures are 40 years old.
- Okay, keep the chatter down.
- CAG, Boomer.
We've got a lot more contacts showin' up.
Looks like a couple of squadrons, at least.
All Vipers, weapons free.
Let's go get 'em.
- What the--
I've lost power.
Jolly. Jolly, take over.
Jolly, can you read me?
What are they doing?
I don't know.
They're going straight in.
Com chatter's gone.
They're not talking any more.
CAG, Boomer.
Do you read?
Boomer, this is CAG.
If you can hear me they must've done
something to our computer system.
Some sort of electronic jamming.
I've never seen anything like this.
There's no cockpits.
Nobody's flying these things.
Oh, my God.
No!
- Boomer, get us out of here!
- Right.
Once again,
we are processing the information
that we have been given...
and I urge you all to try to stay calm.
As we get more information,
I will pass it along to you.
We appreciate your patience.
Thank you.
- What's going on?
- I'm not sure.
- Any luck over there, Captain?
- No. Just picking up
a lot of confusing chatter.
Well, to be honest with you,
I'm kind of glad you're stickin' around.
Makes us all feel better
just seeing you out there.
Well, don't get too comfortable.
This old junker I'm in
was meant for show, not combat.
If we run into a problem
I'll do what I can to protect you.
But the first sign of trouble,
you pour on the speed and you run.
Don't you worry about that.
I got my hand on the throttle.
It hasn't left since I got
that first message.
Colonial Heavy 798 out.
Two missiles now.
-Jam the warheads!
- I'm trying.
Can't find their frequency.
Drop a swallow.
Got two left.
Damn it. Come on!
- Ah, frak!
- What?
- Check the screen ahead.
- Oh. Guess we found the main fight.
- Missile lock!
- We got one left.
- We're hit!
- Oh, really?
Helo-- Hey!
- Are you okay?
- Present!
Stay with me.
Okay, we have a fuel leak.
We have to put down and repair it.
- Nearest world is Caprica.
- Lot of company between us and there.
Yeah.
So we're cruisin'?
Best way to avoid attracting attention.
No power signature,
go in a straight line.
Unless somebody actually
gets close enough to see us...
we just look like a chunk of debris
on the sensors.
I think we have enough inertia
to make it to Caprica 's ionosphere...
then we power up
and find a place to land.
Nice. Nice thinkin' there.
Preliminary reports indicate...
a thermonuclear device
in the 50-megaton range...
was detonated over Caprica City
30 minutes ago.
Nuclear detonations
have been reported...
on the planets Arilon, Icon...
Sagittarian and Geminon.
No reports of casualties,
but they will be high.
How many people
in Caprica City alone?
- Seven million.
- Mourn the dead later.
Right now the best thing we can do
is get this ship into the fight.
- Yes?
- Excuse me.
Um, one of the passengers
has a short wave wireless.
They've heard a report
that Caprica has been nuked.
It has, hasn't it?
Caprica and three other colonies.
I guess I, uh...
I should go make an announcement
or something.
I'll do it.
I'm a member of the political cabinet.
It's my responsibility.
While I'm doing that,
I would ask that you...
contact the Ministry of Civil Defence
and see what we can do to help.
- Including the colonies of Caprica...
- Picon...
- Oh, my God.
Arilon and Tauron.
- What about Trevor?
- What about Geminon?
- Anything on Geminon?
- My kids are on Geminon!
Okay, stop, stop! Please, stop!
Please, I'm trying
to reach the government right now
to get more information.
In the meantime,
we should all be prepared for
an extended stay aboard this ship.
So, uh, you, please,
and you, uh...
take an inventory of
the emergency supplies and rations.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who put you in charge?
Well, that's a good question.
The answer is no one.
But this is a government ship,
and I am the senior government official,
so that puts me in charge.
So why don't you help me out
and go down into the cargo area...
and see about setting it up
as a living space.
Everyone else, please, uh,
please try and stay calm. Thank you.
All right,
this is the passenger manifest.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
My parents moved to Picon
two months ago...
to be closer to my sisters
and their families...
and their grandkids and--
Um--
Madam Secretary,
we've got your comlink.
Yeah.
Thank God you’re not here, Laura.
Thank God.
-Jack.
- l've never seen anything like it.
- Where is the president?
- Dust in the air, thousands of people
wandering the streets.
Where is the president, Jack?
- Is he alive?
- I don't know. I think so.
We hear all kinds of things.
Have the Cylons made any demands?
Do we know what they want?
No. No contact.
I'm pretty sure about that.
Has anyone discussed--
Has anyone discussed
the possibility of surrender?
- Has it been considered?
- After Picon was nuked...
the president offered a complete
unconditional surrender.
- The Cylons didn't even respond.
- Colonial Heavy 789.
- Where?
What should we do?
Uh, copy that.
The Cylons have found us.
- There's an inbound missile.
- Where the hell did our escort go?
Krypter, krypter, krypter.
This is Apollo to Colonial Heavy 798.
l'm declaring an emergency.
Flight systems are off-line.
Need assistance.
That's six.
- How you comin' on that fuel line?
- Almost there.
We'll be airborne pretty soon.
- Okay, that should do it.
- Sharon.
Grab your sidearm.
- Helo--
-Just stand your ground.
Captain, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Uh, my name's Aaron Doral.
I met you before.
Took some publicity photos
with you and your father.
- What are these things?
- Electric pulse generators
from the Galactica.
Really? That's interesting.
Captain, I can't tell you
how glad I am to see you.
Oh? Why is that?
Personally, I'd feel a lot better if someone
qualified were in charge around here.
- Is something wrong with your pilot?
- No.
It's just that he's not the one
giving orders.
This is, uh--
It's a bad situation, isn't it, sir?
- Yes, it is.
- Right.
What if we transfer the "L" containers
from bay three to bay four?
- Then we would have
one, two and three for passengers.
- Yeah, that's doable.
That's a lot of heavy lifting
without dock loaders.
A little hard work is just what
the people need right now.
Captain, good to see you again.
- Likewise. Thanks for the lift.
- You should thank her.
- Start the cargo transfer
and prep bay three for survivors.
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry. Survivors?
As soon as the attack began,
the government ordered
a full stop on all civilian vessels...
so now we've got hundreds
of stranded ships in the solar system.
Some are lost, some are damaged,
some are losing power.
We have enough space on this ship
to accommodate up to 500 people...
and we're going
to need every bit of it.
But we don't even know
what the tactical situation is out there.
The tactical situation
is that we are losing, right, Captain?
- Right.
- So we pick up
as many people as we can...
we try to find a safe haven
to put down.
Captain, I'd like you to look over
the navigational charts...
for a likely place
to hide from the Cylons.
That's all.
Lady's in charge.
That's as close as you get, okay?
Let's just settle down here.
Settle down and no one gets hurt.
I've gotta get on board.
I'll give you 50,000 cubits.
- We're not taking money!
- Sixty thousand!
This isn't a rescue ship.
This is a military vessel,
and we're not taking money.
- Please! You've gotta take my nephew!
- We are not taking money.
- Please!
- Take the children!
What about the children?
- What about my wife?
- Yeah, what about the children?
All right, all right, all right!
Children first. Children.
- Go ahead, baby, go ahead.
- How many are there?
- There's still room, right?
- What about us?
- All right, we can take
three more people.
- Three?
That's the maximum load
if we're gonna break orbit.
- Who chooses the three, you?
- No one chooses. No one.
- Lottery.
Everyone gets a number.
We put the numbers in a box,
take out three.
- That's it. No arguing, no appeal.
- How can we trust you?
And I will shoot the first person
who tries to board before then.
Helo, get your flight manual
and tear out the pages.
Attention. lnbound Dradis contact,
rated highly probable enemy fighter.
All hands standby
for battle manoeuvers.
- Launch Vipers.
- Vipers clear to launch.
Joker, this is Shooter.
I have control. Stand by.
Viper 1 1 04, clear forward.
Nav-con green.
Interval check.
Mag-cap ready.
Cap door open.
Thrust positive and good luck.
Interval... check.
Thrusters positive.
Stand by.
Thrusters fluctuating.
Abort takeoff.
Viper8547, copy that.
Throttle down, tube safe.
- Roger, Viper.
- Frak! Get me outta here!
Go, go, go!
Get the bird out.
Cally, Prosna, on the nose.
Next two wing push.
Last two guide.
Okay, move, move!
Ladder's on. Get her outta there!
Cally, Prosna, figure out what's goin' on.
- Three frakkin' aborts, Chief?
- We're on it, sir.
- It's the pressure reg valve again.
- We should pull it.
We can't.
We don't have a spare.
Bow up half.
Forward left one quarter.
Stern right full.
lnbound enemy contact bearing 247...
range 1 15, closing.
- Let's go!
- Come on, let's go!
- We should pull the valve
and bypass the whole system.
- We can't do that. The relay will blow.
- It'll hold, I'm telling you.
- Just pull the valve!
Firing. Miss!
- Watch it, watch it.
- Engines all ahead full.
Ahead full, sir.
Engines report ahead full.
I got him. Terra 's got him.
Terra 's got him! No!
- I can't get a shot.
I can't get a shot!
- Vipers, stay in formation.
- I can't get a lock.
Oh, wait. I got him, I got him.
- Come on!
- Ready!
Clear the tube! Let's go!
Get her in. Move, move!
- Oh, frak me!
He's irradiating some weapon at me,
but it doesn't seem to have any effect.
All Vipers, systems are go.
- Hold it together, guys.
- Come on.
- I'm all right!
- Radiological alarm.
He's got nukes.
Come on!
Galactica, you've got an inbound nuke.
All Vipers, break.
- Break, break!
- Brace for contact, my friend.
I haven't heard that in a while.
Galactica, Starbuck.
The forward section
of the port flight pod
has sustained heavy damage.
Galactica, you've got
violent decompressions
all along the port flightpod.
Do you read me, Galactica?
Radiation levels within norms.
The hull plating kept out
most of the hard stuff.
Sir, portstern thrusters are locked
open. All bow thrusters non responsive.
We're in an uncontrolled
lateral counter clockwise spin.
Send a D.C. party up to aux control
and have 'em cut all the fuel lines
to the stern thruster.
Okay, we have got buckled supports
all along the port flight pod...
and chain reaction decompressions
occurring everywhere forward
of frame two-- 250.
That's a problem.
- Saul, take personal command
of the D.C. units.
- Me?
Sir, the stern thruster's still locked open.
We need you.
- You're either the X.O. or you're not.
- Casualty list to sickbay.
- Sir.Sickbay is cut off.
Attention. All decks switch
emergency power relays...
to positive and low.
Go, guys, go! Move it! Go!
Chief, we're losing pressure.
The port pod, it's buckling.
We need help!
- Report.
- We've got structural buckling
all along this line.
- We've gotta get those fires out!
- I know. Fire suppressors are down.
Water main is down.
I'm tryin' to fight this fire
with handheld gear.
We've got another decompression
heading toward the port pod.
What are your orders, sir? Sir?
All right, listen. I need you
to get the rest of your D.C. teams
down from the landing bay.
- Give 'em hand--
- No time.
Seal off everything forward of frame 30
and start an emergency vent
of all compartments.
Wait. I've got over a hundred people
trapped up behind frame 34.
I just need a minute to get 'em out.
If we don't seal it off now,
we're gonna lose a lot more
than a hundred men. Seal it off. Now.
- They just need a minute!
- We don't have a minute!
If the fire reaches the hangar pods,
it'll ignite the fuel lines and
we'll lose this ship. Do it!
All hands, seal off all bulkheads
25 through 40.
It's an order.
- Get out of here now! Go!
Get in the compartment!
Venting complete.
Fires are out.
If they remembered their training,
then they had their suits on...
and they were braced
for possible vent action.
There's a lot of rooks in there.
No one's a rookie any more.
One, twenty-seven.
One, two, seven.
Here.
Thank the Lords of Kobol.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Last one.
- Forty-seven.
- Is that yours?
Excuse me. I forgot my glasses.
I must've left them somewhere.
Could you please read this for me?
Hey. Aren't you Gaius Baltar?
I haven't done anything.
This lady has ticket number 47.
This lady here.
- Could you come up here, please?
- Yeah. Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'm giving up my seat.
Like hell.
A civilian should take my place.
You're going.
Look at those clouds.
Sharon, look at those clouds...
and tell me this isn't
the end of everything.
- Helo.
- Whatever future is left is going
to depend on whoever survives.
Give me one reason why
l'm a better choice than one of
the greatest minds of our time.
- Helo--
- You can do this without me.
I know you can.
You've proven it.
Get on board.
- What?
I think you better go.
Stay back, stay back.
It's over. It's over!
Stay back. Stay back. Stay back.
lt's over! lt's over!
It's over!
Get down! Get down!
This is an official
Colonial government broadcast.
All ministers and officials
should now go to case orange.
Repeat. This is an official
Colonial government broadcast.
All ministers and officials
should now go to case orange.
It's an automated message. It's designed
to be sent out in case the president...
the vice-president and most of
the cabinet are dead or incapacitated.
I need you to send my I.D. code
back on the exact same frequency.
Yes, ma'am.
"D"as in dog...
dash 4, 5, 6...
dash 3, 4, 5...
dash "A" as in apple.
Thank you.
How far down?
Forty-third in line of succession.
I know all 42 ahead of me,
from the president down.
Most of us served with him
in the first administration.
Some of them came with him
from the mayor's office.
I was there with him
on his first campaign.
I never really liked politics.
I kept telling myself I was getting out...
but he had this way about him.
Just couldn't say no.
Thank you.
We'll need a priest.
Please raise you right hand
and repeat after me.
"I, Laura Roslin...
I, Laura Roslin...
"do now avow and affirm...
do now avow and affirm...
"that I take the office of the president
of the Twelve Colonies of Kobol...
that I accept the office of the--
that I accept the office of the president
of the Twelve Colonies of Kobol...
"and that I will protect and defend
the sovereignty of the Colonies...
and that I will protect and defend
with every fibre of my being."
with every fibre of my being.
- Attention.
Loose, one E.M. C. electricalconduit
on decks 15 and 16.
Use extreme caution.
Loose, one E.M. C. electrical conduit
on decks 15 and 16.
Use extreme caution.
What was the final count?
Twenty-six walked out.
Eighty-five didn't.
There's a munitions depot
at Ragnar anchorage.
Boy, it's a super bitch
to anchor a ship there.
The book says that there are 50 pallets
of class "D" warheads in storage there.
- They should also have all the missiles
and small arms munitions we need--
- Go verify that.
Sir.
- Do you know
how many we lost?
- Yes.
Set up a temporary morgue
in hangar bay "B."
Forty seconds, sir.
All I needed was 40 seconds.
Eighty-five of my people.
I told--
I told that son of a bitch.
He's the X.O. of this ship.
Don't you dare forget that.
Now, he made a tough decision.
If it had been me,
I would've made the same one.
Forty seconds, sir.
Resume your post, Chief.
Munitions depot confirmed,
but we have two problems.
One, the Ragnar station is at least
three days away at best speed.
Two, the entire Cylon fleet
is between here and there.
- Specialist.
- Sir?
- Bring me our position.
- Yes, sir.
- You don't want to do this.
- I know I don't.
Because any sane man wouldn't.
It's been, what, 20, 22 years?
- We trained for this.
- Training is one thing, but...
if we're off on our calculations
by even a few degrees...
we could end up
in the middle of the sun.
No choice.
Colonel Tigh, please plot
a hyperlight jump from our position
to the orbit of Ragnar.
Yes, sir.
Priority message, sir.
Engineering, spin up
F. T.L. drives one and two.
- Spinning up F. T.L. drives one and two.
- Lieutenant Gaeta, break out the F.T.L.
tables and warm up the computers.
- We are making a jump.
- Admiral Nagala is dead.
Battlestar Atlantia has been destroyed.
So has the Triton, Solaria, Columbia.
The list goes on.
Who's the senior officer?
Who's in command?
Send a message
to all the Colonial military units.
Use priority channel one.
Message begins...
"Am taking command of fleet."
Geminon Liner 1 701 ,
this is Colonial Heavy 798.
No, strike that.
This is Colonial One.
- Go ahead, Colonial One.
- We have you in sight.
Will approach
your starboard docking hatch.
Copy that, Colonial One.
Thank the Lords of Kobol you're here.
We've been without main power
for over two hours now.
What is it?
"To all Colonial units.
Am taking command of fleet.
"All units ordered to rendezvous
at Ragnar anchorage for regroup
and counter attack.
"Acknowledge by
same encryption protocol.
Adama."
Captain Apollo, please inform
Commander Adama...
that we are currently involved
in rescue operations...
and we require his assistance.
Ask him how many hospital beds
he has available and how long
it will take him to get here.
- I, uh--
- Yes?
I'm not sure he's going to respond
very well to that request.
Then tell him...
this comes directly from the president
of the Twelve Colonies...
- and it's not a request.
- Yes, sir.
And, sir...
Apollo's just my call sign.
My name is Lee Adama.
I know who you are.
But "Captain Apollo" has
a nice ring to it, don't you think?
Is this a joke?
- Are they within voice range?
- Yes, sir.
Colonial One, Galactica.
Galactica Actual
wishes to speak with Apollo.
This is Apollo.
Go ahead, Actual.
Sir.
Hey, are you--
Is your ship all right?
We're both fine.
Thanks for asking.
Is your ship's F.T.L. functioning?
That's affirmative.
Then you're ordered to bring yourself
and all of your passengers...
to the rendezvous point.
Acknowledge.
Acknowledge... receipt of message.
- What the hell does that mean?
- It means I heard you.
You're gonna have to do
a lot better than that, Captain.
We're engaged in rescue operations.
You are to abort your mission
immediately...
and proceed to Ragnar.
The president has given me
a direct order.
You're talking about
the secretary of education.
We're in the middle of a war...
and you're taking orders
from a school teacher?
- We got trouble.
Stand by, Galactica.
What?
Uh--
Inbound Cylon fighters.
How long till they get here?
E.T.A., two minutes.
- He's right. We have to go now--
- No.
- We can't defend this ship agai--
- We're not going to abandon
all those people.
- But, sir, if we stay in--
- I've made my decision, Captain.
You're the president.
- All right, then.
- Permission to go below?
Sir, we have a remote sensor telemetry
at Captain Apollo's location...
and two enemy fighters
closing in on their coordinates.
Colonial One, this is Galactica.
Apollo, you have inbound
enemy fighters coming toward you.
Get out of there!
Apollo! Apollo!
Lee, get-- Lee!
Fifty-kiloton thermonuclear detonation.
Cylons moving off, sir.
Resume... jump prep.
Resume jump prep.
Attention, all hands.
Jump prep under way.
Set condition two throughout the ship.
- Lieutenant, what did you do
to my Viper?
I wondered why the engine gave out.
We're gonna have to pull
the whole mounting. Get the high lift.
I don't know how you managed
to fly this thing, much less land it.
It's not something I wanna
think about now. Where's Prosna?
He's gotta get that fraking gimbal locked
or I'll have his ass.
He's dead, sir.
He died in the fire.
- How many did we lose?
- Eighty-five.
Right.
Oh, Lieutenant--
I don't know if you
heard about Apollo, but--
Heard what?
Right.
Any word on Sharon?
No, sir.
You okay, Chief?
Chief?
Get back to work.
- Three, two, one, launch.
Drone deployed and transmitting.
Now they'll come find us?
There's a lot of interference
around here. A lot of noise.
Keeps my wireless from working.
But hopefully, once
that communications pod I launched
gets far enough away from here...
a Colonial ship will pick up the signal
and start lookin' for us.
Is everyone on Caprica dead?
I don't know.
My dad is in the Colonial fleet.
They told me he's missing...
but I think he's dead too.
What's your name?
Boxey.
You know something? Both my parents
died when I was little too.
Who do you live with?
A bunch of other people
on a ship called the Galactica.
You know what
I love about you, Gaius?
You're a survivor.
The board is green.
The ship reports ready to jump, sir.
Then take us to Ragnar, Colonel.
- Lieutenant Gaeta.
- Yes, sir?
Execute the jump.
All decks prepare
for immediate F.T.L. jump.
The clock is running.
Ten...
nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five...
four...
three...
- two...
- I hate this part.
one.
Jumping.
Report.
Taking a bearing now.
We appear to be in geosynchronous orbit
directly above the Ragnar anchorage.
- Colonel Tigh.
- Sir?
Let's update your chart for a course...
right down into the eye of the storm.
Yes, sir.
Attention, magazine
safety officers. Report to C.I. C.
Captain Apollo?
- That was fun.
I think it worked.
What exactly did you do?
I basically just used the-- the hyperdrive
to manipulate the energy coils.
I put out-- put out a big pulse
of electro--
magnetic energy that must've
disabled the warheads.
Oh--
I'm-- I'm hoping that it
looked like a nuclear explosion.
Oh, so that's what that was.
- So, uh--
- Did it fool the Cylons?
I don't know.
But if-if they weren't fooled,
then they'd be on top of us by now.
Does the rest of the fleet
know about this trick?
I doubt it. It was just a theory
we toyed with in war college. But--
It never used to work
during war games.
The Cylons would see right through it
and destroy the targets anyway.
The lesson here is not to ask
follow-up questions but simply to say...
"Thank you, Captain Apollo,
for saving our collective asses."
You're welcome.
- Now, if I could suggest--
- Evacuate the passenger liner...
and get the hell out of here
before the Cylons realize their mistake.
I'm right with you, Captain.
- Five seconds to turn three.
- Five seconds. Aye, sir.
- And turn.
- Bow pitch positive one half.
Stern pitch negative one quarter.
Bow yaw negative three-quarters.
Crossing into the ionosphere.
All hands, be ready for some chop.
Lords of Kobol, hear my prayer.
Take the souls of your
sons and daughters lost this day...
especially that of Lee Adama,
into your hands.
- And hard seal.
- Hard seal secured, sir.
- Copy that, sir. We show hard seal as well.
Go find me some bullets, Chief.
Copy that, sir.
All right, get your gear.
Let's move out.
All right, people,
let's be quick about this.
- Cally, find the genny,
get some lights on in here.
- Yes, Chief.
Let's find out where the lift is,
get it fired up.
- Come on.
- Excuse me.
My husband, he's in
the Colonial fleet in Geminon.
The Colonial fleet in Geminon.
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
- If you'll head right this way.
- Have you heard anything of Geminon?
Come on.
Captain, I've got two
communication pods left, sir, but that's it.
No jiggers, no drones,
no markers, nothing.
Well, at least you've still
got your electronic suite.
That old crate of mine
can barely navigate from "A" to "B."
That old crate may have
saved your life, sir.
- How's that?
- The Viper Mark Sevens--
the Cylons shut them down like
they threw a switch or something.
And I've been hearing
reports like that from all over.
The only fighters that are having
any success at all are either old
or in need of some major overhaul.
- Is that him?
- Yeah.
Hope he's worth it!
- Sorry, sir.
- Don't be. I hope he's worth it too.
Dr Baltar,
Captain Lee Adama.
The president's asked to see you, sir.
- President Adar is alive?
- No, I'm afraid Adar is dead.
President Laura Roslin
was sworn in a couple of hours ago.
Oh. Who?
If you’ll come with me,
uh, she's this way.
- If there's anything we can do.
- We'll be here.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you so very much.
Oh, Dr Baltar,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
We met at last year's
Caprica City Symposium.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Uh, you'll have to forgive me.
- I'm-l'm bad with faces.
- Oh, no, that's perfectly all right.
I'm sure I wouldn't
remember me either.
Doctor, I need you to serve as my chief
scientific consultant and analyst...
regarding the Cylons
and their technology.
I'd be honoured, Madam President.
- Lieutenant Valerii-- Is it Valerii?
- Yes.
I understand that your ship has
a limited faster-than-light capability?
Uh, yes, sir. The Raptor was designed
to make short jumps ahead of the fleet...
scout for enemy ships,
then jump back and report.
I want you to go out there
and find as many survivors as you can
and bring them back to this position.
We will then form a convoy.
We will guide them
out of the combat zone and into safety.
Yes, sir.
Everybody hold fast.
- I don't want any trouble.
- Okay, let's talk.
- But I'm not goin' to jail.
- What?
You understand me?
I am not goin' to jail.
Nobody's takin' you to jail.
Just calm down.
Frakin' right, you're not.
We're not the police. We're not here
to arrest you. Now put your gun down.
Yeah, maybe.
So who the hell are you?
We're from Colonial Fleet.
We just came to get some equipment
from the station to get back in the fight.
- What fight?
- You don't know?
- Know what?
- There's a war on.
Give me your weapon.
You think I'm stupid or somethin',
is that it? You think I'm stupid?
You expect me to believe that?
I want passage outta here!
I want a safe transport ship with
an untraceable jump system, okay?
Now!
Look, I don't have time
to argue with you, so here's the deal.
We've got over 2,000
people on that ship.
Now, if you think you can shoot
every single one of us, fine.
But if not,
get the hell outta my way!
- Okay--
- Now!
Okay.
Get his weapon.
If he moves, shoot him.
I see they've put you to work.
Ignoring me won't help.
No, I've decided you're
an expression of my, uh...
subconscious mind playing itself out
during my waking states.
So I'm only in your head?
Exactly.
Hm.
Have you considered
the possibility that I can...
very well exist only in your head...
without being a hallucination?
Maybe you see and hear me
because while you were sleeping...
I implanted a chip in your brain
that transmits my image...
right into your conscious mind.
No, see, that's me again.
My subconscious self
is expressing irrational fears...
which I also choose to ignore.
What are you working on?
If you were really a chip in my head,
I wouldn't have to tell you,
now, would I?
Indulge me.
I'm trying to figure out how you managed
to pull this kind of an attack.
You virtually shut down the entire
defence network without firing a shot.
Entire squadrons lost power
just as they engaged the enemy.
The C.N.P. is a navigation program
but you, uh--
You made changes to the program.
You said you were building in...
back doors for your company
to exploit later.
- All true, in a sense.
- That was your job.
Officially.
Unofficially, I had other motives.
We had something, Gaius.
Something... special.
This is insane.
And what I want
most of all is for you to love me.
Love you?
Of course, Gaius.
Don't you understand?
God is love.
No!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Take it easy, guys.
Just slow down.
We don't know much more than that.
It's just imperative that we get
our equipment and get out of here.
What's in there?
Stuff.
Get a light.
Where's your spaceship?
Docked on the other side of the station.
Be careful!
Don't stack 'em so high.
Okay, those warheads over there--
Here's the deal.
They would've brought a nice price
on the open market.
So you're an arms dealer, huh?
People have a right
to protect themselves.
I just supply the means.
You don't look too good.
Be careful with that, all right?
Hey, be careful with that!
Look out!
Commander?
Commander Adama?
Stay back, stay back! It's hot.
It's hot. It's hot. It's unstable.
You guys, go back to the ship.
We need hand lifts...
fire equipment
and a plasma torch.
- Go!
- Wait! Wait, Chief. Listen.
- Commander Adama?
- Yeah.
Anybody hurt out there?
No, sir. We've got some equipment
comin', sir. We're gonna get you
out of there right away.
No!
No, get all the bullets
and equipment into the ship.
Don't waste anybody
on anything else.
- Is there another way out of here?
- Yeah.
Listen, uh-- Listen,
we're gonna go out another way.
- Sir, I don't think that's a wise idea.
- You got your orders.
Tell Colonel Tigh
he's in command until I return.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Most of the passengers
are from Geminon or Picon...
but we've got people from every colony.
Give Billy a copy of
your passenger manifest and a list
of all your emergency supplies.
All right.
What about the power situation?
Our batteries are running pretty low.
Captain Apollo will be
making an engineering survey
of all the ships this afternoon.
Uh, actually the Captain said
it'll be more like...
this evening before
he can coordinate the survey.
All right, this evening then.
But you will get your needs
tended to, Captain.
You have my word on it.
- Thank you, Madam President.
- You're welcome.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Cami.
Hi, Cami. I'm Laura.
Are you alone?
She was travelling
with her grandparents...
but grandmother's having some health
problems since the announcement.
Not to worry, though.
We're taking care of her.
My parents are going to meet me
at the spaceport in Caprica City.
The spaceport. I see.
We're going out for dinner,
and I'm having chicken pie...
and then we're going home,
and then Daddy's going to read to me...
and then I'm going to bed.
Uh, message from Lieutenant Valerii.
She's found a fuel refinery ship
filled with Tylium.
Oh, good.
About time we caught a break. That
brings us up to about 60 ships so far?
- Not bad for a few hours work.
- No, sir.
But only about forty of those ships
have faster-than-light capabilities.
We should start transferring people
off the sub-lights onto the F.T.L. 's
as soon as possible.
All right.
Colonial One, Raptor 312.
I'm back, and I brought a friend.
Welcome back, Boomer.
We got a lot of thirsty ships here eager
to make your friend's acquaintance.
- Did you pick up any
other contacts out there?
- Negative. There's no one left.
- Got a visitor!
- We see him. Can you jam his signal?
Trying.
It definitely scanned us
before it jumped.
We have to go. Now.
Cylons'll be here any minute.
- Will they track us through a jump?
- No, sir. It's impossible.
- Theoretically impossible.
- Theoretically.
There are still thousands
of people on the sub-light ships.
- We can't just leave them.
- I agree.
We should use every second to get as
many people off the sub-lights as we can.
We can wait to jump until we pick up
a Cylon strike force moving--
We're easy targets. They're gonna
jump in the middle of our ships...
with nukes and wipe us out
before we have the chance to react.
We can't leave them behind.
You'll be sacrificing thousands of people.
But we'll be saving tens of thousands.
Sorry to make it a numbers game, but we're
talking about the survival of our race.
We don't have the luxury of
taking risks and hoping for the best...
because if we lose,
we lose everything.
And Madam President, this is a decision
that needs to be made right now.
Order the fleet
to jump to Ragnar immediately.
Madam President, something else
you should be aware of.
I have cancer.
I know.
Little things.
Couple of comments you made.
My prognosis is doubtful.
I wish I could say it was
the least of my worries.
But the world is coming to and end...
and all I can think about is that I have
cancer and I'm probably going to die.
How selfish is that?
It's not selfish.
It's human.
Is there something
you wanted to say to me?
Well, I-I just thought you should know.
That little girl you met earlier, Cami.
Her ship can't make the jump.
Thank you.
This is your pilot speaking.
Passengers please take your seats
and stand by to jump.
Thank you.
Set E.S.B. trajectory.
- Colonial One, for
God's sake, you can't just leave us here.
- Set.
- Cycle cryo-fans.
- Colonial One, this is Picon 26.
- I can't believe you want us
to leave these people behind.
- Cycled.
At least tell us where you're going.
We'll follow at sub-light.
- Please!
- No.
If they're captured,
then the Cylons know too.
I've got 50 people on board.
Colonial One, do you copy this?
- Spinning up F.T.L. drive now.
- Don't leave us here.
Show a little humanity.
We don't have any weapons.
All ships prepare to jump
on our mark. Five...
- Colonial One, please respond.
- four...
- May the Lords of Kobol
protect those souls we leave behind.
- three...
- I’ve got Dradis contacts.
We've got targets heading this way.
- two...
- I see them too. Are they Colonials?
- one...
- Oh, my God, they're Cylons!
-mark.
I hope you people rot in hell for this!
- You all right?
I'm fine. It’s just
somethin' about this place.
What about this place?
Yeah, ever since I got here,
somethin' in the air affects my allergies.
You always keep me in front of you.
Military training, right?
Never turn your back on a stranger?
That kind of thing?
Suspicion and distrust.
That's-- That's military life, right?
So you're a gun-dealer-philosopher,
I take it, right?
I'm an observer of human nature.
When you get right down to it...
humanity is not a pretty race.
I mean, we're only one step away from...
beating each other with clubs like
savages fighting over scraps of meat.
Maybe the Cylons are
God's retribution for our many sins.
What if God decided he made a mistake...
and he decided to give souls
to another creature, like the Cylons?
God didn't create the Cylons.
Man did.
And I'm pretty sure we didn't
include a soul in the programming.
Let's go.
How about you go first for a while?
Copy that. Chief says we're
lookin' at three hours minimum...
before we have all the warheads
in our magazines.
The book says there's also 50 tons
of quandal--
Action stations! Action stations!
We have multiple contacts through
the storm towards the anchorage.
- Looks like more than 50 ships.
- Cut us loose from the station.
Launch the alert fighters.
Set condition one
throughout the ship.
- Prepare to launch--
- Wait!
Wait. I'm getting
Colonial signals now.
Confirm that.
Don’t just accept friendly l.D.
Confirmed, sir.
Incoming ships are friendly.
Action stations stand down.
The leadship is requesting permission
to come along side, sir.
They say--
They say they have the president
of the colonies aboard.
Grant their request.
We are in the middle of repairing
and rearming this ship.
We can't afford to lose a single man
off the line to start caring for refugees.
We have 50,000 people out there.
Some of them are hurt.
Our priority has to be
caring for refugees--
My priority is
preparing this ship for combat.
In case you haven't heard,
there's a war on.
Colonel...
the war is over, and we lost.
- We'll see about that.
- Oh, yes, we will.
In the meantime, however,
as president of the colonies...
- I'm giving you a direct order...
- You don't give orders on this ship!
- to provide men and equipment!
- Hold on, Colonel.
At least give us a couple
of disaster pods, huh?
Us?
Sir, we have 50,000 people
out there. Fifty thousand.
Some of them are sick,
some are wounded.
Two disaster pods, Colonel.
You can do that.
Because you're the old man's son
and because he's gonna be...
so damned happy you're alive.
Okay. Two pods.
But no personnel.
You get them yourselves and
you distribute them yourselves.
And you are all off this ship
before we jump back.
You report to the flight deck.
You're senior pilot now, Captain.
Yes, sir.
Knowing this place is gonna be a
museum, they might have given us a map.
- Oh, I think it's this way.
- Yeah?
Yep.
As soon as the other magazine's loaded,
I want a status report on
Commander Adama's whereabouts.
Okay.
Dualla. Hi.
Um, we're kind of lost... again.
We need to get to the C.I.C.
Could you--
It's this way.
There's someone
I want you to meet.
A new crew member.
And he's gonna need some quarters.
I think I can manage that.
Hey.
I thought you were dead.
Well, I thought
you were in hack.
It's-- It's good to be wrong.
Well, you-you should be
used to it by now.
Everyone has a skill.
So, how-- How go the repairs?
On track. Another hour
and she'll be ready to launch.
So I guess you're the new CAG now.
- Yeah, that's what they tell me.
- That's good.
That's the last thing I want.
Not a big enough dipstick
for the job.
Attention,
D. C. T. 14, report to port hanger bay.
Attention, D. C. T. 14,
report to port hanger bay.
I'll be in the squadron...
ready room.
Hey.
Does your father know
you're still breathing?
I'll let him know.
What is it about this place?
What's it doin' to me?
Must be your allergies.
- I don't have allergies.
- I didn't think so.
What you got is silica pathways
to the brain...
or whatever it is you call
that thing you pretend to think with.
It's decomposing as we speak.
It's the storm, isn't it?
It puts out something.
Something you discovered
has an effect on Cylon technology.
That's it, isn't it?
And this is a refuge.
That's why you put a fleet out here.
Last ditch effort to hide
from the Cylon attack, right?
Well, it's not enough, Adama.
I mean,
I've been here for... hours.
Once they find you...
it won't take them
that long to destroy you.
They'll be in and out
before they even get a headache.
Maybe.
But you--
but you won't find out because
you'll be dead in a few minutes.
How does that make you feel,
if you can feel?
I can feel more than you could
ever conceive, Adama.
But I won't die.
When this body dies, my consciousness
will be transferred to another one.
And when that happens--
I think I'll tell the others
exactly where you are...
and then I think
that they'll come here...
and they'll kill all of you...
and I'll be here watching it happen.
You know what I think?
I think if you could've
transferred outta here...
you would've done it
long before now.
I think the storm's radiation
really clogged up your connection.
You're not goin' anywhere.
You're stuck in that body.
It doesn't matter.
Sooner or later...
the day comes when you can't hide
from the things you've done.
So let me get this straight.
You're saying that the Cylons...
found a way to use your navigation
program to disable our ships?
Essentially, uh, yes.
I think they're using the C.N.P.
to infect your ships with some kind
of computer virus...
which makes them susceptible
to Cylon commands.
Uh, well you can see
we-we do have...
your C.N.P. navigation program
here on Galactica.
But our computers
aren't networked...
so it's never been loaded into
primary memory or even test run.
Good. Well, that's good.
You shouldn't have any problems then.
Still, I should, uh...
purge all remaining references to it
that appear on your memory tapes.
Right. I should probably
retrofit the newer Vipers as well.
Uh, here's the checklist
for the C.I.C. computer.
Ah. Thank you.
- Must be hard for you.
- Mm.
What do you mean?
Just having something you created...
twisted and used like this
must be...
horrible.
The guilt?
I remember you telling me once...
that guilt was something
small people feel...
when they run out of excuses
for their behaviour.
It is... hard. Uh--
I feel... responsible, in a way...
uh, for what happened.
But you don't. That's part
of the reason I fell in love with you.
You have a clarity of spirit.
You're not burdened by...
conscience or guilt or regret.
I bet. Uh--
Just try to remember
it's not really your fault.
I mean--
You didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
It's not like you knew
what they were gonna do.
It's not like you knew you were lying.
Not like you were breaking the law.
Not like you cheat on women.
Not like the world's coming apart
and all you can think about...
is Gaius Baltar.
No. No, I know...
exactly what you're saying.
I know.
Right. Well--
Just let me know
if you need anything.
You know, I really do hope
you make it out of here alive.
I think we can have
a real future together.
Yeah, that'll be special.
You don't have to be sarcastic.
Especially when I'm trying to help you.
How are you trying to help me?
How-How are you trying to do that?
See anything there that looks familiar?
No. Should l?
Now you mention it, l--
I have seen something like it...
somewhere before.
Yes.
ln your briefcase.
You used to carry it around with you.
You said it was
your electronic organizer.
That would be a lie.
Then it's--
It's a Cylon device.
That would follow.
- Did you--
- No.
Not my job.
- Then that means--
- Say it.
There's another Cylon aboard this ship.
- Everything okay there, Doc?
- Uh, yeah, fine.
I've just finished erasing the program
from the defence mainframe.
I'm just going to check it again.
Attention. Recovering spacecraft aft.
Repeat, recovering spacecraft aft.
You're not helping.
I'm sorry. How can I help?
Well, for a start,
you can tell me what that is.
- Honestly, I don't know.
- Well, it hasn't exploded.
Yet.
I'm just guessing.
- I have to warn them.
- I do.
- How do you propose to do that?
"Oh, look, a Cylon device."
"Really? Well, how do you know what
a Cylon device looks like, Doctor?"
"Oh, I forgot to mention
I'm familiar with their technology...
because I've been having sex
with a Cylon for the last two years now."
I'll come up with something.
I love surprises.
Speaking of sex.
I--
I don't think that's such
a good idea right now, really.
- Really.
- Why not?
No one will know.
It'll be our little secret.
- Doctor.
- Yes?
You asked for a report on how many
civilian ships had your C.N.P. program.
Right. Thank you.
Are you all right?
You look a little flushed.
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking someone else might need
to be implicated as a Cylon agent.
He doesn't seem the type.
And I don't remember
seeing him at any of the Cylon parties.
Funny.
He's a civilian.
He's an outsider.
And he's been aboard
this ship for weeks...
with virtually unlimited access
to this very room.
There is one problem though.
Morally?
Practically.
So far, aboard this ship,
no one even suspects...
the Cylons look like us now.
This just gets worse and worse.
Now the Cylons look like us.
Down to our blood.
You realize what this means.
They could be anywhere.
Could be anyone.
I've had time to think about it.
So what do we do?
I don't know.
How we doing on the warheads?
Magazine two is secure.
Three and four within the hour.
Something else--
Lee is alive.
Commander?
I'm sorry.
I, uh, gotta go.
Ship's doctor says at first glance...
everything in Leoben's body
appears human.
Internal organs,
lymphatic system, the works.
Well, the, uh, tissue sample yielded
unique chemical compounds...
during the cremation that revealed
the nature of the samples to be synthetic.
- So, he was a Cylon.
- Yes, he was.
And now we have a problem.
A big one.
If the Cylons look like us...
then any one of us
could be a Cylon.
That's-- That's a very
frightening possibility.
We need a way to screen
human from Cylon.
And that's where you come in.
Me? Um--
Rumour has it you're a genius.
Well, uh...
I'll certainly give it my all...
Commander.
Keep this to yourself for now.
We don't want start panic or people
to begin accusing their neighbours...
of being Cylons because they don't
brush their teeth in the morning.
I'll be very discreet.
You understand the mission.
Put my head outside the storm,
look around...
Listen for wireless traffic,
come home.
No heroics.
This is strictly recon.
- Look, listen, return.
- You don't have to worry about me.
My taste for heroics vanished about the
time I engaged that first Cylon fighter.
Lee...
Zak failed basic flight.
- What?
- Or at least he should have.
But he didn't...
because I passed him.
His technique was sloppy,
and he had no feel for flying.
But I passed him...
because he and I--
Because I felt something, and I let it
get in the way of doing my job.
And I couldn't fail him.
Why are you telling me this?
Why-Why now?
It's the end of the world, Lee.
I thought I should confess my sins.
Set!
- Halt! No sudden moves.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute, guys.
Down on your knees
and cross your ankles now!
All right.
J-J-Just wait a minute.
- W-What? What do you want?
- Hands behind your head.
If he's really a Cylon, why hasn't the
storm radiation made him sick by now?
Well, I can only theorize that
it takes a while for the storm's effects...
to become readily apparent
on Cylon physiology.
By the time he'd encountered Leoben,
he'd been here for several hours.
I don't suppose it matters to you
that I am not a Cylon!
Smartest thing you could do right now
would be to shut your mouth.
Are you sure?
One can never be
a hundred per cent sure.
B-But the evidence, uh--
The evidence seems conclusive.
Basically-- Basically all I did
was I expanded on--
on your doctor's analysis
of Leoben's corpse.
I then went around
the C.I.C. discreetly...
taking random hair samples of people
who'd been working there.
I subjected that to a special form
of spectral-analysis...
that I've been experimenting on
for quite some time now.
I then wrote a
clinical computer subroutine...
to screen that for
synthetic chemical combinations.
Uh-- His ones-- His samples
were the only samples...
to register as synthetic,
as you can see.
- I'll take your word for it.
- Right.
And just like that...
Dr Baltar invents
the "Amazing Cylon Detector."
Gentlemen, I understand your concerns.
This is a difficult situation.
But I think you need to take a step back,
take a deep breath...
and really look at
what you're doing here!
I want everyone aboard
this ship screened.
- No exceptions.
- No problem.
Whoa! Whoa! Look,
I-I-I don't know about anybody else...
but I can tell you
that I-I-I'm human.
I'm from Oasis.
It's a couple stops out of Caprica City.
I-I grew up on the south side. I went
to the Kobol Colleges o-on Geminon!
I-I studied public relations!
Oh, by the way, I-I don't know
if this is important--
might be important,
might not be important--
but earlier when I was on the C.I.C.,
I noticed that Mr Doral...
seemed to be doing, um--
Well, I'm not exactly sure
what it was that he was doing...
but he seemed very interested
in this odd looking device...
on the bottom of
the, uh, Dradis console.
- What are you-- What?
- Yep.
We should really make a copy
of your brain pattern at some point.
What device? What are you
talking about? He's lying.
- He is frakkin' lying!
- Combat, this is Tigh.
- Isolate the Dradis console immediately.
- Don't listen to him!
Nobody comes near it
until I get up there.
Lords of Kobol.
This isn't happening to me.
- Colonel, your orders, sir?
- If he moves, kill him.
You mixed the samples up!
I'm human!
- It's not hot, sir.
- Very well. Remove it.
Uh, I don't see anything
in the maintenance records, sir.
But I'm pretty sure I first noticed it
about a week ago.
You didn't say anything, didn't investigate
a new piece of equipment...
that just appeared in C.I.C.?
No, sir. I just assumed that
it was part of the museum.
- Sorry, sir. There's no excuse.
- You're not alone, Lieutenant.
Any one of us should have seen the
perfectly obvious staring us in the face.
Especially the ship's X.O.
- What should I do with it, sir?
- Take it to Dr Baltar.
I've given him clearance.
He's become our resident Cylon expert.
Have him take it to the lab,
figure out whether it's a bug...
or whatever the hell it is.
In the meantime, I want
every inch of this ship...
searched for any other equipment
that just appeared in the last week.
Starbuck, Galactica.
You should be approaching turn eight.
Copy that.
Starting to lose wireless contact.
Making the final turn now.
Galactica, Starbuck.
I've reached the threshold.
- Galactica, do you read me?
That can't be right.
As you were.
And medical supplies
are running low again...
Madam President.
Uh, three ships have reported
engine trouble and want to know...
when they'll be receiving
engineering assistance from Galactica.
It's a good question. Hello.
Commander, have a seat.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Keep going, Billy.
Uh, the captain
of the Astral Queen...
wants you to know that he's got
nearly 500 convicted criminals...
under heavy guard in his cargo hold.
They were being transported
to a penal station...
- when the attack happened.
- Oh, great.
He wants to know
what to do with them.
- What to do with them?
- Well, with food and medical supplies...
being what they are,
I think he's considering just--
No, no. No, we're not gonna start that.
They're still human beings.
Tell the captain I expect daily reports
on the well-being of his prisoners.
And if there's any mysterious deaths...
the Astral Queen may find herself
on her own...
without the Galactica's protection.
- Yes, Madam President.
- Thank you, Billy.
You planning to stage
a military coup?
- What?
- Do you plan to declare martial law...
take over the government?
- Of course not.
- Then you do acknowledge...
my position as president as constituted
under the Articles of Colonization.
Ms Roslin...
my primary objective
at the present time...
is to repair the Galactica...
and continue to fight.
What we know at this moment is there
are 50,000 civilian refugees out there...
who don't stand a chance
without your ship to protect them.
We're aware of the tactical situation.
And I'm sure that you'll all be safe here
on Ragnar after we leave.
After you leave?
- Where're you going?
- To find the enemy.
We're at war.
That's my mission.
I honestly don't know why...
I have to keep telling you this.
But the war is over.
It hasn't begun yet.
That's insane.
You would rather that we run?
Yes, absolutely.
That is the only sane thing to do here.
Exactly that-- run.
We leave this solar system,
and we don't look back.
- And we go where?
- I don't know.
Another star system. Another planet.
Somewhere where
the Cylons won't find us.
You can run if you’d like.
This ship will stand and it will fight.
I'm gonna be straight with you here.
The human race is
about to be wiped out.
We have 50,000 people left,
and that's it.
Now, if we are even
going to survive as a species...
then we need to get the hell out of here,
and we need to start having babies.
Excuse me.
I didn't get an accurate count.
It looks like two base stars
with 10 fighter squadrons...
and two recon drone
detachments patrolling the area.
- Starbuck, were you followed?
- Negative. No sign of pursuit.
By the way they were deployed...
I'd say they're waiting for us
to come to them.
Bring her home.
Thank you, Starbuck.
Continue present course.
Return to visual contact
and stand by for instructions.
- Captain--
- Copy that, Galactica. Starbuck out.
Lieutenant Gaeta, stay, please.
How the hell did they find us?
Doesn't really matter.
They've got us.
- Why aren't they coming in after us, sir?
- Why should they?
They can just sit out there and wait us out.
What difference does it make to them?
They're machines. We're the ones
that need food, medicine, fuel.
I'm not gonna play their game.
I'm not gonna go out there
and try to fight 'em.
Can we plot a jump
from inside the storm?
With all this E.M. interference
muckin' up the F.T.L. fix?
I agree, sir. I don't think
we should attempt a jump...
until we've cleared
the storm threshold.
Have to be quick about it though.
They'll launch everything they have
first glimpse they get.
Stick our nose out just far enough
to get a good F.T.L. fix, then jump?
- Hi.
I-I'm getting ready to head back
to the transport.
Oh.
- What about the civilians?
- They're probably safe for the time being.
You mean leave them here?
The Cylons may not even know
they're here in the first place.
- They're probably only after us.
- That's one hell of an assumption.
Well, we can't very well
cram 50,000 men...
women and children
aboard this ship.
I know this is awkward and all...
but what happened
in the passage way was--
Yeah.
I don't know why
I did that. Sorry.
I'm not suggesting that. I'm just
saying we can't leave them behind.
- They should jump with us.
- I don't see how we can manage that...
- without jeopardizing our ship.
- We pick a jump spot...
far enough outside
the combat zone--
What the hell is outside
the combat zone at this point?
They better start having babies.
- Is that an order?
- Maybe, before too long.
Okay, we're gonna take
the civilians with us.
We're gonna leave this solar system,
and we're not gonna come back.
- We're running?
- This war is over.
We lost.
My father's right.
It's time for us to get out of here.
So where are we going, Commander?
The Prolmar Sector.
That's way past the Red Line.
Can you plot that jump?
- I've never plotted a jump that far, sir.
- No one has. Can you plot that jump?
- Yes, sir.
- Do it...
by yourself.
This is a bad tactical position.
We'll pull the Galactica out five clicks.
The civilians will come out behind us,
cross the threshold...
and make the jump
while we hold off the Cylons.
Once the civilians
have made the jump...
every fighter is to make
an immediate combat landing.
- We don't have much time.
- I'll tell them.
I want all my pilots to return.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir, I do.
So, can I ask
what changed your mind?
You can ask.
So, what do we do
about our prisoner?
What? You ca-- You can't--
You can't do this!
You can't just--
You can't just leave me here to die!
You've got food, water,
all the luxuries of home.
No, I-I'm begging you.
Don't do this!
- I'm not a Cylon!
- Maybe, but we can't take that chance.
I'm not a Cylon!
What kind of people are you?
Don't leave me!
- Action stations.
Set condition one throughout the ship.
Repeat.Action stations. Action stations.
Repeat.Action stations.
Action stations.
- The fleet is ready to jump, sir.
- Set condition one throughout the ship.
- Lieutenant Gaeta.
-Yes, sir?
Disperse to all fleet--
final coordinates.
Yes, sir.
- Stand by to execute battle plan.
- Sir.
Weapons grid to full power.
Stand by enemy suppression barrage.
Incoming, 72 Cylon fighters,
closing at 1 -2-0, mark, 4-8.
Enemy suppression fire.
All batteries execute.
All batteries commence firing.
All decks,
switch emergency power relays.
Perimeter established.
- Launch Vipers.
- Vipers clear to launch.
Broken formation. Razzle-dazzle. Don't
let 'em use their targeting computers.
And for frak's sake, stay out
of Galactica 's firing solution!
Vipers in position.
Signal Vipers, engage fighters only.
Leave base stars to us. Execute.
Galactica to all civilian ships.
Commence jumping in sequence.
Incoming ordnance!
Apollo, do you read me?
Aaah!
Come on, boys!
Looks like you broke your ship, Apollo.
I've had worse.
But thanks!
Function check on
the damage control panel.
They're targeting the landing bays.
We've gotta get those fighters
back on board...
and retract the pods,
or we won't be able to jump.
Fleet status.
- Last civilian ship is away.
- Recall all fighters.
Stand by to secure landing bays.
Galactica to all Vipers. Break off.
Come on home. Repeat. come on home.
Viper 1 0-26, aboard.
- Eleven-ten, aboard.
- F.T.L., go!
Sub-light, go!
The board is green. Ship reports ready for
jump as soon as landing bay's secure.
Two Vipers still out there, sir--
Starbuck and Apollo.
We can't stand toe to toe with
those baseships. Retract the pods.
I can't leave 'em here.
- Patch me through to Starbuck.
- Sir.
What do you hear?
Starbuck, Galactica.
- What?
- Morning, Starbuck. What do you hear?
Nothin' but the rain.
Grab your gun
and bring the cat in.
Aye aye, sir!
Comin' home.
I'm losing power. I'm not gonna
make it, Starbuck. It's over. Just leave!
- Damn it! That's an order!
- Lee, shut up and hold still!
Yaaah!
Oh, no.
You are beyond insane!
Kickin' in the burn!
Come on.
We're coming in a little hot,
don't you think?
No. Not really.
Come on.
- They're comin' in.
- Hang on!
- They're aboard.
- Stand by for jump.
Landing decks secure!
Jump!
With heavy hearts, we lift up
their bodies to you, O Lords of Kobol...
in the knowledge that you will take
from them their burdens...
and give them life eternal.
We also pray that you
look down upon us now...
with mercy and with love...
just as you did upon our forefathers
many years ago.
Just as you led us from Kobol
and found the Twelve Worlds...
so now we hope and pray...
that you will lead us
to a new home...
where we may begin life anew.
So say we all.
- So say we all.
- So say we all!
Are they the lucky ones?
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
We're a long way from home.
We've jumped way beyond
the Red Line...
into uncharted space.
Limited supplies. Limited fuel.
No allies.
And now no hope!
Maybe it would've been better for us
to have died quickly...
back on the colonies
with our families...
instead of dying out here slowly...
in the emptiness of dark space.
Where shall we go?
What shall we do?
"Life here began out there."
Those are the first words
of the sacred scrolls.
And they were told to us
by the Lords of Kobol...
many countless centuries ago.
And they made it perfectly clear
that we are not alone in this universe.
Elosha, there's a 13th colony
of human kind, is there not?
Yes. The scrolls tell us a 13th tribe
left Kobol in the Early Days.
They travelled far and made their home
upon a planet called Earth...
which circled a distant
and unknown star.
It's not unknown.
I know where it is!
Earth--
the most guarded secret we have.
The location was only known
by the senior commanders of the fleet...
and we dared
not share it with the public.
Not while there was
a Cylon threat upon us.
For now we have a refuge to go to...
a refuge that the Cylons
know nothing about!
It won't be an easy journey.
It will be long and arduous.
But I promise you one thing.
On the memory of those
lying here before you...
we shall find it.
And Earth will become
our new home.
- So say we all!
- So say we all.
- Dismissed.
As you were.
Just trying to avoid another trip
to the brig, sir.
Lieutenant Thrace--
Kara--
What you did out there today
with Lee Adama...
it was, uh, a hell of a piece of flying.
The commander has always said that
you were the best pilot he has ever seen.
Well, today you proved it.
Now...
about yesterday...
during the game--
Well, maybe I was out of line too.
And I just--
I wanted to say, um...
I'm sorry.
Well, don't you have anything to say?
Permission to speak
off the record, sir.
Granted.
You're a bastard.
You just don't know when
to keep your mouth shut, do you?
I am offering you a clean slate here.
I'm not interested in
a clean slate with you.
You're dangerous.
- You know why?
- This'll be good.
Because you're weak.
- Because you're a drunk.
- Are you done?
- Yes, sir.
- You're returned to flight status.
Let's see how long that lasts.
- Come in.
Firstly, I suppose that I should
thank you for deciding to bring us--
Listen, you were right,
I was wrong.
Let's just leave it at that.
All right.
There's no Earth.
You made it all up.
President Adar and I once talked
about the legends surrounding Earth.
He knew nothing about
a secret location regarding Earth.
And if the president
knew nothing about it...
what are the chances
that you do?
You're right.
There's no Earth.
It's all a legend.
Then why?
Because it's not enough to just live.
You have to have something to live for.
Let it be Earth.
They'll never forgive you.
Maybe.
But in the meantime...
I've given all of us
a fighting chance to survive.
And isn't that what you said
was the most important thing...
survival of the human race?
- Who else knows?
- Not a soul.
All right.
I'll keep your secret.
But I want something in return.
I'm listening.
If this civilization is going to function...
it's going to need a government...
a civilian government
run by the president of the colonies.
So you'll be in charge of the fleet...
but military decisions stay with me.
Yes.
Then I'll think about it,
Madam President.
I guess I'm gonna start reprogramming.
Your escape is a temporary one at best.
We will find you.
Yeah, you can try.
It's a big universe.
You haven't addressed
the real problem, of course.
Yes, yes. There may be Cylon agents...
living among us,
waiting to strike at any moment.
Some may not even know
they're Cylons at all.
They could be sleeper agents programmed
to perfectly impersonate human beings...
until activation.
If there are Cylons aboard this ship,
we'll find them.
We? You're not on their side, Gaius.
I am not on anybody's side.
And tomorrow I'll begin a formal
combat patrol around the fleet.
Good. Have a good night.
- I just--
- Why don't we...
save this for another time, son?
Dualla--
Ta-da!
- Nice to be small.
- There you go, Chief.
Nice to be small.
Goodnight, Commander.
Goodnight, Captain.
We have to get out of this storm.
The radiation affects our silica relays.
- Where did they go?
- I don't know.
- They were prepared for a big jump.
- We can't let them go.
Hmm. Unfortunately I agree.
If we do, they'll return one day
and seek revenge.
- It's in their nature.
- We have no choice.
It may take several decades
to track them down.
Don't worry.
We'll find them.
By your command.