Hello Rachael called home and Jay
please leave message
Have a nice day!
Jay?
Speaks David.
Your neighbor and friend remember?
I know you're there
can answer please?
By the way...
When seedlings that message?
Go there spent a year.
Do not you think enough time has passed?
You can not let what happened ruin your birthdays forever.
I think Rachael would not want to see re so.
Life goes on.
You have to come out of the woodwork.
'm Worried about you, Jay.
Please do not do this day
opinion the last year.
Have you opened the gift from Rachael?
Do not be looking for it forever.
And if something is damaged?
Watch  there is no let it rot.
Anyway...
Brought you some shopping supermecado.
Malta and I also bought you a little present.
Nothing too expensive, do not entusiasmes.
I want you to know that you are not alone.
It is painful enough term lost it.
Do not make us feel that we missed you too.
Happy birthday, buddy.
For our friend: Happy Birthday!
For a new start is necessary to cut the tape.
Come
Make a U-turn.
It's the wrong route to your destination.
in the wrong route to your destination.
Good morning, Mr. Guard.
Good day.
I done something wrong?
Can not park in this area without a license.
I thought that in a place as isolated as it does not bother anyone.
Your papers, please.
Thanks for coperação.
Have a nice day.
Also.
A half a mile, turn left.
Sit wherever you want, I've got it.
Have you chosen?
Bring me the number two and a cafe.
You got it.
Thank you.
What the hell.
Stop!
Come here!
My God. No.
Come on please.
Please
A one kilometer, turn right.
Thank you.
Hello, David. I am.
I wanted to thank you for being my friend.
And you get tired and never being.
You have noticed that my car
is not in the garage.
You must be thinking, where the hell I was.
You told me to leave the nest and that's exactly what I did.
I do not know where I'm going.
But I wanted to tell you I'm fine.
By the way...
Thanks for the reminder.
This was right for me.
You soon.
Cheers, mate.
A half a mile, turn left.
Thank you.
At a quilómetrovivre, turn right.
Turn right.
Reached your destination.
Go there.
Is this?
Damn.
PREVIOUS DAY
as you know, no mobile phones are allowed in class.
But your daughter does not respect this rule.
Their conduct is reprehensible.
As such, I hope you enjoy this temporary suspension
To have a serious talk with her.
I'm sorry, but...
It's hard to believe.
Not look like a behavior of Lucy
I do not know what might have caused this.
Sorry...
Your Hand?
Thank you.
Can I ask what happened?
We had a gas leak in the house. It was last week.
I lit one of those scented candles.
AND BUM!
There was a fireball around me.
Fortunately. Lucy had opened a window moments before.
I was lucky to only burn your hand.
And the hair  hence this ridiculous scarf.
I regret what happened. Must have been a big scare.
Do you think that may have changed the behavior of Lucy?
I do not see how.
She did not even hurt.
But it could have been tragic.
Feeling close to death can change a person.
Me and Lucy discussed because the window.
Without any reason because of the window.
I was furious because I was too cold and we constipated.
Chid for the closed but ignored me.
Who would guess that in that window would save his life.
Ironic, is not it?
Given what happened.
Do not suspederei oficiamente.
I think Lucy does not deserve it
it will take a few days off
However I want you to promise that
will take a few days off
Not to complicate matters further.
We agree?
Course. I really appreciate it and I promise I will again behave well.
Lucy.
Lucy, are you home?
It told you to
purchasing new curtains?
Lucy.
Mother are you doing here?
- What do you think? I'm looking for you.
Please, not now.
I want to know who gave you a cellphone.
No one.
So how do you pay it?
I'm not.
So who is?
No One.
Ena a Free phone and makes calls to
tassel. Fantastic!
Stole it?
Of course not!
So what's this? Go!
Gave me my boyfriend.
Since  when you have a boyfriend?
- Since last week.
Really? Yes
I wish you had a boyfriend.
Maybe apredesses something about life on planet earth.
But you can not even get boyfriend.
Even with sweatshirts to say you love DICK
so you know Philip K. Dick is the best
author of science fiction in the world.
My God, you're really ignorant.
I just want to know how did you get a cell phone.
I found it ok? found it!
And why do calls if it is not yours?
It's hard not wanna talk about it.
Will be more complicated if not
explicares tudu me.
Where you think you're?
I do not talk to the phone in class
if that's what the director told you.
He says yes. Otherwise he would not have called me.
Not true.
The phone does not even work.
What
The phone this spoiled.
Never worked.
If you do not want to work for that?
This is even stranger.
You pretend that you use it just to piss you armares
and teachers?
Is this?
No.
So why do you do it?
The director was very clear on the matter.
Want to tell me they are lying?
- I just hear.
- You hear What?
The phone
Do not say you did not work?
Yes, but sometimes shot it from the bag and put it in the ear.
For what?
I hear things.
Oh, God.
What things?
Words.
Words ? radio play, is it?
Not have said it does not work.
So how do you hear words?
Actually, it's only one word per day.
Not understand.
I hear a single word
Each day a new word.
Lucy, you're not making any sense.
I knew not entendias,
so do not say anything.
Okay!.
You find a phone that does not work.
Not have a signal.
But says words.
Yes
What words are these?
Tips.
Tips on What?
Promise not you call?
These scaring me.
You have to promise.
- Ok, I promise.
Each word is a hint of what
save me every day.
It's not funny.
In these  joke, right?
Look like I'm kidding?
This is serious but do not want
to panic.
How do you want me to respond?
Hear the rest and take it easy, okay?
I hear.
Remembered the fire?
How euposso forget?
All started there.
As well?
This morning I found the phone but did not work.
I tried to find out the reason
once seemed new.
I tried on and off and check the signal.
Suddenly I heard a word.
What word?
Window
I only heard the word window
I came home and went straight to the kitchen window
without knowing why.
And I opened it.
You know what happened next.
You opened the window that saved our lives
because the phone told you?
I know that appears crazy.
I want to pair with it immediately.
Non Yesterday was the word "ticket".
And then?
Did you see the news?
Hear a gang shootout in concert
and two kids died.
I was supposed to have gone but did not.
Do you know why?
No, why?
I lost my ticket.
Glad you lost the ticket.
But how do you expect me to believe
hear these words or tips?
You know I never believed in witchcraft or suprestições
.
've Always been very rational.
So believe what I'm saying.
Tell me one more thing...
What?
What's the word today?
Have saved your life?
I know what the word is
but still nothing happened.
So what?
And why would I tell you if
not believe me?
Like you want me to believe,
if not you tell me?
I have an idea.
I will write the word
and so will not know until it happened.
So no sneaky paranoid.
Paranoia, I?
I have a better idea.
What?
Can I see your phone?
Why?
I just want to see you for a second.
What is the idea?
I'll show you.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry but I have to put a stop to it.
If you need tips, listen to me
instead of a spoiled phone.
Lucy!.
Not!
Hang in there.
Do not let go of me, please.
Grab my hand.
I'm holding you.
Do not let go, do not let go.
Help me, mother.
Grab tightly, darling.
I'm slipping. I'm slipping.
Mother holds me.
Look at me.
I do not get off, baby.
Do not let go of me.
This phone will kill you
and not save you.
Think again.
Hand
Mother, do you think this a good idea?
I do not see how
flee the city makes any difference.
Promised thy Director to
would spend a few days with you.
Only the two of us and nobody else.
But always just us two wherever.
Need to realize what is really wrong with you
and this phone.
Can not think of home.
And if you're tired of being just the two because
do not you bring your imaginary boyfriend?
Maybe I can not get a boyfriend because you did not
. Must be genetic.
After all, where are we going?
I do not know.
Since than to Mexico.
For God's sake, lucy,
we are not evading police.
Do you think that only criminals is that
want to go to mexico?
Calm. Let me think.
Look, it's simple...
Can not come to West
because that's where we are.
We can not go south because
are not marginal.
North  E, forget it. If you do not arrange man in los Angeles, much less in San Francisco.
Are left with one opçõa.
What is it?
Las Vegas.
Wanted.
There Tell me how often the
hear these words?
Daily. I told you.
E is just a word a day right?
Yes
So if each word lasts 24 hours, after midnight you should hear another.
Reckon so.
Can not wait.
You know where we are going?
Yet.
Do not know
also liked to travel into the unknown.
What are you doing?
Also I'm traveling.
What's the book?
"The Time Machine" by H. G. Wells.
Not have made the movie?
Miscellaneous.
For  you want then read the book?
I'm actually reading it for the 3rd time.
Are you crazy? why?
Because I'm doing a thesis on "Time Machine".
See is time travel like that.
Because you do not see the
trilogy "Back to the Future"?
Instead of the same book you read three times.
Actually, only read the book once.
Because I've traveled back in time
two times and I went to the moment before having read it.
So I do not remember. therefore.
Is as if you were reading the 1st time.
What?
You need to relax.
I'm messing about you.
How many bedrooms?
A with two beds. please.
Thirty dollars.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Finally 'll be able to sleep.
You can not nothing.
Do you think you'll be able to sleep without knowing
the next word that will save my daughter?
I said I only hear one word per day.
I know, but we are already the next day.
Will pass midnight,
if you have not noticed.
Are you serious?
Of course I am. You better take the phone and hearken
.
We will not sleep while not hearing the word of God.
But it did not and so. I can not force the phone to tell me words each time aptece me.
Happens when
has to happen, not when I want.
Can you at least try, please?
Mom, I'm tired.
Try there, for God's sake.
I have done this alone and do not know if
result you especada looking.
Do you want covering your eyes?
I think I can hear something.
What? What do you hear?
I hear...
"Sleep"
Do not be a smart.
Brace yourself, okay?
I hear nothing.
Can we do this tomorrow?
Expected.
What?
I'm getting.
So says.
King
What?
"King" and the word King
What does that mean?
I mean that. "King" is the hint.
King of what?
I do not know. But it will save my life
this is guaranteed.
What King?
Perhaps the king kong.
I heard that girls love.
Do not think joke.
We can sleep now?
Nothing will happen now
but worth thinking about tomorrow.
Expected.
What?
You can not sleep in this bed.
Why not?
Is not safe.
What?
Jump out of bed and come with me.
Are you kidding?
Mom, are you crazy?
Please.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
We need a King size bed
I think I have no tonight.
Can check? It is very important.
There is a room but is unable.
Fits perfectly.
The toilet is clogged.
- Do not care.
Farewell.
If "King" you will save, you will sleep on one.
Here
We can not take risks.
Was here the King Kong and evidence left.
If you need to pee,
uses the tub.
Rise and shine, my Queen.
Hurry up you have to find a King
time?
How do I look?
You do remember my mother.
I take that as a compliment.
Some think we have a sexy mom.
I know that the kids of the neighborhood
call you.
Bofo Ma.
Bofo Ma?
What the hell is this?
Good Mother to fu...
Dress...
My God, lucy. this is horrible.
Mother, you're too antinadinha.
So never get yourself a boyfriend.
And you really need a
And you is better you train this laughter,
it look like a choked dog.
Where  we have breakfast?
Burger King where else?
Here you go.
Just found this.
There is no Burger King
a radius of 20km.
Still think you should eat
one. Just in case.
And how do you think would save me a hamburger?
There is no question a King
I bought this for you.
"The shining" Stephen King
Really?
Do not let go. at least until midnight.
And I thought that is what I was going crazy
.
You know that Stephen King writes
heaps of horror stories.
And usually the pricipal character has a sad ending.
This history, for example, is a bath of blood
pricipio end.
I remember from the movie
EJA'm nervous enough.
Change the subject.
Never know what you had offered me a book
.
Of course I gave.
No, this is the first.
've Offered you a daily.
This is not quite a book.
Is, type it after him.
I'm going to the house to the bathroom.
Expected.
Stephen takes you.
Still think we'll use it for something else
.
Take it
Do not use all the pages.
Guard some for me.
O clown! Where is cocoa you owe me?
I said I gave you.
You said the same yesterday.
I want the money now.
I do not have it here I'll give you tomorrow.
You have until midnight or never
more you play chess.
Where you think you're
backpack with my daughter?
Let me go crazy Gaja.
Not off anything.
Take're hands off me.
Give me that. Thief.
Off me already said.
Give me the bag!
Give me the bag.
Cow! Get off me!
Is this what you want?
Mother!
're Gonna die, bitch!
Disappears.
Run to the car, Lucy.
Corre Lucy.
Shoot
a book against a guy with a gun.
Gone mad?
He'd shoot you.
What I supposed to do?
Do not you put the taua
life at risk for my sake.
I know how to defend myself.
Damn Stephen King.
Instead of protecting you, this phone is
will kill you.
What is this?
My protector.
My God .
This is not the mimhas things.
WHAT?
This backpack is not mine.
Where did you get this?
I thought the thief had your bag.
I put mine under the seat. Did you see?
I thought he had taken it.
Apparently not.
Damn.
We have to go back.
No way.
I have all my stuff there.
Forget. I'll buy you other books.
My thesis were months of work.
If you can go back in time,
're comfortable.
Sorry, but another way not voltamosatrás.
What now do this stuff?
Do not touch anything.
Better not leave our fingerprints on it
.
Throw it out the window.
These are the conditions:
Tonight I want a bed to myself and not tell you the "word" before dawn.
You forget one thing.
What?
The day is not over yet.
It is better grabbing you to your protetctor.
Hold the steering wheel.
There you go.
Not the tires.
I'm done.
You just hang the King
Do you think if I hear the phone,
also listened to the words?
I do not know.
Why not try?
How is the voice?
What voice?
The voice you hear.
Is a man or woman?
Who said I hear voices?
So as you hear the words?
Appear in my head.
I do not know how.
This is an aberration.
Balls .
What is it?
Hurts my head.
Hurts so much?
Yes hurts
We stopped at a pharmacy and buy some pills.
Ray phone.
's Radiation.
Yet conzinha the brain and becomes a mutant.
Mother ..
Something is happening.
What?
I have a new word.
I just heard a new word.
How so? Is that I'm holding the phone
.
I know. I do not understand.
It is not just a word a day?
I do not make the rules. Tabém'm confused.
But I have another word, I have!
For God's sake Lucy.
When is this going to end?
You're kidding, right?
No, I'm not.
So what the hell is the new word?
Ar
?
Yes
Like "Wind"
Here you go.
Takes lots of it.
How's the headache now?
What are you doing?
Leave the window open.
I'm getting cold.
You can also close the other?
Not think it's prudent.
I better never tell you
word.
Why?
Because probably this evening
gonna make me sleep in a bouncy bed.
Started by
say that this happened because I'm paranoid.
But now you're acting much worse.
Not learned anything with the "King"?
If the "air" will save me,
will be of an unexpected way.
So do not try to help because they only do worse.
Stops but the car.
Ok, I close the windows.
Stop the car.
Do not need to bother you.
Why?
Stops or vomit in your lap.
Lucy!
Come on, Lucy.
Lucy,
back here!
Reached your destination.
Damn.
My God.
Lucy.
PREVIOUS DAY
Claire.
Hello, Claire.
Now with this site?
Yes
Account there that goes mana?
Alloys Not me two years ago and suddenly
leave me a message
To come against thee
near the end of the world.
This is a psychological test?
Matt, you may seem weird, but...
I need your help with a
of my patients.
One of your patients need me?
This is very serious.
I think you might be the only salvation from this patient.
You are a psychiatrist who is not me.
Can you hear me?
I'm all ears.
I have in my charge a very special patient.
Name is Daniel Doyle and has 17 years.
Are hospitalized a year ago in
Psychiatric Center.
Still work in this madhouse?
Yeah I was promoted to vice president last week.
Congratulations V.P.
Only lasted one day.
What happened?
Divergent opinions.
For example wanted to discharge the
Daniel against my opinion.
And what is your opnion?
I think he will not last anything outside.
What do you mean?
Suicide.
I see...
And you want me to do?
Daniel's girlfriend died
and he can not overcome it.
I think he needs to talk to someone
believing that understands.
Someone he can respect.
And you think I am?
Yes I think.
Talk to him. please?
Claire, my girlfriend did not die.
I know.
But you almost died.
Is such a nice kid.
It reminds me of you.
Really?
And you can explain to me why
made me come here?
You will get there.
Now listen to me very carefully.
Ok, continues!
There are things a year, during the holidays
The  Daniel went camping lake
Mirage with his girlfriend, Jennifer.
She was in the water while Daniel took pictures
All went well until Jennifer felt bad
disappeared in istante.
But Daniel
reacted quickly launched into the water and grabbed a
Touxe it to land and provided first aid.
But unfortunately she did not survive.
Here begins the problem of Daniel.
He says not stand
loses it and decided to end his life too.
A week after her funeral
he jumped into the lake and... guess what?
Reckon not died.
Okay. But more is that exptraordinário
and awakened again when I was trying to save his girlfriend.
I'm a bit confused.
What I said was, he jumped into the lake, drowned drowned and woke up trying to save Jennifer.
But Jennifer is not dead?
You. But it will not be if you travel back in time.
Let me see if I understand.
During drowning, he travels back in time. and wakes up when the accident happened on the lake.
Exactly. At the time she was drowning.
What happens next?
He tries to save her but can not.
So try to return back repeatedly in the hope of one day getting saved it.
It's an endless circle of time.
Correct.
There is another interesting thing.
Really? What will?
Go up to the top of the first aircraft
and call me when you're there.
Looking for a small cover behind the right wing.
Can you see it?
Yes I think so.
Open it and tell me what you find.
A digital camera.
And a key.
You see the camera?
- Yes
Daniel says he can only travel in time if
take this camera with him.
Explains it there?
Take a picture of yourself before
die and that is what makes time travel.
The kid has an incredible imagination.
You bet.
How he was pararaos your care?
Was caught trying to drown
but managed to stop it.
Troxeram him to the psychiatric center and
Directorate agreed to admit him.
Same Direction
now think ECE is now cured.
Correct.
There is one thing I do not understand.
Made me come here just to get the camera
the kid or is there something more behind this hostória?
're Scaring me seriously.
What is really happening?
I stumbled across a big problem.
Do not tell me!
Let me guess.
Your opinion was even stronger.
I think it's family problem.
Spit, claire.
What did you do?
Before giving high to Daniel,
I took it from there.
Do not tell me that the kidnapped boy?
I had to do something.
Where is he?
Can you see the atrázs tickets?
Yes
He is in there.
The boy is on the plane?
And where the hell are you?
I was with him but the police caught me
and now I'm under house arrest.
Endoideste?
What I supposed to do?
Once he has a chance, will try to drown.
Conscience of what you did?
You will not be able to exercise more. And you're stuck.
No matter, since save Daniel.
Matt, please, he is alone.
I can not get involved in this
got problems arriving.
I only ask you to talk to him
Claire Sorry, but I can not.
Have you forgotten that you were in the same situation?
Quse I lost my own brother because
was also just worried about me.
OS signals were more than evident
but I did not know.
And I am very sorry.
So now if there's anything I can do to help
someone in the same situation...
... I will not hesitate.
How long did you take the camera to the kid?
Since lodged Center.
Okay
If the kid thinks this camera is
a time machine.
I want to know how it works.
You are here, Daniel?
Daniel?
Are you Daniel?
Who are you?
I'm matt.
Brother of Claire.
Welcome to flying aimlessly, matt.
I never liked flying.
I like to have both feet on the ground.
Do not tell me...
Also're Psychiatrist.
I'm no doctor no.
Although Claire
I think I can help.
God knows why.
Once  helped a dog.
But I am also a veterinarian.
Actually, I'm unemployed.
Let's say I'm an asshole.
Type, like you, no offense.
You know she just wants to help you. right?
No result.
From to realize.
I understand your angst toward life.
It is painful to lose a girlfriend that way.
I know how it can get around the head.
Really?
Your girlfriend also died?
No.
I hope not.
How so?
She disappeared.
Kidnapped or something?
He's gone.
And here I thought
was the biggest asshole.
Good observation.
I do not blame her.
I was a silly kid.
What happened?
Had  16.
He was a rich kid
Raised in a wealthy family in Chicago.
My parents had big plans for me.
He was a prodigy student and planned to follow
medicine.
All was well.
But fate decided to intervene.
Guess?
I fell in love.
The problem was that...
She was 20 and was a taxi driver.
I should have known better than to try to force my parents,
to accept that I wanted to marry,
with a taxi driver for 20 years, immigrant...
Ecom diamond on a tattooed guy.
My God...
My parents Iançaram up
a war against us.
It was crazy.
Yet
thought he could win.
So, she and I decideimos
pretend we had finished...
... Until I was of legal age.
During two years.
It was really hard.
But we had a secret signal.
Whenever we crossed we played in the nose.
Is a very old gesture.
Used by tribe Arctic.
Whenever men left for
a long hunting trip in the Arctic.
The women lo touched on the nose as well.
Means...
My heart will follow you to the ends of
world.
Thought it was an appropriate signal.
Because the environment around us was...
... Cold as a winter night in the Arctic.
Apart sad thing is that not survived.
It was not easy to fool my parents.
Discovered she was not legalized in
and threatened with extradition.
Great drama of adolescence, right?
What happened to you?
Never saw her again.
And you did?
I tried to go back in time.
Like you.
How?
Needless to say I could not.
It seems to me you're stranded.
Life as a black comedy.
At that time only thought of ending my life.
And now I walk with a
injectable pen wallet.
Pen injection?
Epinephrine injector.
I'm allergic to bee stings.
Without this, a sting can be deadly.
Pathetic, no?
Tell me out, what has changed in your life since then
What made you change the blade by
an injectable pen?
Hope.
Like you, I am hopeful
find like stepping back in time
back to be with my girlfriend.
But I think to kill me
is not the solution.
Unless you and your camera
prove me otherwise.
What kind of precise proof?
Could you bring me some pictures.
As they say,
"A picture is worth a thousand words".
If the camera
devolveres me and helping me out of here
I bring you the photos you need.
I'll see what I can do.
Thanks for pass the night there.
How could I refuse accommodation
Free as a theme park.
What do you think?
I think those handcuffs
will hurt quite your resume.
Sorry but desperate situations exirgem extreme actions.
We can not let go without
sure it will be fine.
He will never be well unless we let go.
You know, mom and dad have missed you.
You should try to forgive them.
Maybe.
It was a pen esters love you
the wrong girl.
It was not the wrong girl.
Sorry, do not know what
said this in a bad way.
My God, was about ten years ago.
Ever you heard of it?
No.
I find it hard to believe you're still in love.
But you are, are not you?
I think it's a bit late for
a therapy session.
Honestly, in part, I envy you.
What they both need is to go to sleep.
I will make them possible.
Good night - Good night
Go West?
Log  Young al.
Thank you.
Do not tell me you let him go?
You said you wanted that Daniel
speak with someone who could respect
Someone he believed that understood. right?
Yes, said.
The only way of really Daniel
trust me, it was freed.
He is not ready.
We know that he tried to commit suicide before.
When we think of doing something so terrible ourselves...
I felt so unhappy and alone that
never thought anyone could endure that.
I know because I felt it.
I felt so unhappy and alone that
never thought anyone could endure that.
Daniel might still think about suicide.
But now it's different.
He now knows that others
managed to overcome the same pain.
He knows he's not alone.
And you know I'm here ready to help.
I certainly hope you're right, Matt.
I think that is where it goes.
Where?
He tried to drown himself in the lake Mirage
to wake up and save his girlfriend in the same location.
I think that is where it goes and
is only 3 hours away.
He will die, Matt.
I know I will.
No. Do not worry.
Let me handle this.
Encontá it and I'll be alright.
My sister is 65 years old.
One day he comes home and hears a strange sound coming from
room.
She enters and runs into his daughter
40 years, my niece...
... Playing with a vibrator.
You know what a vibradoor, right?
Yes, I know.
Internet.
OK, I see.
Then she told ihe:
What the hell are you doing?
And the daughter said...
Mom, I'm 40 years...
... Look at me. 'm ugly...
I'll never get married.
This is the only husband who will.
Is sad.
Yeah.
The next day...
My brother comes home...
And heard the same buzz coming from the
daughter's room...
He walked in and there she was...
... To use the vibrator.
He said: What the hell is this?
And she replied:
Father, I have explained the mother...
I'm 40, I'm ugly and I'll never marry.
This is like my husband.
ready, he turned his back in sadness.
The next day, my sister comes home...
And finds him on the couch with a beer in one hand...
And the vibrator on the other hand...
Watching football on TV.
She Tell him:
What the hell is this?
And he said: What is the problem?...
I'm drinking beer and see
the game with my son.
With son.
Where you say you are?
Not said.
So, where are you?
I was born in Iceland but grew up in California.
I think the drastic climate change
affected my head.
Well I ended up in an asylum.
Really?
When was this?
Very recently.
Is not cause for alarm. 'm harmless.
You look well.
You know...
I have had to put up with psychiatrists.
How so?
I used to faint...
Every time he tried... you see?...
Me to lie down with my wife.
I could not do anything because
fainted before starting.
You see my luck?
So...
The doctors thought it was
head and sent me to a psychiatric hospital.
Then they asked me a series of
Marados tests.
Finally, they found that
'm just allergic to latex.
See? I can not use rubber.
You mean condoms?
All kind of rubber.
But pricipalmente condoms.
The first anfinal diagnosis was right.
I have a problem in the "head"
this is really weird.
's Not all bad.
At least I won...
... The best parking there.
Cool.
Tell me...
You should also have gone through
much there in the nuthouse.
Like any good drama,
there is always comical moments.
This account there.
On one occasion, we had the visit of a rich lady who contributed
with large donations.
Senhoara was a class with
and very conservative.
Visista During a guided tour of the hospital...
She went straight to the room where
a patient was masturbating.
He chocadissima and said:
- This is shameful. How is that even let it?
The doctor explained: Sorry,
this patient has a serious problem...
He thinks  if you do it several times a day
, testicles explode and die.
You know that this can even happen.
So the lady. there understood.
Said. Oh, that's really horrible.
And they continued to visit.
But the room then she sees the nurse
Chavez, good and sexy.
The oral sex in another patient.
The lady went up.
Screaming: How is this justified?
The doctor was so embarrassed
and without knowing what to say.
Then he turned to her and said.
Is the same disease but with better health insurance.
Best health insurance.
Here we are.
Thank you.
Good luck.
You can fill me
the balloon, please?
Where are your parents?
My mother was inside
buy me chocolate.
Please.
Okay. First stretching herself.
Mom.
My lord.
Can you hear me?
An ambulance.
It's your lucky day, boss!
Go there.
Come respira.vá there buddy
Come on sir.
Please breathe.
Breathe.
're Gonna get.
This.
That's right.
Lord can you hear me?
Yes
What is what?
Justin.
Justin Time.
Justin Time
's funny.
Had an allergic reaction.
The ambulance is on the way.
'll Be fine.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Justin Time
I'm Daniel.
Praser. 'm Helen.
So for ondevais?
Forward.
Figured that...
Else could catch
to ride across.
I go to Mirage Lake.
I think I can let you near there.
Fantastic.
What are you doing to Lake Mirage?
I have with my girlfriend.
We notice that you are willing to see.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Good.
And whither goest thou?
I will return here.
These 70km road is my job.
You walk back and forth all day?
Correct.
Not
wanna know the amount of cars that break down here.
If cars were insects,
this road would like a web-of-spider
So you're kind Spider Woman.
Not in the sense of a black widow spider as
that kills the male after mating.
I refer to the woman as the _aranha
Superhero, Spiderman.
What saves people and is adored for it.
Account there.
How is your girlfriend?
's Hottie?
Why?
Do you like women?
Do you think I'm a dyke just because
drive a tow truck?
Not what I meant.
I asked you for asking.
're Humorous.
But, you have someone you like?
A boyfriend?
Yes
I've had.
This work does not leave me time
free to date.
I think I'll still get to single reform.
So it's a good idea
get yourself a vibrator.
Excellent idea.
Here we are.
Here  Daniel.
The Mirage Lake is on.
I have to get back to work
on my favorite road.
It was a pleasure to meet you Helen.
Good luck to you and your girlfriend.
Thank you.
And do not worry about boyfriends
If you do not find it you will find.
Thanks for the ride.
Always the orders.
My God.
Lucy.
Mom, there's a new word.
WHAT?
I just heard a new word.
What kind of word?
"Air".
I bet if you call a tow truck and the car sacares
water, it still works.
I will not let you lose that bet.
I have something for you.
Evidence of time travel?
I never said I would bring thee proof.
He said he would bring  the photos you need.
Thank you.
But call a tow.
Okay.
And thank you...
For all
Take care of yourself.
Helena
Towing Service.
I need to tow on Lake Mirage.
What coicidência. already been there today.
I'll be on my way. Do not move.
Do not leave, do not.
Matt?
Justin Time
We had a secret signal.
What do you mean...
My heart will follow you to the ends of the world
.
Sync Adaptation maru maru lucio lucio lucio copied by maru