Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I remember a world
with no wars...
no warriors.
All that has changed.
Now I see a dying land.
And the enemy grows stronger.
Is there someone
with the courage...
to step f orward?
But I f ear f or him...
as I f ear f or us.
Ryan! Breakf ast is on the table.
I've gotta run, honey.
Be back around 5:00.
Bye.
Shoot.
Bravo, no.
Look, where's Ryan?
Go on. You go find him.
Make sure he eats his breakf ast.
Yeah.
What?
Do you mind?
Dog.
Yeah.
- Hey, Ryan!
- Yeah?
To your right.
Have I told you
about the real kung fu masters?
Then let go
of your limitations.
Imagine a world
beyond anything you've ever seen.
A world of no worries, of perf ect bliss,
where anything can happen.
A world def ended
by great warriors.
No guns, no lasers,
no morphing.
They use the f orces of nature
as their weapons.
Fire, metal...
wood...
water...
and earth.
Warriors who fight
f or integrity and honor...
sail upon their enemies
with the grace of a dancer...
and knock them senseless...
with the touch of a f eather.
Well, it's cooking time.
Hey, Ming.
Are they real?
Ancient Chinese secret.
Red f or 12!
Set, hut!
- Go!
- Go, Ken!
- We can still win.
- There's no way they can make it.
Time out!
- Red team.
- Ryan, Chucky, today!
Coming, Coach.
- Guys, we have time f or one more play.
- Here you go.
We're gonna sweep left. No, we're gonna
sweep right. Toby, you get the ball.
No way, Coach. Left tackle's
been bustin' through the line all game.
Hey, I've played a f ew games
in my day, son. Okay?
I said sweep right, so we're
gonna sweep right. Now let's go!
- We can do it.
- Yeah, it's a good play.
- Brad.
- Guys, throw 'em over here.
Thanks.
Their right saf ety comes in
on every running play.
If you f ake to Toby, then bootleg left,
you have a clear path to the end zone.
Sure, "Coach."
All right. Ready!
- Break!
- Gimp!
Let's go, Ry.
Blue 42! Go!
Hut!
All right! Way to go!
Wow!
Yes!
All right!
Nice call.
Thanks, Chucky.
You got dissed, man.
It was your call.
What's the diff erence?
You. That's the whole point.
- You made the diff erence.
- Watch out!
Hey, we're walkin' here!
Hey, Brad!
Ryan called your winning play.
Aren't you gonna thank him?
Did you say somethin',
or did you f art?
Ryan called the play.
You heard him.
And he told you
exactly what to do.
Oh, really? I thought you said
that was your ingenious idea.
Bootleg left,
clear path to the end zone.
- That was a great call, man.
- Thanks.
Too bad you can't play ball.
You're pretty smart.
Come on.
Let's get lost.
Wait a second.
You want to hang out
with us tonight?
- Yeah. Sure.
- Cool.
Well, we'll be around
the Orono tunnel about 8:00.
- Great. We'll be there.
- All right.
You too, Upchuck.
Break.
You got a death wish, man?
I mean, the guy's evil.
Lucif er thinks
he's a little extreme.
- He's up to somethin'.
- So you're not comin'?
I didn't say that.
After all, you're the man.
See you there.
Pass!
Touchdown!
An incredible pass from the man
simply known as...
"Ry."
- Darn.
- Hey, Mom.
The man I was looking f or.
Dinner's almost served.
Fabulous frozen. Got a showing in 20
minutes, so you'll have to eat alone.
- How was your game?
- We won.
Brad got a touchdown
on the last play.
- I came up with the play.
- Really?
Hey, that's great.
I'm very proud of you.
Proud of what?
I didn't score the touchdown.
That's okay.
- Yeah, right.
- No, it is. You're a part of that team.
And it sounds to me like
they couldn't have won without you.
When's Dad getting back?
Now, are you saying that your f ather is
a better cook than your mother?
No off ense.
Oh, yes, you are gonna
need something.
- How about Min's? My treat.
- Ming, Mom.
You've only been there
a hundred times.
Yeah, Ming. I know.
Look, your mama's losing her mind, going
in and out of that door all day long.
You bear with me
a little longer?
I'll be back
in a couple hours.
Sorry.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
You okay, Mr. Lang? It's slippery here.
You gotta watch your step.
- What's goin' on?
- Oh, nothin'.
Come on.
- What's got you singin' the blues?
- Nothin'.
Come on.
I got somethin' f or you.
- What is it?
- Come on.
I'll be right there.
What's this?
Oh, I f ound that
when I was about your age.
It's a cocoon.
I was on my way home
from school.
I saw it lying on the ground,
just sitting there...
moving around,
something inside.
I got on my hands and knees
and looked close...
and I see this moth
struggling to get out.
But he couldn't do it. So I reached down
and tore open the cocoon.
And out he came.
Takes off into the air and flies away.
But then, all of a sudden,
down he came into the ground.
Dead.
What happened?
I interrupted his journey.
We all have cocoons.
The struggle to free ourselves makes us
whole and gives us the strength to fly.
It's pretty hard to fly
when you have a broken wing.
Always so certain of that,
aren't you?
Ancient Chinese secret,
remember?
- A book?
- No, a manuscript.
I was like you once.
Never f elt I was good enough.
Always wanted to be
like someone else.
But this-- this helped me become
the person I wanted to be.
A cook?
No. Myself.
This is Tao.
It means the way to something, yourself,
being the person you want to be.
I got all the self-help books I need
from my mom. She doesn't get it either.
This isn't like the books
your mom gave you.
I gotta go.
Check it out.
- It's yours.
- Catch you later.
Man, this place makes me itch.
- This is creepy. Let's get outta here.
- What?
This is our ticket,
so don't blow it.
We're in.
So you boys decided
to show up.
So what are we gonna do here?
We're gonna play
f ollow the leader.
You're the leader.
- It's a bad idea.
- Just relax, okay?
No. See? I told you
somethin' was up.
And I bet
it's gonna get worse.
I bet they're gonna carve
their initials into our chest...
or make hot dogs
out of our wieners.
- Hot dogs with meatballs on the side.
- Shut up.
Me, oh, my. You know, I just remembered,
I have a Spanish test tomorrow.
To hang with us,
you gotta be initiated.
Come on, you wussies! Let's go!
- All right, guys.
- Wait.
All right.
Now, this is simple.
All you gotta do is walk across
and give us an autograph.
- Make your mark.
- You said you wouldn't make him do it.
He can't.
- Don't listen to him.
- We all did it.
You want in? It's up to you.
- Don't.
- He's a wussy.
- Don't do it.
- Don't.
Fine. I'll meet you
on the other side.
- Baby!
- All right, man. Come on!
Take a swim today?
Shut up!
- Watch out.
- Don't slip, man.
- Watch it!
- Yeah!
Come on! Yeah!
Come on, Jeff ers.
Are you cool?
Let's go.
Come on, buddy.
Come on.
He's just making fun of you.
Man, this is stupid.
Make like Tom and "cruise."
Shut up. I can do this, okay?
Look, he did it.
Yeah. But you're not him.
- Damn.
- Let's go!
- He's picking up the can.
- Are you afraid?
- Come on!
- Come on down.
- Don't do it!
- Shut up.
- Come on. You got it.
- You got it. Keep goin'.
You guys, don't distract him.
- He's gonna f all in!
- Hey, big guy, you got it.
Come on.
Come on! You got it.
What are you doing?
Go f or it!
You're movin' like a baby! Why don't you
just get down and crawl? Come on!
- Stop it!
- Come on.
Come on! You got it!
- Don't look down!
- That's it. Yes!
Hey, you see that?
- What?
- He's freakin'.
You never know when it's gonna
take a dump. You gotta be quick.
Come on! Let's go.
You gotta be quick.
Come on!
What is that?
Grab him!
- Oh, my God!
- Get him out!
What--
Dry?
Tracy?
Come on, guys.
Cut it out.
Look, this isn't funny.
Bravo!
Hey, you!
Gotcha!
Oh, my God.
It works.
My leg.
It works! Yes!
Set!
Blue 42!
Set! Hike!
Jeff ers spins
past the def enders!
Oh, he cuts back,
spinning, stiff-arming!
Back to the sidelines.
He goes.
He's spinning past the def enders.
Split the stiff-arm!
Spins again.
Fumble! But Jeff ers recovers.
He spins back to mid-field.
At the ten! The five--
- Get off me!
- You're not getting away, Newcomer!
- Let go! No!
- No such luck.
Let go, punk.
Hold your blade!
Who's there?
- Are you hurt?
- He's a Newcomer, Elysia.
Came right up out of the river.
I saw it with my own eyes.
And he's mine!
You're really a Newcomer?
I just f ell in the water.
I slipped,
and then those things...
they came out,
and they tried to kill me.
Those were Komodo's men.
We're not saf e here.
Come on.
Elysia, a little reward
f or my eff orts?
Virtue be yours!
Your patrol was sent to spy
on their Lif espring, Commander.
- You were not supposed to be seen.
- General, we were attacked.
Well, you can explain it
to him yourself.
He's not happy.
Bye-bye!
Commander.
Failure...
is in your eyes.
An open wound inf ects
like a disease...
and it spreads...
like an inf ection.
I smell f ear.
Fear of what?
Death?
My lord...
please.
Look.
I brought you this.
It's from a boy.
He's a Newcomer.
Newcomer?
Rise.
Slowly stand up.
Don't be afraid.
I want to take away
your terror.
There is nothing to f ear...
because...
nothing dies.
Listen.
Lif e...
is but a dream...
flowing into another dream.
Bye.
General Grillo...
I ask you this:
What's the point of power...
if you don't abuse people?
Open it.
My lord,
it's the symbol of Tao!
Could this be the--
the manuscript?
Lieutenants!
At last.
Find this Newcomer
and bring him to me.
Pleasure, my lord.
Alive.
Who are you?
Where am I?
I'm Elysia.
You're in Tao.
- Tao?
- Yes, Tao.
The manuscript. I thought it was
just a story. I didn't believe him.
What manuscript?
What does it look like?
- That. It has that on the cover.
- The Manuscript of Legend?
- The what?
- The Manuscript of Legend.
Master Chung once told us about
an ancient book that had special powers.
He said, if it was ever returned to Tao,
it could change everything.
- Who's Master Chung?
- He's our leader.
When he came to Tao,
he taught ways of peace and harmony.
But it didn't last.
Komodo began mining the Lif espring
f or a mineral called zubrium.
The Lif esprings are
where we live.
They radiate energy
to all of Tao.
Without zubrium
they die out.
Komodo uses the zubrium
to keep himself young and strong.
That's why he's so desperate f or it.
Now only one Lif espring remains.
Can't anyone stop him?
No, not even
the Warriors of Virtue.
Warriors? Kung fu?
What do they look like?
They're Rooz.
This is our Lif espring.
Listen to me,
citizens of Tao.
Please calm yourselves.
- We cannot let our f ears def eat us.
- We must remain calm.
The Warriors of Virtue
will protect us!
But Master Chung,
has Yun returned?
He has not.
Then how can
the Warriors of Virtue protect us...
if there are
only f our of them?
Komodo's soldiers have already
been spotted inside the green.
- What are we going to do?
- We're doomed!
Oh, we're dead!
Listen to me, please!
Master Chung, we have hope.
- A Newcomer has arrived.
- Newcomer?
He's too small
to be a Newcomer.
Houston,
we have a problem.
Newcomer, Elysia said
you have brought the manuscript.
May I see it?
It is important, Newcomer.
The name is Ryan Jeff ers.
Show me the Warriors of Virtue,
please?
I trained these five warriors
to protect Tao.
Each upholds honor...
and integrity.
Do they fight with kung fu?
They use the f orce
of nature's elements:
wood, fire...
earth, metal...
and water.
Ming was right.
This is Lai,
virtue of order...
the stability of wood.
Meticulous, logical...
often a bit cranky.
Tsun, the virtue
of Ioyalty...
security of earth.
Kind and nurturing.
Chi, virtue
of high wisdom...
power of fire.
Often playful...
but very wise.
Yee, virtue
of righteousness...
strength of metal.
He does not speak,
seeing every choice as right or wrong.
- Nothing in between.
- You said there were five.
Yes. The other is Yun...
their leader.
Virtue of benevolence,
f orce of water.
Where is he?
Yun has lost
his will to fight.
God, they're so cool.
Uh-oh.
But not ready!
Don't be afraid.
This is Yee.
Ryan. How's it goin'?
It's all right.
This is Chi...
Tsun...
and Lai.
He is a Newcomer, and he has brought
something important to us.
Now, Ryan Jeff ers,
may we see the manuscript?
Look, I don't have it.
One of you guys has it.
Us?
When you saved me from Komodo's
soldiers, it was in my backpack.
- At the river. Remember?
- Backpack? What's a backpack?
Yun knows where it is.
If the Newcomer was saved at the river,
it would have been Yun.
- Forget Yun.
- But what if he can help?
Yun does not care about our cause
anymore. He will not help.
In this struggle,
all five of you must work together.
We must find Yun.
Without
the Manuscript of Legend...
we cannot def eat Komodo.
What are you thinking about?
Home.
I wonder if my mom and dad
are worried about me.
What are your parents like?
I don't know.
No. They're pretty cool.
I mean, they're nice.
I wish I'd known
my mother and f ather.
They died just after
my brother and I were born.
Master Chung
looked after us.
Where is your brother?
He was recently killed.
I'm sorry.
You must've been a great leader
in your world to be trusted...
with the Manuscript of Legend.
Not really.
I was just a bad f ollower.
- But I'd sure like to show them now.
- Show them what?
That I can run,
play f ootball...
just like everyone else!
What?
Nothing. I just think
I f ound a friend.
So have I.
Come on. There's something
I want to show you.
- What?
- Come on!
All this was built
in honor of the Rooz.
During the Old Order,
they were revered by everyone.
- How come Yee doesn't talk?
- He used to.
But after the war
in Tao started...
he saw so much suff ering
that he hasn't spoken since.
Why'd Yun leave everyone?
- He killed someone in the battle.
- So what? It was a battle. People die.
It was a lif e!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it that way.
It's just that the Warriors of Virtue
made a creed never to kill.
But Yun--
Someday you'll understand.
Understand what?
You remind me of my brother.
He's alway--
Let go of me!
- What are you doing?
- Shut up!
- Move it.
- Help!
Help!
- Hey, Yun.
- Let go!
Come to play?
Where's your sword?
You killed anyone today?
Mantose! Get up!
Barbra-Rotious, this way!
You're Yun, aren't you?
I'm Ryan, the Newcomer.
You saved me
at the river, remember?
Can I have the manuscript?
I need to bring it back to them.
The Manuscript of Legend?
You mean, you don't have it?
Then Komodo must have it.
You have to help them get it back.
Master Chung says they need you.
Come on. Let's go.
You don't understand.
Where are you going?
You're supposed to be
one of them!
Honor! Integrity! Remember?
You can't run away f orever!
No wonder they gave up on you.
Wimp!
Lai was right.
He doesn't care.
- Let's go.
- Cool.
It can't be.
Irrational.
Cool.
Thank you, Ryan.
Tsun, l--
I knew you'd return.
- Thanks.
- There was always wisdom in your heart.
Welcome home.
You should not have left.
Order has been disrupted.
I was wrong.
The Newcomer helped me realize that.
Come on.
It is good you've returned.
Thank you.
Tell them about the manuscript.
Komodo has it.
We will never stop Komodo now.
Its knowledge is his.
That's not so.
It's good to see
all of you together again.
Forgive me.
The Newcomer brought
the manuscript.
He is the only one
with the eyes to see what is written.
Me?
Master, on my lif e, I will
get the manuscript back from Komodo.
Yun is back!
The Warriors of Virtue
are united again!
Thank you, Ryan!
My lord, all the zubrium has been mined
from this Lif espring.
The army stands at readiness.
The only question is,
what do we do since Yun has returned?
Do not think thoughts.
The Rooz were born to die.
Even reunited,
they cannot def eat me.
Isn't that why they seek
the manuscript? Yes, it is.
- My lord, f orgive--
- Do not...
think thoughts.
Outside, anxiety exists.
And where there is anxiety...
there is error.
And where there is error...
there is opportunity.
They're panicking!
Do not think thoughts!
Let them make their mistake.
Forgive me, my lord...
but if the manuscript can harm us,
why don't we just destroy it?
It cannot be destroyed.
You can be destroyed.
Your armies can be destroyed.
But it cannot be destroyed!
Get out.
Get away from me!
General Grillo.
My lord?
Can I survive when I have destroyed
the last Lif espring in Tao?
And do you expect me to stay
in a world where I cannot survive?
No, my lord.
Another world is waiting.
The manuscript...
will help us to get
to this other world.
Then why do we need
the Newcomer?
Well, because he is
the teller of tales.
And I do not see f ailure
in your eyes.
The Newcomer
shall be yours, my lord.
General.
Do--
Does purple suit me?
Very much, my lord.
Then you are dismissed.
I don't like it. We should tell
Master Chung what we're doing.
- There's no time.
- Just listen to what she's saying.
But Komodo can attack us
at any time.
- He said to be patient.
- Patience is not my virtue.
If all of us go,
there will be chaos.
And I made a pledge to protect these
people. We can't leave them def enseless.
I let the manuscript f all
into Komodo's hands...
and I made a pledge
to Master Chung.
I will go myself.
- I'll go with you too.
- What about me?
Master Chung says I'm the only one
who can read the manuscript.
That would be unwise.
What did he say?
Yee said we must keep you from harm.
You're a friend.
Relax. It's just
a cool way to shake hands.
Okay. You're gettin' it.
You got it.
All right.
Good luck.
Thank you, Mosely.
Do I look like a baby-sitter?
The next time, why don't you volunteer
to get us something to eat?
Your stupid ideas.
If I hear one more thing
come out of your mouth--
Your breath stinks.
Never mind.
My lord,
Elysia is here.
Your guilt is obscene.
It was a lif e!
Yield to vengeance.
Medication time.
-The Newcomer has taken a liking to you.
-Yes.
And you care f or him.
- He has f allen under my spell.
- A wicked spell it is.
What are you afraid of?
- Not you.
- That's my girl.
Oh, yes.
I wouldn't touch that
if I were you.
That's Yun's sword.
Nobody touches Yun's sword.
Not even Yun, anymore.
Know what I mean?
You again.
What do you want?
I've got a deal f or you, Newcomer.
- I've got something you want.
- What?
I'm not telling
until I get something in return.
- Tell me now, partner.
- Take it easy. Whoa!
I'll tell you.
I've got the manuscript.
You what?
Stole it right out
from under Komodo's nose.
- Show it to me.
- Are you crazy?
It's hid, hid where
no one's gonna find it but me.
But I'll take you there.
I have to tell them.
You're not listenin' to me.
The manuscript's not theirs.
It's yours.
Look, once they use up all the power,
how are you gonna get home?
You wanna stay here f orever?
Never see your f amily, friends?
Ever?
Now, take it from me, Newcomer.
It's now or never.
No. Look, I can't leave them.
They need me here.
Fine.
You're not interested?
I'll ask someone else.
Mudlap.
Wait.
A small reward f or my eff orts.
It's a good watch.
Well, it's better than nothin'.
Come on.
Hey, wait up!
Where are we?
- Let go!
- Welcome to the other side.
- Thanks, General Grillo.
- Jerk!
- Virtue be yours.
- Let go!
Let go of my arm!
My arm, you punk! Let go!
That is not your way.
Komodo's lies
have blinded your vision.
But the truth is still there.
In your heart.
The manuscript.
It's too easy.
What? Hmm?
Protectors of Tao,
weak...
vulnerable.
What are you doing here?
Oh, are you really
that surprised, Yun?
Virtue of Benevolence
who kills?
- It was an accident!
- Enjoy your restitution.
Please, Elysia.
Don't let him destroy
our Lif espring.
I should have listened to Tsun.
Rooz!
Thank you f or hanging around.
I have concocted a recipe...
f or kangaroo stew.
First...
simply chop the meat
into many tiny little pieces...
and sprinkle with a hint
of benevolence.
Don't--
Marinate in wisdom
f or many, many, many years.
Add just a touch...
of order!
And let it simmer...
in righteousness.
Goes down very well with a...
nice cold vial of zubrium.
My lord, please!
Growl. Roll over.
- Beg!
- Please!
Go away.
Komodo, you f orgot Ioyalty.
Loyalty...
only lasts so long.
Then it spoils.
Chi...
your stupidity astounds me.
You come uninvited
into my lair...
animals that you are.
Like animals, I shall
serve you up as supper...
to my close friend...
and most honored guest...
ladies and gentlemen...
the Newcomer!
No! Not Ryan!
It was Master Chung.
Chung. Ah.
- He took the Newcomer from me.
- We've got to get out of here.
I'll add just a dash
of old man to the dish.
And I'll enjoy your Lif espring
f or dessert!
Yes!
General Grillo.
Drink.
- Do it.
- Hmm?
Is it worth it, Grillo?
General Grillo!
You belong with us,
like it was when we were young.
You f orget, Yun.
Even then we played
on opposite sides.
We were still friends.
Drop them!
Good boy, General!
Chi, give us some light here.
Uh-oh.
Don't anyone move.
Yee, don't panic!
Oh, no.
Problem.
Yee, the ring!
Yee, is that a tunnel?
Let's get out of here.
Forget the ring. Let's go!
Don't panic.
We've got you!
Ready, Chi? On three.
One, two...
three!
Go, go, go!
Will the manuscript
really get me home?
Yes, Ryan.
By helping the Rooz...
you will find your way home.
What about my leg?
What matters is not
what you gain there...
but in your heart.
I want it to be strong,
like it is now.
Do you consider
the Warriors of Virtue strong?
Yeah. Look at them.
Their strength
is not in what you see.
It is in their virtue.
That is their Kung.
What's Kung?
Kung is your energy...
your inner strength.
It can be positive or negative.
Those like Komodo
use negative Kung...
to kill and destroy.
But if you can bring your virtues
together within yourself...
you will create positive Kung.
With that, you will always
have the power...
to do the right thing.
If no one else can read the manuscript,
how will I be able to?
The answer lies within you.
When I tell you to run,
take that path and go.
Do not stop until you get
to the Lif espring.
- Who's that?
- It's Komodo.
You should go now. Run!
Where are you going, Newcomer?
Eat this, sucker!
Master Chung!
Come on!
Master Chung, help!
I ask you one last time.
I am in hell.
It's my prison.
How can I be free?
The only hells in this world...
are in your heart...
where all the battles
must be f ought.
Get out of here!
Are you all right?
There are too many of them. We must
leave. We've got to get out of here.
Stupid Rooz!
Oh, no.
We shouldn't have left.
There's no time f or blame, Chi.
- We must find the others.
- There's only one place still saf e.
What are you doing here?
Ryan, I wanted to tell you.
No, you're on his side.
- You're a traitor!
- No, Ryan.
Listen to me, Ryan.
Let me explain.
No. Master Chung is dead.
I saw him die.
How can you do this to them?
They protected you.
Protect with their creed
not to kill...
ever?
Well, they did kill.
Yun killed.
- It was one of the bad guys.
- It was my brother.
I don't believe you.
You're lying.
It's over now.
Yun, the others,
they're dead.
- Komodo killed them.
- Shut up!
- Just shut up, Elysia!
- But it's okay f or you.
No, it's not. You set me up.
You said you were my friend.
No, you get to go home, right?
Oh, Ryan, please, listen to me.
Do what Komodo says.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Please? Listen--
Looking f or me?
I know your sorrow.
I know...
your Ioneliness.
Look at me!
I am everything you can become.
I am...
your darkest thoughts, Ryan.
And I am proud
to be your destiny.
No one will ever
laugh at you again.
I promise you that.
Let's go home...
with your new leg.
Ryan Jeff ers...
touchdown.
Open the book.
My lord.
The last Lif espring is now
completely under our control.
But the Rooz have escaped,
all of them.
Go away.
Get out!
Read me the book.
What does it say?
Do it, Ryan. Please.
Read it to me!
Do it.
You'll get to go home.
Read the words!
Shit happens.
- Shit--
- Happens.
Shit happens.
You can't read the book,
can you?
Can you?
Komodo, please,
give him another chance.
You mean nothing to me!
No one touches my master.
I want him alive!
Willy Beest! Mosely! Help!
Hey, guys.
- All right.
- Virtue be yours!
Good-bye, Master Chung.
I don't want to see it anymore.
I don't want to be here.
I don't want to see death.
I just want to go home.
Will this help?
Get out of here, creep.
Gee, come on, take it.
It'll make you f eel better.
Make me f eel better?
A watch?
Yeah, probably f or you.
All you care about is your stupid
little things and your rewards.
You don't know what's important.
All you care about is how much you get.
Just get out of here. You sold me out.
You sold yourself out. Go away.
I just want to help.
I don't need your help.
Get out of here, you two-f oot creep!
The Rooz need your help.
They're at the Temple Ruin.
Search harder.
- Leave no crevice unexplored.
- We've done that already.
- Just do it!
- Whatever.
General Grillo!
The manuscript.
We have searched everywhere,
my lord, but--
Then you have not looked
everywhere...
have you?
Find it.
- Get out!
- Go!
I can't help you.
I tried to read it,
but it's empty.
There's nothing.
It's empty.
I'm sorry.
I tried to read it...
but I can't.
Yee's right.
This is our home.
Live or die.
It's time, Yun.
Why not?
You've come uninvited
into our Lif espring, Komodo.
This is our home.
We want it back.
Warriors...
come out and play!
What?
Where is he?
Rooz!
Oh, no. Five.
Still nothing to say?
Then I will be your voice!
Lai.
The center cannot hold.
Things f all apart.
You're just illusion, Komodo.
Uh-oh.
Betrayal...
is f ar more alluring, Tsun.
How can I help the Rooz?
The answer lies within you, Ryan.
Master Chung?
Help me.
Five is one. Positive Kung.
To take a lif e,
you lose a part of yourself.
He lost his power.
That's it.
I am cruelty!
Can you stop me, Yun?
Are you ready to kill again...
Virtue of Benevolence?
Eat this!
Yun, where is Komodo?
What do we do now?
Master?
Yun, why didn't you
listen to me?
You act in such haste.
The Lif espring is gone.
Master, I've f ailed you.
Please, tell me what to do now.
Now you can go to hell!
No, Yee. He'll break his neck.
Hey, Komodo!
Looking f or this?
Remember me? I'm your friend.
And I'm proud to be your destiny.
Chi, five is one! Positive Kung!
Do it now!
The medallions!
- Water!
- Fire!
- Wood!
- Earth!
- Is everyone all right?
- Yeah.
Yee!
Ryan.
- Did it work?
- Mm-hmm.
- It worked.
- What's this?
I can read the manuscript.
Chi.
Five is one.
Positive Kung.
To take a lif e,
you lose a part of yourself.
Ryan sacrificed himself
to save us.
Komodo expended his energy...
trying to kill Ryan
with negative Kung.
It weakened him.
You made the diff erence, Ryan.
It gave us time to combine
our f orces to def eat him.
Oh, no!
General Grillo, it's over.
Join us in peace.
It's the only way.
Excuse me?
Excuse me.
- I'm--
- Komodo?
I'm lost, and could someone
please tell me the way?
How do I get home?
This is your home.
The Lif espring is alive!
General?
Release all the villagers.
Thank you.
Yee talked.
Ryan.
Are you in or out, Jeff ers?
Don't stand there like a dork!
Ryan, he's just making fun of you.
Man, this is stupid.
Let's make like Tom and "cruise."
Why not?
I can't believe it!
What are you doing?
Finally. I'm glad
you came to your senses.
We got a lot to talk about.
Let's get out of here.
Jeff ers, you'll never make the cut!
Pansy ass!
Shut up, Brad!
Tracy, save it!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Get me out of here! Help!
Quick!
I don't know.
We've gotta help him.
What are you looking at, you wussies?
Get me out of here!
Swim hard, Brad.
You think we ought to call 9-1-1?
Definitely.
How was your night?
Virtuous.
So how many houses did you sell?
Oh, at least 12.
We're set f or lif e.
Good night, honey.
Good night.
Mom?
I love you.
I love you too.
"Spread your wings."
Shake.
Good boy, Bravo.
Hey, Bravo, do you
want to hear about Tao?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org