Encoded by VYTO.
Support us by visiting P2PDL.com
I want you
to enter death.
Here we are,
just like I promised.
Let's do this.
Hi.
I'm Marsden,
we talked on the phone.
I know who you are.
You're late.
Sorry, we, uh,
we made a wrong turn
about 100 miles back.
Tried to call you.
There's no reception out here.
That explains it then.
No, it doesn't.
Look...
I don't know what to tell you.
I have been standing
in the blazing heat
for more than an hour,
a minor pain
in the grand scheme of things.
The pain of your birth
hunts you down in the end.
Okay, maybe it's time
to unpack now.
Yeah.
Okay.
The rules are simple.
No smoking on the premises,
no pets,
and no moving of any furniture.
See you later.
Oh, no, baby, I got it.
It's good.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I'll be in there.
Excuse me, excuse me.
You know how you said
you were waiting out
in the hot sun all day?
Yes.
Why didn't you go
inside the house?
I don't go in there.
Crazy, crazy bitch.
Oh, man.
Pirino, seriously?
I warned you.
You know
this place is a disaster.
Look, me and Colline,
we're gonna take
the master bedroom, all right?
And why is that?
Because I'm me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Dick.
How?
How did we let Pirino
get us into this mess?
He means well.
I guess.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
You got this on your own?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll see you
out there, okay?
Okay.
When Pirino said we were
roughing it, he was
not joking, was he?
Yeah.
It's okay though,
Maybe it'll help
with the ritual.
Listen to you, man.
I made some changes, you know.
Besides, we're camping, right?
This is like the Taj Mahal
of camping tents.
Yeah, right.
This old lady's
got some strange taste.
Yeah, seriously.
It's kind of weird though,
I feel like, I don't know,
like I've seen this shit
somewhere before.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, remember
when we first came to L.A.,
we stopped at that
bed and breakfast?
Yeah, Joshua Tree.
Remember?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, look, it's an antique.
Oh, God.
Oh, do you remember
when your dad
taught us the waltz?
There you go.
Why do you want to waltz?
You know.
I know, we hated it, huh?
One, two, three.
One, two...
You still suck.
I'm a better waltzer than you.
Yeah, well...
I make up for it in style.
You're not gonna leave me?
I'm not making
that mistake again.
I promise.
I'm here for you.
For me?
You know, Lilly was a part
of both of us.
You really got to be there
for her, too.
Of course.
And your son.
Maybe this isn't
just my deal.
We have to do this together.
100%, I promise.
100%.
Hey, I'm putting
my faith in Pirino.
Pirino of all people, come on.
I trust Pirino.
Well, you're crazy.
Shut up.
I trust you too.
You do?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go unpack.
Okay.
Don't lose yourself in here
and keep me lonely.
Fuck.
Someone down there?
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Is anyone in there?
Hey, thinking about her, huh?
Yeah.
Come on.
It's time for a huggy-hug.
Huggy-hug. Jesus.
I was a good mom, you know?
Yeah. You are.
Hey, forget about that.
Come help me with this stuff,
I can't do this
in my condition.
Your condition?
Jesus.
It's not even
pea-sized yet.
Yeah.
Best to be cautious.
Remember when we were younger,
we talked about having our kids
and watching them
grow up together?
Yeah.
We can still do it.
Hey, Colline.
Yeah.
When Marsden
stayed with you guys...
did he ever
talk about me or Lilly?
I'm sure he was thinking
about you, Sera.
Wow.
Mars,
you did good, man.
This is perfect.
You said you wanted
death effigy, right?
It's beautiful.
Hey, you know,
I've been meaning
to give this to you.
What's this?
Remember that week you
and Serafina went to Paris,
Lilly stayed with us?
Yeah.
Why didn't you
tell me about this?
I just found it recently,
it was under the rug
in the guest room.
I miss her, man.
You know, when she passed,
it broke us all up.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
She's gonna take time, right?
Time is now, man.
It's tonight.
Huh?
Throw that energy around.
You wanna put this up?
Let's raise it.
Yeah, let's see
what happens to it.
Yeah, I got it.
One, two, three.
Breathe in and out,
deeply from the abdomen.
You can do this,
you can do this.
We each brought an object
that holds Lilly's energy.
These are attachments
to a life that is no more.
We have to die
to these attachments
in order to set ourselves free.
I can't do this.
You can do it.
You have more toys at home,
you have more pictures at home,
you can do this.
That's good.
I want you guys
to start breathing.
Rapidly.
Fast, tight breathing.
Equal amounts of air
in and out
through your nostrils.
Elevating your consciousness
out of your bodies.
I want you to face death,
enter death,
don't be afraid of death.
Without the awareness of death,
life is ordinary and trivial.
It's only because
death stalks us
that life comes alive.
I want you to face
the mysteries of death,
face it in a way others
dare not tread.
I want you to
forget your religion.
I want you to leave behind
your spiritual beliefs.
Any preconception you have
of what death is.
There is no heaven,
there is no hell,
there is no afterlife,
there is no reincarnation!
Death is the infinite abyss
of pure nonexistence.
Enter it and be done.
I want you to call death
with me, call death.
I call death.
I can't say that.
You can say it,
"I call death."
I call death.
Say it!
Say it.
I call death.
I call death!
I call death! I call death!
I call death.
I call death!
I call death! I call death!
You call death!
Okay, guys,
let's just breathe.
Deep breaths from the abdomen.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I can't remember anything.
Does anybody remember
planning this trip?
Sure. We, uh...
Honey.
I don't remember either.
Huh.
I can't remember a thing.
What?
Oh, my God.
I just saw something
in the house.
Something in the house,
we're all outside.
Mars, babe.
You really scared the crap
out of me.
Yeah,
that was spiritual,
heavy breathing nonsense.
It's pointless.
Have you ever hallucinated
like that before?
No.
You okay, sweetheart?
It's not just your memory.
I can't remember how
and why we came out here.
How did our life
get to be such a nightmare?
Baby, is everything okay
in there?
Yeah.
Come back to bed.
Yeah, in a minute.
Wake up.
Mars.
Marsden.
I want to know who did this.
Somebody speak!
I saw that burn in the fire.
Yeah.
Do you think this is funny?
No, not at all.
If this is your idea
of helping people,
it's sick, it's fucking stupid.
Look, Sera, I don't know
what's going on
but there's no one here
who'd do this.
Okay?
This is my daughter's doll.
I can still
smell her scent in it,
I can smell her,
I can feel her.
How dare you!
No, why don't you
stand up for her?
Look, guys, there's got to be
a rational explanation, okay?
Did you do this, man?
Where's the needle
and the thread?
Maybe you did it.
I'll find out.
Show you who your friends
really are.
Sera.
Oh, my God.
That trick was revolting.
I get it, shock therapy.
Why didn't you just tell me?
Did you think
I was gonna stop you?
I probably would have.
Look, if you want me to be
part of this whole
spiritual guru thing,
we got to start
trusting each other.
Why do you think
I would do that?
I didn't do that.
The whole point was
to release the inner demons,
so why would I recycle them?
It doesn't make any sense.
Look, if this is gonna work,
we have to be a unified front.
Great. She's tearing
our room apart.
Damn it.
Fuck.
Colline?
Colline!
She okay?
Oh, my God.
What?
Who cut you?
No, no, no, no,
it's just stitched up.
What happened to you?
Listen, you guys stay right
here, I'll be right back.
Something hit me.
It burns!
Baby, it hurts.
Here, all together.
It's okay, just relax.
All right.
Guys, get upstairs.
Get in a room, lock the door
and call the police, okay?
Let's take her outside.
Fuck it.
Just go upstairs.
Hurry up.
Go with her, go with her.
I'm right behind you.
We got to find him!
Just go upstairs!
Get him!
Go upstairs!
Lock the door!
We're gonna get him, all right?
We're gonna get him.
Lock the door!
Hey, come on!
Snap out of it, man.
Go check
the front of the house,
I'll check
the back of the house.
Okay.
All right?
Hurry up, come on.
Let's go.
Marsden, get down here!
Shit.
Marsden, get out here!
Pirino!
Pirino?
Jeez.
Oh, my God.
There's nobody out there.
What do you mean?
He's gone.
He's completely gone.
How can that be?
He took the car.
Come on.
What?
Why?
I just don't get it.
I mean, how the hell
can someone stitch you up
that quickly?
I just don't get it.
Doesn't make any sense.
You were only alone
for a couple of minutes.
At least we know you weren't
hallucinating earlier on.
Yeah.
I still can't
remember anything.
Look, let's just
get out of here.
He took the car.
Well, this is
just fucking great.
We have no car...
no food.
And somehow
we got to get to a hospital.
And how do you
propose we do that?
Fuck.
We're gonna have to walk.
He's right.
There's no other way.
That's 50 miles.
50 miles to the nearest town.
Look, we're gonna have
to figure out some protection.
You don't plan this right,
we could die out there.
What if he comes back?
Fuck him, I hope he comes back.
Oh, screw it, screw it.
I'm taking a break.
Oh, God.
If we can't walk
a quarter of a mile
I don't think we can make 50.
I mean, there's
bound to be some cars
once we hit the highway.
We didn't see any
driving up past Barstow.
Guys, we got to stay
positive, all right?
I don't know.
Maybe if we
get into that valley,
we might be
able to pick up a signal.
What do you think?
Looks like about 20 miles.
That's less than 50.
Oh, God.
We're gonna die.
Yeah.
This ain't right.
How can this be possible?
I don't know.
There's not supposed to be
an eclipse right now, is there?
The moon is working
on its own almanac.
What does this mean?
Guys, we should go back.
No, dude, we should
just keep going.
I don't want to go back
to that house.
What do you think now?
Maybe we should go?
Oh, shit!
Go, go!
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
It's the end of the world.
Hey!
Maybe it was just the wind.
Maybe there's a window open
on the other side.
No, no.
Pirino, it's just a wall
on that side, man.
Go and check it out.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Oh, God.
Get out of there!
Shit.
Look, man, you come out
or we're coming in!
Marsden.
Dude you just signed your
own fucking death warrant!
Go!
Remember, there's, like,
an axe or a crowbar.
Yeah, I saw that.
Go get it, Pirino, go!
Okay, listen, take care.
Hey, take this, okay?
Come on, man!
Come on!
I'll try.
Ah!
God.
That armor's thick.
So's the wall, man.
What the hell is this thing
doing down here?
Don't let it psych you out.
Any two-bit magician
can do that!
Look, motherfucker,
I ain't scared, man!
You ain't scaring nobody!
I got a big axe out here!
It's going to up your ass,
through your mouth,
smashing your teeth out,
you motherfucker!
You dirty motherfucker!
Hey, Mr. Spiritual Leader.
Come on, calm down.
Look, I got an idea.
Got it?
Yeah.
Definitely don't think he's
gonna get out of there, man.
Are we?
I was thinking of us
last night.
Yeah. Me and you.
I got something.
People are
being warned to stay indoors.
The electrical storm
has already claimed hundreds
of thousands of lives.
Reports are still coming in
from every
corner of the globe.
Scientists remain perplexed
as to the cause of the eclipse
and how it could be visible
on every continent.
Religious leaders
in Europe, India,
the Middle East and America
have called all peoples
of all faiths to pray.
How can this be possible?
I mean, how can the eclipse be
seen all over the world
or even, like...
It's the wrath of God.
Look, I wasn't
religious before but
I guess it took the
end of the world.
Seriously, am I the only one
that's gonna keep
their fucking head on?
No.
Maybe Colline's right.
Great.
We have to save our baby.
Are you serious?
What?
How could you do this to me?
Did you think
that I would never find out?
I'm not stupid.
Did you think that I'm stupid?
I'm sorry!
God, I'm sorry!
It was like the worst
year of my life.
Yeah, it was the worst year
of my life too,
and I didn't go running
into the arms of somebody else.
I'm so sorry, just forgive me.
Ten years, man.
Ten years of spiritual work.
I still want to kick your ass.
Fuck.
Spiritual work, my ass.
You're a fraud, our whole
relationship's a joke.
We came here
because we trusted you.
Now we're all gonna die.
You trusted me?
None of you trusted me!
None of you believed in me!
Especially you.
You know what a joke is?
You know what the fraud is?
Right there.
Fuck you.
Sera, I'm sorry,
but Marsden and I go way back.
No. No, we don't.
I was always
meant to have his baby.
No. I'm not going to hear
any of that high school
abortion shit.
We put that in the past.
This is destiny.
Sweetheart.
Aaahhh!
Give it back!
Get the fuck away from me!
Is this a high school
promise ring?
Have you lost your mind?
Come on, the end of the world
is happening
and what the fuck are we doing?
Talking about this!
Sera.
No, you get away from me.
I don't know you people.
Sera.
I don't know you.
I love you, Sera, I'm sorry.
Fuck!
Why?
Our baby.
Sera!
God, shit.
Come on.
Please, please, open the door.
Just leave me alone!
I do not want you
coming in this bedroom.
Why don't you go sleep
with Colline or Pirino
for all I care.
The three of you can go
doing this, whatever you do.
Sera, I'm sorry, okay.
Look, when Lilly died...
I know I left.
That was a weak move,
but I was scared, okay.
I've been an arrogant prick
our whole relationship,
and it took electrical
hellfire for me to see that.
I don't know
how you can forgive me,
but I'm begging you, please.
I miss you, sweetheart.
I'm sorry, Sera.
I am so mad at you right now.
I mean, if this is the end...
you know, like,
if this is really
the end of it all,
I want you to know something.
I'm nothing without you.
I mean, whether
we get out of here or not,
whether we stay
together or not,
I'm always gonna love you.
Nothing's ever gonna
change that.
Not even you.
You shouldn't have done that.
Look who's talking.
It's bad timing.
We're out of time.
You know what?
When we get out of here,
if we get out of here,
me and you are gonna settle up.
I'm so sorry, man.
Right now we got
bigger problems.
Come on.
This is it.
I found some kerosene,
candles and a couple
of lanterns.
It's not much.
All our food's out there.
Oh, great.
We still got water.
I'm assuming
cannibalism isn't an option.
I really screwed up, man.
I'm sorry.
Save it.
It's just the two of us.
We'll keep each other safe.
What do you make
of this shit, man?
I've been studying Tarot cards
and symbols for years and this,
this right here,
this freaks me out.
How would she know about
this months in advance?
Clear premonition.
Oh, come on, man.
I don't believe
in that shit.
Well, you know what?
Your belief system needs
to get a little more flexible.
It's that landlady.
She owns this place.
We figure her out,
we figure everything out.
So now she is in charge
of the weather, huh?
Hey, she knew about
the guy in the basement.
What?
What did she say
when we first pulled up?
What did she say to you?
I don't know,
she spoke in riddles.
You know what she said?
She threatened me
for causing her pain.
I'm gonna go to bed.
Well, you know what?
It's been 36 hours,
I'm gonna get some rest.
Maybe things will be
better in the morning.
Sweet dreams.
Oh.
Oh, where's your heart?
Where is your heart?
I'm scared.
Lilly?
Wake the fuck up!
Sera?
Sera.
Oh, my God.
You're okay.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hurry up.
Sit up, come on.
Get your back up.
Okay.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, my God.
How is he doing this?
My baby.
Oh, my God.
My baby's gone.
Why is he doing this?
My baby is gone!
Fuck this, man!
Fuck death!
Why did you cut the rope?
You, it sees through you,
it will shut you up.
Oh, you know all this bullshit?
Yeah.
You're a liar!
Why did you cut the rope?
Just answer that.
He can see into your soul!
Why did you cut the rope?
Stop!
I'm leaving.
I'm out of here!
Colline!
No, baby, no!
I'm glad Lilly died.
She was a mistake.
Fuck her!
No!
No, hey!
Baby, no!
No!
Colline, no!
No! No!
I know.
I'm sorry.
Marsden!
Whoa, man.
Are you out of your
fucking mind?
Colline was right.
Why did she cut the rope?
Why did you cut the rope?
Don't you take another step,
Mars, don't make me do it.
Look, she's innocent.
There's something
else down here, man.
You know that.
Pi.
Please, this won't
bring her back.
Please.
Baby.
I'm sorry.
You know what?
I think we can cut these.
You know, I really think
they're made out of our own
nerve endings or something.
How is that possible?
How can any of this be?
Shit.
We have unfinished business.
Colline?
Shut up.
Mars.
What did you just do?
I put them into time out,
just the way
you like it, right?
No more distractions
from your work, right, daddy?
You thought you could get away
with dismissing me
the way you dismissed Lilly?
Trying to ignore me? Really?
You have a stitch
on the back of your neck
that leads into your brain.
You like it, huh?
You like it.
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
All men are puppets!
That is the infinite abyss
of pure nonexistence!
How does it feel to be
fucked and thrown aside
like a piece of shit, huh?
How does it feel to be
fucked and thrown aside
like a piece of shit?
Look, Colline, I'm so sorry.
Death is...
No heaven, no hell.
No afterlife, no reincarnation.
No other side.
Say it!
Drop your spiritual beliefs.
Our hearts have
descended together to dance
in the fires of hell
for all eternity.
I'm sorry.
You took a piece of me.
Now it's time
to return the favor.
You like that.
God, please, just tell me how
the fuck to get out of this!
Please!
Fuck!
This is your fault.
My fault?
You're the one that wanted us
to come on death trip,
bring us all the way out here,
meditate on death.
This is your fault, man.
It's not my fault.
Death found us.
Shit!
Lilly...
Baby, if you can
hear me right now...
You have to cross over, baby.
I love you so much.
You have to let go of us.
I saw something out there.
There's just no one out there.
No.
There's something out there.
We have to help her cross over.
Okay.
I don't want to die here.
We'll make it out of here,
I promise.
It's good to see you
two together again.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I started all this.
I'm gonna end it.
Where are you going, man?
To hell.
What is it?
It's ball lightning.
It's beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
Ah!
No!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
Aah!
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, P.
You okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no.
Look at me.
It's okay. It's okay.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
No!
Don't!
Wait!
Shit!
Wait, wait.
Please.
What have we done?
Fuck.
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
♪ Gently down the stream ♪
♪ Merrily, merrily, merrily,
merrily, life is but a dream ♪
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
♪ Gently down the stream ♪
♪ Merrily, merrily, merrily,
merrily, life is but a dream ♪
Oh, fuck you.
Fuck you.
Whoever is doing this,
fuck you!
But remember...
...the pain you birth
hunts you down in the end.
The pain you birth is the pain
that hunts us down in the end.
What?
It's not Lilly
who needs to be saved.
Baby, it's us.
What did we do?
Let me go, I'm scared.
Mommy.
Lilly?
My God, Sera.
Sera.
Quantum physics.
That's what it's got to be.
We've been, like, sucked into
a parallel universe
or something.
No, no.
I won't let you.
No, come on,
I can hear, please.
No, the thing up there
is not her.
No, it's not Lilly.
It's not.
Sera, listen,
I know what this is.
What?
We have to ask
for Lilly's forgiveness.
Why?
We were terrible parents.
Oh, no.
Yes, we were.
We always put ourselves first.
No, we gave her everything.
No, no!
We treated her like a doll,
a disposable doll, Sera.
No. Pirino, he drugged us.
He drugged us.
What?
Yeah.
Yeah, can't you get it?
We're walking around
our own house
and we can't even recognize it.
Lilly's still alive.
She's still alive.
What's wrong?
Can't you feel it? Come on.
Baby.
It's okay.
Me and Daddy are here.
You're safe now.
Sera!
Let her out!
Let her out of there!
Lilly...
Is that you?
My poor baby.
It's my fault.
It's your daddy's fault.
How can you forgive me?
Just take me.
We have missed you.
You missed me?
You must all return,
no matter what.
Return where?
You know where.
No, I don't.
This is real.
How would it be?
I'm a human.
Are you?
Of course I am.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Self deception is a cruel mess.
Tell me what the fuck
is going on!
You know what's there.
You're back.
This is today.
Am I dead?
No.
Then where am I?
Hell.
You don't have to die
to get there.
How the fuck can I be there
and here at the same time?
How can anyone
be anywhere at any time?
This is the mystery
of consciousness.
You can occupy
many bodies at once.
Some physical, some ethereal...
but ultimately an illusion.
A part of you is in
Lilly's subconscious now
in her dying
mental images.
Your lives
that feel so real
are merely dreams
within dreams,
rising and collapsing
like waves
in the ocean of
consciousness.
You and Lilly
are right here...
right now.
Crystallized into form
by the power of
your mutual pain.
Tell me...
What kind of god
would make
a fucking place like this?
You tell me that.
Tell me!
The god you dreamed up!
Suffer or surrender.
It is always your choice.
It was never locked.
Why don't you turn
the light of your attention
back onto
your own shadow?
What happened?
Oh, man.
What? What?
Put a little less pedal
on that metal.
You guys were the ones
that wanted to leave Vegas.
I wanted to stay.
Yeah, well, we just want
to get home in one piece.
Oh, my God.
Get off his back, he's fine.
Hey, Lilly Willy,
you want to drive?
Hey, no, no, no,
put your seat...
She's awake.
Oh, my God.
Look, we're doing
everything that we can.
And we're gonna keep trying.
There was, um...
There was another car,
and, um...
There was no other driver.
It was me.
Yes, there was.
It jumped the median
and it wasn't our fault.
It wasn't our fault.
I can't lose
you right now, please,
I can't lose you right now.
I'm sorry.
I don't know
how I got to this realization.
This. This,
we can't do this anymore.
God, no, listen.
We did it.
What?
There was no other car.
You know there wasn't.
No.
Yes.
Come on.
No, no.
Yes, there was and I do not
want to talk about this.
You wanted me to lie.
There's no way to know it.
Listen.
We're just killing ourselves.
Look at this shit.
Look at it.
There was no other car.
Sera, listen to me.
I'm so sick and tired
of killing ourselves...
with guilt.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't watch
this happen to you.
Or to me.
It's gonna get better.
I miss Lilly too.
I miss her so much, baby.
I miss her so much.
Encoded by VYTO.
Support us by visiting P2PDL.com