YOU'RE LOOKING AT GARY,
INDIANA, U.S.A.,
A CITY WITH THE HIGHEST
MURDER RATE IN AMERICA,
MAYBE THE WORLD.
A FACTORY TOWN THAT SOMEHOW
BECAME A GANG TOWN.
BACK IN THE FIFTIES,
THE COMMUNITY WAS SUPPORTED
BY THE U.S. STEEL MILL.
IT WAS DAMN HARD WORK,
BUT PEOPLE RAISED
THEIR FAMILIES WELL.
THEN JUST 20 YEARS LATER,
WITHOUT WARNING,
US STEEL SHUT DOWN
70% OF THE MILL.
AT FIRST, THE WORKERS THOUGHT
IT WAS TEMPORARY,
BUT IT WASN'T.
THEIR SAVINGS WENT,
UNEMPLOYMENT RAN OUT,
AND SLOWLY,
THE FORMER STEELWORKERS
LOST THE LAST TWO THINGS
THEY HAD LEFT--
THEIR PRIDE AND THEIR HOPE.
AND THAT HAS BEEN
THE INHERITANCE
OF THE CHILDREN OF GARY.
THIS WAS THE PALACE
MOVIE THEATER.
THE LAST MOVIE THAT PLAYED
HERE WAS STAR WARS.
THAT'S THE BAKERY.
IT USED TO MAKE
THE BEST DAMN
GLAZED AND CHOCOLATE
DOUGHNUTS IN TOWN.
THAT'S WHERE
HAYNES' RESTAURANT ONCE STOOD.
THEY HAD THE BEST
BARBECUED RIBS.
THIS IS
THE MEMORIAL AUDITORIUM--
HOME OF TWO STATE
BASKETBALL CHAMPIONSHIPS.
MORE THAN 350,000 BACK THEN.
NOW THERE'S
ONLY 150,000 LEFT
THAT STILL CALL GARY
THEIR HOME.
THIS ABANDONED STEEL MILL
IS NOW HEADQUARTERS
TO A GANG CALLED
THE DIABLOS.
AND THE OLD TRAIN DEPOT
IS A HANGOUT FOR THEIR RIVALS--
THE REBELS.
HEY, PUNK!
FUCK HIM, MAN!
WHAT'S UP, PUNK?
YOU READY FOR THE BALL?
I WANT IT.
YOU GOT IT?
YO, SHUT UP!
HE'LL KNOCK YOUR ASS OUT!
SHUT UP! SHOOT! SHOOT!
OH! THAT'S SHIT!
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
THE BROTHER'S FROM,
BUT THAT SHIT
IS NOT RIGHT.
YOU BETTER GET OUT OF HERE.
GRAMS.
COME HERE, MAN.
NICE GAME, MAN.
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF MY FACE.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
YOU DID GOOD OUT THERE.
THANKS, MAN.
APPRECIATE IT.
WHERE YOU LEARN
TO PLAY LIKE THAT?
JUST A LITTLE
SOMETHING
I PICKED UP
ON THE STREET,
THAT'S ALL.
GOING TO COME BACK,
GIVE US A CHANCE
TO WIN SOME OF
THAT PAPER BACK?
I GOT A LITTLE
TRIP TO TAKE
OUT OF TOWN,
BUT I'LL STOP
BACK TO HOLLER
AT EVERYBODY.
KAYO.
YEAH, GIVE
THE MAN HIS DUE.
THANKS, MAN.
IF IT WERE UP TO ME,
YOU WOULDN'T GET SHIT.
I'M JUST HERE
TO PLAY, MAN,
THAT'S ALL.
EXCUSE ME.
YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE CARE
OF THAT PUNK HUSTLER, RIGHT?
YEAH, YOU KNOW I AM.
NOW IF YOU'RE THROUGH
BULLSHITTING,
WE GOT A LOT
REAL BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
ALL THAT MONEY?
FOR BASKETBALL?
AIN'T BAD
FOR A LITTLE HUSTLE.
BUT YOU DIDN'T TELL THEM
YOU GOT A BASKETBALL
SCHOLARSHIP TO UCLA.
WHY WOULD I?
IT'S A ONE-TIME DEAL.
I DON'T GET YOU.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
MAN, WHAT DON'T YOU GET?
IT'S EASY MONEY.
ME AND BRENDA WANT
TO CHILL IN STYLE.
WHATEVER.
ALL THAT MONEY,
I BET YOU WERE
DUNKIN' ON 'EM
LIKE JORDAN!
DID YOU STICK
YOUR TONGUE OUT?
NAH, BUT I WAS
RIPPIN' 'EM OFF PROPER.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING?
BUT ON THE REAL DEAL,
YOU KNOW WHY I'M SO GOOD?
NO, KENNY. TELL US,
WHY ARE YOU SO GOOD?
WELL, IT'S GENETICS,
MARCUS.
AND IF YOU'RE
NOT BORN WITH IT,
YOU DON'T GET IT.
FOLKS,
KENNY DOESN'T KNOW WHERE
HE GOT HIS GENES FROM.
BACK TO YOU, BRAD.
I KNOW WHERE.
YOU KNOW WHERE?
THE STORE CLOSES
ABOUT 7:00,
SO MEET ME THERE
AND DON'T BE LATE.
I'LL MAKE A PHONE CALL
TO MY LADY
AND BE RIGHT BACK.
USE THE PHONE
IN THE STORE.
BOOKMANS WILL LET YOU.
I NEED MY PRIVACY
IN A PHONE BOOTH.
OH, THE LOVEBIRDS
NEED THEIR PRIVACY.
OH, HOW CUTE.
YOU JUST WANT
TO TAKE NOTES.
COOL OUT.
YOU'RE LOOKING MIGHTY
WELL, MISS DAWSON.
HEY, MR. BOOKMAN.
I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
TAKE A BREAK.
HOW YOU DOING,
MISS DAWSON?
DID YOU BRING
YOUR COUPONS?
BUT--BUT--
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
CHECK THIS. I GOT PLANS
LIKE YOU WON'T BELIEVE.
[MACHINE GUN FIRE]
OH, NO!
KENNY! KENNY!
KENNY!
I TOLD YOU!
THE BOOKMAN MARKET.
I JUST SENT
FOR THE POLICE.
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
KENNY!
OH!
OH, MY GOD!
[MARCUS]
KENNY, GET UP!
GET UP, KENNY!
GET UP!
GODDAMN!
DON'T YOU
DIE ON ME, MAN!
PLEASE!
WHY DOESN'T SOMEONE
CALL AN AMBULANCE?
KENNY! DON'T LEAVE ME!
DON'T LEAVE ME!
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[POLICE RADIO]
IT'S UNREAL.
WE PRACTICALLY RAISED
THAT BOY'S MOTHER.
THESE ARE GOOD PEOPLE.
IT'S A DAMN TRAGEDY!
DO YOU KNOW IF
HE WAS IN A GANG?
OH,
NOT KENNY THOMPSON!
MARCUS, WAS KENNY IN
SOME KIND OF TROUBLE
WITH THE GANGS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS IT WOULD
BE A WASTE OF TIME
TO ASK WHETHER
YOU SAW ANYTHING.
WHY?
NOBODY EVER SEES
ANYTHING AROUND HERE.
THEY BURY THEIR DEAD,
AND NOBODY EVER SEES
ANYTHING.
THAT SO?
UH, MARVIN--
I'M TALKING TO
THIS DETECTIVE.
SO...TALK TO ME.
ANYTHING YOU SAY
IS BETWEEN US.
NOBODY ELSE
HAS TO KNOW.
SUPPOSE...
I DIDN'T SEE THE GUNMAN,
BUT I DID GET
THE LICENSE NUMBER
OF THE CAR.
BLUE COUGAR
WITH A BROKEN RIGHT
TAILLIGHT.
LOOKS TO ME LIKE
YOU HAD IT IN MIND
TO GIVE ME THIS.
THESE ARE GOOD PEOPLE.
THE BOY'S MOTHER--
HE'S NEVER BEEN
IN ANY TROUBLE--
SHE RUNS
THE BEAUTY PARLOR
ACROSS THE STREET.
...BROTHERS CAN'T TALK?
YOU GUYS ALWAYS
PICKIN' ON...
WAS THAT
THE SMART THING TO DO?
PROBABLY NOT,
BUT DO YOU THINK
I WAS WRONG?
IT'S GOT TO BE YOU,
DOESN'T IT, MARVIN?
FINALLY,
IT'S GOT TO BE ME.
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I FEEL DAMN GOOD ABOUT IT.
RRRR!
NOW, SON, DON'T GO TRYING
TO GET YOUR OWN JUSTICE.
IT JUST AIN'T RIGHT.
YEAH. WE'LL SEE.
WELL, AREN'T YOU
GOING AFTER HIM?
AND DO WHAT, HONEY?
LOCK HIM UP TILL
HE COOLS DOWN?
HE'LL COME
TO HIS SENSES.
HE JUST NEEDS
A LITTLE TIME.
THIS IS DETECTIVE WAITS
ON THAT 2829--
BLUE COUGAR
WITH THE BROKEN
RIGHT TAILLIGHT?
ANYTHING NEW
ON THAT YET?
THIS IS DISPATCHER.
NEGATIVE ON THE BLUE
COUGAR.
WE'RE STILL CHECKING.
WHAT'S THE WORD, MAN?
I'M FROM THE HOOD, BOY
CAN'T COME MAKIN'
THINGS
LIKE A LIVIN' HELL LIVIN'
ALONE ON THE GHETTO STREETS
Gs ALL LOOK AT ME
AS I RIDE BY
SHIT, I'M LIVIN' IN THE LAND
WHERE THEY DRIVE-BY
BACK TO THE HIDEAWAY,
RIGHT AWAY
SNITCHINGEST NIGGERS
I FIGURE GOTS TO DIE TODAY
BETTER YOU THAN ME
SEEMS THAT'S
THE ATTITUDE
OF A BROTHER THAT'S BEEN
RAISED ON THE STREET
WHAT'S THE WORD, MAN?
WHAT'S THE WORD, MAN...
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WANT ME TO SHOW
THIS PUNK TO THE DOOR?
IT'S COOL.
RECOGNIZE, BOY.
I KNOW YOU,
DON'T I?
YEAH, I'M THE WORD MAN.
I KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING
ON THE STREETS.
THE WORD MAN, HUH?
SO WHAT'S THE WORD
ON THE STREETS?
LOSE THE COUGAR.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR IT.
OLD MAN FROM
THE GROCERY STORE
GAVE YOU UP.
NOT MR. BOOKMAN?
THOUGHT YOU'D
WANT TO KNOW.
THAT'S MY FAVORITE
FUCKIN' STORE.
WHY'D HE DO
THAT SHIT, MAN?
'CAUSE HE'S FUCKED UP
LIKE THAT.
WHAT'S YOUR ANGLE?
I LIVE ON THE STREETS.
SOMETIMES I GET MESSED WITH.
WE DON'T WANT YOU
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT
ANYMORE.
AIN'T NOBODY
EVER GOING TO MESS
WITH YOU AGAIN.
YOU'RE ONE OF US
NOW.
KAYO.
BURN THE COUGAR.
NO PROBLEM.
I GOT THAT.
I WANT YOU TO CHECK OUT
THAT BOOKMAN STORE.
THE OLD MAN SAYS
HE DIDN'T RAT US OUT,
YOU LET HIM ALONE.
IF HE OWNS UP,
YOU TAKE HIS ASS OUT.
I BELIEVE
IN THE HONOR SYSTEM.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THAT HONOR SYSTEM.
I LIKE THAT.
TAKE HIS ASS OUT.
YEAH.
[SIREN]
ALL RIGHT.
IS THIS THE CAR
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR?
YES, IT IS.
IF THEY KNOW
WE MADE THE CAR,
THEY KNOW WHERE
WE GOT THE INFORMATION.
THE MONEY'S STILL
IN THE TILL.
GO ON AND GET IT.
IT AIN'T
ABOUT THE MONEY!
I CAN MAKE
MORE IN A DAY
THAN YOU CAN
IN A LIFETIME.
WHAT'S THIS
OLD PUNK SHIT?
YOU TALKED
TO THE POLICE?
I TOLD THEM WHERE
THAT BOY'S MOTHER LIVED.
HE'S LYING.
HE GAVE US UP.
WHY WOULD YOU DO
THAT?
WE AIN'T NEVER
DID NOTHING
TO YOUR STORE.
WE PAID
FOR EVERYTHING
WE TOOK.
YOU SHOULDN'T
EVEN GET INVOLVED
IN THIS TYPE
OF SHIT HERE.
NOT MUCH HERE, OLD MAN.
EVERY OTHER STORE
GET HIT BUT YOU.
WE RESPECTED YOU!
LOOK WHAT THE FUCK
YOU DO TO US!
DID TO YOU?
WHY IS IT ALWAYS
WHAT SOMEBODY'S
DOING TO YOU?
DON'T MATTER NO MORE,
'CAUSE YOU FUCKED UP!
YOU SEE, THAT'S WHAT
AMERICA'S MISSING TODAY.
BALLS!
IT TAKES A LOT
TO SHOOT A BOY DOWN
IN A PHONE BOOTH,
DOESN'T IT?
THIS MAN RIGHT HERE,
HE GOT BIG
HUMONGOUS BALLS!
SAY YOU'RE
FUCKING SORRY, MAN.
THE FUCKING CUSTOMER'S
ALWAYS RIGHT.
OW! AAH! SHIT, MAN!
HE'S BLEEDING LIKE
A MOTHERFUCKER, MAN!
UH-HUH.
HOW'S YOUR ASS FEEL NOW?
FEELING ANY PAIN?
FEEL PAIN, HUH?
TAKE SOME ASPIRIN
AND PAIN RELIEVER.
FEEL PAIN!
FUCK THIS OLD
MOTHERFUCKER!
BETTER YET, BOBBY, BRING
YOUR MOTHERFUCKING ASS
OVER HERE.
MAN, IT AIN'T EVEN
GOING ON LIKE THAT.
YOU WANT TO BE
A REBEL OR NOT?
COME ON OVER HERE,
MAN!
YOU GOING TO BUST
THIS CAPS UP
IN HIS ASS.
YOU WANT
TO GET YOUR STRIPE
FOR A REBEL OR WHAT?
KILL THAT MOTHERFUCKER,
BOBBY.
IT'S INITIATION DAY.
YOU'RE OLD.
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE
SOON ANYWAY.
QUIT THAT BULLSHIT.
POP HIS OLD ASS.
I'M GOD!
YOU'RE NOTHING!
IT'S TIME TO CROSS
THE LINE, BABY.
DO THAT SHIT,
OR I'M GOING
TO TAKE THAT GUN BACK
AND POP YOUR MOTHERFUCKING
ASS, YOU HEAR ME?
I SAID POP HIS ASS!
BRING YOUR ASS ON
SO WE CAN GET THE FUCK
UP OUT OF HERE.
FOR GOD'S SAKE
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE
MORE POWER TO THE PEOPLE?
FOR GOD'S SAKE
YOU GOT TO GIVE
MORE POWER TO THE PEOPLE
FOR GOD'S SAKE
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE
MORE POWER TO THE PEOPLE?
FOR GOD'S SAKE
GOT TO HAVE IT,
MORE POWER
FOR GOD'S SAKE
MARVIN BOOKMAN,
YOU'RE A DAMN FOOL.
YOU JUST LIE STILL, PAPA,
AND DON'T PAY
ANY ATTENTION TO HER.
HELLO, MOMS.
HOW IS HE?
HE WAS SHOT
IN THE SHOULDER,
BUT THE DOCTOR
SAID HE'D LIVE.
AND HOW YOU HOLDING UP?
I'M DOING FINE NOW.
SIS.
COME HERE, JOHN.
HOW YOU DOING, POPS?
WELL...
I'M NOT GOING
INTO THE STORE TODAY.
I SHOULD'VE MADE YOU
LEAVE HERE A LONG TIME AGO.
WHEN IS THE LAST TIME
ANYBODY MADE HIM DO
ANYTHING?
POPS, THIS PLACE
IS JUST NOT RIGHT--
THIS PLACE WAS
A GOOD PLACE.
I COME HERE
WITH NOTHING.
GOT A JOB
AT U.S. STEEL.
YEAH, YEAH, I REMEMBER.
THE DAY THE WAR ENDED
YOU QUIT THE MILL
WITH $9,500 IN THE BANK.
MARRIED YOUR MOTHER,
BOUGHT THE STORE.
IF I STAYED IN THE MILL,
I MIGHT'VE MADE FOREMAN,
BUT I'D BE
OUT OF WORK BY NOW.
MAYBE LIVING
ON THE STREET,
LIKE SOME OF MY FRIENDS.
PEOPLE WORK
ALL THEIR LIVES
AND WIND UP SLEEPING
IN A CARDBOARD BOX
IN A DOORWAY.
IS IT ANY WONDER
THESE KIDS TODAY
DON'T WANT TO WORK?
THEY DON'T EVEN WANT
TO LIVE TO GROW OLD.
I'M GETTING YOU
OUT OF HERE
SO THIS CAN NEVER
HAPPEN AGAIN.
YOU SHOULD COME BACK MORE.
YOUR MOTHER MISSES YOU.
GET SOME REST, O.K.?
I GOT A FRIEND IN L.A.
LOOKING FOR AN APARTMENT
NEAR ME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU AND POPS,
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE ANYMORE.
YOU'RE JUST
LIKE THEM--
TELLING
US WHAT TO DO.
BUT THERE AIN'T
NOTHING HERE.
YOU'RE LIVING
IN THE PAST.
MY JOHNNY WOULDN'T
TALK LIKE THAT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS
OVER A CUP OF COFFEE,
O.K.?
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD.
LET ME BORROW
YOUR CAR.
MRS. BOOKMAN--
STAY THE HELL
AWAY FROM ME.
MY HUSBAND HAD TO DO
THE RIGHT THING.
WHERE WERE YOU?
YOU KNEW WHAT THOSE
ANIMALS COULD DO.
MISTAKES WERE MADE.
WE GOT THERE TOO LATE.
MARVIN MADE THE MISTAKE
TRUSTING YOU.
I'M GOING TO FIND
THE ONE THAT DID THIS
TO YOUR HUSBAND.
YOU'RE JUST
A WASTE OF TIME.
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE
UP THERE
HOGGING EVERYTHING
THEN AT LAST
WE WILL HAVE A BLAST
ABOUT THE PEOPLE'S
MONEY AND THINGS
AND IF THEY GO
FAR AWAY
MIGHT AS WELL
GIVE SOME TO ME
LET HIM LIVE
HIS HEART OUT
BUT NEVER ADD MISERY
GIRL, SOME PEOPLE
ARE STARVING TO DEATH
NEVER KNEW
BUT ONLY HEARD OF
AND THEY NEVER HAD
HAPPINESS
FOR GOD'S SAKE
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE
MORE POWER TO THE PEOPLE?
FOR GOD'S SAKE
YOU BETTER GIVE
MORE POWER TO THE PEOPLE
YEAH
FOR GOD'S SAKE...
HEY!
WHAT THE FUCK?
WHAT'S UP, OLD MAN?
THE STORE CLOSED!
WE RUN THIS
MOTHERFUCKER NOW.
GET OUT
BEFORE YOU GET HURT.
PUT IT BACK!
WE STAKE CLAIM ON THIS
MOTHERFUCKING PLACE.
I'M GOING TO SAY IT ONCE!
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE!
COME ON. GET OUT OF HERE!
LOOKIT THERE.
[BONES CRACKING]
DROP YOUR GUN!
PUT YOUR GUN DOWN!
GET THE FUCK--AAH!
OH, SHIT!
GET BACK! GET BACK!
GET BACK!
WHAT YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
DO IT!
PUT THE GUN DOWN!
I'M PUTTING THE GUN
DOWN, MAN.
FUCK YOU!
IT'S COOL, MAN.
AAH!
ONE LEG,
GET YOUR ASS OUT!
AND BRING
YOUR ASS HOME.
AAH!
THAT'S FOR KENNY,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
RUN! RUN!
GET UP! RUN!
NICE TO HAVE YOU
BACK HOME.
THANKS.
SORRY TO HEAR ABOUT
YOUR SON, LAURIE.
WELL, WELL!
LOOK AT THAT.
SOMEBODY FAMOUS.
CAN I HAVE YOUR
AUTOGRAPH, MR. BOOKMAN?
HA HA!
PLEASE?
THIS MARKET
IS CONFISCATED PROPERTY.
IT'S OURS NOW.
YOU KNOW, THIS USED
TO BE MY FAVORITE
GROCERY STORE.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
I'D COME IN HERE,
AND YOUR FATHER
WOULD GIVE ME
A FRESH SLICE
OF BOLOGNA.
I LIKED YOUR DAD,
SO I STAYED OFF
HIS ASS.
I PROTECTED HIM.
AND HOW DOES HE SHOW
HIS APPRECIATION?
THIS IS A VERY SAD DAY,
JOHN BOOKMAN.
I JUST CANCELED
YOUR CHARGE ACCOUNT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
LIKE YOUR PAPA,
STARTING SOMETHING
YOU CAN'T FINISH.
THAT AIN'T NEVER BEEN
MY STYLE...BROTHA.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
POLICE COMING!
LET'S GET UP OUT OF HERE!
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER...
STAR.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
THEY GOT THE MONEY.
THEY GOT THE POWER.
THEY RUN THE STREETS.
THAT'S NOT EVEN
WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
I REMEMBER
IT USED TO BE
ABOUT GETTING OUT.
NOT THIS BUNCH.
THEY DON'T WANT
TO GET OUT.
THERE'S NO PLACE
FOR THEM TO GO.
THERE'S NOTHING
OUT THERE FOR THEM.
THEY'RE MORE SCARED
OF LIVING THAN DYING.
THEY DON'T CRY.
THEY DON'T MOURN.
THEY JUST KILL
EACH OTHER!
THAT'S THE DESTINY
OF YOUNG PEOPLE HERE.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD HAPPEN
TO KENNY.
WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO OUR CITY, HUH?
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE OWNED
THE STREETS.
THERE'S A HUSTLER
ON THE RISE
GOT TO GET BY
GET BY
TWO FOR SEVEN
ON MY SIDE
OH, MY, MY
THERE'S A HUSTLER
ON THE RISE
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
THE SITUATION IS SUCH
THAT MY OCCUPATION
IS BIG TIME
OH, FUCK THAT, DALE!
TALKING ALL THAT
GOOFY SHIT.
LET ME SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
YEAH, YEAH.
HEY, STEP ON OUT, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, BASE.
WHAT'S UP,
DELIVERY BOY?
WHAT THE FUCK
YOU DOING HERE?
SOMEBODY PLACE A ORDER
AROUND THIS MOTHERFUCKER?
HUH?
GIVE ME THIS
MOTHERFUCKING BALL.
ALL RIGHT, KAYO.
SEE YOU LATER, SUCKER.
WHAT THE FUCK
YOU WANT, MAN?
YOU WANT?
I WAS JUST WATCHING.
TAKE YOUR ASS
ON OVER THERE AND WATCH.
WELL, WELL, WELL, WELL
COME ON, COME ON
OH OOH...
HEY!
HEY, JOHNNY!
HEY, MAN, I DON'T WANT
YOUR DAMN AUTOGRAPH.
IT'S ME, MAN.
WHAT, YOU COME BACK HERE
LOOKING FOR A FRESH MARK
TO HUSTLE OR WHAT?
BUBBA, IS THAT YOU,
MAN?
IT'S ME.
STILL HERE.
I'VE AGED A LITTLE BIT,
BUT SO HAVE YOU.
YOU BETTER
SUCK THAT GUT IN.
TELL ME.
HOW IS UNCLE BENNY?
WELL, UNCLE BENNY
CLOSED HIS CANDY STORE
A WHILE BACK
AND DIED A FEW WEEKS LATER,
I GUESS,
OF NOTHING TO DO.
WOW, I'M SORRY.
DIDN'T YOUR FOLKS
WRITE YOU ABOUT IT?
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
THEY COULD HAVE.
I JUST DON'T REMEMBER.
THAT'S ALL.
OH, I SEE. WELL...
I AIN'T SEEN YOU
BACK HERE AT ALL, MAN.
NO, NO,
I'VE BEEN BACK.
A QUICKIE
TO SEE YOUR PARENTS?
YOU KNOW, FLYING IN
IN THE MORNING
AND LEAVING
RIGHT BACK OUT AT NIGHT?
THAT WAY YOU DON'T HAVE
TO RUN INTO US, RIGHT?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I'M HERE, ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, YOU HERE.
WELL, LOOK.
DID YOU THINK IT WAS
GOING TO BE LIKE IT WAS?
I MEAN, YOU AND US REBELS
RUNNING AROUND DRINKING,
SCREWING ALL AROUND
THE PLACE?
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
GOING TO BE LIKE THAT?
IT AIN'T, 'CAUSE
ALL YOU ALL LEFT.
WE AIN'T GOT ENOUGH
PEOPLE LEFT HERE
TO TAKE CARE
OF THIS PLACE.
NOT EVEN.
YOU SHOULD'VE COME BACK
ONCE IN A WHILE, JOHNNY.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S HERE FOR YOU?
IF YOU HAD ANY SENSE,
YOU'D GET OUT, TOO.
OH, MAN.
YOU GOING BACK AGAIN
TOMORROW,
AND FRANKLY,
I DON'T GIVE A FUCK
WHAT YOU THINK.
FUCK YOU, MOTHERFUCKER.
SHOUT IT
ON THE STREETS
OUR GUEST TODAY
IS JOHNNY BOOKMAN,
LOCAL STAR
AT NORTHWESTERN,
ALL-AMERICAN,
AND NFL STAR.
HEY, JOHN, THANKS
FOR BEING WITH US TODAY.
THANKS FOR ALLOWING ME
THE TIME.
SPY, GET THE HELL
OVER HERE!
BE COOL, BABY.
JOHN, EVERYONE
AT THE STATION WAS SORRY
TO HEAR ABOUT THE ASSAULT
AND ROBBERY ON YOUR FATHER.
FIRST OF ALL,
LET ME SET
THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
THERE WAS
A GANG SHOOTING
IN FRONT OF HIS STORE.
DAMN, HE AIN'T
A BAD-LOOKING OLD MAN.
THE POLICE FAILED
TO GIVE HIM
PROPER PROTECTION.
ALL THE REPORTS WERE
HE WAS ROBBED.
THEY CAME IN HIS STORE
JUST TO KILL HIM.
THEY UNDERESTIMATED
HIS SPIRIT.
UNDERESTIMATE
HIS SPIRIT!
I THOUGHT BOOKMAN'S
FATHER WAS DEAD!
BOBBY WAS SUPPOSED
TO HAVE KILLED HIM.
SHOULD'VE LET ME
HAVE HIM.
I COULD'VE DONE BETTER.
HE REPORTED
WHAT HE SAW.
ISN'T THAT WHAT
WE SHOULD DO?
NOW, NOW, THAT'S SNITCHING
RIGHT THERE.
YOUR FAMILY'S GONE.
HE DESERVED
THAT SHIT.
PISSED OFF AT MAYOR RITTER,
WHO RAN ON
THE LAW AND ORDER TICKET.
HE'S TURNING HIS BACK
ON THE PEOPLE...
CROOKED-ASS MOUTH!
DAMN.
I WANT TO SAY THIS
TO THOSE PUNKS
WHO DID THIS
TO MY FATHER.
YOU'LL HAVE TO MEET UP
WITH ME REAL SOON.
WE'RE GOING TO GET
THAT ASS JOHN BOOKMAN.
THANKS FOR BEING
ON THE SHOW, JOHN.
THERE'S A PHONE CALL
FOR YOU--
THE MAYOR'S OFFICE.
NO SHIT.
WHAT TOOK HIM
SO LONG?
SO TELL ME,
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO
ABOUT THESE GANGS?
FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
YOU USED TO BE
A GANG MEMBER,
A FOUNDING MEMBER
OF THE REBS.
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE...
BUT WE DIDN'T
KILL PEOPLE.
YES, BUT, UH...
YOU STARTED SOMETHING,
AND IT'S OUT
OF CONTROL NOW.
BECAUSE YOU LET IT.
DON'T LAY
THIS SHIT ON ME!
YOU ARE PISSED OFF
BECAUSE YOU'VE
BECOME A VICTIM
OF SOMETHING
YOU STARTED YOURSELF.
YOU SEE, MR. BOOKMAN,
I'M AFRAID THAT IS
YOUR LEGACY TO GARY.
SO DON'T BE COMING IN HERE
WAVING THAT LITTLE CIGAR
AROUND, BLAMING US.
MY OWN FATHER WORKED
IN THE STEEL MILLS
AND GOT HIMSELF KILLED
ON THE JOB.
THE COMPANY SETTLEMENT
PUT ME THROUGH LAW SCHOOL.
I CAME BACK.
WHERE WERE YOU
ALL THESE YEARS?
LET'S NOT TALK ABOUT ME.
LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE LOUSY JOB
YOU'VE DONE.
SO YOU THINK
IF WE GO OUT
AND FOCUS
ON THIS AREA,
CRIME IS GOING
TO DRY UP.
LIGHTEN UP, HUH?
CALM DOWN.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, OUR MAIN CONCERN HERE
IS THE SAFETY
OF YOUR FAMILY.
THEREFORE, I SUGGEST
WE SET UP A MEETING
WITH REVEREND DORSEY
AT THE CHRISTIAN CHAPEL.
SO WHAT'S REVEREND DORSEY
GOING TO DO?
THE REVEREND SERVES
AS AN INTERMEDIARY
BETWEEN THE GANGS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TELLING ME?
YOU'RE GOING TO NEGOTIATE
WITH THESE PUNKS?
THAT CAN BE ARRANGED.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
MR. BOOKMAN,
YOU HAVE
A BETTER SUGGESTION.
MICHAEL, THAT'S
A HELL OF AN IDEA.
THANK YOU, SIR.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
RIGHT. O.K.
SET IT UP.
GOOD.
AND IF IT DOESN'T WORK,
LIKE YOU SAID, MR. MAYOR,
I STARTED THE REBELS.
I CAN TERMINATE THEM.
I WANT TO THANK ALL OF YOU
FOR COMING.
I KNOW YOU'RE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE VIOLENCE
IN OUR CITY.
I JUST HAD A LONG TALK
WITH THE MAYOR.
WHAT EXACTLY
DID YOU DISCUSS?
WHAT HE HAS TO DO.
HE'LL DO THEM
OR FIND A NEW MAYOR.
WHEN I DIE
HALLELUJAH,
BYE AND BYE
ALL THE WAY
I WILL GET
A BRIGHTER LOVE
OH, MY WORD
WHEN I DIE
HALLELUJAH
BRIGHTER LOVE
BRIGHTER
LOVE
PRAY
THE CHOIR CAN TAKE
A 10-MINUTE BREAK.
REVEREND, ARE YOU GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT?
I'LL BE FINE.
Y'ALL JUST GET SOME AIR.
AHEM!
YOU REQUESTED
OUR PRESENCE?
YES. THE MAYOR
CALLED ME TODAY.
AND HOW IS OUR FRIEND
THE MAYOR?
VERY UPSET.
ESPECIALLY OVER THIS
GROCERY STORE BUSINESS.
OH, YEAH.
I HEARD SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT.
I HEARD THE OLD MAN
HAD A CHATTERY SIDE.
NOW, MARVIN BOOKMAN
IS AN OLD MAN.
YOU KNOW THAT SOMETIMES
OLD MEN MAKE MISTAKES.
OLD MEN BETTER LEARN,
REVEREND.
WELL, SOMETIMES
WE HAVE TO REACH
DEEP WITHIN OURSELVES
TO FIND FORGIVENESS.
PERHAPS I SHOULD
ALSO MENTION
THAT JOHNNY BOOKMAN IS
A VERY HIGH-PROFILE PERSON.
I MET THE GREAT MAN.
I WASN'T IMPRESSED.
THE MEDIA, BROTHERS.
IT'S GOING TO BE VERY HARD
DOING BUSINESS
IN A GOLDFISH BOWL.
THE MAYOR CAN'T LOOK
THE OTHER WAY FOREVER.
SO SHINE HIM ON.
GET BOOKMAN
ON A PLANE OUT.
IS THAT YOUR SERMON
OF THE DAY?
LOOK...
I'M JUST TRYING
TO KEEP PEACE
IN THE COMMUNITY.
AS ALWAYS,
YOU MAKE GOOD SENSE,
REVEREND.
THE REBS WILL TALK
TO THE FAMILY.
WHAT ELSE YOU GET
OUT OF THIS?
WELL, I AM NEGOTIATING
FOR AN EXPANSION
OF MY HOMELESS SHELTER.
PERHAPS A GESTURE
OF BROTHERLY LOVE
CERTAINLY WOULDN'T
HURT MY EFFORTS, HUH?
SO WE'LL CALL A TRUCE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT JOHNNY BOOKMAN.
HE UNDERSTANDS THE STREETS.
SURE.
BROTHERLY LOVE,
REVEREND.
DON'T FORGET
TO PUT US UP FOR
THAT NOBEL PRIZE.
HA HA HA!
YEAH!
BY AY YA
BROTHERLY LOVE,
HUH?
I HEARD THAT,
BROTHER.
YOU HAVE A NICE DAY,
REV, O.K.?
JOHNNY BOOKMAN!
WE SAW YOU
ON THE TV!
MRS. JONES,
HOW ARE YOU?
STILL GOING STRONG!
KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
IN PRO BASKETBALL,
THEY HIT 'EM UP
LIKE THIS HERE.
I FLY BETTER
THAN JORDAN.
MAYBE I SHOULD PLAY
FOR THE BULLS,
HUH, MR. BOOKMAN?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TRY OUT FOR THE TOILETS.
WE'RE NOT PLAYING
NO RIDDLES HERE.
CHECK THIS OUT.
A MESSAGE FOR YOU.
10:00, TOMORROW MORNING,
THE CHRISTIANS' CHAPEL.
SPYRO GOT SOMETHING ON
AT NOON FOR YOU, BABY.
FOR SURE!
TELL HIM I GOT
THE MESSAGE, O.K.?
I'M BUSY RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE AROUND 2:00.
IT SEEM LIKE YOU GOT
A MOTHERFUCKING ATTITUDE
OR SOMETHING, BRO.
GET OUT OF MY FACE.
HA HA HA HA!
WHAT THE FUCK
YOU LAUGHING AT?
GET THIS MOTHERFUCKER
OUTSIDE. COME ON!
GET OUR ASS
ON OUT OF HERE!
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT?
GET HIM OUT--
JUST CALL ME
BARBER BE KICKIN'.
LOOK AT YOUR
MOTHERFUCKIN' SELF NOW!
YOU DONE FUCKED UP!
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
A NICE SCAR ON YOUR FACE?
OH, JOHNNY, JOHNNY.
THAT'S ALWAYS BEEN
YOUR PROBLEM, PARTNER.
PICK A FIGHT
WITH TOO MANY PEOPLE,
THEN JUST FALL APART.
JAKE, DON'T BRING
THAT SHIT NOW, MAN.
LET ME GIVE YOU
A HAND.
HOW YOU BEEN,
PARTNER?
OH, MAN.
PROBLEM HERE?
I DON'T SEE
NO PROBLEM. YOU?
NO PROBLEM.
PUNKS, GET YOUR ASSES
OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
BRO.
LET'S GO!
THE WAY THEY
DO MY LIFE
YEAH, MAKE ME WANT
TO HOLLER
THE WAY THEY
DO MY LIFE
THIS AIN'T
LIVIN'
THE BIBLE
SAYS
WE GOT TO BE
FORGIVIN'
WALKIN',
TALKIN
NAH NAH
NA NA NA NA
NA NA NA
NA NA NA...
THERE'S SOMETHING
I FORGOT TO TELL YOU, MAN.
I WAS HOME
WATCHING TV ONE NIGHT.
I WAS WATCHING
PAY-PER-VIEW.
I SAW YOUR BOY FIGHT.
THIS GUY WENT PLUNK!
OH, MAN,
DON'T GO THERE.
I GAVE THE KID
HIS SHOT.
HE GOT KNOCKED DOWN
IN TWO ROUNDS.
SO WHAT?
YEAH, RIGHT.
TELL ME SOMETHING,
YOU STILL
IN CLEVELAND, RIGHT?
YEAH, MAN,
I'M IN CLEVELAND
TRAINING
SOME NEW TALENT.
YOU KNOW, JOHNNY,
THESE KIDS ARE
NOT LIKE US.
THEY DON'T WANT
TO WORK.
ALL THEY WANT
IS MONEY.
I GOT 20 YEARS
ON MOST OF THESE
SUCKERS.
I CAN STILL
KICK THEIR BUTTS!
WHOA, WHOA!
CHILL OUT, BROTHER.
LOOK, I KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE COMING FROM, MAN,
BUT I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
COME ALL THE WAY TO GARY
TO HELP ME
IN SOME STREET FIGHT.
I CAME BACK
TO BURY KENNY.
LAURIE'S SON?
OUR SON.
A SON?
DAMN, I'M SORRY, JAKE.
I NEVER KNEW HIM,
JOHNNY.
HEARD HE WAS
A GREAT ATHLETE.
WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU AND LAURIE?
IT WAS OVER BETWEEN US
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT
SHE WAS PREGNANT.
YOU KNOW LAURIE--
STRONG, BLACK WOMAN.
SHE MADE IT CLEAR
SHE WANTED THE BABY,
BUT NOT ME.
DID HE KNOW
YOU WERE THE FATHER?
YEAH, SHE TOLD HIM
WHEN HE WAS 9 YEARS OLD.
LOOK, I SENT MONEY.
I DID EVERYTHING.
SHE NEVER
CASHED MY CHECKS.
I DID THE BEST
I COULD DO.
SHE WANTED ME TO KNOW
THEY DIDN'T NEED ME.
THERE'S LOTS
WE'D BOTH LIKE
TO LEAVE IN THE PAST.
BAPTISTS...
JOHN!
JOHN BOOKMAN.
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU
IN HERE.
THE FELLAS TELL ME
YOU GAVE THEM HELL
ON TELEVISION.
THROW UP BOTH MY HANDS
HEY
MAKES ME WANT TO HOLLER
THROW UP BOTH MY HANDS
THIS AIN'T LIVIN'...
JAKE TREVOR.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON,
CHAMP?
SLICK, IT'S BEEN
A WHILE, MY MAN.
MEANING SINCE YOU
LEFT THE REBELS?
DAMN RIGHT,
IT'S BEEN A LONG WHILE.
YEAH. I SEE
YOU'RE STILL HERE, HUH?
GOT A LITTLE
HARDWARE STORE
OVER ON GRANT,
BUT I'M DOING O.K.
LOT OF SHIT'S CHANGED
IN THIS TOWN.
SHIT CHANGES,
BUT I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING
IN THE STREET.
IF YOU REMEMBER
BACK IN THE DAY,
WE WERE A GANG,
PROTECTION GANG.
REMEMBER THAT?
YEAH.
THOSE DAYS ARE GONE.
NOW IT'S ALL ABOUT
DRIVE-BY SHOOTINGS.
IT ISN'T ABOUT
ROCKS AND BOTTLES
ANYMORE.
IT'S ABOUT
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS.
I CAN UNDERSTAND
ALL THAT,
BUT I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT KENNY'S DEATH.
I DON'T SHOOT RUMORS, MAN.
HEY, SLICK, I SAID
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU HEARD, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
MY BOY SAW KENNY
HUSTLING A REBEL
OVER A BASKETBALL GAME.
YOUR BOY SAW WHAT?
YOU WANTED TO KNOW.
I TOLD YOU.
WHAT DID HE
GET HIM FOR?
300 BUCKS.
YOU TELLING ME
THAT MY BOY GOT KILLED
FOR 300 BILLS, MAN?
THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE TELLING ME?
NO, WHAT I'M TRYING
TO TELL YOU IS
THEY DIDN'T KILL HIM
OVER THE MONEY.
THEY KILLED HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS
HUSTLING THEM.
IT AIN'T ABOUT
BREAKING FINGERS ANYMORE.
WHO'S RUNNING
THE SHOW, MAN?
JUST LIKE
THE OLD DAYS
WITH YOU AND JOHN,
ONLY NOW IT'S
SPYRO AND DAMIEN.
NOTHING GOES DOWN
IN THIS TOWN
THEY DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN I'LL TAKE
CARE OF THIS.
WAIT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU
AND JOHN BACK IN THE HOOD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU GUYS ARE UP TO,
BUT I'LL BET
THERE'LL BE CHANGES
IN THIS TOWN.
I JUST WANT
TO BE A PART OF IT.
THE LORD
TOOK HIS SOUL
AND HE SET
HE SET MY CHILD FREE
HE'S GONE
HE'S GONE TO HEAVEN
OH, HOW HAPPY
HOW HAPPY HE'LL BE
YEAH, YEAH, HE WON'T
HAVE TO WORRY
OR SHED
NO MORE TEARS
FOR HE'S GONE HOME
WHERE HE'LL HAVE
NO MORE FEARS
ANOTHER ANGEL
HAS GONE ON HOME
TO BE WITH MY LORD
ANOTHER ANGEL
HAS GONE ON HOME
TO BE WITH MY LORD
ANOTHER ANGEL, YEAH
HAS GONE ON HOME
TO BE WITH MY LORD
HOW'D YOU FIND OUT?
JOHNNY WENT ON
SOME TV SHOWS,
AND SOME NEWSPAPERS
PICKED UP THE STORY.
I READ IT SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW,
YOU SHOULD'VE CALLED ME.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT
ANY MORE KILLING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'LL DO,
JUST FORGET WHAT
THEY DID TO KENNY?
IT WON'T BE FOR KENNY.
IT'LL BE
FOR JAKE TREVOR,
WHO'S ALWAYS
LOOKING FOR A FIGHT.
GOT TO HIT SOMEBODY,
EVEN IF IT MAKES
EVERYTHING WORSE!
GIVE ME THAT!
WHAT'S UP, JAKE?
OH, MAN.
I FOUND OUT WHY
THEY KILLED KENNY, MAN.
THE REBELS HAD
A B-BALL RACKET GOING.
KENNY MADE A SLICK MOVE
ON THEM.
DOES LAURIE
KNOW ABOUT THIS?
NO, SHE DON'T KNOW
ABOUT IT YET.
THAT'S THE WAY
I WANT TO KEEP IT, MAN.
YOU READY TO MAKE
THIS HIT WITH ME?
HEY, MAN, SLOW DOWN.
I GOT A MEETING TOMORROW
WITH THE REBELS
AT THE CHURCH
ON 35th STREET.
WHAT FOR?
SET UP A TRUCE.
START A DIALOG.
YOU MUST BE
OUT OF YOUR MIND.
I NEVER THOUGHT
YOU'D SELL OUT!
HEY, HEY.  COME ON, JAKE.
THIS IS ME YOU TALKIN' TO !
IT AIN'T GOING
TO COME DOWN THAT WAY!
BULLSHIT! YOU KNOW
AS WELL I KNOW
YOU GOT TO HAVE POWER
TO MAKE A TRUCE.
WHERE'S YOUR POWER,
JOHNNY?
ALL YOU WANT
IS REVENGE?
DAMN RIGHT,
I WANT REVENGE!
WHAT I WANT HERE
IS A LITTLE RESPECT!
TAKE THIS OUT
TO THE STREET!
HAVE YOU HEARD?
OUR GOOD FRIEND JOHNNY
WANTS TO MAKE A TRUCE
WITH THE PEOPLE
THAT KILLED OUR SON.
AND LET THEM
OFF THE HOOK?
NO, I WANT THEM ARRESTED
AND PUT ON TRIAL.
IT WON'T
HAPPEN THAT FAST.
THEY GOT A LOCK
ON THE POLITICIANS.
WE GOT
TO NEGOTIATE.
WE DON'T LIKE
WHAT THEY SAY,
WE GO ANOTHER WAY.
I WANT TO BE THERE.
I WAS HOPING
YOU'D BOTH BE THERE.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU CAN COUNT ME OUT.
LET ME TELL
BOTH OF YOU SOMETHING.
I KNOW
WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
AW, JAKE, MAN.
COME ON.
HEY, JAKE!
JAKE, MAN,
COME BACK. JAKE!
OH!
[TIRES SCREECH]
WHERE'S SPYRO, MY MAN?
RIGHT THERE.
YOU WANT SOMETHING,
BROTHER?
YOUR NAME SPYRO?
YEAH. WHY?
I JUST WANTED TO SEE
WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE.
RIGHT NOW I'M JUST
LOOKING FOR NAMES
AND FACES.
YOU'RE JAKE TREVOR.
MY OLD MAN TOLD ME
HOW GREAT A FIGHTER
YOU WAS.
YOUR OLD MAN WAS RIGHT.
I HEARD OF YOU.
HEARD YOU WERE
BACK IN TOWN.
WHAT FOR?
KENNY THOMPSON.
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
THAT KID WHO WAS
AT THE BASKETBALL--
WHAT'S YOUR INTEREST?
HE WAS MY SON, MAN.
WHAT DOES THAT
LEAVE YOU, SPYRO?
A DEAD MAN.
YOU'RE A DEAD MAN!
FUCK YOU, OLD MAN.
"YOU A DEAD MAN."
YOU SEE ME, MAN?
FUCKIN' THREATS ARE SHIT.
FUCK HIM.
THIS MOTHERFUCKIN'
RAP SHIT
I GOT IT LOCKED
FROM CALI TO PAKISTAN
I OWN THE WHOLE
FUCKIN' BLOCK
'CAUSE I GOT
SOME NIGGER SHIT FOR '96
THIS MOTHERFUCKER RAY IS
IN THE MOTHERFUCKIN' MIX
SO, NIGGERS, GET YOUR STICKS
AND YOUR STONES AND SHIT
AS I HIT YOUR WARES
WITH ANOTHER HIT
COME LISTEN TO MY SHIT
I'M MOTHERFUCKIN'
SHAQ TIGHT...
ON BEHALF OF THE MAYOR
AND MYSELF,
I'D LIKE TO THANK YOU
FOR COMING HERE
TO THIS, UH,
HOUSE OF WORSHIP
TO TRY AND SETTLE MATTERS
REGARDING THIS SERIOUS
AND TRAGIC SITUATION.
I'LL BE LEAVING YOU
IN THE PRIVACY
OF THE GOOD REVEREND DORSEY,
WHO WILL MEDIATE ALL SIDES.
AND IF I CAN BE
OF ANY HELP,
I'LL BE RIGHT OUTSIDE.
THANK YOU,
MR. CASEY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I'VE KNOWN THE BOOKMANS
FOR AS LONG
AS I'VE BEEN HERE.
I'VE KNOWN LAURIE THOMPSON
SINCE SHE WAS,
WHAT, THIS HIGH?
SPY, DAMIEN--
I KNOW YOUR FOLKS.
AND THE REST OF YOU,
I KNOW YOUR COUSINS,
YOUR AUNTS,
YOUR BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
SO I'M STANDING
IN THE MIDDLE HERE.
I AM THE MEDIATOR,
SO LET'S TALK.
LET'S STOP THIS THING.
IF THE OLD MAN KEEPS
HIS MOUTH SHUT,
WE'LL CALL IT DONE.
SHORT, SWEET, SIMPLE.
DONE IS DONE,
FACT IS FACT,
AND GOD'S TRUTH
IS THE TRUTH.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE--
TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
WHO SHOT MY FATHER?
I THOUGHT
WE'RE BEING SERIOUS.
I DON'T WANT
NO JOKES.
DAMAGE WAS DONE
ON BOTH SIDES.
MARVIN BOOKMAN
DID THE WRONG THING,
BUT THE RETALIATION
WAS WRONG, TOO.
JUST A MINUTE.
MY HUSBAND DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING WRONG.
THESE ANIMALS
KILLED HER SON
IN FRONT OF OUR STORE.
HOLD UP.
YOU DON'T NOTHIN'
ABOUT THAT SHIT, BITCH.
THAT'S PRETTY TOUGH TALK
COMING FROM A FAGGOT
WHO DON'T KNOW WHAT SEX
HIS MOTHER IS.
REVEREND,
THIS WASN'T OUR DEAL,
BUT I'LL THROW THIS
IN THE POT,
AND THAT'LL BE IT.
OUR BOY,
HE MISSED HIS SHOT,
AND WE DON'T MISS MANY.
NOW IF THAT OLD MAN
CAN KEEP HIS
FUCKIN' MOUTH SHUT,
THEN MAYBE,
JUST MAYBE,
HE'LL BE ABLE
TO SURVIVE
ON OUR STREETS.
BURN IN HELL!
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
YOU'RE NOTHING MORE
THAN THE DOGSHIT
WE WASH UP
FROM OUR SIDEWALKS
IN THE MORNING.
GRACIE, PLEASE.
OH, QUIT THIS,
REVEREND.
WHAT KIND OF DEAL
IS THIS?
WE SPEND OUR LIFETIME
WORKING AND STRIVING
FOR GOODNESS,
AND YOU SELL US OUT
TO HIM?
AND HERE'S OUR DEAL.
I WANT EVERYONE INVOLVED
TO TURN THEMSELVES IN
TO THE POLICE,
AND I WANT THE BOY
WHO SHOT MY HUSBAND
TO CONFESS,
AND MAYBE,
JUST MAYBE
WE'LL LET YOU SURVIVE.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
YOU CAN'T JUST WALK OUT.
WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED HERE?
I THINK WORLD WAR III
WAS DECLARED.
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN A WHILE, BOBBY.
WHERE YOU BEEN?
I BEEN AROUND.
YOU KNOW ME.
I'M ALWAYS
TAKIN' CARE OF BUSINESS.
BOBBY, EXPLAIN
SOMETHING TO ME.
HOW CAN YOU MISS
HITTING A MAN
IN THE HEAD
AT POINTBLANK
RANGE?
I THOUGHT I HIT HIM.
WHAT ALL THIS PUNK SHIT
ABOUT ANYWAY?
SINCE WHEN DO WE CHANGE
HOW WE DO THINGS?
GET A MESSAGE OVER
TO REVEREND DORSEY.
LET HIM KNOW
NOTHING WILL HAPPEN
TO THE BOOKMAN FAMILY.
THAT'S MY WORD.
WHAT ABOUT
ALL THE OTHER SUCKERS?
ONLY THE BOOKMANS.
I SAY WE
BUST OUT THE STEEL,
WE TAKE OUT
THE WHOLE FAMILY,
WE TAKE AWAY
OUR PROBLEMS.
WE WAIT, WE LOSE.
HEY, CHILL,
MY BROTHER.
WORD IS THAT DIABLOS
AND RANGERS SAY
WE CAN'T CONTROL
OUR HOOD.
YOU WANT BE IN A WAR
OVER THIS PUNK SHIT?
HEY, WHAT'S UP
WITH THE GUN?
WHAT'S UP
WITH THE GUN, MAN?
I CAN'T GO OUT
LIKE THAT, MAN!
NO! YOU DON'T NEED
TO DO THIS, MAN, NO!
FUCK YEAH!
PUNK ASS NIGGA.
[JUKEBOX PLAYING
RAP MUSIC]
WELL, HELLO TO YOU
SOON-TO-BE SICK-ASS PEOPLE.
THE NAME'S KAYO
WITH THE AYO.
I'M FROM YOUR
HEALTH DEPARTMENT,
AND WE ARE NOW
OFFICIALLY CLOSED.
WHAT, Y'ALL DIDN'T
HEAR ME IN HERE?
I SAY WE'RE CLOSED!
WHUP THEIR ASS!
GET THEM THE FUCK UP
OUTTA HERE!
MOTHERFUCKIN' SHIT!
TURN THAT PUNK-ASS
SHIT OFF!
WEAK-ASS SHIT!
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
WHY I'M DOIN' THIS?
ASK THE BOOKMANS
WHY I'M DOIN'
THIS SHIT.
THE BOOKMANS?
YEAH, THE BOOKMANS!
HEY, THE BOOKMANS
NICE FOLKS, MAN.
MAN, THIS NIGGER
TRIPPIN', MAN.
WHAT YOU NIGGERS
TALKIN' ABOUT?
WHOA!
OH, THOSE BOOKMANS!
YOU FUCK WITH THEM?
HELL, NO. I WANT TO
BURN THEIR SHIT DOWN.
THEY DON'T EVEN
ACCEPT FOOD STAMPS.
COME ON, MAN!
WHY WE NEED ALL THIS?
IT AIN'T COOL
LIKE THAT, MAN.
HEY, FUCK THE BOOKMANS!
GET UP OUTTA HERE!
THIS THE MAN
THAT SHOT YOU?
FOUND HIM TODAY.
THAT'S HIM.
HMM.
HE SAID HE WAS GOD,
THAT HE COULDN'T
BRING HIMSELF
TO KILL ME.
AND THE GUN CHECKS OUT.
LOOKS LIKE YOU WIN
THIS ONE, COACH.
NO, NO, NOT YET.
YOU GOT WHAT YOU
NEGOTIATED FOR.
THEY GAVE YOU
THIS KID BOBBY.
LAW OF THE JUNGLE.
LIFE FOR A LIFE.
BUT SUPPOSE
I WANT MORE?
SUPPOSE I WANT
ALL OF THEM,
DAMIEN, SPYRO,
INCLUDED?
I'D WALK AWAY A WINNER
IF I WERE YOU, COACH.
THEY MADE THE GESTURE.
I SAY ACCEPT IT
AND WALK AWAY.
A KID WAS MURDERED,
EXECUTED.
DOESN'T THAT BOTHER YOU?
WE COULDN'T DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
BOOKMAN, YOU GOT
A CONVICTION,
A SENTENCE,
AND AN EXECUTION.
WHAT IS
YOUR PROBLEM?
MY PROBLEM IS,
YOU'RE IN MY FATHER'S ROOM.
YOU WANT TO GET OUT?
[ANGRY MURMURING]
HOLD IT!
WE'RE STILL
IN THE HOUSE OF GOD.
I WANT YOU
TO REMEMBER THAT.
I TALKED TO JOHNNY
AND GRACIE.
YOU KNOW THEM.
THEY'RE JUST AS UPSET
AS YOU ARE.
THEY BROUGHT IT
ON THEMSELVES.
NO! NO, DON'T SAY THAT.
THEY DIDN'T BRING IT
ON THEMSELVES.
WE GOT TO MAKE 'EM GO
FOR OUR OWN SAKE!
ANNIE, HOW CAN YOU,
OF ANYBODY IN THIS ROOM,
SAY THAT?
YOU LOST TWO SONS
TO DRIVE-BYS.
JOHN.
MY FAMILY REGRETS THE PROBLEMS
THAT YOU'RE HAVING.
BUT THE BIG QUESTION IS,
TO SURVIVE--
IS THAT ALL YOU WANT?
YOU WANT EVERYTHING
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
WELL, EVERYTHING
WON'T BE ALL RIGHT
BECAUSE ONCE
THE GANGS FIND OUT
THAT THEY CAN RUN US OUT,
YOUR LIFE IS GOING
TO BE A LIVING HELL.
YOU SURE CAN
TALK THE TALK.
YOU MEAN YOU WANT US
TO SHOOT IT OUT
WITH THE REBS?
MRS. JONES, I'M PROBABLY
A VERY LUCKY PERSON
BECAUSE I CAN AFFORD
TO TAKE MY FAMILY
OUT OF HERE.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
BUT IT'S UP TO YOU
TO DECIDE
WHETHER YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD'S
WORTH FIGHTING FOR.
HOW WE GONNA
DO THAT?
YEAH, TELL US
SOMETHING.
LOOK.
THEIR POWER LIES
IN THEIR UNITY.
A GANG WORKS TOGETHER
AS A TEAM.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
LIKE A TEAM.
IF THEY FIGHT ONE OF US,
THEY FIGHT ALL OF US.
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
GOD TESTS US.
NOT IN OUR FAITH IN HIM,
BUT IN OUR INNER COURAGE,
WHETHER WE'RE WILLING TO PUT
OUR BODIES ON THE LINE.
NOW, I THINK
MR. BOOKMAN IS RIGHT,
SO I'M WILLING
TO FOLLOW HIM.
AND I PRAY
THAT YOU WILL, TOO.
NOW THE WAR'S ON
I'M TIRED OF WAITIN',
LET'S GET IT ON
NOW OR LATER,
RIGHT NOW THE WAR'S ON
I'M TIRED OF WAITIN',
LET'S GET IT ON
NOW OR LATER,
RIGHT NOW THE WAR'S ON
I'M TIRED OF WAITIN',
LET'S GET IT ON...
LET'S SEE
WHAT THESE BITCHES
GOTTA SAY.
DIABLOS AND RANGERS
IN OUR HOUSE?
WE CAN HANDLE THIS.
TO BE EXACT,
OR SO THE STORY GOES
IF YOU LOOK CLOSER
ON THE MAP
THE CHILEANS TAUGHT ME
HOW TO BUST MY GAT
UNTIL WE FUCKED THE CAR
THEY LEFT ME
TO TAKE MY EARTH BACK
A REVOLUTIONARY ACT SHOULD
HAVE A CERTAIN TRACK
I'LL FIND THE FACTS
NOW WE GOT ILLUMINATI
ALL ON OUR BACKS
CHECK TO SEE IF WE DUE
PROCESS AND PAY TAX...
SPYRO.
BLOOD.
HOW YOU DOIN',
BROTHER?
ALL RIGHT, BROTHER.
BIG BROTHER.
HEY, BLOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
ALL RIGHT.
HOW YOU DOIN', BRO?
HEARD YOU GOT TROUBLE.
EVERYTHING'S COOL.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
SHOOTING A KID
IN A PHONE BOOTH
FOR A FUCKIN'
$300 HUSTLE?
WAS THAT GOOD
FOR BUSINESS?
LOOK, THE MEDIA COVERAGE IS
SCARING OUR MAJOR SUPPLIERS.
THEY CUTTING BACK
ON THE HIGH-GRADE SHIT.
YOU LET THEM KNOW
EVERYTHING'S UNDER CONTROL.
YOUR ACTIONS
ARE SCARING PEOPLE
ON MY STREETS.
WE HAVE PEOPLE
WITH FAMILIES THERE.
WE'RE NOT BEHIND YOU
ON THIS.
YOU CROSS OVER
ONTO BROADWAY
WITH THIS SHIT,
AND YOUR ASS
WILL PAY.
AIN'T NOBODY
PAYIN' A THING.
WE KNOW
WHAT'S GOIN' DOWN.
WELL, I HOPE YOU DO,
LITTLE BROTHER.
OUR ORGANIZATIONS
HAVE ENJOYED
GREAT PROSPERITY,
AND ONLY THROUGH PEACE
CAN THIS CONTINUE.
YOU BETTER
WATCH YOURSELF.
HA HA HA!
I'M TIRED OF WAITIN',
LET'S GET IT ON
NOW OR LATER,
RIGHT NOW THE WAR'S ON
I'M TIRED OF WAITIN',
LET'S GET IT ON
NOW OR LATER,
RIGHT NOW THE WAR'S ON
[JOHN]
O.K., REVEREND,
LAY IT OUT FOR US.
THE RED IS THE EL DIABLOS,
THE REBS ARE GRAY,
AND THE YELLOW
IS THE RANGERS' TERRITORY.
WHAT'S TO STOP THEM
FROM JOINING FORCES?
THE RANGERS
AND THE DIABLOS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT IF THE REBS
THINK THEY ARE?
WE GOT TO PIT
ALL THREE GANGS
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
BREAK THE TRUCE.
THEN THEY'LL
KNOCK EACH OTHER OFF
FOR US.
[REVEREND]
WHAT IF THEY CATCH ON?
WILL WE FIGHT
ALL THREE GANGS
TOGETHER ALONE?
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
WE GOT TO GET SOMEBODY
ON THE INSIDE
THAT CAN SET THEM UP.
THAT'LL WORK.
AND, REVEREND...
WE NEED SOMEBODY
THAT THE GANGS TRUST.
[CREAK]
WHO IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT TAKE THE BACK WAY OUT.
I THINK I BETTER.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
GET OFF ME!
NOW SIT DOWN.
WHAT'LL WE DO
WITH THIS LITTLE PUNK?
MAYBE WE OUGHT
TO JUST KILL HIM.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
SHOOTING HIM MYSELF.
WE CAN'T SHOOT HIM
IN A COMMUNITY REC CENTER.
BESIDES, WE GOT TO
MAKE IT LOOK LIKE
IT'S AN ACCIDENT.
YOU DON'T SCARE ME.
I'M A REB.
MAN,
YOU AIN'T NO REB.
THEY WOULDN'T LET
SQUIRTS IN THE REBS.
WE KNOW BECAUSE
WE STARTED THEM.
YEAH, WHEN THERE WERE
STILL DINOSAURS.
YOU GOT A BIG MOUTH.
YOU DON'T KNOW
NOTHING, MAN.
AND YOU KNOW
EVERYTHING.
I KNOW YOU'LL DIE
WITH THAT DUMB-ASS PLAN.
DON'T YOU BE
TALKIN' ABOUT
NOBODY DYING.
JUST TAKE IT EASY.
SO A LITTLE WAR
WOULDN'T BOTHER YOU?
I AIN'T GOT NO LOVE
FOR ANYONE.
I'M A BUSINESSMAN.
IT'S ALL FAIR.
THEN WHY NOT HELP US
BE MORE FAIR?
I MIGHT BE INTERESTED
FOR A PRICE.
O.K., THEN.
HOW ABOUT SOME GUNS,
AMMUNITION, EXPLOSIVES,
THAT KIND OF THING?
A MAN WHO EARNS
WHAT YOU DO
CAN AFFORD THE BEST.
I KNOW WHERE
TO GET YOU THE BEST.
YOU CAN'T TRUST HIM.
YES, YOU CAN.
SURE, YOU CAN.
HE'S GOING
TO SELL YOU OUT.
WAIT. NOW JUST
HEAR ME OUT.
I DID SOMETHING
I WISH I HADN'T HAVE.
I HEARD THAT COP SAYING
HE HAD A LICENSE NUMBER
HE GOT FROM YOUR FATHER.
I WAS THE ONE
WHO RATTED HIM TO SPYRO.
A MINUTE
AFTER I OPENED MY MOUTH,
I WISH I HADN'T HAVE.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
I WANT TO MAKE IT UP.
ALL RIGHT. CHILL.
STILL GONNA COST YOU,
THOUGH.
WELL, LIKE YOU SAID,
I CAN AFFORD IT.
IT'LL TAKE A FEW HOURS
TO SET UP THIS BUY,
BUT I'M TALKING 12, 15 Gs,
NOW, CASH,
ALL IN HUNDREDS.
10% OF THAT STICKS TO ME.
MY COMMISSION.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU GOT A CONTRACT,
AN ENFORCEABLE ONE.
IT'S AS GOOD AS DONE.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
HE'S GOING TO GO
STRAIGHT TO SPYRO.
NO, NO.
THAT 10% COMMISSION,
I DON'T THINK SO.
ALL RIGHT?
RRRRAHH!
SEE WHERE I HIT
THE CHEST AREA?
DON'T HIT
THE STOMACH AREA.
HIT SOMETHING THAT BREAKS,
LIKE THE FACE
OR THE RIBS
OR THE KNEECAPS.
THIS IS JUST LIKE A GUN.
DON'T PULL IT UNLESS
YOU'RE GONNA USE IT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT THAT?
WE'RE NOT BUNTING.
WE'RE FOLLOWING THROUGH.
ALL THE WAY THROUGH.
KIM, COME UP HERE
AND TRY SOME.
ATTAGIRL.
WHERE'D YOU LEARN
ALL THIS, HONEY?
I USED TO BE A REBEL,
AND I LIKE BASEBALL.
ATTAGIRL!
ALL RIGHT, KIM.
MRS. HEYWOOD,
COME OVER HERE NOW.
YOU TOLD ME WE WOULDN'T
HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
MRS. HEYWOOD,
THE REVEREND TOLD ME
THAT GOD SAID
IT'S O.K.
TO BE PREPARED,
NOW, DIDN'T HE?
THEN I'M GONNA
PREPARE YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME PREPARE YOU.
HOLD IT UP.
ATTAGIRL.
ALL RIGHT! ONE MORE.
SHOW ME YOU COULD.
YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT,
MRS. HEYWOOD!
GIMME FIVE!
ALL RIGHT!
I DID NOT KNOW
WHAT SPYRO WANTED,
SO I BROUGHT
A TASTE OF EVERYTHING.
LOOKS GOOD TO ME.
WE'LL TAKE IT ALL.
SPYRO AND DAMIEN,
THEY GONNA LOVE
THIS SHIT.
THERE'S A LOT OF
MERCHANDISE THERE.
BUT BECAUSE
IT'S FOR THE REBS,
I'LL GIVE YOU
A VERY SPECIAL PRICE--
ONLY $18,000.
FUCK THAT. SPYRO SAID
15 FOR EVERYTHING,
AND THAT'S IT.
GET IT.
15,000 IS WHAT WE GOT.
THAT'S REAL CHEAP
FOR TOP MERCHANDISE
LIKE THIS.
YOU CAN KEEP
THE BAG, TOO.
SOLD, EH?
SOLD.
ARE THE REBS
HAVING A WAR
OR SOMETHING?
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION,
ESE.
SOUNDS LIKE ONE HELL
OF A FUCKIN' PARTY,
IF YOU ASK ME.
ALL RIGHT.
WE PAID FOR IT.
YOU LOAD IT UP.
THAT WAS SOME PRETTY GOOD
NEGOTIATING WE JUST DID.
SHIT. WE WOULD'VE
GOT IT CHEAPER
IF YOU LET ME
DO THE TALKING.
YOU DONE GOOD,
LITTLE BROTHER.
YOU DONE GOOD.
NOBODY'S GONNA KNOW
WHO'S BUYING THOSE GUNS.
AIN'T NOBODY GONNA KNOW
IT'S YOU KICKIN' THEIR ASS.
YOU THINK
THEY BOUGHT THAT?
NO DOUBT. I'M GLAD
I AIN'T SNITCHED
TO THE REBS.
BUT I DIDN'T FIGURE
YOU WOULD.
YOU'RE TOO GOOD
A BUSINESSMAN.
BUT THIS IS MY LAST DEAL.
I'M OUTTA HERE FOREVER.
WHERE YOU GOING?
SEATTLE. THAT'S WHERE
RAYMOND WANTS TO GO.
HE SAID IT'S NICE THERE.
WHO'S RAYMOND?
HE WAS MY BROTHER.
HE WAS A BANGER.
HE GOT KILLED.
I MEANT WHAT I SAID
ABOUT YOUR FATHER.
HE ALWAYS TREATED ME
DECENT.
YEAH, BUT I'M
TREATING YOU BETTER.
HERE'S YOUR
10% COMMISSION.
1,500.
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU, BROTHER.
STAY UP, MY BROTHER.
STAY COOL,
LITTLE MAN.
WHAT'S THE WORD, MAN?
CLYDE, COME UP HERE.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED
WHAT YOU CAN DO
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE
TO SOMEBODY.
YOU CAN STEP
ON A FOOT.
YOU CAN GOUGE AN EYE.
GO FOR IT.
DON'T PULL BACK.
OR GO FOR THE TESTICLES
AND SQUEEZE.
OH, CLYDE, I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO HURT YOU, CLYDE.
WE'LL DO THIS AGAIN
TOMORROW.
EVERYBODY,
JUST GO HOME, RELAX--
UM...
SEE YOU LATER, O.K.?
ALL RIGHT, GREAT.
HELLO, LAURIE.
JAKE.
YOU LOOKED PRETTY GOOD
OVER THERE.
THANKS. IT'S EVERYTHING
YOU TAUGHT ME.
YOU GOT A LITTLE TIME
FOR SOME CONVERSATION?
YEAH.
IT'S LONG OVERDUE.
COME ON.
IT'S A LITTLE AWKWARD
FOR ME,
ME COMING BACK THIS WAY
AND ALL,
UNDER THESE CONDITIONS.
YEAH.
YOU MISSED A LOT,
NOT KNOWING KENNY.
YOU KNOW, HE WAS
A LOT LIKE YOU--
HEADSTRONG,
FULL OF HIS OWN WAYS
ABOUT THINGS.
BASKETBALL WAS HIS LIFE.
HE WAS GOING TO BE
A BIG STAR.
HE HAD A PLAN,
JUST LIKE YOU.
I WAS GOING TO BE
HEAVYWEIGHT CHAMP.
AND I KNEW
YOU COULD DO IT.
NO DOUBT IN MY MIND.
YOU NEVER LET ME KNOW.
THAT'S WHY
I HAD TO LET YOU GO.
LET ME GO?
LAURIE...
YOU LET ME GO?
COME ON, LAURIE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO GET
IN THE WAY OF YOUR DREAMS.
YOU WOULD'VE NEVER
FORGIVEN ME FOR IT.
IT WOULD'VE KILLED
WHATEVER WE HAD.
THAT'S JUST LIKE ME,
KILLING THINGS.
I READ ABOUT THAT.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
THOSE THINGS HAPPEN
TO BOXERS.
YOU TOOK A CHANCE.
IT COULD'VE BEEN YOU.
IT WAS NEVER THE SAME
AFTER THAT.
I THOUGHT ABOUT
A COMEBACK,
BUT COME BACK
FROM WHAT?
I WAS A FAILURE,
ALL-AROUND FAILURE.
I FAILED MYSELF,
I FAILED YOU.
I COULDN'T EVEN
FACE UP TO YOU.
ESPECIALLY...
AFTER HOW YOU
SENT ME AWAY.
[SIGHS]
KENNY KNEW
ALL ABOUT YOU,
AND HE HAD AN ALBUM
OF ALL YOUR FIGHTS.
HE KNEW YOU HADN'T
FORGOTTEN US
AND THAT YOU TRIED
TO SEND US SOME MONEY.
AND HE LOVED YOU.
HE LOVED YOU.
I MADE SURE OF THAT.
I NEVER HEARD
FROM HIM.
HE, UM...
HE WANTED TO, UH...
WAIT UNTIL HE WAS
ALL GROWN UP.
HE WANTED YOU
TO KNOW HIM AS A MAN...
AND AS A FRIEND.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY, BABY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY ANYTHING.
COME HERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
KID CAME THROUGH.
I CHECKED 'EM OUT.
THEY WORK.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
YOU WERE RIGHT
THIS TIME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
THIS TIME?
I CARRIED THESE UP
ALL BY MYSELF
WHILE YOU GUYS
WERE HOLDING HANDS.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
HOW DO YOU LIKE
MY PARTY?
[ SHOUTING, CHATTERING
INDISTINCT ]
[ CONTINUES ]
[COUPLE GRUNTING
AND GROANING]
[MAN]
OPEN UP! UHH!
[WOMAN]
OW!
AHH!
AAH!
AH, YEAH!
UH-HUH!
[CAR STARTING]
WHO IS IT, BABY?
WHO IS IT, HUH?
HEY, MOTHERFUCK,
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE
DOING IN THERE.
GET OUT!
COME ON, COME ON.
DON'T GET SO ROUGH.
THAT'S MY GRANDMOTHER'S
CAR, MAN.
GET OUT OF MY GRANDMOTHER'S
CAR WITH THAT SHIT.
GET OUT OF
MY MOTHERFUCKING CAR.
[CAR STARTS]
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL, MAN?
IN THE OLD DAYS,
IT NEVER TOOK YOU THIS LONG
TO HOT-WIRE A CAR.
WHAT YOU MEAN,
"OLD DAYS," MAN?
GET RID OF THAT.
IF THEY SMELL
THAT CHEAP-ASS
CIGAR SMOKE,
THEY'LL KNOW YOU'VE
BEEN IN THE CAR.
AIN'T NO CHEAP CIGAR.
COST ME $1.25.
I DO THE SMOKING,
YOU LOAD THE WEAPONS.
I DONE STASHED THE SHIT.
I GOT TO LOAD
THE WEAPONS,
I GOT TO DRIVE THE CAR,
AND LAURIE
MAKES THE PLANS.
WHAT YOU GONNA DO,
BOSS?
I'M THE EXECUTIVE
IN CHARGE, BROTHER.
NOW YOU'RE
THE EXECUTIVE.
SHIT.
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU, MAN.
HERE YOU GO, MAN.
DON'T LOSE THIS.
I'M NOT
BULLSHITTING YOU.
O.K., BLOOD.
GIMME THE MONEY.
REBELS DON'T KNOW IT,
BUT THEY'RE DECLARING WAR
ON THE DIABLOS TONIGHT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
GET OUT OF HERE.
GO! GO!
YOU WANT ONE MORE?
WHY THE HELL NOT?
WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS, MAN?
WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT?
THAT WAS
DAMIEN'S CAR.
I KNOW IT'S HIS CAR!
DIDN'T MISS YOUR ASS,
BIG CUE BALL-HEAD
MOTHERFUCKER!
AND, SPYRO,
YOU HIGH-YELLOW BITCH!
COME OVER
FUCKING ME--
WHAT THE FUCK Y'ALL
STANDING AROUND FOR?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YEAH, THIS MEANS WAR,
MOTHERFUCKER.
LOOKS LIKE
A DAMN GOOD PARTY.
IT SURE DOES, BABY.
THE REBS HIT THE DIABLOS,
AND THEY'RE GETTING READY
TO RETALIATE.
RIGHT. WE'RE LOOKING
AT ALL-OUT WAR HERE.
I DON'T WANT OUR POLICEMEN
CAUGHT IN A CROSSFIRE.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
NO, MIKE, NO, NO.
YOU ARE GOING TO BE HERE.
I'M GOING
TO A MAYOR'S CONVENTION
IN NEW ORLEANS.
AAH!
RAYMOND.
RAFAEL.
WHAT'S HAPPENING, MAN?
MY FAVORITE CUSTOMERS.
WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU TODAY?
WE NEED
SOME HARDWARE.
I CAN GET YOU
ANYTHING YOU WANT
IN 4-5 DAYS.
NO. WE NEED IT NOW.
I'M NOT THE FUCKING
PENTAGON, MAN, O.K.?
THE SHIPMENT I SOLD YOU,
THAT WAS IT.
THERE IS NO MORE.
SOME OLD MAN
AND THIS KID.
HE USUALLY RIDES
ON A SCOOTER.
DRESS CLEAN SQUARE?
WITH A MUSTACHE?
THAT'S HIM.
THAT'S YOUR MAN.
IT'S THAT FUCKIN' BOOKMAN,
THAT EX-FOOTBALL PLAYER.
SHIT! THAT'S WHERE
I KNOW HIM FROM!
HEY, GUYS,
THAT'S JOHN BOOKMAN.
MOTHERFUCKER!
SPY, STOP IT!
HUH? YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
YEAH!
NOW I KNOW
WHO HIT THE DIABLOS.
WHAT THE FUCK GOOD
DOES THAT DO US, MAN?
BLOOD AIN'T GONNA
BELIEVE THIS SHIT.
YOU JUST KILLED
THE ONLY FUCKIN'
WITNESS!
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
D-MAN?
YOU GOING SOFT?
FUCK NO! I AIN'T
GOING CRAZY, THOUGH!
YOU'RE GOING
FUCKING NUTS!
WE JUST GOT TO PROVE
TO BLOOD
THAT THE GROCERY BOY
AND HIS FRIENDS HAVE
GOT THOSE WEAPONS.
WE GOT TO TAKE THEM OUT,
LEVEL THE WHOLE
FUCKING HOOD.
HERE'S THIS KID
YOU WAS LOOKING FOR.
HIS ASS HAD
$1,500 ON HIM.
THAT MONEY DON'T MEAN SHIT.
I CAN ALWAYS GET CREEP.
I'M A BUSINESSMAN, MAN!
FOR REAL, DAMIEN.
I GOT INFORMATION.
ANYTHING YOU WANT TO KNOW,
I'LL TELL YOU, MAN,
ABOUT SPYRO, KAYO,
THAT BITCH PRINCESS,
ANYBODY, MAN!
WE CAN WORK AS A TEAM.
WE CAN GET MONEY, MAN.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THIS IS
VERY DISAPPOINTING.
WE'VE SHOWN YOU
NOTHING BUT LOVE, DINK...
AND RESPECT,
BECAUSE WE CARE
ABOUT YOU.
WE ALWAYS CARED.
MAN, WHAT'S THIS
COMING TO, THOUGH?
THIS IS WHAT THIS
IS COMING TO.
[BONE CRACKS]
SLEEP WELL...
LITTLE WORD MAN.
JOHN BOOKMAN THOUGHT
THAT HE COULD TAKE THIS TOWN
BACK FROM US.
HE WAS WRONG.
JOHN BOOKMAN TRIED TO
CROSS US WITH THE DIABLOS.
HE WAS WRONG AGAIN.
YEAH!
RIGHT!
NOW WE WILL BURN THIS WHOLE
FUCKIN' BLOCK TO THE GROUND.
BURN IT ALL.
AAH! AAH!
HELP ME!
JESUS.
DINK.
[SIRENS]
THIS IS A REAL TRAGEDY
HERE, REVEREND.
ALL THESE PEOPLE
LOSING THEIR HOMES.
I SURE HOPE
THEY GOT INSURANCE.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS?
YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
BROUGHT THIS DOWN.
AND THIS IS
JUST THE BEGINNING.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
BOOKMAN BOUGHT SOME
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS,
HIT THE DIABLOS,
MADE IT LOOK LIKE
IT WAS US.
WE NEED TO KNOW WHERE
THESE WEAPONS ARE.
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY MOVE THEM AROUND.
NEXT TIME THEY DO,
WE'RE GONNA BE THERE.
YOU SEE TO IT,
OR MORE PLAGUES
WILL DESCEND.
THEY JUST TORCHED
GRANT STREET
AND KILLED THE KID DINK.
HE WAS ONLY
14 YEARS OLD.
THAT'S THEIR WAY
OF DELIVERING
A MESSAGE TO US.
HEY, COME ON, MAN!
KEEP UP!
YOU KNOW, I'M TRYING
TO GET TO MY GUNS, MAN!
HERE THEY COME!
I BELIEVE SHIT DANNY BOY
THE NEXT KAYO, HUH?
WHAT WE GOT HERE,
ALL TYPES OF ARMY WARE?
LOOK AT THEM GEEZERS RUN,
OLD COWARD ASSES!
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
THANKS FOR THE TIP,
REV.
WE WON'T NEVER
FORGET THIS.
YOU GOT ALL
THEIR HARDWARE.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST LET THEM GO?
YOU JUST RUN HOME
AND PRAY
FOR THEIR ASSES.
YOU DID GOOD, O.K.?
LOOK LIKE THE REVEREND
DID HIS JOB, HUH?
RIGHT.
I GUESS WE BETTER
DO OURS.
HEY, TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
BABY, YOU COMING BACK?
SHIT. YOU KNOW
I'M COMING BACK.
I'M HOME NOW.
WHAT THE FUCK Y'ALL THINK
Y'ALL DOING?
WHO DOIN' THIS SHIT? ME!
WHO GETS THE FIRST GUN? ME!
Y'ALL NIGGERS
MUST BE GOIN' CRAZY.
HEY, WHERE THE GUNS AT?
I DON'T WANT THIS SHIT!
GIVE ME THIS SHOTGUN.
LET'S MOVE THIS SHIT.
THEY OUGHT TO HAVE THEM
LOADED BY NOW.
THEY'RE IN FOR
A BIG SURPRISE.
GIVE 'EM A TARGET.
[CLICK]
ALL RIGHT! DROP 'EM!
GOOD JOB, JAKE.
WE'RE KICKING THEIR ASS!
HA HA HA HA.
AAH!
LITTLE SOMETHING FOR YOU,
MARCUS.
HOPE YOU LIKED IT.
LET'S GO BURN
THIS SUCKER.
RIGHT.
BURN THIS SUCKER
DOWN, MAN.
COME ON, BABY.
PLAY BALL.
BACK OFF, MAN. BACK OFF!
DAMN.
OOH!
SHIT.
HEY!
NO!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
GET DOWN.
DON'T TRY IT!
I AM HOLDING A 12-GAUGE
SEMI-AUTOMATIC SHOTGUN
LOADED WITH DOUBLE-OUGHT
THAT MAKES
AN AWFUL BIG MESS!
Y'ALL BETTER
DROP 'EM RIGHT NOW.
PUT 'EM DOWN!
NOW, BACK OFF!
YOU BETTER
LISTEN TO HIM.
TAKE A LOOK UP THAT ALLEY
AT YOUR FRIENDS.
THEY'RE LYING THERE DEAD.
I SAID, LOOK, GOD DAMN IT!
PRETTY, AIN'T THEY?
AND WHO DO YOU THINK
PUT THEM THERE?
SPYRO AND DAMIEN
PUT THEM THERE!
BUT WHERE ARE THEY NOW?
WHERE THE FUCK ARE THEY?
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO
BE STANDING STRONG.
HEY, YOU!
YOU THROUGH WITH THE REBELS
TONIGHT, AIN'T YOU?
MAN, DON'T NOBODY
WANT TO HURT Y'ALL,
BUT YOU GOING TO GET HURT.
YOU WILL GET HURT.
IF I DON'T HURT YOU,
MY FRIENDS WILL.
Y'ALL GET OUT OF HERE.
EVERYBODY EXCEPT
THAT GUY IN THE RED MOVE!
PICK UP ALL THEM GUNS
AND PUT THEM
IN THE GARBAGE CAN.
HURRY UP! MOVE!
GET THEM LAST TWO.
COME HERE!
GOD DAMN IT.
GET YOUR ASS OUT!
GET YOUR ASS OUT
OF HERE!
WHERE'D YOU
LEARN TO WOLF
LIKE THAT?
ALL THAT SHOTGUN SHIT
SCARED ME, TOO.
LIKED TO SCARE
MYSELF TO DEATH.
THAT HAND LOOKS BAD.
NO. IT'S BEEN BETTER.
BULLET WENT
STRAIGHT THROUGH.
GET IT TAKEN CARE OF.
I'M GLAD I DIDN'T
HAVE TO KILL NONE
OF THEM KIDS.
I THOUGHT I'D
FEEL BETTER ABOUT
GOING AFTER THEM
FOR KENNY'S SAKE,
BUT I DON'T.
THEY'RE HIS AGE.
BUT THEY CAME TO KILL US.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
AH!
DAMN.
THESE BROTHERS
TRIED TO BURN DOWN
MY HARDWARE STORE.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU'RE
NOT WITH THEM.
I WAS JUST DOING
WHAT I WAS TOLD.
YOU GOT NEW RULES.
YOU JUST RESIGNED
FROM THE GANG.
WE CAN'T BE OUT HERE ALONE.
WHO GOING TO PROTECT US?
WE WILL.
YOU HEARD THE MAN--
US, THE ORIGINAL REBELS.
HUH. REBELS.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
HEY, BOY,
YOU GOT A HOME?
I GOT A HOME.
THEN GET IN IT!
GET YOUR LITTLE
FAKE-ASS REBEL ASS
HOME. MOVE!
GET UP!
DAMN SHAME IT HAD
TO COME TO THIS,
ISN'T IT?
ALL RIGHT.
SURE YOU'RE HAND'S O.K.?
YEAH. IT'S COOL.
DAMN. IT'S ABOUT TIME.
BUBBA, YOU'RE LOOKING
GOOD, MY MAN.
NEVER FELT BETTER.
IT SURE FEELS GOOD,
ALL US REBELS
TOGETHER AGAIN,
BUT, DAMN,
WHO'S GOING FIRST?
WE ALL ARE.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO!
I'LL BE BACK!
I PROMISE YOU!
I'M NOT DONE YET!
GET TO THE OLD
STEEL MILL, FAST!
THE FACT
THAT JOHN BOOKMAN
USED ALL THOSE
HEAVY WEAPONS ON US
IS PROOF IN ITSELF
THAT HE WAS THE ONE
THAT RAIDED THE DIABLOS.
LET'S HOPE BLOOD AGREES.
HEY, KID, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
NOBODY HAD ROOM
FOR ME IN THE CAR.
WHERE THE HELL
IS SPYRO
AND DAMIEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY YELLED SOMETHING ABOUT
GOING TO THE OLD STEEL MILL.
JOHN, YOU REMEMBER
THE SHORTCUT?
YEAH. I SHOULD.
I WORKED THERE
FIVE YEARS.
HAVE THE COPS
MEET US AT THE MILL.
I GUESS WE
BETTER MOP UP.
YOU GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT, LAURIE?
YEAH. I'M GOING
TO FIND MARCUS.
YOU GOT IT. LET'S GO.
I'VE KNOWN BLOOD
ALL OF HIS LIFE.
THERE SHOULD HAVE
NEVER BEEN TROUBLE
BETWEEN US.
THINGS AIN'T NEVER GOING
TO BE LIKE THEY WERE.
WE GOT TO GET
TO BLOOD FIRST.
SPEED UP!
THIS ISN'T THE SHORTCUT
I WAS THINKING ABOUT.
NO. YOU DONE FORGOT.
OH, MAN!
MARCUS, MARCUS!
I'LL GET YOU
SOME HELP.
DON'T MOVE.
I'LL GET YOU
SOME HELP.
DON'T MOVE.
JUST STAY THERE.
AAH!
GET YOUR BITCH ASS UP!
GET YOUR BITCH ASS UP.
GET THE FUCK UP.
YOU MUST NOT HAVE TALKED
TO YOUR FAMILY ABOUT ME YET.
I OFFED
YOUR PUNK-ASS SON!
DO I HAVE TO DO
YOUR BITCH ASS, TOO?
YOU DID IT?
AAH!
AH!
UGH!
WHAT THE FUCK YOU GOING
TO DO WITH THAT NOW?
GET UP!
HOW YOU KNOW
THAT MOTHERFUCKER
AIN'T GOING TO
BLOW UP IN YOUR FACE?
WELL, LET'S FIND OUT.
WOMAN'S INTUITION.
HYAH!
AH!
YOU PIECE OF SHIT!
YOU'RE DEAD NOW!
GET YOUR FUCKING ASS UP!
PUNK!
AH!
BRING YOUR ASS
BACK HERE.
LET'S SEE WHAT
YOU GOT, MOTHERFUCKER!
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT!
UHH!
SON OF A BITCH!
YOU KILLED
YOUR SON, MAN.
YOU KILLED MY SON,
MOTHERFUCKER!
YOU CARE
ABOUT HIM NOW, HUH?
YOU DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW HIM, MAN.
YEAH. YOU.
I KNOW ABOUT YOU.
YOU REMIND ME
OF MY OLD MAN.
I DIDN'T KNOW HIM,
BUT, YOU SEE,
I'M YOUR SON.
YOU MADE ME WHAT I AM.
YOU CREATED ME. NOW
YOU'RE GOING TO KILL ME?
HUH? UHH!
[CRACK]
UHH!
ARGH!
[SNAP]
OH...JESUS.
UHH!
YOU MOTHERFUCKER!
YAHH!
AAH!
LOOK, SON OF A BITCH!
THIS IS IT.
AAH!
AH! OH!
UHH!
AH!
[GUNSHOTS]
MAN...
JAKE, THEY SET US UP, MAN!
YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE ME!
CHILL.
MR. BOOKMAN, MR. TREVOR...
IT'S TIME WE NEIGHBORS MET.
LET ME EXPLAIN
SOMETHING TO YOU,
MY BROTHER.
JUST BECAUSE
DAMIEN'S DEAD,
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU CAN MOVE IN.
I WON'T BE
THAT FAR AWAY.
I'M BACK HOME, BLOOD,
AND I'M WORKING
WITH HIM...
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
WELL, THERE GOES
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
WELL, WELL,
HERE THEY ARE,
LATE AS USUAL.
YEP. I KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
ROCKETS
MOON SHOTS
SPEND IT ON
THE HAVE-NOTS
MONEY
WE MAKE IT
BEFORE WE SEE IT
YOU TAKE IT
OH, MAKES ME
WANNA HOLLER
THE WAY THEY DO MY LIFE
OH, MAKES ME
WANNA HOLLER
THE WAY THEY DO MY LIFE
THIS AIN'T LIVIN'
YOU KNOW THE BIBLE SAYS
YA GOT TO BE MORE GIVIN'
WHOA-OH-OH-OH
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO
NO, NO-NO, NO
INFLATION
NO CHANCE
TO INCREASE
FINANCE
BILLS PILE UP
SKY-HIGH
SEND THAT BOY OFF
TO DIE
OH, MAKES ME
WANNA HOLLER
THE WAY THEY DO MY LIFE
WHOA, MAKES ME
WANNA HOLLER
THE WAY THEY DO MY LIFE
THIS AIN'T LIVIN'
YOU KNOW,
YOU KNOW, THE BIBLE SAYS
YA GOTTA BE MORE GIVIN'
WHOA-OH-OH-OH
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO
WELL, WELL, WELL
WELL, YEAH
COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON
OOH-WAH
COME ON,
COME ON
OH
OOH, OOH, BABY
YEAH, YEAH
IN THE NAME OF JUSTICE
IN THE NAME OF PEACE
IN THE NAME OF HARMONY
LET THE VIOLENCE CEASE
IN THE NAME OF RIGHT
IN THE NAME OF WRONG
IN THE NAME OF BEIN'
BEHIND THE EIGHTBALL
A LITTLE BIT TOO LONG
WE ALL KNOW
THERE'S GOT TO
BE A BETTER WAY
WE ALL FEEL
WE'D LIKE TO
HAVE A BETTER SAY
WE ALL SEE
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A BETTER CHOICE
WITH YOUR GOOD EAR
LISTEN TO THE VOICE--OOH
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
CAN'T YOU
HEAR THE VOICES?
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
EACH AND EVERY DAY
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
WELL, WELL
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
IN THE NAME OF FREEDOM
AND OF FAIR PLAY
IN THE NAME OF SUNSHINE
LET THERE BE
A BRIGHTER DAY
IN THE NAME OF CHILDREN
LIVIN' ON THE STREETS
IN THE NAME OF
CLEANIN' UP AMERICA
FROM SEA TO SHININ' SEA
WE ALL KNOW
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A BETTER WAY
WE ALL FEEL
WE'D LIKE TO HAVE
A BETTER SAY
WE ALL SEE
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A BETTER CHOICE
WITH YOUR GOOD EAR
LISTEN TO THE VOICE, OOH
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
CAN'T YOU
HEAR THE VOICES?
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
ALL OVER THE WORLD
SHOUT
SAVE THE PEOPLE
OF THE STREETS
SHOUT
OH, GOD
OF THE STREETS
SAVE THE PEOPLE
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
GOOD GOD ALMIGHTY,
GOOD GOD ALMIGHTY
SHOUT
OF THE STREETS
GOOD GOD ALMIGHTY...