vulgar expression? n,
as r? tenders in English? s
Traducci n: Reef
Recordings raw, unprocessed
S it for internal use - running not're
- Once m s ...?
- I blame his cousin Trevor.
No, I do not think so ...
- Watch your back. We have insurance.
- Ayuadame?
Do not ...!
- Why ??
- I do the investigation here ?!?
"S ?, I told you that you can come
directly to my room n! "
- In "Special Abilities" on my resume.
- I am convinced.
- And so ...
- Undoubtedly, the only thing there.
Beautiful ...
L bet that? Tears flow
first interview.
- Who? Mam? or pap ??
- Both.
Good: the stakes bet?
Sizzler.
- That restaurant let it broke ?.
- Plus dessert tray.
Can I ask you something?
- Oh, what ???
-? Qu? about the girl.
Get p? Cheap PILLS. ? Oxides, benzo s ...
Ta-do, Beth; probably late.
I think she was sexually assaulted.
- ?Really ...?
- I know.
-? Qu? they are "? oxides" and "benzo"? ?So?
- Est s kidding? ? D? Nde you find this guy?
? Why? hire professionals,
Agatha in the net when you can ...
- This has something to say, no?
- Sorry: Thiele Where'd I have my curr lum????
In the net.
- Until cu ndo, autodidactule?
- Almost est ?.
- Almost?
- S ?.
MICR? Phone ...
Two MICR? Phones.
MICR Telephone - MICR phone both?.
We are fine?
- S ?, we are ready.
- Thank you.
I look at the c? Mara and ....
It's too late to want
to go to the bathroom? or?
Gives.
Bun. As? we start ...
With the beginning.
? Cu? They are the first memories
Carson?
When I was born ?, it was ...
- As? perfect.
- It was a blessing n?.
A blessing? Absolute n.
A? L like to keep after m? Y ...
Pretend it was
? Qu? and m is? Y ...
It is good, nice and ...
The care and ...
Intelligent and talented.
He liked Sunday school.
Learned? Throughout the Bible by heart.
You said a verse ...
Did you quote immediately.
Our religion has us
every Sunday in church.
And Carson?
he went.
He earned a scholarship to East Lake.
A school cat? Lica prestige.
And we are not cat licos? -
as? ISTEA ?? is.
- My hair?
- S ?, You look great.
Ace: arrived Carson?
East Lake in the first year you.
Not knowing anyone;
it was new.
But I've always tried
be kind to all new.
S is the school ?, cat? Lica, but
Not that all religion? N.
But she does and always har? ...
do what is right, the things.
And she wanted? To integrate.
I miss the times when spending
time together; I need, but ...
I can not stay with an f? Rmaco.
Just a second ...
I'm sorry about that.
I'm going to do and work.
Not as ?.
Do me a favor?
Tell me what is? S ready.
Well, let's start.
? Cu? L is your full name?
Carson Morris.
? Cu? L mainly is your drug?
Heroine.
? Want to convert this
in one sentence?
Carson said participating in
an educational program on addiction? n.
He knew that his family
intervention? n planned.
Your mother tells me you could? To quote the entire Bible from memory.
No "whole Bible" but ...
S? many verses, or ...
He knew that alg? N d a.
Jason, give me please
behind? s bible.
Hebrew 2:18.
You know the type.
"For what I suffered ?,
? He himself was tempted "
"It can and those who tempt
to help them. "
What I have.
Le peg? It was trade.
Great job, Carson.
- Why? TIVE me?
- I want to see with your eyes.
I'm not filming.
It all started? to fight ...
At first I thought? it was something
teenagers, but ...
The kids dearly.
And they were like or years
Carson was usual ...
For them around.
S? I thought? that He wanted to
integrate. And fracas ?.
Began? to come in the afternoon and
No regres? home and not call anything.
So? L started? to dress up
that way Goth, which ...
It really bothers me.
I swear it seemed to have changed
overnight.
- He became? in ...
- Like a zombie. It became? a zombie.
Somehow Kattath? Nico.
What? Date in bed, not waking up, trying to wake her, but she was asleep.
Then he came
drinking and drugs ...
Sometimes ...
His ...
It's like she be? for all ?.
And do not remember
hac always a.
I ask, but ...
Sorry, it s? What a light bulb.
I just finished work and ...
Everyone is? in the church.
Help! Someone help me
I think we can handle -
Thank you.
Luckily, the d? Bil and I was able to help calm down.
Bet blames school
In particular.
And I say that the school is not to blame and not others ...
We are.
Steve was shaking worse
when you arruin? your business.
We have struggled financially,
I think she felt?
we offer as a duty? a.
As? that was the? only reason? n
str? s home?
No, I have no problems with the domain
anger, I dir? s that ... ?.
- But they belong control.
- HOW TO will keep control?
Generally silent, ...
You can disable this
in one sentence? "I have my ..."
I hold my anger under control ...
Taking it in me? and silent.
As? that for MANAGERIAL?
No s? what you want, take the TV
the window? As? manages.
- No, what I'm saying.
- S? ...
I said at the end that if ...
If you do not give to drink
It was completed and ...
I'll go and have to take
Carson m ?.
God was
much of it.
Carson, you believe in God?
It s not? ...
If there is a God, do not s? ...
I think that no matter qui? N know what? about m ?.
Register ofrec? Family Morris
Carson ...?
Why? you can not stop?
At least for one day? To?
Let's see c? mo goes.
Because when I stop,
I like? To break his Drug Addiction was n.
He found? points
He found? pills ...
S lives? What to Ameth.
S? What matters.
Obscured a drug ...
I broke the esp? Spirit ...
The intent? ...
I tried as hard
to be a good mother ...
I He wanted to be a woman
better than me.
- No s? what you want to see here ?.
- Rule E-n to ... cross sections.
Use photos as wallpaper
between scenes documentary.
Then I have to go here? ...
I actually like? To
out less, as we ...
- The subject of light, ...
- Do not touch anything.
- No of course ...
- Thank you, Beth.
- Okay ...
- ?Really.
We arrived and instant taneously.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Look in the drawers.
- He said not to touch anything.
Come on, slots: what we do. Noti? E,
Make use of your imagination? N ... daily.
- Do not have much time, come back!
- Okay ...
- No, that's too - no.
- S ?, is good ...!
? You like? To ...?
- That you think it is?
- ?With Qu??
Look at this.
The possession? No demon? Aca and mental illness?
? Qu? It is wrong with that? It could? Be something, right?
- Wait wait ...
- ?So you think?
We have: Dependent teenager
Satan? S passionate home problems?
Seriously ... this girl
to keep secrets.
- I want to find them, right?
- Okay, I understand.
- Look under the bed.
- ?Okay!
Look wrists Extra home? To!
Jes? S!
Bye, Carson.
? Have you found a good thing?
Fante, I'll stop now.
As? many episodes of this series
actually filmed?
? Qu? is this, "Questions and Answers"? I have no idea.
- Eight ...? Nine?
- Okay.
- Nine.
- Nine? Bun.
? Cu? L is the emission? No action?
-? Qu? percentage of? success?
- S ?.
Fifty-Fifty ...? Work 50% 's
grave after? s six seasons.
It is a draw, as? than ...
- Go hard cute, no?
- Not for long, brother.
Real aging heavyweight r? I ask.
Maybe it will get better.
As? you are one of fan? II
who wants to save the woman.
- Not, is s mad??? I do not know ...
- And that the school teaches the pel cula???
You've seen too many pel? Particles bad.
You read poetry? A?
- What? est? s ...?
- Take some exterior shots.
- I ruin the scene?
- Rule E-No.
But now?
- Now you see the house?
- S ?, is now perfect.
- Can I ask you something?
- Clear.
I have seen his book rooms on the possession? No demon? Aca.
S? ...?
- You believe in that sort of thing? ?Really?
- Do you?
- My room n ...?
- S ?, as? that: camar graph ...?
- S? ...
- You believe in demon possession n here???
S not ... not ?.
I have not seen any evidence
in this sense.
- What you call "evidence"?
- Do not s ?.
- Jason!
- ?I'm sorry! I'm sorry ...
You have to pull these frameworks.
- ?I'm sorry!
- You Think you have the ace time ??
What ?, s sorry, I have ...
Just a second ...
No s? cu? many times someone
I used this loop.
And ...? What? channel is this?
It is for educational purposes;
Schools, as things ?.
My mom? I gave these candles
Scented Christmas.
This is called "Celebrate home."
?You like?
It sounds very festive.
Almost close ...
He found what? ...
I can not even ...
It's good.
? This is ... inside me ?.
Carson ...!
- Jason!
- Bleed stitches!
Thank you.
Memory
Conoc? his drug ...
Always keep
? Erve? Ele pr? Tactical.
- I had time to read the story ...
- The three S p pages, buddy?.
Well, I've been on a plane? N of two hours,
then four hours in the terminal.
History and found ning? N place ...
Thank you.
The lawyer in front of the c? Mara five
minutes I will come? to do with some support.
And some water.
- S ?, of course.
- Thank you.
His name is Carson; Coppersmith
with heroine by v? intravenous.
? It p? Loss of knowledge, changes
Personality, star oscillators.
-? Qui tions are the parents?
- Steve Father; It is forgiving.
Alcohol guilty last? Lic.
Beth's mother; it is religious.
Pray for Carson to improve.
Jes? S never spoke? before.
- Something abuse, trauma ...?
- Nothing STILL to?. Nothing nothing.
My mom? a few times he went,
father was drinking a couple of years ...
We may neglect
parents, but thin.
Maybe there is something
Rehabilitation? n.
Okay; Mam: Let's start with you.
? Qu? est? s ready
to do today
If Carson refuse treatment?
To outside the house.
Father're ready
its? II to this?
Can I be honest?
Amid the life of his daughter.
You be? best.
I do not think
to give out of the house.
The staying? on the streets, to be?
As? t? and buy drugs?
- As long as l is? here? ...
It offers a free accommodation
having money to the p? PILLS
It is very f? easy for her
a dependent here ?.
I'm not saying it's your fault, dad ?.
But aju? I still dependent.
You understand me?
Su? Unique opportunity to get a better
establishing a l? mite to.
Best.
- Thank you ...
- Okay.
- What do I do.
-? Qu? hell ...?
- Carson.
I'm Dr. Dean. Prentiss.
If? SIT, please.
No, do not do that now.
S? I have to listen,
nobody force? to do anything.
I have to go
to my room n first.
I want to hear what
dec? rtelo in the face.
Carson, not going anywhere
until we heard.
If? SIT, please.
Steve.
I saw students ranging from
Note 10 to memorize verses? asses Bible
af? rmaco that har? to any
a-and buy pills.
Unless you get help now
I will not give money to your pocket
And, painful as it is,
I can not stand idly
seeing yourself killed
right in front of my eyes.
Bun.
- I have to go.
-? And Where'd you go?
Steve arrives.
As? the cardinal sin of gluttony did not help.
I can not avoid.
Okay ...
Carson ...
We love you.
And we are extremely proud
with everything you do.
But we can not stay
idly
you looking c? mo you destroy.
The path must travel far
is altered
And I think that's what is? Or
We respond to our prayers.
God does not care about m ?.
Here? ...?
That's because nesocote? Ti ...
Do not despise!
In order ...
Well ... McKee?
Carson, you're a very good friend
Strong and want to improve.
Many fun? N together
then suddenly things have changed.
Locked in your mom ?!
? MPU? It? ... fucking bitch!
- Stop, Carson!
- It Stops immediately!
- What? est? s doing? D? Jala alone!
- Basta, I tell you!
D? D pulled ...? Pulled go.
Fledged e-n.
Carson in.
Carson is not unusual
what happens to your.
And I've been there ?.
And I'm addicted.
I've lost everything ...
Forgiveness? my work, family,
esteem ...
S ?, but now that is?
star of the television? n as well? than ...
You went well.
We left with good
Because I have help.
I s? c? mo feel.
If you do not like taking drugs.
Even love? E? Ti from now ...
They are user storage.
But there s? c? mo ending.
You do not know what this is ...
D? Game you.
You do not believe ?.
- Try me.
- No thanks.
Tell c? Mo you feel
In fact, Carson.
- A what? you mean?
- Do not s ?; c? Shut up, Jason.
E-n rule, Carson.
M? Rame.
There is something ...
The evil inside me ?.
Taking medicines, argue that the r? Or controlled.
A violent feeling.
There is a mont? N of names
work happening now.
As? with the addiction? n.
'Re Possessed.
But you can do better, Carson.
STILL? To no good in you.
I'm tired of all the fighting with him.
Then we will help you.
Best.
They do.
It was completely ...!
A crazy, and attacked girlfriend and
Trat? to put the letter in the neck.
And I think it is? pose? do!
S ?, pose? Do!
He was taken after? s your
of course ...
Okay, great.
It s definitely ?, S ?.
No, you have a clip
PROMOTION? N of hormig? N.
You're welcome, bye ...!
Center of Hope -
Office buildings
- You'll do fine.
- Thank you.
Hi Dean, I'm glad to see you.
- Kordis, also n?.
- Welcome.
- You must be Carson.
- S ?.
Dr. John Kordis agrad ?.
Hope Welcome Center.
- Nice and me.
- Est s in the right place?.
Stick out your tongue ...
I have checked his eyes, right?
A little more? S ...
I have check your bag, right?
No drugs or alcohol.
Otherwise you est? expelled immediately.
If you have something, d? Melo now.
Best.
- C m going?
- Okay.
Okay?
I want you to get an idea
be? in the pr? Xima week.
- When us? the last time?
- Now about six hours.
As? in the pr? ximas hours
you experience? the retreat.
- I s? what that is, right?
- S ?.
Good to be? to? n worse,
but you not be? alone.
In the fifth d? A, I'll let drugs
body - it is clean.
S? What then start
really work, right?
Bun.
If you know that make noise
put the keys in alg? n place.
But I have to ...
Well, in the pocket.
- Okay.
- Do not ...
- Put my stethoscope?
- S ?, put it to you.
Carson is? at first
detoxification process? n.
F? Basically, you should not? Be m? S f? Cil,
but psicol challenges? cal est? n reci? n beginning.
? Qu? She did drugs
It called the automedicaci? n.
As you go
the recovery? n
And i ?? your body clean of drugs,
lose? the mechanism of cooperation? n.
Go? Ironically, its status? Minimum and behavior
It may worsen as it cleans.
And Carson spoke? with you
on the possession? No demon? here?
They came here? in the village office
They said they are extratere TRI.
A woman was right in that chair
And I say that is Marilyn Monroe.
As? I prefer not to take statements
seriously, do not validate your imagination? n.
FIRST D? A
- No, no!
- T calmly bad ...?
You? Tiu? I that change.
- I think that explore ...
- As? that "explores"!
- Do not brag!
- Have sexual connotations.
Well, that ace? is.
You must remain between us.
Caf ?, cigarette ...
Hello, Callie.
- What? is it?
- C mo is s???
I best.
I want to talk a little with you
Carson.
That's ... the new or? A, right?
S ?, The new ni? A.
I have not talked to her,
Spoke? with no one.
? One can say in one sentence,
as "Carson speaks to no one"?
Carson barely speak
anyone.
If your'd say
she thinks that I have?
Can you talk about that?
You know ...
In fact I think that's
damblageal ?, about that ...
? Qu? I think ...
And again, in one sentence?
Carson needs help.
- Carson ...
- I need ... you.
Most? A of them know c? Mo start group
At night, but we got someone new as well? than ...
Before beginning, we always present:
name and why? We're here ?.
Eric,? Why? do not you go tonight?
My name is Eric.
I'm here? why
He was caught at the airport.
Now I miss my tour with the band -
-Cold as hell.
? Why? est? s really here ??
I'm addicted to heroine.
They depend Felice.
Dust - Coca na?.
I'm Callie ...
Coca bag? Na and Alcohol
Faculty of time.
Hi, I'm Adam; It depends on everyone:
drugs, alcohol, sex ...
The combination? N of the three
usually the best ...
I'm Judy and I like
whiskey and ...
I must say that I am an alcoholic? Lico
be there ?.
Bye, I'm Julia, they are dependent;
powder shoot coca? na, LSD, everything.
Carson ...
The heroine, pills ...
AL-80, Klonopin and Xanax,
about a year you from now.
- As? that is? s against the devil.
-? Qu? ...?
- Enough, Callie.
- But they told me is? He poses? da by a demon.
It is normal to feel as ?;
We are all feeling.
- Is it a feeling s?.
- Est? well, sorry ...
S? we're on television? ny stuff, but this ...
That's fucked up is? I ask.
We feelings
Carson seriously.
Carson ...?
There are things we do not know ...
Qui? N poa 'Say I have a demon?
If you do crazy stuff has demon.
As? that ... you can have a demon.
? Why? I can not say that?
You know?
No s? all of them;
Ment as if they'd know an.
I want to talk to me,
but talking to Jason, the shrimp? graph.
Jason.
Well, we do.
Was made.
- Now record. V? Ase indicator?
- S ?.
If you do not like looking at you,
As you can twist ?.
But looking at the screen,
SEAGA? sure that you appear in the frame.
- ?True?
- S ?.
Once I changed me ?, start
you mean things magazine
I do not think we can
tell dem? s' here ?.
Personal things, dir? As
s? the three million viewers.
S? ... Okay.
I think we will have a utico ther effect?;
You see c? Mo feel, it downloads ...
? L considered a personal friend.
Finally; When it's over ...
Ape? I at the bot? N.
- When you get back to school?
- The next to or, if you collect enough money?.
And then? What? ... Do pel? Particles?
M? S good you have a stable job,
But overall, great ...
S ?, I remember
the "grand assembly".
It was to be a biologist marine logo.
- A n as? can be.
- We'll see about that.
Well, try.
I think you have it.
I think everything go? all right.
S? ...?
Gives.
D? A THREE
Please env? Enos esp? Spirit
balance and self-control ...
Detoxification No ... that's really dif? Cult.
I am suffering ... Sorry ...
And I do not s? why? I'm here ?.
I said I'd try ?, but ...
S? it will never work.
I do it for my mom?
And the father, as? than ...
At least be? N safe.
But the bad feelings return.
Back and ...
No s? c? mo stop.
It's always worse
sooner the better.
- You do not know.
- Cr em, what s ?.
I've seen this,
doing for 25 years.
- Trat? to warn.
- I'll be grateful.
But now I speak of
These feelings you have.
Carson ...?
We go now, right?
- IACAT that ...!
- Bye!
- Adi s, Carson!
Bye, Carson!
Me? MBR ?? i? Eaz ?.
I do not like to touch me now.
It is part of the recall, right?
- That's right.
- Okay.
Nice place you have here ?.
- The tennis court.
- Its beautiful.
- Quite.
- S? ...
You look good, make the color of hand ...
- So ... right?
- S ?.
? You make friends
it sticks to you by other people?
I'm here? people your age?
- I'm sure they are.
- S? ...
S? ...?
? Cu l be at least ... to pray;
Pray.
Okay ...
Let us together hands, right?
Our Father who is? S in heaven,
sfin? EASC? be your name,
Your life kingdom,
H? Gase your will ...
What? Date here ?.
Carson!
Therefore: the 12th of October.
It is the third d? to here? in Carson.
Steps of recovery? N do not help,
Not do better.
He found? East
Carson's trash.
Covers
death and violence.
Here? there is another.
?Fuck!
A, sorry.
-? Qu? pel? cula?
- Nothing, nothing fires.
God ... Look, filming it.
Something est? going with it
borates in front of his mother.
- That's going to recover, Jason.
- Everyone recovery n v myth?.
I've seen this a dozen,
hundreds of times.
Now take my socks head;
Let's see what he does.
When you leave here ?, you give
luneco people? i, slippery places,
tools to meet people;
But how to handle?
As? we do RPGs.
Eric be? a man
Carson.
- Eric?
- We love and you???
- Do not ...
- Why? do not?
I do not use drugs and ...
I ask you not to give me
drugs again.
But if he does not har ...?
could? be your friend.
Bini? Or ...
Give to talk with the devil.
-? Qu? ...?
- You said you were pose both?.
Give to talk with the devil in you;
? L want to spec? Cally for love? EASC? ...
- Cu-cu u u, demon ...?
- Eric, you use.
No m? S, please.
Carson ...
You did well at first;
Est? S excited then, but the e-n rule.
? Have you looked into my eyes ...
You said exactly what ...
As? for starters.
Look, I was trying to do an exercise.
All right; Carson, for this type
exercise is to trigger emotions.
? What ??
Tina take me? less Hell.
-? Qu? ...?
- And wait.
- I hope that you.
- Finish, Carson.
- Have you prepared last dose?.
- HOW TO know Tina?
- Do not s ?.
- Let die.
- You hear? D? Pulled in peace.
Felice ...
Co 'or' MPU? It? ...
You let your face with a supplier
drugs, and? l cogi? the ass.
- What ??
- F easy ...?
- Carson?
- It is a crisis!
- You turn give way.
-? His ltame!
Shanti, give 50 mg of Haldol.
- Back ... Olv date of c ... how do?
- Carson, I hear?
-? Qu? I told you?
- You insulted.
- Say you were looking at the leaves of the patients.
- I have not looked at any connector.
- What s ?.
- I can not control now.
If something bad happens ...
I'm sorry.
D? A FIVE
I'm worried.
Carson became? a presence m? s
disturbing than I expected.
A patient costly maintenance,
draws others to her drama ...
And the fact that we are facing a team
The shooting did not help ?.
I understand; if it is too, retirement -
I do not want to be harmful.
?Can I ask a question? ? Why?
Do not allow a priest to perform an exorcism?
I mean, if it will not work,
? Why? He has no excuse for Agatha.
If aliment? the imagination? n,
it really helped? Carson?
? Why? we est? here?
And hide under pre ?.
- Everything is on the storm drain and?.
- But if it works, then ...
Perhaps as? I really healed.
Shows every sign.
? Y cu? Them are  signs
"Doctor"?
- ?Really ...?
- What ?? Those not prove anything ...
The drastic changes
personality and voice.
Seizures or convulsions, p? Loss of memory,
biting or unexplained injuries.
Unnatural superhuman force.
These are the s? Symptoms and
mental illness.
Well ... speaking languages
that not knowing ...?
You concern? N is admirable.
S ?? But yes
in fact you care ...
Let us help
things do not get worse.
Need quack,
but Detoxification n.
It has been detoxified, and status
est? worse.
There are usually
best people?
Disc? Lpeme ...
- Okay.
- Bye.
- You can interview in Carson?
- Of course.
S? Per.
Path.
You put it under your bed Carson?
I saw the cameras and hidden me
I cross saw me when I was sick.
? Think it's something more s
an addiction? n to drugs?
I've seen this, right?
- Here ??
- Do not.
In my village in Cameroon? N,
when I was a ni? a.
He had to a Ms. in my church
exactly the same situation? n.
Remember what they did
to help?
S? ...
They tied the
old? tree in the village,
prayed over it and cover
the blood of males cabr years.
S? that will sound Thiele
crazy, but ...
You can have a bath or with the bat,
but the devil is not going.
And function ??
S ?, function ?.
But she died ?.
"Super".
Hey.
No s? what? say.
See now, Jason?
I would have liked to be met
before this.
Play a game
with my friend McKee.
The mall ...
Let's see cu? NTAS free stuff
could? to receive.
I like shoplifting, s? I ...
Free samples of products confiter? A
perfume and stuff.
Eyelet? I can do it that way,
ordinary things.
And here? we demonolog? to
Our Jason Hurwitz.
I do not give a fuck, Tim.
- Fante, rob? things in her room n?
- Go here ?.
Today is October 15.
I put my hand on ...
Tom? this water sanctified.
I'm doing this to prove that happens
Carson really something.
I'm a little disappointed
the whole family ...
My way over the years
marijuana, alcohol, alucin? genos
things m? s cool ...
My life has become
uncontrollable.
When Ameth ...
She opens the mind, brother.
I can write for hours ...
Since I'm here ?, I can
It is not an f? verse formula.
Or I'll do well, or do you love? And? You.
As? that was when used and sex,
Amorth m? I do not feel anything ...
Gen ...
Or even I knew that you were all ?, as ...
Disappear into the unknown.
It is the pain ...
Inside.
You off.
And I like being here ?.
I pl? Ce? I.
Nicicare you.
I know.
No ass does not hurt.
I s? I'll ask cowards
also caught? No feelings.
People here? in the living room.
- It's time to work on you.
- S ?, but that is totally unnecessary.
You may feel like you d today;
You can not feel the same tomorrow.
- Then do not come back.
- But what? est? s running?
For fun
And self-destruction? N?
? It kills you after death? S death?
S ?, very funny; Fuck.
Carson, no!
God, they do instead!
Everyone, take away!
Jason, Al? Jate it!
God ...
Se? Or, take out of the darkness,
bring to light!
Out of the darkness
Shanti!
Est? S well?
- ?Fuck!
- Listen, little stops you!
? What ?? ? Qu? is ...?
- Keep the shit again!
-? Qu? passes, Jason?
- I have to be here ?.
- ?Do not!
- ?Get out of my way!
- I want to see what? about that!
"? C? Mo feel f? Physically?"
As ass.
"? C? Mo you feel emotionally opposite
The m physician and the process "?
As ass.
S ?,? Qui? N is?
I o? Do you have outside the infirmary to,
but you may return m? s late.
No, est? well-I s? what ...
Anyway, no s?
c? mo respond.
What? is it?
S? What He wanted to say that ...
I think.
You are? Unique.
I wish and can do
something for you.
You could? To, but ...
- What ??
- You can not apply.
- Do not.
- It's not fair to you.
- Tell me and I decide ?.
Is ...
It does not work.
As? I did not do better and ...
I need something.
Well ...? What ??
No s? another way to control it.
I can do that!
Carson ...
Come on, rule of s-n ...
E-n rule.
Everything will be okay, do you?
S ??
Bun.
Carson ...?
Carson,? What? you do?
Carson ... stop.
? Do you have a Futhi?
- Do you?
- Carson, stop!
-? Qu? pas? with ...?
- God, I is s kidding?
-? Qu? pas you? in the hand?
- Carson did this.
- It is disgusting that dick.
- S ?.
- Have a knife, carrot clean or something ??
- He has bitten the finger.
You have to tell someone, be
for alg? n type really helps.
This girl is crazy;
If shooting.
- ?, What is s tonight?
- S ?.
- E-almost midnight!
- I do not care.
- You'll wake everyone!
- I do not mind, Tim!
Or ste he said Dale?:
"Give your possession? N Cream"!
AHEAD? N, whether to a king,
a straitjacket or whatever.
? Anyone have anything against it?
No noise.
Carson!
Carson?
Carson ...?
?Fuck!
-? Where'd the hell is ??
- Do not s ?.
God, that is!
D? Where are ??
See you?
Fuck me ...
- Here? no, you must ...
- C Shut up!
? You or? Do that?
Carson?
- Not here ?, I want to go back.
- Listen and you ...
Path.
Come on, Tim, let ...
What? Ah ?, what date? Date ah ?!
- C mo?
- Do not s ?!
- I turn here ?!
- Come on, Tim!
Here ?, God ...
Carson! Carson!
Carson!
Assistance was one that was running?
Carson? ? Can you describe
? Qu? It happened tonight?
- Trying to help.
- Qui n I tried to help?
- You want out of here ??
- Jason!
? Qui? Nes were they fleeing?
? Qu? est? s doing here ??
- I dir what ?.
- Qui tions were?
Oh? Give me again? Get ...
Okay ...
I had to fire my aide? Ef ?;
SUITE hope you get that? No.
Remember, a proposal for Carson
remove to Psychiatrist? tric hospital.
In other words, give up.
- We are not equip to try ...
- There follow, equip yourself!
You can bring staff
Est? S paying s? The fat!
Hey, I'm five
addict pro bono ...
Shit, excuse me!
We are all whores, right?
This girl is my responsibility!
Est? seriously ill and that he has covered.
- Put lives in danger!
- Due to new opportunities have!
Well, here? I take decisions m? Dicas.
S ?? Pet? one EVALUATION? n
tomorrow Psychiatrist? trica.
And I hope I will definitely propose
Transfer Carson.
Path. And I will propose the use
another unit in the future.
Leave the damn room!
- Ad where are you going?
- I have a job; Saco please?
Ad? Where are you going?
They let you make holy water?
Tim has to permanently hospitalized.
S? ...?
You realize what happens if a inflicts
a Psychiatrist? trica unit? It's crazy!
If not crazy,
having to let go.
?Fuck!
They have a ca? Da
And they were throwing away the key!
You want to try to stop
save, DOBI ...
?Fuck!
Breathe deeply, please.
As? that good - again.
Very good, thank you.
So? C? Mo you feel now, f? Basically?
I feel better; I mean ...
... I feel like part of the dif? Cult
removal of the past, as? than ...
Best.
You feel depressed,
something like this?
You spoke? before about ...
He is pose? Given by "a demon".
I think it was a kind
TME? fora of the ...
That part of me? that is? evil
I feel I can not control.
Good, d? Jame to take the tension n.
I control? early
I'm fine.
E-n rule, has to take over.
Part of the exam.
What? This is it?
God, this hatred ...
That's the worst part
of my work. You will have? to exclude you.
- It was the only way!
- Never the only way!
You knew the rules when you arrived
Center of Hope!
Let things wrapped me
"I'll call and have their parents.
Wait: she did,
I did it.
- What ??
- She was unconscious, no?
- You bring drugs my unit?
- Esc chame: When you hear ...?
Nasty Bastard!
Disparate? He had to complete.
- I realize ...
- No matter, Suzanne ...
- Moved ...
- It Not what s my job, my career?.
- I understand, but we will not ...
- ?Is the law! Done!
- Hey, you've committed.
- Shut up, Tim.
Get that damn c? Mara
ahead of us!
? Qu? react to n have
what happened today?
You want to fuck react to n?I give you my react to n dick!
Here? est? I react to n!
You will have? what to do
process at home!
It's Monday ... From what I can tell,
STILL? Salt? of the House.
I keep thinking about c? Mo Carson
And ATAC? the friend intervention? n.
Definitely ...
Something strange or respects.
My? Wednesday night ... STILL? Anything.
- ?Hello?
- Beth, I'm Jason series.
- I want to know what? about Carson.
- What ??
- Where's D? Carson?
- I can not talk with you.
It's exactly what I do; 'See what ?, cerr
Salt? house for a week.
- You know you as ?!
- I saw the house.
- I have to close and to call the police?.
- No, listen, Beth!
Do not do anything wrong, right?
Look: S I have to help her.
Jason, wait a minute.
Beth? Qu? is?
Beth? Qu? is that?
Fuck me ...
?I'm sorry!
Bet?
Beth, you?
Shit ... So.
Hello ... breaking properties?
Hi, McKee, quer? A
I bring you a new interview.
The producer says he wants
material that; can?
- To change or ...
- No, your eyes turn blue.
- Thanks are goats.
- Great.
As? as you said you started? Carson
with CIT ?? eniile and you have not seen.
- But you said you still friends?
- S ?.
After making
? Why? the intervention? n?
It s not ?. I mean ...
It's crazy.
? Have you ever done something
that a ...
Do not.
But McKee ... I want to be your star,
you tell your own story.
I told my story.
I mean ... I did nothing.
I do not know? why ?; one must ask
in? l, and like me because? to know!
For your friend
already it said enough.
You do not want to look like a liar
on television? national n, right?
Bun. May.
A tease ...
That's it, that ...
I think it will take
everything so seriously.
Tachinatul is no big deal.
Spunea? I really?
I tell you, the other,
believe in Satan? s.
And, you know, if everything was lu Christian Fish
then? qu? It is going to be with us?
Well, she wanted? To integrate,
I get it.
I mean ... especially Kiley and Mark.
I think she wanted? An see
to d? nde they are going to go in the game ...
But, I mean ...
It was not real, s? What a joke,
but she tom? too far.
What you did, McKee?
What? you've done?
- S as a joke, so?.
- Look, do not think my dick stick.
What? you've done?
We have not done anything, right?
Whatever happened, he was fired
brought to the room? n with her.
- See pel cula s what it was a joke?.
- Wait ...
Tambi? N ... There is no shooting.
S ?, there is a shootout.
Or I give me much worse
TV,? It is not as ??
Path.
God, not tom ?.
be? ADEV? r? ciune ...
C? Shut up that wine.
We will'll love.
We do it all the time.
I've done it many times, s? ...
Not really, it's a joke.
Fuck.
"Demonicus Codex".
Book Devil.
It is aut? ntica.
- And the charm ...
- S ?, everyone repeats after s of m ?, right?
"Silence brings to life hell."
Silence brings demons to life.
Silence brings demons to life ...
Satan? S, I hear we ...
Satan? S, hears us
receives the blood sacrifice.
Demon Moloch ...
I will give this dish.
receives you.
- ?Ready?
-. No, continue
Moloch ...
M ?, Come Moloch.
? Qu? est? happening?
We leave, we will ...
M? S r? I ask
Job
McKee! Come McKee
You left it all ?.
You know what you do?
- I'm sorry ...
- Do you know what they'll do?
- Look, I did not know to ...?
- McKee, I need the book.
-? Qu? book?
- Cursed book used in the ritual.
? Qu? are you gonna do with him?
Give me the book.
Best.
I have the book that I downloaded
Exorcism things on the net
I like? A ?, but all Popa and do
Pending my cock.
Jesus Christ, who is the real demon And nobody helps you.
- What ??
- You went to our SUITE n?
- S ?, bring m s late, I?.
- You have what?
- To discover what happened ?.
- Get immediate or call the cop!
Look, I'm here? to help,
? Are you then you get the c? Mara, right?
Do not go to that house, Jason,
you have to bring the c? mara again ...
- L Cu is the plan?
- Get the footage and call the police to?.
My room? No, please ...
- Here ?.
- Hold down.
- Prepare?
- ?Do it!
? Qu? est? all going ??
- What? you want?
- Where's D? Carson?
I think I told you not want
to join emi ...
- Where are ?? D?
- Ad where are you going?
-? Qu? hell is? s doing here ??
- I do not agree, no?
I said I want to leave!
Just ...? Stop!
- Where's D? Carson?
- I'll show you, but ... Enough!
She's that?
Fuck ...
- Go, slots, up!
- God ...
I Duce insurance; I'll stick with Steve,
to give the t? title of "Father of A? o".
- And I'm going to get another angle?.
- Okay, I understand.
Carson ...?
We turned back to the crew n.
Let me ...
Carson, me, Jason!
?I can enter?
Fuck ...
Here ?, put the c? Mara down
You can see under the door.
Carson ...?
I am ...
?Fuck!
? Qu? about ...? As? Beth, tr? Eme water.
Water and towels now!
Steve ...
- S? ...?
- A brief interview, right?
- ?Do you want a cookie? Do not? Best.
- ?Do not!
Carson, I hear?
Hey, Carson?
No, what you did to your face ...
Fuck ...
Carson ...
She is not? here ?!
That is not true!
S ?, it is!
? And you know who you are; His name is Moloch
And it can be sent to where they came from!
It merciful lord forever
And forgive,
receives pray for m ?,
Your humble servant, who is with sin,
to be forgiven and you can use
this fight on their behalf.
You far spies unclean spirit, along with
His power of Satan? S, the enemy ...
Leather and stay away from this creature
Se? or, why? l ?, mand right?
Whoever neg? higher than
heaven into the depths of hell!
You away from this
It servant of the lord!
- Steve, Where's d??? the control panel?
-? Qu? ...?
- A no power!
- I will show you
Ven.
- Fuck ...
- Do not go.
- Steve, lights ...
Fuck ...
- Ad where are you going?
- I'll be right back!
Jesus Christ ...
Go Go ...!
?Fuck!
Carson?
Jason!
- Oh, is s good???
-? Qu? ...?
- Get up; He d catch? to me.
- Okay ...
Come!
To come?
D? Where are ??
- Where are ?? D?
- Do not s ?!
Tim!
Tim, where is? S friend?
Care. Tim!
Fuck. Tim!
- Where's D? Steve?
- Do not s ?.
Carson?
Carson, I Tim.
Est? S ah ??
Se? Or Carson, come in the house ...
Carson,? What? is that?
Leave that!
Carson, That one down the knife!
- Carson ...?
- Tim?
Carson!
- Jason, take this.
- Okay.
- I'll give Tim.
- Do not get anywhere!
- Cu date!
Tim!
Tim ...!
Jason, I did not ...
I have not told the truth ...
When we interview ...
Carson ...
Because Carson violently
Is cri? violence.
Beth, not now.
We have to find Carson.
I've always seen violence
Family and ...
Steve drink and drink
Downloads to m? ...
And I can download
Carson ...
Fuck me ...
Se? Or God ...
God, my fucking God ...
Carson ...
S? that is? s ah ?!
Suzanne!
Tim!
? Qu? fuck me-sii?
Tim?
Jason!
God ...!
Carson!
S? that is? s ah?
inside, Carson ...
?Please!
God!
Carson!
Carson! S? What are you
all ?!
I s? you hear me!
I s? you hear me;
not to give in, I'm here ?!
Do not stop, fight!
Back to m ?, please ...
Jason ...
They had to finish.
You came back for me? ...
Volv? to normal
for you ...
- Steve, no ...
- God ...!
God, Jason!
Jason!
Carson ...
Traducci n: Reef
Demons