CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE
BY BMG VIDEO
[SHANGRI-LAS TUNE PLAYS]
[LIP-SYNCHING TO WOMAN'S VOICE]
THE PAST
PAST
WELL, NOW, LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT THE PAST
THE PAST
IS FILLED WITH...
SILENT JOYS
AND BROKEN TOYS
LAUGHING GIRLS
AND TEASING BOYS
WAS I EVER IN LOVE?
I CALLED IT LOVE
I MEAN
IT FELT LIKE LOVE
THERE WERE MOMENTS WHEN
WELL...
THERE WERE
MOMENTS WHEN...
Man: NOBODY ON THAT
PARTICULAR NIGHT
SHOWERED AND SHAVED
TO GO TO A RIOT.
THERE HAD BEEN
RACE RIOTS,
ANTI-WAR RIOTS,
THERE HAD BEEN ALL SORTS
OF CIVIL RIGHTS RIOTS,
AND NOW IT WAS TIME
FOR THE GAY RIOT.
RAIDS WERE NOT UNUSUAL,
SO SEEING A RAID
WAS SEEING A RAID.
THIS WAS JUST A RAID.
EVERY OTHER GROUP
HAD MADE THEIR POINT
IN THE SIXTIES,
BUT WE WERE NEVER
GOING TO MAKE OURS.
NOBODY WAS WORRIED
ABOUT THE FAGGOTS.
YOU COULD DO
WHAT YOU WANT WITH THEM,
BUT SUDDENLY HERE WERE
THE FAGGOTS NOW REVOLTING.
AND THE PAPERS TALKED ABOUT
PEOPLE LIGHTING BONFIRES
AND TRASH BASKETS
AND THROWING THEM
THROUGH THE WINDOWS
AND I PERSONALLY THOUGHT,
"OH, MY GOD.
HOMOSEXUALS ARE
GOING TO BE THE BOGEYMEN
OF THE SEVENTIES."
WELL, I THINK IT HAD
SOMETHING TO DO
WITH JUDY GARLAND'S DEATH.
IT WAS
BEYOND FRIGHTENING.
IT WAS, UM,
TRAUMATIZING
AND, IN PART,
I AM STILL TRAUMATIZED
BY IT TO THIS DAY.
ON A SCALE OF 1 TO 10,
AS FAR AS A RIOT GOES,
IT WASN'T
A VERY GOOD RIOT.
IT WAS OVER
BEFORE IT STARTED,
AND SOME HEADS
WERE BUSTED ON BOTH SIDES,
BUT THAT WAS IT.
IF MY MOTHER HEARS
THE WORD "STONEWALL",
SHE HAS TO TAKE
A HEART PILL.
Man: I WAS WITH
THE MATTACHINE SOCIETY,
AND WE SORT OF BELIEVED
IN WEARING COATS AND TIES
AND MAKING THE MOST
RESPECTABLE APPEARANCE
AS WE COULD.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO SEE GAY PEOPLE
GO ON A RAMPAGE
AND DESTROY THEIR OWN
NEIGHBORHOOD.
SEE, THERE'S AS MANY
STONEWALL STORIES
AS THERE IS GAY QUEENS
IN NEW YORK.
AND THAT'S A SHITLOAD
OF STORIES, BABY.
EVERYWHERE YOU GO
IN MANHATTAN, OR AMERICA,
OR THE ENTIRE DAMN WORLD,
YOU'RE GONNA HEAR
SOME NEW LEGEND.
WELL, THIS IS MY LEGEND,
HONEY, O.K.?
MY STONEWALL LEGEND.
DUM DOO DOO DOO DOO
DOO DOO DOO
OOH-AH OOH-AH,
OOH, OOH, KITTY
TELL US ABOUT THE BOY
FROM NEW YORK CITY
OOH-AH OOH-AH,
COME ON, KITTY
OH, YEAH-EAH AH
HE'S KINDA TALL
HE'S REALLY FINE
YEAH YEAH
SOME DAY I HOPE
TO MAKE HIM MINE, ALL MINE
YEAH YEAH
AND HE'S NEAT
AND OH SO SWEET
AND JUST THE WAY
HE LOOKED AT ME
HE SWEPT ME
OFF MY FEET
YEAH YEAH
OOH OOH OOH WHEE
YOU OUGHT TO COME AND SEE
HOW HE WALKS
YEAH YEAH
AND HOW HE TALKS
YEAH, YEAH
OOH AH, OOH AH,
OOH OOH, KITTY
TELL US ABOUT THE BOY
FROM NEW YORK CITY
HE'S REALLY DOWN
AND HE'S NO CLOWN
YEAH YEAH
HE HAS THE FINEST
PENTHOUSE
I'VE EVER
SEEN IN TOWN
YEAH-YEAH
AND HE'S CUTE
IN HIS MOHAIR SUIT
AND HE KEEPS
HIS POCKETS FULL
OF SPENDING LOOT
YEAH-YEAH
OOH, OOH OOH WHEE
YOU OUGHT TO
COME AND SEE
HE'S THE MOST
YEAH, YEAH
FROM COAST TO COAST
OOH-AH OOH-AH
OOH OOH, KITTY
TELL US ABOUT THE BOY
FROM NEW YORK CITY
OOH-AH OOH-AH
COME ON, KITTY
TELL US ABOUT THE BOY
FROM NEW YORK CITY
OOH-AH OOH-AH
OOH OOH, KITTY...
HEY, IT AIN'T LADYLIKE
TO RUN, DAMN IT!
I GOTTA PEE, TOO, GIRL.
OOH!
Helen: YOU AIN'T BEEN SO FAR
AS CONEY ISLAND.
LaMiranda: LIFE'S A CRUISE
FOR YOU, BITCH.
Moxie: HEY, MATINEE
GIRLS, SHOWTIME.
[GIGGLING]
Helen: I DO SO
LOVE AN AUDIENCE.
I'M GOING OUT
WITH ROBERT CLOHESSEY
TONIGHT!
HEY,
LINDO.
HEY, BRAKE, BABY.
LaMiranda:
BIG CAR, SMALL WEENIE.
Helen: I'M TELLING YOU, GIRL.
YOU SHOULD HAVE COME
TO THAT PARTY.
ALL THE GUYS WERE THERE.
LOLLYPOP WAS THERE,
CHUCKY WAS THERE
WITH BELLS ON.
LaMiranda:
YEAH, BUT NO BALLS,
RIGHT, HONEY?
SLOW DOWN.
Man: MARCH ON
PHILADELPHIA.
Man: HOMOSEXUAL RIGHTS.
PLEASE JOIN US.
Helen: NO MONEY.
HEY, MARCH ON
PHILADELPHIA.
FOR WHAT?
HOMOSEXUAL RIGHTS.
WHY DON'T YOU BE THERE?
SURE.
GREAT. DON'T FORGET.
TRICK OR TREAT!
[SMOOCH]
LaMiranda: HEY, VITO.
YOU REMIND ME OF MY DEAD FATHER.
Moxie: HEY, VITO.
DO YOU WANT ME TO COME
HOME WITH YOU TONIGHT?
Helen: HEY, VITO.
HOW ARE THEY HANGING?
SHAVING OUR
SHOULDERS YET?
O.K., GIRLS. WE SEE I.D.
OR WE SEE BLOOD.
LaMiranda:
HERE'S MY I.D., BABY.
YOU RECOGNIZE?
LOOKS OUT OF DATE TO ME.
Vito: COME ON, SISSIES.
MOVE ON, MOVE ON.
LaMiranda:
AH, KISS MY I.D.
Helen:
HEY, MUSSOLINI.
Vito: HEY, PUNK.
HEY, VITO.
MY I.D.'s IN THE CAR.
TAKE A HIKE.
I'M WITH THEM.
YEAH? YOU FUCKIN'
MOTHER'S WITH THEM.
VITO, WHAT ARE
YOU GOING THROUGH?
QUIT RAGGIN'
ON OUR RIDE.
YEAH, VITO.
DON'T BUST MY BALLS,
BUDDY.
Moxie: YEAH, VITO.
DON'T BUST HIS BALLS.
YOU FAIRIES
JUST GET THE FUCK
OUTTA MY FACE.
PARTY OVER HERE.
DIVA COMING THROUGH!
MOXIE, GIRL, AIN'T IT
PAST YOUR BEDTIME?
BACK UP, FELLAS.
THE BITCHES IS BACK
ON THE BLOCK!
Moxie: OUT OF MY WAY.
I'M DRINKING.
WHO'S PAYING?
LISTEN, UH...
THANKS A LOT.
YOU OWE ME ONE, O.K.?
HAVE A NICE LIFE.
YOUNG MAN?
YOUNG, YOUNG,
YOUNG-YOUNG MAN.
MY I.D.'s
IN THE CAR.
WHEN YOU'RE YOU, SWEETNESS,
A FACE IS ALL
THE I.D. YOU NEED.
SEE THE OLD MONEY
BY THE WURLITZER?
HE WOULD LIKE
TO FURNISH YOUR THIRST
WITH A COOLING LIBATION.
RIGHT.
A DRINK, TWINKIE.
WHAT'LL IT BE?
OH! ALL RIGHT.
SURE.
A BUD?
AH. HOUSE BEER.
HIT ME WITH IT.
BELIEVE ME, BABY.
YOU WON'T FEEL A THING.
OH, ANGELO.
OH, SHIT. WE'RE OUT.
CHICA!
CHICA,  I LOVE THAT
OUTFIT MORE EVERY TIME
I SEE IT.
WHICH IS
A LOT OF LOVE,
HONEY.
AND
A LOT OF NERVE
TOO, GIRL.
TRAMP.
ALLOW ME TO THANK
YOU IN PERSON
FOR ACCEPTING
MY OFFER.
DON'T MENTION IT.
DO HAVE ONE
YOURSELF, MY DEAR.
WHY? WHAT THE HELL
HAVE I EVER DONE
TO YOU?
HEY, LADY ERNESTINE.
GIVE ME A SHOT
OF JACKIE D.
THAT'S PRINCESS
ERNESTINE TO YOU,
BITCH.
THAT'S PRINCESS BITCH
TO YOU, LADY.
JUST GET YOUR ASS
IN LINE, LaMIRANDA.
I'M SERVING
MR. SMITH, HERE.
SMITH?
WE'RE ALL SMITH
IN THIS PLACE,
BABY.
I'M PRINCESS
ERNESTINE SMITH.
I'M LaMIRANDA SMITH.
AND THIS IS...
MATTY DEAN. SMITH.
MY NAME IS AUGUST.
LOOKS MORE LIKE
DECEMBER TO ME.
I TRUST YOU'RE IMMUNE
TO HEPATITIS.
WHOOPS.
DAMN IT, PERRY.
WHAT DAY IS IT?
Mr. August:
OH, DEAR.
Ernestine:
THEY WERE ALREADY
HERE ON TUESDAY.
EXCUSE ME.
KEEP THE CHANGE.
Ernestine:
CALL VINNIE,
GODDAMN IT.
DON'T GIVE YOUR
REAL NAME, BABY.
Cop: SHOWTIME, LADIES.
COME ON.
LET'S KEEP IT MOVING.
I HAVE 2 LETTERS
FOR EVERYONE HERE--
"I" AND "D."
COME ON, COME ON.
MOVE. MOVE.
MOVE, MOVE-MOVE-MOVE!
YOU.
WASHROOM.
HEY, ERNIE.
OH, ERNIE.
ERNESTINE?
GOOD EVENING,
OFFICER.
HOW 'BOUT A DRINK
WHILE WE'RE SWEATING
AWAY HERE, HUH?
WHAT WAS I THINKING OF?
Man: PUT THAT SHIT AWAY!
JOHNNY WALKER
FOR NEW YORK'S
FINEST, PRINCESS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
OFFICERS.
GENTLEMEN, WELCOME
TO THE STONEWALL INN.
WE WEREN'T EXPECTING
YOU FELLAS.
ORDERS FROM ON THE HIGH.
WHAT CAN I TELL YOU?
WHAT CAN ANYONE
TELL ANYBODY,
RIGHT?
SO, DRINK.
IS THAT WHISKEY,
OR IS THAT
GODDAMN WHISKEY?
FRIGGIN' ANGEL'S PISS.
THESE STUPID-ASS
FAIRIES DON'T KNOW
HOW LUCKY THEY ARE.
AM I RIGHT?
DAMN STRAIGHT.
BEST BOOZE...
AND THE PRETTIEST
BAR CHICKS.
AH-OOH!
Cop:  PLAYBOY  CENTERFOLD
COME TO LIFE.
IF IT AIN'T HOLLY
GO-FRIGGIN'-LIGHTLY.
LET'S SEE YOU,
PRETTY THING.
OH, SO CLASSY
AND DAINTY, IT IS.
Cop: SMELLS GOOD, TOO.
Cop: AW, SHE LOOKS
BETTER WITHOUT THEM.
THERE. NOW WE CAN
GET US A REAL
GOOD LOOK.
WASHROOM.
I GAVE YOU 2 WORDS--
WASH, AND ROOM.
Cop: COME ON,
YOU HEARD HIM. GO.
THIS WAY, FELLAS.
Cop: YEAH, LET'S SEE
IF THE CHEAP WIG FLUBS.
Cop: THAT'S IT.
HOLD YOUR BREATH, HONEY.
Cop: POOR LITTLE
WET FAGGOT, HUH?
Cop: JESUS CHRIST.
I.D.?
OH, BABY.
LaMIRANDA, GIRL,
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
PUT YOURSELF
THROUGH THIS?
WHY, PRINCESS ERNESTINE,
IT'S FOR THE SHEER,
IRRESISTIBLE,
GODDAMN GLAMOUR OF IT ALL.
Cop: HANDS UP, FAGGOT.
HEY! LEAVE HIM ALONE!
COME ON. HE AIN'T
HURTIN' NOBODY, RIGHT?
HE AIN'T HURTIN'
NOBODY, RIGHT?
OOOPH!
THAT'S RIGHT, KID.
NO ONE'S HURTING
NO ONE...EXCEPT YOU.
HE DON'T
HANG AROUND
WITH THE GANG NO MORE
AND HE DON'T DO
THE WILD THINGS
THAT HE DID BEFORE
OOH OOH OOH...
HE USED TO ACT BAD
HE USED TO,
BUT HE QUIT
IT MAKES ME SO SAD
'CAUSE I KNOW THAT
HE DID IT FOR ME
AND I CAN SEE...
HIS HEART IS OUT
IN THE STREET...
LaMiranda: DON'T LOOK
AT ME, GODDAMN IT.
THAT SON-OF-A-BITCH,
I THINK HE BROKE
MY GODDAMN NOSE.
AW, FORGET YOU.
THEY CONFISCATED
MY DAMN MAKE-UP BAG.
NOW THAT'S
BRUTALITY.
HOW CAN THEY
JUST DO THIS,
LIKE WE DON'T HAVE
A FUCKING CONSTITUTION
OR NOTHING?
WE DON'T. THEY DO.
WHO THE FUCK
IS "THEY?"
AMERICA. BIG AMERICA.
THE OTHER AMERICA.
FUCK BIG AMERICA.
WE'RE THE REAL
AMERICA.
AT LEAST WE BELIEVE
IN FUCKING FREEDOM,
RIGHT?
YOU DON'T EVEN GET
WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT, DO YOU?
YEAH,
LITTLE OLD DUMB ME.
HOW COULD I POSSIBLY
GET IT?
I'M SORRY.
SHIT,
I DON'T EVEN
GET IT.
GOD, I AM SUCH
AN ASSHOLE.
SOMEHOW,
I REALLY BELIEVED
THAT IT WOULD BE
DIFFERENT IN NEW YORK.
[SNIFFLING]
YEAH, WELL,
MS. LIBERTY LIED.
I ALMOST FORGOT
PEOPLE DID THAT.
YOU'RE FREE
TO JOIN ME,
IF YOU'D LIKE.
I DON'T DO TEARS.
DON'T YOU EVER
GET THIS ANGRY?
I DON'T DO ANGRY.
IT'S ALL I DO.
THAT'S HER,
RIGHT OVER THERE.
NOW YOU KNOW Y'ALL
ARE GONNA BE
RAPTURED UP
TO HEAVEN FOR
YOUR DEEDS TODAY,
DON'T YOU, BOSTONIA?
YOU GOT THAT
GODDAMN RIGHT,
IF I AIN'T DRAGGED
SCREAMING TO BELLEVUE FIRST.
I MEAN,
AM I CRAZY OR WHAT?
AND WHO IS THIS KID
I'M BAILING OUT OF
THE SLAMMER
FOR GETTING HIS
GODDAMN ASS CAUGHT
WHERE IT AIN'T WANTED
OR PAID FOR, EXCUSE ME?
I'M MATTY DEAN.
MATTY DEAN?
A GODDAMN HILLBILLY.
BOSTONIA--
YOU DO NOT SPEAK
OR I WILL SLAP YOU
UPSIDE YOUR HEAD.
KID, I WAS THERE
AND I SAW WHAT YOU DID.
NOW YOU MAY  THINK
THAT IT LOOKS SORT OF
COOL, HUH?
YEAH, MAYBE EVEN
FELT
KINDA COOL  IN SOME FREAKY WAY.
IT IS NOT COOL TO GIVE
THOSE MOTHERFUCKERS
ANY KIND OF EXCUSE
TO PUT THEIR HANDS ON YOU.
IF WE BLEED, WE DO NOT WIN.
Y'ALL DIG?
WELL, MAYBE IT'S
THEIR TURN TO BLEED.
WAKE-UP CALL.
IF YOU GIVE THEM CAUSE
TO MESS WITH YOU AGAIN,
I'LL KICK YOUR ASSES MYSELF,
IS THAT CLEAR?
GODDAMN IT.
YOU KIDS ARE GONNA BREAK
MY GODDAMN HEART.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
HE KIND OF LIKED ME.
MATTY DEAN, DO THEY GOT
DRAGS WHERE YOU COME FROM?
NATURALLY.
THEN YOU KNOW
IT AIN'T HIP
TO CALL A D.Q. "HE."
OH, DID I CALL
HIM "HIM?" OR "HE?"
"SHE?"
IS YOUR FAMILY RICH?
WHAT'S MY FAMILY
GOT TO DO WITH ME?
I'M JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW SOMEBODY SO SMART
CAN BE SO STUPID?
WELL, I AIN'T GOT
NO BUDDY IN A STRETCH LIMO.
THAT AIN'T HERS.
BOSTONIA'S GOT
SOME RICH JOHN
WHO TAKES CARE OF HER.
SO, WHICH ARE YOU,
A HE OR A SHE?
DEPENDS ON
WHO'S PAYING, BABE.
Matty: THAT'S A DRAFT
NOTICE, RIGHT?
YEP.
UNFORTUNATE FOR THEM,
I HAVE FLAT FEET.
WELCOME TO
TEENY BOP HEAVEN.
I'LL MAKE YOU UP
A BED.
Matty:
MINE WAS THIS KID,
WHEN I WAS A KID MYSELF.
HE USED TO COME AROUND
WITH HIS DAD TO,
YOU KNOW,
PAINT THE FENCE,
AND STUFF.
I USED TO WATCH HIM
FROM MY WINDOW,
MOWING THE LAWN
WITH HIS SHIRT OFF.
DID YOU EVER TELL HIM
HOW YOU FELT?
WELL, HE ALWAYS
USED TO COME OVER
WITH HIS POP.
THEN ONE TIME
HE CAME ALONE,
AND WE CAME TOGETHER.
BUT I NEVER
TOLD HIM, NO.
WHO WAS YOUR FIRST?
FIRST LAY?
FIRST LOVE.
I DON'T DO LOVE.
AIN'T NO
PERCENTAGE IN IT.
LaMIRANDA,
WHAT DO YOUR FAMILY
THINK OF YOU?
THEY DRINK
TO FORGET ME.
YOURS?
WELL, WHEN I FIRST
TOLD THEM THAT I WAS
A HOMOSEXUAL--
WAIT. WHEN YOU
WHAT?
THEY DIDN'T
BELIEVE ME.
YOU DID NOT.
I DID.
FUCK YOU.
YOU DID NOT!
I WAS 15.
GET OUT OF TOWN.
DIDN'T I SAY YOU WAS RICH?
YOU DID, YEAH.
MARY,
PLEASE.
YOU TELL POOR FOLKS,
"MOMMY, I'M A HOMOSEXUAL,"
AND THEY WILL DRAG YOUR ASS
OUT INTO THE DAMN YARD
AND WHIP YOU WITH
A CAR AERIAL, O.K.?
IS THAT WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU?
WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT ME.
YOU WANT SOME BREAKFAST?
OH, CHRIST.
I SHOULD GET
OUT OF HERE
AND LET YOU
GET SOME SLEEP.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I HAVE TO GO
TO A MEETING.
A.A.?
WELL, NO.
UM...O.K.
I'M GOING
TO A MEETING OF
THE HOMOPHILE SOCIETY,
A GROUP OF
HOMOSEXUAL MEN
WORKING FOR LIBERATION
ACCEPTANCE,
AND INTEGRATION.
YOU TRAVELED
ACROSS AMERICA
TO HAND OUT FLYERS,
THEN YOU TALK TO ME
LIKE I'M DUMB?
LET'S EAT.
LISTEN, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GO.
YOU CAN STAY HERE
AS LONG AS YOU NEED TO.
I KNOW I NEVER
SAID THANK YOU.
I'M LOUSY AT THIS SHIT.
Man: A STEINWAY
IS LIKE A FERRARI.
YOU JUST DON'T LET
ANY SCHMUCK
IN THE DRIVING SEAT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD
HAVE CALLED ME,
ARNIE.
I'M NOT A PRIEST.
YOU CAN TALK TO ME
BEFORE
YOU SCREW UP.
O.K. YEAH.
I'M CALM NOW.
AFTER I HANG UP,
I'M GONNA GO CHANT
OR SOMETHING.
HOW'S THAT?
[HANGS UP
TELEPHONE]
MOVING ON,
WE'RE HERE TODAY
TO CONFIRM DETAILS
WITH THE DAUGHTERS
OF BILITIS
REPRESENTED TODAY
BY AGNES PUGIN
AS TO THE PRECISE
NATURE OF OUR MARCH
ON INDEPENDENCE HALL
IN PHILADELPHIA,
AGREEMENT ON CODES
OF CONDUCT,
ETCETERA, ETCETERA.
WELL, NATURALLY
THE IDEA WOULD BE
TO TAKE A CACHE
OF MORTAR SHELLS
AND LEVEL THE PLACE.
HOWEVER, SINCE WE ARE
A PEACEFUL, POLITICAL
LOBBY GROUP
AND NOT THE BLACK
PANTHERS,
WE'LL FORGO
YOUR MORTAR SHELLS.
THE PANTHERS
NEVER BOMBED
ANYONE, BURT,
THOUGH GOD KNOWS
WHO'D BLAME THEM.
Burt:
MOVING ON, O.K.
DRESS SENSE.
AGNES HAS CONFIRMED
THAT THE DAUGHTERS
OF BILITIS
ARE IN COMPLETE ACCORD
WITH OUR DECISION
THAT EVERYONE SHOULD
DRESS AS SENSIBLY
AND AS FORMALLY
AS POSSIBLE.
TUXES, PROM DRESSES...
Burt: ETHAN!
SUITS. TIES.
NO PATTERNS, PLEASE.
DARK SOCKS, POLISHED SHOES,
NEAT HAIR CUTS,
NO DENIM, NO CHINOS.
IF YOU'VE GOT GLASSES,
PLEASE WEAR THEM.
EXCUSE ME. HAIRCUTS?
YOU COULD WEAR A HAT
AND TUCK YOUR HAIR INTO IT,
BUT NEAT HAIR
WOULD BE IDEAL,
AND, I MIGHT ADD,
POSSIBLY QUITE BECOMING.
Agnes: LISTEN, PEOPLE.
THIS DRESS CODE THING,
IT'S REALLY A DRAG,
I KNOW.
BUT THIS IS THE FIRST
CIVIL ACTION OF ITS KIND
AND IT'S VITAL THAT
WE MAKE A GOOD
IMPRESSION.
DO YOU SEE?
Burt: UH, MOVING ON.
FOR THE LADIES...
THE WOMEN.
SKIRTS. BLOUSES...
Bostonia: VITO!
OH, NEW COLOGNE?
Man: 400...
500--
STOP ME IF
I'M BORING YOU--
700, 750,
A COZY GRAND.
STASH IT.
WE GOT COMPANY.
A LADY
IN THE HOUSE.
DON'T MIND ME, BOYS.
SO WHAT YOU'RE
TELLING ME
IS I PAY YOU
TO BUST ME LESS,
YOU BUST ME MORE.
I PAY YOU FOR WARNINGS,
I GET JACK SHIT.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO MAKE
MONEY TO PAY YOU,
BUILD A MINT IN MY ASS
AND SHIT DOLLAR BILLS?
Man on phone:
THIS IS A ROUTINE
SHAKE-DOWN.
WHAT THE FUCK
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
LISTEN, I GOT A COUSIN
WHO RUNS A FAG BAR
IN THE EAST VILLAGE.
THE PRECINCT THERE
IS SO FRIGGIN' ORGANIZED,
THEY GOT A BUST ROTA.
NOW THAT'S
BUSINESS.
LAST NIGHT,
I GOT 2 NELLIES IN STIR
AND AN EMPTY BAR
BY 1:30.
THAT IS NOT BUSINESS.
I'LL TALK TO THE CHIEF.
HOW'S THAT?
YEAH. YOU DO THAT,
AND YOU ASK HIM
ARE WE IN BUSINESS
OR AM I PAYING THE WRONG
PRECINCT, ALL RIGHT?
TAKE A PILL! JEEZ.
WHAT?
WHAT? WHAT KIND
OF FACE IS THAT,
HUH?
CRYPTICA?
I'M WARNING YOU,
BOSTONIA.
YOU KEEP YOUR FOOT
OFF MY DICK.
I'M ON THE PHONE
CHEWING OUT
THE DEPUTY CHIEF
OF FRIGGIN' POLICE,
FOR CHRISSAKES.
BLOW IT OUT YOUR ASS,
YOU GODDAMN LOSER.
IF YOU'RE SO HOT,
WHY ARE YOU TALKING TO
THE FUCKING DEPUTY?
I DO NOT LIKE
TO SEE MY KIDS
BLEEDIN' ON THE FLOOR
OF NO PADDYWAGON, O.K.?
COME ON, YOUR KIDS?
THAT DAFFY LITTLE
HEIFER WAS ASKING
TO GET ROUGHED UP.
SHE GETS OFF
ON MAKING WAVES.
YOU KNOW THAT.
AH, THE HELL
WITH THEM ALL.
COULDN'T WE JUST
GET A-GODDAMN-WAY
FROM THIS
TIRED TOWN?
SOMEPLACE WHERE
NOBODY KNOWS US?
HONEY, NOBODY
KNOWS US HERE.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT--YEAH.
AND YOU KEEP IT
THAT WAY.
YOU GET OFF ME
BEFORE SOME SUCKER
COMES IN HERE
AND SEES US.
VINNIE, YOU ARE SUCH
A ROMANTIC.
YEAH! CATCH YA!
ANGELO!
BOSS?
ANY OTHER SAD FREAK
WALKS PAST YOU
INTO MY OFFICE
WITHOUT SO MUCH AS EVEN
A KNOCK ON MY DOOR,
I'M GONNA BREAK YOUR
FUCKIN' FEATHERS FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
YOU HAVE TO TRY
AND UNDERSTAND BURT.
HE'S NOT THE HIPPEST
GUY ON THE BLOCK
BUT HE HAS A GREAT BRAIN,
GREAT CONNECTIONS,
AND A GREAT DEAL OF MONEY,
ALL OF WHICH
HE CONTRIBUTES
GENEROUSLY...
OH! IT'S CASH
THAT COUNTS, RIGHT?
HEY, YOU'RE ONLY HEARING
WHAT YOU WANT TO HEAR.
BURT'S GIVEN A GREAT
DEAL OF HIMSELF
TO FURTHERING THIS CAUSE.
HE'S JUST KIND OF
OUT OF ANOTHER TIME.
IT'S JUST THAT
I DIDN'T COME
ACROSS AMERICA
TO HAND OUT FLYERS
IN A SUIT, YOU KNOW?
WHAT
DID
YOU COME HERE FOR?
I KNOW. I CAME HERE
AS A FRESHMAN AT COLUMBIA,
AND I WAS GONNA KICK
THE WORLD'S ASS.
WHEN YOU'RE 19,
FINDING SOMETHING
TO FIGHT FOR
CAN BE KIND OF A THRILL.
I'M GLAD SOMEBODY'S
GETTING A KICK
OUT OF IT.
I'M NOT 19 ANYMORE.
I SPENT ALMOST 10 YEARS
TEACHING BROOKLYN KIDS
ABOUT WALT WHITMAN
AND SHAKESPEARE,
NEVER MENTIONING
WHAT REALLY
MATTERED TO ME
OR I'M OUT OF THERE.
I'VE SEEN THEM
COME AND GO,
AND THE ONES WHO SURVIVE
ARE THE ONES
WHO LEARN HOW
TO WORK IT FROM INSIDE.
SEE, I'M NOT IN THIS
FOR THE FIGHT ANYMORE.
I'M IN THIS TO WIN.
LISTEN, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING RIGHT NOW?
OH, NOTHING.
I'M GOTTA MEET
SOMEBODY LATER,
MUCH LATER,
BUT I'M FREE
RIGHT NOW FOR NOW.
YOU WANNA WALK?
I'LL SHOW YOU NEW YORK.
SO HOW LATE IS HE
NOW?
ABOUT 30 SECONDS
LATER THAN THE LAST
TIME YOU ASKED ME.
DON'T PISS ME OFF,
GIRLFRIEND.
OOH, BOY!
THIS STUD MUST
BE SOMETHING
FOR MISS
LaMIRANDA THING
TO SIT WAITING
ON HER HIND LEGS
THIS WAY.
THERE MUST BE
SOME SERIOUS
DISH HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING?
PARDONNEZ MOI?
DOES HE KISS?
IS HE HUNG LIKE
AN OX OR A CHIPMUNK?
IS HE A BULL-DAGGER
IN MAN DRAG? COME ON!
I THINK MAYBE
HE'S A COMMUNIST.
MMM! AND SO CUTE?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S KINDA FREAKY,
YOU KNOW?
HE THINK MAYBE
HE DROPPED OUT OF
COLLEGE OR SOMETHING
TO SLUM IT
WITH THE STREET TRASH.
BUT WE NEVER REALLY
DID NOTHING YET.
GOD, YOU ARE SAD!
WELL, WE ALMOST
KISSED THIS MORNING.
AND HE WAS, YOU KNOW,
SCARY, BUT NICE.
AND LAST NIGHT
WE JUST TALKED
ALL NIGHT,
AND HE HELPED ME
COOK BREAKFAST.
ALL NIGHT? NO SEX?
NO WONDER YOU LOOK
LIKE SHIT.
OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT HIM
OVER THERE?
MATTY DEAN.
MATTY DEAN!
YOU'RE LATE!
THAT'S O.K.
GOOD MEETING?
KINDA WEIRD.
WOW. YOUR EYELASHES
ARE REALLY BIG.
EXCUSE ME!
MATTY DEAN,
I WANT YOU TO MEET
MY BEST GIRLFRIENDS.
THIS IS MISS MOXIE.
KISSY, KISSY.
AND THIS IS
HELEN WHEELS.
OH!
HI.
EVENIN'...
LADIES.
TAXI!
[ALL TALKING EXCITEDLY]
COME ON.
I ALWAYS DO THIS.
I GOT IT.
I'M THE BELLHOP
HERE.
UP OR DOWN,
PROSTITUTES?
O.K. UP WE GO.
FIRST FLOOR,
LINGERIE.
[RINGING BELLS]
[DING DING
DING DING]
TONIGHT,
MY BEAUTIFUL SISTERS,
WE KISS GOODBYE
LITTLE JOSE,
FOR TONIGHT,
LITTLE JOSE DIES.
GOODBYE, LITTLE JOSE.
AND NOW,
THIS LITTLE BODY
HOLDS THE SOUL
OF CAMELLIA.
AND RELEASE HER
WITH A KISS.
WELCOME INTO
THE LIFE, BABY.
YOU REMEMBER, CHILD,
IT'S GOING TO BE
A HARD LIFE...
BUT, OH, CAMELLIA,
WHAT RICHES
IT WILL SHOW YOU.
EMBRACE IT ALL,
SWEETNESS,
AND LET IT
EMBRACE YOU.
...YEARS OF
RIGOROUS TRAINING
AND WAITING.
WHO WILL BE CHOSEN?
WHO WILL GO?
BUT NOW THE WAIT
IS FINALLY OVER.
THE MOMENT OF
AMERICA'S DATE WITH
DESTINY HAS COME.
THE NATION RISES
TO MEET THE CHALLENGE
POSED BY
PRESIDENT KENNEDY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M LOOKIN' AT YOU.
[LAUGHS] OH, GOD!
HEY.
DON'T HIDE
FROM ME.
THE NEXT STOP
FOR AMERICA...THE MOON.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'D LIKE?
I'D LIKE TO
SEE YOU NAKED.
BABY, YOU AIN'T
READY FOR THAT.
NO WAY.
I'M READY.
I NEED TO SEE YOU.
DARE ME?
I WILL IF YOU WILL.
WOW.
HA. YOU KNOW ME.
SUCH A TOMBOY.
DON'T WORRY, BABY.
IF KINSEY CALLS,
YOU'RE THE BUTCH ONE.
I DON'T MIND IT.
I LIKE IT.
I LIKE TO LOOK
AT YOU.
DO YOU LIKE TO
LOOK AT ME?
WHAT ARE YOU,
SOME KINDA FAG?
I'M GETTIN'
A TESTOSTERONE RUSH.
I FEEL THE NEED
TO COMPETE.
OH, NO!
DON'T WASTE THAT!
GET SOMEONE UNDER
THERE!
COME HERE.
YOU COME HERE.
IS THAT THE WAY
YOU GOT NAMED?
EXACTLY THAT WAY.
EXCEPT I CRIED
A LOT MORE.
THAT WAS THE LAST
TIME I EVER CRIED.
WHAT WAS YOUR NAME
BEFORE?
I FORGET.
HECTOR.
MORE MANLY, RIGHT?
LaMIRANDA'S NICE.
I-IT'S YOU.
IT ALL MAKES ME
FEEL KINDA NOT...
NOT COMPLETE.
OH, BABY.
ONE THING YOU AIN'T
IS INCOMPLETE.
YOU WANNA JOIN
THE LIFE?
I WANNA JOIN YOU.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD?
HOW YOU DOING?
O.K.
[TYPING]
YOU'RE PROWLING, MATT.
SORRY.
UH-UH.
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN WORK
WITH YOU STANDING
THIS CLOSE.
I'M READING
THIS LETTER.
"DEAR BRUCE COMPTON,
"I READ YOUR
BEAUTIFUL ARTICLE
ON THE BROTHERHOOD
"OVER AND OVER AND OVER.
"YOUR WORDS
GO AROUND MY HEAD
"LIKE A SONG.
"I WANNA SHOUT THEM
OUT IN SCHOOL.
"HERE SO FAR
FROM NEW YORK,
"AND A MILLION MILES
FROM ANYTHING REAL,
"I CAN DREAM OF SOMEONE
TO STAND BESIDE ME
TO FIGHT TOGETHER
FOR LOVE."
BRUCE COMPTON?
HOW COME YOU DIDN'T
USE YOUR REAL NAME?
I SHOULD HAVE.
I WONDER WHAT
HIS REAL NAME WAS.
AH...
WHAT'S A REAL NAME,
ANYHOW?
COULD HAVE BEEN
ANYONE.
COULD HAVE BEEN...
ME.
COULD IT, MATT?
MATTY DEAN'S
NOT YOUR REAL NAME.
IT IS TO ME.
WHY WOULD YOU CHOOSE
MATTY DEAN?
SUCH A HICK NAME.
I GUESS I NEVER
REALLY WANTED
A CLASSY LIFE.
YOU CAME TO
THE RIGHT TOWN.
HOW'D YOU GET AHOLD
OF OUR MAGAZINE
OUT THERE?
MY FIRST COPY...
A FRIEND...
OF A FRIEND
OF A FRIEND.
YOU KNOW.
IT'S THE OLDEST STORY.
HOW DOES
THE STORY END?
IT'S JUST BEGINNING.
OOH-AH, OOH-AH,
COME ON, KITTY
OH, YEAH
TELL US ABOUT THE BOY
FROM NEW YORK CITY
[LIP-SYNCHING]
HE CAN DANCE
AND MAKE ROMANCE
YEAH, YEAH
THAT'S WHEN
I FELL IN LOVE
WITH JUST ONE GLANCE
YEAH, YEAH
HE WAS SHY
AND SO WAS I
AND NOW I KNOW
WE'LL NEVER, EVER
SAY GOODBYE
YEAH, YEAH
OOH, OOH, OOH-EEE
YOU OUGHT TO
COME AND SEE
HE'S THE MOST
YEAH, YEAH
FROM COAST TO COAST
OOH-AH, OOH-AH,
OOH, OOH KITTY
OH, YEAH
TELL US ABOUT THE BOY
FROM NEW YORK CITY
PSST!
OH, MY GOD!
Woman: I LOVE
THOSE SHOES.
[TITTERING]
WEAPONS DOWN, MEN.
AT EASE.
HEY, BROS, FROS,
AND SISTERS WITH SOUL.
I'M READY FOR ACTION.
WHERE DO I SIGN?
LADIES TO THE LEFT.
OH, I AIN'T NO LADY,
MR. SIR. I'M SORRY.
SEE, THAT'S WHY I WALKED
THE MIDDLE OF THE ROOM.
STORY OF MY DAMNED LIFE.
OH.
I HAVE THIS LITTLE OLD
INDUCTION NOTICE HERE.
HECTOR DUARTE?
WELL...KIND OF.
SEE, I HAD MY NAME
LEGALLY CHANGED.
LaMIRANDA QUERIDES.
REPORTING FOR DUTY, SIR!
[LAUGHTER]
ARE WE TO UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE SOME KIND OF
INVERT?
SHY? ME?
OH, MARY!
ARE YOU
A HOMOSEXUAL?
OH!
SURE.
LEAST SO MY BOYFRIEND
TELLS ME.
WE WAS KINDA HOPING
WE COULD ENLIST
AT THE SAME TIME
AND BE POSTED
TO THE SAME CREW.
SHUT UP.
SO SORRY,
I'M SURE.
ROOM 17.
DEFINITELY.
ROOM 17,
AROUND THE SIDE
OF THE BUILDING.
ENTRANCE
IN THE BACK.
ROOM 17.
FOR PSYCHOLOGICAL
EVALUATION.
OH! MY FAVORITE.
SO YOU CRUISE
THROUGH THIS
IN 10 MINUTES, TOPS.
O.K.? YOU'LL BE
HOME IN TIME FOR
THE DOTTIE SHOW.
YEAH, WELL,
I NEVER WAS NO GOOD
AT CRUISING.
LaMIRANDA...
ARE YOU SCARED?
I SEEN A SHRINK,
O.K.?
THEY MADE ME SEE ONE
IN JUVENILE HALL
WHEN I WAS 11.
THEY WANTED
TO GIVE ME THAT
ELECTRONIC TREATMENT,
YOU KNOW, WHEN THEY SHOW
THE PICTURES OF OILY BOYS,
AND THEN THEY ZAP YOU?
AVERSION THERAPY?
FOR WHAT?
FOR STAYING OUT LATE
ON A SCHOOL NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHIT, MATTY DEAN.
COME ON.
YOU'RE WITH ME, NOW.
I WON'T LET THEM
HURT YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT?
WHAT DO I KNOW
ABOUT ANYTHING?
HECTOR JULIO DUARTE.
HECTOR...
LaMIRANDA, DOCTOR.
LaMIRANDA QUERIDES.
BUT, UH, YOU WEREN'T
BORN LaMIRANDA,
WERE YOU, HECTOR?
YOU WEREN'T
BORN A DOCTOR,
BUT YOU QUALIFIED.
AND YOU'RE NOW WHAT,
A MAN
OR A WOMAN?
OH HO HO, DOCTOR.
HOW FIFTIES YOU BE.
ME, I'M LIVING
IN THE OTHER STATE
BETWEEN MALENESS
AND FEMALENESS.
WHICH IS?
FABULOUSNESS.
HECTOR...
DO YOU
WANT TO FIGHT
FOR YOUR COUNTRY?
OH, I WANNA FIGHT,
DOC.
I WANNA FIGHT FOR LOVE...
LIBERTY,
AND THE CONSTITUTION.
I WANNA FIGHT THE KONG,
THE RUSKIES,
YOU, YOUR MOM,
YOUR POP,
AND THE WHOLE HOUSE
OF FUCKING UN-AMERICAN
ACTIVITIES.
I WANNA KICK
THE WORLD'S ASS,
AND I DON'T NEED YOU
TO LET ME!
YOU'RE FORCING ME!
WHAT?
GUESS IT'S MY TURN
TO LOOK AT YOU.
I'M SCARED, MATTY.
I AIN'T NEVER HAD
NO HERO BEFORE.
I NEVER KISSED
NO ONE BEFORE
OR MADE LOVE.
[HISPANIC ACCENT]
BUT YOU AIN'T
NEVER BEEN
LOVED LIKE THIS
BEFORE, BABY.
YOU LOVE ME?
NOW IT'S ME
WHO'S SCARED.
WHEN I SAY I'M IN LOVE,
YOU BEST BELIEVE
I'M IN LOVE, L-U-V!
HERE COMES MY GUY
WALKIN' DOWN THE STREET
LOOK HOW HE WALKS
WITH A DANCIN' BEAT
DA DA DA DA DA
THICK, WAVY HAIR
A LITTLE TOO LONG
ALL DAY LONG HE'S
SINGIN' A SONG
AND WHEN I SEE HIM
IN THE STREET
MY HEART TAKES A LEAP...
MARCH ON PHILADELPHIA?
GONNA WALK RIGHT UP
TO HIM
MARCH ON PHILADELPHIA?
GIVE HIM
A GREAT BIG KISS, MUAH!
TELL HIM THAT I LOVE HIM,
TELL HIM THAT I CARE
TELL HIM THAT
I'LL ALWAYS BE THERE
WHAT COLOR
ARE HIS EYES?
I DUNNO, HE'S ALWAYS
WEARING SHADES
IS HE TALL?
WELL,
I GOTTA LOOK UP
YEAH? WELL, I HEAR
HE'S BAD
HMM. HE'S GOOD-BAD,
BUT HE'S NOT EVIL
TELL ME MORE
BIG BULKY SWEATERS
TO MATCH HIS EYES
TELL ME MORE
DIRTY FINGERNAILS
OH, BOY WHAT A PRIZE
TIGHT TAPERED PANTS
AH, AH, AH
HIGH BUTTON SHOES
HE'S ALWAYS LOOKIN'
LIKE-A HE'S GOT
THE BLUES
AND WHEN I SEE HIM
IN THE STREET
MY HEART TAKES A LEAP
AND SKIPS A BEAT
GONNA WALK
RIGHT UP TO HIM
GIVE HIM
A GREAT BIG KISS, MUAH!
AND TELL HIM THAT I LOVE HIM,
TELL HIM THAT I CARE
TELL HIM THAT I'LL
ALWAYS BE THERE
IS HE
A GOOD DANCER?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
IS HE A GOOD DANCER?
WELL, HOW
DOES HE DANCE?
CLOSE
VERY, VERY CLOSE
OOH, OOH, OOH, OOH
LOOK AT MISS PIGLET
IN HER MUD BATH.
WHEN WAS THE
LAST TIME YOU TOOK
A BATH, GIRL?
HEY, I DON'T HAVE TO
ANSWER THAT QUESTION.
OH, GIRL, BE STILL
AND STOP SWITCHING
BEFORE I MISS THE LAST
FEW STRANDS OF HAIRS
YOU STILL GOT UP HERE.
WELL, AT LEAST
SOME OF IT IS STILL
MY OWN DAMN HAIR.
[STRUMMING GUITAR]
UH-OH. IS THIS
FUZZY FELT HERE
SOME SOURCE OF PRIDE
TO THIS SICK, SEEDY,
MESSY QUEEN
I'M DEALING WITH
OVER HERE?
WOULD YOU SHUT
THE HELL UP?
MY MAN IS TRYING TO
CALL UPON HIS MUSE,
DAMN IT!
[GASPS]
[SINGING]
MMM!
WHEN WE GROWS
WITH THE BLUE
MINE EYES HAVE SEEN
THE COMIN' OF
MMM-MM!
THE NEGROES AND THE JEWS
I HAVE SEEN
THE COUNTRIES TRAMPLED
DID HE JUST SAY NEGROES?
WHERE THE LAWS OF MAN
ABUSE
UH-HUH!
BUT YOU CRUSH
THE HOMOSEXUAL
Moxie: LaMIRANDA...
GIRL,
COME GET HIM.
LaMIRANDA,
PLEASE HAVE HIM STOP.
Helen:
YES, PLEASE.
...GO MARCHIN' ON--
NOW?
UH, BABY?
IT SUCKS, DON'T IT?
Moxie: MM-HMM!
SUCKS? TCH!
CHICKIE, HOW COULD
ANYTHING ABOUT YOU SUCK?
Moxie: WELL...
IT JUST SOUNDS
A LITTLE...
LITERARY.
LITERAL.
LITERAL...ISTIC.
YOU DIG?
YOU THINK IT'S
TOO LITERAL?
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
I SAID, AIN'T IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHATEVER.
IT'S TOO...
IT'S TOO GOD DAMNED
PREACHY, YOU KNOW?
IT'S A LITTLE
WHITE-BREAD, ALSO.
WHITE BOY.
YEAH!
BUT IT'S FABULOUS
OTHERWISE.
PERMISSION
TO PUKE, MA'AM.
SHUT UP, BITCH.
I AIN'T THE ONE
THAT'S COMING ON
LIKE BOBBY DYLAN
IN A COMA, NOW AM I?
THE FEMALES BY NATURE
DO NOT HAVE THE SAME
SEXUAL DRIVES AS MALES.
AND THEREFORE,
MEN WHO SUFFER
FROM AN ABNORMAL
SEXUAL COMPULSION
ARE FORCED TO TURN
TO OTHERS
WHO HAVE THE SAME
UNCONTROLLABLE NEED
TO SATISFY THEIR
UNNATURAL DESIRES.
THEY TURN TO OTHER MEN,
OTHER HOMOSEXUALS.
AND NOW THIS, OF COURSE,
FINDS THE SEED FALLING
ON BARREN SOIL,
WHICH LEADS TO
MORE FRUSTRATION AND
INCREASING COMPULSION
LIKE THE DOPE ADDICT.
UNLIKE DRUG ADDICTION,
HOWEVER,
NONE OF THIS CAN BE
BLAMED ON THE INDIVIDUAL.
HOMOSEXUALITY IS AN ILLNESS,
A CONDITION--
UH...SPARKED BY THE
CHEMICAL IMBALANCE
IN THE BRAIN.
ON THE FACE OF
THIS EVIDENCE,
FAULTY FAMILY
CONFIGURATIONS
ARE NOT GROUNDS FOR
DENYING ANY AMERICAN CITIZEN
THEIR BASIC
CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS.
I...
I THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
ANY QUESTIONS?
YOU'RE NOT TALKING, MATTY.
OH, I WAS JUST
WONDERING.
WHY ARE WE HEADING
INTO GREENWICH
VILLAGE
TO MEET THE PRESS
WHEN WE SHOULD BE
CHECKING INTO
THE PSYCHO WARD
TO HAVE OUR EXCESS
OF SPERM DEPOSITS
SIPHONED OFF?
IT'S JUST AN OPINION,
MATTY.
HITLER AND THE BOYS
HAD AN OPINION,
BURT.
NOW WAIT. THE FACT IS
THAT THE IDEA OF SICKNESS
IS A CONCEPT
THAT AMERICA CAN DEAL WITH.
AND AT THIS STAGE,
QUITE FRANKLY,
SYMPATHY WOULD BE
A HUGE STEP FOR US.
YOU MEAN PITY.
ANY WORD THAT MEANS
NOT HATE IS A STEP,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I CAN'T THINK.
COULDN'T YOU TRY THINKING?
UH...
YOU DONE?
NO.
NOW I'M DONE.
O.K. WE CAN FIGHT
ALL WE WANT BETWEEN US,
BUT THIS MEETING IS WITH
OUR ONLY ALLY IN THE PRESS.
WE NEED TO PRESENT
A UNITED FRONT.
ISN'T THAT REASONABLE?
BUT NATURALLY, BURT.
WE'RE ALWAYS
REASONABLE.
YOU'LL TELL THEM
I'M HERE RIGHT?
I'M GOING TO TELL
EVERYONE. RELAX.
WE'LL HAVE
A COUPLE OF DRINKS?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A LOT OF DRINKS.
HOWEVER, I CAN'T...
RANDOLPH ERZERSKY?
YES, YES! HI. HI!
GLAD TO MEET YOU.
YES. BURT?
PLEASE CALL ME
RANDY.
THIS IS THE
VILLAGE VOICE
REPORTER, RANDY.
UM, ETHAN,
MATTY DEAN
HI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
MATTY DEAN. GREAT.
OH, RAOUL.
LISTEN, I BROUGHT ALONG
A PHOTOGRAPHER WITH ME.
WOULD YOU GUYS
BE WILLING TO POSE
FOR SOME SHOTS?
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM
FOR US.
RIGHT?
OH. GOOD. GREAT.
I'M GOING TO START
THE FIRST SHOT
RIGHT OVER HERE.
STAY RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE. GREAT.
O.K. THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
GOOD. O.K.
SMILING A LITTLE?
GOOD.
YEAH. KEEP THAT HAND
DOWN. THANKS.
A LITTLE TO
THE LEFT, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT.
I LIKE IT.
GOOD.
SHADES, ETHAN?
JUST INJECTING
A LITTLE STYLE.
THAT'S GREAT.
SO THE PLAN HERE
IS WHAT?
UH, WE...SIT DOWN...
WE ANNOUNCE OURSELVES
AS HOMOSEXUALS,
THEN WE ORDER DRINKS...
AT WHICH POINT
THEY ARE COMPELLED
TO REFUSE US.
AS DICTATED BY?
BY OUR FASCIST
AND UNAMERICAN
STATE LAWS.
THEN WE FLAMETHROW
THE PLACE.
HE'S A REAL KIDDER.
MATTY.
YOU KNOW
HOW IT IS, BURT.
CHEMICAL IMBALANCE.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU
GUYS?
WE ARE A GROUP
OF HOMOSEXUALS,
AND WE WOULD LIKE
TO ORDER A BEER
EACH.
IT'S TEQUILA
FOR ME, BURT.
O.K., SO THAT'S, UH,
BEERS AND TEQUILA,
RIGHT?
FOR THIS GROUP OF
HOMOSEXUALS.
YES.
RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
UM...HOW ABOUT
HIM?
TEQUILA, PLEASE.
LIME. A LITTLE SALT.
O.K. THANKS.
THAT'S HOW MANY BEERS
AND HOW MANY HOMOSEXUALS?
WELL, IT'S 3 ACTUAL
AND 2 HONORARY
HOMOSEXUALS,
INCLUDING A QUITE
YOUNG HOMOSEXUAL,
AND WE'RE DRINKING
4 BEERS AND A TEQUILA.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
MAKE THAT 2 TEQUILAS.
ACTUAL TEQUILA
OR HONORARY TEQUILA?
MIGHT WE SEE
YOUR MANAGER?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
[LAUGHS] HOMOSEXUALS?
HOW DO I KNOW
IF YOU'RE HOMOSEXUALS?
SEEM PRETTY
NORMAL TO ME.
KINDA SUPERNORMAL,
AS A MATTER OF FACT.
THESE DAYS,
WHO CAN TELL?
EVEN I COULD BE A HOMO,
FOR CHRIST'S SAKES.
AND FAG MONEY
IS STILL MONEY.
GET THESE BOYS
A DRINK.
ON THE HOUSE, FELLAS.
DRINKS ARE ON ME,
FELLAS.
WELL, SEE IF YOU CAN TELL
IF THEY'RE HOMO DRINKS
OR HETERO DRINKS.
I CAN'T DO THIS
MUCH LONGER.
I JUST DON'T HAVE
THE CONSTITUTION.
IN FRONT OF THE PRESS,
SUDDENLY EVERYBODY'S
A LIBERAL.
MAYBE YOU GUYS
ARE BEHIND THE TIMES.
NO. IT IS
A STATE LAW.
THERE'S ONE PLACE
WE CAN GUARANTEE
SELF-CONFESSED
FAGGOTS WILL NOT
BE SERVED.
A FAGGOT BAR.
FOLLOW ME, GUYS.
FAGGOT BAR?
I LIKE THAT.
HEY, VITO.
WHAT'S UP?
HI.
GOOD EVENING.
HI. WE'RE A COUPLE.
[GIGGLING]
HI, VITO!
MATTY, YOU LITTLE
SHOW-STOPPER.
MY PRETTY PATOOTIE.
HOW'S THE CLASSY
CHASSIS?
IN NEED OF
A LITTLE SERVICING,
TENDERBOX.
OH, YOU TEASE.
WHAT LANGUAGE IS THIS?
I FEEL LIKE A WETBACK
IN MY OWN NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU ARE.
BURT.
BURT?
YEAH.
OH.
HI.
WE'RE A HOMOSEXUAL GROUP
OF SELF-CONFESSED
HOMOSEXUALS--
HEY, VITO!
GOD DAMN
TROUBLE-MAKERS.
VITO, GIRL,
WHERE ARE YOU?
HEY, PRINCESS,
BE COOL.
YOU JUST HAVE TO
REFUSE.
I DONE THAT, SWEETIE.
NOW GET THESE LOSERS
OUT. VITO!
VITO, YOU HEAR ME?
THROW THESE FOOLS
OUTTA HERE!
HEY, CHUMP,
TAKE A HIKE!
HEY!
HEY, PUNK!
VITO!
COOL IT, BABY.
NOW ISN'T THAT
NICER, PEOPLE?
YOU KIDS
WANT A DRINK?
ACTUALLY, UH...NO.
EXCUSE ME?
WE WANNA BE
REFUSED, BO.
IT'S A POLITICAL
STATEMENT.
WATCH YOUR
GODDAMN MOUTH!
NOW YOU KNOW VINNIE
DON'T ALLOW THAT SHIT
IN HERE, BO.
CHILD, WHAT DID I
TELL YOU ABOUT MESSING
WITH THAT STUFF?
WE JUST WANT
AN OFFICIAL REFUSAL,
THEN WE'LL BE DONE,
O.K.?
FOR CRYING
OUT LOUD.
PRINCESS.
I DONE REFUSED
TWICE ALREADY,
GODDAMN IT.
REFUSE AGAIN.
OFFICIAL-LIKE.
THE STATE LIQUOR
AUTHORITY
PROHIBITS THE
SELLING OF LIQUOR
TO HOMOSEXUALS.
THEREFORE, I REGRET
WE MUST REFUSE
TO SERVE YOU.
HAPPY, EVERYBODY?
YOU OWE ME A DANCE.
OH, I...
IT'S ALLOWED HERE,
SWEETNESS.
Ernestine: IT'S ALLOWED
HERE, SWEETNESS!
I WOULD BE DELIGHTED.
DON'T STEP ON
HER BLUE SUEDE SHOES.
WELL, I THINK WE GOT
OUR STORY.
LET'S GET THE HELL
OUTTA HERE.
IS THIS A
PRIVATE REVOLUTION,
OR CAN ANYONE JOIN?
HI, BABY.
SO, HOW'S LIFE
ON THE FRONT LINE?
AW...YOU KNOW.
HA HA HA.
OH, LaMIRANDA,
THIS IS ETHAN.
LaMIRANDA.
I NEVER KNEW
RADICALS CAME
WITH SUCH PRETTY
PACKAGES.
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO CHECK OUT
ONE OF THESE
MEETINGS MYSELF.
YOU KNOW,
YOU REALLY SHOULD.
WE SHOULD TAKE YOU
DOWN TO PHILLY
WITH US.
THAT WOULD WAKE UP
MIDDLE AMERICA.
YOU GUYS GOING
TO PHILADELPHIA?
ON A SIGHT-SEEING
TOUR TO THE LIBERTY
BELL, OR WHAT?
WE GOT A BIG DEAL
CIVIL RIGHTS MARCH
HAPPENING
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
IT'S KIND OF A DRAG.
THEY WANT US ALL TO
WEAR DRESSES AND SUITS
LIKE JOHN AND JACKIE
KENNEDY-STYLE SQUARES.
WELL, I KNOW WHO
I'M GOIN' AS.
SOUNDS LIKE
MY KINDA DRAG.
SERIOUSLY,
I MAYBE MIGHT BE
INTERESTED
IN COMING ALONG.
MATTY'S BEEN
TELLING ME WHAT
YOU GUYS
ARE TRYING TO DO,
AND IT ALL SOUNDS
KIND OF UP ASSWARDS
TO ME,
BUT AT LEAST YOU'RE
GETTING SOMETHING
TOGETHER, RIGHT?
MATT, YOU BEEN DOING
A LITTLE OUTREACH
WORK?
OH, LaMIRANDA AND I
ARE ROOMMATES, ETHAN.
OH, DON'T OVERSELL
IT ON MY ACCOUNT,
MASSA MATTY DEAN,
SUH!
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TELL
LOVER BOY HERE
THAT I'M YOUR
FUCKING MAID?!
LaMIRANDA. BABY.
I'M TOO DRUNK TO RUN.
WOULD YOU STOP?
WHEN YOU SEE THIS FACE,
YOU WILL SEE NO TEARS
HERE, O.K.?
NO TEARS.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT THE PICKET
IN PHILADELPHIA
'CAUSE THEY GOT THESE
DUMB OLD DRESS CODES,
AND I KNEW THAT WOULD
NEVER GO WITH YOU.
AND YOU NEVER TOLD THEM
ABOUT ME BECAUSE I DON'T
GO WITH YOU, RIGHT?
TCH! MY HERO.
IS IT MY FAULT
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW
TO BE A GUY?
WHAT?
IS IT MY FAULT
THAT I WASN'T BORN
WITH A PROMINENT
SISSY GENE?
IS IT MY FAULT
THERE ARE MEN
WHO LOOK GOOD
WITHOUT 6 POUNDS
OF FACE PAINT?
IS THAT MY FAULT?
IT AIN'T MY FUCKING
FAULT.
YEAH, WHOSE FAULT
IS IT THAT YOU'RE
SUCH A PRICK?
YOU WANNA LEAD
A LITTLE WHILE?
MM-MM.
IT'S NICE TO FOLLOW
FOR A CHANGE.
ROUGH DAY?
HA. TRY DECADE.
I NEVER DANCED
WITH A MAN BEFORE.
OH, GET OUTTA HERE.
I HAVEN'T.
YOU'RE SERIOUS.
YEAH.
NOT EVEN IN PRIVATE?
I'VE BEEN SO BUSY
FIGHTING FOR
THE RIGHT TO DANCE,
I--I JUST NEVER
TOOK THE TIME
TO TRY IT.
WHEN WE FORMED
THE SOCIETY
OVER 15 YEARS AGO,
YOU COULDN'T FIND
3 PEOPLE
WHO'D EVEN SAY
THE WORD HOMOSEXUAL
IN PUBLIC.
THEN THIS KID
COMES ALONG WITH
ALL THE ANSWERS,
LIKE IT'S SO DAMN
EASY.
YOU CAN'T TELL
THESE YOUNG'UNS NOTHING.
I WAS NEVER YOUNG.
WE DIDN'T HAVE
TEENAGERS BACK THEN.
NO, WE GOT OLD
THE MINUTE WE HIT
PUBERTY.
OH, I HEAR THAT.
YOU SHOULDA BEEN
A DRAG QUEEN, SWEETNESS.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
OUR MOTTO
IS DANCE, DAMN IT,
'CAUSE HONEY,
THEY MAY BE COMING
FOR YOU IN THE MORNING,
SO YOU MAY AS WELL DANCE
ALL NIGHT.
SORRY.
I'M JUST YOUR
PLAIN OLD VANILLA-
FLAVORED HOMO.
NO KINKS. NO TWISTS.
NO ADDITIVES.
PLENTY OF NUTS,
THOUGH.
AND BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
I DO SALUTE YOU.
BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
I'M HONORED.
DANCE, DAMN IT!
[SHANGRI-LAS TUNE]
PRESENT.
GO OUT WITH YOU?
WHY NOT?
DO I LIKE TO DANCE?
OF COURSE.
TAKE A WALK ALONG
THE BEACH TONIGHT?
I'D LOVE TO.
DON'T TRY TO TOUCH ME.
BECAUSE THAT WILL
NEVER HAPPEN...
AGAIN.
SHALL WE DANCE?
[MUSIC]
WHY, VINNIE!
TOP OF THE MORNING
TO YOU, BABY.
MY BACKSEAT
OR YOURS?
WILL YOU STOP WITH
THE IRONICS FOR RIGHT NOW?
I'D LIKE SOME CONVERSATION.
ARE YOU O.K.,
SWEETNESS?
SURE, I'M O.K.
I'M ALWAYS O.K.
I JUST NEED TO TALK
WITH YOU BACK AND FORTH
FOR A WHILE.
YOU FOLLOW ME, HUH?
VINNIE, DARLING,
NOW DON'T THINK
I AIN'T INTO THIS
5:00 IN THE MORNING
FROZEN AND CONFUSED
DRAG-ASS WALKS
THROUGH THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE THING,
BUT YOU'RE IN DANGER
OF SPOILING ME.
SEE THAT WINDOW
UP THERE?
THERE'S A CLINIC
BEHIND THAT WINDOW.
THEY CALL IT
"THE PALACE OF DREAMS."
AND THAT'S
HOW THEY LAUGH
THE DAY AWAY
IN THE MERRY OLD
LAND OF OZ.
THAT'S O.K.
IT'S O.K. TO LAUGH.
YOU REMEMBER
ANGELINA HEART?
YEAH, THAT PRISSY
GET-ME LITTLE QUEEN.
WE USED TO
CALL HER ANGINA.
THAT HIGH COURT JUDGE
SHE WAS SEEING
BOUGHT HER A LITTLE
HOLIDAY AT THE PALACE
OF DREAMS.
NOW SHE'S
A MARRIED WOMAN,
THE MOST ADMIRED
HOSTESS IN ST. LOUIS.
NO. DAMN!
SHE ALWAYS DID
SEE HERSELF AS
COCO CHANEL.
LISTEN...
NOW THAT'S A SWEET
STORY, DOLL,
AND IT'S DISH
TO DIE FOR,
BUT THAT AIN'T
THE PALACE OF
MY DREAMS, HONEY.
WELL, IT IS THE PALACE
OF MY FUCKING DREAMS,
AND YOU GET WITH IT.
ALL RIGHT?
VINNIE, YOU'D MAKE
AN UGLY CHICK.
YOU'D HAVE TO SHAVE
YOUR DAMN KNUCKLES
JUST FOR STARTERS.
SHUT UP!
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
JESUS, VINNIE!
LOOK WHAT
YOU FUCKING DID!
DON'T MAKE ME
KICK THE SHIT
OUT OF YOU!
YOU MADE ME TOUCH YOU!
RIGHT OUT HERE
IN THE OPEN!
JUST--WILL YOU JUST
LISTEN FOR ONE SECOND
IN YOUR SMART-ASS
FRIGGIN' LIFE?!
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN
AND HEAR ME.
ALL RIGHT?
I AM LISTENING.
I HEAR YOU, BABY.
DON'T FUCKIN'
TOUCH ME!
I DON'T NEED
A FUCKIN' MOTHER!
I NEED A WIFE.
I NEED TO BE JUST
MR. NORMAL EVERYDAY.
AND WHAT IS
WRONG WITH THAT?
NOW I'VE ALREADY
BOOKED YOU IN TO
SEE THE DOC,
SO HOW'S ABOUT THAT?
WELL, YOU CAN JUST
UNBOOK ME, SWEETNESS.
HOW'S ABOUT THAT?
THIS IS SO YOU.
ARE YOU SCARED OF
BEING A NORMAL
PERSON OR WHAT?
I AM SCARED OF
LOSING LITTLE BO
DOWNSTAIRS IS WHAT!
WHAT ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT THIS FOR?
I AM A CHICK
WITH A DICK
WHO AIN'T DONE
WITH HER DICK YET.
AND LET'S FACE IT,
SWEETNESS,
NEITHER ARE YOU.
I CAN TAKE IT
OR LEAVE IT, BO.
IT'S YOU
I GOTTA HAVE.
YOU'VE GOT ME.
BUT THEY AIN'T NEVER
GONNA LET US BE.
NO, THEY AIN'T
NEVER GONNA LET US BE.
AIN'T NO OPERATION
GONNA CHANGE THAT.
COME HERE.
WE CAN'T...
THERE'S
TOO MANY WINDOWS.
[LIP-SYNCHING]
I WAS WALKING
DOWN THE STREET
AND IT WAS GETTING
MIGHTY LATE
WELL, THE TRUTH
OF THE MATTER IS
THIS POOR GIRL HAD BEEN
ABANDONED BY HER DATE
WHEN FROM OUT OF NOWHERE
CAME THIS MUSIC
LOUD AND CLEAR
LET ME SEE
FROM OVER THERE
NO, OVER THERE.
OVER THERE?
YEAH.
WELL, I OPENED
UP THE DOOR
AND MUCH TO MY SURPRISE
THE GIRLS
WERE WEARING FORMALS
AND THE BOYS
WERE WEARING TIES
AND I FEEL
THAT I SHOULD MENTION
THAT THE BAND
WAS AT ATTENTION
THEY JUST STOOD THERE
OH SO NEAT
WHILE THEY PLAYED
THEIR SWINGING BEAT
SO I GRABBED
THIS LITTLE BOY
WHO CAME STRUTTING
CROSS THE ROOM
I SAID WHAT'S THAT?
AND HE SAID...
SOPHISTICATED BOOM BOOM
IT'S BEEN LONG OVERDUE
[ZIP]
SOPHISTICATED BOOM BOOM
WE'VE BEEN NEEDING
SOMETHING NEW
SOPHISTICATED BOOM BOOM
NOW STAND UP
STRAIGHT AND TALL
LIKE YOUR BACK'S
AGAINST THE WALL
TAKE 2 STEPS FORWARD
AND SHAKE YOUR HIPS
BOOM BOOM
[SOPRANO]
AAAAH
AH AH OOH OOH
GOOD MORNING, AGNES.
WAH AH AH AH OOH
WA WA WA WA WA WA
WOO HOO
OOH OOH OOH
O.K., JUST TAKE
ANY SEAT.
LET'S GO, FOLKS.
LET'S GO.
BLLDIP BLLDIP BLLDIP
IT'S BEEN LONG OVERDUE
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
THAT'S NOT VERY
SOPHISTICATED
WE'VE BEEN NEEDING
SOMETHING NEW
YEAH YEAH YEAH
I DO THINK
SHE'S BLOWING HER COOL
SOPHISTICATED BOOM BOOM
NOW STAND UP
STRAIGHT AND TALL
LIKE YOUR BACK'S
AGAINST THE WALL
TAKE 2 STEPS FORWARD
NOW SHAKE YOUR HIPS
BOOM BOOM
OOOH OOOH
OOH OOH OOOOH
OOOOH...
[CLOCK BELL TOLLS]
MINE EYES HAVE SEEN
THE STRUGGLES
OF THE NEGROES
AND THE JEWS
I HAVE SEEN
THE COUNTRIES TRAMPLED
AND THE LAWS
OF MEN ABUSED
BUT YOU CRUSH
THE HOMOSEXUAL
WITH ANYTHING YOU CHOOSE
AND WE GO MARCHING ON
GLORY, GLORY HALLELUJAH
AS WE GO MARCHING ON
WE'RE DROWNED OUT
BY INJUSTICE
'TIL OUR WHISPERS
CAN'T BE HEARD
YOU HAVE SHATTERED
ALL OUR HOPES AND DREAMS
AND YET
WE'VE NEVER STIRRED
WE'RE RISING IN A CHORUS
AND SOON
YOU'LL HEAR EVERY WORD
AS WE GO MARCHING ON
GLORY, GLORY HALLELUJAH
THE CIVIL RIGHTS
YOU TOOK FROM US
WE WANT THEM BACK AGAIN
AND WE'LL TALK
AND WRITE AND PICKET
UNTIL WE SEE YA BEND
IF YOU DO NOT
GIVE THEM TO US
WE WILL TAKE THEM
IN THE END
AS WE GO MARCHING ON
GLORY, GLORY HALLELUJAH
THANK GOD
THAT'S OVER,
THE BIG ONE.
HUH?
AT LEAST
NO ONE GOT KILLED.
YOU WANT COFFEE?
NO MILK,
PLENTY OF SUGAR.
MAYBE IT WOULD'VE
BEEN BETTER.
WHAT?
IF WE'D ALL
BEEN KILLED.
IF THE WHOLE MARCH
HAD BEEN WIPED OUT
BY A GRENADE
OR SOMETHING.
AT LEAST IT WOULD
HAVE MADE THE PAPERS.
MAYBE THAT WOULD'VE
MOBILIZED PEOPLE.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
MORE THAN 30 PEOPLE
WHO ACTUALLY
GIVE A SHIT.
WE NEED SOMETHING
TO GET 'EM OUT OF
WHATEVER HOLE
THEY'RE IN.
WELL, A LOT OF
THOSE PEOPLE ARE
JUST NOT ABLE
TO EVEN CONCEIVE OF
THESE ISSUES,
LET ALONE
MARCH FOR THEM.
THAT DITZY QUEEN
WE WERE TALKING WITH
THE OTHER DAY?
LaMIRANDA?
HIM.
HE'S GONNA MARCH?
HE COULD BARELY
CROSS THE ROOM
IN THOSE HEELS.
SHE PREFERS TO
BE CALLED HER.
WELL,
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
I ASKED HER WHY
THEY PREFER TO
BE CALLED "HER".
SHE SAID
THE FEMININE
WAS THE HIGHEST
ANY MALE
COULD ASPIRE TO.
I KNOW YOU'RE
PARAPHRASING,
'CAUSE NO WAY
IS THAT IN HIS
VOCABULARY.
O.K.
PACK YOUR BAGS.
WE NEED A HOLIDAY.
I'M TAKING YOU
TO FIRE ISLAND
FOR A COUPLE
OF DAYS.
BRING A SWIMSUIT,
SOME SHADES,
AND A FRIVOLOUS
ATTITUDE.
I HAVE TO
WORK TOMORROW.
WHO DOESN'T?
CALL IN SICK.
COME ON, MATT.
YOU CAN ADVANCE
YOUR DISHWASHING
CAREER
AFTER
A LONG WEEKEND.
WE NEED TO
SURROUND YOU
WITH POSITIVE IMAGES
OF FAGGOTRY,
RIGHT NOW.
DO THIS WITH ME,
HUH?
I WANNA SEE
YOU SMILE AGAIN.
SOUNDS TERRIFIC.
FORGIVE ME, FATHER,
FOR I HAVE SINNED.
IT'S BEEN A LIFETIME
SINCE MY LAST
CONFESSION,
AND UH--EVERY SIN,
FATHER,
I'VE COMMITTED
EVERY SIN,
LUST, GREED,
ANGER...
EVEN PRIDE.
WHO AM I TO
FEEL PRIDE?
A MAN WHO HAS
EVERYTHING...
IN FACT ACTUALLY
HAS NOTHING.
THE ONLY
THING I WANT
IS THE ONE THING
THAT I DO HAVE,
AND I AIN'T
ALLOWED TO WANT IT.
SO...
I DON'T REALLY
HAVE IT.
BUT THAT'S ME,
FATHER.
THIS IS ME.
FORGIVE ME,
FATHER...
FOR I HAVE SINNED.
SEEMS LIKE THE OTHER DAY
MY BABY WENT AWAY
HE WENT AWAY
ACROSS THE SEA
IT'S BEEN 2 YEARS OR SO
SINCE I SAW
MY BABY GO
AND THEN THIS LETTER
CAME FOR ME
HE SAID THAT
WE WERE THROUGH
HE'D FOUND SOMEBODY NEW
OH, LET ME THINK,
LET ME THINK
WHAT CAN I DO?
OH NO
OH, NO NO NO NO NO
REMEMBER
WALKIN' IN THE SAND
WALKIN' HAND IN HAND
REMEMBER
THE NIGHT
WAS SO EXCITING
REMEMBER
HIS SMILE
WAS SO INVITING
REMEMBER
WHEN HE TOUCHED
MY CHEEK
REMEMBER
WITH HIS FINGERTIPS
SOFTLY
SOFTLY WE'D MEET
WITH OUR LIPS
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO
THE BOY
THAT I ONCE KNEW?
THE BOY WHO SAID
HE'D BE TRUE
OH, WHAT WILL
HAPPEN TO...
[INAUDIBLE CHATTERING]
OH, IT'S COLD!
OW!
NOW TELL ME,
AM I CONFUSED?
DID WE DIE AND JUST
GO TO HEAVEN?
THIS PLACE
HAS IT ALL.
REMEMBER
WAIT UNTIL LATER
AT THE DANCE.
YOU'LL SEE MORE
BEAUTIFUL MEN
IN ONE ROOM
THAN YOU EVER
DREAMED OF.
AAAHHH!
[LOUD WHISTLE]
PUT YOUR TOWEL ON,
MATTY.
WHAT?
LOCAL ORDINANCE
FROM THE DARK AGES.
YOU CAN'T WEAR
SUGGESTIVE SWIMSUITS
UNCOVERED
ON THE BEACH.
YOU MEAN WE CAN'T.
DON'T GIVE
THESE ASSHOLES
ANY EXCUSES,
O.K., MATTY?
DID WE JUST DIE
AND GO TO HEAVEN?
SOMEWHERE OVER
THE RAINBOW
WAY UP HIGH
THERE'S A LAND
THAT I HEARD OF
ONCE IN A LULLABY
SOMEWHERE OVER
THE RAINBOW...
...JUDY GARLAND STARTED
WORKING IN VAUDEVILLE
AT THE AGE OF 2,
A FAMILY ACT CALLED
THE GUMM SISTERS.
THE PUNISHING
SCHEDULES INVOLVED
LED TO A LASTING
ADDICTION TO BARBITURATES.
...A SPECIAL OSCAR
AT THE AGE OF 17
FOR BEST JUVENILE ACTRESS
FOR
THE WIZARD OF OZ...
JUDY GARLAND BECAME
IDENTIFIED...
SHE WAS MOST RECENTLY MARRIED
TO HUSBAND NUMBER 5,
NICKY DEANS.
JUDY GARLAND
DIED IN LONDON, ENGLAND
WHERE THEY WERE
DEANS IS SAID
TO BE INCONSOLABLE.
SO IS HOLLYWOOD,
AND INDEED AMERICA ITSELF,
AS THOUSANDS MOURN
THE LOSS
OF ONE OF THE LAST
TRUE GREAT AND GENUINE STARS.
I CAME
AS SOON AS I HEARD.
SWEET OF YOU.
SOMEWHERE
OVER THE RAINBOW
BLUEBIRDS FLY
BIRDS FLY
OVER THE RAINBOW
YOU O.K.?
WHY, THEN,
OH WHY CAN'T I?
I HEARD SHE GOT
FOUND ON THE JOHN.
GOD, LIFE IS SORDID.
I GAVE UP
FOLLOWING POLITICS
BECAUSE I COULD
NOT DEAL WITH
THE HEARTBREAK,
HONEY.
KENNEDY,
MALCOLM X,
DR. KING,
AND WHAT HAPPENS?
I RETREAT INTO
THE SAFETY OF
SUPERFICIALITY
ONLY TO FIND
GREATER GRIEF
THAN I THINK
I'VE EVER KNOWN.
SOMEWHERE OVER
THE RAINBOW...
BOY, OH, BOY.
CHECK YOU OUT.
YOU SHOULD
BE ITALIAN.
I DO WALLOW GOOD,
DON'T I?
IT'S BECAUSE
I'M SINCERE.
AND WHAT WOULD
IT TAKE TO...
BRING YOU UP?
ICE CREAM...
IN THE SUN...
WITH THE MAN I LOVE.
NOTHING MUCH.
O.K.
EXCUSE ME?
[CLAPS]
GET UP.
I'M TAKING YOU OUT.
YOU MEAN
AMONGST PEOPLE?
YEP, AMONGST FOLKS.
GET DRESSED.
VINNIE,
ARE YOU HIGH?
I AIN'T CHANGED.
I'M JUST--
I'M COMING OUT A LITTLE.
GET DRESSED,
YOU DIZZY FRIGGIN' FILLY.
GODDAMN IT!
PLEASE.
THAT'S
THE MAGIC WORD,
SWEETNESS.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WILD PARTY.
THEY CAN'T
DANCE YET.
THEY WILL.
THERE'S
A CHOREOGRAPHER
COMING OR...
YOU'RE HATING THIS.
ANYWAY,
THEY CAN'T DANCE
UNTIL
THE WOMAN DANCES.
WHO, THE DRAG QUEEN
IN THE ROMAN SANDALS?
THAT'S NOT A DRAG
QUEEN, MATTY.
AND SINCE YOU GOTTA GO
YOU HAD BETTER GO NOW
GO NOW
BEFORE YOU SEE ME CRY
AND I DON'T WANT
YOU TO TELL ME
JUST WHAT YOU
INTEND TO DO NOW...
HEY!
KEEP IT CLEAN, BOYS.
RIGHT?
IT'S NOT LIKE THIS.
IT'S LIKE THIS. O.K.?
WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT?
ANCIENT LOCAL
ORDINANCES?
JESUS, ETHAN!
WE'VE ALREADY SAID...
MORE ICE CREAM,
BABY?
I'VE BEEN EATING
THE STUFF ALL DAY.
ANY MORE
AND I'M GONNA
BE A DANCER
WITH
THE BEEF TRUST
CHORUS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
EAT ALL NIGHT?
VINNIE.
AMBROSIA?
ISN'T SHE A LITTLE
MUSCULAR?
DON'T, FRANK,
IT'S NOT NICE.
THE CHECK, SIR?
[CLEARS THROAT]
WHAT OTHER
ICE CREAM YOU GOT?
I'M AFRAID
YOU'VE EXHAUSTED
OUR ENTIRE STOCK.
WELL, SEND OUT FOR SOME.
WE'RE HUNGRY.
MY APOLOGIES, SIR.
PLEASE, ALLOW ME
TO PRESENT YOU
THIS MEAL
WITH COMPLIMENTS
OF THE ESTABLISHMENT.
OH, YEAH?
AND I BEG
YOUR FORGIVENESS BUT,
THROUGH
AN UNFORGIVABLE ERROR
BY A JUNIOR MEMBER
OF OUR STAFF,
THIS TABLE HAS
BEEN DOUBLE-BOOKED,
AND THE MANAGEMENT
WERE WONDERING
IF YOU WOULD MIND
SACRIFICING YOUR PLACES
JUST A LITTLE EARLY
TO AVOID DISAPPOINTING
THE NEXT PARTY
OF DINERS?
SWEETNESS!
[SNAPS FINGERS]
MY COMPLIMENTS.
OOH, LOOK AT ALL THAT MONEY!
I'M SORRY, MATT.
THE WORLD'S TOO BIG
TO SAVE ALL AT ONE TIME.
LOOK AT US.
NOW THERE'S NO
EYE-CONTACT IN PRIVATE.
THEY'RE WINNING.
WE COULD REALLY
LOVE EACH OTHER,
YOU KNOW, MATT?
SHIT, I'M SORRY.
IT'S A HABIT.
WHEN YOU'VE SPENT
YOUR LIFE LOOKING
OVER YOUR SHOULDER...
WELL, YOU KNOW
HOW IT IS.
YEAH.
[SHANGRI-LAS TUNE]
THE FUTURE
TOMORROW?
WELL...
TOMORROW'S
A LONG WAY OFF
MAYBE SOMEDAY
I'LL HOLD SOMEBODY'S HAND
MAYBE SOMEWHERE
SOMEONE WILL UNDERSTAND
YOU KNOW,
I USED TO SING
A TISKET, A TASKET
A GREEN AND YELLOW BASKET
I'M ALL PACKED UP
AND I'M ON MY WAY
I'M GONNA FALL
IN LOVE
BUT AT THE MOMENT
IT DOESN'T LOOK GOOD
AT THE MOMENT
IT WILL
NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN
I DON'T THINK
IT WILL EVER HAPPEN...
AGAIN
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
LaMIRANDA?
[DOOR OPENING]
MATTY DEAN?
BABY?
I'M YOUR KNIGHT
IN SHINING ARMOR,
BABY,
YOUR BOY
AND YOUR LADY.
I'M YOUR MAMA LION.
I'M YOUR MAN.
I WILL FIGHT FOR YOU,
DRESS FOR YOU,
EVEN CRY FOR YOU.
BUT ONLY FOR YOU,
BABY,
NEVER FOR THEM.
NEVER...FOR THEM.
HEY, CRYPTICA.
HMM?
YOU LOVE ME?
NOW, WHAT KIND OF
ASSHOLE QUESTION IS THAT?
I EVER TELL YOU
I LOVE YOU?
NO, YOU SON OF A BITCH.
AAAHHHH!
VINNIE!
NOOOOO!
GOD!
NOOOO!
NOOOOO, VINNIE!
GOD!
NO!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
ALL AMERICA TAKES TIME OUT
TO MOURN ITS OWN
GIRL NEXT DOOR,
JUDY GARLAND,
ONE OF THE LAST TRUE GREATS
AND GENUINE STARS.
[RECORDING OF JUDY GARLAND
SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
AGED ONLY 47 WHEN SHE CAME
TO THE END OF
HER YELLOW BRICK ROAD,
HER TRAGIC SAGA OVER,
SHE IS AT PEACE AT LAST.
SOMETHING INSIDE OF ME
STARTED A LITTLE SYMPHONY
ZING WENT
THE STRINGS OF MY HEART
[SIREN]
I HEARD
A ROBIN SING...
JUDY STAYS.
[JUDY GARLAND SONG
CONTINUES TO PLAY]
AND WHO IS GONNA BE
OUR FIRST LUCKY CONTESTANT
ON THIS WEEK'S EDITION
OF JEOPARDY!?
I HOPE EVERYONE IS WEARING
THE LEGAL MINIMUM
REQUIREMENT
OF 3 ITEMS OF CLOTHING
APPROPRIATE THEIR GENDER
AS PRESCRIBED BY NATURE.
OTHERWISE, THOSE CONTESTANTS
ARE GONNA FIND THEMSELVES
WITH THE GRAND BOOBY PRIZE,
AN ALL-EXPENSES PAID
LUXURY TRIP...
DOWNTOWN.
YOU!
I'M SORRY, SISTER,
THAT PATHETIC LITTLE
BLOUSE DON'T SAY
"MAN" TO ME.
BUST THE LITTLE JODIE
FOR SOLICITING.
BUST THAT ONE FOR
LOOKING AT ME FUNNY.
WHAT THE HELL?
BUST THE SELECTION.
[SIRENS]
[SCREAMING]
ALL RIGHT, GET 'EM ALL OUT OF THERE!
YOU WANNA GO FOR IT,
OFFICER?
STRUT YOUR STUFF,
GIRLFRIEND!
GIVE THEM HELL,
HELEN, HONEY!
WHOO!
COME ON, STAY IN LINE.
STAY IN LINE.
DON'T PUSH ME, MARY,
I AM NOT
IN THE MOOD.
AW, SHE AIN'T
AIN'T WE IN THE MOOD?
ARE WE ON THE RAG,
DEARIE?
WELL, WHAT IF
MY LITTLE BUDDY HERE
IS IN THE MOOD, HUH?
POOR LITTLE FAGGOT
DON'T KNOW WHETHER
TO KILL ME OR KISS ME.
YEAH!
WHOO!
GUESS I MADE UP
MY MIND.
DIRTY ROTTEN PIG!
COME ALONG WITH ME.
GET OUTTA MY WAY.
STAND BACK!
COME ON, COME ON,
STAND BACK.
GO ON BACK
IN THE BAR!
GO ON BACK IN THE BAR!
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
DO IT!
GO BACK, GO BACK!
COME ON, GO, GO, GO, GO!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
BACK IN THE BAR!
[CHANTING]
GET OUT! GET OUT!
WE NEED MORE STUFF!
I DO SO
LOVE A PARTY.
IT'S THE FOURTH
OF FUCKING JULY!
COME ON.
YES, IT IS, HONEY!
LET'S GO, BABIES!
GET AWAY
FROM THAT WINDOW!
HEY, I'LL KICK YOUR ASS!
[CURSING IN SPANISH]
COME ON, HIT ME,
I DARE YOU!
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO DO THIS TO US.
BASTARD!
YOU BASTARDS!
COME ON, BABY,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
WE ARE
THE STONEWALL GIRLS
WE WEAR
OUR HAIR IN CURLS
WE WEAR NO UNDERWEAR
WE SHOW OUR PUBIC HAIR
WE ARE
THE VILLAGE QUEENS
WE ALWAYS
WEAR BLUE JEANS
WE WEAR OUR HAIR IN CURLS
BECAUSE WE THINK
WE'RE GIRLS
EVERYONE HAS THEIR OWN
STONEWALL LEGEND.
THAT'S MINE.
I MAYBE DIDN'T GET EXACTLY
EVERY DETAIL DOWN PERFECT,
BUT THAT'S THE STORY
OF MY LIFE, HONEY.
WE WEAR OUR HAIR IN CURLS
BECAUSE WE THINK
WE'RE GIRLS
WHAT THE HELL?
I AM A DRAG QUEEN,
AND WE DON'T ALWAYS
DEAL IN REALITY.
YOU COULD SAY WE DEAL
IN SOMETHING KINDA REALER.
WE DEAL IN DREAMS.
WE'RE AMERICAN AS APPLE PIE.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE
BY BMG VIDEO
CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY
THE NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE, INC.
PUBLIC PERFORMANCE OF CAPTIONS
PROHIBITED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
WHEN YOU WERE BORN
THEY LOOKED AT YOU AND SAID
WHAT A GOOD GIRL,
WHAT A SMART GIRL
WHAT A PRETTY GIRL
GOT THESE CHAINS
HANGING AROUND OUR NECKS
PEOPLE WANT TO
STRANGLE US WITH
BEFORE WE TAKE
OUR FIRST BREATH
AFRAID OF CHANGE
AFRAID OF STAYING
THE SAME
WHEN TEMPTATION CALLS
WE JUST LOOK AWAY
THIS NAME IS
THE HAIR SHIRT I WEAR
AND THIS HAIR SHIRT IS WOVEN
FROM YOUR VIOLENT HAND
THIS SONG IS
THE CROSS THAT I BEAR
BEAR WITH ME,
BEAR WITH ME
BE WITH ME TONIGHT
I KNOW THAT
IT ISN'T RIGHT
BUT BE WITH ME TONIGHT
GO TO SCHOOL
I WRITE EXAMS
WITH THE BEST OF THEM
IF I DROP OUT
DOES ANYONE GIVE A DAMN?
AND IF THEY DO
THEY'LL SOON FORGET
'CAUSE IT WON'T
TAKE MUCH FOR ME
TO SHOW MY LIFE
AND WHO I AM
WAKE UP SCARED
I WAKE UP STRANGE
I WAKE UP WONDERING
IF ANYTHING IN MY LIFE
IS EVER GONNA CHANGE
I WAKE UP SCARED
I WAKE UP
STRANGE
AND EVERYTHING AROUND ME
STAYS THE SAME
IT'S THE HAIR SHIRT I WEAR
AND THIS HAIR SHIRT
IS WOVEN FROM
YOUR VIOLENT HAND
THIS SONG IS
THE CROSS THAT I BEAR
BEAR WITH ME
BEAR WITH ME,
BE WITH ME TONIGHT
I KNOW THAT
IT ISN'T RIGHT
BUT BE WITH ME TONIGHT
I COULDN'T TELL YOU
I WAS WRONG
CHICKENED OUT
SAT DOWN
AND I WROTE THIS SONG
I COULDN'T TELL YOU
THAT YOU WERE RIGHT
SO INSTEAD
I LOOKED IN THE MIRROR
I WATCHED TV,
LAID AWAKE ALL NIGHT
OH, WE'VE GOT THESE CHAINS
HANGING 'ROUND OUR NECKS
PEOPLE WANT TO
STRANGLE US WITH 'EM
BEFORE WE TAKE
OUR FIRST BREATH
AFRAID OF CHANGE
AFRAID OF STAYING THE SAME
WHEN TEMPTATION CALLS
YEAH HEY!
OH, THIS NAME IS
THE HAIR SHIRT I WEAR
AND THIS HAIR SHIRT
IS WOVEN FROM
IS WOVEN FROM,
IS WOVEN FROM YOUR HAND
THIS SONG IS
THE CROSS THAT I BEAR
BEAR WITH ME
BEAR WITH ME,
BE WITH ME TONIGHT
WHEN I WAS BORN
THEY LOOKED AT ME
AND SAID
WHAT A GOOD BOY,
WHAT A SMART BOY
WHAT A STRONG BOY
WHEN YOU WERE BORN
THEY LOOKED AT YOU
AND SAID
WHAT A GOOD GIRL,
WHAT A SMART GIRL
WHAT A PRETTY GIRL
YEAH YEAH