(girl)
High school.
If you believe the hype,
it will be the greatest
years of our lives.
Oh, that's not me,
by the way.
That's me...
with my brother.
And what you're about to watch
is actually about my first day
in seventh grade.
Are you ready,
guys?
(all)
Totally ready!
♪♪
♪ This time is so fantastic ♪
♪ And we're psyched to
get scholastic ♪
♪ 'Cause it's day one
of the school year ♪
♪ I got the right guy
and my friends by my side ♪
♪ I got my pom-poms and made
it a cheer ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ And I'm
the class president... ♪
CJ, shut this off.
Stop.
♪ ... having 500 friends ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And every one in Glee ♪
♪ Is so proud
and so friendly ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ 'Cause it's high school
the cool school ♪
♪ The totally-we-rule school ♪
♪ The yeah school
the whoo school ♪
♪ The shake-it-like-a-fool
school ♪
♪ Where friendship
never ends ♪♪
Okay, high school
is nothing like that.
Trust me.
They're a bunch
of liars.
Ronbie,
please don't ruin
"High School High Musical."
And my last night
of summer.
(all)
Yeah, don't ruin it for her.
Okay, here's where things
get a little weird.
But stay with me,
it will make sense.
Well, don't lie to her!
Sing what high school's
really like.
Go on, go on.
Sing her
the truth.
Sing it!
♪ Your brother's
kind of right ♪
♪ High school's a struggle
and a fight ♪
♪ I'm overscheduled and
have no time for friends ♪
♪ What? ♪
♪ Because I got five Fs they
took the letter off my chest ♪
♪ And now my season's
at an end ♪
Ahh!
♪ And we
didn't make Glee ♪
♪ So we're sad
not happy ♪
Sorry, guys.
Now off my stage!
(yelling)
(crashing)
It gets worse?
Oh yeah.
School starts at 7:30.
I have five hours
of homework a night.
Final exams make me
wanna vomit.
♪ And you lose all
the friends you have now ♪
♪ 'Cause you grow apart and like
different things ♪
♪ Or they start to act
like they're way too cool ♪
Can we at least
sing happy again?
(all)
Yeah!
♪ 'Cause in high school
the song school ♪
♪ The homework-all-night-long
school ♪
♪ The low school
the strife school ♪
♪ The no-time-for-a-life
school ♪
♪ And yeah you'll lose
the friends you have now ♪♪
(alarm beeping)
(gasping)
Yep,
you guessed it.
That last part was a dream
and I'm freaking out.
Why?
Because singing teens just
informed me
my future
is bleak and friendless.
♪♪
Hey, hon?
Think there's something
wrong with CJ.
Oh.
Of course there is.
Summer's over and someone told
her high school horror stories
last night.
Hey, I told her the truth.
And what was that?
That high school's gross
and makes you vomit
and I'm gonna lose all
the friends that I have now.
Why, you little--
Get him!
So you might be wondering why
I'm so freaked out about
a silly dream and something
that's two years away.
But my friends are
the most important thing to me.
And losing them was all I could
think about.
Not what a perfect first day
of seventh grade it seemed.
Not our new principal,
who seems to float with terror.
Not even that Paul Shmalter,
the hall monitor,
grew a moustache
over the summer.
No.
All I could think about was,
will I lose my best friends
before high school?
Happy first day,
best friend of mine.
Fenwick Fraser,
possessor of one mega brain,
100 stylish ties
and the first friend
I ever made.
It's a piggy bank.
You're gonna need it.
With skyrocketing
college tuition,
you'll graduate in deep debt,
yet unemployable because
your parents smothered you
with their crippling sense
of entitlement.
You wanna be friends?
Yes.
And since then,
he's always there for me.
I can't
hang out anymore.
What?
Look, if I want to
go to Stanford
and rule the world someday,
I need to focus now on
scholarships, not friendships.
Well, what about lunch?
Studying.
What about study hall?
Well, what about...
See you at graduation!
Okay, I admit it.
It did seem like I just lost
best friend number one
before homeroom.
But I also knew I had
BFF number two,
Christian Powers, AKA Crispo,
who just got
his braces off,
finally got the haircut
I suggested
and, after saving
his life in kindergarten,
vowed to be my best friend
forever.
(school bell ringing)
Now that I got my
braces off,
I can't stop
licking my teeth.
Okay, stop that.
Just smile and help me
figure out a way to
knock some
sense back into Fen.
Hey, Crispo!
Her Highness, Mindy Minus,
the most popular
girl in school.
I hate her.
Wow, you look
different.
Yeah, I got this new hair
and this awesome
jacket that's awesome.
Yeah, you're
friends with us now.
♪♪
Right now, it does seem
my high school dream
was becoming
a middle school nightmare.
I just lost Fenwick to
Study World
and Crispo
to Popular World.
But did I panic?
Yes.
But I knew I just needed to find
something that would bring us
all back to
Best Friend Forever World.
But what?
(chirping)
Guess who ate my
rhubarb experiments
in the school garden
all summer
but is not
eating them anymore!
Why do you
have it on your desk?
So we can suffer the same
pain and humiliation
that he caused me.
And that's when I realized I was
going to get my best friends
back by freeing
Mr. Slinko's raccoon.
Why?
Because I knew since
kindergarten
my best buds could not
resist a good rescue mission.
Teacher took Angelica.
But we're gonna
get her back.
Lookout!
Looking out.
Rope?
Horsey!
No, rope!
We don't
need a horsey.
Don't eat it.
Besides, who's gonna
say no to this face?
You can
sit down now.
♪♪
Do not disturb
Smart Time, please.
I need your help.
Here we go.
I'm just going to
tell you what it is.
Fine, but whatever it is
better be important,
like really important.
Like "make my face freeze
so I don't even know
how to react" important.
We're going to free
Slinko's raccoon.
(school bell ringing)
Look, in case you
haven't noticed,
we have
a new principal,
and getting in trouble
on our first day
is not on my
list of things to do.
♪♪
I'm in.
Great.
Now we just need--
(all)
Crispo!
♪♪
(boy)
Crispo!
(girl)
(boy)
Crispo!
Hey, guys.
Did you hear?
I'm popular now.
It's so much fun.
(girl)
Crispo!
(boy)
(girl)
Crispo!
Put your hand down.
'Cause you know
what else is fun?
Low fives.
(girl)
Crispo!
Saving the caged raccoon
in Mr. Slinko's class.
He looks so sad.
I got just the thing
to get the job done.
(thundering)
(animal growling)
Here we go.
♪♪
The coast is clear.
Operation: Stay Friends Forever
is going super smooth.
By the end of second period,
we were all back together.
I even made a new friend.
Okay, we just have to
get you on our cart,
disguise you as our
secret science fair project,
then roll you outside
to freedom.
Um, raccoons
don't speak English.
Just get him
on the cart.
(chirping)
Hey, you.
Don't hide those eyes.
(record scratching)
Uh...
Hey, Mindy,
what's up?
Crispo's cool cred,
thanks to me.
♪♪
And just like that, the plan
started falling apart.
The plan
is falling apart!
I just said that.
We lost our lookout!
The coast
is still clear.
Oh my gosh.
Still clear.
Ooh, he's heavy.
(chirping)
(glass breaking)
Get you on the cart.
(clunking)
(CJ)
A little help!
I told you this would
only lead to trouble.
And I can't
have trouble!
There's no trouble.
Do you see
any trouble?
(school bell ringing)
(door closing)
♪♪
(bird squawking)
Huh.
(woman)
Well, well, well.
Cutting your first class on
the first day of school?
What do you have to
say for yourselves?
This is all
her fault!
♪♪
Names, now.
Uh, names?
What are names?
I'm so--
I don't know what--
I don't understand.
CJ Martin
and Fenwick Fraser,
who must've gotten lost
on their way to class.
I don't
trust their faces.
I can read faces,
it's a gift.
He's right.
We're so lost.
We are so lost
and so sorry.
Where are we?
Your new "princiaplness."
The bow is nice.
I like the bow.
Students, meet the new leader
of Pootatuck Middle School,
Principal Hader.
But perhaps you should
call me Principal Changer
due to all the changes
I'm making to old PMS.
New floors, new ceilings
and a brand-new
administration facility.
You mean new
principal's office.
No, it's an
administration facility.
Principal's office.
It's an
administration facility.
But it's mostly
a principal's--
Allow me to explain.
Our school has always had an
amazing eighth grade patio.
Eighth graders loved it.
And us seventh graders couldn't
wait to get it.
But this year... it's gone.
And in its place is a
construction site nicknamed...
(all)
The Death Star.
The board wanted me
to have it!
All I want is for
everyone's first day back
to be so great
you chant my name.
(children chanting)
Hader, Hader, Hader...
Us too.
Good!
I can think of
100 things you could say
to me right now
before you... walk...
That's cool.
Catch you later,
my...
my BFF!
Hey!
Where's my cart?
♪♪
(school bell ringing)
Are you aware that
Henry Slinko
has a raccoon
in his classroom?
It's in a cage!
What's your point?
Uh, I guess it would be
that a feral raccoon
in school is bad.
Hmm,
here's what's bad.
This school's test scores.
Parents who forget
to sign their
child's
gym release form.
And my new administration
facility,
which is not done yet!
(truck beeping)
Well, I don't know,
I think the Death Star's
coming along nicely.
Do I threaten you,
Mr. Roberts?
A woman boss
about the same age?
Wait, who calls this
the Death Star?
The same ones that
call you Darth Hader.
(gasping)
I will bring order to
this school, I assure you.
(truck beeping)
And get that beeping
thing away from me!
If anything
happens to my office,
I don't have the funds
to replace it.
(truck beeping)
And you.
Your job is to
guide students, not me,
so go... guide them.
You know
where the door is.
I'll just use
the wall.
♪♪
(CJ)
So next period, as the entire
eighth grade gave up hope
of saving
their beloved patio..
(all gasping)
... I did not give up hope
on saving my friendships
or saving that raccoon.
(chirping)
No.
And yes,
I'm prone to adventure,
but your plans always
lead to trouble.
What?
Name three.
The Pudding Incident,
the Glasgow Fiasco,
Ice Hallway.
Okay, good memory.
But I can think of a hundred
reasons why we should--
Besides,
Crispo's gone.
Her Highness Mindy Minus
has pulled him into
the gorgeous vortex.
(boy)
Crispo!
♪♪
(giggling)
It is a cool jacket.
I picked out
that jacket!
♪♪
Oh no, she's coming!
Don't look
into her eyes.
Whatever you guys are up to
sounds weird
and I don't like it.
Crispo is going to be the most
popular boy in the school
and even though he doesn't
know it yet, we're dating.
That's not dating.
Our love is real!
So stay away from him
or I will come down on you
like Paul Shmalter on
sixth graders.
♪♪
(siren blaring)
(chuckling menacingly)
How many things
have to go wrong
before you realize your
plan is dangerous?
I don't know,
nine?
(Crispo)
This book is good.
Boy, I sure
like books.
Crispo?
Keep talking,
but look at Fen, not me.
Uh, okay, but why
are we doing this?
Meet me at the first floor
water fountain
if you
want to know more.
Do we have to go?
Keep talking.
(Crispo)
Look, Mindy told me that
I had to choose between
you guys and her.
But I don't
want to choose.
I love you guys.
But Mindy's
so pretty.
So I'm hiding
behind a book.
Okay, but...
there's a raccoon trapped in
a cage that needs our help.
So what are we
gonna do about it?
Go back to my intense studies
and stay out of trouble.
Mindy smells
like strawberries.
So would the raccoon
if it wore lip gloss.
And what if it has a raccoon
wife and raccoon kids
and they're all scared
'cause Dad didn't come home
from his raccoon job?
What else you got?
This is middle school.
This is our time to
get crazy and live life.
I've seen the future
and nobody has time
for anything.
So what
do you say?
One last adventure.
If it doesn't work out,
you can go back to your
intense studies and you
can go back to stra--
Fine, I'll do it.
You had me at
"raccoon kids."
(school bell ringing)
Okay, so science class was
pretty straightforward.
Slinko gave us the standard
"What do you remember from
last year?" test.
Crispo used the time to
invent secret hand code signals
that we did not understand.
Mark Chernoff
completely failed at
the cover-your-fart-with-a-cough
move.
(farting)
(coughing)
(school bell ringing)
Then the bell rang
and we get back to our story.
(chirping)
He's been taunting me
for years.
But this year I got him.
Raccoons
don't hold grudges.
They're looking for food
and a mate all the time.
Oh, not this one.
This one wants me.
Which is
why after school,
he is entering my raccoon
relocation program.
Wait, what's that?
It's where I drop him off
100 miles away
from this school
and my rhubarb
experiments.
(Crispo)
What about his raccoon wife
and raccoon kids?
Then I guess Mom's coaching
raccoon soccer this year.
(chuckling)
But, allow me to give him
one last view of the game.
Aren't you
gonna leave?
Now?
With the door
wide open?
Not after
my cart disappeared.
Out!
Okay.
Minor setback.
(Crispo)
Relax.
All we need is
a sky elevator
or rocket boots.
Get up to that window...
pull cage out said
window onto sky elevator
or rocket boots,
then lower Mr. Raccoony
to freedom.
You can't be serious.
(animal growling)
Do you see
the sunglasses?
Okay, one small problem.
There's no such thing
as sky elevators
or rocket boots!
(chirping)
(truck beeping)
What about a crane?
Okay, stay
with that for now.
All right, everybody,
that's lunch.
♪♪
The plan was simple.
Well, not simple,
but potentially doable.
Because our parents didn't sign
our release forms,
we couldn't
participate in gym class.
Now sit on the bench
and feel bad
while we all have fun
running and sweating and
breathing in field dust.
(coughing)
Make a hole.
(whistle blowing)
We didn't sit long.
(CJ)
Go, go, go!
Oh, do not
try this at home.
Looking out.
And by lowering the bucket
just 42 centimeters,
Crispo would be able to
pull the raccoon onto the crane
then I lower him to freedom.
(gears grinding)
Ooh!
Wrong lever.
♪♪
Okay, just sit down
and don't
touch anything!
(engine revving)
It butt starts?
Shut it off!
It won't
butt shut off!
Stand back!
Never mind!
(screaming)
Hit that, hit that!
Turn it off,
turn it off!
♪♪
Jump off!
Just jump off!
In case you were still
wondering,
this was not part of the plan.
(CJ)
Okay, if you're just joining us,
here's a quick recap.
The night before
my first day of seventh grade,
a singing high school dream
informed me that...
♪ High school's hard
and miserable ♪
♪ You'll lose your
friends from middle school ♪♪
So I decided to keep my
friends together
with one
last adventure--
freeing this raccoon.
My smart BFF agreed to join me,
reluctantly.
And my newly
popular BFF agreed to join us,
as long as we're not
seen together.
Which resumes our story here,
with our new principal about to
enter her new administration
facility.
(engine rumbling)
(screaming)
Okay, bad news.
We just destroyed
Darth Hader's new office.
But good news,
we got the eighth grade
patio back.
(cheering)
Hey!
Hey, you!
Again, the bad news.
Okay.
I know I'm the smartest
kid in school,
but what do we do?
We did what every responsible
student should do
when they've
made an honest mistake.
Oh...
Split up!
♪♪
You, find them!
Two medium ones and a tally,
all wearing gym clothes.
Lady, it's not our
job to hunt down kids in--
Do it!
Who is that?
Paul Shmalter,
the hall monitor.
Put down those sixth graders
and bring me anyone
wearing gym clothes
who is not in gym class.
Hey, you.
You off to
sixth period?
You bet I am!
♪♪
Okay, hide,
just hide.
(whimpering)
You don't
need the book!
What we need is to change out
of these clothes
and get to
Spanish class.
(school bell ringing)
Which we are now
officially cutting.
(door opening)
♪♪
This looks bad, right?
Yeah.
It was an accident.
But, hey,
it's middle school!
Time to try new things--
hundreds of things-- and learn
from our mistakes, right?
But this one thing
got out of hand and, boy,
have we learned a lot.
And it was my fault--
don't blame them.
Wait, are you
telling me that--
They smashed it
with a tractor.
Three of them:
two boys, one girl.
W-was the girl
wearing red sneakers?
I don't have specifics!
Then how can
I help you?
(clunking)
You know what?
I don't want your
help finding them.
You sure about that?
And I don't need
your help.
I'm Principal Changer.
I'm changing
this school.
And I will think
about making some changes
to my guidance staff
in the future!
Okay, as your
guidance counselor,
allow me to guide you.
Out this window,
then along the side of
the building to the last door
on your right.
There you will find
the lost-and-found bin
from last year.
Put found clothes
over your gym clothes
and when you get to class,
you tell your teacher
you were with me,
which I will confirm.
What kind of
guidance counselor are you?
♪♪
The totally awesome
and probably future-fired kind.
Now, stay low
and good luck.
Wait.
Won't the sidewalks be crawling
with construction workers
and Principal Hader?
Yes.
So, uh, let's
think about that
and try to come up with
a solution.
♪♪
Remember, they are
wearing gym clothes.
And they are evil.
Happy hunting,
fellas.
All right, let's go.
Here we go,
split up!
♪♪
Jackpot!
Quick, put the clothes on
and let's get to class.
♪♪
(gasping)
Stop right there!
(record scratching)
♪♪
(chuckling)
Oh, I got you.
♪♪
(meowing)
And lookee
what Crispo found
(animal growling)
in the lost and found.
We don't need
sunglasses!
(man)
They gotta be
around here somewhere.
(man)
Got it, got it.
Yo!
Hey, right there!
Go, go, go!
Get 'em, let's get 'em!
Slow-motion would really enhance
this moment, don't you think?
♪♪
♪ Ugh ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Ugh ♪
♪ Shake it, shake it ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Ugh ♪
♪ Shake it, shake it ♪
♪ Shake what you got ♪
♪ Ugh ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Ugh ♪♪
Move!
♪♪
(CJ)
Come on!
(all panting)
I feel so alive!
Good.
Because those of us
not on Planet Crispo,
we're dead!
That way, that way,
that way.
Wait.
This is my mom's car.
(beeping)
(CJ)
Come on, come on,
let's go, let's go.
Go, go, move, move!
Ow, my foot!
Check over there!
Okay.
I can think of
a hundred things
you'd rather be doing
right now, but--
Get down, get down!
Relax.
My dad got the tinted windows
and ultra-quiet package.
Really?
Hello!
We're in here!
(man)
Hey, I lost my shoe!
I'm a construction man,
somebody
ran over my building!
Get down!
I said relax.
They can't see in.
(man)
Not over here.
Let's go, let's...
What about her?
(cell phone vibrating)
"Hey, sweetie, just dropped
off your gym release.
XOXOX"-- Oh.
♪♪
There were three of them
in the parking lot.
But we lost them.
Perfect.
Because that means
they're not in class.
So I just have to wait for
sixth period attendance
to be returned and the three
that are missing will be mine.
Then I will expel
the office-destroying
delinquents from this school
and be cheered.
(children chanting)
Hader, Hader,
Hader, Hader, Hader...
♪♪
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Oh, hi, hon.
Yeah, um,
I dropped off CJ's form
and I stopped by the house
to grab a snack
and feed the fish.
Yeah.
Everyone looked like they were
having a really happy first day.
♪♪
(door closing)
We are not happy.
Instead of being in
sixth period Spanish,
we are at su casa!
(CJ)
Just to reiterate, this was
definitely not the plan.
Ooh, water pita!
Don't eat that.
♪♪
Why did you have to
rescue a raccoon?
I mean, why not
do something easy
like steal a school bus or
kidnap Gym Coach LaBeau?
Is Coach LaBeau
a dude or a woman?
It doesn't matter as long
as he/she is happy.
Makes sense.
Why did you have to
rescue a raccoon?
Hey, you agreed
to do it.
Guys, chill.
I just want her
to tell us why.
It's not just about rescuing
the raccoon, okay?
It's about rescuing us.
♪♪
My brother and this
singing dream/nightmare
said that middle school
friendships
don't make it
to high school.
And I didn't want that
happening to us.
Why would you think
we wouldn't stay friends?
Yeah, we're gonna
be friends forever.
Liars.
You said, "See you after
graduation."
And you're hiding our
friendship behind a book.
You still have
Angelica?
Cool sunglasses.
It's her beach look.
And she's
my good luck charm.
We rescued her the first day
of kindergarten, remember?
And she likes hugs.
I like hugs.
Don't you dare--
CJ.
♪♪
This is nice.
Besides, what does
Ronbie know about
high school, anyways?
I know
it's horrifying.
But you get out at
2:00.
Now why are you here
and is Fen
wearing my pants?
Maybe.
It's a long story
that starts with us
destroying the new
principal's office
while trying to
free a raccoon
and ends
with us in Mom's car
getting expelled once
Mrs. Knapp hands in
sixth period attendance.
Cat-Knapp
still teaches Spanish?
Cat-Knapp?
She's like 90 years old
and sleeps all class long.
(snoring)
You don't have to
worry about attendance.
She never takes it.
So you're saying if
we get back to school
by seventh period,
the crazy new principal
won't know we were gone?
Yep.
♪♪
(animal growling)
We've got seven minutes.
Why are you all
looking at me like that?
(tires screeching)
Can't this thing
go any faster?
(rock music blaring)
The speed limit is
15 miles per hour
and do you
see the potholes?
(tires screeching)
Change the station,
I hate this song.
(classical music playing)
(snoring)
(school bell ringing)
Can you stop?
Look, the speed limit
is 35!
(tires screeching)
(all)
Yeah!
(tires screeching)
(all)
No!
Pass her,
you've gotta pass her!
With minors in the car.
You want me to
lose my license?!
We've got
three minutes!
Angelica
will lead the way!
CJ said she was
good luck.
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
She is good luck.
Have you seen
Crispo?
No.
What are you doing?
Go back, go back!
You passed the school!
(tires screeching)
(screaming)
Front door's
always locked,
but the maintenance door
is always open.
Move!
♪♪
(CJ)
Love you!
Love you too.
I can't hold
Angelica anymore.
He's still going
with the book?
♪♪
(Crispo)
Hey, there you are.
Let's get to seventh period
totally on time.
♪♪
(panting)
Where were you
and what are you wearing?
I was in the bathroom.
For an hour?
Yeah, it was so bad
I had to change my clothes.
(gasping)
(chirping)
What are you doing?
We're gonna
make it!
No!
No raccoon!
The door's open!
Which means
Slinko's coming back!
It's looking at me!
It's giving me
the look.
It's not about saving
the raccoon, remember?
It's about saving us.
And we have
10 seconds to save us.
No, do not go
into that...
(school bell ringing)
Welcome to study hall.
Open your books...
study.
If you have to go
to the bathroom, go nuts.
(CJ grunting)
Come on,
gotta get you free.
Hello, CJ.
Decide to skip
study hall?
Uh, no, I...
This is Paul Shmalter,
the hall monitor.
I have a class cutter
by the name of...
Anybody need help...
or sunglasses?
We don't need
sunglasses!
We just let him go while
the halls are empty,
guide him down the
stairs to an open door.
But I can't
get it open.
I know what to do!
Help her.
Move!
Ready?
Be free!
(chirping)
(toilet flushing)
♪♪
(screeching)
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
Huh.
Raccoons do hold grudges.
(screaming)
(all screaming)
(screaming continues)
We've done
a good job here today.
Fire!
There must be a fire!
No, no, no!
(fire alarm ringing)
Side note:
Never pull a fire alarm
unless you are positive
you see a fire.
And not
a loose raccoon.
(screaming continues)
(woman on PA)
Fire alarm detected.
Please move quickly
to the exits.
(Hader)
Remain calm.
Remain calm, everyone.
Good,
go to the exits.
(all screaming)
Remain calm!
Remain calm,
for goodness sakes!
(screaming continues)
(sirens blaring)
Heck of
a first day back.
All right,
go on this way.
(screaming)
Oh!
♪♪
Well,
that was easy.
(Hader)
Well, look who it is again.
You two.
With another kid who has
a book in front of his face.
Principal Hader.
There was a...
a raccoon in the hall,
but we let it out the door.
Good thing
we were here.
Oh, really?
Is that what happened here,
new kid whose face
I can't see or trust?
(Crispo)
We like doing good things
for our school
that we love.
Things.
What is that?
What is it saying?
What he means is
the confidence
and strength you project
inspires us all to
do great things.
Thank you.
Well,
you're welcome.
I am here to inspire.
And might I suggest
early dismissal.
We've had a lot
of excitement today
and I think you'll win
even more students
with your compassion.
(whispering)
Do it before
somebody dies.
I am compassionate too.
Hader, Hader, Hader...
(all chanting)
Hader, Hader, Hader,
Hader, Hader, Hader...
Oh, early
dismissal, everyone!
(school bell ringing)
(all cheering)
Principal Hader!
I saw them,
the three of them!
All in--
Shut it, Paul.
I'm being cheered.
(cheering)
(Hader)
Up high.
Principal Changer
in the house!
Well, thanks for that,
uh, one last adventure.
I guess it's back to your
studies and back to your book.
See you around.
Seriously,
you're leaving?
(Crispo)
'Cause if we're gonna stay
friends forever,
we're gonna need
a lot more one-last adventures.
Well, this is
middle school,
the time to live life
and try new things.
How many things?
I can think of
a hundred.
(Crispo)
Ooh!
Then we're
gonna need these.
(animal growling)
So looking back,
do I recommend freeing a raccoon
on your first day of school?
Yeah!
Because I learned that no matter
how bad things get,
we have the power
to make things better.
I learned that with friends by
your side, you can do anything.
And I learned that slow-motion
makes everything look cool.
♪♪
But if you don't have
a raccoon in your homeroom,
try just getting out of your
comfort zone.
Sure, it might
get a little crazy,
but isn't that the point?
And the biggest thing I learned
from my singing dream
is that these are
the greatest years of our lives,
so let's make sure
we break out.
All you need is
a little courage,
a couple of good friends--
oh, and don't forget
the sunglasses.
One down and 99 to go.