Here we have 121 divided by 9,
Then we get Y,
Someone?
That there is a replacement, meaning
cell phones are not allowed,
No cell phones among the l ,,, es,
No cell phone during class,
Mr, Lawrence,
Yes, Speaking,
Yes, 4 secondary school, literature,
Tomorrow, Excellent, Yes, Thanks,
No cell phones,
Jessica and I made love,
Now it's weird, What should I do?
It seems that Mr, Lawrence three
days in Vegas partying,
Thanks for the notice,
Jimmy, Put it away,
Let's go back to work,
Beautiful, Laugh at him, Perfect,
Kiss her on the cheek,
This is a great place for
engagement photos, Thank you, Graham,
You're welcome, Is your relationship
stable than I will ever have,
That's right,
Oops, Sorry, I have these
receive, Hello, darling,
Do not call me 'baby',
- What's wrong with that?
Nicknames for couples,
- Sure, And do we have?
Not exactly courtship,
- But what do we have?
A conversation?
- Yes, we are talking to each other,
We do not go out with each other,
- Wait, What?
I do not talk about this now, but
can you do me a favor?
Want to have lunch with me?
I left my card at home lying,
Sure, And then to The Mill?
Something to eat and maybe karaoke?
Maybe I should go,
Can you hurry? I'm hungry,
Yes, I love you,
Eskimo Kisses,
That was my girlfriend,
We are in love, so ,,, smile,
Sorry,
- Yes?
Hypothetically, if a young bachelor
The literature teacher would vervangen-
which book here would be him
best help?
I think this is best,
- Oh, "Vampire Bats",
Amazing, Very helpful,
Are you a replacement?
How well do you get there from, but yes,
Hello, my name is Quinn,
Hello, T,J,
- Nice to meet you,
Say, that's not a job for a
65-year-old hearing-impaired lady?
Yes, Or for science students
who have to pay their education,
I've never seen before,
- I just started as a teacher,
Third grade social studies,
- Henderson's class?
Yes,
- I replaced her last month,
Gabe Willis, Real asshole,
- Yeah, a terrible guy,
Can you give him a slap?
- For you, for me, for America,
Good, Before you do that, may I
have number, miss ,,,
T,J,
Ms, Hanson sounds so out,
You do not give
fake phone?
If so, can you my real
get tonight at The Mill,
Karaoke Friday, We see each other there,
- Okay, that's fine,
How are you?
How was the shoot?
Pay more than the technical
college, How did it go for you?
Only a shovel in my crotch,
- Progress,
You have exactly three minutes,
I have an important meeting,
Of course, Mr, Millan ,,,
- No no no,
It is Professor Millan,
I have not been to six universities
studied to be called Mr, Millan,
Professor Millan, we think
we more working formulas have-
which can be thought
predict and influence them,
Mind Control?
- The term has a bad name ,,, yes,
- Yes,
This is not only
a dead end,
But I expect one more realistic
project of my students,
We have only a little more
equipment necessary for research,
We wondered, or hoped,
To give us a recommendation for
a scholarship could give,
$ 10,000?
- To start with,
Yes sir,
We wrote a proposal,
We typing it out,
This is our ,,,
- This copy is for you,
A preliminary copy,
- I should have typing,
Gentlemen,
I'm here to help you,
I want to help as much as possible,
But I can such projects
not finance,
You sit in the top 10%, There
you would benefit from them,
But we need your approval
needed to get started,
When the next budget round
could think of us?
Then we talk it down,
- Good idea, I could do that,
But I'm too busy
for childish experimentation,
Is it a ,,, maybe ,,,
- No,
I have not heard right,
- It is definitely no,
Like you,
- So ,,,
- See if we have forgotten nothing,
A nice day,
That could have been better,
- I met my dream girl,
Good for you,
I am very happy for you,
I recognize that tone of yours,
- What makes it so obvious?
How's Amy?
- Good, It goes well with us,
We can have a very good bunch
be, very soon,
We have great fun together,
- Awesome,
And then she's going out with someone, and I
hear from her friends,
That's not easy,
I miss you very easily with a
girl was laughing, watching a movie,
Gluten-free ecological
Share rice cakes,
That is no longer,
- No, And you wanna know why?
News:The '60s are over,
It is not that way anymore,
It is not so,
You know what would go?
And what to do now? Fuck,
That may sound wrong,
Girls fuck until you find one
which is not as crazy as the rest,
You know, you are wrong,
I feel sorry for you,
I'm not wrong,
and I feel sorry for you,
I want that big moment,
We meet on the street
rain and kissing unabashedly,
That's my wish list,
- That you have to throw away,
Throw away your wishlist,
That is shameful,
You're already now how long behind it
girl ,,, a year?
More than one year,
- How long do you keep that up?
I have calculated, She is literally
65% of my perfect mate,
We both love
Quantum Leap,
That's ,,, As far as I'm with her,
I have to give it a chance,
Do you understand the cooking system
Sitzmans for class?
Thermal fluids
are a complete mystery,
I do not understand,
- I only know the words,
Guys, how are you?
They say nowadays,
Why are not you at work?
I wanted to say
you guys look sexy today,
Great combination, Which
jeans is good, Graham,
Lee, what's going on?
Honestly, Okay, Sam Beckett
has escaped from his cage,
I have a vague
and general idea where he is,
You hear African rattlesnake
crawling around in our apartment?
Technically speaking?
- No, given exactly,
The answer to both is yes,
He can be there,
I'm 99 ,,, 84, 85 percent sure
that he is not in the kitchen,
But you know
how I am with technique,
I want to meter hose not around
feel crawl tonight,
You said 'meter hose,
I thought as a gay,
I mean it when I say that I do for you
save your eyes and make blind,
Guys, we go to the city and
you treat yourself to a drink,
And we forget
this whole event,
Sorry we're late, T-Sizzle
had to get sand out of his taco,
I have a project for Andersons
done, and now I'm ready,
What kind of project?
Making love with a boy?
That's never homework,
sex with the boys,
We can relax tonight?
Girls score? Do you see that one?
Are you the party and
bachelor life never was?
No!
- Never, Why do you ask that?
Daryl, you're 37,
you are not too old for this life?
Go ahead,
First, I'm 39 and,
second, never in my life,
No one can pin down,
- Pound for pound,
And if you are girls kings
you are not even princes,
You are now more than a year
in that zone friendship with Amy?
I do not like that, We have
all problems with girls,
Rachel and I have half a year
ago broke,
I inherited her hose and the whole
time herrinnerd her face,
And her skin,
And her hugs,
They are so warm,
It's so ,,, present,
You have a voice like an angel,
I saw Derek a birthmark
has on its left hand,
Mr, substitute, How are you?
- And you, professor?
You deserve a drink after a long
day with Gabe Willis,
There is more needed,
- We forget Gabe Willis,
Ladies and germs,
for the fourteenth week
sing the 'Three Wise Men'
"Crimson and Clover",
Everything good? I'm Dirty D!
- Everything okay?
He's a friend, Do not worry,
- I did not say anything,
You give me that look
- That look?
That look,
- What look?
Such "I loathe you
and you find a slet'-look,
That look,
- Does this look better?
Amy, is this look better?
- That is none better,
That felt good,
- You're so immature,
You're immature,
- You talk to a lot of girls,
Listen, We can not assume
and having fun?
Say that again,
- Can we have fun?
Say it with a different accent,
Good kiss,
- Shut up,
You should keep your mouth shut,
- You gotta keep your mouth shut, Bitch,
Come now, T, J!
- Another few minutes,
Owning an Indian
restaurant is on my wish list,
Is that on your wish list?
- I'll show you,
I have my wishlist always with me,
Not really,
- That's crazy,
This is very crazy,
- What's on yours?
Are extra, I want a movie
figure, In a disaster,
I want to be as a person
which runs for his life,
That, or in a film
with Jason Statham,
And a disaster
with Jason Statham?
A dream that becomes real,
Professional golf tournament?
- I played golf at school,
A dream to play professionally,
- I've never waved,
Have not you ever played golf?
- T, J,, come, We go now,
Another few minutes,
No, I do it in my pants
if I do not see Derek, I'm going now,
She is ,,,
Want another shot?
- Yes please,
This is better than Christmas,
Can I touch it?
- Do not touch the buttons,
I do as I want,
- That they he told me,
We are in love,
Everybody, we're in love,
We are not in love,
- When we first met ,,,
You, T, J,
We would ,,,
tomorrow to go play golf,
I do not have time,
To prepare lessons,
Look,
T,J, learn ,,,
You must sooner or later things
by stripes, right?
Can you tomorrow? Yes?
Good Evening,
- Good Evening,
I've seen that,
It was ,,, fore!
Hi, How are you?
- Good, You've come,
Would I do?
- Yes,
Shall we?
- Yeah, let's go play golf,
How very good you are,
I'm kidding,
- I should hope,
You have to hit it in the water,
Therefore more here,
Graham, how are these
fantastic morning with you?
Not as good as you,
- No? What is going on?
I spent $ 250 yesterday,
- $ 250 on drinks?
No, On taxis
Amy went with me, She was a
little drunk, No problem,
She talked about NSync and stuff,
Boybands interest me anything,
They are bigger than One
Direction, The future is uncertain,
Is she angry, Take a taxi to
home, I'm going after her,
Come back here, Arguing
about the same, five, six times,
Goodness,
- They must be mature,
As a consolation:T,J, and I had
another great night,
You and the teacher, You see each other
billions of times this month,
30 billion and once,
If you do not play golf, you're going
the film or antiquarian,
I see sides of you I never
seen, You playboy, Go away,
Stop, Continue,
- All right, go ahead,
Did not know we had milk,
- You must be dehydrated,
Is that almond milk?
- Lee? What are you doing?
Lee! What are you doing?
- I create a snake-friendly environment,
And if I play Jason Mraz,
then the right,
Snakes love Jason Mraz,
- Time for me to go,
Lots of fun,
Thanks again for the food,
- I find it to be fine with you,
You know, we do this for a while now,
And I thought ,,,
You do know that ,,,
Maybe we can officially ,,,
- Listen, Quinn,
Okay, I do not want you
give the wrong impression,
I like to go with you
and I'm glad I met you,
But I am at the moment
not looking for anything serious,
I am now in the friend zone?
This is not the right time,
- It's a terrible time,
You are a giant guy,
- You're a fine fellow,
I see you as a good friend,
- Yes, friend,
It's not the right time,
- You know, I think you're cute,
It should not feel uncomfortable,
- I do not have feelings at all,
You know, So ,,,
- I'm sorry I encouraged you,
No no no,
Do not be silly,
Do not be silly, Do not,
You decide how to proceed,
- It's okay,
I'm cool, you're cool,
We are cool,
Great, but now I have to
off, Thanks for the food,
Thank you, Hug,
Shit,
Hello Friend,
I saw what happened,
I sat in the bushes,
I just want to say
what you mean to me,
As I stood there,
I googled how to comfort a friend,
And the first thing you say is:
"I am your friend,"
And the second?
- The second is ,,,
"I'm always ready for you,"
And then:"You are not alone,"
You do not want her, She has narrow
hips, Not good to give birth,
You want one with wide hips,
Then they shoot out,
You have a good physique,
Now we have done it,
and it was great,
When I think of people
who do-
they are usually more than that,
if you know what I mean,
Stop, I would not want to talk about it,
I'm just saying
that we should consider it,
Therefore, we should not see each other
see, I do not be fooled,
And I want our friendship
do not ruin it,
And you means a lot to me,
Therefore, we must consider it,
Can not we just chill?
You know, just chilling out,
That's a new adjective
noun for this relationship,
Yes, Walk on road
difficult conversations,
It is not a difficult conversation
if you have it every day,
With T,J, and that stupid snake
this is the last thing I want to do now,
This is the correct distraction above,
Ready?
Here we go, The goal is that Lee
gives you a thousand dollars,
Remember that it's not mind control
is, but influence,
You should affect him
he gives you the money,
When we were filming this, we get the
Professor Milan Stock Exchange,
Then we go to work,
Lee! What is it for there, buddy?
- Awesome,
Nice of you to come here,
This we should do more often,
So ,,, okay,
I'm hypnotized or something?
- No,
I was once hypnotized,
That was fantastic,
It was hilarious, I thought I
was a dog and had a tail,
Is that the end of the story?
- Yes, Dog and tail,
Lee, can I borrow a thousand dollars?
- No, I do not have a thousand dollars,
And your parents?
- I'm now between jobs,
And women, You would give me a
tussenman call,
Are you therefore come? Around me
thousand dollars to extort?
We call Lee ,,,
- I get a thousand dollars or not?
No, I have no money,
and my father either,
He may earn 12,500 with
bottling its own water,
He distributes it,
The hot tap,
Lee, would you help me? We are
friends and I need your help,
You're the only one I can
questions, Can you help me?
I can not say which, and
pay you back as soon as possible,
No, I'm sorry, but
I do not have a thousand dollars,
Listen, if it's any consolation,
I would have made love with you,
You said it, and I enjoyed ,,,,
I saw the two of us together,
- We call Trent,
I do not quite see naked,
But you should do so,
Test this nonsense on a girl,
That is guaranteed,
Then we go to work,
- Find that snake, okay?
I do not like this rejection,
Go with someone,
I should've kissed you,
On the mouth,
What?
- Nothing,
He sounded so convincing,
'I want to make love to you',
Was he serious?
- He'd kiss you on the mouth,
Does he really want me here with women
go seduce? I'm mature,
This is technique,
We do not use math
formula to pick up women,
We use it to T,J, and Amy
love let us be,
That is too crazy for words,
Crass, Too much fun,
Very nice,
I find it wonderful to have fun,
- Really?
My evening is not perfect
if I do not get your number,
If I may get ,,,
Absolutely,
I think I know you,
Or not,
You're totally my type,
- What?
I think I love you,
You do not know me, creep,
I am ready,
- 7, 4, 6,
7, 4, 6,
- 8, 2, 9,
8, 2, 9,
- 7 3,
7, 3,
- 4,
4,
- 6, 4,
7, 9, 4, 5,
Those are 14 digits ,,,
You're not here,
Can I pour something?
I want to have a nice evening,
Only a rose,
- That's why you should choose me ,
I know all the vice presidents,
Ignore him, I have a tree house
I've been working on for 14 years,
I love Bette Midler,
- Me too, I do Jazzercise,
Look, The angle between its head
and shoulder is 60 degrees,
What does it mean?
- Increased interest,
We have to think of questions,
- Hey guys,
That is old, we may issue
look this week?
Yes, I fast forward,
- No,
I want to see if Marissa Steve and Paul
choose, For the study,
Why? Steve is at the end
this episode turned away,
Thanks, That's my melon,
- That I wanted to distribute,
But it's a good episode,
We need to simplify it,
Delete does not mean anything,
Social status, Family history,
Perfume,
Only the most important,
Good news, guys,
- Did you find the snake?
No, he's here somewhere,
But I started for myself,
Cool,
People on celebrities
sell similar chips on eBay?
You know?
- Yes ,,,
In the kitchen looking for food
that looks like celebrities,
Then I can be here all day
search for Sam Beckett,
That still does not succeed,
That's not a job,
That's certainly a job,
What is this?
What have we here?
Sometimes they are hard to find,
Like these,
My goodness, is that Willem Dafoe?
That's him, I think,
25! 30! 75! $ 400!
7 million dollars!
There's the rent,
There is a new car,
We see something overlooked,
Under what circumstances
she looked away?
Yes, she looked at her friend,
she looked at me, Recalibrate I 95%,
That's not it,
No, That's not it,
That's us,
What?
- The opposite risk of errors,
It is not the women,
We are, We are the X-factor,
We must distinguish ourselves
of the other men,
You flirt already two minutes, but
do not drink offered yet,
I do not even know your name,
Why would I flirt with you?
Slow down, prospector,
- My name is Libby,
I'm alright, Begin with
the elements of Euclid,
The principle of Archimedes,
The Cartesian coordinates,
What?
- What are we doing?
We observe,
- Yes,
Look, What is he doing now? Step 1,
- A girl find to take,
No, trust is step one,
Step 2?
- Step 2 is jealousy,
I was just saying,
J-A-L-O-E-S-I-E,
I want to be a heartbreaker,
I play along during the interview,
Oh okay,
That's Foot Doctor,
Loves 80s music,
That's High Heels, Nice girl,
but no sense of humor,
That's Reader, Likes classical
novels, Only drink wine,
I owe them something,
You're number four on my list,
Why does Libby
I offered her a drink?
P measured along the horizontal
perpendicular line from P to Y-axis,
Do not look to the breasts,
Mass to maintain balance,
Stirs in her glass, I'm sitting
the compression ratio?
Hi, I see you staring at me,
Heavens, what a big breasts,
Poor back,
The concept of forbidden fruit,
You want what you can not have,
What is she?
You must be jealous say
She must be happy now,
I do not know if you're serious,
- That's my secret,
Look,
- What?
I drew one pilgrim on one napkin,
Look what he has on his head,
He talks to her,
- It is a pilgrim penis hat,
Consider yourself a superstar?
- No, Does a superstar this?
Yes,
- Yes, It works,
You did damn,
- Shit, It works,
What works?
- We did it,
We have to go,
We need to document this,
Where are you going?
This is a pilgrim penis hat,
It has a buckle and a hat ,,,
- Shut up,
We tell someone?
- Not yet,
No, Not yet,
I'm T,J, call,
- What? No!
We would not tell you, That is
the worst thing you can do,
Why?
- We do not know if it works,
We tested it and it works,
- We tested it once,
Putting the Wright brothers immediately
300 people in a jumbo jet?
I suggest that we first here
a bit of fun to go along stairs,
It is not to decorate,
- You're wrong,
If your chances with T,J, want
screw up, go ahead,
Flush it if you want,
but do not take me,
What do you suggest?
- We will first slow,
Seeing in perspective,
We are young and single,
We just mathematician
minimized uncertainty,
We must first
solve a few things,
Then we can the ladies love
let it be us, Well?
Okay, But once it works, I call T,J,
Because this is ,,, science,
- This is technique,
I want to return this shirt,
- Of course, no problem,
It's too tight,
Okay ,,,
Okay, very beautiful,
You've won the lottery,
You can now pay for that trip,
Amazing, You are a
attractive bunch,
Honestly, you're the
attractive couple ever,
What size you usually wear?
- Extra ,,, extra ,,, extra ,,, large,
Thanks again,
We are very curious,
The pleasure is all mine,
How long have you been dating?
A Tuesday year,
That you stand it so long with him,
I was sitting by him long ago,
And it is only 60% cotton,
I want 100%,
Cotton,
Do you want your money back,
or do you want to exchange for one-
XXXL shirt cotton?
Can I return the money
and decide later?
No problem,
- Put it on my card,
You are incredibly attractive,
Our band is now stronger,
I agree with that, Steve?
- You two should have lunch,
Thank you,
- I'm sorry, friend,
Wait, What is going on?
Caught in time jumps
Dr, Beckett of life to life-
and corrects mistakes, hoping
he jumps back home,
Daniel Craig,
Nothing in this,
Cheers,
This tastes so good that costs flat
more than the entree,
I can only drink water,
- He's an alcoholic,
Not something for a first date,
But I struggle with it now,
It's okay if you get to know me,
- It affects his life,
Here it goes well,
but later he gets a relapse,
I grab your napkin,
Shelly did you kiss?
- I thought she was mine,
She is yours, And she is 70,
- I know,
Cozy, It was cozy,
I go bungee jumping with Crystal,
- Crystal is great,
They parachuted last week,
Unbelievable,
I have this on potato
Anne Hathaway seems sold,
Hello, who's there?
Is that opportunity that calling? Yes!
He eats all of Snickers, And say
then:"I'm late for work,"
Hungry? Why wait until you
fired? Very sad,
He gives the homeless a dollar,
Appears to be the Gerald Ford,
Since in the gutter, Crazy,
Del, Slut, Slut,
What is your educational philosophy
to form young minds?
The mind of a child is beautiful,
Not yet filled with hatred and disgust
where the world is full of them,
But with love and creativity
which we do not have anymore,
We forget our own youth
this guy spirits surrounds,
Who am I
in order to stand in the way?
The question is, is was the
educational philosophy of youth?
Let's
as a starting point,
Interesting,
- Bosh,
What this has with
Charles Dickens to do?
Absolutely everything,
That looks good,
You have a nice shirt,
I love this shirt,
You will like this shirt?
Hello, How is it pink?
Quinn, you want chimichanga?
Hi, You are cute,
And you, Graham? I want tacos,
- Wow,
Watch what you say, I have one here
woman of Mexican descent,
Then order them,
- Sorry, some insensitive,
I could eat her taco,
Harrison, you sly dog,
You are not on the list,
- Do not do that,
I'm kidding,
- Go away, This guy,
Quinn, you look giant sexy,
- I feel sexy tonight,
Give me two, Boom,
What have we here?
A romance in the stairwell?
Is that Chris Denclaw?
- Get lost,
Are you ready?
- Everyone from the clothes,
Everyone from the clothes,
Robbie, how are you?
- Graham, glad you're here,
Got my shirt now?
- He wears other people's shirts,
Have fun, boys, There is plenty
food and enough women,
Daryl, All right, buddy?
Does anyone want a hot dog?
- I want a hot dog,
That was a good joke,
- Have you ever played poker with them?
What are we talking about?
- Yes, Amy, Jessica, Megan,
Come, take a picture,
The Constantinian dynasty,
- Everytime,
You, me, this bottle, trio,
what do you say?
Where are we going?
I do not even ,,,
I had not told you yet
I have a date with Amy,
Good for you,
- We're laser gaming,
Then to my house
Quantum Leap and wine,
Cute,
- How are you and T, J?
T, J,, yes, T,
No idea, Go with her lunch,
Sushi, And they must pay,
You do not pay her,
- I'm doing her a favor,
I worry that she's in love with me,
Love you, honey,
Sorry, can you one of them?
- This one?
You're not going to drink alone?
Want some company?
My husband is a little sick,
No, this is wrong, I'm not going ,,,
Sorry,
You, me and this bottle a menage ,,, no,
Wait a second,
- Have a nice day, Sorry,
Can I get your number?
I do not know your name, but ,,,
You've cut your hair,
- This is the new me,
I miss the old,
- Really? Well, I do not,
It's been a while,
How are you?
I'm fine,
School, work, you know the drill,
Let's take a bottle of champagne
order-
find something with fire
and to speak the champagne,
What are you talking about?
The elements of Euclid and the ,,,
Archimedes' principle and ,,,
The integer is required omega
the equinox coefficient ,,,
I Froot Loops,
and I remove Froot Loops,
And Cornflakes,
- Should you go to the bathroom?
No idea,
That was weird,
We can home to me
to watch a movie,
I'm busy tonight,
- I have something to fill your evening,
I run two services tonight, and
must write, You know that,
Do you remember?
- Yes,
An essay for English,
- No history,
No, I told you English,
Mr, Popular,
- No, I've been very busy,
What I'm trying to say is ,,,
Dumb phone, Who is calling me now?
Marissa? Shit, it was forgotten,
I have T,J, call, Wait, T,J, is
here, I am not fine,
That spring roll, Tell her how you feel,
What I wanted to say is ,,,
Asshole,
Got a problem?
- Sorry,
Sorry, everyone,
- Quinn, I have to go,
Wait, T,J,
I'll walk you to the car,
My car is parked nearby,
- No, you do not ,,,
Do not work too hard,
Your breasts look great,
Well done, asshole,
- Shut up,
Scott Bakula is so handsome,
He is a national treasure,
You smell nice tonight,
Thank you,
- I like your hair,
I'm tired, just want ,,,
We go to your room
and see who calls the first,
You have to go now,
- I love your breasts wonderful,
I'll see you later,
Scott, what should we do?
I must have missed something,
Something is missing,
What happened to you on?
- The formula contains an error,
What happened?
Amy and I watched Quantum Leap,
I do not know how to say it,
Everything, but everything went wrong,
The same happened to me,
I took T,J, out to dinner,
I cried for an old guy
and her breasts,
You yelled at her breasts?
- We need to fix this,
Before we go to the professor,
- I forgot about that with Milan,
I'm working on a proposal,
- I have to cancel that appointment,
Marissa,
Gentlemen, let me be brief,
In ten minutes, I'm going with my
woman at a True Blood party,
Professor Milan, how are you?
- Good thank you,
Do you believe in the theory of
Love at first sight?
What did you think?
My wife fell in love
when she saw my corpulent body,
Okay, perfect,
- Perfect,
Well, that's no longer theory,
We have a formula
which proves that,
Factors affecting millions
one human interaction,
Her words and clothing,
What they want to hear, What we say,
Two different things,
- Where she is, how she bends,
Every important detail
in this formula,
Use it when you talk,
every woman falls in love with you,
And that's what we have,
I am president of a leading
standing technical College
and you can mind control over
exercise someone?
Okay, Look at this,
Say, I walk to the library
here on campus,
And who is that? A baby,
All alone, How sad,
I go to her and make sure
I'm her dream choice,
And she wants nothing but a
have relationship with me,
The only way,
I feel safe and secure,
I am a supplier,
And that's all,
Do not tell me you felt nothing,
I considered jumping out the window
when I heard the drivel,
I think he does not understand us,
- We say smart things,
I take it back,
- Rewind,
I think you can not understand
how successful we are,
Dozens? Hundreds of women
This method recent weeks,
Are you tired? I'm tired, I take
my vitamin tablets, but ,,,
We have sex very often,
- I understand you not,
You come here and talk about
decorating girls,
You are chauvinistic,
onverantwoordelijke-
despicable, deplorable,
selfish, zielige-
talent wasteful,
potentieverspillende-
huge idiots, The largest ever
studied here,
Thank you,
- You're welcome,
Rebecca, do me a favor and make
sure it idioten-
prohibited from ever being my
office visit,
Thank you,
- Why are you such an asshole?
What did you call me?
John, is everything okay?
- Watch and weep,
Hi, come on in, No, come on in,
We close the door,
so you can not escape,
Graham made a compliment,
without exaggeration,
The reliability index of 95%
and the volume that will be expressed ,,,
,,, By variable X,
- Where are you going tonight?
I am married,
- What? I do not care,
I'm coming, sweetheart, But I have a few
idiots to get rid of,
Let me on a more intimate
illustrate manner,
But that's my wife,
- We turn the wedding ring,
You two weeks against
the decision before go-
and may your side of the case to
bring forward before,
Shit,
- It could have been better,
I'm too drunk
to think about this,
I'm exhausted, I'm going home,
- I stay a while,
I'm going to destroy the barmaid,
- Success, We see each other at home,
I come here to have fun,
I heard you had a fine
last night,
Unbelievable that you barmaid
decorated, Cool,
Why Amy just left the apartment?
When was the last time you
talked? Two weeks ago?
Really,
- We went out, had fun
No problem,
- No problem, A little one,
Are you listening to yourself?
You know what you've done?
You're going out with Amy, My 65%
perfect companion Amy,
Amy is the love of my life,
- So what?
Sure, So what,
- Reason,
Do you really want to do this?
- Yes, I love my T-shirt,
You want to see me without T-shirt,
- That would be like,
Goodness, Coward,
I would not do it,
You little girl, No wonder
Amy you do not like,
Would you not air in your lungs
have to live?
Wait a minute,
You're like a baby,
You use a cooking machine,
- You're a girl with a vagina,
A small vagina? You have still
always a hit phone, Why?
Those are cool, Indian in the Cupboard
is your favorite movie,
You look Felicity and eat frootloops,
I've seen you cry,
I think Felicity well, You too,
- No! Only season two,
Want a little reality?
Here then,
My name is Quinn, I like T, J,,
but I'm too chicken to say anything,
Did you learn from your boyfriend?
- You learned that the flickering camp?
You carry on purpose Felicity T-shirts,
- You've got a Sega Game Gear,
She was the love of my life,
- Love? She had nothing against me,
Slang!
Karma comes in the form of arrow and
arc, Never talk to me anymore,
Sam Beckett,
You fickle mistress,
My pants sits between my cheeks,
T,J, Wait,
- Hi, what are you doing here?
I have to tell you something,
- What happened to your foot?
Part of my klotedag,
- Sorry,
I want to talk, I was not myself
as you might have noticed,
I treat people badly, Stable
since a long time in a candy shop,
Why are you telling me that?
- They disappeared when I saw you,
Every time I talk to you,
if only one SEC
that is the best of the day,
Do you know that John Adams and
John Quincy Adams family?
Who is this?
- Quinn ,,, This is my ,,,
Really? He?
- Annoying, Do you want a hug?
No!
So much corduroy,
- Yes, We have to go now,
We'll talk later, okay?
- Take it easy,
Bye, T,J,
Jakkie, I collected coins
and I've seen everything,
I can only ,,, Jakkie,
Quinn! You used the
like a champion,
Let me see you smile,
That was a good one,
Nice picture, Stay in this position,
That's a nice one,
That feels good,
1, 2, Have already taken him, Sorry
This is for the family album,
Ready, What do you think?
We did not even look,
- What?
Is this the best place
for an anniversary album?
What does it matter whether it's here or somewhere
otherwise, It's just a picture,
Watch your words,
- Joe, do not excite yourself,
I know what the problem is,
- He needs a lesson in manners,
I have two fists,
one for each side of your face,
Do not get excited, Joe, Quiet,
What is her name?
- What?
The girl's name
that makes you behave so,
I know what you're trying,
I have not experienced bunch necessary-
coming here and trying my
sense of self-worth to verhogen-
and my relationship with young love
trying to recover,
Mr Lawrence, Mr Lawrence!
Give me that phone,
Jake find me believe I like it,
What should I do?
Is not that tricky, Emily? You know what
you need to do to me?
Assign him now he had some
has dignity,
Will you do that, Emily?
Would you do that for me?
Give a little dignity?
Let him alone, Emily?
Would you do that please?
The lesson today is:Things in
real life that does not exist,
Number one:True love,
Should we write it?
- 'Should we write it? "
Yes, you should write down,
Put your books close,
There will be an exam,
The examination of life,
You will all fail,
You are all corrupt,
And that's what the real hell,
Thank you, Really,
It was a pleasure,
That's the last time I
Craftsman tools use,
That's life, Drink some, Stick your
finger on to the women,
I am glad that we no woman
have, We do what we want,
Look at that guy,
So pathetic there,
I would be his eulogy at his
good days must ven-
for they are gone,
That are dead,
This is so great,
- I want nothing more than this life,
Can you keep your mouth shut,
Please,
Got a problem?
- Do you know how pathetic you sound?
Yes, What?
You believe you are single
because you want to,
Yes,
- The reality is different,
You're single
because you have no choice,
No woman wants to go out with you,
as long as you behave so pathetic,
Wastrel,
For life,
I'm sick,
Sorry, Why am I
everybody cry?
Drive you?
- What you did was not necessary,
Sure, But walk away,
This toast is like
the Christmas album of Kenny G,
$ 1,200,
I am happy for you,
- What happened to you on?
I might have 20 young lives
ruined, my friends hate me-
the love of my life
disappeared, should I go on?
You have to see the positive,
- That's not so simple,
I told her I love her
am, and she rejected me,
You know what? Life goes on,
One girl pointed you,
There are bigger problems in the
world, I'm not comforted,
Do not whine and do not worry
about what you can not influence,
Worry about your example
damaged friendships,
It bothers me that a good guy
like you-
so much time and talent wasted on
such childish things,
Grow up, Quinn,
Thanks, dude,
- You're welcome,
Do not pretend you do not want this,
How are you?
- I did not know you were coming,
Yes,
- Graham, I just wanted to say ,,,
Good Evening, This is exciting,
I can not wait for her,
I've been waiting all week on a
great excuse yours,
We sincerely apologize for ,,,
- I'm sorry, Graham, I mean it,
What are you doing?
- It was foolish to mess with Amy,
You're my best friend, I want our
friendship not put at stake,
Forget that girl, You are a good
guy and deserves better,
Can this not equally bromance
wait?
What about me?
- Give us a few seconds,
Quinn, what are you doing?
- Let's talk like men,
Professor Millan, you will find
that what we do is meaningless,
And that's it,
We've been assholes,
Something I've learned is that no
single book can teach me to ,,,
,,, Let me act like women
a complete idiot,
Damn, I know,
Becky Forrester,
What?
I thought Becky Forrester
was correct, I did that,
But she made it out the day before
my twenty-first birthday,
The next evening
I wanted to be aggressive,
But instead
I met this girl,
And ten months later, she was
Ms, Millan,
Strange things
dissolve that way,
Guys, I understand you,
Really,
But I have already told you:
Women ,,,
are an example of things
men can never understand,
Never,
But nevertheless ,,,
We love it,
Quinn, I should call Amy?
- Who is Amy?
At this time we chill,
as they want to express,
We fought,
- Lusten you raisins?
I love raisins,
- Unfortunately I only have a whole bag,
There you go, Amy,
I need to buy new ones,
- I also have new shoes,
I also have new shoes,
- I live alone,
I put some pillows on the couch,
The whole room is lighter,
Sounds good,
- Keep things together,
Has to do with Feng Shui,
One ,,,
,,, Two ,,, three,
I had not met him yet,
I did not know who he was,
You know ,,, One Direction
does not have a ceiling,
Therefore, they are what they are,
- I did exactly as told,
She was so angry,
she had no words,
The Back Street Boys
can they sit on back seat,
That looks like
a racetrack in Tijuana,
Hi, Quinn,
- How are you?
You know Libby, I believe,
I want to thank you officially it
you showed us how sorry we were,
Until recently,
Oh baby, you're so sweet,
You changed our view
in the entire universe,
I am happy that
you that was recognized,
And so fast,
- You're a gem,
And man among boys,
- Have a nice evening,
Shoot some more arrows, Cupid,
You are annoying,
I'm out of here,
We need to talk, Okay?
Ladies and germs,
We have a newcomer,
Help me this man
karaoke virginity to lose,
Graham Jacobs, Come here,
I think there is nothing
to talk about,
What ,,,
Hello, My name is Graham,
I'm going to sing something
I usually sing alone,
But now I'm going to
sing for everyone,
Just like the time
Derek and I did it,
It makes me so horny,
This song was always
for someone in particular,
But I'm open to suggestions,
Can be for you, you're cute,
I learned a lot about myself,
And I just have to sit there,
Now, a random white man,
who thinks he's funny is-
Tupac sing,
T,J, Hi, It's Quinn,
Come about 20 minutes to the New
Strand Theater, Hope to see you,
Quinn?
It's weird when you call me and me
asks to go to a cinema,
Hello Madam, and welcome
New Strand Theatre,
What is this?
Tonight we turn
the latest film by Jason Statham,
I forgot his name,
but he plays Keith Ramsberg,
There is a knife fight scene,
and he shows his dewooling buttocks,
Quinn, this is great,
but I've already told you ,,,
Sorry to interrupt,
When we practiced, you always said
ball long to get rolling, never short,
Do you remember that?
- Yes,
We can be friends,
and that's great,
But I want you to know
I'm going to try it,
If I do not take the opportunity to
wells, then why do I play?
I'm not asking you to marry me,
Not even to go together,
But I ask you,
you want to see Jason Statham?
You said it at the end
his bare buttocks show?
Yes, He does,
- In this case, it is worth,
Amazing,
Would you like popcorn?
- Please,
This is a terrible movie,
- The worst,
Translation:Monique Z, Widingsj
Ripped and edited by relentless