Chester's Mill was like any other town.
I love you, too, Rusty!
A typical place in every way.
You off to the game today, Big Jim?
Until...
the unimaginable.
What the hell happened here?
Hey, no.
Don't touch that!
I have just learned
that the barrier around Chester's Mill
is being called a dome.
No, no, no, stop!
We're trapped.
The dome kept everyone in.
Why us? Maybe we're being punished.
And threatened to let
all their secrets out.
What the hell do you want from me?
He's lying to you!
But the dome had secrets of its own.
We found this egg.
What does "The pink stars
are falling in lines" mean?
And one thing was certain...
there was no escape.
This dome can't break us!
Look at what it's doing!
We're all gonna die in here.
Tonight...
I really love the story
'cause it's a survival story.
- Step back.
- ... the cast and producers
go inside this incredible story.
Well, in season one we
had to establish the dome.
We had to establish the
chaos that it brought.
And the horror without
reveals the horror within.
Shut up! All you do is lie.
And take an exclusive look ahead...
Second season is much more
about the characters'
journeys and who they are.
Someone has to make the hard choices!
- ... at the next chapter.
- We start to explore
what that dome is doing to the people.
- Why did you leave me?
- With never-before-seen moments.
This season will answer a lot of questions.
And a warning.
How do you explain all this?
You just have no idea what's gonna happen.
- No one...
- Oh, my God, my
- mom's in there!
- ... is safe.
- Junior!
- Gear up,
'cause it's about to get even crazier.
You're listening to WYBS,
the Mill's only 100%
independent home of rock.
In a typical small town...
Sorry to bother you. Sam Verdreaux called.
He wants us to know that he
heard some kind of a bang.
... even the biggest
problems can seem simple.
You were right to get me, Linda.
Never know with this damn place.
Monday mornings have been
brutal since they opened
that Denny's over in Westlake.
I'll take your French toast
any day of the week, Rose.
Big Jim Rennie was working
on his next election.
What is this?
That's me buying your next vote.
Says the guy who always runs unopposed.
Big Jim is the main
councilman left in the town.
He's also a used car salesman.
So you know you can trust him.
We're all in this together.
Julia Shumway
searched for her next headline.
So you're the newspaper woman?
I'm the new editor of
The Independent. Yeah.
Julia is a reporter who moves to
Chester's Mill with her husband,
who's a doctor.
You see that truck?
That's its fourth propane
delivery this week.
I called Sheriff Perkins three days ago.
He sounded nervous.
She wants to know the truth
and she's not gonna stop
till she gets the truth.
I'll do some digging.
God.
You all right, there?
When we first meet
Junior Rennie, he's madly
in love with Angie McAlister.
I love you.
It's been a fun summer.
And she has just told him good-bye.
Ouch.
Angie is not really looking
for a serious relationship.
She is really trying to
get out of Chester's Mill
and make a better life for herself.
You're the only person in the whole world
who knows the real me.
And that's why I can't be with you.
He has this kind of, like, hole
in his heart after losing Angie.
I'm gonna be late for work.
And he's wanting to get
back with her any way he can.
It was a quiet place.
But even Chester's Mill had a dark side.
When we first meet Barbie,
he's definitely in town
under some suspicious circumstances.
We're not quite sure who he is,
where he's come from.
We think he's a bad guy.
He's got a big secret.
A big secret...
So we got a problem here.
... and some really bad luck.
_
Imagine if you're in an
ordinary American town.
Suddenly you hear a rumbling and shaking.
And the ground is moving under your feet.
It's like, everybody thinks
there's an earthquake.
Just the feeling
of the wind and the gust.
All of a sudden...
boom, it hits.
You really see the horror of it,
you know, the... our famous image
from the first season is
the cow being split in half.
Aah!
Ugh.
It really was a good symbol
for sort of what happens.
You know, the town gets severed.
The dome comes down, people
lose limbs, people get cut in half.
The world sort of flips upside down.
You have the unexplainable, the chaotic,
the terrifying, all happening at once.
You okay?
What the hell?
Right when the dome comes down, Joe
is found, you know, on his farm.
Joe McAlister is an everyday kid who's 16
years old. Pretty good in science and math.
Joe's parents are trapped outside the dome.
It's some sort of invisible fence.
Whatever it is, I'd
probably stop touching it.
One of the things that was most terrifying
about the premise is the
idea that it's invisible.
You'd be walking down the
street or driving your car
or your truck or your
little plane, and you would
hit this invisible barrier.
Run!
What the hell is happening?
Am I doing something wrong?
Power's out, Carolyn.
Cashier said the pumps'll be back on soon.
"Chester's Mill is known
for its rich, fertile land
and warm, inviting people."
Norrie is a L.A. kid who,
uh, has a real attitude about anything
that isn't big-city hip.
She has two mothers and they're
not happy with her behavior.
- For the millionth time... that was an accident.
- That's what you said
when you knocked out that girl's tooth.
So they're taking her to boot camp.
And they are in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Is everyone all right?
Nothing about this
is all right.
The barrier had a
mysterious effect on Norrie.
Norrie!
And then all of a sudden,
she's on the ground
in the middle of the street
having a seizure, mumbling...
The pink stars are falling.
Sheriff Perkins,
the plane smashed right into it.
- Into what?
- Whatever it is,
it cut off all our roads.
Not just the roads...
the whole town.
Suddenly, the peaceful
town of Chester's Mill
would never be the same.
In season two, we're genuinely trapped.
- Coming up...
- Get down!
... an exclusive scene
from season two of Under the Dome.
In an instant, Chester's
Mill had been forever changed.
- All right, everybody...
- And as authorities
mobilized on the outside...
... puts the dome over
Chester's Mill at roughly...
- Did he just call it a dome?
- Yeah.
... fear began to surface on the inside.
What the hell is going on?
Isn't it obvious?
We're under attack.
Nobody knows a damn thing,
so there's no point in
spreading any rumors.
There's an initial panic
of people not knowing what it is.
Why is that dome here? Is there a specific
reason that this dome hit us?
No one was safe. And
neither were their secrets.
Any sign of your husband?
Not yet.
Julia hadn't seen her husband,
Peter, since the dome appeared.
She just assumes that he's
helping out in the chaos. He's a doctor.
- Is the doc with you?
- He's not here?
Listen, your husband hasn't
worked Sundays in weeks.
She thinks he must have been
trapped outside the dome.
And then, enter a tall, dark stranger.
Who the hell are you?
Or blond.
Barbie.
Barbie?
- It's a nickname.
- I think Barbie,
from the get-go, would love
to have run back into the woods
- and just hid out.
- What about you?
- Where are you off to?
- Uh, the motels are all booked up, so
I'm just gonna rough it.
Don't be ridiculous.
You can stay with Peter and me.
- How do you guys have power?
- Backup generator.
That's Peter, behind you.
To Barbie, Peter Shumway
was a familiar face.
Stephen King frequently
writes about the ideal
American town
when it's like the worm inside the apple.
And what's the worm gonna
be inside of Chester's Mill?
It's like a ghost town in here.
I should be able to hold down the fort.
It's easier to reach
consensus when there's only
one voice to listen to, right?
Sheriff Duke Perkins was
the town's long-respected lawman.
What are you gettin' at, Jim?
No one knew about his
corrupt dealings with Big Jim.
What do we do when the people
start asking about the propane?
Well, that has nothing to do with this.
Oh. Big Jim has been storing up
some propane for a-a certain amount of
drug-making.
There's a lot I've tried
to protect you from.
Like what?
But something within the
dome triggered a reaction.
My chest.
Duke, is it your pacemaker?
- No, Duke!
- And Duke
took their secrets to the grave.
Holy hell.
Big Jim wasted no time
asserting himself, keeping
his other business partner,
Reverend Coggins, in line.
You're using our stuff...
you're high as a kite.
S... so what? It's Judgment Day, Jim.
And he never missed an opportunity...
- The flames are too high.
- ... to take center stage in a crisis.
You know, I always saw Big Jim as a guy
who recited Winston Churchill
speeches in the shower.
And, uh, wished that he was
in a time and place when
he could've been that guy.
Thank you, everyone,
for a job well done.
Well, we couldn't have done
it without you, Big Jim.
Oh...
Where were you yesterday,
- Junior?
- Nowhere.
Big Jim tightened
his grip on the town
and on his son.
Junior is, uh, Big Jim's only son,
and on the one hand,
Big Jim wants to help him,
wants to keep him out of trouble.
People are looking to me
to lead.
It reflects poorly when my son is AWOL.
On the other hand,
he kind of wears Big Jim's patience,
because he's constantly
having to deal with this kid
who's doing all these crazy things.
Like when he puts his girlfriend
in the fallout shelter.
What the hell do you want from me?
Junior kidnaps Angie
because he believes...
now that this dome has come down...
that there's something wrong with her.
I think it scrambled your brain.
One of us has a scrambled brain, all right.
You can't see it, but I can.
He truly believes the
dome is infecting her mind,
so he's out to save her any way he can.
I don't believe we've been, uh,
formally introduced.
I'm, uh, Jim Rennie.
People around here call me Big Jim.
Barbie.
Big Jim was now the law in town.
Well, that's kind of a... funny name
for a fellow with your
particular expertise.
And he needed soldiers.
What is your objective here, huh?
Is it to bring him in or
we trying to take him out?
I don't see it makes a difference
to a guy like you, does it?
Barbie intuitively goes,
"That's a guy I've got to watch out for."
I told you, we're finishing this.
Why is that?
So you can show the town
what a big man Big Jim is?
Barbie notices along the way that
this guy is just power-hungry
and up to no good.
Sometimes an example
needs to be made, you know?
Command respect.
God, I swear, you ask
more questions than anybody I've ever met.
Well, you know you're
pretty good at evading them.
Barbie couldn't escape Chester's Mill,
or the wife of the man he'd killed.
You all right?
You were, uh, talking in your sleep.
Yelling, actually.
He's obviously very handsome, and, so,
you know, there's an
attraction, there's chemistry.
Thanks again for letting me crash here.
With my husband missing and
everything that happened today,
it was nice to have the company.
They get really close, and they form
this fast friendship, this bond.
Julia continued to ask questions.
And you really were just
passing through Chester's Mill?
No connection to anyone here in town?
No.
So, we start this chess game
between the two of them.
Being a reporter, she
knows the questions to ask.
- So, you went through my stuff?
- You lied to me.
When Julia suddenly fell ill,
Barbie decided to reveal
her husband's secrets.
I've got the cash, but my wife's home.
Meet me at the other spot.
Julia learns that her husband Peter had
a gambling problem that he was concealing.
And Barbie was coming
to collect those debts.
- I don't have it!
- Yeah? My boss is not gonna like that.
So, where is he now?
He doesn't come completely clean.
He must have taken off.
And then, eventually,
finds himself against
the ropes with no way out.
I found this life insurance policy today.
Julia soon discovered the truth
behind her husband's death.
He needed you to kill him.
She processes everything that happened,
and she realizes, well,
Peter had put Barbie in a situation
where he really had no choice.
It was shoot or be shot.
You know, in some weird way,
I think he did all this
to try to protect me.
'Cause this would be void
if he committed suicide.
Barbie's done enough heroics
in Chester's Mill already
to prove that he's sort of
more the hero than the villain.
But in the future,
there can be no more lies.
With secrets no longer between them...
We're gonna be okay.
... Julia and Barbie's
relationship quickly deepened.
Well, your son takes after you, too.
He stopped what could have
been a full-blown riot.
Big Jim's relationship with
his son had also evolved.
You ever consider a
career in law enforcement?
When Junior was made a deputy,
he earned Big Jim's respect.
A chip off the old block.
But that respect would be short-lived.
There is a pipe
that bursts in the fallout shelter,
and Big Jim hears it.
He goes to look,
and finds Angie.
You're gonna get me out of here, right?
He does something really interesting.
He doesn't pick her up
and drag her out of there and get her help.
I just, uh, I just need to
think on this a little bit.
No, no, no, you can't leave me down here!
You can't! You... No.
No! Wait! Wait!
Help! Help!
You think the dome is
gonna be here forever?
Coming up...
This is the real discovery.
There's something else at work here.
What does it mean?
Excuse me.
Where can a girl charge up in this town?
Everyone was adjusting
to life under the dome.
I have a generator.
Norrie goes to this kind of
teenage bonfire where
they're all mourning the loss
of their electronics.
Without my music, I can get a
little, you know, super bitchy.
Well, there's definitely an immediate
attraction to Norrie
from Joe. He sees
this new girl.
She's dressed differently,
she talks differently.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
Uh, maybe I can fix it.
Really? That thing blew
up like the Death Star.
Yeah, but the Empire rebuilt the Death Star
in The Return of the Jedi.
I like nerds.
Norrie?
- Oh, God.
- Norrie,
are you here... ?
And
her mom finds her.
Let's go.
And the second she grabs Joe's hand...
- Oh, my God. Norrie?
- What happened?
Pink stars are falling in lines.
- Norrie?!
- The pink stars are falling
- in lines.
- Norrie.
And that's the first time
you see them seizing together.
Well, they're obviously
meant to be in some way.
- You ready?
- Let's do it.
Of all the things to do after
you've had a double seizure.
Let's try it again.
And we record ourselves doing that
to see what happens.
The pink stars are falling...
That's the first step to
them figuring things out.
What does this mean?
Maybe we're not supposed to tell anyone.
Why not?
'Cause the dome doesn't want us to.
The dome continued to reveal
itself to those inside...
What is this?
... while forces outside
had other intentions.
Look.
They're bussing in more soldiers?
No. Civilians.
It's been nearly a week
since this thing came down.
Why bus the families in now?
Haven't you ever been to camp?
They're finally giving
us our own visitors day.
Yeah, visitor day was interesting,
because it, uh... at first,
it's set up as if it's a nice thing.
It's a lovely day in which we
all get to see our relatives.
Sinners!
The happy day wouldn't last long.
Over and over,
the Lord has spoken one word in my ear.
MOAB.
- MOAB!
- Thank you, Reverend.
Thank you for those inspiring words.
Visitor day is set up
as a sort of family reunion.
"What's... happening... out there?"
Barbie comes to find out
that's not the intent at all.
They're not about to let this
thing mess with the outside world.
It's the episode that starts out
with the best-case scenario
and ends with the worst-case scenario.
MOAB.
Come again?
What your reverend was ranting about.
MOAB is not a city. It's an acronym...
For "the mother of all bombs."
The army is gonna blow up the dome,
even if that means blowing us up with it.
Good Lord.
- We're all just gonna die.
- No.
No. We get everybody to a shelter.
Where?
The old cement factory.
Some of those tunnels run pretty deep.
Faced with their final moments,
Chester's Millers each made their peace...
Last call.
... including Big Jim.
Why are you doing this?
Well, if we're all gonna die today,
you might as well die a free woman.
Norrie and Joe are going
on kind of their first
little adventure together, and
there's a huge missile
coming straight for us.
And, of course...
... what else do you do
when the world's ending?
It's just this special,
fiery moment between both of them.
When we touched, we
didn't have the seizures.
More importantly, we didn't die.
The fact that we can't blow up that dome
kind of sets everybody to thinking that
this dome thing is bigger
and stronger and more
important than any of us
can ever really think about.
They're now really cut
off from the outside world
because everything outside
the dome is now a wasteland.
And they're stuck
because
if a bomb can't touch the dome, what can?
It kind of reinforces the idea
that we're gonna be
here for a while and that
he needs to step it up and be the leader.
God told me to come out here.
What the hell you doing here?
Jim, I know you think
this town belongs to you,
and maybe... maybe it used to,
but today...
Today's a new day.
You know, you're right, Reverend.
Big Jim felt that Reverend Coggins
was getting crazy, was
gonna lead to problems.
You don't want to make an enemy
of Big Jim under the dome.
And that's when Big Jim starts
to realize, "Wow, I could be king."
He's on a mission to control his enemies
and to put himself in charge.
With no end in sight to their ordeal...
Damn it.
- Now what?
- I lost the signal.
... Julia worked to uncover
the mysteries of the dome.
Julia ends up
running around with Dodee...
- We're close.
- All right.
... trying to get a signal,
which they think is going
to be the source of the dome.
I think it's coming from them.
I know it doesn't make any sense.
It sort of does.
It was time to share their secret.
The pink stars are falling in lines.
Okay, I'm officially freaked out.
Norrie and Joe continue
to test their connection to the dome.
Anything?
Yeah. You're really good at that.
From the dome, Joe.
I didn't feel anything, like a seizure.
Me neither, unfortunately.
Maybe we're going about it all wrong.
Joe, being smart,
figures out that there may be something
at the center of the
dome that powers the dome.
It shouldn't be too far now.
Norrie and Joe go off on a search.
The hair's standing up on my arms.
There it is.
They start uncovering this
mound in the ground, and
there's another dome.
And as they uncover the dirt and leaves,
they see a small egg.
So, what was weird has gotten even weirder.
Maybe it's the generator
that created the whole dome.
The discovery of the mini-dome
and the discovery of the egg...
- Okay.
- ... It's really sort of
our portal into the next phase
of the dome.
Norrie?
Joe and Norrie discover
the dome had ways to communicate with them.
Mom?
I need to find my mom.
Because something horrible
is about to happen.
Mom, you're not going anywhere.
Norrie's mother was diabetic.
You have to be brave.
The dome's arrival had caused
dangerously limited resources...
I will, I promise.
... and cut off her access
to life-saving insulin.
Bring her back.
I'll do anything you want.
Just tell me what you want!
I've never met anyone like her before.
It's kind of amazing
to feel that connected.
It's even more intense at the egg.
The egg?
What egg?
For Julia, that egg is confirmation
that there are other forces at work here.
It's pink. It was black before.
She's kind of mesmerized
by the egg and the mini-dome
and trying to figure out what's going on.
And all of a sudden...
The monarch will be crowned.
What did you just say?
Who are you talking to?
Julia realizes that she's chosen
in some way to be connected to it.
The monarch will be crowned.
What the hell you doing here?
Junior was angry that his
father had released Angie
from the fallout shelter.
I just want to make sure she's safe.
You're not in your right mind, Junior.
You sound just like your
mother did at the end.
The rejection pushed Junior
toward Big Jim's lifelong enemy...
My dad kicked me out.
... where he learned a family secret.
I can't imagine your dad's
an easy man to live with,
especially after your mother dying.
It was, um...
a tragic accident.
Is that what he told you?
You told me she died in a car crash.
The ultimate drama is going
to be about family, and
that family has its tragedy
that gets very messy.
Wasn't an accident, was it?
No.
Junior wants his dad to, like,
tell the truth for once.
Your mother had been...
unsteady
for a while.
He explains that she committed suicide.
He's been protecting Junior
from the truth of the situation.
Why...
did you lie to me?
'Cause I didn't want you
to know that she chose
to leave you.
I'm so sorry.
Just to hear it from Big Jim's mouth
is what he kind of needed
in order to rebuild their relationship.
You got a problem with this?
Allow me.
I believe you.
Angie.
Hey.
I just had a seizure at the diner.
What do you mean, you had a seizure?
I was just standing there, and then I...
I went blank and collapsed.
Angie! The pink stars are falling in lines.
Did you say,
"The pink stars are falling"?
How did you know that?
And, obviously, those words are
a connection somehow, but
they're not sure exactly why.
It's what you found in the woods, isn't it?
And you're not freaking out about it?
I can't deny that I'm a part of this now.
Me,
Angie and Norrie all place
our hands on the mini-dome.
It's almost like... these are locks...
... and our hands are the keys.
We notice that there's a
fourth handprint that appears
that there isn't a person for.
I think we need a fourth hand.
I knew you'd come find me.
Why have you always said
that the dome is making me sick?
Because it's true.
But there's more,
isn't there? Yeah.
Junior is
seeing all the pieces come together,
and so he's finally feeling
like he can show Angie
his mom's art studio.
A couple months
before she died, she
had this dream about me.
And she just started painting
this as fast as she could.
Pink stars.
When he reveals
this different side of him and his mother,
she starts to question, maybe I was sick.
Maybe he knows more than I do.
Maybe, way back then, she
knew the dome was coming.
And I must be part of it,
because I'm in this painting.
And now, obviously, you're part of it, too.
She doesn't trust him still,
but they're just connected in this way.
The four hands are the four
people who can unlock the mystery
of the dome.
And the phrase that no one
has known what it's meant...
"The pink stars are falling"...
the pink stars fall.
Then the dome lights up.
Oh, my God.
It's the pink stars.
And it projects all these
beautiful constellations...
the dipper,
Castor and Pollux and all that stuff.
It's kind of a star map.
It's a piece of what the
dome means, but it doesn't
outright give answers.
Beautiful!
But... what does it mean?
Big Jim was constantly on high alert...
You got one second to tell me
why I shouldn't blow your damn head off.
... but he never expected to see
his old friend Maxine Seagrave.
Because you don't want to
ruin this beautiful face?
Maxine's another one of his business
associates in the illegal drug trade.
This is, uh,
Dale Barbara. He...
We find out
that Barbie and Jim are
connected through Maxine.
In terms of Big Jim, she
was partners with him.
In terms of Barbie,
she was sleeping with him,
and Barbie works for her
as a collector.
We make a damn good team.
And as long as this dome is around,
I can see us making
this town our playground.
What are you doing?
We're finished, Max.
Maxine, ultimately,
sort of draws the conclusion that Julia is
why I won't join sides with her.
First, she turns up out of nowhere
and turns out to be the woman
who was sleeping with Barbie,
who's now sort of my boyfriend.
Can I help you?
Right now you can't even help yourself.
And the first time
I get to meet her face-to-face,
she puts a bullet in me.
It's so cold-hearted,
um, that it's kind of great.
You hungry?
After unlocking the star map,
Junior and Angie were left
to wonder what it all meant.
Can you believe it, Angie?
The way our lives are braided together,
and they will be forever.
What? Are you insane?
It is not about you and me.
It will never be about you...
- I don't believe you.
- Well, believe it.
We will never be together!
Then I'm out. I'm done
with you, with this,
the mini-dome, all of it.
I've never met someone so selfish!
Junior's departure had consequences,
as the dome unleashed its wrath.
Julia?! Julia, hey, hey,
hey, hey, stay with me.
Hey, you got to hurry, Joe. She's crashing.
And a mysterious storm descended.
It's not just weather. It's the dome.
I think it's angry at us.
Junior! Look at what it's doing!
It's sending a message!
You have to come back to the group.
It takes all of us,
or we're nothing.
Barbie worked frantically to save Julia.
Come on!
Come on. We got to go!
Angie!
And after Junior's change of heart,
the storm receded.
I was right.
Storm's breaking up.
Julia survived the attack,
but Maxine would have to answer for it.
You know it's Max who shot her, right?
And I also know that it's time to stop her.
Big Jim hates Maxine
because she has the goods
on him, and she threatens
to tell the town.
Should take both of us to do it.
Well, we're gonna do this by my rules, Jim.
We're taking Max alive.
Barbie now becomes the... the one
really fighting for order in this town.
Big Jim evolves into
a man who's seeking to capitalize
on the chaos of this town.
You're not saving Chester's Mill.
You're eating this town alive.
Big Jim is a smart guy.
He's a practical guy,
and he sees Barbie as... at
the beginning, at least...
as someone who could be useful to him,
and, throughout the course of the season,
Big Jim realizes that maybe
Barbie's not really the guy
to be on his team.
I'm gonna go get our car.
We'll take them down to the station.
So Big Jim realized that he could kill
several birds with one stone.
He'd kill Maxine and her bodyguard.
And then he could get rid of Barbie by
putting the blame on him.
Barbie, put that weapon down!
Put it down now!
Linda, thank God!
- He's gone nuts!
- He's lying to you!
He killed 'em.
I was next.
Linda, I'm telling you...
Shoot that son of a bitch!
This has been a very dark
day in Chester's Mill.
Maxine Seagrave and her
business associate were murdered.
An attempt was made on
the life of Julia Shumway.
One person is responsible for all this:
Dale "Barbie" Barbara.
Big Jim uses
his powers of persuasion
and he is able to convince the town
that he is the leader, that
Barbie committed these murders.
The people...
will seek the death penalty.
The four hands knew that the dome
was communicating with them.
But to what end?
What do we do now?
If these stars are really us,
then we have to go to the
same spot on the big dome.
Joe figures out that they're
being called to go to the big dome.
They all go to the dome, put their hands
on it, they see
this kind of ghostly image
of Big Jim coming forward.
Dad?
And he starts bleeding
and he gets these knife wounds.
Junior's freaking out, and
all four of us look down
and we have these knives.
Junior?
No! What the hell was that?
I... I thought we were
coming here for answers.
I think that was it.
Big Jim has to die.
And I think we're supposed to do it.
Season two, we explore
- the mythology of the dome.
- Coming up...
What's happening?
... an exclusive scene from season two
of Under the Dome.
What's it doing?
I think it's mad we didn't kill Big Jim.
- Angie, we can't do that.
- Joe,
Norrie and Angie grappled
with what to do next.
It wants him dead.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Maybe so that he doesn't kill your monarch?
And they found a mysterious
cocoon inside the mini-dome.
When the butterfly hatches,
the monarch will be crowned.
Dodee's continued suspicions
led her to a discovery.
And transmissions from the outside
helped her understand
the importance of the egg.
Any idea where the hell
that egg thing is, soldier?
There is evidence that the outside world
knows what's going on.
The military's looking for an egg?
Yeah. And I've seen it.
It was at Joe McAlister's barn.
When Big Jim learns about the egg,
he thinks that that's the key to the dome.
Maybe if you get this thing,
you could bring down the dome.
He doesn't want the dome to come down yet.
He hasn't yet exercised
all his power or his ambition.
He wants to have control of that egg.
Linda?
The radio station's on fire.
Could it be arson?
No idea.
It's Barbie.
We've been broadcasting info
about him night and day.
I'd be careful, Linda.
If you find Barbie, you call me.
The entire town was looking for Barbie.
And he needed help to
save Julia from Big Jim.
Julia's still at the
clinic. Now, if she wakes up,
he's gonna kill her.
Wh... why?
Because if she tells people
that it wasn't actually me that shot her,
his whole story falls apart.
So help me save Julia.
With Angie's help,
Barbie took Julia to safety.
I love you.
Drive fast!
Put your hands on your head!
With Barbie in custody,
Big Jim went looking for the egg.
What the hell?
But Joe and Norrie were one step ahead.
Where is it?
We have no idea what you're talking about.
They had moved the egg.
And now found the butterfly
was ready to hatch.
It's really happening.
When, uh, the monarch hatched,
- they didn't know how to get it out.
- What the hell?
Every time its wings
touched the invisible dome,
It would cause a black color to appear.
Is it just me or is it
getting crazy dark outside?
The black spots began to also cover
the big dome outside
until Chester's Mill was in total darkness.
So, now what?
Junior soon found them.
And was forced to make a decision.
Things are happening, Junior!
Do you want your dad
to lock that thing away
before it can give us any answers?
Let's go.
When Julia woke up, there
was no time to waste.
Where's Barbie?
I guess everyone's out
dealing with the blackout.
And with everybody distracted,
Julia and Angie freed Barbie.
Angie? Angie McAlister?
We're on the move
with the mini-dome.
Joe!
Thank God!
- Don't take another step.
- Junior, stop!
No! This guy's a psychopath!
Hey, is that supposed to do that?
The four hands don't
know why they were chosen.
And they were desperate to figure out a way
to release this monarch.
And maybe make the dome go away.
It opens the mini-dome,
now we have the egg,
and the butterfly is up floating around.
Okay.
Another piece to the puzzle.
You're the monarch.
What do we do?
We have to take that egg
to the real authorities.
Like Big Jim?
No, we are not taking
anything to that monster.
I'm done listening to
you all run down my dad.
He's the only thing
keeping this town together.
Hand it over, Julia.
Run!
Once again, Barbie sacrificed
himself to protect his friends.
Barbie! Go!
Get up!
You're done!
As the authorities searched for the egg,
What the hell does "The pink
stars are falling in lines" mean?
Big Jim learned of his late wife's
mysterious connection
It's like she knew all
this was gonna happen.
How is that possible?
I don't know.
If your wife saw the dome coming,
that means your family's important.
That means you're important.
Big Jim starts to believe
that maybe their family
was kind of ordained
in some way to deal with this dome.
You and I need to do what nobody else
in Chester's Mill can.
We need to make the hard decisions,
act on them and lead.
Big Jim Rennie
with a message for Julia Shumway.
Big Jim says to her, "Give me
the egg or Barbie's gonna die."
Fail to comply within the hour,
and Barbie pays the ultimate price.
It's everyone or it's him.
That's a really impossible
decision to make.
We have to help him.
How do we protect Chester's
Mill and save Barbie?
We can't.
She's willing to
make the hard choice.
This has to be my decision.
Big Jim had made himself
judge, jury and executioner.
Today Chester's Mill
sentences Dale Barbara to death.
With Barbie moments away from hanging,
Julia did her part
to protect the egg.
Something's about to go down.
If there's pink stars in the sky,
something is about to happen.
Big Jim thinks
it's telling him that
he's doing the right thing
to kill Barbie.
Clearly the Good Lord
has looked upon our work
here today with favor.
Junior very much wants
to do the right thing,
but it's a big, big sign, and he can't help
but think, do I kill this man or see what
the dome will reveal to him?
Did we make the wrong choice,
and the pink stars and the glowing dome,
is it actually gonna wipe us all out?
Now, son! Do it now!
Do we kill him? Do we not kill him?
What is this light?
It is a very tense moment.
The stakes are very high.
Now, Junior! Do it now!
CBS Monday...
Something awful is happening out there.
... Under the Dome returns.
There has been no official statement
on reported abnormal magnetic activity.
And not everyone will survive.
Oh, my God! My mom's in there!
Now, an exclusive scene from
next week's season premiere,
written by Stephen King.
- Whoa!
- Whoa, watch out!
She hit her head!
Mom.
Get down!
Let's get her up! Ready?
Whoa, look out!
Hurry! That door!
What do we do?!
- Get the table!
- Okay.
Watch her arm! Let's get
it, let's get it, yeah!
Whoa!
What is happening?!
It's pulling all the nails out!
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -