Molly.
Molly!
Ahh, Molly.
Molly.
Hay.
There you are.
Where were you?
Bad dog!
All right, this is it.
Don't worry, this is just in case
something goes terribly wrong.
I'm actually coming over.
I'll just talk to you...
No, no.  Listen to me
- You have to stop me!
- I'm hanging up now.
No!
Molly?
Molly.
- Molly?
- She's on the couch.
What?  James!
What are you doing here?
What was that crazy phone
call about Howard?
What?
Your call, you were screening about
stopping you from doing something.
Listen, I don't know what
you're talking about.
But you have to leave, I'm working
on something extremely important.
This your new invention to show the board?
That's right.
Oh, it's cute.
They would have liked it.
What do you mean?
They've already selected mine to be funded.
What?
It's over.
Sorry champ, you're finished.
No, no!  No not yet.
I'm sorry Howard, but what's done is done.
You can't change it.
That's what you think.
Were you doing?
I know what you've been working on
but it's irrelevant now
because my invention is going
to blow yours of the water
and I'm about to prove it.
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah, see you soon old friend.
The time is 12:04 PM.
and I embark.
Ahh.
Uh!
Hello?
Hello.
You! What is the time?
What is the exact time?
Ahhh!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
It works.
July 1.
11:59 AM
This is 5 minutes in the past.
Oh, it's perfect.
Why am I not in the garage?
What am I doing here?
No!
That makes sense... The
rotation of the earth.
I'd travels through time not space.
I did it!  I'm the world's
first time traveler.
911 please state your emergency.
You'll have to excuse me Miss.
I have some gloating to do.
Hello?  Hello is someone there?
This is my neighborhood!
Hello?
Ha!
What happened?
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
You disappeared two more of you burst in
one of you shot the other one
then you jumped in the box
and disappeared again.
Wait, I killed myself?
Yes.
Oh god, no no no.
The moment I got into the machine
I must've started a chain reaction...
Howard this is incredible! You've
created a working time machine!
No, no no no.  I have to turn it off.
I-I-I I have to destroy it
- Howard, stop!
- What!
You can't do that.
This machine is revolutionary.
It's better than anything
I could ever create
You can use it.  To save yourself.
Oh you mean, go back again.
And stop herself from ever killing
yourself in the first place.
None of this has to happen.
You can change it.
You know, maybe you're right.
I can fix this.
- What time is it?
- Twel...
12:07
I got in at 12:04
I may just have enough time.
OK.
- Thanks James.
- You're welcome.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Oh my god are you OK?
What time is it?
Huh?
I need to know the exact time.
Quickly.
It's, 12:02.
OK, 5 minutes again.
I only have a couple of
minutes to get back.
What are you doing?
No time to explain.  I've got to go.
Close.
I can make it!
Unless I'm the one to get shot.
What if I'm the one to get shot!?!
?
Jeff, am I the one that gets shot?
No!  Don't kill me!
I'm such an idiot.
No-no-no-no-no-no-no.
What is going on?
I have to stop myself from starting this.
From ever time traveling at all.
Time traveling?  Howard, what's happening?
There's no time!
Howard stop!
I was lying. I didn't get the grant.
This letter is fake.
I came here because...
Well, it doesn't matter. I have to
go back and fix this, remember?
What are you talking about?
I'll do better this time.
I can change what happened.
Hi, this is Howard, leave me a message.
GodDamnIt, pick up!
- Howard?
- Jim!  Jim.
You have to stop me... from
doing what I'm about to do.
What are you talking about?
Howard?
Damn it!
Hello?
Yeah, I'm actually coming over.
I'll just...
No no listened.
- You have to stop me from...  Jim!
- I'm hanging up now.
No!
Well, there's still time.
No!  Don't kill me!
I'm such an idiot!
No-no-no-no-no-no-no.
What is going on?
I have to stop myself from starting this.
From ever time traveling at all.
Time traveling?  Howard what's happening?
No there's no time.
Howard stop.
I was lying,
I didn't get the grant.
This letter is fake.
I came here because...
Well, it doesn't matter.
I have to go back and fix this, remember?
What are you talking about?
I'll do better this time.
I can change what happened.
Can't leave yet.
OK?
We have to put this thing back in.  C'mon.
What is happening?
Howard will be here soon,
and when he gets here
he'll know you stole this.
Howard's dead.
No he's not.
Not yet.
There's still one more.
Quick, over hear.
Get down.  Hide.
Listen carefully.
You have to do this exactly the
same way, if this is going to work.
Gimme that.
Ha!
What happened?
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
You disappeared two more of you burst in
one of you shot the other one
then you jumped in the box
and disappeared again.
Wait,
I killed myself?
Yes.
Oh god!
No-no-no
The moment that I got into the machine
I must have started a chain of events...
Howard this is incredible, you've
created a working time machine.
No, no no no
I have to turn it off.
I-I-I-I have to destroy it
I have to...
- Howard stop!
- What!
You can't do that.
This machine is revolutionary.
It's better than anything
I could ever create
You can use it, to save yourself.
Oh, you mean go back again.
And stop yourself from ever killing
yourself in the first place.
None of this has to happen.
You can change it.
You know, maybe you're right.
I can fix this.
- What time is it?
- Twel...
12:07
And I got in at 12:04
I may just have enough time.
OK.
- Thanks James.
- You're welcome.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
OK.  Do you understand what's going on?
You know what you have to do?
Yes.
Get in there.
You sure this is going to work?
It already has.
Perfect.
Subtitles By MightyMike77070