www.titlovi.com
d
( all cheering )
AAH!
( birds chirping )
( sighs )
COME ON, RUDY.
( barking )
IT'S OKAY.
DO YOU WANNA SIT DOWN?
GOOD, BOY.
( bell rings )
HEY, CHRISTY. CHRISTY.
CHRISTY!
HEY, HOWARD HUGHES!
DID YOU NOT HEAR ME CALLING?
ELLIOTT WANTS TO KNOW
IF YOU'RE COMING TONIGHT.
UM...
IT'S FRIDAY NIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S THE SEASON KICK-OFF PARTY.
YOU HAVE TO BE THERE.
MINDY, I'M JUST
NOT THAT INTERESTED.
HEY, CHRISTY.
HE IS SO IN LOVE WITH YOU,
IT MAKES ME SICK.
KYLE WALKER'S
NOT IN LOVE WITH ME.
I HOPE NOT. YOU DON'T
NEED SOMEONE LIKE THAT
TO RUIN YOUR REPUTATION.
MY REPUTATION?
WELL, YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU CARE ANYWAY?
( indistinct chatter )
HEY, SWEETIE.
HEY, BABE.
SO, IS EVERYBODY
COMING TONIGHT?
OOH, CAN I DRIVE YOUR CAR?
NOBODY DRIVES
MY CAR BUT ME.
PLEASE?
( chuckles ) NO.
BUT YES, MOST OF THE TEAM
WILL BE THERE.
MOST OF THE TEAM,
BUT NOT ALL, RIGHT?
HE WOULDN'T DARE SHOW HIS FACE
AT SOCIAL EVENTS.
'CAUSE IF HE DID,
IT'D BE A SOCIAL FUNERAL.
( door closes )
ALL RIGHT, LET'S START
WHERE WE LEFT OFF YESTERDAY.
OPEN YOUR BOOKS TO PAGE 72.
CARTER, DID YOU HAVE ANY TROUBLE
WITH THAT LAST NIGHT?
AND FOLLOW ALONG WITH ME.
THE DIAMETER OF THE MOON
IS ABOUT 261,000 MILES.
AND THE DISTANCE
FROM THE EARTH TO THE MOON
IS ABOUT 283,000 MILES.
USE THESE NUMBERS
AND THE CONCEPT
OF SIMILAR TRIANGLES
TO COMPUTE THE DISTANCE.
( echoing )
HOW DOES THE DISTANCE
YOU COMPUTED
COMPARE TO THE DISTANCE
YOU MEASURED ON YOUR EXPERIMENT?
YES?
CAN I GET A DRINK OF WATER?
MM-HMM.
OH, MY GOD!
( students murmuring )
HEY. HEY!
WHAT IS WITH YOU?
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
REALLY WEIRD ALL DAY.
YOU'VE BEEN DREAMING
OF KYLE WALKER AND HOW MUCH
YOU WANT HIS HOT BODY, HUH?
I DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA COME TONIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO COME.
ANYBODY WHO'S ANYBODY'S
GONNA BE THERE.
I JUST WANNA GET SOME SLEEP.
YOU'RE COMING.
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
d
( cheering )
( indistinct chatter )
I DON'T KNOW WHY ELLIOTT
HATES KYLE. HE'S A GOOD GUY.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
FOR SOME REASON, HE JUST--
THAT'S THE FUNNIEST--
THAT'S MY SHOE!
SHUT THE HELL UP
OR I'LL KICK YOUR--
OH, SHIT.
( gagging )
HEY, LYNN, STILL COMING OVER
WEDNESDAY NIGHT?
I'LL BE THERE.
8:00, RIGHT?
BULLSHIT.
THIS PARTY'S
FOR THE WHOLE TEAM, RIGHT?
THE LAST I CHECKED,
I'M STILL ON THE ROSTER.
NOT FOR LONG YOU AIN'T.
JUST KEEP DRINKING, HUH?
WHAT THE HELL, MAN?
WHAT A DICK.
HEY.
NO, I LEAVE THE TRYING
UP TO OTHERS. I ACTUALLY
EMBARRASSED THE UNDERCLASSMEN.
RIGHT.
HEY, SO I MEANT TO ASK YOU
BUT YOU DISAPPEARED SO QUICKLY.
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY?
NOTHING.
OH, WELL, YEAH, I MEAN,
I SCREAM AND SHOUT "OH, MY GOD"
IN CLASS ALL THE TIME,
SO I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
IT'S-IT'S STUPID.
HEY, COME ON.
YOU CAN TELL ME, YOU KNOW.
WALKER! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU LOVE TO RUIN MY SHIT.
THIS JUST FIGURES.
LOOK, MAN, I WASN'T TRYING
TO RUIN ANYTHING, ALL RIGHT?
BULLSHIT. YOU WERE JUST TRYING
TO BE AN ASS AND SHOW UP
WHERE YOU'RE NOT WELCOME.
I WAS JUST LEAVING, ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU WERE.
SEE, YOU TRY TO MAKE FRIENDS,
BUT YOU HAVE NO FRIENDS.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
THEREFORE, NOBODY LIKES YOU.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE!
STOP IT. YOU'RE SO JUVENILE.
I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW.
WE'RE TRYING TO LEAVE NOW.
( indistinct chatter )
( engine starts )
( car drives off )
IF SHE NEVER BELIEVED YOU,
WHY SHOULD SHE BELIEVE ME?
MAYBE SHE WON'T,
BUT YOU WON'T KNOW
UNLESS YOU TRY.
( banging )
HELLO?
MOM?
( gasps )
CHRISTY?
MOM, WHAT?
MINDY CALLED.
I'M MAKING MYSELF
SOME BREAKFAST.
CAN I FIX YOU SOMETHING?
NOTHING. JUST COFFEE.
( sighs )
ROUGH NIGHT?
NOT REALLY.
WHAT TIME DID YOU GET IN?
AROUND MIDNIGHT.
WERE YOU DRINKING?
MOM...
WELL, WERE YOU?
NO.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH. IT'S FINE.
( phone rings )
HELLO?
HEY, COACH.
SO DID I TELL YOU
ABOUT JACOBS'?
NO. NO, I DIDN'T HEAR.
WELL, AFTER YOU LEFT
LAST NIGHT,
WE REALLY STARTED TO PARTY.
REALLY?
WELL, EVERYONE ELSE DID.
ELLIOTT AND I
STAYED IN THE BARN
MOST OF THE NIGHT.
OH, PLEASE, SPARE ME.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
IS HE OKAY?
OH, NO, HE'S TOTALLY FINE,
BUT HE GOT PULLED OVER.
AND GET THIS--
BECAUSE HE HAD
A TAIL LIGHT OUT.
AND THIS IS IMPORTANT
BECAUSE...?
WELL, HE HAD BEEN DRINKING.
DRINKING?
HE'S KICKED OFF THE TEAM.
YEAH. ELLIOTT'S BEEN
BITCHING ABOUT IT ALL DAY.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
THIS PISSED OFF SINCE
WE LOST CONFERENCE LAST YEAR.
RIGHT, BUT SHOULDN'T ELLIOTT
SINCE HE'S THE CAP--
HE WOULDN'T EVEN SPEAK
TO THE POOR KID.
OH, THIS IS CLASSIC.
WHAT IS?
( both chuckle )
I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
YEAH.
SO ANYWAY, I HOPE IT
DOESN'T EFFECT ELLIOTT'S...
GAMEPLAY,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
OH, MINDY...
( laughs )
IS THAT YOUR DAD?
YEAH.
WHO'S THE OLD GUY?
SOME PROFESSOR WHO WAS HELPING
MY DAD OUT WITH SOMETHING.
LOOK AT US.
MAN, I LOVE THAT OUTFIT.
I WAS CUTE.
( chuckles )
WHO KNEW, RIGHT?
YEAH, SURE, I'LL TALK TO HIM.
ALL RIGHT, COACH.
ALL RIGHT, BYE.
( birds chirping )
( engine starts )
WHAT AN IDIOT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
COACH CALLED ME.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU'RE NOT WANTED.
SO BEAT IT.
HEY.
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
I GOT PULLED OVER, ALL RIGHT?
WHY WERE YOU DRIVING?
GOD, IF IT'S NOT MY PARENTS,
IT'S YOU.
I THOUGHT I WAS OKAY.
IT WAS ALMOST
3:00 IN THE MORNING,
SO I DROVE HOME.
HALFWAY HOME,
DIXON PULLED ME OVER
FOR A BROKEN TAIL LIGHT
AND SMELLED BEER.
HE NAILED ME WITH A D.W.I.,
UNDERAGE DRINKING,
AND THE BROKEN TAIL LIGHT.
I EARNED MYSELF
A ONE-WAY TICKET
OFF THE HOCKEY TEAM
AND INTO A.A.
WELL, IF YOU NEED ANYTHING--
I WON'T.
LOOK, I TRY TO DO
THE RIGHT THING,
BUT FORGET IT.
YOU GOT YOURSELF
INTO THIS MESS...
YOU'LL PAY THE CONSEQUENCES.
( gasps )
( indistinct
radio transmission )
I CAN'T GET THIS
DAMN THING TO WORK. HERE.
TELL THEM THEY HAVE
A BIG EXAM NEXT WEEK.
STUDENTS OF MEAD HIGH,
CLASSES WILL BE CANCELED
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
I WOULD ASK THAT YOU PLEASE
LEAVE THE PREMISES IMMEDIATELY.
( phone rings )
HEY.
THEY BLOCKED TRAFFIC.
THEY'RE SAYING THAT
SCHOOL'S CANCELED.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HELLO? CHRISTY?
CHRISTY?
Girl: WHAT HAPPENED?
CAN'T SAY. JUST BACK UP.
HEY.
DO THEY KNOW WHO IT IS?
THEY AREN'T TALKING.
I HAD A DREAM LAST NIGHT.
DREAM ABOUT WHAT?
NEVER MIND.
IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
I HAVE TO GO INSIDE.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
A VERY GOOD IDEA.
KYLE, I HAD A DREAM
THAT SOMEONE DIED
IN THE GUYS' LOCKER ROOM.
I JUST WANNA SEE.
THERE'S NOTHING TO SEE, CHRIS.
THEY'RE REMOVING THE BODY.
PLEASE.
I JUST WANNA SEE
WHERE IT HAPPENED.
( indistinct chatter )
IT'S OKAY, YOU CAN GO.
I'M NOT LEAVING YOU.
KYLE, SERIOUSLY.
CHRIS, I'M NOT
LEAVING YOU, OKAY?
OKAY.
WAIT.
MY NOTEPAD.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
Man 1:
WHAT DO WE TELL HIS PARENTS?
Man 2: WE'RE GONNA TELL THEM
THAT IT LOOKS LIKE A SUICIDE.
Man 2: BUT WE'RE GONNA TREAT IT
LIKE A MURDER INVESTIGATION
UNTIL WE GET THE RESULTS BACK
FROM THE AUTOPSY.
Man 1:
WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER STUDENTS?
Man 2: WE'RE GONNA KEEP
THE SCHOOL LOCKED DOWN
UNTIL WE DO
A MORE THOROUGH INVESTIGATION.
Man 2: I'M GONNA NEED
A COMPLETE LIST OF EVERYBODY
THAT WAS IN THE SCHOOL
DURING THE WEEKEND,
JUST IN CASE.
WE MAKE SURE ALL STUDENTS
SIGN IN AND OUT IN THE OFFICE
OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL HOURS.
SO, DO YOU THINK
WE HAVE FOUL PLAY HERE?
WE SHOULD GO.
( sighs )
SOMETHING I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
WE-WE WERE JUST ACTUALLY GOING--
THAT'S ENOUGH, OKAY?
THAT'S ENOUGH!
JOHNSON, TAKE THESE TWO
DOWN TO THE STATION
FOR QUESTIONING.
SCHOOL'S OFF LIMITS
RIGHT NOW, KIDS.
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
MM-HMM.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
THIS IS A CRIME SCENE,
NOT A PLAYGROUND. LET'S MOVE.
( bangs locker )
HEY! SETTLE DOWN!
YOU GOT A LOT OF QUESTIONS
TO ANSWER.
( indistinct chatter )
I DON'T QUITE GRASP YOUR STORY.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS STUPID,
BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
YOU JUST HAD TO SEE
A CRIME SCENE.
YES.
A CRIME SCENE THAT YOU
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
EXCEPT THAT YOU
HAD A DREAM ABOUT IT.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
IT'S MY FAULT.
WE WANTED TO GET A CLOSER LOOK
AT WHAT WAS GOING ON.
IS THAT RIGHT?
NO, IT'S MY FAULT.
I MADE KYLE TAKE ME INSIDE.
SEE, I DON'T CARE
WHOSE FAULT IT WAS.
KYLE HAD A KEY TO THE SCHOOL...
AND THERE WAS NO FORCED ENTRY
INTO THE SCHOOL.
YOU WANNA EXPLAIN
THAT ONE, KYLE?
YOU CAN ASK MS. WILLIAMS
ABOUT THAT IF YOU WANT.
I DON'T WANNA ASK MS. WILLIAMS.
I'M ASKING YOU.
I'M A T.A. SO I HAVE IT
IN CASE THEY NEED ME TO SET UP
IN THE MORNINGS, ALL RIGHT?
DID MS. WILLIAMS NEED YOU
TO SET UP DURING THE WEEKEND?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING
IN THE SCHOOL ON THE WEEKEND?
THE TEAM WAS WORKING OUT.
MAYBE YOU CAN EXPLAIN
WHY THE ONLY TWO NAMES
ON THIS ENTIRE LIST
THAT DIDN'T SIGN OUT
WERE YOU AND ERIC JACOBS.
I GUESS I FORGOT.
YOU FORGOT.
ANY PARTICULAR REASON WHY
YOU MIGHT HAVE FORGOT, KYLE?
I DON'T THINK I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GETTING AT.
EVERY SINGLE MEMBER
ON THIS TEAM MANAGED TO SIGN OUT
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
WELL, UNLIKE THE REST
OF THE TEAM, I CARE
ABOUT MY FUTURE.
SO AFTER THE WORKOUT,
I WENT INTO THE ART ROOM
TO WORK ON A PROJECT.
REALLY? LET ME ASK YOU
ANOTHER QUESTION, KYLE.
WERE YOU AND ERIC JACOBS CLOSE?
WE'RE TEAMMATES,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN.
NO. WERE YOU CLOSE?
WERE YOU FRIENDS?
NO, NOT REALLY.
CHRISTY? WERE YOU
AND ERIC JACOBS CLOSE?
NO.
THEN WHY IN GOD'S NAME
WERE YOU TWO IN THAT SCHOOL?
IF HE WASN'T FRIENDS
WITH EITHER ONE OF YOU,
THEN HOW DID YOU
EVEN KNOW HE WAS MISSING?
I TOLD YOU, I HAD A DREAM
THAT SOMEONE DIED THERE.
THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU DREAMED IT.
THIS IS A QUIET TOWN,
AND I WANNA KEEP IT THAT WAY.
YOU TWO STAY PUT
UNTIL YOUR PARENTS ARRIVE.
( door closes )
I'M REALLY SORRY, KYLE.
DON'T BE.
I FEEL REALLY BAD.
IT'S FINE.
STILL, FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I AM SORRY.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE,
ALL RIGHT?
OH, BABY,
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
ARE YOU OKAY?
Kyle: MOM. MOM, I'M FINE.
YOU CAN LET GO NOW.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING, KYLE?
WHY THE HELL WERE YOU THERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
IT'S A LONG STORY.
SERIOUSLY, CAN WE
TALK ABOUT THIS LATER?
I DIDN'T WANNA TELL YOU BECAUSE
I DIDN'T THINK IT MATTERED.
HONEY, YOU CAN TELL ME ANYTHING.
I KNOW.
( phone rings )
THIS IS DIXON.
REALLY?
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN?
I APPRECIATE YOU
LETTING ME KNOW.
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS THE CORONER'S OFFICE.
THEY'VE COMPLETED THE AUTOPSY.
AND?
ERIC JACOBS' DEATH
WAS NOT A SUICIDE.
THERE'S BRUISING ON HIS NECK
TO INDICATE THAT
HE WAS STRANGLED.
WHOEVER DID THIS
STAGED IT TO MAKE IT
LOOK LIKE HE HUNG HIMSELF.
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU SAYING,
HOWARD?
I'M SAYING THIS
IS OFFICIALLY
A MURDER INVESTIGATION.
( engine starts )
MAY I HELP YOU?
PROFESSOR McGREGOR?
YES?
MY NAME'S CHRISTY DAWSON.
YES, TED'S DAUGHTER.
I WONDERED WHEN
YOU WOULD STOP BY.
PLEASE, COME IN.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHERE ELSE TO GO.
MY FATHER SPOKE OF YOU OFTEN.
HE TOLD ME THAT YOU TAUGHT
A CLASS IN PARAPSYCHOLOGY,
AND I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE...
THAT I MAY
BETTER EXPLAIN THINGS TO YOU.
SINCE HE DIED, I'VE BEEN
HAVING THIS RECURRING DREAM
ABOUT MY DAD.
I WOULDN'T HAVE THOUGHT
ANYTHING OF IT, BUT...
IT SEEMED REAL.
DID YOU FATHER SPEAK TO YOU?
YOU WERE RIGHT TO COME TO ME.
I WONDERED IF
YOU WOULD RECEIVE IT.
SORRY?
YOUR GIFT.
YOU ARE A DREAMER, CHRISTY.
YOU HAVE THE ABILITY
TO DREAM OF AND EVEN INTERACT
WITH A SPIRIT OR GHOST.
I HAVE NO DOUBT IN MY MIND
THAT YOU WERE TALKING WITH
YOUR FATHER IN THAT DREAM.
IT'S A TEST,
HIS WAY OF MAKING SURE
THAT YOU POSSESS
THE TRAITS
AND QUALITIES NEEDED.
WHY DIDN'T HE
SAY ANYTHING TO ME
WHEN HE WAS ALIVE?
YOUR ABILITIES
ARE STILL ADVANCING, CHRISTY.
THEY WILL SOON
ESCALATE FAR BEYOND
THOSE YOUR FATHER HAD.
IT WILL HAPPEN IN STAGES.
YOUR COMMUNICATIONS
WITH THE SPIRIT WORLD
WILL BECOME
MORE UNDERSTANDABLE.
YOU MAY EVEN NEED
TO TAKE VENGEANCE
FOR THE WRONGFUL DEATH
OF A SPIRIT,
FREEING IT FROM CAPTIVITY
ON OUR PLANE OF EXISTENCE.
I HAVE BEEN HAVING
THIS NEW DREAM LATELY...
WITH A LITTLE BOY.
HE SEEMS FAMILIAR TO ME, BUT...
YOU WILL FIND OUT SOON
I'M SURE.
YOU HAVE
ALL THE ATTRIBUTES
TO BECOME
A VERY ADVANCED MEDIUM.
MY MOTHER
WILL NEVER UNDERSTAND THIS.
SHE'S NOT SUPPOSED TO.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU
WOULD NEVER GET HOME.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU TODAY?
THE RUMOR MILL
HAS BEEN RUNNING NONSTOP.
SO I HEARD THAT YOU
AND WALKER WERE ARRESTED.
WE WEREN'T ARRESTED,
WE WERE QUESTIONED,
AND IT WAS ENTIRELY MY FAULT,
NOT KYLE'S.
SO YOU WEREN'T HANDCUFFED
AND TAKEN DOWNTOWN?
I THOUGHT IT WOULD MEAN
WALKER WOULD BE OFF THE TEAM.
GLAD TO SEE
YOU HAVE YOUR PRIORITIES, MIN.
WHAT?
SO ANYWAY,
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED?
I'M SURPRISED YOU'RE NOT
TELLING ME WHAT HAPPENED,
RUMORS ARE JUST
FARFETCHED ALTERCATIONS
OF THE TRUTH.
ALTERCATIONS?
WHATEVER.
SO DID YOU REALLY
BREAK INTO THE SCHOOL?
KYLE SORT OF HAD A KEY.
A KEY? TO THE SCHOOL?
TO THE ART ROOM. HE'S A T.A.
HE IS SUCH A NERD.
WHY DO YOU DO THAT?
DO WHAT?
BAD MOUTH KYLE ALL THE TIME.
I DON'T.
OKAY, SO MAYBE I DO,
BUT KYLE WALKER'S A LOSER
AND HE DESERVES IT.
WELL, HE DOES.
OKAY. WELL,
WE CAN TALK ABOUT THIS LATER.
BUT-BUT YOU DIDN'T FINISH
TELLING ME WHAT HAPPENED.
AND I DON'T DOUBT
YOU'RE GONNA CALL ME LATER
AND ASK ME EVERYTHING IN DETAIL.
( sighs )
I'M SORRY,
I'M JUST REALLY TIRED.
BUT I REALLY WANNA KNOW.
JUST CALL ME LATER.
BYE.
( car engine starts )
( phone rings )
YOU MISS ME ALREADY?
NOT WHAT I WAS EXPECTING,
BUT I'LL TAKE IT.
KYLE?
YEAH. DID I CALL AT A BAD TIME?
NO. MINDY JUST LEFT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS HER CALLING.
AND HOW IS THE DRAMA QUEEN?
THE SAME.
WELL, NO SURPRISE THERE.
OH, NO?
NO.
SO WHAT'S UP?
WITH THE CALL, I MEAN.
WELL, I GUESS
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED TODAY,
I JUST NEEDED TO TALK TO SOMEONE
FOR BREAKING INTO
A RESTRICTED AREA.
YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
IT'S JUST REALLY...
CONFUSING.
YEAH, AND...
WEIRD.
YES.
GOD, THANK YOU.
LISTEN, CHRISTY, I, UM...
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON, KYLE.
WELL, NEITHER DO I, BUT THAT'S
NOT WHAT I WAS GONNA ASK.
YOU WEREN'T?
NO.
YEAH, I FEEL STUPID.
NO, NO, NO, DON'T-DON'T
FEEL STUPID. I, UM...
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF, UM...
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE AT
THE GAME TOMORROW NIGHT.
I'M WORKING AT THE RINK.
RIGHT.
SO I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
BYE, KYLE.
BYE.
WHAT A MORON.
( engine starts )
Mindy: ELLIOTT'S BEEN
BITCHING ABOUT IT ALL DAY.
Kyle:
WELL, IF YOU NEED ANYTHING--
Eric: I WON'T.
Kyle: YOU GOT YOURSELF
INTO THIS MESS...
YOU'LL PAY THE CONSEQUENCES.
Cop 1:
STUDENTS OF MEAD HIGH,
CLASSES WILL BE CANCELED
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
I WOULD ASK THAT YOU PLEASE
LEAVE THE PREMISES IMMEDIATELY.
Cop 2:
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
Kyle: WE-WE WERE JUST ACTUALLY--
Cop 3: THAT'S ENOUGH, OKAY?
THAT'S ENOUGH!
Prof. McGregor:
YOU ARE A DREAMER, CHRISTY.
JUST LIKE YOUR FATHER.
HI.
UM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHERE'S YOUR MOM?
SHE CAN'T HELP ME.
WHAT?
THERE WILL BE MORE.
MORE?
MORE PEOPLE WILL DIE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IT WON'T STOP.
NOT UNLESS YOU STOP IT.
HOW? I-I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT HAS TO BE YOU.
WHY ME?
YOU SAW ME.
Woman:
CLASSES AT MEAD HIGH SCHOOL
OF LOCAL SOPHOMORE
ERIC JACOBS CONTINUES.
POLICE TOLD THIS REPORTER
THAT UNTIL MORE EVIDENCE
IS GATHERED,
THEY WILL HAVE TO WAIT
TO ARREST THEIR KEY SUSPECT.
AND THE ICE DOGS
TRAIL THE BLADES 0-2.
( booing )
THE PUCK IS PICKED UP
BY CARTER VAN OWEN.
AND HE SHOOTS!
( buzzer sounds )
SCORES!
IT'S GREAT TO SEE HIM
NOT SHYING AWAY FROM THE PUCK.
HIS COLLARBONE WAS BROKEN
AT LAST YEAR'S CONFERENCE FINAL
AGAINST THE BLADES.
THIS COMEBACK
COULDN'T LOOK ANY BETTER.
( cheering )
SMITHE TAKES THE PUCK
INTO THE ZONE
SIX MINUTES LEFT
IN THE SECOND PERIOD.
WHOO! GO, ELLIOTT!
GO, ELLIOTT!
CALM DOWN,
YOU'LL HAVE AN ANEURISM.
DANIEL COMING AROUND
THE RIGHT SIDE.
THE PUCK GETS LOSE
AND FALLS BACK TO SMITHE.
SAVED BY HANSEN. HERE COMES
WALKER WITH THE REBOUND.
KYLE WALKER HAS JUST TIED UP
THE GAME FOR THE ICE DOGS!
d
( cheering )
VAN OWEN OFF THE LINE CHANGE.
PASSES UP TO WALKER.
( whistle blows )
OH, AND THE NET COMES OFF.
AS WE KICK OFF
THE THIRD PERIOD.
RIGHT HERE.
OH, I THINK SHE WENT
TO THE BATHROOM OR SOMETHING.
GO! GO!
YEAH!
HEY, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING!
NUMBER EIGHT
WITH THE PUCK.
HE PASSES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AND HE SCORES!
( cheering )
AND THE PUCK
IS PICKED UP BY VAN OWEN!
NO, NO.
COME ON, COACH!
KYLE, LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
d
( cheering )
FOLLOWED BY VAN OWEN
AND TURNER.
TURNER PASSES TO VAN OWEN.
OH, WITH THREE SECONDS LEFT
IN THE GAME,
THIS IS A HUGE COMEBACK
FOR THE ICE DOGS.
WHAT A WAY TO START THE SEASON.
( buzzer sounds )
( cheering )
GOOD JOB, BOYS.
HEY, YOU STICKING AROUND?
YEAH, MAYBE.
GOOD, I'LL LOOK FOR YOU.
OKAY.
WHOA. EASY,
SMITHEY.
YEAH, SHIT, SMITHEY.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
HIS MOM'S GONNA HAVE
TO ICE THAT NOW.
DUDE, YOU'RE SUCH A DUMBASS.
( throws puck )
I'M OUT. GRETZKY'S OUT.
HAT TRICK HERE
NEEDS TO TAKE A CRAP.
SHUT UP, VAN OWEN.
GET OUT OF HERE.
OH, CAN I HAVE YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
YOU'RE MY HERO. ( laughs )
HA HA. YEAH, YEAH.
HEY, WALKER, GREAT GAME.
NICE GAME, BUD.
THANKS.
DON'T THINK THIS
CHANGES ANYTHING.
ONE GOOD GAME
DOESN'T MAKE YOU A SOMEBODY.
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE THE RESPECT
I GET AS CAPTAIN.
YEAH, WELL, KEEP TELLING
YOURSELF THAT, HUH?
WHEN I'M ON THE ICE,
I PLAY FOR ME.
MAYBE THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM.
GOOD GAME TONIGHT, KYLE.
YEAH, YOU, TOO.
LOOK, A BUNCH OF US GUYS
ARE GETTING TOGETHER
AT MY HOUSE TOMORROW NIGHT.
WE THOUGHT IT'D BE
GOOD TO GET TOGETHER
FOR SUPPORT AND SHIT.
JACOBS WASN'T
THAT BAD OF A GUY.
HE JUST LIKED THE ATTENTION
HE GOT WHEN SMITHE STARTED
STICKING UP FOR HIM.
WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
IT'S NOT JUST
SMITHE AND JACOBS.
THE WHOLE TEAM ACTED LIKE
I WAS SOME SORT OF A VIRUS
AND NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN
EVERYTHING'S DIFFERENT?
LOOK, YOU PLAYED WELL TONIGHT.
ISN'T IT ENOUGH
YOU'VE REGAINED OUR RESPECT?
WHAT DID I EVER DO
TO LOSE IT, HUH?
( chuckles )
( locks )
ELLIOTT. ELLIOTT, WAIT.
SWEETIE, STOP.
GOOD GOD!
GET UP.
WELL, YOU COULD HELP ME.
PLEASE.
YOU CAN GO ON WITHOUT ME.
I WAS SO EXCITED.
YOU WERE DOING SO WELL.
LISTEN TO ME, MINDY.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS,
OKAY? GOD DAMN IT, MINDY.
JUST SHUT UP!
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW?
YEAH.
JESUS CHRIST, KYLE.
SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
THEY WENT HOME, I GUESS.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
THE OTHER GUYS SAID.
TWO-FACED SONS OF BITCHES
IS WHAT THEY ARE.
WELL, THAT'S A LITTLE HARSH,
DON'T YOU THINK?
NO, I DON'T, ACTUALLY.
NEVER MIND.
I'M SORRY.
CHRISTY, THERE'S BEEN SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO ASK YOU
FOR A WHILE NOW.
YEAH?
LISTEN, I KNOW THE TIMING IS BAD
WITH EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED.
I JUST DON'T WANT ANYTHING ELSE
TO HAPPEN BEFORE.
WHERE YOU GOING?
PLEASE, JUST TALK TO ME.
( groaning )
I'M GONNA GO CALL 911.
CHRISTY, IT'S NOT
THE WAY IT LOOKS.
DAMN IT.
THANKS, LYNNIE.
ANY TIME.
HEY, YOU PROMISE
YOU'LL GIVE ME A CALL
IF HE KEEPS THIS UP?
YEAH, HE'S FINE.
HE JUST NEEDED TIME
TO COOL OFF.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S GOOD, YEAH.
TAKE CARE.
BYE.
SEE YOU LATER.
BE CAREFUL.
Christy: NO, IT'S NOT A JOKE.
I'M SERIOUS!
( groaning )
ELLIOTT?
ELLIOTT, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WHERE'S ELLIOTT?
IT WAS JUST--
MINDY, STOP!
Kyle: ELLIOTT, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WHAT DID YOU DO?!
WHAT? I DIDN'T--
I DIDN'T DO THIS.
IT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
WHAT, YOU'RE
COVERING FOR HIM NOW?
YEAH. NO. WHAT?
DON'T MOVE.
DON'T TOUCH HIM!
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP.
YOU'RE A LOUSY LIAR.
I SWEAR TO GOD,
IF ANYTHING IS WRONG WITH HIM,
I WILL KILL YOU MYSELF!
MINDY...
MINDY, WE FOUND THEM LIKE THIS.
SHUT UP. SHUT UP!
WHAT, YOU DIDN'T
HURT HIM ENOUGH LAST YEAR?
YOU THOUGHT
YOU'D FINISH HIM OFF?!
( groans )
I'M SO SORRY, SWEETIE.
IT'S OKAY, I GOT YOU.
IT'S OKAY, HELP'S COMING.
IT'S OKAY, SHE'S JUST UPSET.
SHE NEEDS SOMEONE TO BLAME.
WELL, WHY WOULD
SOMETHING HAPPEN TO ME?
THEY ALWAYS LOOK LIKE THIS
AFTER A GAME.
( siren wailing )
CHRISTY.
( siren wails )
( indistinct
radio transmission )
I'M SORRY.
Cop: THE FIRST TIME
YOU SAW THE VICTIMS
WAS WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
YES. WAIT,
I MEAN NO, NO, NO. I WAS...
YES, I WAS WITH CHRISTY,
BUT NO, SHE'S NOT MY GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT'S WITH THE KNUCKLES?
I TOLD YOU.
I GOT A NEW PAIR OF GLOVES AND
THEY AREN'T BROKEN IN YET.
- YEAH.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT THIS LOOKS LIKE
FROM OUR PERSPECTIVE, CHRISTY.
I DO.
THEN YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY I HAVE TO TAKE YOU
TO THE STATION
FOR FURTHER QUESTIONING.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU KNOW,
I-I JUST DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
YOU HAVE BEEN
AT TWO CRIME SCENES
IN THE SAME NUMBER OF DAYS.
AND?
AND I'M TAKING YOU IN
FOR FURTHER QUESTIONING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ARE YOU CUFFING ME?
ROB.
I'M TAKING HIM IN, CHIEF.
ON WHAT GROUNDS?
WHAT? YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
I'LL ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS
YOU WANT.
WERE YOU WITH HIM
ALL NIGHT, CHRISTY?
CAN YOU BE ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN
THAT HE DIDN'T KILL
CARTER VAN OWEN?
OR ASSAULT JOSEPH TURNER?
OR ELLIOTT SMITHE?
HE WOULDN'T.
I NEED YOU TO BE
ABSOLUTELY SURE.
HE... I... KYLE, I--
IT'S OKAY.
I'LL GO WITH THEM.
NO, I'LL GO WITH YOU.
AFRAID THAT'S
NOT POSSIBLE, CHRISTY.
ROB, WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE CARE OF MS. DAWSON HERE.
I'D LIKE A WORD
WITH MR. WALKER... ALONE.
( siren wails )
( indistinct
radio transmission )
( engine starts )
( siren wails )
STOP IT.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO BE COMFORTABLE.
I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE--
KYLE WALKER
BETTER WATCH HIMSELF.
THE NEXT TIME I SEE HIM,
I'M GONNA RIP HIS EYES OUT.
I'M JUST GLAD
YOU SHOWED UP WHEN YOU DID.
OTHERWISE, WHO KNOWS
WHAT COULD'VE HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW,
I KNEW HE WAS A FREAK.
BUT I DIDN'T THINK
HE'D GO AS FAR AS...
( sighs )
ANYWAY...
I STOPPED HIM.
( chuckles )
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D EVER DO
IF I LOST YOU.
COME HERE.
( chuckles )
I THINK YOU'LL BE BACK
TO YOUR OLD SELF IN NO TIME.
OW.
I'M SORRY.
DID I HURT YOU?
IT'S NOTHING THAT WON'T HEAL.
I TOLD YOU,
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU DO US
ALL A FAVOR AND KEEP
THAT BIG MOUTH SHUT.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST HAVE
JOHNSON JERK YOU OFF
AND GET IT OVER WITH.
LET'S SEE HOW TOUGH
YOU ARE INSIDE, FELLA, HUH?
( beeping )
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT TO DO THIS.
DON'T I? YOU'RE NOT
A MINOR ANYMORE, KYLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YOU CAN'T ARREST ME.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
DON'T TELL ME
HOW TO DO MY JOB.
I CAN HOLD YOU
FOR UP TO 48 HOURS.
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING
YOU WANTED TO KNOW.
WELL, EVERYTHING YOU SAID
DOESN'T QUITE ADD UP.
DID YOU CHECK THE WOODS?
DID ANYBODY EVEN TRY
TO LOOK FOR ANOTHER SUSPECT?
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
WE ALREADY SPOKE
WITH ELLIOTT SMITHE.
HE GAVE US A STATEMENT
TELLING US THAT YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT ASSAULTED THEM.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT JOE?
HE'LL TELL YOU I WASN'T THERE.
JOE TURNER?
JOE TURNER'S GONNA BE LUCKY
IF HE EVEN LIVES, KYLE.
I'M FINE, DAD, REALLY.
YOUR MOTHER CAN BRING SOMETHING
OVER LATER IF YOU NEED IT.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY.
I DOUBT THAT.
LOOK AT ME, DAD.
HOW IS EVERYTHING
GONNA BE OKAY?
I'M COMPLETELY FUCKED!
WATCH YOUR LANGUAGE.
HOCKEY'S THE LEAST
OF OUR WORRIES.
ARE WE DONE?
THIS ISN'T A GAME, SON.
YOU COULD STILL
BE IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
( chuckles )
WELL, THANKS.
BUT I'M A BIG BOY NOW.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
( chuckles )
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
TURNER'S DEAD.
( door opens )
WE'LL CONTINUE THIS LATER.
HEY. IF YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR MINDY,
SHE SHOULD BE BACK SOON.
SHE WAS HERE ALL NIGHT.
SHE WENT HOME TO GET SOME SLEEP.
YEAH, I DIDN'T SLEEP MUCH
LAST NIGHT EITHER.
( chuckles )
OUT PARTYING, HUH?
NOT EXACTLY.
HOW YOU DOING, L?
I'M GREAT, CHRIS.
I THINK I'LL RUN
A MARATHON LATER.
SERIOUSLY.
I CAME TO SEE HOW YOU WERE.
I'M IN PAIN.
I HAVEN'T SHOWERED.
I HATE BEING IN HERE AGAIN.
IT MAKES ME FEEL WEAK.
YOU LOOK PRETTY GOOD, THOUGH,
ASIDE FROM THE BRUISES.
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
( chuckles )
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
IT WAS WALKER.
HE'S COMPLETELY LOST IT.
WE'RE NOT KIDS ANYMORE.
KYLE'S A DANGEROUS GUY.
YOU SHOULD STAY AWAY FROM HIM.
WHAT HAPPENED TO US?
NOTHING.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
KYLE WOULD NEVER HURT YOU.
WHY WOULD I LIE ABOUT
SOMEONE TRYING TO KILL ME?
HEY. I BROUGHT THE, UH--
YOUR FRIEND HERE
IS SIDING WITH
HER BOYFRIEND.
WHAT?
IT WAS DARK.
ELLIOTT MUST NOT HAVE SEEN--
I SAW PERFECTLY WELL.
COME ON,
YOU KNOW HE WOULDN'T HURT YOU.
GET OUT OF HERE. YOU OBVIOUSLY
DON'T RESPECT OUR FRIENDSHIP
IF YOU'RE TRUSTING SOME FREAK
OVER TWO OF YOUR BEST FRIENDS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
TWO OF MY BEST FRIENDS WOULD--
WE WERE BOTH THERE.
WALKER WAS STANDING
OVER ELLIOTT.
THAT'S ALL THE PROOF I NEED.
JUST GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
SO HOW'S THE SEASON GOING?
THERE IS NO SEASON.
BUT I HEARD
THINGS WERE GOING WELL.
WELL, THEN YOU HEARD WRONG.
MR. SMITHE...
I-I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU REMEMBER ME,
BUT MY NAME'S CHRISTY DAWSON--
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
I'M A LITTLE DISTRACTED,
AS YOU CAN PROBABLY TELL.
YEAH, I CAN UNDERSTAND.
IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
MAYBE.
WHAT IS IT?
WELL, I DON'T WANNA PRY, BUT...
FORGET IT.
NO, TELL ME.
YOU WON'T OFFEND ME.
I KNOW THEY DON'T GET ALONG MUCH
ANYMORE, BUT KYLE WOULD NEVER DO
ANYTHING TO HURT ELLIOTT.
CHRISTY, ELLIOTT'S UPSET.
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT,
THEY CANCELED THE REST
OF OUR HOCKEY SEASON.
HE'S A LOT OF THINGS,
BUT HE'S NOT A LIAR.
THE POLICE WON'T PUT
THE WRONG MAN IN JAIL.
THEY ALREADY HAVE.
GO HOME, CHRISTY.
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS
WHERE ELLIOTT'S CONCERNED.
IT WAS NICE CHATTING WITH YOU.
( laughter )
GO! GO!
GET OVER HERE!
I GOT IT!
OVER HERE!
COME ON!
ELLIOTT.
YOU KNOW THAT
PICTURE OF ELLIOTT?
YEAH.
I THINK HE'S CUTE.
I THINK KYLE'S CUTE.
I DON'T LIKE KYLE.
HOW COME?
JUST BECAUSE.
HEY, CHRISTY.
HI. HI, KYLE.
HEY.
WHO ARE YOU?
THIS IS MY FRIEND MINDY.
SHE JUST MOVED HERE
FROM INDIANA.
HEY.
Boy: HEY, GUYS,
ARE WE PLAYING OR NOT?
CHRISTY, YOU WANNA PLAY?
SURE. MINDY?
OKAY, BUT I AM NOT
PLAYING GOALIE.
( beeping )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I HAD TO SEE YOU.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M HANGING IN THERE.
KYLE, I'M REALLY SORRY.
I MESSED UP.
CHRIS, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
I'M IN HERE.
IT WAS MY DREAM.
CHRISTY...
I WENT AND SAW ELLIOTT TODAY.
WHAT'D HE HAVE TO SAY?
HE SAID YOU WERE THE ONE THAT...
HE LOOKED ME IN THE EYE
AND TOLD ME THAT
YOU ATTACKED THEM.
LISTEN TO ME. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH ELLIOTT.
BUT ALL I KNOW IS THAT
HE STILL THINKS I BROKE
HIS COLLARBONE LAST YEAR.
UGH!
ELLIOTT!
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
YEAH, WELL,
TRY TELLING HIM THAT.
WE WERE BEST FRIENDS.
I NEVER WOULD'VE
DONE THAT TO HIM.
I KNOW.
YOU WOULDN'T LIE TO ME,
WOULD YOU?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I SPENT THE LAST YEAR
CONFUSED OUT OF MY MIND AS TO
WHY WE WEREN'T FRIENDS ANYMORE.
AND NOW?
I MISS YOU.
( door opens )
Man: MS. DAWSON, TIME'S UP.
KYLE...
DON'T GET YOURSELF
INTO ANY MORE TROUBLE.
OKAY, I'LL TRY NOT TO.
YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON I KNOW
THAT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE
I MIGHT NOT BE CRAZY AFTER ALL.
COME ON. YOU'RE ABOUT AS CRAZY
AS I AM A MURDERER.
( birds chirping )
HONEY, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
LOOK, I CAN CALL THE HOSPITAL,
GET SOMEONE TO COVER.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I'LL BE FINE.
IT'S OKAY, GO.
YOU'LL CALL MY CELL PHONE
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING AT ALL.
AND YOU'LL LOCK THE DOOR
AFTER I GO...
AND AGAIN
AFTER LYNN GETS HERE.
I WILL.
OKAY.
MOM...
KYLE'S GONNA BE OKAY, RIGHT?
HONEY, IF YOU THINK
KYLE IS INNOCENT, I DO, TOO.
I TRUST YOU.
HOWIE'S GONNA SEE THAT AS WELL.
YOU TRY TO GET SOME REST, OKAY?
I LOVE YOU, MOM.
I LOVE YOU, TOO, BABY.
( phone rings )
LYNN, YOU BETTER HAVE
A DAMN GOOD REASON
FOR BEING LATE.
HELLO?
LYNN?
( dial tone )
( phone beeps )
Mindy: STOP IT! ( laughs )
OH, HI, CHRISTY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
SHH. UM, WHAT? WHEN?
SHH. HUH?
I DIDN'T CALL BEFORE.
ANYWAY, I DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA MAKE IT TONIGHT.
WHAT? WHY?
I JUST--
I'M SORRY.
SOMETHING'S COME UP.
YOU'LL BE OKAY,
THOUGH, WON'T YOU?
I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE SAFE.
YEAH, I'VE GOT THE DOG.
( chuckles )
OKAY, THANKS, CHRISTY.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
( dial tone )
( phone beeps )
BYE.
( sighs )
( crickets chirping )
( beeping )
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
I HAVE A FEELING
SOMETHING TERRIBLE
IS GONNA HAPPEN.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE HERE,
EVERYBODY'S SAFE.
YEAH, DON'T COUNT ON IT.
EXCUSE ME?
I SAID DON'T COUNT ON IT!
I'M A SITTING DUCK IN HERE!
YOU'LL BE FINE.
IT'S PRETTY EASY TO START
SLINGING AROUND ACCUSATIONS
WHILE YOU'RE
SITTING IN HERE, KYLE.
I'M NOT ACCUSING ANYBODY,
BUT PEOPLE ARE DYING
AND I DO NOT WANT TO BE NEXT!
YEAH, UM...
I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
I'M INNOCENT!
( bangs door )
( crickets chirping )
RUDY. COME ON.
( choking )
( banging )
( beeping )
WHO'S WATCHING
ELLIOTT TONIGHT?
WHY WOULD WE
WANNA WATCH HIM?
I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE TAKING SHIFTS
KEEPING AN EYE ON HIM.
YOU JUST DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
WE ALREADY CAUGHT THE KILLER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
WHY WOULD ANYBODY LIE ABOUT
SOMEBODY TRYING TO KILL THEM?
( groans ) YOU HAVE NO IDEA
THE MISTAKE THAT YOU'RE MAKING.
( groans )
WALKER? WALKER!
( grunts )
( groans )
( thunder rumbles )
( gasps )
( panting )
DON'T TOUCH WHAT'S MINE!
( gasps )
( panting )
( indistinct chatter )
WHAT THE HELL KIND OF HOSPITAL
ARE YOU RUNNING OVER THERE?
NO, FORGET IT.
NO, WE'LL FIND HIM OUR SELF.
WHAT HAPPENED?
Christy: HOWIE.
HE WAS IN MY HOUSE.
HE'S TRYING TO KILL ME.
WHO'S TRYING
TO KILL YOU, CHRISTY?
I FOUND MY DOG
AND IT WAS ON MY MIRROR
AND THE BARN.
WHAT BARN? WOULD YOU
PLEASE JUST SLOW DOWN,
START FROM THE BEGINNING,
AND TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED.
CHIEF. ( sighs )
WALKER ESCAPED.
GIVE US A SECOND, CHRISTY.
HOWIE--
PLEASE, JUST GIVE US A SECOND.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, ESCAPED?
I MEAN, GONE, SIR.
YOU FIND HIM,
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH TROUBLE YOU CAN CAUSE?
YES, SIR.
THEN YOU FIND HIM... NOW.
ELLIOTT SMITHE IS MISSING, TOO.
SMITHE AND WALKER?
I DON'T KNOW
IF WE HAVE ANOTHER VICTIM
ON OUR HANDS HERE, ROB,
OR IF THEY'RE
WORKING AS A TEAM.
( sighs )
Boy: STOP IT! LET GO!
STOP IT, ELLIOTT!
LET ME GO!
LET GO?
YOU WANT ME TO LET GO?
ELLIOTT, KNOCK IT OFF!
Woman:
NINE-YEAR-OLD CHARLIE SMITHE
OF WAUPACA
DIED OUT ON THE STAIRWAY
CHARLIE'S DEATH CURRENTLY
REMAINS UNDER INVESTIGATION
THAT THEY'RE CLOSING
THE INVESTIGATION.
DIXON WAS ALSO THE FIRST
TO ARRIVE AT THE SCENE.
AFTER FALLING DOWN
A FLIGHT OF STAIRS
AT HIS FAMILY'S HOME.
MOM! DAD! STOP IT!
HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO SAY IT?
DON'T TOUCH WHAT'S MINE!
I WON'T! I PROMISE!
YOU'RE HURTING ME!
NO, I'M NOT!
SMITHE DIED AT HIS HOME
SHORTLY BEFORE 3:00 P.M.
BUT THIS REPORT
HAS NOT BEEN RELEASED.
CHARLIE'S DEATH STILL REMAINS
UNDER INVESTIGATION.
A WITNESS HAS COME FORWARD
AND SAID THE FALL
WAS NOT ACCIDENTAL.
AT HIS FAMILY'S HOME.
A WITNESS HAS COME FORWARD
AND SAID THE FALL
WAS NOT ACCIDENTAL.
POLICE INVESTIGATING THE DEATH
OF NINE-YEAR-OLD CHARLIE SMITHE
THE SUSPECT WOULD BE
CHARGED WITH RECKLESS
OR INTENTIONAL HOMICIDE.
SMITHE DIED AT HIS HOME
SHORTLY BEFORE 3:00 P.M.
POLICE INVESTIGATING THE DEATH
OF NINE-YEAR-OLD CHARLIE SMITHE
BUT THIS REPORT
HAS NOT BEEN RELEASED.
POLICE OFFICER HOWARD DIXON
WAS AMONG THOSE
ATTENDING CHARLIE'S FUNERAL
ON TUESDAY.
THE SUSPECT WOULD BE
CHARGED WITH RECKLESS
OR INTENTIONAL HOMICIDE.
AN ARREST OF AN
UNIDENTIFIED SUBJECT
WAS MADE A WEEK LATER.
AN ARREST OF AN
UNIDENTIFIED SUBJECT
WAS MADE A WEEK LATER.
TO BE CONSIDERED
AN ACCIDENT.
( crickets chirping )
( engine starts )
WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME THIS SOONER?
BECAUSE ANGELA AND I
DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
WE COME RUNNING IN,
CHARLIE'S JUST LYING THERE.
ELLIOTT AND KYLE WERE BOTH
AT THE TOP OF THE STAIRS.
WE THOUGHT IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
WHAT'S YOUR EXCUSE NOW, LARRY?
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
UH, STILL NO SIGN OF 'EM, SIR.
BUT, UM,
FORENSICS WANTS TO KNOW
IF YOU WANNA DO AN AUTOPSY
ON THE MARINER GIRL.
MINDY MARINER?
ELLIOTT'S GIRLFRIEND?
TELL THEM TO GO AHEAD.
LARRY, LISTEN,
I WANT YOU TO GO HOME
AND I WANT YOU TO WAIT THERE.
IF ELLIOTT SHOWS UP,
YOU CONTACT ME DIRECTLY.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
YEAH.
ROB, LISTEN, I NEED
EVERYBODY WE HAVE OUT THERE
LOOKING FOR THOSE KIDS.
I DON'T WANT THEM
LEAVING OUR JURISDICTION.
( tires screech )
( gasps )
( grunting )
( groans )
ISN'T THIS PERFECT?
YOU AND ME, ALONE, HERE,
NOBODY ELSE AROUND?
WHERE'S KYLE?
HOW THE HELL SHOULD I KNOW?
ISN'T HE YOUR ACCOMPLICE
IN ALL THIS?
( grunts ) NO.
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU THINK THAT?
HE WAS WITH YOU
WHEN CHARLIE DIED.
( chuckles ) NICE.
YOU KNOW... ( grunts )
I KNEW THE LITTLE KID
IN MY DREAM LOOKED FAMILIAR,
BUT IT WASN'T UNTIL I HEARD
YOU HELPED KYLE ESCAPE
THAT I REALIZED WHO HE WAS.
I DIDN'T HELP.
WHY'D YOU KILL CHARLIE?
I DIDN'T KILL HIM.
HE FELL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
DON'T YOU GET IT?
IT'S YOU.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN YOU.
IF KYLE'S THE KILLER,
YOU WON'T WANT HIM ANYMORE.
AND TURNER...
TURNER WAS A LUCKY BREAK
BECAUSE IF HE HAD WOKEN UP
AND BLABBED EVERYTHING, THEN...
AND MY LITTLE BROTHER,
CHARLIE...
MOM KEPT SAYING, "PLAY FAIR."
( grunts )
AND I TRIED.
BUT THE LITTLE BRAT...
WOULDN'T STOP
PLAYING WITH MY STUFF.
AND I HAD TO MAKE IT
CLEAR TO HIM
THAT NOBODY-- NOBODY--
MESSES WITH MY SHIT!
( whimpers )
HE WAS JUST A KID.
( chuckles )
SO WAS I.
BESIDES, IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
( grunts )
SO WHY ERIC?
ERIC JACOBS?
IT WAS A SIMPLE TASK--
TO NOT TALK TO SOMEONE
WHO TURNS EVERYONE
AND EVERYTHING HE TOUCHES
INTO SHIT!
Eric: HE NAILED ME WITH A D.W.I.
UNDERAGE DRINKING,
AND THE BROKEN TAIL LIGHT.
OFF THE HOCKEY TEAM
AND INTO A.A.
YOU KILLED HIM
BECAUSE HE TALKED TO KYLE?
KYLE WALKER IS THE BAIN
OF MY FREAKING EXISTENCE.
I SHOULD'VE KILLED HIM
WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
HEY, YOU THINK THERE'S
ANY CHANCE I'LL GET
BACK ON THE TEAM THIS SEASON?
YOU'RE AN IDIOT!
WHAT'D YOU TELL THEM?
TELL WHO?
WHAT THE--
WHAT?
I KNOW YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT ME! WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
NOTHING!
DON'T LIE TO ME!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
( grunts )
WHEN IT LOOKS LIKE SUICIDE,
YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH MURDER.
YOU CROSSED THE LINE.
LINE? WHAT LINE?
RED LINE! BLUE LINE!
GOLD LINE! SLAP SHOT!
OFF SIDES! I'M SICK OF IT!
IS IT TOO DIFFICULT
TO FREAKING LISTEN, CHRISTY?!
NO. PLEASE, ENLIGHTEN ME.
ELLIOTT, GREAT GAME.
HOLD UP A SECOND.
WHAT WAS THAT IN THERE?
WHAT?
HEY!
( grunting )
( groans )
( groaning )
WHAT THE HELL, MAN?
YOU HAVE TOTALLY LOST IT.
( groans )
( screams )
( groaning )
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I HAVEN'T TOLD YOU.
WOULDN'T IT BE FUNNY
IF I WENT AND SAW WALKER,
LIKE, IN JAIL
AND I TOOK PICTURES OF HIM?
WHY WOULD YOU WANNA GO DO
SOMETHING STUPID LIKE THAT?
OKAY, I WON'T.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
DOING THAT. YOU KNOW IT.
( gagging )
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK
BY KILLING MY BEST FRIEND
THAT I'D SUDDENLY FALL
HEAD OVER HEALS FOR YOU?
I PRACTICALLY
THREW MYSELF AT YOU.
I DON'T RECALL ANY ATTEMPT
OF YOU THROWING YOURSELF AT ME.
WHY DO YOU THINK I ALWAYS
MADE SURE YOU WERE THERE
EVERY TIME SHE AND I
WERE GETTING IT ON?
( gun cocks )
GO GET HELP.
YEAH, CHRISTY, GO GET HELP.
SHUT IT!
I'M NOT LEAVING YOU.
CHRISTY, PLEASE.
GO GET HELP.
I'M NOT LEAVING YOU.
IS THIS OUR YOUNG LOVERS'
FIRST QUARREL? ( chuckles )
CHRIS,
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING.
I CAN GIVE YOU
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING I WANT.
NO? THIS LOSER'S
SO OBSESSED WITH YOU,
HE KEEPS YOUR PICTURE
POSTED ALL OVER HIS WALLS.
OH, YEAH?
WHO'S THE ONE
WEARING MY CLOTHES?
( chuckles )
IT'S A GOOD LIKENESS.
WHAT MADE YOU LOSE IT?
I AM COMPLETELY TOGETHER.
OH, YEAH, CLEARLY.
( grunting )
( sirens wailing )
KYLE!
LET HER GO.
( sirens wailing )
YOU DON'T DESERVE HER.
PLEASE, JUST LET HER GO.
TAKE ME INSTEAD.
I LET HER GO, YOU RUN,
YOU GET SHOT.
( sirens wailing )
SEE, WHAT YOU HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND IS YOU HAVE NOTHING.
THEREFORE, YOU ARE NOTHING!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
SHUT UP!
( sirens wailing )
COVER THE BACK.
( grunting )
ELLIOTT SMITHE! DROP THE GUN!
PUT YOUR HANDS
WHERE I CAN SEE THEM!
NO!
KYLE! NO!
( indistinct
radio transmission )
GET ME AN AMBULANCE.
Man: YES, SIR.
CHRIS, CHECK THE BACK!
Man: GO! GO!
( sirens wailing )
( indistinct
radio transmission )
YOUR VITAL SIGNS
ALL LOOK GOOD AT THIS TIME.
BUT IF YOU HAVE
ANY SYMPTOMS THAT REOCCUR,
DON'T HESITATE TO CALL US BACK
OR TAKE YOURSELF DOWN
TO THE HOSPITAL.
THANK YOU.
MR. WALKER...
NEXT TIME YOU DECIDE TO STEAL
A POLICE OFFICER'S WEAPON...
YOU MAKE SURE YOU'RE OLD ENOUGH
TO BE WEARING ONE
OF OUR UNIFORMS.
THANK YOU, SIR.
YOUR MOM'S ON HER WAY DOWN.
THANKS, HOWIE.
( indistinct chatter )
THANK YOU.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
IT'S JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING.
KYLE, YOU REALLY
DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T WANT IT,
I COULD USE THE EXTRA MONEY
FOR ART SCHOOL.
NO, I WANT IT.
d BUT I DON'T KNOW
THE WORDS THAT YOU'RE SAYING d
d I FEEL EVERY BREATH
THAT YOU TAKE d
SO YOU LIKE IT?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I LOVE IT.
HERE, I'LL PUT IT ON.
d YOU SAY
YOU'RE NOT READY TO LOVE d
d YOU WILL KNOW IF
YOU DON'T LOVE HER d
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I JUST WANNA SEE
HOW IT LOOKS.
d I FEEL EVERY BREATH
THAT YOU TAKE d
d BUT I CAN'T REACH THE EARTH
d YOU'RE IN HEAVEN
d YOU SAY
YOU'RE NOT READY TO LOVE d
( water running )
d YOU WON'T KNOW
IF YOU DON'T... d
( gasps )
d WHAT DO I DO?
d HOW DO I GO ON?
d TRAPPED IN THIS DREAM
d OF VISIONS FROM BEYOND
d SHADOWS CLOSING IN
d DARKNESS AWAITS
FROM DEEP WITHIN d
d LIGHTS TURN TO SHADOWS
d SHADOWS
d SHADOWS TAKING OVER ME
d IT'S GETTING HARDER TO SEE
d IS THIS MY FATE
d OR MY ETERNITY?
d WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
d HOW DID I GET HERE?
d VOICES UNKNOWN
d THEY WILL NEVER
LEAVE ME ALONE d
d SHADOWS CLOSING IN
d DARKNESS AWAITS
FROM DEEP WITHIN d
d LIGHTS TURN TO SHADOWS
d SHADOWS
d WALKING DOWN THE STREET
d THAT NEVER SEEMS TO END
d SAME FACES OF THOSE
THAT I DON'T KNOW d
d TRAPPED BETWEEN THE SPACE
OF LIGHT AND DARK d
d SHADOWS TAKING OVER ME
d IT'S GETTING HARDER TO SEE
d IS THIS MY FATE
d OR MY ETERNITY?
d OH
d SHADOWS TAKING OVER ME
d IT'S GETTING HARDER TO SEE
d IS THIS MY FATE
d OR MY ETERNITY?
d OOH
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com