Look what I caught.
Raymond, don't put that in my...
...sink.
Thought we could eat it.
What is it?
Catfish. I caught it in the lake.
Set up the boat.
Thought it'd be good for David.
You know, fresh air.
- Honey, he's really sick.
- It's a couple of hours.
Catch some fish,
eat some gumbo...
- Well, how clean is that lake?
- It's as clean as the ocean.
Eve...
...he's not up there.
Well, he didn't come down.
Check around the house.
I'll check outside.
David!
Hey, David!
David! David!
David!
I found something.
Get out of the way.
Get out of the way!
Do you recognize this?
- This is my son's.
- Where's my son?
- Where's my son? Where's my son?
- Raymond!
David! David!
David! David! David!
Please find my son.
Please find him.
- Where's my son?
- Hey, hey, hold it.
- No. God, no...
David! Where's my son?
Where's my son?
My son!
Where's my son? David!
I wanna visit Mom and Dad today.
We can't, it's too far.
Ben said he'd take me.
Look, Ethan, everyone talks nice
at funerals, okay?
Hey, you two.
- We're almost done.
- Can we go to the cemetery after?
Of course.
You all right?
Are you gonna be our new dad?
No.
Look...
...your parents would want you
to have a reaI mommy and daddy.
Just because I love you, doesn't mean
I'd be a good parent.
I'm a cop.
A good day for me means
coming home in one piece...
...to a studio apartment
and having chicken fingers.
Ethan?
Ethan, honey, come with me.
I have some people for you to meet.
It's okay. Go.
Go.
It's okay.
Come on.
It's okay. Come here.
I'm not leaving you, Abby.
I'll be there for you whenever
you need me. Always. I promise.
We need you now, Ben.
Excuse me, Mr. Koch, I need you
to sign some documents...
...so we can finalize this paperwork.
So how long have you known
the children?
Their whole life.
I've known their parents-
I knew their parents
since high schooI.
Oh, that must be a terrible loss
for you too, then. Thanks, CaroI.
Yeah.
Losing your friends beats what I'm
feeling right now, I'll tell you that.
Well, you're doing the right thing.
- Am I?
- Yeah. Sign on the second page.
Thanks.
Excuse me...
...can you keep a secret?
- What?
- A secret.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Here.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you, like, the hall monitor
or something?
No, I'm a mother.
And my secret is that I know
that everyone in this place...
...is just as scared as you are.
And I know that because
I've been on both sides.
Really?
But you know what?
I learned a lot about families.
And I learned you have to
protect your children.
And that you have to be
a good mother.
- Can we get we get some ice cream?
- Sure we can, buddy.
Hi. I'm Raymond.
You must be Ethan's sister.
- Yeah. Abby.
- Hi.
Are-? Are you taking him?
We lost our boy.
The truth is, I'm just not ready
to stop being a mother.
He's really lucky.
Now, be a big boy, Ethan.
And be really good, okay?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Don't worry. We're still gonna
see each other. All the time, okay?
You know another thing
that I learned about families:
It's that when you have
a five-bedroom home...
...you should definitely have
more than one child.
Here we are.
This is the foyer.
This is the formaI living room.
Come on, Abby.
See this? This is an atrium.
Raymond designed that.
No, Ethan, don't touch!
It's all right. It's all right.
This is your home too.
Come on. This is the staircase.
It goes up to the bedrooms.
I'll show you that in a minute.
This is the dining room.
And this is the den.
Raymond, wanna show him
what you bought him?
Oh, yeah. Ethan, buddy.
Look straight ahead.
- Yes!
- We'll never see him again.
- I love this game.
- Okay, here we go.
Now, up here we have
the bedrooms.
This is our room. I expect
breakfast in bed every Mother's Day.
Now, this- I think we can make this
a playroom. What do you think?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Ethan, this is your room.
- Oh, this is so cooI.
- You like it?
- I think he likes it.
Now, I unpacked your things.
I put them where they should be, okay.
- Bathroom's right there.
- Okay.
All right.
We put Ethan close to us.
Why don't I show Abby the tower?
Your room. Come on.
You're gonna love it.
Word of warning:
Eve is a light sleeper.
- No backflips or cartwheels, okay?
- Right.
Here we are.
I'm up here alone?
You're an adult now. Time for you
to have your own space.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
You have the best view
in the whole house.
Look out this window. You and Ethan
are gonna be so happy here.
- What's in there?
- Don't go in there.
That's was our son's room.
Do not go in there.
Of course not.
There he is. Why don't you two
get your rooms in order...
...and I will meet you downstairs.
We'll eat in an hour.
Okay.
I saw a lake when we drove up.
Come.
Be carefuI.
- Let's go swimming.
- No, no. Stay right where you are.
What are you two doing?
Your mother's been worried sick.
Come on.
Ethan, come on.
Come on, buddy, let's go.
Abby, you coming?
Never, never go down to the lake
without us again.
Sorry.
You must tell me before you leave.
I don't know how it was before, but
you cannot run around by yourselves.
You have no idea
how dangerous it is here.
Besides, it's dinnertime.
Raymond, is the grill ready?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hungry?
Come on.
Yes, I'm checking now.
It's okay, Abby. Go back to bed.
There's someone outside.
Look, I called it in, Abby.
They're gonna make a drive-by.
I just saw someone outside!
I heard you, and it's
gonna be okay. All right?
Abby, look, don't worry about it.
Abby.
Listen to me.
- Abby!
- Ethan. Are you okay?
He's scared.
This is why we stay
close to the house, okay?
Abby said she saw
someone outside.
It's the middle of the night.
Where were you?
Do you want to sleep
with Mommy tonight?
It's fine. I'll stay with him.
I want Abby.
Okay. You're both safe now.
Here, baby.
There she is. Have a seat.
How many pancakes do you want?
- Two's fine.
- Okay.
- Raymond, breakfast.
- I'll be right down.
He is in his office
at 6 every morning.
- I hope he doesn't wake you.
- Oh, no. I didn't hear him, it's fine.
I need some help around
the house today. Can I get...
...two volunteers?
Ethan, you...
You'll help Eve with the laundry, okay?
And I'll show you both how.
All right. Look, Ethan.
At the laundry. Okay.
What you wanna
make sure is...
Excuse me, Abby.
That's my father's gun.
His keepsake from the war.
Eve thinks I got rid of it, so:
All right, Ethan. You open it up, right?
Okay? See this?
And then what you wanna do
is you set the dials.
- Press?
- Okay. Yes.
Well, no, actually this one.
See, that one.
That's what you're gonna have to
ask your sister. Abby?
I'd like to say this only once.
Great. Okay. So then you have to
get detergent, which is up here.
All right. Down the stairs
all the way to the top...
...through that door is the attic.
A lot of work to do.
After you.
So, what do you think,
is it hot in here?
No.
- Not really.
- Well, this should be...
...the hottest room in the house.
Especially in summer.
That means all the hot air
is escaping.
- Isn't that a good thing?
- Well, no. Not in the winter.
I boarded this with new insulation
and you can help me with the rest.
Okay? Lose this window,
we'll make it airtight.
What do you think?
We'll do a little each day.
Be a nice way for us to
get to know each other.
- Okay.
- Good. Tell you what.
You... You can wear my tooI belt.
Leave it. It's okay.
I got plenty of those.
- Okay.
- Can you handle it?
Good.
David.
Why are you here?
You are never to come in here.
You promised, Abby.
Sorry.
Can you keep a secret?
- Yes.
- You sure?
Yeah.
Don't tell Eve.
Really, don't.
- Okay.
- Good.
Come on, now get out of here
before Eve finds you.
Abby, where are you going?
Walk.
It's lunchtime.
Oh, no, it's fine. I'll have
mine when I get back.
I don't want you wandering outside.
I'm not wandering,
I'm going to the lake.
No. Absolutely not.
Why not?
Because this is my house,
and these are my rules...
...and it's for your own good.
Do I have to spell it out?
- What is the problem?
- How about no lunch...
...and no walk.
Now go to your room!
Okay.
Sorry.
Abby, can you get the door please?
There's no one at the door.
There's never anyone at the door.
- Hey.
- Oh, my God, hi!
How are you?
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Eve was right.
You two are stir-crazy.
She should know.
Well, it's a nice big house.
Great view.
There's a game room
with a PlayStation.
See, it doesn't get any
better than that, does it?
Hey.
What's going on with you?
Get us out of here.
She is so weird.
It's like they have all this land...
...and we're not allowed to leave
the house. There's a gross mattress...
...in the basement.
We can't use the phone.
We need a dial-out code
to make a phone call.
Abby. Look, you gotta
try to make this work.
I don't know if
Eve or Raymond told you this...
...but you know they lost their
little boy, their son, David, right?
- Yeah.
- He drowned. Down at the lake.
I tell you because
if you think they're mean...
...or if they don't
understand, believe me...
...they do understand.
Make it work for a few more weeks.
Because then, when I come back
to take you to Six Flags...
- Six Flags!
- ... I wanna see smiles...
...on both of your faces.
Hey.
Why is there a mattress
in the basement?
Why are you sneaking around
I'm not sneaking, it's just,
there's nowhere to go.
You guys don't even let us
out of the house.
Don't be silly,
we let you out of the house.
No, you don't.
You're always watching.
Well, is there something
you don't want us to see?
No.
We are responsible for you.
We protect you.
Ben protects us.
Ben Koch?
The man who lives downtown
in a one-bedroom apartment?
- That's who protects you?
- Yes.
He said we can stay with him.
- Ben doesn't want to be your parent.
- You don't know that.
Where is this attitude
coming from, young lady?
This is all for you.
For your safety. Your own parents
couldn't protect you.
Don't you dare talk about my parents.
You don't know my parents.
We are your parents.
Fuck you.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Now sit down!
- Honey, I think that-
- Raymond, don't.
It's okay, Ethan.
Eat your food.
It's okay.
House is locked tight.
Rug rats are asleep.
No, it's not right.
Not yet.
Hi, honey.
Raymond, are you gonna clean up?
- Why?
- She's gonna be here at 3:00.
Yes. I'll be ready.
- Morning, Abby.
- Hi.
Who's gonna be here at 3:00?
Caseworker.
And you missed breakfast.
It's 8:30.
You know, Abby...
...you might wanna
clean up a bit for the caseworker.
Put your hair back.
Put a cute sweater on. Like mine.
It's just nice to make an effort
when guests are coming, you know?
No offense.
Actually, I'm not really into that
whole Stepford Wives look.
No offense.
What's with the lockdown?
Are we under siege?
Around here we protect
our family, Abby.
You look cute.
What was wrong
with the other alarm?
Your mom bought an upgrade.
Double locks on all the doors.
She's not my mom.
- Hi.
- Hey.
May I speak to you
for a moment, please?
Right here is fine.
I don't know what outhouse
you were raised in...
...but don't ever say a nasty
remark about me again.
Otherwise, you're out of here.
And Ethan stays with us.
You're in my way, Eve.
I'm twice the bitch
you think you are.
It's just a standard checklist.
It shouldn't take too long.
But I do ask that you let
the children show me around.
Of course.
Okay, Abby and Ethan,
show me your rooms.
So, Ethan, you like your new home?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? All right.
Nice.
Lonely up here?
Anything you want
to talk to me about?
If we stay with this couple...
...and I leave to go to college...
...what happens to my brother?
Well, he could stay right here in
foster care and they could adopt him.
Adopt him?
What if I wanted to adopt him?
What if I wanted him to stay with me?
I have no say in that whatsoever?
You can be his legaI guardian
by the time you're 18.
And when I do turn 18...
...they can't do anything to stop me?
You have a claim to your little brother
for as long as you live.
And no one can take that
away from you.
Okay?
It's okay.
Any other sedatives?
No.
- Any codeine? Any Vicodin?
- No.
Don't most adults have some sort
of pain medication?
But you know children.
They explore. They're curious and we
don't want their curiosity to kill them.
So just be carefuI with what kind of
medication you have in the home.
Of course.
Okay. Take care, now.
- It was our pleasure.
- Thanks for coming.
- Have a safe trip back to the city.
- All right. Bye.
Let me get that.
Aren't you gonna
check the basement?
Well, should I check the basement?
David would play alone down here.
We've learned to keep
a better eye on our kids.
It was right here.
There used to be a bed right here.
- He slept here. There used to-
- Honestly.
- You think there was a bed here?
- Why do you think that?
I don't know,
I just know it was right here.
Well, there were some old blankets.
I threw them away.
What has gotten into you?
You know,
she said this to us last night.
Just...
Is this about
our conversation upstairs?
- No.
- About your brother?
No! No, that's not it at all.
There was a bed right here.
Okay, enough. Let's go upstairs.
I'm so sorry.
Abby, come on.
Come on.
- Drive safe. Bye.
- Okay. Bye-bye.
I made your favorite.
What about the kids' dinner?
Isn't this perfect?
Eve?
Honey?
Honey, talk to me.
It'll be different this time, I promise.
Chicken.
Peas. Salad.
Wine.
Perfect.
Drink your wine, Raymond.
Sit up.
You have chores.
Afterwards, maybe you can go
with your mother to run some errands.
Get you out of the house.
Raymond.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I'll be in the office.
Hi there.
Raymond said I have chores.
Sit down.
Relax. Take it easy.
Oh, would you mind finishing
the dishes I left in the sink?
- Okay.
- Great. Thank you.
- What'd you do?
- I don't know!
- Cut myself!
- Eve, Abby hurt herself.
Oh, God. It hurts really bad.
Oh, my God!
Don't move.
I want to go to the hospitaI.
Eve was a nurse, Abby.
Oh, dear. Look at that.
It's okay, it's okay.
Can't be clumsy
when dealing with glass, Abby.
It was already broken, Eve.
What are you doing?
- Be still.
- I don't want that.
- It's okay.
- I really don't want it.
It's okay, Abby.
Now, you ever had stitches?
Hold still.
Oh, my God!
Raymond, hold her.
- This is what a mother does, Abby.
- My God!
She comforts her child.
Heals her when she's sick.
Corrects her when she's wrong.
Oh, my God.
She does it because she wants to.
Expecting nothing in return.
Oh, my God.
That's all I've ever wanted to be.
Oh, my God!
To be a good mother.
- What is that?
- This is for pain.
- I'm not in pain.
- You will be.
- But he promised.
- Your father is very busy.
He doesn't have time
to drive you to a cemetery.
- He's not my father.
- Ethan.
He's not.
Don't, Ethan.
What are you doing
out of bed, Abby?
I don't feeI well.
What did you give me?
I can make you some eggs.
No.
Toast?
You have to eat something.
Ben Koch called yesterday.
I told him about your condition.
Yesterday I was fine.
No, Abby, you've been
in bed for three days.
He said he'd stop by when he could.
Eat up, baby.
- Oh, my God, Ethan.
- Help me.
- Are you okay?
- I'm reaI sick.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, doctor, thank you.
Yes, fluids. All right,
thank you very much.
So he said to just keep doing
what we're doing.
That dehydration is the danger.
Was it food poisoning?
I don't know, honey.
I mean, we all ate the same thing.
- I wanna use the phone.
- Why?
I wanna call Ben
and tell him about this.
- All right, I'll call him tomorrow.
- Why can't I call him?
Because it's 3:00
in the morning, Abby.
Eve will take care of it.
And I want you in your
own bed tonight, all right?
It's all right, baby, Mommy's here.
It's okay, Ethan.
I'm here.
You're not having any dinner, Abby?
Have some soup, sweetie.
I made it for Ethan.
Good morning, Ethan.
Lots of fluids. Doctor's orders.
This is warm tea.
It's easy on your tummy,
make you feeI better.
This is not food poisoning.
It's not?
No. It's obviously
something else.
Take him to the hospitaI.
I can do it all here.
You said you were gonna call Ben.
I called Ben.
He's gonna come by later this week.
When did you talk to him?
About an hour ago.
While you were sleeping.
Well, call him again.
Mind your manners, Abby. The man
isn't at your beck and call, all right.
Here, sweetie.
I know my brother and I know
that something is wrong with him.
How are you feeling, sweetie?
Do you want me to make you
something to eat?
Oh, my God.
Raymond...
...help me.
Not now.
You warned me about your wife
when I went in your son's room.
My son?
Made herself sick
nursing that boy to health.
I've never been more proud of her
in my entire life.
Who is that?
That's David.
Our last foster child.
"Tyler"?
Oh, God.
Ethan. I've got the car keys.
Ethan? Ethan, we're leaving, okay?
Okay. Come on.
It's okay.
There you go. Here's your jacket.
Put your arm through.
Okay, sit up.
I'm sorry.
Okay...
Oh, God.
Shit.
I'll be right back, okay?
I'll be right back.
Come on, come on.
Okay.
Come on, come on, come on.
No!
Come on, start. Shit. Start.
Shit.
Oh, God.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Oh, you're cold.
I'll bring Ben back with me.
I promise, okay?
You forgot my keys.
You children make it so hard.
I spend every waking minute...
...wiping your snotty fucking noses...
...and still you are so ungratefuI!
And you can't even do what I ask.
- What did you do to Ethan?
- I love Ethan.
Did you love David too?
Where were you taking my son?
Never go outside!
Bad girls get sent to their rooms.
Help me! Help!
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
Are you ready to apologize?
Yes.
Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
I have no fucking idea.
If you don't eat...
...you'll never leave.
You're so sick, Ethan.
That's why
your first mommy left you.
It's okay.
It's gonna make you
feeI better, baby.
There you go.
Go to sleep, baby.
I'm never gonna leave you, Ethan.
Mommy's right here.
Mommy will never, never leave you.
You make one sound
and I'll kill him.
- Hey.
- Hey. How's it going?
It's great. It's a beautifuI day.
Yeah.
- Anything I can do for you?
- Yeah, I'm here to get the kids.
You do remember me?
- Yeah. Ben.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, Ben Koch, right?
- Yeah.
Family friend, yeah.
I wish you would've called first.
I did. No one answered.
We planned this.
I was gonna take them to Six Flags.
Oh, dear. You know,
Eve drove the kids downtown.
- Some children's art exhibit.
- She did?
Yeah, they won't be back
untiI this evening.
Well, I'll tell them you came by.
It's a shame.
Yeah. A shame. Okay.
Oh, hey, look,
I brought this for Ethan.
- You mind if I put this in his room?
- No, I'll give it to him.
You know what? It's okay.
I'll give it to him myself.
- It's a great house you got here.
- Thanks.
Mind if I take a look around?
Of course. Come on in.
This is a fantastic place.
- You want something to drink?
- No, I'm fine.
So where's his room?
Upstairs. End of the hallway.
All right.
- This one?
- No.
That's it.
Nice room.
Yeah, you know, it's all Eve.
I got a gift for Abby...
...but, you know, I should probably
give it to her in person.
How's she doing?
She's a handfuI. You know,
Eve calls her our summer project.
Well, I guess just tell the kids
we'll reschedule.
That is strange, you know.
I thought they were
looking forward to it.
- They change like the weather.
- Yeah.
Thanks. Have a good day.
- You too.
- All right.
He's gone.
Oh, my God.
I got you.
I'm putting him back to bed.
Ethan. Ethan.
Oh, God.
Ethan. Ethan, I'm gonna
get us out of here.
I'm gonna get some help, okay?
Abby!
Hello.
Gotcha.
Hello? Hello?
We're sorry. No outside calls can
be made without a dial-out code.
Yeah, this is Officer Ben Koch
of the L.A.P.D.
Yeah, I'm at 100 Pine Haven Lane.
I'm proceeding inside
on suspicion of child endangerment.
Abby.
I know you can hear me.
You're not going anywhere.
Abby! I got you.
You just can't leave.
Worthless.
Ethan, honey, you stay right there.
You're safe now, baby.
Mommy will be right back.
I have had enough of you!
AII I ever wanted
was to be a good mother!
But you're not good!
And you're not my mother.
Ethan?
Ethan.
Okay. Okay.
Are you okay?
Stop!
You stay away from my son!
Put the gun down, Raymond.
Put it down.
Ben?
It's okay, Abby.
Yeah.