There is a legend about a bird...
which sings just once in its life...
more sweetly than
any other creature...
on the face of the earth.
From the moment it leaves the nest...
it searches for a thorn tree...
and doesn't rest
until it's found one.
Then, singing among
the savage branches...
it impales itself upon the
longest, sharpest spine.
And dying, it rises
above its own agony...
to out-carol the lark
and the nightingale...
and the whole world
stills to listen...
and God in his heaven smiles.
For the best is bought only
at the cost of great pain...
or so says the legend.
Inside, everybody!
You, priest!
-Don't you know about the curfew?
-A man is dying.
And what's this?
His dinner?
His family is very poor,
his children are starving.
Meat! Chicken!
-We haven't seen this in months.
-All we get is macaroni.
For God's sake, have mercy on them!
Out whoring and drinking, more like.
All rotten priests are the same.
-On your way, priest.
-And don't break curfew again.
It's not much, but it
will help. Bring them out.
-Dear God. How many more?
-The Allies have landed in Sicily.
Mussolini can't last
now. It won't be long.
It will be long enough.
You are all welcome here.
And you can take this off.
You don't need it anymore.
-It is the law.
-It's a Fascist law.
-This is the house of God.
-lf there is a God at all.
He has forsaken us.
Perhaps it is we who
have forgotten him.
This man seems to
doubt the power of God.
So put your faith in me.
You're under my protection now,
and no harm will come to you.
And you don't need this.
Follow me.
No. There are too many already.
lf the Fascists find
out, what happens to me?
This is my church. I am responsible.
We are all responsible, Father.
I absolve you of any blame.
lf the authorities find out...
I値l say it was all my
doing. Go back to your dinner.
It's best you don't know.
Come along.
Follow me this way. Come along.
It isn't much, I know, but you'll be
safe here for as long as you need to be.
Thank you from the bottom
of my heart. You are a saint.
No. Far from it. Please.
I値l try to find a
doctor for you tomorrow.
Meanwhile, make yourselves
as comfortable as possible.
Father, my grandson, Samuel...
protect him.
And find a safe haven for him...
if such a place still exists.
You can both live in that place.
I don't want to live.
I saw what the Nazis did...
to his parents.
To my wife.
When I know that the boy is safe...
I want to be with her.
I値l do what I can for him.
You swear on your sacred,
solemn love of God?
I swear on my sacred oath.
Now rest.
There are too many. We have
no food for them tomorrow.
I値l find some.
-And we need some medicine.
-I値l find some.
And you must rest, My Lord.
You put us all to shame.
No. We must do what we can.
I値l do the rest.
I know these are
difficult times, Ralph...
but when the Holy Father says mass...
his servant should not be late.
All across Europe, thousands
of displaced people...
are seeking some sanctuary
from this ravaging war...
and Holy Mother Church
is doing nothing.
What has that to do with being late?
We know that punctuality and
obedience are not your virtues...
but at least you could
show some respect.
And, you know, we do whatever we can.
No, Your Eminence, we do
as little as possible...
because we don't want to offend
one Great Power or the other...
until we know which side will win.
Meanwhile, the homeless
have nowhere to go...
no future to look forward to,
and no one to take care of them.
-So I do what I can.
-Are you going to be a politician now?
Listen to me, Ralph. Many
people admire your work.
It has even been discussed
with the Holy Father himself...
and I think your future as
a cardinal seems assured.
It's all I have hoped for
you, ever since I致e met you.
But...
you cannot have one
breath of scandal...
not one hint of it...
-to taint your dazzling future.
-What scandal?
You know perfectly well
what I知 talking about.
Your management of the great
fortune of Mary Carson...
which you brought into the Church,
and which you are in charge of.
-I致e used this much for the refugees.
-You cannot use any of it.
The money belongs to the Church...
and you cannot use the
tiniest fraction of it...
for purposes the Church
does not deem appropriate.
-Saving human lives is not appropriate?
-Of course it is appropriate...
and you know that.
But it is not up to you to decide.
-It is not your decision.
-What am I to do?
My priests and I
scrounge, beg, and steal...
to feed the refugees for one night...
never knowing whether
they will starve the next.
Then we have to
persuade the Church...
-to loosen her purse strings.
-And when the war is over?
-Then they can go home.
-Most of them have no homes now.
-There are other countries-- -Who
don't want them, won't take them.
Then we have to use our political...
diplomatic power...
and convince them to
change their policies...
and to help find
countries of refuge...
for these unfortunate souls.
I値l do...
what I can...
if you give me your sacred word...
now...
that you will not
use one penny more...
of the Carson money.
-I can't make that vow.
-You must.
Not only for me, but for yourself.
You have not only friends here.
There are powerful forces
lining up against you.
Let them do their worst...
and then, at last,
I値l know the truth.
Does God want me for my ability...
or does the Church want
me for Mary Carson's money?
To tell you the truth, the
Church definitely wants you for...
your ability to do the Church's work.
And God...
God...
All he wants...
is your faith.
I値l be careful, Vittorio.
There'll be no scandal.
I値l take it for a promise.
Come.
Turn her off, mate.
G'day, Mrs. O'Neill.
Bill, Tony. Any luck?
It's a waste of time. It's
dry. There's no water here.
But this whole area is an artesian
basin. There must be water.
-I知 at 3,000 feet.
-The sheep cannot last much longer.
This drought's killing
us all, Mrs. O'Neill...
and the thing is, Tony's joined up.
He's off to New Guinea.
His mom don't want him to
go, and that's a fact, but...
-I got to do my bit, Mrs. O'Neill.
-Yes.
I know you're desperate for water...
but we want to go to Sydney
with him to see him off.
Who knows when he'll be home again.
-All right, Bill. Thanks anyway.
-I知 sorry.
I値l come back on Monday,
and take this lot down.
Good luck in New Guinea, Tony.
I値l say g'day to your
brothers if I see them.
She needs a man around the place.
Women aren't cut out
for this sort of work.
Old Mary Carson ran
Drogheda good enough.
Mary Carson was different.
Miss Meggie's a lady.
...but when he retired in 1911...
he thought his military
career was over.
However, when the German
invaders defeated...
Now, Dane, we all know...
that the present German Nazi
leader is Adolf Hitler...
but can you tell me the name
of the allied Italian dictator?
-You there, Dane?
-Mommy! Mommy!
Dane, come back here this instant.
You haven't finished school.
Justine?
-...so I thought we'd lost you both.
-No, because it's boring.
-Justine.
-She can't hear.
Have you been studying
as well as your brother?
-Yes, Mrs. H.
-It's Mrs. Henderson, Justine...
not Mrs. H. Mind your
manners, thank you.
Then she asked me about Rome.
That's where your friend
the Archbishop is, isn't he?
-That's right.
-Does he know the Pope?
I think he's met him a
couple of times, yeah.
Any luck?
They're not going to be drilling
anymore, Mom. Tony's joined up.
-It's got to rain.
-It will, dear, in God's good time.
After a week of it, we'll
be wishing it'd stop.
Come on, you.
That's it for today, then, children.
Talk to you all again on Monday.
Over and out.
Why does she call me
''children''? I知 not a child.
You are for just a little
while longer yet, Justine.
Tell you what, why don't you go
and make us a nice cup of tea?
Why is it always me?
Why can't Mrs. Smith?
Because she's busy cooking
your dinner. Now, go on.
I have half a mind to go out
and drill that damn well myself.
No, Meggie, that's men's work.
So is running this place. I致e
been doing quite well at that.
-Isn't right. Your brothers should
be here. -They're not.
Bob and Jack are fighting
a war in New Guinea...
so I知 afraid running
Drogheda's up to me...
whether you like it or not.
Why bother? We don't
even own this place.
-It belongs to the Church.
-That's why we have to take care of it.
My daddy would find
water if he was here.
The only liquid your father could find
would be the beer at the nearest pub.
I知 sorry, Justine.
I didn't mean that.
Yes, you did. You always do.
lf you hated him so much,
why did you marry him?
-Justine.
-I値l take care of her, Mom.
You must guard your tongue, Meggie.
That girl shouldn't grow up believing
her father is the devil incarnate.
-Why not? It's true.
-Then she has a point.
lf it's true, why did you marry him?
-Mom, it's old ground.
-Not to her.
And what's Dane to think?
-I mean, Luke isn't even his real father.
-He'll hear you!
No, he doesn't.
lf anyone knew, it would destroy
Father Ralph's position in the Church.
Mom, Luke isn't here.
Ralph isn't here. I知
Dane's mother and father...
-and that is all he need ever know.
-And you don't think blood will out?
That boy already has his heart
set on becoming a priest...
-just like his father.
-He's a child, he'll grow out of it.
I hope so. Otherwise, you'll
lose him to God as well.
Please...
just let it rain.
Dear God, please bring some
rain to stop the drought.
And God bless Justine,
and Grandma Fee...
and Uncle Jack, and Mommy...
and a very special blessing
for my daddy, wherever he is.
Amen.
Right, into bed.
Do you miss your father, Dane?
Well, I don't know him,
so I can't really miss him.
-I miss not having a daddy, though.
-Yeah, I know.
-Justine thinks you hate him.
-Hate?
That's a very strong
word, my darling.
-I don't hate your daddy.
-Do you think he'll ever come back here?
Why? Aren't I enough for you?
Yes. You're the best
mommy in all the world.
Yeah, you say that now,
but you know, one day...
you're going to meet
a beautiful girl...
you're going to fall in love...
get married, and
have lots of babies...
and then she'll be the
best mommy in all the world.
No, I知 going to be a priest.
Priests don't get married.
You are much too young to be
thinking about things like that.
Why? Would you mind?
No, not if it's what
you really wanted.
But it's a big decision to make.
Wait until you're much, much older.
-All right. Night, Mom.
-Good night, my darling.
Sleep tight.
-Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Good night.
What on earth are you doing?
Just practicing for
when I知 an actress.
-It makes you look awfully grown up.
-I am grown up.
Not to me. You're
still my little girl.
I do try, Justine.
I know you miss your
father, but he's not here.
You always call him ''your father.''
You never say ''my husband.''
That's because I don't think of
myself as married to Luke anymore.
You're not divorced. You're
Catholic, you can't be divorced.
-And you must've loved him to marry him.
-Oh, for pity's sake, Justine.
Yes, I thought I loved him once.
It took me a while to
realize I was wrong...
but he gave me you,
so it wasn't all bad.
You're right about one
thing: I do wish he was here.
That's not going to happen. I知
sorry, but that's the way it is.
-At least he'd love me.
-And do you think I don't?
You know, your father wasn't
the man you think he was.
Wash that makeup off
before you go to bed.
...on rural properties in Australia,
as the two-year drought continues.
Overseas, Australian troops have
gained more ground in New Guinea...
but the Japanese continue
to inflict heavy casualties.
And, following the
invasion of Sicily...
the Allies have announced that
none of the Italian cities...
including Rome, will be
excluded from bombing raids...
because of historical
importance. Meanwhile...
They won't bomb the Vatican.
He'll be safe.
...is besieged. It is
being softened up...
with fierce bombardment
from sea and air...
Sweet Mary, mother of Jesus...
have mercy.
Take this burden from me.
I think of her...
every minute of my life.
Let me forget her.
Let me serve you in peace.
I have repented my sin.
I will never see her again.
Only please, I beg of you...
take this burden from me.
''Dead.''
''Dead, and never
called me mother! ''
What are you laughing at?
-You. You look funny.
-This is a melodrama.
It isn't supposed to be
serious. I was very good.
Why do you want to
be an actress, Justie?
I love being other people.
I don't like being me.
I hate it out here
in the Never Never.
-No one to talk to, nothing to do.
-You can talk to me.
Yes, but you go on
about Jesus all the time.
It gets a bit boring.
I want to be like
her, Aunt Mary Carson.
-Rich and interesting.
-She loved Jesus.
She must have. She left all
of her money to the Church.
She didn't really.
She left all her money to that priest
Mommy's so fond of, Father Ralph.
He's an archbishop.
I bet there was something
funny going on there.
-I bet really she was in love with him.
-You can't love a priest.
Yes, you can. You can't marry one...
but there's nothing to stop
you being in love with him.
It's very romantic, being in
love with a man you can't have.
Do you think Mommy ever loved Daddy?
Probably, when they got married.
Why does she hate him so much now?
-He left her.
-No, he didn't.
He was wonderful to her.
She left him. Mrs. Smith
told me. I壇 never do that.
I壇 never walk out on a
man if I really loved him.
I wish Daddy would come here.
I know he'd take me away from
here, and we'd go to Sydney...
and I壇 become a great actress and
look after him for always and always.
Grandma's home.
We'd better get cleaned up.
You know how she goes on.
Mom.
Mom, Mrs. Smith wants to know...
Mom, are you all right?
This is where you met Luke,
isn't it? Where you courted?
You should never have left
him. He's your husband.
Go back to him, I beg
you, and have babies.
-Have lots more babies.
-Mom, what's the matter?
Dear Mom...
this letter will probably come
as a bit of a shock to you.
It's hard to believe it was three
years ago we all said goodbye.
I致e seen a lot of action since
then, Mom. North Africa, Europe.
As you know, Mom, we've been shipped
to New Guinea to stop the Japs.
We've been fighting pretty hard on the
Kokoda Trail these past eight months.
The jungle's purgatory, Mom.
Anyway, some of the young
blokes were caught in an ambush.
They were wounded pretty
badly, held down by sniper fire.
Young lads, they were. Been
here since the beginning.
We couldn't just leave them
out there to die, Mom...
so me and a couple of
boys, we went to get them.
That's what we're here
for, isn't it, Mom?
Well, we got to the blokes safely...
and started leading
them out of there...
when the Japanese just
came out of nowhere.
Like ghosts, they were.
They had us pinned down pretty good
and, at first, we stood our ground...
but we had to get out of there.
We were trapped.
So I just let loose.
I don't know what happened then.
I think I got a couple of them.
The thing is, one of them got me.
I知 all right now.
Some specialists have looked at me.
Nothing serious, except...
''Nothing serious,'' he says.
Except he'll never be able
to have children, ever.
lf that isn't serious,
I don't know what is.
At least he'll be out of
the war. He'll be home.
We need a man about the place.
Yes!
Luke?
What the hell are you doing here?
How are you feeling?
You want a cup of tea?
I reckon you need one.
Some folk might say it
was lucky I was passing by.
But then, gratitude never really was
one of your strong points, was it, Megan?
I put four sugars in there. You
probably had a bit of a shock.
And you're it.
There's some spares for the drill.
I値l see if I can get it going again.
There's no point, there's no water.
-Who says?
-Bill Masters. It's his drill.
Bill Masters couldn't direct
traffic down a one-way street.
No, it's there, but two
years without rain...
it'll be deep, and we surely need it.
-''We''?
-Figure of speech.
Every station from here to
the black stump needs water.
-So how are you feeling?
-I致e got a lousy headache.
That's not surprising.
That's a nasty gash.
But I don't think
there's any harm done.
You never answered my question.
What are you doing here?
I had a bit of time on my hands. I
thought I壇 come down and see my wife.
I haven't been your wife
for a long time, Luke.
And I wanted to see my boy.
I heard around the traps I致e
got a son. Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't think you'd care.
You never took much notice of Justine.
Boys are different.
I致e always wanted a son.
Megan...
I値l do whatever you say,
but I want to see my son.
-You want some more tea, Grandma?
-No, thank you, dear.
I think I値l have
a nap before dinner.
Here's your mommy home.
-Who's that man?
-Go and get Justine, dear.
Tell her it's her father.
Daddy?
G'day, Mrs. C.
Daddy!
That's what I call a real homecoming.
-This is Dane.
-G'day, Dane.
G'day, Dad.
Is it really you? It is!
What a sight for sore eyes you are.
It's me, Mrs. Smith. It's really me.
Lost a bit of weight, I see.
Mr. Luke, what a card you
are. You haven't changed.
A bit older and wiser, perhaps.
I like to think so, anyway.
How about you get back in that
kitchen? I need a bit of feeding up.
-Welcome home, Luke.
-It's you that hasn't changed.
-You're looking younger than ever.
-Liar.
This is a bit of
all-right, isn't it?
-I壇 forgotten how charming he can be.
-Yes, when he wants something.
Mom, he's too old for cane cutting,
and he's looking for a meal ticket...
-and it's not going to be me.
-You're too hard on him, dear.
A little Christian charity
might not go astray.
I am not going back to
Luke, Mom. He never loved me.
He spent more time with his
mates than he ever did with me.
What about the
children? They need him.
So do you, only you're
too stubborn to admit it.
-I don't need anyone.
-We all need someone.
I miss your father.
You can't tell me you haven't
been lonely for the last 10 years.
I know what loneliness is.
Yes, I致e been lonely,
Mom, but not for Luke.
No, obviously.
You were unfaithful to him.
You've been pining for
10 years for a priest...
-a man you can never have.
-I have his son.
-His son needs a father.
-Luke is not his father.
-And I don't trust him.
-Then change him, dear.
You're quite a witch, after all.
It was for you that Father Ralph
broke his most sacred, solemn vow.
All tucked in?
Good as gold. At least the
kids were pleased to see me.
-Do you mind, Mrs. C?
-I don't mind you smoking.
But I do mind you calling me Mrs. C.
-Fine. Fee.
-That's better.
It does my heart good
to see you sitting there.
-We need a man about the place.
-You surely do.
Drogheda's not exactly
looking its best.
It hasn't been easy, you know.
Most of the able-bodied
men are fighting a war.
I think you've done great...
considering you've had
everything stacked against you.
-But if you need help, I知 here now.
-For how long?
As long as I知 needed, or wanted.
That raises the question
of where you'll sleep.
-Mom.
-It's all right, Megan.
I wasn't expecting to turn up here
like the proverbial bad penny...
-and jump straight into the cot with you.
-I知 glad to hear it.
I値l bunk down at the
old shearer's quarters.
It's not very comfortable.
It'll be a palace compared to
some of the places I致e slept in.
Besides, all those feather beds
up there, they make a man soft.
That's just what Jack used to say.
What do you think you're doing...
coming in here, charming
the pants off everyone?
-Not quite everyone, it seems.
-I知 serious, Luke.
What do you want?
Nothing that you're
not prepared to give.
You're my wife, and
they're my children...
and I just want what I致e always
wanted: a little place of our own.
-I want to settle down with my family.
-Simple as that?
Luke, you can't just
ignore the last 10 years.
You can't just walk in here
as if nothing's happened.
All those years, the kids needed
a father, where the hell were you?
You walked out on me, remember?
And what about you, all those years?
You can't tell me that you haven't
needed a husband, wanted a man.
The real reason that I致e come
back here is to say that I知 sorry.
I apologize.
You were right, and I was wrong.
Look, I miss you...
and I want you back.
I love you, Megan.
I always have.
-What's this?
-That's your dowry.
There's $20,000 there,
with 10 years interest.
I don't want it.
When you left me, you told
me I could keep the money...
so long as you didn't
have to see me again.
Well...
you've seen me.
Keep the money.
They can't do this.
The Allies are winning.
They can do what they want.
They're coming close to
San Lorenzo. I must go.
There's nothing you
can do there tonight.
Keep calm. You are safe here.
What is it, Grandpa?
What's happening?
It is the end of the world.
This is your doing.
This is God's vengeance
for bringing them here.
You even brought Jews
to a Christian place.
-Father, that's enough.
-I curse you.
What are you doing? Get
back down there. Go on.
You're safe here. You're
20 feet underground.
This is the best bomb shelter ever
built. Why would you want to be out?
What I told you is true.
This is your sanctuary.
Here, you're safe.
That's why I chose this place.
Now, go back to your
places, all of you.
-Go on.
-I知 sorry, Father. We did try.
Listen to me. Listen!
The bombs won't last much longer.
And you should be happy,
they're American bombs...
and that means the end of the
war is coming closer and closer.
Good for the Yanks!
That's the spirit.
I know you're all
frightened. I am, too.
But we're in God's hands now,
and he's spared our lives so far.
Let's give thanks to him.
-Should I pray, too, Grandpa?
-Pray, Samuel.
Pray with all your heart.
Pray for that priest.
He will be your salvation.
Our Father, who art in heaven...
hallowed be Thy name.
Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done...
on Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive us our trespasses...
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation...
but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
Grandpa!
Samuel, come here, boy. Come here.
Hush. Don't cry.
He's safe with God now, and
you'll be all right, Samuel.
I promise you.
I swore to your grandfather
that I壇 keep you safe...
and I will.
I will.
You promised me no scandal,
and look what you have done.
Thousands taken from
the Carson estate.
-Believe me, it was a worthy cause.
-You broke your word.
Food, yes. Medicine, clothing, yes.
All that, the Church might forgive.
But money to buy
passage to America...
for some
little boy--
He was a very special case.
It's always a special
case. Every case is special.
I agree with you, but if
your enemies know about it...
they will do everything in
their power to destroy you.
Is that what the Church is?
Intrigue, power, politics?
Yes, that's what the Church
is: power and politics.
And you should have learned
that a long time ago.
In their eyes, you committed a crime.
The Church demands
obedience to your vows.
Where was your vow of poverty
when you used the Carson money?
Where was your vow of obedience
when you broke your word to me?
And let's not talk about
your vow of chastity.
And on top of everything...
you neglected the fortune
you're in charge of: Drogheda.
-It's also the Church's property.
-Your Eminence?
Don't you know that Drogheda
is devastated by drought?
There is often drought in Australia.
Drought.
Perhaps you should see for yourself.
I知 going to send
you back to Australia.
Not to Australia.
Vittorio, I beg you.
I warned you, but
you wouldn't listen.
lf this comes out, there
will be a scandal here...
and you are better out of it.
And there, you can discuss...
the resettlement of refugees
in that country after the war.
It would do much to
repair your reputation.
Not Australia.
Please!
Why not?
Is there any temptation there?
Then perhaps, like our
Lord in the wilderness...
you should learn to resist it.
Can he drive it yet?
The boy's a legend.
Go on.
You're good.
Don't pet the dog before dinner.
There you go, Dad.
-Great tucker, Justine.
-Thanks, Dad. Mom helped.
I just supervised.
You'll make someone
a great little wife.
I知 not going to get
married, not for a long time.
I知 going to be an actress.
My word, Dane, we're going to
have an actress in the family.
She just likes showing off.
And what about you, boy?
What do you want to be?
A priest.
Is that so? And why's that?
I don't know, I just want to.
I think that's a terrific thing...
but having a wife and a family...
that's a very special thing, too.
It's been hard on us
all, not being together.
I bought a farm. Put a
deposit on it, anyway.
We could all live together.
And then you might decide that
having a family of your own...
is much better than being a priest.
It's been pretty good this
last little while, hasn't it?
-Yes.
-Too right.
And it will get better
and better, I promise.
When can we move, Dad?
When can we go there?
That's not up to me. That's
up to your mother to decide.
But we'll talk about
that after dinner.
Can you pass the salt?
Pass the bread, Mom.
Yeah, good night.
-Good night, darling.
-Good night, Dad.
-Good night, Mom.
-Good night, Justine.
You don't play fair, Luke.
You come swanning in here
like Father Christmas...
making them think you're the
most wonderful man in the world.
Well, I am.
Walk me home?
-Scared of the dark?
-No.
Scared of losing you.
This isn't going to work.
At least let me try.
You owe me that much.
And you owe it to the children.
-Meggie?
-Mom!
-I知 going to Sydney.
-What's happened?
Jack's been sent there
to see some specialist.
He says he'll be in hospital for a
while. I have to be there to see him.
-Please, Mom, let me drive.
-No, I致e got to get used to it.
Now that you're going to be
living with Luke on his farm...
I値l be doing a lot of driving.
-The children told me.
-It's not definite yet.
Hopefully, you'll have
more children. Sons.
I already have a son.
What if he becomes a priest?
Who'll inherit all this
if Dane never has children?
He can't inherit Drogheda anyway,
Mom. It belongs to the Church.
It's ours to care for, at
least as long as we have sons.
And it should have been ours.
Your father and your brothers
worked hard for this place.
It's the most spiteful
thing Mary Carson ever did.
Just leave them there. Thank you.
-You sure you'll be all right, Mom?
-Oh, Meggie, I知 not a child.
Give my love to Jackie.
-Hello, Meggie.
-Ralph.
-You're looking very well.
-And you.
-I had no idea you were coming.
-It was all very sudden.
You didn't write.
You didn't telephone.
Ten years of nothing. Only
letters to Mom about Drogheda.
-What could I say?
-That you missed me.
That you were coming home.
I mean, how were you going
to get out to Drogheda?
I値l be staying at the presbytery in
town. I was going to call from there.
Why there? Why are you staying there?
I have a lot of Church
business to take care of.
A lot of things have changed, Meggie.
Yes, they have.
-How bad is the drought?
-It's over two years now.
We're running half
the sheep we used to...
which you'd have known if
you'd read the reports properly.
For pity's sake,
Meggie, stop the car.
-Why did you come back?
-Because of the drought.
To see for myself.
-Are you so unhappy I知 here?
-Yes.
No.
Ralph, 10 years ago
you said you loved me...
and even though I knew you
loved God more, it didn't matter.
But then you left me.
You went back to Rome and I
tried very hard to forget you...
without much success.
I waited and I dreamed. I
didn't hear a word from you.
And now, just when I thought I壇
found a way to live without you...
you turn up, out of the blue.
Why have you come back?
Why do you always come back just
when I think I don't need you?
I had no choice, Meggie.
The Church sent me.
I certainly had no idea
you'd be at the station.
I had planned to keep some distance.
But now, seeing you...
I can't let things
be the way they were.
I知 going back to Luke.
You did very good. But you, mate,
you got to keep your head down.
You got to keep your head
down near the horse's head.
You gotta talk to him like a friend.
Gotta let him know you're his boss.
Mom doesn't do that.
Yeah, well, your mom's always
been a bit formal in the saddle.
Who's that with Mom?
Trouble, that's who it is.
Dane, Justine, I want you
to meet someone very special.
This is Archbishop de Bricassart.
He's come all the way from Rome.
Hello, Justine.
Hello, Dane.
-Dane, don't be so prissy.
-Justine, behave yourself.
Hello, Luke. Thanks
for helping out here.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it for Meggie.
-I値l go and stable the horses.
-I will, Dad.
No. You stay here with your ma and...
him.
-Dane.
-Yes, Dad.
Justine.
He's too cute!
-Have you ever met the Pope?
-Quite a few times.
-What's he like?
-Dane, he's just a man.
In a white dress.
Justine.
It's all right,
Meggie. I知 used to it.
And it's true. The Pope
is a very special man.
The representative of God on
Earth, but still, he's only a man.
We're all only men, trying to
serve God the best way we can.
That's what I want to do.
Dane, that's enough.
-That's a very big decision, Dane.
-No, it isn't. It's easy.
Don't argue with
the Archbishop, Dane.
I知 not arguing, I知
agreeing with him.
You're just a nipper, and
you're much too young...
to be worrying about your future yet.
So why are you here?
There must be more important
things to do in Europe.
My superiors were
concerned about Drogheda.
Why? Have I been
doing such a bad job?
You've been doing remarkably well...
but the Vatican doesn't
understand Australian droughts.
-What are you going to do, pray for rain?
-Of course.
And there are other reasons.
The war in Europe is
winding down, at last...
and countless thousands of
people are displaced, misplaced...
and can't go home again.
They have no homes, or
even countries, to go to.
We have to find other
places for them to live.
-Here?
-Some of them, I hope.
I致e been sent here to try and
negotiate with the Australian government.
-They're coming here?
-They have to go somewhere, Luke.
Cripes, that's the
last thing we need...
is a bunch of reffos
running around Australia.
Luke!
I got no taste for
this. Best be on my way.
I知 sorry, Ralph.
-Why don't people want the refugees?
-Because they're different.
And people don't like
things to be different.
I used to come here when
I was sad or lonely...
when I needed to talk
to you, to see you.
I壇 close my eyes,
and I壇 dream of you.
And you'd always be here. Always.
Just as you are now.
Is that what it's like with God?
Can you walk into any empty
church and just talk to him...
like I came here to talk to you?
-I don't think God hears me anymore.
-Why?
-What's happened to you?
-Perhaps it's the war.
Perhaps I don't want
things to be different.
-What do you think of Dane?
-He's a fine boy.
You and Luke must
be very proud of him.
He wants to be a priest.
Stop him, I beg you.
I couldn't bear it.
Because of me?
I lost you to God. I don't
want to lose Dane, as well.
Meggie, you never lost me.
You think I haven't wanted you?
Every moment, waking,
sleeping, praying...
you've been in my
heart and in my mind.
I need the warmth of
someone real beside me...
not the cold love of God.
Luke?
He's changed, he
wants to settle down.
I知 pregnant. I知 going
to have Luke's baby.
-What?
-That's what you wanted, isn't it?
''Marry Luke and be
happy,'' you said.
''Settle down and
have lots of babies.''
Well, that's exactly
what I知 going to do.
I知 going to be a
good Catholic girl...
and have lots and lots of
babies, Luke's babies...
-just as you said I should.
-Oh, Meggie.
Hello, Luke.
You again.
For Meggie's sake, I think you
and l should sort a few things out.
We've got nothing to sort out.
She's my wife, you're the intruder.
But she lives here.
Not for much longer.
Meggie's back with me.
-She's going to have my baby.
-Yes, she told me.
I知 very pleased for you both.
Drogheda is a wonderful
place for children.
No, we're not staying here.
-But there's no reason for you to leave.
-Yes, there is.
You think I want this new kid
growing up in this Catholic hothouse?
Look what happened to
the other two, to Dane.
The Church has never
interfered with your life.
Maybe not the Church directly.
But you have, haven't you?
So, I知 buying a place of my own.
Not much by your standards,
but I think we'll be happy.
And she won't be here for
you to come running back to...
every time you need
a dose of reality.
But you can stay on here. I値l
hire you to manage the place.
I知 not slaving the rest of my
days working for some mick in Rome.
Meggie's brothers can break their
backs running this place for you...
when they get back from the war...
but I値l have no part of it.
You conned old Mary Carson
into giving you this place...
and I壇 love to know the
truth of that one one day...
but it's all yours now...
lock, stock and barrel.
And I wish you the joy of it.
But I keep Meggie.
-My Lord.
-Why don't you call me Ralph?
-Because you're an archbishop.
-Pretend I知 not.
Not here.
It's one of the last
waterholes left...
because of the drought.
The wild animals come
here at sunset to drink.
I love it here.
Do you like being a priest?
Sometimes I find it
very difficult, Dane.
I seem to spend my
life searching for God.
Father Hammond, my
teacher, says God is here.
-They say God is everywhere.
-Yes, but especially here.
You're very lucky, Dane.
Not everyone has this.
-You said he was everywhere.
-You sound like a Jesuit.
I知 going to a Jesuit school
in Sydney in a couple of years.
At least, I was.
Now Dad's come back, and
he isn't too keen on it.
What's all this about you
wanting to be a priest?
Everyone says I should wait
until I知 older to decide...
-but I don't know why.
-You're very young, and you'll change.
In a couple of years, things
will happen to your body...
and you'll start getting
interested in girls...
and that's a very big
problem for a priest.
I know about girls.
I致e seen the animals.
I know what goes on.
You may know certain facts,
but you can't know the feeling.
That doesn't happen till later.
I fell in love once, and my
whole life has been a battle...
to decide if I love
her more than God.
But you wouldn't leave the Church.
No.
No, she deserves the best
that life can give her...
and I don't think that's me.
So it's all right?
I wish it were that easy.
Look.
Where's the ward? Thank you.
So silly, all this
rain here in Sydney...
and 1,000 miles away, we're
desperate for one drop.
Now, what did the
specialist say, Jack?
Same as all the others.
You ain't going to get any
grandsons out of me, Mom.
Half a man, that's what I am now.
Don't talk like that, you
can still have a fine life.
It was never very important before,
getting married, having kids.
Plenty of time for that, I
thought. Any bloke can do that.
That's the easy part.
I was wrong.
-I知 sorry, Mom.
-Don't be silly.
I know how much you wanted grandchildren
to carry on the family line.
I have grandchildren:
Justine and Dane.
Yeah, but they're Luke's kids.
They're not Clearys to carry
on at Drogheda, are they?
''Sons,'' you always used to say.
''Sons are what a mother cares about.''
All your sons have been
a disappointment to you.
Stu's dead, Frank locked up
for the rest of his life...
and now me.
My sons have been my greatest joy.
-Momma...
-It is God's will, dear.
We must trust in him.
-What is it?
-It's Luke.
He thinks you're encouraging
Dane to become a priest.
-I won't be a problem much longer.
-Why?
Because you're leaving...
and when you all move away,
he won't have to see me again.
-But I値l still see you.
-No, Meggie.
Sooner or later, I値l be
going back to Rome, and...
you two have a life together
that doesn't include me.
We can still see each
other while you're here.
-You're part of my life.
-I知 part of your past.
You've chosen a new life with
Luke, which is right and proper...
though I don't think
it'll be easy for you.
The last thing you need
at the moment is me.
I知 upsetting you,
making Luke angry...
and hurting myself.
I didn't want to come back here.
And when I had to,
I swore to myself...
that I壇 see you as
little as possible.
What a fool I was.
What I really wanted
was for things...
to be as they always
had been between us.
But you're right.
Too much has changed.
Go with Luke...
and find as much
happiness as you can.
Well, here we are.
Home sweet home.
It's fine.
-Where's all the livestock?
-There ain't none yet.
This place hasn't been worked in years.
That's why I picked it up for a song.
We'll get some stock cheap...
and we'll have it looking
like a farm in no time.
Come on, Dane, let's find a creek.
Of course, it needs a
bit of fixing up, but...
It's a great big kitchen...
and the stoves come off the hearth.
I値l get you a new one
in a couple of years.
A bit of soap and water, you
won't even know the place.
You can hang the baby's
things up here. And look.
We can put Justine in there...
and Dane can go in here.
And this...
And this is us.
So, what do you think?
-It's awful, Luke.
-It's not that bad.
It is. It's terrible.
It's gonna take months to
make this place livable.
When it does, we can put the
cot there for the little one.
And then, when he gets bigger,
he can move in with Dane.
So what's the bed like?
I don't know. You try.
I知 going to go make a cup of tea.
Well, this is the life.
All the family together.
What are we gonna do about school,
Dad? Will we still use the wireless?
At least you'll be going to
school in Sydney next year.
I have to wait another two.
Dane, your father doesn't
want you to go to Sydney.
He needs you here
on the farm, you see.
There's a school at
Gladstone, 20 miles away.
It's a good school for country boys.
-Is it Catholic?
-No.
Then why do I have to go there?
Because your father says so, darling.
-But I知 going to be a priest.
-No, you ain't.
lf you feel the same
when you leave school...
-we'll talk about it then, all right?
-No, we won't.
It's not for now...
it's for always.
He'll never be able to have children.
Never have sons.
He'll never know the beauty
of God's greatest gift.
How can you do it?
How can you possibly
choose a life like yours?
How can you not want
to have children?
I wanted to make the sacrifice...
to prove my love for God.
You have every right
to be here, of course.
But you must know, I would
much rather you weren't.
You think I don't know
about you and Meggie?
Mary Carson knew.
She knew it the moment she
saw the two of you meet...
all those years ago.
And I think I always knew it, too.
But I didn't want to believe it.
And now, just when I thought everything
was over, you had to come back.
Fee, I知 a priest.
There's nothing between us.
Then either I知 a
fool, or you're a liar.
No, you're not a fool,
and I知 not a liar.
That's all over now.
She's chosen Luke.
She chose Luke once before.
Look what happened then.
Do you really think
Meggie doesn't love you?
She doesn't want Luke. She
wants a father for the children.
She wants you.
And all you would have to do
is to say the word, one word...
and she would be with
you in a heartbeat.
I can't.
I am nothing, I have nothing.
Is that what you told her?
Don't do to Meggie what
you did to Mary Carson.
Don't destroy her with love.
Grandma!
You should see the new farm, it's
awful. But Dad's going to fix it up.
How's Uncle Jack?
When's he coming home?
Not for a while, dear.
You're still here?
-He won't let me be a priest.
-That's enough.
You don't discuss family
business with strangers.
-Ralph is not a stranger.
-He is to me.
I壇 like to hear what
the boy has to say.
No.
Dane's my son, and I値l
bring him up my way.
I don't want you interfering with his
education. I want you off this place.
This is Church property, Luke. And
the Church demands that I be here.
I値l stay as long as they need me.
Then we'll get out of your way.
My family and I will be out of
this place by the end of the week.
What?
And if I ever catch you
sniffing around my boy...
or my wife, or
anything else of mine...
I値l break your bloody neck.
Luke, please.
Luke, we cannot go to the farm,
not yet. There's too much to do.
We're getting out of here.
There's a curse on this place.
There's no running water,
the house is falling down.
So we'll have to
rough it for a while.
But I知 not going to be lorded
over by some snotty-nosed priest.
He's just trying to help.
I don't want his help, I
want him out of my life.
I want him out of Dane's life,
and I want him out of your life.
I知 not going, Luke, not
until the farm is ready.
-You're my wife and you'll go where I say.
-You don't own me!
This is the same as last time, me
dancing to your beck and call...
stuck in some dump
somewhere, never seeing you.
-It's him, isn't it? That priest.
-Don't be ridiculous.
I never understood
before, but I do now.
So how many times has he
had his grubby hands on you?
Don't you ever say that!
-Luke!
-I知 sorry.
The baby, Luke, the baby!
Mr. O'Neill...
there was nothing we could do
to save the baby. I知 sorry.
And Meggie? Mrs. O'Neill?
She'll be fine.
I知 afraid...
Mr. O'Neill, I don't think she'll
be able to have any more children.
I could be wrong, and she should
see a specialist in Sydney, but...
She's resting now.
Mr. O'Neill, I think she
might like to see you.
Yeah, sure.
How are you feeling?
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I was angry.
You made me angry.
You'll be up and about in a few
days, and we'll be out of here.
Didn't the doctor tell you?
There won't be any more children.
-Yeah, he told me.
-I値l never be able to give you a son.
Don't get yourself all worked up
about it. I致e already got a son.
I致e got Dane.
Meggie wants to see you.
Some Catholic mumbo-jumbo, I guess.
Meggie, I知 so sorry.
It's my fault. I was such a fool.
-You couldn't have known.
-I could have.
I was married to him, I
know what he's capable of.
There's no need for this now.
I so much wanted to
believe that he'd changed...
and that I could live with him,
because the children needed a father.
You should have
written to me, told me.
I just couldn't stand
the guilt anymore.
You have no idea how much
guilt a woman is made to feel...
when she leaves her husband.
You found the strength
to leave him once.
I was unfaithful to
Luke, and I lied to you.
Don't do this to yourself.
This is God's revenge, isn't it?
He's taken my baby.
My poor, sweet, innocent baby.
My baby.
Don't.
Do whatever you want with me.
Do whatever you like with me.
You can have my faith...
have my vocation...
have my life.
But not her.
Don't play games with her.
Let her be happy.
It's not right, Justine. You
haven't been doing your homework.
Open your history book to Page 87.
Yes, Mrs. Henderson.
You've been on your feet all
morning. Why don't you sit down?
I知 all right, Mom.
Really. I promise you.
Where's Ralph?
Went into town early to
talk to Father Hammond.
Did you tell him?
You must. You must put
an end to these lies.
You must tell Luke,
and you must tell Ralph.
No. The problem isn't with Ralph.
It's with Luke and me.
I can't tell Ralph about Dane.
But I can put the rest of it right.
I wish Ralph had never come back.
Look, don't blame Ralph, blame Luke.
He hit me. He caused this.
-So when will you be ready to go?
-I知 not going, Luke.
Look, I did a really bad thing.
I should never have agreed
to us getting back together.
You seemed pretty keen on the
idea till that priest turned up.
This has nothing to do with
Ralph. This is my decision.
-You're my wife.
-I was your wife.
Whatever there was between
us was over a long time ago.
I realize that now.
-Is that your final word?
-Yes.
I知 sorry.
-Dane.
-What do you want with him?
It's none of your business anymore.
Go to your room, get
your things packed.
-Where are we going?
-We aren't going anywhere.
-It's just me and Dane.
-Oh, no. You are not having Dane.
You try and stop me.
-You're coming with me.
-But I don't want to go.
You'll do as you're told. Get to
your room and get your things packed.
-You must tell him now.
-I can't.
-What about me? Why not me?
-I don't want you. I知 sick of girls.
-All I want is my son.
-But I love you.
I want to be with
you. I don't like her.
-I hate her.
-Not half as much as I do.
You walked out on me once before.
I was a fool to trust you again.
-You can't just take Dane.
-He's my son, too!
All these years you kept him from me.
You never even told me I had a son.
That's why I came back when I heard.
You think I came back here for you?
You think I came back for your
nagging and moaning again...
and carrying on like Lady Muck?
I was prepared to put up with
you for the sake of the boy.
But all I want is him. Now,
I told you to go and pack.
-No!
-You'll do without, then. Come on.
For God's sake, Luke,
please, don't do this.
-You watch me.
-Daddy!
-Daddy, I知 coming with you.
-You get back there with the other skirts.
Mommy, I don't want to go!
-Listen, please.
-Help me, Mommy!
-Take me with you, Daddy!
-As for you, go back to that priest.
-Meggie, tell him!
-You can't handle a real man.
Don't! No, don't!
Dane!
Mommy!
Luke's gone, and he's taken Dane.
-He can't do that.
-There wasn't much I could do to stop him.
Bring him back to me. Please
make Luke bring him back to me.
Come here, boy. Come on.
I致e been to the store, got you
some new pants and some shirts.
It's about time you were in long
pants, instead of those silly shorts.
This is a big adventure, two
blokes out here in the Never Never.
Why don't you go and
put those new pants on?
First long pants you've ever had.
They'll make you
feel like a new man...
for a new life.
All right, Dad.
Look, boy, I know you're
upset, but it's done.
-So try and forget the past.
-I値l never forget Mom.
No one's expecting you
to. You'll see her again.
But in the meantime, Dane...
make the most of it,
because I知 all you got.
Look at you. Quite the
young man about town.
Two, four, six, eight.
Bog in, don't wait.
Can I say grace?
Well, you know, that
stuff gives me the willies.
lf you must.
-Is there no chance between you?
-How can you ask me that?
-You were going back to him.
-Because the children needed a father...
and because I was lonely.
So I went back to Luke,
but it wasn't for love.
When he hit me, when I lost the
child, I realized he hated me.
He didn't come back here for
me, he came back here for Dane.
lf he had taken Justine as well,
maybe I could forgive him...
but he broke her heart,
and she blames me for that.
I致e made such a mess of
things. What am I going to do?
First of all, we must
get Dane back to you.
Yes.
I don't want to be too optimistic,
but I think you've got a good case.
It would be easier if you and Mr. O'Neill
were divorced or legally separated...
but in most cases of this kind...
the court will usually award
custody of any children...
-to the mother.
-Thank God.
Of course, you had agreed
to go back to Mr. O'Neill.
-He attacked her physically.
-She is his wife.
She lost a child because of him.
And that will get a lot
of sympathy, of course...
but this is not a divorce case.
Dane's welfare will be the
judge's primary concern.
Is there anything you
haven't told me? Anything...
I知 sorry to be personal.
Anything that might
reflect on you as a mother?
Any special friendships outside
the marriage, for example?
Luke does not approve of my friendship
with Archbishop de Bricassart.
I imagine he'll try and
make something out of that.
I don't think that
will get him very far...
unless there's more to
it than meets the eye.
There's considerably more to it
than meets the eye, Mr. Gough.
The eye cannot see
what is in the heart.
And what is in my heart
is pure and wonderful.
Archbishop?
I am religious counselor to Mrs.
O'Neill. I have been for a very long time.
As you were to Mary Carson?
As I was to Mary Carson.
I知 sorry to have to probe,
but the court may do the same.
So, let's see if we can't get
Dane back to you, Mrs. O'Neill.
Thank you.
I lied to him.
After all the promises I
made to myself and to you...
that I wouldn't tell any more lies...
and I couldn't tell him the truth.
We both lied, to get Dane back.
You heard what he said.
lf anyone knew, if anyone found out
how much we have loved each other...
I shall lose Dane,
and I can't risk that.
Father Ralph. Is Mommy with you?
Not this time, Dane. I致e
come to talk to your father.
-Want to see me on my new pony?
-Sure.
Meggie wants legal custody of Dane.
Look, Father Ralph, he can jump, too.
The natural place for that
boy is with his father...
and I値l take it to every
court in the land if I have to.
You can't win, Luke. The
courts always favor the mother.
We'll see about that.
Now, if that's all...
you'd best be on your way. Cheers.
Justine, I need to talk to you.
You can't stay in your room forever.
I have some news about
your father and Dane.
-What's the news?
-You may not like it very much.
I知 taking your father
to court to get Dane back.
-Why are you so horrible to Daddy?
-That's not fair, Justine.
Don't hate me.
You know, when I was your age...
I used to think your grandma
didn't love me. Well, I was wrong.
It breaks my heart to
think you feel the same way.
I just want to be happy.
We were happy, sort of,
when Daddy came back.
Till that priest showed up.
This has nothing to
do with Father Ralph.
And when we get Dane back,
we will be happy again.
I won't be, not here.
I want to be with Dad.
-After what he did to you?
-He didn't mean it. He loves me.
Justine, Luke doesn't
love either of us.
He does, I know he does.
Listen to me.
They may ask you some
questions in court...
so I want you to think
about this very seriously.
Remember all the things
Luke did when he came back?
He never paid you any
attention. It was always Dane.
Now, that is true, isn't it?
Just think about it, promise me?
It's all I ask.
Look, why don't you
have something to eat?
Or better still, come
downstairs and eat with us.
-Is he here, Father Ralph?
-Yes. He's helping me...
-Dane?
-Mommy!
Are you all right? Has
he been looking after you?
We're doing great. Aren't we, Dane?
Why don't you come
and live with us, Mom?
And Justine, and Grandma.
We'd have a great time.
Darling.
Luke.
Come on.
And is there no hope of reconciliation
with your husband, Mrs. O'Neill?
No, Your Honor.
I壇 have her back in a moment,
Your Honor, but she doesn't want me.
You hit me! I lost a
child because of you!
-What kind of love is that?
-That was an accident.
-You made me lose my temper.
-I warn you...
I will not tolerate
this sort of behavior.
This is a court of
law, not a farmyard.
Remember this:
I have to decide who is the
most suitable parent for the boy.
At the moment, I am not
impressed by either of you.
Why did you wait 10 years...
before making contact with
your family, Mr. O'Neill?
I didn't know that I had a
son until a few months ago.
She didn't even tell me
that she was pregnant.
I heard it round the tracks,
so I was pretty cut up about it.
I mean, what man...
wouldn't want to be a
good father to his own son?
Most men want to be good
husbands to their wives.
I was that.
I was saving to buy
a place of our own.
Isn稚 it true that you already
had the money to buy your farm?
You had $20,000 given to
you by your wife's family.
That was her money, her
dowry. I wasn't gonna touch it.
But you still took it.
You stole it from me.
I put that money into
an account under my name.
And I never touched a penny of it.
I offered it back to Megan,
but she refused to take it.
-Is that true, Mrs.
O'Neill? -Yes, but it--
Carry on, Mr. Gough.
Didn't you tell your wife...
that the only reason
you came back to her...
was for Dane?
That was a big part.
Perhaps the biggest.
But I still loved her.
And it was great. I thought
that everything was sweet.
Until that priest turned up,
and then everything changed.
Megan said it was over between us.
And I got mad...
and I said some things that
I shouldn't have said...
and I did some things
that I shouldn't have done.
Maybe.
Why do you think
the arrival of the...
-Archbishop de Bricassart, Your Honor.
-...priest...
changed your wife's mind?
I don't know.
He's always had some
kind of hold over her.
It's a Catholic thing.
So your son has been
raised as a Catholic?
Too right.
Look, I don't mind him
being raised a mick...
I beg your pardon, Your Worship.
But it's gone too far.
Dane is a good boy.
But they've got their claws
in him. The Church, I mean.
They even own Drogheda, his home.
He goes on about being
a priest all the time.
He needs his dad.
And you don't want
him to be a priest?
What father would?
Why are you not in uniform,
serving your country?
I would be like a shot, Your Honor...
but I did my back cutting cane,
and the army say they won't have me.
Tell me about your farm, Mr. O'Neill.
It's a bit rough and ready at the
moment. Hasn't been worked in years.
But with some hard work...
And with your bad back, you
would expect Dane to help.
Of course. I couldn't
manage the place on my own.
And his schooling?
There's a good school 20 miles away.
How would he get there?
He'd walk part of the
way and catch the bus.
-How far?
-Four miles.
There and back?
So you would expect the boy...
to walk eight miles a day...
do his schoolwork, do his
homework, and help you on the farm?
It would be tough. But
all country boys do it.
Most country boys have a
mother to take care of them.
-Who would do the cooking?
-Me.
-And the washing?
-Me...
till he was old enough.
And who would take care
of him if he got sick?
Me.
As well as managing the farm.
You'd be a very busy
man, Mr. O'Neill.
I think Mr. O'Neill
cooked his goose today.
He sounded like he only
wants Dane for child labor.
-More like a slave.
-Indeed.
Can I have a word, Archbishop?
Excuse us, please.
It isn't over yet.
You heard what Mr. Gough
said. You heard Luke.
I don't think it's that simple. I
don't know what the judge will say.
He's going to give
Dane to me. He must.
Why take the risk?
Why not end it now? Tell the truth.
Tell someone Luke
isn't Dane's father.
Because there's no need.
All this time, I wanted
someone to understand...
what my life with Luke was like.
You never believed me.
Now everyone will know.
The judge wants to
put you on the stand.
-Why?
-It's this Catholic thing.
Shook him rigid when he heard
about Dane wanting to be a priest.
Why, it shook me, too.
His Honor's real old-time
Protestant. He can't stand micks.
Begging your pardon, Archbishop.
Come on, Justine, we're going home.
Where's Justine?
She's not well. She's
not coming today.
But the judge might want
to ask her some questions.
She's sick.
In any case, I think it might be
better if the judge doesn't talk to her.
What is your relationship
with Mrs. O'Neill, Archbishop?
I致e known Mrs. O'Neill
since she was very young.
Since she first came
here many years ago.
I advise her on religious matters.
And what is your
relationship with Drogheda?
The Church owns Drogheda. The
Clearys manage it for the Church.
The Catholic Church
owns all of Drogheda?
-Yes.
-How so?
The property was left to the
Church by Mary Carson, who owned it.
Left to you.
What does Mr. O'Neill mean by that?
The Archbishop was Mary Carson's
religious advisor as well.
She left the property
to the Church...
so long as the worth and ability of
Ralph de Bricassart is appreciated.
So, you would have a
considerable personal interest...
in what happens at Drogheda?
Not in the day-to-day running of the
place. The Clearys do that very well.
But we do have an
interest, of course.
It's more than an interest.
You're always poking your nose in.
Mr. O'Neill. Please.
Having control of such
an enormous property...
must be helpful to your career.
Being a priest is not
a career, Your Honor.
Nevertheless, the Church
continues to appreciate...
your worth and ability.
I hope I致e been of service.
What is your Church's
position regarding...
Mr. and Mrs. O'Neill's marriage?
It is the position of the Church
that their marriage is sacrosanct.
So you would advise Mrs. O'Neill
that her place is with her husband?
Yes.
-And she chooses to ignore you?
-I only advise.
And do you also advise
Dane on religious matters?
I hardly know Dane. I致e spent
very little time with him.
But you have spoken
about religion with him?
-Briefly, yes-- -Do
you see what I mean?
The micks have really
got their claws--
Mr. O'Neill, I appreciate that
you're representing yourself.
So you are aware of Dane's
desire to become a priest?
Yes.
And have you tried to discourage him?
I have tried to point
out the disadvantages...
the sacrifices he must make.
So you have, in effect, advised
him on religious matters?
-I have briefly discussed God with him.
-See what I mean?
Do you have an attitude to
Dane's desire to become a priest?
Of course.
Are you able to share
that attitude with us?
A calling to the priesthood
is a sacred thing.
lf it's a true vocation, it's
the greatest gift I can imagine.
Even at his age?
He is very young...
but there have been
saints as young as he.
There have indeed, Archbishop.
That will be all. Thank you.
I値l go and see how Justine is.
I知 sorry, Meggie. It was an
unfortunate line of questioning.
You've broken all your other vows.
Why do you have to be
honest at my expense?
Because this is too important.
More important than
Dane coming back to me?
You heard the judge. You know
what he thinks about Catholics.
I couldn't lie. I
couldn't lie about Dane.
He's not going to become a priest.
He's a little boy growing up
here, miles from anywhere...
and the Church is magical to him.
God's his friend, someone
to talk to when he's lonely.
But he'll grow out of it.
He'll want to get
married and have children.
I couldn't lie.
Damn you.
There you are, at last. I致e got
dinner on and a nice cup of tea.
Mrs. Smith, where's Justine?
She's not in her room.
No? She took off early this
morning, just after you left.
-Didn't you know?
-No, we didn't know.
But where the devil could she be?
It went very well today, Dane.
-The judge doesn't like Catholics,
does he? -Not much.
Nor do l.
-Then why do you love me?
-Because you're my son.
And I壇 love you no matter what.
Looks like we got visitors.
-Justine!
-Dane!
Hello, Dad. I致e got dinner ready.
What are you doing here? Stupid.
You're gonna ruin everything.
No, it's all right. I知
gonna make it all right.
You'll see.
Yeah, well, maybe you
can help after all.
That's a young girl.
Now, what's for supper?
Why did you run away
from home, Justine?
Because I wanted to be with my daddy.
-Don't you love your mommy?
-No.
She's never loved me.
She's never cared about me.
-Never been interested in what I wanted.
-That is not true.
Drogheda doesn't feel like home.
I wanted a proper
home, a proper family.
So you were happy when your
father came to Drogheda?
Yes. He was wonderful to us.
Even Mom was happy...
till he showed up.
Then Mom changed.
She didn't seem to care
about Daddy anymore.
She wanted to be with the priest.
She spent all her time with him,
whispering to him, hugging him.
She started having rows with Dad.
And then she said we weren't
gonna move to the farm.
We had to stay at
Drogheda without Dad.
I didn't want that. I just
want to be with my dad.
I don't understand why
she doesn't love him.
I do.
Tell me, Justine...
how do you feel about your religion?
I don't have a religion. I used
to be Catholic. Not anymore.
I can't stand it now. They're
always ramming it down my throat.
Mom, the nuns, and now him.
-That is not true!
-It's worse for Dane.
-They're trying to force him to be
a priest. -Why do you say this?
-He doesn't want to be...
-You see what I mean?
It's not true, Justine. You're
lying! Why are you lying?
That's gone far enough!
All his life he has never had a
father. I brought him up on his own.
I never heard from
Luke, from my husband.
But Dane has been given
love and affection...
and my two brothers have
been like a father to him.
For nine years...
For nine years he ignored Dane...
just as he completely
ignored Justine.
You walked out on me, remember?
-Mr. O'Neill. -I never
even knew that I had--
I will not warn you again.
The marriage was over.
Be that as it may,
do you not think...
that a man has the right
to know that he has a son?
Would you tell His Honor why you
won't go back to your husband?
Because he was violent toward me.
Because of him, I lost
the child I was carrying.
And I won't be able to have any more.
-Is this child Mr. O'Neill's child?
-Of course.
I have no more questions, Your Honor.
-Would you like a little break,
Mrs. O'Neill? -No, thank you.
Mr. O'Neill, do you
have any questions?
Why did you leave me?
Because you neglected me and
you ignored your children.
Dane wasn't even born
when you walked out on me.
Justine was. You didn't
even want to see her.
She was two years old before
you even set eyes on her.
Because I was so busy working.
As Your Honor is very well
aware, this is not a divorce case.
Quite right, Mr. Gough.
I don't see any value in going back
over your marriage, Mr. O'Neill.
We are agreed that there is
an irreconcilable breakdown.
I知 not.
I loved my wife and
my child, my children.
And I took my duty as a husband
and provider very seriously.
I tried to look after their future...
and I will not have
my boy become a priest!
You weren't even there!
All these years you haven't
cared what your son wanted to be.
-Why do you care now?
-I didn't know I had a son.
He lied to me.
He came back after all those
years and he said he wanted me.
He didn't want me.
All he wanted was Dane.
He lied to me and then he hit me.
What happened right before
I hit you? Right before?
-We had an argument.
-Why?
Because I wouldn't move to the farm.
-And what did you
do? -Nothing. l--
No. What did you do?
-I believe I tried to hit you.
-Mr. O'Neill.
She
made me--
I will not allow that
behavior in this court!
Violence is not an answer
to your marital problems.
There is nothing that Mrs.
O'Neill could have done...
that would justify
what you did to her.
I warn you, outbursts of this
kind do nothing to help your case.
Now, if you have any
further questions...
you'll ask them in
a gentlemanly manner.
Otherwise, sit down.
No, I知 through.
I am extremely sorry...
for the loss that you have
suffered, Mrs. O'Neill.
That will be all. Thank you.
Thank you.
I find myself...
in an extremely difficult position.
The only way I can
see to resolve it...
is to ask Dane some
questions in private.
Mr. O'Neill, do you
have any objection?
No, Your Honor.
-Mrs. O'Neill?
-No.
-Do you love your mother, Dane?
-Very much.
And do you love your father?
I don't know him very well.
I love the idea of having a father.
Do you like living with him?
Sort of. He's very good to me, but...
I miss my mom.
lf you could choose...
who would you rather live with,
your mother or your father?
lf I say Dad, then
my mom would be upset.
And if I say Mom, then
my dad would be cross.
I suppose that's why
you've got to choose.
Can't you give me any idea?
My dad isn't too keen
on my being Catholic...
so it would be better
if I lived with my mom.
We're going to lose him.
You know that, don't you?
And it's so easy. You only
have to tell the truth.
I can't do that to Ralph.
You love him so much, you'd
risk everything for him?
Don't make it worse for me.
He is not going to give
Dane to Luke. He can't.
lf he does?
I don't know. I don't
know anything anymore.
I watch Dane with Luke,
and I see that he's happy.
They say he needs a father more
than anything in the world...
and I wonder if Luke isn't right.
Maybe he does need a stronger
guiding hand than mine...
because if I知 not very careful...
I知 going to lose Dane, no
matter what the judge decides...
to Luke or to God.
Dane, what does the Pope mean to you?
He's the head of the Church, and
the representative of God on Earth.
-Do you believe everything he says?
-Yes. He's infallible.
He speaks for God.
-And you love your king and country?
-Yes.
Now, if your king were to
tell you to do something...
to fight for your country...
and the Pope wanted you
to do something else...
who would you believe?
Now, you promised to
tell me the truth, Dane.
Who would you obey? Your
king and country, or the Pope?
God.
This has not been an
easy decision for me.
As a general rule...
I believe that the best home life...
for any child of separated parents...
is with the mother.
However...
this may not be true in Dane's case.
It is unfortunate that the
boy has been brought up...
in such a hotbed of Popery.
Your Honor.
I mean no personal
disrespect, Archbishop...
but I知 sure you'll agree...
that Dane has an obsession
with his religion.
I think Dane is a very
sincere young man, Your Honor.
Yes. So do l.
But what Mrs. O'Neill
cannot provide...
and what Dane so clearly needs...
is the strong, guiding
hand of a father.
Dane's obsession, in my mind...
is unhealthy in one so young.
I think we need to undo some of
the damage that has been done.
But I don't know that Mr. O'Neill
can provide properly for the boy.
I believe that Dane's best
interests are probably served...
by sending him to a foster
home for a period of time...
-No! Mommy!
-...by making him a ward of the court.
No, please. Please, no.
Mrs. O'Neill.
-No, Mommy, don't let them take me.
-I知 attempting to be fair.
Is there anything you wish to
say, that might change my mind?
No, l...
Tell him.
Only that I知 his mother.
I gave birth to him, I致e
loved him all his life.
I know him better than
anyone else in the world.
You say that he has had too
much religious influence.
Well, perhaps, but
it's not been unkind.
Dane's been free to decide
what he believes for himself.
None of us wants him to become
a priest. Why would I want that?
I want him to grow up
strong and healthy...
to find a wife and have
children of his own...
if only, selfishly, that I
might have some grandchildren.
But if his vocation is
to become a priest...
then none of us have the right
to take that away from him.
Not Luke, not you, not l.
Not anyone.
Please, you can't send him to strangers
who don't know him, who don't love him.
Please.
Believe me, Mrs. O'Neill, I think
you've done a sterling job...
under very difficult circumstances.
But before the boy is much older...
I believe he needs a sense
of balance in his life.
Very well.
lf you won't let me have
him, then give him to Luke.
At least they know each other.
Very well.
I award custody of the
boy, Dane O'Neill...
to his father.
No, you can't do that.
-Mom.
-Because...
Because Dane is my only grandson,
perhaps the only grandson I値l ever have.
Please don't take away
my hope for the future.
I am trying to give you hope
for the future, Mrs. Cleary.
Mr. O'Neill.
Do not treat this lightly.
Do not abuse the boy.
Children are not property...
a way of getting free
labor for your farm.
I will want to see
Dane's school report...
and I will want to be certain that
you are caring for him properly...
before I let this
arrangement continue.
But me, what about me?
Your case is not in
my purview, young lady.
But it's not fair. I
want to be with my daddy.
This court is adjourned.
-I will come and see you whenever I can.
-But why does it have to be like this?
-Why can't we all be together?
-Dane, you know why.
You were so brave in court.
Why won't you come and live
with Dad? You're married to him.
I can't. I just can't.
-Why? Don't you love me?
-With all my heart.
Then why?
-Please don't cry, please.
-We have to go. It's a long way.
You have to go with Daddy now.
But be brave, and I will come
and see you as soon as I can.
-Come on.
-I don't want you. I want my mommy.
It's a bit late for that now, sport.
Didn't have to be like this.
It could have been so easy.
Come on.
-We should get you home.
-I want my son back.
God has had enough from me.
Make him give me my son back.
Hello, everybody.
Jack.
-Welcome home.
-Good to see you.
Put a smile on your face, girl.
They only shot off my privates.
It's not the end of the world.
Good to see you, everybody.
-Luke's determined to keep the boy, then?
-And he has the court on his side.
You done well with the place,
Meggie. Can't have been easy.
It wasn't.
It is wonderful to have you
back to take charge again.
I壇 have come back sooner if
I壇 known how bad things are.
-How long since you've had rain?
-Why didn't you come back sooner?
I phoned the hospital. You
were discharged last week.
I was expecting you then.
Where did you go?
I went to Melbourne.
Went to see Frank.
Look, Mom, we all know
he's in for murder.
But he's my brother,
and I wanted to see him.
How is he?
He's very sick. It's pneumonia.
It's bad news, Mom. The
thing is, he might not live.
Looks like rain in those clouds.
We haven't had rain here
for two years. We need rain.
Somebody should've told me.
I am his mother. I
have a right to know.
Almost everyone I
love is buried here.
Dane isn't dead, Meggie.
A terrible thing has happened,
but it's not the end of the world.
You'll still see Dane.
You're still his mother.
And in a few years, the
court order will expire...
and then you can have
him with you again.
But you can't stop living until then.
You have to go on and make the best of it.
You can't know what it means
to a mother to lose a son.
Look at Mom.
She went on living.
She didn't give up just because
her son Frank went to jail...
and she won't now.
Even if Dane were dead...
even if some terrible
accident had happened...
you'd grieve, but
you don't stop living.
Is that what you told
the mothers in Rome...
who lost their sons fighting?
Did you tell them to be happy
because their sons are with God?
At some point in the
war, I lost my faith.
In all that suffering, I
couldn't see God's purpose.
I couldn't understand how he
could let such evil happen.
I began to doubt.
My superiors sent me here
to work for the refugees.
But in the end...
I had to see you.
-I thought perhaps you might
still love me. -Perhaps?
I thought perhaps you
might still want me.
You might want to
make a life with me.
-You never told me this.
-You were going back to Luke.
-You were going to have his child.
-Do you think that mattered to me?
Do you think I wasn't longing
to hear you say those words?
Perhaps, if you'd told me...
none of this would've happened.
Perhaps, if you'd been honest, I壇
have told Luke to leave long before.
Perhaps, if you hadn't lied to
me, I would still have my son.
-I didn't lie to you.
-You didn't tell me the truth.
Meggie, my list of
sins is long enough.
Besides, I had nothing to offer you.
You don't think love is enough?
Ten years, Meggie. How could
I be sure you still loved me?
How could you not be?
All my life I致e loved you.
Sometimes I hated God
because he took you from me...
but always my love
for you was stronger.
Suddenly, I知 not so sure.
So are you going to
tell me what's wrong?
Why won't you let me see Mom?
You gotta get used to
this situation, Dane...
and I don't want her upsetting you.
-But she's my mom.
-And I知 your dad.
And you'll do as I
say. Now come down.
All right. You can stay up there all
night, if that's what you bloody well want.
But there's a storm coming, so
if you don't want to get wet...
and if you're hungry, and if you
want to sleep in a comfortable bed...
you'll come down. Otherwise,
I値l give your tucker to the dog.
Blue.
Come here.
I got a nice big piece
of steak for you tonight.
Yeah, Dane's piece. Come on.
My dearest Frank.
It's the rain we need,
but it's going to be bad.
There could be some
flooding. Where's Justine?
-She's in her room.
-You better get her down.
-We'll need all the help we can get.
-I値l fetch her.
-Seen Mom?
-She's with Mrs. Smith, isn't she?
Justine, open the door.
-What for?
-I want to talk to you.
Your mother isn't here.
So, you're gonna spend
the whole day up here...
moping about how unhappy you
are, and what a mess your life is.
That's my business.
There are a few other things that
are your business first, young lady.
-You can ride, can't you?
-Yes.
Then get changed into your
riding clothes and put this on.
What if I don't want to?
Justine, you're a country girl...
and your family runs this
station. It's been good to you.
It's given you security
and a safe future.
When you're old enough
to go out on your own...
you can do whatever you want,
but right now Drogheda needs you.
Why?
As you well know,
there's a storm coming...
and half the hands are useless...
and animals are going to die
unless you get off your fat behind.
It's not fat.
Maybe not, but it sure is
lazy. And we need your help.
Are you going to help us, Justine?
Not for your mother or for me...
but for yourself and Drogheda.
lf you put it like
that, how can I refuse?
You would make a good
actress, you know.
You sure had me fooled.
Young Billy!
-Boys! You got them horses ready?
-Yes.
Right, we've got to get everything
up to the top paddock. Let's go!
There's a strong filly!
Move it!
Get on! Move on!
Move!
Get in there!
It's so very beautiful.
God in all his glory.
I thought you didn't
believe in God anymore.
We'll never make it
back to Drogheda now.
There's a boundary rider's shack
on One Tree Hill. We'll go there.
What about the others?
They'll be back at
Drogheda by now. Come on.
-Dane, hold that gate!
-I致e got it, Dad.
-Go on, get up there.
-Come on, Blue, get around back!
-Get up there! Move your behinds!
-Come on, Blue!
Get around back. Come on, boy!
-That all, Dad?
-No, I can't find that blasted ram.
-And that bugger cost me a fortune.
-Can't be too far away.
You get your horse. Come on. Giddap!
Blue, get behind!
Sorry if it's a bit rough and ready,
but it's only used in emergencies.
At least we won't starve.
It's safe and dry, anyway.
-I値l see if I can get a fire going.
-Here's your dinner.
-It's Bully Beef.
-Gourmet treats.
You know, I lied to
you the other day.
I致e never stopped
loving you. I never could.
It's just I知 so confused.
I don't understand
what you want from me.
I don't know what I want myself...
except...
Giddap!
Blue, come on!
Dane! It's a waste of
time. It's nearly dark.
We won't be able to see.
Over there! Told you!
Dane, be careful!
Dane! Giddap!
Dad!
Dane!
Go on.
Dad! Help!
My leg! Over here!
-Dad, over here!
-Hold on, Son! Hold on!
-My leg! Over here!
-Hold on.
-Dad, help.
-Dad, my leg hurts.
-Wait there. Hang on.
Okay. All right. You'll be fine.
Here, drink this.
The sugar's 'cause you've had a
bit of a shock, and the whiskey...
well, why not?
What about the ram?
I値l go back in a tick. He's in
the bushes. He's not going anywhere.
It's broken.
It's not that bad, it's a clean break,
but it's going to have to be set.
-Now, you trust me?
-Yeah.
Good man.
Now, it's going to hurt.
All right.
So have another swig of this...
and you can say a prayer if you like.
I致e never done this on a
person before, only a dog.
You ready?
-Morning.
Stay there. You get breakfast in bed.
It's baked beans and Bully Beef, I知
afraid. That's the best I could do.
Smells marvelous. I知 starving.
-Last night was wonderful.
-Yes, it was.
We got lots to do.
We need to find some feed for the horses,
and I知 sure Blackie's starving, too.
Mrs. Cleary, I知 afraid he
doesn't want to see you, ma'am.
What do you mean? Why not?
He wouldn't say. He
was very determined.
But he must. I知 his
mother. He can't not see me.
I知 sorry. There's nothing I can do.
He can be difficult. They
get like that sometimes.
-Probably feels he's let you down.
-I知 his mother.
I知 sorry, ma'am.
-How is he?
-He's not very well at all, I知 afraid.
lf he won't see me,
does he need a priest?
Father Donovan's giving
him last rites now, ma'am.
I知 going to miss this
place, Bully Beef and all.
I致e been happy here.
That's what you said at Matlock
Island, but you had to leave.
This time, I知 not sure I want to go.
Ralph, all your life you've been so sure
what you wanted, what you believed in...
that I can't bear
to see you in doubt.
I don't know what's
real anymore. I don't.
In Rome, before the war,
I had a worthwhile life.
I thought I was doing some
good for the world, for God.
And then the war swept over
us, and God disappeared.
And now nothing makes sense anymore.
-But the refugees, I thought--
-Yes, working for them...
I feel I have a purpose again.
But even that puts
me at odds with God.
-With God or with the Church?
-Both.
lf I left the Church, I壇 have
nothing. You understand that.
You're a priest.
You have nothing now.
I致e never loved you for what
you have. I love for what you are.
And I love you...
so much. That I know.
lf you want me just as I am...
foolish, misguided, dirt-poor...
I知 yours.
I致e waited my whole
life to hear you say that.
No.
Meggie...
I知 offering to give
up the priesthood.
And do what? Shear sheep?
Why not?
No, Ralph.
When I知 beside you...
it's as close to
heaven as I can imagine.
But even when you're making love...
it's as if you're trying to
reach something beyond me.
Look, it's a wonderful idea...
the two of us living
together in the wilderness.
But it's not what you really want.
What I want is you.
We can always come back
here for a few days.
Depending on how long you stay.
lf you won't have me, either...
then I really don't know
what I知 going to do.
I do.
You're going to help me get
these sheep back to Drogheda.
Dane! Got a visitor.
-Gran.
-Dane.
Darling, what's happened?
Broke my leg. It hurts
like anything, Gran.
Gran, it hurts. Take me
home. Please, take me home.
-I want Mom.
-There, there, darling.
It'll be all right. Gran's here now.
She'll make everything all right.
There.
He's sleeping now. Doctor
gave him a sedative.
Put the leg in plaster. Said
you did a very good job...
-setting the break.
-That's a wonder.
Never actually done
it on a person before.
Only on me dog, Blue.
-You've got a lot to do here.
-Yeah, heaps.
But I want to make a go
of it, for Dane's sake.
He's my son, and...
I can't manage the place on my own...
and the boy doesn't
seem much interested.
I知 not surprised. He wants to do
something else with his life, doesn't he?
We'll work it out.
-You'll break Meggie's heart.
-Like she broke mine.
She didn't break your heart.
She was a pretty girl and a good catch,
but mostly what you saw was her money.
I offered her that money
back, like I told the judge.
Only 'cause you knew
she'd never take it.
I壇 be surprised if
you even had the money.
Did you spend all of
it? All of her dowry?
Well, I kept a few quid.
Enough for the deposit
on this place, anyway.
Just as I thought.
You know, you were clever, Luke.
Maybe a bit too clever
for your own good.
Everything you did when
you came back to Drogheda...
was part of a plan to get Dane.
-And I got him, too.
-Is that such a triumph?
My first son, Frank...
was not my husband's child.
When Frank found out, he ran away
and got in with bad company...
and ended up killing a man.
And I never saw him again.
He died in a prison cell...
and I didn't even have
a chance to say goodbye.
-Don't let that happen to Dane.
-It can't. It's different.
Dane'll never turn bad like Frank...
because I値l always be there for
him, like a good father should...
to teach him right from wrong.
But you're not his father.
lf I知 not, I壇 like to know who is.
Can't you guess?
That bloody priest.
I知 going to kill him.
I知 going to break every
bone in his body, I swear.
So why didn't she tell the judge?
He never would've given
Dane to me if she had.
To keep Dane, she would've
had to destroy Ralph...
and his life in the Church.
She gave away the boy she loved
for the sake of the man she loved.
Still, it makes sense, doesn't it?
Now we know why
Dane's so keen on God.
-Does Ralph know?
-No.
And you must never tell him.
It's no wonder she never
told me we had a son.
So how does it feel, Fee?
Having a lying bitch for a daughter
and a fornicating priest as her lover?
It's in the past, Luke.
We've all done things we regret.
Ain't that the truth?
Biggest mistake I ever
made was marrying her.
Let me take Dane away. I beg you.
Let there be an end to this, now.
You tell his dad to come and see me.
You promise me you will never
tell Ralph or Dane the truth?
-Why would I promise a thing like that?
-Because if you do...
Ralph will be forced to leave the
Church, and he will marry Meggie...
and they and Dane and
Justine will be a family.
And you will have nothing.
Well, we can't have
that, now, can we?
All right, Fee. I promise
I won't tell a living soul.
But I want to speak to that priest.
Meg, Justine! Mom's home!
We were worried about you, Mom.
I知 quite capable of
looking after myself.
Are you all right? What
have you been doing?
I致e been trying to come
to terms with Frank's death.
But that was two days ago,
Mom. Where have you been?
I went to see Luke and Dane.
Why?
Because Luke is my son-in-law,
and Dane is my grandson.
Is that reason enough?
I tried to persuade
Luke to give up Dane.
He wouldn't.
He wants to talk to Ralph.
To me?
Mrs. Smith, I would
love a cup of tea.
And so the spark ignites the fuel
and then forces the piston down.
-Hello, Dane. Luke.
-Father Ralph! Father!
Just hold your horses.
-You'll have plenty of time to talk to him.
-How's the leg?
Getting better. I致e been
through the war, as Dad says.
So what can I do for you?
-I thought you wanted to see me.
-Yes.
Just this once.
And then I never want
to see your face again.
Dane, take a good look.
Now, is that what you want to be?
A namby-pamby priest
in a woman's dress...
like this gutless wonder?
Is that why you got me
out here? To call me names?
Partly, yes.
I壇 hoped it was more serious.
I壇 hoped you were going to give Dane
back to his mother, where he belongs.
-Is that what you want?
-That's what Meggie wants.
-And you?
-I want what Meggie wants.
I値l bet you do.
I値l bet...
you're an expert at
what Meggie wants.
You shouldn't say things
like that in front of the boy.
Why not?
Why shouldn't the boy
know what his mother is?
And what you are?
All right, you've had your fun.
Now, for God's sake, let the boy go.
Make me.
I don't understand.
You want the boy?
You fight for him.
I知 a priest, Luke. I don't fight.
lf you don't fight...
you don't get the boy.
No! Stop!
This is stupid.
Dad, stop!
-I will not fight!
-A real man would.
No! Father!
Hit him, Father! Hit him!
Now you get out of here.
I won't fight a man
that won't fight back.
But that settles it. The boy is mine.
Dane, you come with me.
Father! No!
No!
The boy...
is mine.
-Dane?
-Mommy!
Dane!
Thank you.
This is an odd place to pray.
God is everywhere.
Our Lord was born in a stable.
And I needed somewhere quiet.
Dane prays here, too.
We all use it for different reasons.
I pretend it's a theater sometimes...
filled with people
cheering my performances.
And Mom used it as a
ballroom and danced with Dad.
Why did you have to come?
We were happy until you came here.
-Justie!
-Mom was gonna go back to Dad...
and he was gonna love
me, even if Mom didn't.
But you stopped that.
That had nothing to do with me.
No?
Funny that it all went wrong
just when you showed up.
And then, when Dad didn't
want me and took Dane...
I was sad at first.
But then something else happened.
What was that?
I thought, ''lf Dane isn't here...
''Mom will have to love me.''
But she didn't.
And she won't now, because
you interfered again.
I did what had to be done, Justine.
Dane would never have been happy.
But I might have been.
This was my chance of
happiness with Mom...
until you got Dane back.
I thought you loved Dane.
I do, with all my heart.
But everyone loves Dane.
There doesn't seem to
be any left over for me.
Justine, that's not true.
Isn稚 it?
I saw you when you came
back, all beaten and bloody.
Did he put up a good
fight, my father?
To stop you taking Dane...
because he loved him?
But nobody loves me.
Justine thinks that
you don't love her.
I know.
I don't know how to
tell her that I do...
not in any way she'll believe.
I see so much of myself in Justine...
and too much of Mom in me.
When I was a little girl...
back in New Zealand,
before we came here...
we were very poor.
I remember I was about
four or five years old...
and there was a doll
in a shop window.
I used to go and look at her every
day. I even gave her a name: Agnes.
She was pretty, with golden hair.
I wanted her so much.
On my next birthday,
Mom gave me Agnes...
all wrapped in brown paper.
Don't know how she could afford
it, and I didn't care then...
because she had given me the
most perfect present I壇 ever had.
So, you see...
it didn't matter that she never
told me she loved me, ever.
'Cause just once...
she'd given me the most
beautiful thing in the world.
I致e never been able to find
quite the right doll for Justine.
-So you're going back?
-To Sydney.
The government has finally
agreed to an inquiry...
into refugees and stateless people.
Of course, I have to be there.
And then on to Rome.
Have you found what
you were looking for?
Oh, yes.
I found that loving you...
is a blessing, not a burden.
And in fighting for Dane...
I discovered a strength
I never knew I had.
And it's the duty of the strong...
to protect, to fight for those
who can't fight for themselves...
especially children.
That's why I have to go back to
the war. That's where my work is.
I haven't found God.
I wish I understood this
God that you love so much.
I wish I did, too.
At night, I look at
the infinity of stars...
and I feel...
something beyond mortality.
I don't know what it is...
but I have to find out, or try.
I don't care what's out there.
God is love, and love is here.
What are you reading?
Hamlet.
I知 learning Ophelia's mad scene.
May l?
You really do want to
become an actress, don't you?
It's all I致e ever wanted to do.
Justine, I wanted to
tell you I知 sorry.
Come here.
Look, I know the last few
months haven't been easy for you.
All that business with
your father, and...
I am sorry things turned
out the way they did.
I壇 like to try and do
something to make it up to you.
How soon can you start
acting school in Sydney?
-I can't till I知 16.
-But if you were in Sydney...
you could go to acting classes,
or maybe see some theater.
-You mean-- -Look,
the thing is...
I don't want you to think that I知
trying to get rid of you, or anything.
I don't want to hurt you anymore.
Mom, don't be silly.
I wouldn't think that.
Going to school in Sydney is the
best present you could ever give me.
Better than a pretty doll?
Mom?
Never mind.
Just be happy.
Thank you.
All aboard!
I love you.