MALIBU
SPORT FISHING PIER
Malibu Seafood - Fish Market
Patio Cafe
MALIBU
27 MILES picturesque beauty
ZUMA BEACH
1/2 mile
I am okay.
Can you times
keep it short? - Clear.
Hi! Are you Johnny? - Yes.
Congratulations
to your profit. - Thank you.
Charlie, where are you then?
Hello?
Cool hut. - Because I can
get used to it. - Yes, is not bad.
Krasser shit.
- Not bad?
Sorry, folks,
have probably eaten something bad.
Have you in the car actually in the pocket
puked or could you's keep in stomach?
www.zvi.com, okay?
Sorry?
- Well, too much information.
Speaking of information.
I know why I'm here, but ...
You guys can not yet
all have won.
What's coming then
here at this rally?
Can I get a bit
Ask attention?
I believe,
I can answer all your questions.
First of all:
Welcome.
Hi! - Hi!
- On behalf of Winfree,
the brand new download service
for cutting-edge, international films.
My name is Maureen.
I'm the housekeeper.
You've already seen me in the clip,
in which the winners have been notified.
First, I say to each
of you briefly what. Charles ...
You are interested in
Technology and Computer.
A little.
Okay.
And Johnny, you are very athletic.
Yes, ma'am.
Vincent, a medical student, right?
- Correct.
Toll! Lola, you know by now, if you
want to make your Master? - Not yet.
Maggie,
how's your clothing line?
Fantastic.
Would you like safely.
And Jenna, I am pleased,
that you care for a few days
from your teacher
free might.
Now, you see, we have
a little research operated.
As a precondition to you
to invite in the Beach House.
My job is, you stay
to make as pleasant as possible.
As the winner of all your costs are covered
and you have the whole house.
You can watch freely
the refrigerator and the bar operate.
Also you have access to the pool,
the barbecue, all sports equipment
and one of the most beautiful private beaches,
has to offer to our country.
For a whole week.
Two rules. First:
This is really for each of you.
If one of you home earlier
want to go, then you must all go.
Secondly:
Nobody goes into the sea
after nightfall.
Well then, if you still
have any questions, ask me.
Everything, what you should know about the beach,
Joe tells you, the lifeguard.
You can find him from sunrise to
Sunset in his station on the beach.
So much for the rules.
Do you still have any questions?
Well, the allocation of rooms
depends on the bulletin board.
All right. - I would say,
we bring our luggage to the room
and head to the bar,
as long as the hot tub heats. And off!
Since I'm in.
- I've heard bar?
That's what I call "très chique".
Here's can withstand up. - Wow!
So, unfortunately, I still do not know,
which bikini to wear.
If you have multiple doing?
- Yes it is.
I like the purple.
- To me or to you?
Really?
- Yes, I have designed.
These are all sample parts.
And that's perfect now, to try them.
Yes. - Your steamer trunk
is still around in the way.
Oh ...
Yes, I imagine it away later.
Age, look,
This is the bedroom of the women.
What?
- You can see everything in detail.
Charlie, you're
really a tensioner, man.
It forces you no mitzugucken.
So I want. - Me too.
But Depends which undresses.
So, ladies, come on,
always nice to get out of the clothes.
Now making a
after another naked.
Very beautiful.
There you are. Keep it up.
Wait.
Before you go forth what, wait. - Why?
Perhaps here,
just like in these reality shows,
any hidden cameras.
I have in this computer freak
a really strange feeling.
I do not trust.
- There is something on that.
The was also a long time
in the house in front of us. - Precisely. - And ...
I do not know how you stand to
but I do not let me film determined.
I have an app
on my phone.
The automatically recognizes the frequencies
by all camera models. - Really?
Yes, if there are cameras here
we notice that.
What are they doing there?
- Who cares?
But wait a minute ...
What was that?
There is a camera.
Certainly. - Really?
Okay.
- And she's turned on at the moment.
These perverts
Watch us straight.
These Lola-brat is really hot.
But if we report,
might send us home all.
No. It's out of the question.
We're barely here. - Okay.
We have a plan and only,
then to avenge us. - Okay.
Sounds great.
You know what?
If the want to clamp,
we will give them what to tension.
The will
still surprised. Music, please. - Okay.
Wow, cool thing.
Maggie, what a show.
Are they in reality strippers?
- No idea.
Just as moving are the
perhaps supermodels or so.
Real juicy and plump.
Guys, this is indeed so hot here.
The thinking determines
we would always do.
Take off you. But not give them
the full program. That they do not get.
Real beautiful mares.
- Yes man. Krass.
Damn it.
Hey, Hypno-Boy.
Are you on reception?
Earth to Vincent.
Total kicked off.
Only that it's you know, not a bad word
about Jenna. Otherwise I'm going to kill you.
No, whence?
I am focussing more on Maggie.
No, ah northeast.
- What's going on at once?
Is only just
become interesting.
Well, sorry, guys.
They strapped that we sit and watch.
- Vincent, excellently observed.
The finger I had
almost overlooked. - That's not good.
Gentlemen, not good. - At least
I can rewind the recording
and all over again
run from the front.
But then you do not want
be in the room, because ...
But if you want, then remain.
- No I do not want this.
A second hand
can I always need.
I am happy,
if I may leave the room.
I plan an interesting technique.
- We'll just go out.
We will treat your privacy.
- Scratch you a calm.
The makes me crazy.
Which one?
- Maggie, the brunette.
The area is hot.
But actually, I have to say,
all of which are of the finest quality.
This is really frustrating.
I'm just air for them.
Then you must
not change what, kid.
Man, do not misunderstand. But I
take of an old lifeguard
but no advice
in matters of love. - Very friendly.
Then I'll times
verklickern two things. First:
I have a trunk
like a baby elephant.
Hello, My Big,
you have plenty of room in there?
Second: The talk about
that it would not arrive on the size,
is a huge bullshit.
Can you fully depreciate.
Look at me. You have to admit,
I look damn good.
Am well built,
Class complexion and so on.
I have in my
Lifeguard house just wait
they come to me automatically.
I also add very much that I
have already saved many relationships.
If I'm not even in it over there,
Then I push myself as a marriage counselor.
Dr. Joe, the lifeguard,
Slash marriage counselor, at your service.
You kidding me yet. - With what?
So that I am a marriage counselor? - No.
But I just do not think you
the women fly on its own, man.
I swear that's true.
No shit, buddy.
But if I am to be honest,
it is not enough that you want them.
You must namely
want to have you.
And how do I do that?
Tell me that. - Okay.
Then listen well.
I'll tell you this only once.
Go down to the harbor
Get a candle.
And so you stand easy
tonight at her bedroom window.
But do not get too close, get it?
Perhaps she finds it but shit.
Are you really sure?
I tell you, stand at the window, okay?
With your candle.
Unselfish you keep vigil.
In any weather.
Wow! - Cool.
The Hammer.
All right.
Shall We Dance?
Do not be shy.
Good night, ladies.
Good night.
What was that?
- A seal or so.
Well, do I sign out.
So, we'll see you tomorrow morning.
Good night, ladies.
Good night.
- What about your jacket?
Keep them. It reflects.
So I recognize you in the dark.
May I keep you company?
- Sure, come on in.
That's the Pleasant
at my job.
In addition, I am learning
always know cool people.
What exactly are you doing?
I do not know
where to start.
The manager.
Sometimes I cook
or yoga teacher or tour guide.
Girlfriend, if someone needs a.
- I'd like to do but have not yoga.
Seven clock tomorrow morning.
In all its freshness. - Ouch!
And when does the second hour?
Only to be number two,
you're accustomed.
Very funny.
That was a splash.
I like the prelude.
Especially if he knows what he's doing.
Yes, great.
Okay, so,
I must confess to you what.
I've never really done.
Hey, I can muck, myself.
Already clear.
I make the guys pretty sharp.
But I was very conservative upbringing.
So, after all. I'm still virgin.
But that's okay for me.
Everything else I've done.
No shit, everything.
Want to wait until the wedding?
- No. That's not it.
For the right person happens's.
What are you waiting, Lola?
At a friend, a lover,
a married types, an ax murderer?
So, if I'm honest,
I've never been in love.
I do not even know
how love feels.
Can you tell me that?
I can try.
I might even say,
that love and I are old friends.
Anyway, there is nothing better,
as the feeling of love or ...
... The feeling in someone
really love to be.
I guess,
does not help me.
Only patience.
That will come.
Well, I think,
I'm going in now.
Or I'll go walk on the beach.
I can not decide anyway.
So to me
now waiting for my bed.
I have, in the middle
at night a yoga class.
Me too.
- Thank you for the good conversation, Maureen.
Come on out!
Come out! Is okay!
I'm sorry,
if I scared you.
I have looked at Maggie.
She looks damn good.
But you're not bad either.
You can indeed look calm.
Did you her already said?
I could never do.
Hey, never say never.
If you hire the right,
makes you go that way already.
Would you give me
my robe rich?
Clear.
This coat here?
Yes, the Blue.
Easy Leg him down here.
- Okay.
Here.
Thank you.
I'm going again.
Hey!
That's you.
With you I have no more today
expected. - And what are you doing here?
I can not sleep.
- Why not?
Because I always
must think about you.
Jenna, Jenna!
Say, why are you?
Keep The Love lighter wings
these walls was not made of stone.
Now you leave me so unsatisfied?
And what satisfaction
can it be today?
He did not
written exactly
but how do I know Shakespeare,
he would now say: "Come to me".
Give me a moment.
Come on, I catch you.
Come on!
Really now? - Yes.
Come on now.
Okay.
Absolutely no thing.
Ready? - And how.
- Ready? Good.
Everything OK?
If you anhättest no panties,
I could start right away.
I understand you so bad.
Say that again please just.
I could set it aside.
I'm a master of the tongue.
Aha, a master of the tongue.
- Convince yourself of it.
Wait.
- Do you like that?
Someone's coming.
Stop, someone's coming.
Are you all right, kid?
Are you about all alone?
Yes.
But I would not want you here
my favorite walk sit stay.
I need a lot of movement.
As a compensation. For my age
I'm always pretty namely wuschig.
Say, you're with your parents
or a couple of friends here?
Or all alone?
I ...
No, lady, I mean ...
I, I'm alone.
Oh, my darling,
you might cold?
Do you want to know ...
... Actually else
know something, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Oh God!
- Shall I get you a blanket?
No thanks.
- Here, take my scarf.
No. - Yes Yes.
Good. - Yes, much better.
Cuckoo!
I found you.
Was it just for you horny
as for you, young man?
Now it's my turn.
Just do not, Lady!
I'm warning you! - Shame.
But I Publish my phone number
at Miss Maureen, okay?
I live very close.
In the senior residence 'Feierabend'.
- Yes OK.
And you, my child, have to learn,
to share in life.
Bye! - Bye!
Nice to meet you.
What did you do to your
Defense put forward?
Thank you. Okay?
Now you're with the supervision of it.
Not to look away.
Sharks are not particularly
keen on human flesh.
They confuse people with Robben.
The only reason it comes to shark attacks.
Are you crazy? Why you hang here
so lazy rum? I need you.
So, I have to ask very.
I do not hang around here.
I am cool
after the starting yoga exercises.
Okay, you've caught me.
I cool my cunt.
I hope that they
even still works.
These are pain,
I tell you.
I really have to say,
Yoga is very dangerous. No shit.
So, help me up.
Help on me.
No, not you.
Let me go. Hands off!
What do you need me?
Well, Lola was jogging on the beach and
has a stranded baby seal found.
Are you hurt?
They ran to Joe and has
then phoned the vet.
Make, please,
open the door. - Clear.
Is a funny guy.
Dr. Spencer has his him in
Brought Institute for marine mammals.
Now Lola wants a Charity Party
on the legs,
for donations
to collect the seal.
I find really strong.
- Thanks man.
At the party I am
definitely at the start.
So, then I'm
You wanted to come anyway.
- I wish that? - Yes.
Here's it but pretty cool.
- Out here? - Sure, of course.
Namely, with a live band.
We have space for more than
hundred partygoers. Bar tables, bar.
Oh yes, that is good.
While we have a whole list
aufgebrummt with rules get,
But we can
certainly talk to Maureen.
You have really a plan.
- Oh yes, and as I have to.
Is like a fashion show,
just without Models.
So with less Zickerei. And who knows,
what I still think of everything to Friday.
Incidentally, the party is on Friday.
Yeah!
Not you.
Hey, excuse me!
Do you have a second?
Yes, already. What's up?
- Excellent, man.
Andy West. For friends:
Andy West Coast. Tips joke, huh?
I'm Agent. And in this job
I'm always looking for Models.
You have a really interesting face.
My card. - No shit? - Yes.
But you hear
probably ever.
Because you, my friend,
look like a real movie star.
Suppose I am interested.
- Did you Headshots?
Is that something to drink?
Real funny, buddy!
Just go once a bartender and say,
you would have liked a few headshots with ice.
No, little one, now let's be serious.
These are pictures, man.
So professional photos.
Do you have any? - No I did not.
I ... - It does not matter
we do it like this:
I call to a colleague.
The cares drum.
Be easy back here tomorrow.
Namely, at the same time. - Cool.
Cool thing, man!
Do me a Favour
and wear something fancier.
I would say,
a white shirt.
Wait a minute. Perhaps the police chief.
See you tomorrow. Okay?
Hi, yes ...
AJT talent agency
Andy West
Unselfish you keep vigil.
Selfless. In any weather.
Good morning, guys.
Has pretty intense
rained last night, huh?
What is the?
Well ...
And because you are so nice guys,
get her from me
my irresistible,
very special,
over hot chocolate pudding.
Really?
But is nice of you. - Is really not a thing.
You guys deserve this.
May we ever a little nibble?
- It's out of the question. Only when he's finished.
Are the dolphins?
Right there in front.
What dolphins? I am fully on dolphins.
- Yes, I think that's what. - I see nothing.
Pudding.
Can I have some?
Actually, I have the
only for the guys made. - Oh shame.
Yes that is
a real men's pudding.
Men pudding?
I've never heard of.
Hey, I have a couple of yoga exercises
not clear. Will you show it to me again? - Clear.
I'm curious.
Beautifully eat, guys.
Oh yeah. Really delicious.
That is
the best pudding ever.
No shit. - Thank you.
- What is the secret truth?
How do you mean?
- Why it tastes so good?
Well, the recipe is from my mother,
and she always said,
that one easily
to cook with love.
Oh, with love.
Is indeed cute.
So then,
see you later.
I hope,
that comes back out well.
What did she mean by that? - Wives.
The often say things that make no sense.
Is really the hammer.
Is a gustatory orgasm.
Fuck it all.
Let nothing go to waste.
Saugut.
This is too good.
Revenge is sweet.
Especially with a pudding.
Set camera?
- Camera set!
Can we Use
see on the phone? - Yup. - Cool.
Only a matter of time. - Yes Yes...
Then we wait times.
Here's what in the bush?
- No. - For sure?
Out with it or I
tickle's you out. - I would not advise you.
For sure?
I give up!
Want's to tell me?
Okay.
So ...
We want to male
Roommates avenge their Spanner action.
And now is the camera
directly in their shithouse.
I installed it.
- "Iiih". How so?
"Iiih" real word. But I have
Used gloves. - Yes, good.
Okay, and now comes the best part.
Perhaps they have chocolate pudding with
tons of really nasty laxative gefuttert.
Holy shit. - That's right,
it takes no longer determined long,
until we here the results of our cute,
see little experiment.
Guys, how about
with a round of football?
Cool, right?
We can indeed ask the worm.
What's wrong with him?
- If yes evil!
Oh, man, shit.
So a lousy digestion.
You two really totally weak stomachs.
Nuclear war in the gut.
Johnny.
Johnny!
Is that disgusting.
Johnny?
Oh, fuck!
Drink this.
Beer has the opposite effect.
Shit, really bad.
Sorry, dude.
Shit!
Damn, Johnny, no!
Was that a charge, damn.
Man, is that crass!
Fuck, what's going on?
Fuck!
Shit!
Damn it!
Holy shit!
You too?
- Yes, and how.
That is so disgusting.
One more time!
Oh man!
Oh God!
Unbelievable.
I weggekackt three kilos.
Three kilos weggekackt.
The abdominal muscles feel great.
Oh, fuck!
Is this nasty.
Dude, no! Dude! No!
- Oh no. I can not get ...
No, no ... - Dude!
Damn it all!
Listen only on, dude!
Here, take the beer.
Here, my hand.
- Okay.
A satisfaction. - That comes but
something from the Internet, right?
Sure, of course. What do you think, how many
You-Tube-clicks we get for it?
Much shit?
- Then it fits yes!
The sluts we do cold.
However.
Briefing.
What you have there?
That's my secret,
small security camera.
I've found in the toilet.
And here I have the unique
Proof that we were poisoned.
Of these damned
Bitch wives.
That was in the garbage.
Our shits
comes from the pudding.
Then who so your
small hidden camera tensioner
and palmed us because
in their super delicious chocolate pudding?
Actually it was quite funny
and we survived it. - Toll!
Probably, it is already online,
if I judge this Lola properly.
If they want war,
then she gets him.
Hey, dude, so I do not think
that it has put online.
Get your easy loose.
Funny is funny.
You've got the fucking camera in their
Room hidden. Have you started.
That's not the same.
We must make it clear to them,
that they have gone too far.
Because maybe I get
Reparation sex of Maggie.
Or maybe as
Excuse me a video.
So one that I then me alone
can look at in my spare time.
I give myself even
satisfied with a photo.
I'm a likeable guy.
Jenna!
I'm sorry, honestly.
Us does it quite the same suffering.
That was mean.
- I had no idea.
Honestly not.
Otherwise I would have warned you.
Hey, this is Andy West.
Sorry that I your call
can not accept in person.
Leave me
please leave a message. Ciao.
Have ye found not funny?
No,
So I can not say.
You're doing a great noise.
- Hey, so please. We walk a bit.
Do you think you already
Nasties from?
Well, to be honest, we are ashamed
all of us for what we have done.
Even Jenna, although they
has it knew nothing.
We will prepare you
We are sorry for dinner.
An especially
delicious Thai food.
That will put you
the guys do not buy.
I also do not know if I sisters you
after this shit action still to be trusted.
Please, please, please,
Accept the apology.
Well, I suppose they,
but that only applies to me.
With Charlie and Vincent
you will still need to talk.
Sure, of course.
Good.
I think Johnny is a very honest
and pretty nice boy.
And he looks good enough to eat,
have you not noticed.
That just adds properly. - Displays Lola,
"That does not know how love feels,"
about interest
the opposite sex?
I just said,
He's a nice guy and no more.
You know what?
I ventured enough
to know that when someone says:
and no more,
which actually means the opposite.
You tolerate anyway
no contradiction.
So what.
♪ Lola loves Johnny!
Lola loves Johnny!
Stop!
He might hear you yet.
You like him, then?
- Just not. Just not!
Oh.
- Oh but. Oh but
Liar, liar,
you're an old liar.
Well,
He's a hot guy.
Well finally.
I'll tell you what we are doing now.
We show him the way.
Before dinner, you will make yourself up.
You have to make yourself really sexy.
I also have a top case.
That is it in combination with your tits
simply cut only from the stool.
But really. - All right.
Do you promise me that you behave,
while I'm away? - Of course.
Okay, see you later.
What are you already doing again?
- Nothing, why?
If only once again a secret ingredient.
For those who love boys.
What is it now?
A little finesse,
supports their masculinity.
Aha, their masculinity.
For someone who has never had sex,
you have it but sly old ears.
We Jenna promised,
that we no longer do such things.
You might.
And if.
Food is ready!
Smells so yummy.
Oh, no, Charlie.
The place is only reserved otherwise.
Is indeed something completely new.
I did not realize,
that the spaces are allocated here.
- Charlie, sit down next to me, please, okay?
Johnny.
Earth Johnny!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Tell me,
what does that mean?
An Asian, good food.
Muay Thai.
Does not
a martial art?
Is not it. - Who says we
can trust you? - Yes that's true.
Oh please, but everything is back
came out, is not it?
My dad always says, and is a doctor,
over Poop will not talk while eating.
Guys,
We're really very sorry.
Maggie was the whole day in the kitchen
and has toiled without end,
order you to cook this delicious food.
Of course they expected because that ...
... Her pure skin.
Here, this special sauce
belongs necessarily so.
What do you all have
after eating before?
So we go afterwards
definitely a party.
There is a band playing and we want to check,
whether it is good for our fundraising event.
Cool, we are the
Daredevil troupe.
Okay, well, cool.
So, we are not yet
the daredevil troupe.
You do not like the term well.
Forget it. No shit, I ...
Sorry, friends. That's a private party
and you will not get in.
Take care, friends, makes it good.
Waits
let me through times. Thank you.
Let me take care of it ...
- What. Hi!
Hi! - What's going on? - We are on
Looking for a strong man.
Because you are right with me.
How can I help you, friends?
You look so familiar.
Do we know each other?
We are friends of Maureen.
You mean maybe my brother.
Brother From Another Mother.
♪ Sweet Maureen
You know determines this song.
Could it be,
that you speak of Sweet Melissa?
There is a difference because there ...
- Listen.
I know the difference.
Are you telling me I'm stupid?
I'm doing a video.
So if you ... - I do not care.
So, Maureen has ...
- Oh, Sweet Maureen.
Of course, friends. You can now
all go in. Have fun, and friends.
You can do,
what you want.
Enjoys it.
You can stay as long as you want.
Everyone of you.
Each of you except him.
The band's really cool!
Of course we need for our party!
That you were.
Man silk, disturbed her.
- Shit wives.
Hey people,
where are you going? Oh, men.
They will surely not about
be offended, do not you think?
I do not find that funny.
Not at all.
Do you know what we just
by making had? - Tell it to me.
We did not know how we go again
should come, so we hitchhiked.
We have with our rock-hard
Tails standing by the roadside.
Of course, no one has stopped.
Only this crazy old woman.
Hi, guys!
If you want, we will take with you.
Very happy, but have you
plenty of room for the three of us?
No problem.
We sit down on top of you.
We sit down on top of you all. - Please?
That would suit you so. Are you kidding me? Are you serious when you say that.
Come on, guys,
brings you in safety!
I think I'm crazy.
Oh, Uschi. Afterwards, Uschi!
Afterwards! Driving first to the beach.
We are cut off
namely to the beach.
We thought we got rid of them.
- Guys, can you please help me?
I can in this darkness the
Not recognize Bannister properly.
Bad if you're old ...
A beautiful banister, yes.
Au, not so rough.
Oh, Lord,
get me not to you!
Watch out,
that they do not fall down, Charlie.
Thank you for helping me.
Juhu, dear boys!
- Which has a force. - You are welcome!
Goodbye!
- A nice old lady.
Yes, and how. You she has not even
grabbed by the tail. So shut the fuck up!
You're really mad at me, right?
Or we find
Use for this part?
That's not funny.
The has torn us almost the tails.
I wanted to also not be funny,
but rather practical.
All right. - But if you do not ...
You already know...
Can we perhaps it
use as a hat rack?
As a shoehorn?
We can also throw horseshoes.
Enough penis jokes.
I'm serious now.
FOURTH DAY
With you is yes
again well what's going on.
Hey guys, good morning.
Today is your lucky day.
I'll make you my famous namely,
candied smiley-face pancakes
with whipped us maple syrup.
How much appetite did you?
After your real nasty attack
last night on the most intimate area,
is surely clear,
that we eat your stuff ever again.
You have for the last time
euern had fun.
Well, more remains for us.
I do not know how it's done to you,
but after many dancing at the party,
I have a hammer moderate Kohldampf.
I suppose six. Please stacked.
Come immediately. - I can not's
suffer when food is thrown away.
So, I take a few.
- I like that about you. - On principle.
Here please.
- I'll show you how to be eaten.
We eat from the same plate.
- No, we are not.
Too late.
- It's okay.
Small, you have something
Eaten bad or ...
I'm doing so crappy.
Although is very intimate,
but you had sex in the last few days?
But I have not rumgehurt.
Well, you're too late
or you have not you protected?
You do not think that ... - I think
you should take this test, Jenna.
You know how that goes?
Have previously never made a,
if that's your question.
Is everything in the package.
Let me know if I can help you.
Thank you.
Help the ROBBE - Charity Party
weekend - brings money !
Help the ROBBE
CLICK HERE TO DONATE
Hey, this is Andy West.
Sorry that I your call
can not accept in person.
Leave me
please leave a message. Ciao.
What is it to you for a warthog
raced through the liver?
Hey! - So see you soon.
- Bye, Honey. - Bye.
Call me from Paris.
- Yes I do. - Promised? - Yes.
Okay I got it.
I wish you a good flight. Bye Bye.
Damn it. I guess I'm at
a turning point arrived, man.
You need Joe,
Be the lifeguards.
Johnny, right?
- Yes, how did you know?
I am pleased. I deal
me always with the winners.
I want to know,
who depends here.
So what's up?
I'm not sure, because I
have never thought about it.
Who pulls the well
serious consideration?
Believe me,
Such problems have very many.
You're out of here.
Is anyone ever
come to the beach
and has offered you
To become a movie star and model?
Was that a guy or a woman?
- That was a guy.
Did he touch your penis
or a different part of the body?
Oh no, in this direction it is
not gone. - If yes may be.
I have to exclude it.
Well, listen.
I think something comes
every now and then before.
And if you believe,
that what is for you,
Then Try it out for yourself.
Thank you, Joe.
No thing, man. Good luck with it.
Thank you.
- Keep me up to date.
That should not have happened.
Not really.
That was a few weeks ago
and he is a huge asshole.
At least for one thing
he had to use surely.
This is not now
the right time for such a thing.
It just developed
everything really well with Vincent.
I thought,
that could be really something,
and if I say it to him,
He will hate me for all time.
And if not you tell him?
You make it easy
your little secret.
If yes just typical.
But I pull something not.
I would never do that to him.
Want to have the baby?
- Can I get you now not answer.
I am actually much too young.
- You do not have to justify yourself.
Not really. Before anyone.
Do what you think is right.
Perhaps the bond
between Vincent and you strong enough.
No she is not.
I can not do this.
I can not do that to him the real.
I can not but ...
Shit.
You have to give time to her now.
Hey, Johnny!
Hi, Lola!
Beautiful bikini. - Thank you.
I hop into the hot tub now.
Want to come in with?
According to me.
- I do not want to compel yes.
Sorry, I'm just
not particularly good mood.
Is somehow a
pretty strange day today.
What happened?
Nothing at all. Have still no owner
what belongs. That's the problem.
Then come on in now.
Actually, you're
not my type,
but I'll simply times
make an exception with you.
That is nice of you.
I am not only
the successful college athlete.
I have more hopes
and dreams. I have a degree.
What did you study?
- Sport Sciences.
But one day, as I had
an experience that everything has changed.
That was nice
a while ago in a theater.
Since I had my doubts.
What? I thought,
I'm not your type.
I told you that I
when you make an exception.
But you did not
something tipped into the water?
I'm understandably cautious.
- Is nothing in it except me.
All right.
If a horse in a bar.
The bartender says:
"Why the long face?"
Checked?
- The Gag is 100 years old.
I think I am
really at a crossroads.
No matter which way I look,
everywhere just wasteland.
I have until a week ago
not even seen the sea.
Now I swim in it rum.
Only a few days ago
a stranger comes up to me
and offers me that he helps me,
my dream to live.
No shit,
how often does something like that before already?
Was clear that he
now no longer reports.
I could see already that it on
the world is so much more than I thought times.
Everyone has actually a lot more options.
I think I'll move here.
Very impulsive, do not you think?
- Well, if you say so.
At home keeps me
Simply nothing.
I'm as good as here.
I do not know,
What I should say.
You must indeed say anything.
What you up to?
Okay.
What was that? - Sorry, I thought
Anyway, that brings women in the mood.
Jenna?
Hey, Jenna.
I have you
been looking for everywhere.
Now you've found me yes.
Unfortunately, you did.
So please,
what do you mean "unfortunately"?
Hey. - Have the whole day
I tried, you go out of the way.
Here we have to talk.
This is all much too fast to me.
Well, I really want to ...
I can not...
I do not think this is going to work.
Okay.
We were maybe
really fast.
We do now
just a little slower.
That's fine for me.
Honest. - No, Vincent, no.
You did not understand me.
This is not a good solution. I ...
I think I got us
since purely ridden almost in what.
I want to in any case.
I ... I can not tell you,
if I'm still here tomorrow.
I probably go
home. - What?
You ...
You can now not go easy.
If you do that,
it was really with us.
And all the others
must then also home.
Do you really want do you mean?
You can not be serious.
That was until now
really nice with us two, right?
I would still do anything for you.
You can not just now but
disappear from my life.
Farewell, Vincent.
I hope,
that we are never again.
When I least
would know your reasons.
Well, then I'm going.
- No, I'll go.
I want you to stay.
Your cute,
nocturnal visitor is back.
Was clear. That's cute.
Let yourself his efforts
actually completely cold?
What should I do? Should I bring a
blow, just because he holds a candle stupid?
I think it's beautiful
quite romantic.
If you do find that great,
then you could it perhaps
on behalf of us both suck a.
But I should do it,
then it will last a lifetime
on this action to masturbate.
I would for all time
burning in his brain
as the little bitch that he
his brain has blown out of the tail.
Get ready would him.
Sorry, Charlie.
No, this is not.
Hi.
I'll be right back.
Or not.
Have fun.
- I have that safe.
Hi! - Hey!
- That's a surprise.
Shall we two a bit
to take a walk on the beach? - Good idea.
Well then go.
Hey, you take a chair.
Do you want a beer?
- Yes, I could well tolerated.
So what's up?
I can bury my future plans.
What are your plans?
Jenna wants again
drive back home. Tomorrow.
You know maybe, why?
No, I have not heard anything.
I can anhauen Lola,
which is to talk to her.
What was that?
Jenna?
You do not want to
come to me down?
You know exactly
that the situation does not change,
just because you're in your
Schneckenhaus verkriechst.
So now come down,
otherwise I get high.
You're really very friendly and I know
appreciate the fact that you look after me.
Even in places that I thought,
that no one will find me there,
and the already
the second time this week.
But just because you found me,
that does not mean that you know me.
Or?
You do not know me, no.
And you also do not know anything
about me and my life, Maureen.
Okay, that's enough now.
I'll be high.
But I know you well enough,
to know that you like children.
And that you never do anything
would that could endanger a child.
I just want to
think in peace.
The thing about Vincent
I have finished.
And I know,
that you will not hear the,
but I will here certainly
can get through a day longer.
So. - I'll leave the Beach House.
I can not do this.
So what happens.
And I beseech thee,
Meet any hasty decisions.
Sleep over it again.
Who comes here?
Can I? - Yeah, right.
On the love.
- Hey, fuck you.
Say, only is Vincent shit plan
and now you. What happened?
Hey, all right?
- Can I have one more thing, brother?
Yes, if you still want one.
Respect.
Krass, right?
Wow! - That was pretty bad.
So what I have never seen man.
Dude, why are you doing this?
- What?
What?
So much booze.
I hate beer.
I hate how it smells.
I hate what it tastes like.
I hate it really totally.
That's why I can only drink so's.
If a trick I
learned in the fraternity.
One trick
you've learned since.
Frankly, you do not look
as a connecting brother.
Yes, I am indeed none.
- I do not fit to those who say that.
Although I all their
Shit took part.
I was shot the same.
The only thing that I as
could pull out, is that stupid trick.
And an idea,
what I am and what is not.
Then we change that.
New meeting.
The meeting of the Brotherhood
is hereby opened.
I nominate Charlie
as our President.
Those in favor, raise your hand.
- Here! - Here!
The result is unanimous.
Charlie is the new president of the Brotherhood.
Response!
Only a beer,
then the speech.
I want at
the Brotherhood to thank.
For recognition
my leadership potential.
I would add that this is the largest
Is honor that I have ever approached.
On the Brotherhood.
- In the Brotherhood!
Do you think he was injured?
- No, the grass is still soft.
So, he likes me
actually best.
Well.
You've expressed, but nice.
Oh man,
is the ass hard.
You know what?
You're a pretty decent guy.
The Brotherhood leaves no
her brothers alone. - That's how it looks.
Time for the box, Charlie.
Today is a great day.
Much larger is the evening.
Party!
Subsequently, immediately after Yoga,
we go over
and help others at
the preparations for the party.
I'll call the vet also
and wonder how it's Stanley.
Honestly,
there's even more trouble, folks.
Jenna has with Vincent
Final done.
Oh, here they have yet
so well fitted together.
Yes, we have last night
on the beach talking about it.
She wants to go. If she does that,
then you have all home.
We can not let that happen.
Thus it ruins everything. Even for itself.
I can not stop them.
The only you can and you should
not leave you much time.
I know you're doing anyway,
what you want, but we can talk?
Exactly, I have
made my decision,
and I do not,
that her mind yet what you can change.
For so what friends are for.
Vincent and you all had such a strong bond.
He deserves to know the truth.
I do not know.
I really love him very much, but I can ...
Well, I can not do that to him.
I do not want that.
That would not be fair.
In this week
but is totally much happened, right?
So many great things.
And we do not want to lose
and you still do not.
Maybe you commit
the biggest mistake of your life.
Since I have the matter
already committed.
And I find it hard enough,
having to live with the consequences.
There are usually
several solutions.
Sit down.
I'll make you some tea.
One may a decision,
which affects the rest of life,
not break above the knee.
For everything that we decide, the following applies:
This results in
perhaps unplanned developments.
Everything you've done
and everything you will do even,
based on these decisions.
Everything has to do with everything.
The right decision is important.
It's okay,
I have understood.
Take your time, you need to especially
choose wisely.
What do you think?
How will he react to the truth?
Hey, baby,
I'm pregnant, but not from you.
Is not bad, right? Come on, we're getting married.
How is it looking? I bring not.
It is a bond
received with you.
Did he not also a right to
to decide how it's going on?
Tomorrow.
If I disturb,
then tells me.
No, you do not disturb.
Pretty underpants.
- Thank you, I also find.
So, I'll be honest.
I was here all the time forward.
Already spying again?
- No, that was not really my plan.
I'm just awake, because I
had brutally piss. - Hey, hey!
ZVI!
- This means that again?
Too much information.
Again. - And further?
I've heard everything,
I believe.
Well, sit down.
Then you are now
also one of the girls.
We commit yourself
to silence.
Silence is okay, but I have to
not be a girl, right? - But.
This is a sisterhood.
Swear.
Then I am a brother
and a sister?
Promise easy
you's keep to yourself.
Well, I promise.
Okay, and now go pee.
Can I keep you company?
Sure, of course.
So, what brings you over here?
I come up here forever,
if I can.
The sea has something
incredibly magical about it.
If you share your feelings with him,
it can heal you.
I do not know,
what to feel.
I'm proud of you.
I'm just trying it,
doing the right thing.
You did not have to say,
that you were in the hallway.
So I thought
briefly about it, but ...
You remember me
of someone I once knew.
To whom?
My friend.
- Where is he?
He was a professional soldier, officer.
He's not out
Afghanistan repatriated.
I'm sorry.
He has worked for,
what he firmly believed.
I agree
a little in you.
You're a good guy, Charlie.
You did not deserve it,
Maggie treated you, not really.
It is strange,
because I wanted to.
But now it does me only suffering.
Well, I think,
I was probably not the right person for them.
Maybe you're the right person.
Just as you said,
not for them.
Want to have the, what you
thought the hot tub on the first night?
What?
That to me almost explode the eggs?
Sorry.
You're a great woman and you
not know how he will react.
Do not you think,
you should give him a chance.
The falls really hard for me.
Also because my parents
have never married.
So I was a love child. It's has
Love never existed when I was a little kid.
And I have my, since
I was five, never seen again.
So you can say,
I'm sensitive. - Wow.
I've had no idea.
I do not run so well with
a shield around at the stands on it's.
Who creates it, between the lines
read, reads it, then:
Gorgeous, intelligent dream woman
with a painful childhood.
Sacrifices for their interests to
unplanned children of others raise.
Hopes for the man of her dreams,
of her simply as traveling towards.
And when he does that
and everything is not perfect,
then she throws out everything
and get scared like a chicken during a thunderstorm.
Not bad. - Thank you. - Were a cool
Candidate for "Got to Dance". - Really?
What would you do then?
Never done Miss "I've got it
and also do not know if I want "?
Drag him to the altar
and myself believe it would be his?
Yes, quite possible.
Sounds like me.
Just as I know my Jenna,
showered your child with love,
which she herself has not experienced.
Together with a man,
she loves above all else
and with whom she wants to build a family.
Do you really not want you to him
at least should give a chance
also to make a decision?
Exactly would you
namely also expected.
Thank you for you today all
look let. We are "Nylon Pink".
Thank you!
I want to now the organizers
Lola and Maggie ask on our stage.
Hi guys.
Hey!
Hi together, all right?
Welcome to the
"Help the Robbe" -Benefizparty.
Thank wholeheartedly
for your numerous appearance!
Also we would like to you all
well known Maureen welcome!
Of course we also thank Big Guy
and the whole crew for the party!
You are great!
Yes, let us also walk
our knights in shining armor,
the really very great people,
welcome: Dr. Spencer.
Hi, Doctor!
Thanks, guys, unfortunately, could
Stanley does not provide for the Party,
but he told me that here as a sign
his appreciation given.
Thank you from him!
All right, dear friends,
enjoying the evening and although with "Nylon Pink"!
Now it's celebrating!
Johnny,
where have you been, tell me?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
- You should only need to call back.
That's what I want, yes, but my
Smartphone has fallen into the toilet.
I've lost all my contacts.
I am fully screwed.
A nightmare, man.
I'm so glad to have found you here.
Charlie, that's Andy West.
Andy West, Charlie.
Hi, Charlie, Andy West Coast.
Glad man.
Okay.
Johnny, no shit, man.
I told you that you are a white
Shirt attract shalt. You know what? - Yes.
I have attached a photographer for you.
He has a few pictures of you shot.
Great photos.
I told you clearly made an audition.
Cool, thanks.
But how can I reach you now?
No, I will contact with you.
All right, kid?
And because you me
this great job have taught,
you can not refuse me,
to dance with you.
Sorry, Big Guy.
The Lady dances with me.
For each song,
all night.
Is not that right, Maureen?
Is that Maureen?
I would really also
love dancing with you, but
tonight I'm with Charlie here.
And when saying this,
then it will probably be so.
I ...
...congratulations,
my little friend.
Give me Five.
See you.
Beautiful evening.
All right, Johnny.
Now Enjoy this evening.
I need you tomorrow afternoon.
- Tomorrow in the afternoon. I'll be there.
Great. No shit.
I do not want you any longer zulabern.
I wish you a cool party.
- Okay, man. - See you tomorrow.
I am happy man.
- Okay, man. - Keep a stiff upper lip.
Hey people.
Hey people?
We have made us all right to worry.
Real, you have that?
Sorry, we are running late,
we had there still to clarify some things.
But cool party.
This is now the right time
for a small announcement.
We are engaged.
I'm looking really totally for you.
So, we ...
... Do not have
a lot to talk about.
We can not all our
Lifetime discuss things.
Do you find genuine,
which must be now?
No? No.
You're wasting too much time,
other people nervous with this thing.
With falling since but something better.
Without your stupid filming.
Good or?
Okay, okay.
Can I?
Come on, pull it out.
- At it.
Do you need a ladder?
My lipstick looks good on you.
Toll how you laugh.
Except that you
beautiful and pretty are,
you're also honest.
Thank you.
- And caring and unselfish.
This is hard to find.
You mean to me really a lot.
That is fine.
How was it for you?
That was perfect,
I would say. - Yes?
Yes.
- Fancy a second round?
Now?
Okay, in five minutes.
I come back to it. - Okay.
Did not you also feel
that we are being watched?
So I do about me
no thoughts. Ignore the simple.
Seventh day
Have you seen Vincent?
Oh no.
Why what's going on?
Nothing at all. I'm just...
I'm just woke up and he was gone.
I do not know where he is.
There is still no one lost.
The dive again soon.
How's me this morning?
So what of damned cool!
Does anyone what to feed?
I die of hunger.
Now I want biscuits or burgers,
Pizza, donuts, pancakes ...
A sandwich would be okay.
Oh, save me. Thank you.
Your noise you can
sleep on the plane. Coffee?
Good morning people.
Do you know where Vincent is?
Honestly, yes.
You might like to get out.
Because what awaits you.
Not too sparingly.
Sorry, but now I am a man.
END
Are you laughing because I rumgefurzt?
Come at once
a stranger to me and
offers me
To be a movie star or television star.
So what experienced before?
- Sometimes it.
Was that a guy or a woman?
- It was ... It was a guy.
Has he looked like?
So you're at a turning point.
I see immediately.
Is that funny?
Yeah, so like I said,
I'm at a turning point.
Me too.
Did he angegrabscht your willy?
Okay.
Many girls I made
television know are from Malibu.
I can hardly wait.
I'm doing a little free memory, oh yes.
Yes, Mom?
No no. No, I do Photos
of birds and squirrels.
No, not from the birds.
From birds. Yes.
Mom, NE!
Why did Dad say,
that I am fully behämmert?
He said, I am behämmert,
because I'm out crawled out of you!
I won a trip to Malibu
and am now times for a week away!
May I then
but come back,
I do not suppose that I
a meet, with which I draw together.
Oh please,
I know I'm behämmert.
No, not you.
But, you're behämmert.
Damn it, I hate you.
Hey, no! I had not the interim
Available, I would have a job, right?
You had me may not blow the whistle.
What is that?
No, you're behämmert!
Mom, that would have really cool for
I should be and what are you doing?
You've ruined everything, because you think,
that I would have messed up your life, man.
However, I would!
Anyway, I would
marry a whore.
I would bring them here.
And Grandma, I would imagine they also.
The still behämmerter.
I'm sorry,
I should not have said.
Because of you I always say things,
I do not mean.
I mean you have so,
but you understand it anyway wrong.
You know what? I turn now easy
a cool Suicide Video, Mom.
Hi guys!
I know you're the
Now do not believe.
But yet, I'll leave you.
Goodbye forever.
Actually, I wanted
yes only a week away,
but if I find something cooler,
then you've done it.
Even if it is hell.
Exactly!
I live in hell anyway, Mom!
And with you!