Captioning made possible by
warner bros.
[panting]
[zip]
Run's over.
[siren]
[sighs]
[beep]
Researchers say --
Writer's mind.
...Suspect arsonists.
The best music is on.
[snippets of speech
interspersed with static]
Dinner!
Reality...
Your subscription
has been canceled.
Beauty.
Life--
Your subscription
has been canceled.
[beep]
What's up?
We got a new rookie.
Mike cherry,
in the yellow hat.
Boss: Gabriel, johnny,
get over here.
How's bobby doin'?
Uh, not so good, johnny.
He's still in the hospital.
They haven't figured out
what's wrong with him?
They don't know, man.
Whatever it is
hit him hard and fast.
Don't worry.
He's a tough kid.
They can work miracles
these days.
Yeah, miracles
are expensive.
Ooh.
[wind whistling]
Hey, don't worry.
If you fall...
Your widow gets
a free christmas basket.
All you got to
remember, kid,
Is never step back
and admire your work.
Whoa!
[laughter]
Would you quit
screwing around?
You want to be funny,
chief? Laugh at this.
There's a $500
safety infraction
Out of your check.
Now you wanna earn
your wage or not?
Take a cue from this guy.
3 years on the job,
not one sick day.
I never get sick.
I don't care if you do,
gabriel.
I just care
that you show up.
There's something wrong
with the crane.
You're gonna be the lucky
guys who get to go fix it.
As for you...
Wind shear's come loose.
Get out there
and bolt it down.
The average guy
on this site
Can do that
in 10 minutes.
I'm givin' you
20 minutes
'cause I'm such
a nice guy.
I'll do it.
He's not ready.
[wind whistling]
Gabriel,
you know the rules.
You work the minute
you get here,
Or you don't work.
Now get moving,
Or you'll find yourself
on the unemployment line.
Oh, that's right.
Both: There is no
unemployment line.
He has no safety
at all.
He's gonna go.
Tie me off.
Help me!
Hang on, mike!
Aah!
Hold on to me.
Uhh!
I gotcha.
Hold on to me.
I'm gonna swing you
towards the building.
Uhh!
Aah!
Son of a bitch.
Johnny!
You all right?!
No!
Can you swing
onto that cab?
I need to be
a little--
Get out of there,
johnny!
Hurry up!
It's gonna go!
I can't.
Are you ok?
Go get johnny.
Oh, man.
You almost killed him.
Get out there
and bolt it down.
You're fired.
You got a problem
with that?
Take it up
with the union.
Oh, I forgot.
There is no union.
Tell me again
that I'm fired.
One last thing.
[coughing]
Hey, dad.
Hey, bobby.
How you feelin'?
Like a freak.
So when did
all this happen?
This afternoon,
I guess.
I was asleep.
Mm-hmm.
What happened to you?
Well, I figured if I'm
comin' to the hospital,
I might as well
look the part.
Huh?
You all right, dad?
We're gonna get you
out of here
As soon
as possible, bobby.
Promise.
No, I mean,
will you be all right...
[whispering]
if something should happen?
Hey.
Check this out.
Ohh.
Cray ii gamer goggles.
With 256 gigabytes of
gaming power because...
Reality has
no reset button.
[sighs]
What?
They're too expensive.
Gimme a break, will ya?
I worked
a little overtime.
Oh, man,
this is primo.
Evening, mr. Gabriel.
Hey, doc.
Whoa.
Hehhh.
Could I see you
for a moment?
Sure.
I'll be right back, ok?
Bye, dad.
Whoa.
What, uh,
was that readout?
According to
our diagnostic equipment,
Your son has
a white blood cell count
5 times above what
is humanly possible.
It's purely an equipment
malfunction.
What are you talking about,
the equipment's malfunctioning?
Well, it's not relevant.
We know what's wrong
with bobby.
Your son has contracted
ralph virus.
Ralph virus?
How's that possible?
Lifecorps wiped out
ralph virus.
We certainly thought
it was controlled.
There hasn't been
a new case reported
In over 2 years,
But your son shows all
the symptoms of the virus
Just before
it goes critical.
And the blood work,
Which I performed
personally, confirms it.
Then cure him.
The vaccine is
prohibitively expensive.
I give you guys everything
I make. Everything.
I don't set the prices
here, mr. Gabriel.
I only know that
the billing department
Informs me that
your son's account
Is seriously past due,
And unless you settle
that account,
I won't be allowed to
administer the vaccine.
Your son's not got long
Before his body
begins to shut down.
After that, the vaccine
will have no effect.
How long have I got?
Maybe 12 hours.
A day at the most.
Man: Nurse!
[ding]
[calm music playing]
Man's voice: Lifecorps.
Hi.
[clears throat]
I wouldn't
if I were you.
You're not me.
Ha. Suit yourself.
[ding]
Everyone wants
to cash in...
Nobody wants to pay.
See you 'round.
Mr. Gabriel.
Mr. Gabriel,
I'm honored.
You've got one hour
to process me.
That's very amusing.
This exam, I'm afraid,
takes some time.
It's very involved--
One hour, or I walk.
Well, then, we best get
started, hadn't we?
Have you run these tests
a second time?
Uh, not yet.
Lung scan complete.
Neurology report in.
Bergen: Prepare the subject
for final brain scan.
Nurse: 180. Steady.
Huh.
Extraordinary numbers,
doctor.
Would you look at that?
Helen: Mid-central's data
confirms our findings.
He's really quite
a specimen.
Vital organs, eyes, teeth
are of exceptionally high grade.
Blood, good to superior.
High counts on bone marrow
and pituitary.
The data shows he lost
his wife 6 years ago,
But there is no history
of depression,
And there's no inclination
towards suicide.
That doesn't mean
it isn't there.
One of the, uh, things
We haven't learned
to read, yet, is minds.
Ow!
There we go.
What was that?
Oh, it's vitamin
supplements.
C boosters, b-complex,
flu inhibitors, the works.
Even if you don't end up
signing with us,
You won't get a bug
all winter.
Don't ever stick me
with a needle again
And not tell me first.
Shh shh.
Relax, mr. Gabriel.
I understand.
Now, if you'll make your way out
to our waiting room,
One of our senior administrators
will complete formalities.
Mr. Gabriel,
dr. Helen steele.
I'm corporate officer
here at lifecorps.
You must be very
pleased to know
That you passed
our qualifying exam.
In fact, our staff
was very impressed.
Where's my money?
Sit down, please.
Mr. Gabriel, before we
go any further,
Lifecorps
wants to be certain
That you understand
the gravity
Of the commitment
you're about to make.
Oh, I understand.
You're buying my body,
you're giving me a year,
Then you carve me up
for parts.
That's about right,
isn't it?
Then we can safely say
that you grasp
The essential nature
of the contract.
Yeah. Look, I don't have
a lot of time to chat.
These are the terms
Of your contract
with lifecorps.
$300,000 for one year
To dispose of
as you wish.
For exactly one year.
On September 10th at,
uh, 20 minutes to 8:00,
When the contract
expires,
You will be picked up
By one of our
corporate limousines.
Where's my money?
There's one more thing.
Lifecorps requires
that you be fitted
With one of our
resource bracelets.
[beep]
In case I run.
You made a commitment,
mr. Gabriel.
We expect you
to honor it.
[thundering]
Hey!
[thunder]
Where is my son?
The virus came on faster
than we anticipated.
I'm sorry, mr. Gabriel.
Where is he?
Your son's body
had to be destroyed.
Where's my son?!
I want to see him!
Nobody can, mr. Gabriel.
He's gone.
The vaccine.
What--what about
the vaccine?
They wouldn't
release it.
I tried,
but without payment--
I begged them.
Them?
Who them?
[thunder]
Excuse me.
Excuse me,
mr. Gabriel,
You're not permitted
past reception.
We didn't expect
to see you here so soon.
You can have
your money back.
I don't understand.
I'm givin' it back.
I don't want it.
I'm anton stofeles,
Chief medical officer
of lifecorps.
Why don't we talk in
my office, mr. Gabriel?
I can talk just as fine
right here.
It's only natural
for a new member
To experience a period
of adjustment.
I understand.
You don't understand
anything!
You and your people, you had
the power in your hands,
And you just stood by
and watched my son die.
What's he
talking about?
It was one of
dr. Elliot's cases.
I was just informed.
Did he also inform you that
my son could've been saved?
You think this justifies it?
You think this is worth
more than my son?
Well, it's not!
[people chattering
excitedly]
Your money stinks.
Uh, mr. Gabriel.
Anton: We do still
have a contract.
The hell you do.
You just took my son.
You can't take me.
We'll have to get an early
retrieval order on him.
Was he trading his life
for his son's life?
There are no exceptions,
helen.
You heard what he said.
A public statement
to violate his contract.
Man's a flight risk.
We'll go
to judge hickey.
Helen...
Look at what he's done.
The man's dangerous.
As you can see,
your honor,
Lifecorps client
james gabriel
Has indicated willful intention
to violate his contract.
I can read,
mr. Strathmore.
Your honor, the nature
of my client's business
Is such that any court decision
establishing grounds
For rescinding
a lifecorps contract--
Would hurt
their bottom line.
Would do violence
to fundamental principles
Of contract law.
In a case like this,
counselor,
A company
might have grounds
For discretion
based on conscience.
Lifecorps business is
human body parts, your honor.
I don't believe they deal
in conscience...Yet.
Well, when they do,
Perhaps you can be
the first in line.
Well, I'll take it
under advisement.
As far as discretion,
Lifecorps takes great care
When choosing those
who provide its product...
And those who might need
to receive it.
What lifecorps is asking
of this court
Is power over
life and death.
Life and death are secondary,
your honor.
We merely want
What james gabriel's
contracted to give us.
Johnny: I've never seen
a lock like that.
What the hell's it made of?
Aw, forget it, johnny.
It won't come off.
Can't see you wearin' that
for a year.
Year's a long time, man.
He was all I had, man.
He was a good kid.
Bobby.
Made a man out of me.
Had to be there for him.
Holdin' a job. Sheesh.
Pack his lunch.
Take him to school.
Gimme another hit
of that, would you?
You know,
when his mom died,
Everybody thought
I was nuts,
Not letting him
get adopted.
Who was I
to raise a kid?
A guy like me always
in some kind of trouble.
You did all right.
You were always
a standup guy.
You never turned your back
on no one.
I turned my back
on bobby.
I was a day late
and 300 grand short.
[knock on door]
Ruhhh.
Go away.
[knock on door]
[johnny sighs]
I said go away!
[knock on door]
Fool must be
hard of hearing.
Now, look...
Hi.
Aah!
[club music playing]
Got a cd coming out.
Uh, coffee, please.
You bet.
[beeping]
Man: No, you know,
I usually come here.
I like the crowd,
I like the ambiance.
Mind if I sit here?
It's a little cold
out there.
A little cold
in here, too.
Is that all
you're drinking?
What is it exactly
that you want?
You.
Give me a break, lady.
Thank you.
Yeah, well,
that is just so rude.
Gabriel!
[coughing]
Plasteel bullets.
High impact,
no penetration.
I bring you back dead,
Lifecorps will put
a contract out on me.
You're coming with me.
[coughs]
Maybe he'd rather
come with us.
[sighs]
That's a nice job,
alex.
My job, kilroy.
Oh, I'm truly sorry.
No, you're not.
You're right.
I'm not sorry!
In fact, I don't even
like you, see?
You take a lot of
business from me.
That's because you're
a lousy bounty hunter.
No, no, no, no, no.
A lousy bounty hunter
is a dead bounty hunter.
I'm simply patient.
No, you're just simple.
But maybe this
will register.
You can't have him.
Good-bye, alex.
Think about
who she is.
Think about who I am.
Now, think about
what happens
When I pull
this trigger.
That's a lot
to think about.
Uhh!
Damn it!
Son of a bitch!
What the hell's
going on here?
These guys are bounty
hunters, same as me.
Those guys in uniform
you got away from,
They're lifecorps
trackers.
What happened
to my year?
Well, that oughta
be obvious by now.
Lifecorps put out
an early retrieval on you.
Early retrieval?
That's the word
from lifecorps.
No live ammo.
No track darts.
Nothing in
the bloodstream.
They want you clean,
and they want you yesterday,
And I can't
figure out why.
Come on. We gotta
get you out of here.
Are you coming?
Or would you rather
wait around here
Until those 2 sleeping
beauties wake up?
[moaning]
Hold still, and don't ask me
why I'm doing this, runner.
My name isn't runner.
That doesn't change the fact
that that's what you are.
Come on, we got to
get out of here.
Don't you get it?
You're the prize.
You won't last
10 minutes out here.
You'll be safe here.
No one comes through that door
without an invitation.
Lights.
Are you a buddhist?
I used to be.
What happened?
This happened.
Any more questions?
Yeah. Why are you
helping me?
I'm obliged to protect you
'cause you saved my life.
You're a buddhist.
What's so funny?
All this.
I mean, my bounty hunter
Turns out to be
my bodyguard.
It's a little confusing.
Well, does the door
confuse you?
'cause you can walk
right back out it.
I don't keep
extra blankets.
That ought to
keep you warm.
Don't ask.
I didn't.
You can sleep over there.
I don't usually have men
sleep on my couch.
Where do they sleep?
Look, you want
the couch or not?
I don't mean to complain,
but as a rule,
I don't get blown through
too many windows.
So, tell me, aah,
is it bleedin' back there?
Unh.
Record.
Patient: Robert gabriel.
Identification number:
143-768-299.
Age: 7. Approximate time
of death: 14:45.
Cause of death...
Ralph virus.
Note to file.
Diagnostic software
indicated...
Patient had a high
white blood cell count.
Condition inconsistent
with viral infection.
Filing, get me
systems management.
Mike: Systems.
Mike.
Yeah.
The mdi
diagnostic computer
On ward 9's
malfunctioning.
Did you do
some kind of a check--
I can't figure it out.
Just do a work-up
And let me know as soon
as possible. Thank you.
[buzzing]
[beep]
Burke...
You got gabriel?
Not exactly.
What does that mean?
What the hell's
going on out there?
It means--
You lost gabriel.
I think he's
getting some help.
Who?
I have an idea.
Well, get the hell on it.
Bring in some trackers.
I don't tell you
how to chop 'em up.
You don't tell me
how to bag 'em. Yes?
Ow.
Hold still.
So why'd you sign
the lifecorps contract?
You don't seem the type.
I always wondered what
$300,000 looked like.
And it looks real good,
When you drop it
3 stories.
Really? Is that every
ironworker's dream?
Aah!
My kid was dyin', I couldn't
pay the hospital bills,
So I signed my life away.
Wanna hear more? It goes
downhill from there.
Yeah.
[sprays]
My son died.
And what about you?
You don't look like
the bounty hunter type.
I used to teach
martial arts.
It was spiritual.
It gave me purpose,
but it didn't feed me.
Then this guy I knew
said I had the skills
To make a bounty hunter.
Hard times make you
do hard things.
So, do you have
a picture of him?
Yeah.
Have you said
a prayer for him?
No, I guess I haven't.
Burke:
Proceed with caution.
Remember,
we want him breathing.
Understood?
Man: Understood.
[beeping]
Gabriel!
Get him!
Aah!
I've killed him.
I've killed one
of burke's men.
Gabriel:
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear me?
I killed one
of burke's men.
I'm finished!
Uh, heh heh.
Let this be a little
lesson in leadership.
A simple demonstration,
cause and effect.
Who did this?
It's the girl.
In that apartment.
Ohh, alex.
Alex, alex, alex.
You stepped over the line.
Tell me about burke.
Why?
You mentioned burke.
Tell me about burke.
He's a contractor
for lifecorps.
Those were his men.
He's the guy who killed johnny.
He didn't give him a chance.
Then you know what
we're up against.
Do you know him?
Hey, you do know him,
don't you?
They honed in on you
like radar.
What are you doin'?
I'm looking
for something.
What?
Uh, there's
something here.
The vitamin shot.
Great.
You've been implanted.
They're headed down
west 57th.
And you had better
deliver this time,
For your own sake.
They've gone public.
Hide your face.
You know someone in there
who can pop that implant?
If he's on duty.
He's here. Come on.
Burke: I'm sure I don't have
to remind you gentlemen--
Implants are not
like bracelets.
Scanners can tell you how
far you are from the target,
But they cannot indicate
what floor he is on.
Therefore, you will have
to think 3-dimensionally.
Pair off,
sweep the building,
And remember,
do not damage him...
Or her.
[footsteps]
What are you doing here?
This is illegal, mr. Gabriel.
You must know that.
That's the least
of our worries, doc.
Well, it's not
the least of mine.
[beeping]
It's an alpha transmitter
Inserted between the second
and third vertebrae.
Try to remove it yourself,
you sever the spinal cord.
I think we all want to get as
far away from this as possible.
What is so important
about you?
You took a risk, doc.
I appreciate that.
I wish I could've taken
a greater risk with your son.
Yeah.
Well, well, well.
One never knows
what one will find
When one is making
his rounds,
Does one, doctor?
Security. Here. Now.
Vitamin supplement.
You won't have a bug
all winter.
[coughing]
[panting]
You get this thing
out of me.
Get this thing
out of me!
[beeping]
You don't understand.
I'm a doctor. Tell them!
Look, let me talk to
your superior. Hold on.
Oh, god. Oh, jeez.
Gentlemen,
this is a mistake.
Aah!
Congratulations,
gentlemen.
Meet dr. Bergen.
He works for us.
At least he...
Used to work for us.
We've gotta get you
out of here.
What about you?
Look, I took a big chance
going after you.
I needed one big score
to get out of the business,
But I crossed
to the other side,
And burke's not gonna
let me cross back.
It's over for me.
Where are we going?
The price of freedom
just got higher.
Wait a minute.
That's your apartment.
This is nuts.
Look, all the money I have
is stashed in there.
So I either go in there
and get it,
Or I take you
to lifecorps
And hand you in
like a lotto ticket.
I'll give you 5 minutes.
You've done well
for yourself, alex.
You never were a very
good housekeeper.
Hmm.
Come on.
Where is he?
Why would you throw
everything away
For some runner?
Do you sleep with him?
You know,
That was careless,
killing that tracker.
[chiming]
Now I have to
bring you both in.
Planning on going
on a trip?
I mean...[scoffs]
Wherever you go,
You know I'll find you.
You already have.
Ah, mr. Gabriel,
there you are.
Turn around, burke.
That's my jacket.
I thought
it smelled bad.
So, uh, what's this about,
gabriel, hmm?
Your freedom?
Or is this about alex?
Is it about
your pathetic friend
Who was harboring
a known felon?
No.
Hmm. Well, what do you
expect me to do?
You want me to beg?
Get on your knees.
When pigs fly.
On your knees.
Go on.
Pull the trigger.
Do it.
This one's a big
disappointment, alex.
He can't do it.
I know guys just like this.
You don't know anything
about me.
James aaron gabriel.
Guy who can't hold a job
more than a month.
Court-martialed
out of the army
For assaulting
an officer.
Did 7 years hard labor
at leavenworth.
Paroled early for helping
a guard during a prison riot.
Stats: Dead wife,
dead kid, dead friend.
Current status...
Runner.
Miss anything?
Oh, yeah.
I've got the gun.
You want to blow
my head off, right?
I'm just gonna sit here
and make it easy on you.
I'm gonna count
to a hundred,
And when I get there,
I'm gonna blow your head off.
1...
2...
Gabriel, come on.
3...
In about 95 seconds.
Trackers.
5...6...
7...8...9...
It's just a jacket.
Was a jacket.
96...
97...98...
We just got
a report.
99...
Let me teach you
A little something
About etiquette.
Ohh!
Never interrupt me.
[sighs] ok.
I know a guy
who owes me a favor.
Come on.
[baby crying]
Shh shh shh.
Yes?
I'm sorry. It's
the wrong apartment.
It's ok, alma,
let him in.
Hey, mike.
Hey. You got famous.
Hi, I'm james.
This is a friend
of mine.
Hi.
Anton.
I have been talking
to the board.
The board.
Mm-hmm.
Without my consent.
Oh, I thought
you'd be relieved.
They want you to call off
this retrieval.
I mean, the public will
go mad when it finds out--
The public
wants a good show.
Do you think they're rooting
for james gabriel?
When he's captured,
he'll be yesterday's news.
Anton, a man risks his life
for his son's.
Now, we can't take that kind
of p.R. Damage.
I mean,
have you forgotten?
We are facing pending suicide
legislation in the senate.
Most of those old fools
are already on our books
Waiting for product.
They'll pass it.
I can't believe it.
Oh, god.
Helen, helen.
What?
You are the most brilliant
research scientist I have--
Have ever had.
I admire
your compassion.
And I tell you
that if I had known
About james gabriel's
son sooner,
I would have released
the vaccine,
But I can't change
what's happened.
If I allow gabriel
his freedom,
Scores, perhaps hundreds
of potential runners,
Men and women who are
confirmed as suicides,
Will petition
for theirs.
And then thousands
of people
Who are in need of
their organs will die.
Do you want that
on your conscience?
But, anton...
Anton...
You've been directed
to stop this.
I already have.
You have?
I've recalled burke,
And most of the trackers
are on their way in.
You're giving up on him?
Not at all.
[sighs]
Remember the good old days
when people had heat?
Heat costs money.
[laughs]
Coming from the guy that
gave away 300 grand.
Seemed like a good idea
at the time.
Got any other
good ideas?
What do you think?
I wasn't thinking.
Ahh...
This has to wait.
We're leaving tomorrow.
You're home free.
Relax.
Not yet.
[sighs] not yet.
Hey, gabriel, you used
to work up there
On the high steel beams,
didn't you?
Yeah.
Ever afraid to fall?
No, I'm not afraid
of falling.
It's the landing
that scares me.
[helicopter]
[sirens]
Gabriel,
where's your picture?
Maybe they've given up.
They never give up.
Wow.
What?
Nothing.
Are you sure?
No. It's just that...
I--I must be
seeing things.
Maybe it's lack of sleep
or the memories,
But I look up there
and sometimes I--
That's bobby.
What are you seeing?
My son.
Bobby's alive.
Don't you get it?
It's a setup!
You're doing exactly
what lifecorps wants.
That was my son,
And if he's alive,
I'm gonna find him.
Don't you want
to think about it?
Nothing
to think about.
We have to
have a plan.
No, we don't.
We don't?
'cause you're not
going with me.
Excuse me,
this says I am.
You won't get past
reception without it.
We'll need
to get a lift.
Is it fixed?
There was nothing
wrong with it.
Then why was it
spewing out
Such ridiculously
high figures?
Must have been
a glitch.
Glitch?
No. I spent
hours on it.
Well, it's fine now.
I did the diagnostic,
Ran a comparative test--
it's 100%.
[monitor beeping]
If you think
this is over...
Think again.
[shouting]
Elliot: Come in.
Dr. Steele wishes
to see you.
At head office?
It takes two of you
to deliver this message?
We're here to
accompany you, sir.
Give me 2 minutes.
I have some papers
that she'll need.
The lifecorps building's
a fortress, gabriel.
I know. It's designed
to make sure
No client makes a last-minute
run for the door.
You're never gonna
get out of there.
Maybe not,
but I'll get in.
Advise your men--
this is a target runner.
They're not to use
hot loads.
We have a satellite trace
on the vehicle.
He's on his way, captain.
All right. Put 4 men
on the mezzanine
With sub-net guns
and secure the perimeter.
This is his only way in.
[tires squealing]
These guys are
a walking arsenal.
Look at this stuff.
Why do they carry
all this?
Some runners spend
the last year of their lives
Booby-trapping
their escape route.
Gotta be prepared
for anything.
Steele: Sit.
Rupert...
You knew that removing
The alpha transmitter
from mr. Gabriel
Was a violation
in company procedure.
Yes, I knew.
You were
the attending physician
For mr. Gabriel's son,
is that right?
That's right.
Is there anything
about this case
You feel
I ought to know?
[tires squealing]
So, let me get
this straight,
You're going to walk in
through the lobby,
Take the elevator
to the top floor,
Go straight to stofeles' office
and ask where your son is?
You got a better idea?
[scoffs]
This is not a great plan,
gabriel.
I know.
It needs some work.
Anton?
Hmm?
You got a moment?
Of course.
Bobby gabriel's
unique immune system
Is identified at
the annual school checkup.
Yes?
The boy was purposely infected
by the ralph virus.
This is the requisition
for the virus vaccine.
It was ordered on the day
That bobby gabriel
is listed as deceased.
Someone's been doing
their homework.
Tell me, anton...
You didn't deliberately
set up james gabriel
To sign that contract
So you could use
the both of them...
Did you?
Well...
Yes.
The board has
terminated you, anton,
And now I am in charge.
Where is bobby gabriel?
I posted those on the
internet with a time lock.
If anything happens to
that information or me--
That, dr. Elliot,
was not only disloyal,
But stupid!
Coming as it does on the heels
of your other transgressions,
I have no other choice
but to dismiss you.
Mr. Burke...
Do you have dr. Elliot's
severance package?
Yes, I do.
Right here.
Unh!
Now, helen...
Just a moment here.
I know things have
gotten...Extreme,
But I want you to look
at the bigger picture.
You're wasting
your breath.
The gabriels have something
in their blood
That could potentially
double life expectancy.
Think of the possibilities!
Lifecorps is nothing compared
to what you and I could do!
And become a mercenary?
Like--like this piece
of human slag?
No! I won't do it!
[cocks gun]
Putting a bullet
into my head
Won't change anything,
will it?
Oh, really?
Helen, helen...
Think of your
own mortality.
To be mentioned in the same
breath as salk and pauling.
My god,
you're both insane.
We don't have time
for this.
Helen, come with us.
No.
Please come with us!
All we need is the boy.
We can do without gabriel.
Thank you.
That's what
I've been waiting to hear.
This is burke.
Listen up!
All target restrictions
On runner gabriel,
james r. Rescinded.
Reload with hot ammunition,
shoot to kill.
Roger that!
Do it!
Full body armor,
visors down!
Anton, don't do this.
You know it's not right.
Excuse us,
dr. Steele.
Please!
Show me that card again.
Burke had a red card.
What?
When I first saw him
at lifecorps,
He had a red card.
That'd be for
the restricted floors.
78, I think.
[door slams]
[beep]
[lock clicks]
Ohh!
Are you ready?
For what?
To leave.
The run's not over.
It's loaded.
Here we go.
[snaps fingers]
[ding]
Alex.
Come on.
[ding]
Ok, which is
the restricted floor?
78. 78's always closed.
Burke: I think
they're in elevator 3.
Let's see where
they're going.
They're playing with us.
And now they're
starting to piss me off.
Take this, take a squad,
and get down there.
[noises]
What was that?
Gabriel: Bobby?
Oh, my god.
Bobby?
Are you here
to take us home?
Hey, sweetie.
Do you know where
bobby gabriel is?
They took him upstairs.
Come on.
Stofeles must have
faked their deaths
So he could
experiment on them.
Yeah. I'll show him
where he can stick his--
Hold it. In there.
I'll get their attention.
You get these kids
out of here.
When you get
to the bottom floor,
Start all
the elevators moving.
And you?
I'm gonna get
my kid back.
He's got an army up there.
You don't have a chance.
I've got a chance.
Ok, shh. Quickly.
Come on, guys.
[beeping]
Come on. Hurry.
[ding]
Hey! Where did you
all come from?
Be sure to push
all the buttons!
He's on his way up.
Car 1.
Gabriel's in elevator 1.
He's coming up.
The door opens,
shoot him.
[ding]
Replay last 15 seconds.
I know where you are.
Power mains.
Yaah!
[door unlocks]
Unh.
Irina!
Yes?
Get internal security
down here.
You, get up to maintenance
and get the power back on.
Now, move!
[burke whistles]
Hi.
Aah!
That's for all the trouble
you've caused.
This...
This is for alex.
Son of a bitch.
Aah!
Good-bye, mr. Gabriel!
And that's for johnny.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'll have a hundred
security guards here
In 5 minutes.
I don't have 5 minutes.
Damn.
Uhh.
Anton: Come on.
Come on, burke.
Alex.
Aw!
Not bad.
Do it.
Do it!
No.
Yeah.
Where's gabriel?
Gabriel who?
We're running out
of time here.
Ooh!
Particularly you.
That would
be him now.
Find him and kill him.
Move!
Stofeles.
Bobby.
Dad.
Don't move.
Drop the gun.
Drop it.
Let him go.
He's just a boy.
[scoffs]
I, uh...
I don't react well
to missed opportunities.
If I can't
have you both,
I'd rather eliminate
the possibilities.
No!
[gunshot]
It's over, stofeles.
Give it up.
You think so, huh?
Bobby: No!
Come on!
Ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha!
Aah!
Danny,
get him checked out.
See if there's anything
worth salvaging.
Bobby: Daddy!
Can we go home now?
You bet we can.
Oh, yeah.
Alex.
Come here.
I lied.
I am afraid
of falling.
I'll catch you.
Captioning made possible by
warner bros.
Captioned by the national
captioning institute
--www.Ncicap.Org--