T... D...
S... Z... Th...
B... T... V...
H... T... D... K... G...
S... Z... P... B...
Ba-Ba... T... T...
K... Kuh... Ch...
Th... V... Th...
Zzz... Sss... Bzz... Ch...
B-B-Buh... V-V-Vuh...
G-G-Guh... D-D-Duh...
B-B-Buh... B-B-Buh...
B-B-Beh... B-B-Beh... Bah...
N-N-Nuh... N-N-Nuh...
N-N-Nuh... No.
N-N-Nuh...
F... Feel... Field...
Fill... Filled... Filts...
Foil... Failed... Fell...
Felds... Pill... Pills...
Pall... Nall...
Foal... Foals...
Fold... Fold...
Pool...
Sell... Se...
I'm looking for the M8.
Eh...
Aye, you've gotta go
straight along
that way and...
This is gonna be
pure hard to explain.
- Do you know
where the Asda is?
- No.
Yeah, I don't even know
what way you're pointin'.
What?
- See, if you just drive
straight along up there...
- Yes?
And see the traffic lights
up there?
Take a right.
Then you'll go past
Ibrox Stadium, right?
And go straight through
a roundabout.
Then take a left.
So it's right, then just...
And it's there.
The motorway is there.
It's back of Asda.
You'll see it.
- Back of Asda, see?
- Okay.
- Am I keeping you
from something?
- No.
- Where are you going?
- Along here.
- For what? For work?
- No, I need to go
meet somebody.
- Oh, you're going
to meet someone.
- Aye.
All right.
Thank you.
Sure.
I'm looking for a post office.
Post office?
Yes.
Where are you from?
Where I am from?
Yeah.
Albania.
Oh, are you?
You have
family here?
Yes.
Oh, you do.
That's the reason
I'm saying you have
to go another way...
for another...
It's after the shopping ce...
Hi.
Lost?
Yeah, lost.
What are you
looking for?
I'm looking for the M8.
Up to the roundabout...
Are you walking?
Yep.
- Where are you walking to?
- Home.
Oh, you're going home.
To your family?
No, no, just myself.
Just yourself?
Aye. It's great.
Yeah? How?
I can do whatever I like.
So where are you
coming from?
Govan. Right there.
Sorry?
Govan.
Govan?
Do you work there?
No, no.
Don't work there.
I work for myself.
Do you want a lift?
Eh... Aye, why not?
You'll have to tell me
how to get there.
Just follow this road
straight up.
Okay.
Sure.
So what do you do?
Electrician.
Oh, you're an electrician.
It's cold, right?
Ah, it's a wee bit
nippy, aye.
Yeah.
So what is it youse all doing?
I'm...
I'm just, uh, driving...
just, uh... some furniture
for my family and...
Oh, right?
Yeah.
So you live alone?
Yes.
And you love it?
Aye. It's great.
What do you love
about living alone?
- Nobody to nag you.
- Do I go straight through?
Yeah, just straight through.
Straight through the whole way.
It should be just
cart around that street
and stay in the right hand lane.
What's that?
That's a tattoo
of my name.
Of your name?
Yeah.
What's your name?
Andy.
Andy. Hi.
Pleased to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
- Thank you very much.
Andy!
- Want me?
- You coming?
The spot back here, you get...
you put your hand out.
Anybody can stop.
There's lonely old guys.
Know what I mean?
It was... Hey,
might as well check her out,
driving away in a big van.
- Sure you can
drive this, huh? Huh?
- No girlfriend? Really?
- Nah, I don't have
a girlfriend at all.
You're very charming.
That's better.
Yeah? Sorted?
You have a handsome face.
Aye?
Yeah.
Thanks a lot. Cheers.
- Do you think I'm pretty?
- I think you're gorgeous.
- Do you?
- Aye, definitely.
Good.
And a friendly smile as well.
- Do I?
- Aye, right deep.
- What about your smile?
- Aye.
You've a nice smile yourself.
- Cheers.
- Good.
Good.
No, no, no, lads! No!
Mommy!
Whoo!
I thought...
you had your eye on my towel.
No. I wanted
to speak to you.
Do you know if there's
any good spots to surf
around here?
I'm not a surfer.
Just living in
a little tent over there.
Just hanging around.
Yeah?
Reading, swimming.
You're not from here?
Where are you from?
I'm from
Czech Republic.
Why are you in Scotland?
I just... wanted to
get away from it all.
Yeah?
Why here?
Because it's...
It's nowhere.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa. Excuse me.
Can I talk to you
before you run away,
darling?
I wanted to speak
to you earlier, right,
but you disappeared.
I thought you went
to the ladies' or somethin'.
Anyway, right,
fuck all that shite.
Right?
I really want
to buy you a drink, man.
You look absolutely stunning.
And I...
You know what?
I'm all alone.
You're all alone.
What do you say?
What's one drink?
I saw you on the road.
What, you saw me
on the road?
Earlier, yeah.
Are you having
a laugh with me?
You saw me? You wanna come
get a drink and a dance?
Are you alone here?
Yeah, I'm all alone.
Right?
The man from the car,
he buy the rose for you.
A man's body has been found
washed up on a beach...
near Arbroath.
His wife and child
are reported missing.
The police say the body
has been identified...
as 36-year-old
Kenneth McClelland
from Edinburgh.
The body was found
by a tourist...
and is believed to have been
in the water for some time.
Mr. McClelland was married and
worked as a chemistry lecturer
at Edinburgh University.
The alarm was raised
when he failed to turn up
for work this morning.
His car was found at
the nearby Deer Park Golf Club.
His wife, 32-year-old
Alison McClelland,
and 18-month-old son...
are believed
to have been with him.
A police and coast guard
search operation
involving a helicopter...
has been halted due to fog.
The next bulletin
is on the hour.
Well, plenty to talk about,
as ever, with Kay.
You can call now...
10-500-92-95-00.
You can text as well...
80295.
- It's 8:17.
- Good morning, Gary.
Well, as we've heard,
for a whole host of reasons...
2014 is a very important year
for Scotland.
Of course, the referendum.
We're expecting that date today.
But the Commonwealth Games
and Ryder Cup...
You seem very excited
about that.
I am.
He's jumping out of his seat
at the prospect of the year
he's gonna have...
Fuckin' hell, you're gorgeous.
- You think so?
- It's your eyes.
Somethin' about your eyes.
Your eyes, your lips.
That
black hair.
Yeah?
You just look...
amazing.
Hey, you okay?
Want a hand up?
Want a hand?
Get out, eh? Get out!
Excuse me.
Uh, I'm a bit lost, really.
Am I headed towards Taynuilt?
Yeah.
I am? Is it far?
It's about 10 minutes away.
Ten minutes? Are you...
Are you headed there?
I'm going to the supermarket.
Is it on the way?
Yeah.
I could drop you off
if you'd like.
Yeah?
Here. Let me
turn this up for you.
That's better.
You're very quiet.
So why do you
shop at night then?
People wind me up.
How?
They're ignorant.
What about your friends?
So you don't have any friends?
No.
How about a girlfriend?
How old are you?
I'm 26.
When was the last time
you had a girlfriend?
Never had one.
So don't you get lonely then?
You've very nice hands.
You've beautiful hands.
Do you want to look at me?
This isn't Tesco's,
is it?
No.
I noticed you
looking at me before.
And?
I liked it.
You're uncomfortable.
No. Just want
to go to Tesco's.
So you never think
about it then?
Think about what?
Being with a girl.
When was the last time
you touched someone?
Let me see your hands.
Cold.
I have to get back soon.
How was that?
Cold.
Do you want to do it again?
Yeah.
Do you want to touch my neck?
Here.
How was that?
Yeah.
Your hands are very soft.
I have a place
about 30 minutes away.
Will you come with me there?
Cold.
I won't let that stop us.
Come to me.
Dreaming?
Yes.
Yes, we are.
The bus will be
along in a minute.
Do you not think you should be
wearing a jacket, little lass?
The weather's terrible up here.
You'll catch your death of cold
if you've not got a jacket
or a hat or something on.
You've not got the right
clothes on at all.
You all right there?
Eh?
You okay?
Can I do something for you?
Chase yourself, dafty.
Leave the lassie alone.
She doesn't want anything
to do with you.
Do you need any help?
Yes.
Right.
Let me just take your coat.
Spoon, Jar.
Jar, spoon.
Spoon, Jar. Jar...
Wonder whether that's
working, don't you?
Spoon, Jar.
Jar, spoon.
Stop!
Pull it. Pull it.
♪ Now I've stood
on your shadow ♪
♪ And I've watched it grow
♪ And it's shaken
and it's driven me ♪
♪ And let me know Let me know ♪
♪ Let me know
Let me know about
all the old forty-fives ♪
♪ And the paperback rooms
♪ And it's scattered
all the photographs ♪
♪ Of summers and suns
♪ And you're a real gone kid
♪ And maybe now, baby
♪ Maybe now, baby
♪ I'll do what I should have di♪
♪ 'Cause you're a real
♪ Gone...
Night.
You all right?
If you're frightened, let's go.
Come on.
It's all right.
That's it.
It's okay.
All right.
Okay.
You did it.
You all right?
You just off for a ramble
in the woods then? Eh?
Huh?
You just off for a ramble
in the woods? Yeah, yeah?
Oh, it's, uh...
Watch how you step here.
It's a bit, uh...
It's a bit slippery
round here, but...
this time of year.
It's all right in summer.
Well, it's still wet in summer,
but not as bad as it is now.
But there's plenty
of trails around here.
Have you been here before?
No? First time? Yeah?
Oh, you won't get lost.
They're all clearly marked.
But, uh, there's about
2,000 acres of forest here,
so you shouldn't...
you should have, uh, plenty
of places to go in there.
You on your own?
Yeah.
Yeah, on your own?
Oh, well, it's a nice place
if you want some solitude,
you know,
to "gather your thoughts"
and all that, yeah?
So, uh, enjoy yourself
anyway, okay?
Thank you.