_
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
You said you had information
about an attack.
- I have information.
- Prove it.
Aah!
Homeland - 4x00
"Debrief"
I'm very attracted to this show
because it's
incredibly gripping.
What were his exact words?
An American prisoner of war
has been turned.
If you tell a story well,
people will come.
I am not a terrorist.
I have never been so sure
and so wrong.
I'll do whatever it takes.
He's here!
I'm afraid
you've got this backwards.
I'm the one getting nominated
as Director.
Brody!
_
"Homeland" is about a POW
who has been rescued
after eight years
of really brutal captivity.
Stay down!
I'm an American.
Nicholas Brody
is brought back a hero,
but the main character
of this show, Carrie Mathison,
is unconvinced by this guy.
Carrie Mathison
is a CIA operative.
She's extremely driven
and focused.
I missed something once before.
I won't let that happen again.
Part of her brilliance
has to do with
her being bipolar.
She's really
on the edge of sanity.
Carrie intuits that
this hero has been turned
and is working
for the other side.
Did you ever meet him?
Abu Nazir?
- Was he ever present during
any of your interrogations? - No.
She illicitly starts
observing him very closely.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I know you.
There's a recognition
between them.
Where was it you said
you served again? Baghdad?
Yeah.
How come it's so hard
to talk about
with people who weren't there?
They think
they're playing each other.
They do fall in love.
But it's a doomed romance.
I know I have oatmeal,
but no Yorkshire Gold
out here in the sticks.
Sorry.
How do you know
the tea I drink?
Did you spy on me?
You are a spy, right?
Very quickly,
we learn that Brody might not be
everything he seems.
By the time you watch this,
you'll have read
a lot of things about me.
Brody does wear a suicide vest
into a basement
with the Vice President.
Sergeant Brody, got a call
for you from your daughter.
Brody is brought back
from the edge
because of his love
for his daughter.
Dad, promise me.
You have to promise me
that you're coming home, dad.
I'm coming home, Dana.
Carrie is vindicated
by the audience,
but no one, including her,
is aware of how right she was.
I'm sorry.
She sends herself
to get electro-shock therapy.
That's where we leave Season 1.
_
Brody is able to keep it
a secret for a while,
but Saul comes back
with information.
Everyone knows
what Brody tried to do.
My name is Nicholas Brody.
I was right.
You were right.
So you want to follow Brody?
I'm sending you a guy.
Peter Quinn
is a Black Ops agent.
He's effectively a mercenary.
If Quinn is doing it,
it never happened.
She had been right all along,
and that fills her
with an enormous rage.
I liked you, Carrie.
I loved you.
Freeze!
Hands be your back!
You're a traitor
and a terrorist,
and now it's time
you pay for that.
The big theme in Season 2
was Brody being turned
into a double agent.
I can do this, Saul.
What is Abu Nazir's plan?
I don't know.
But there is a plan, right?
Yes.
Carrie Mathison
is then captured by Abu Nazir.
What have you done to Carrie?
Did you think you could
betray me and just walk away?
Brody has to effect
some sort of rescue.
Walden has a bad heart.
His pacemaker
can be wirelessly accessed
with that serial number.
What are you doing?!
I'm killing you.
Nazir allows Carrie to leave.
She, above all,
wants to capture this guy,
and so she goes after him.
Now Brody has fulfilled
his immunity deal,
and in Carrie's case,
it means possibly having
a personal life with Brody.
And just when you think
everything is rosy...
Somebody moved my car.
...the CIA blows up
right underneath their noses,
and it seems as though
Brody planted the bomb.
In an act of desperation,
Carrie drives Brody
to the border.
This was love.
But it's not goodbye.
_
We start with Season 3.
It's really steeped
in the cloak-and-dagger world
of the CIA.
The President wants closure
for the American people, Saul.
Brody's the poster boy
for this attack.
Saul may be the last Director
of the CIA
unless he does
something profound.
The case officer in question--
she's been diagnosed as bipolar.
Get off of me.
This is a scam!
Where we thought
Carrie was actually being
sold down the river by Saul,
we realize that they've been
in cahoots all along.
Burning her
in front of the Senate?
All an act. We dangled her
to draw the Iranians out.
Javadi himself.
From now on, you work for us.
I'm gonna play you
back into Iran.
Where am I?
Caracas, your new home.
I have a play.
It involves Brody.
So, what is it?
What's your big idea?
Danesh Akbari.
I want him gone.
- Brody can get to him.
- Ohh!
Brody completing this mission--
there's a sense
that he will redeem himself.
For him, personally,
it's extremely important.
It becomes very clear to him
killing another human being is
a soul-destroying thing to do.
There is no redemption for him,
and Carrie really has one thing
to bring him back
to some sense of humanity.
I'm pregnant.
Briefly, he feels
just a sense of hope,
but I think Brody is a character
with little hope.
Brody, run!
Get down now!
He appeared this morning
before a military tribunal,
where he was sentenced to death
by hanging.
Oh, God!
We really had a fantastic time
figuring out how this was
all gonna come to a close.
We've covered so much landscape
between these two characters.
And this is it.
The Brody part of the story
is done.
Brody!
Goodbye, love.
_
In Season 4, we find Carrie,
six months later,
working overseas.
We're all hoping
you'll be on your best behavior
here in Pakistan.
Her job is
to perform drone attacks,
and she's doing
a little too well.
Until something
goes very, very wrong.
- Saul.
- Carrie.
What's going on?
We watch Saul
be replaced by Lockhart.
So he's no longer
the head of the CIA.
He's in the private sector.
I don't know if "Retirement"
is a word that fits
with Saul Berenson.
I think we're walking away
with the job half done.
Saul, could I speak with you?
He is a manipulator.
We haven't really been
talking much lately, Carrie.
He'll probably
find his way back.
What I wanted to talk about,
I couldn't.
So you're worried about her?
I know the warning signs.
Believe me.
Quinn is working for the CIA,
not quite wearing a tie,
but slightly less blood
on his hands.
I controlled myself
for 12 years.
He's fast losing respect
for pretty much everything.
Carrie's all work all the time,
and she can't really engage
on any other level.
She has to come to terms
with Brody's loss.
That's her arc.
It's very difficult being in
the same space with her child.
It evokes Brody.
She's gonna need her mother
to be there for her.
I don't have a choice.
It's way too confronting.
This season,
the band has got to snap.
She cannot tolerate
her culpability.
- What the hell is wrong with you?!
- What is wrong with you?!
It gets ugly.
Jesus, Quinn.
Now it's starting
to just spin out of control.
Ma'am, you have blood
all over the side of your face.
People must know the truth.
I want to be the one
to tell it.
THIS OCTOBER
Are you
in some kind of trouble?
THERE'S
NO
- Carrie, no!
- PLACE
LIKE
Happy hunting.
_
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com