Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What is it ?
Heather, she's in trouble.
You just had a nightmare.
I can feel that something is wrong.
Karen, you just talked to her yeaterday.
I'm sure she's okay.
I know, but something's awful is gonna happen,
I can tell
You're just upset because she's moving away.
Babe, I'm sure she's fine.
It felt so real.
Roger, it felt so horrible.
I know, I know, baby.
Just try to get some sleep.
Hello.
Are you there yet ?
No.
Not yet.
Four more miles.
Are you sure about this ?
Yes, I'm sure.
It's like you are moving
to the other side of the world
No, it's just at the other side of the valley.
I just think it's too soon.
You should be around your friends.
Around Roger and me.
I don't any friends who are friends with my ex.
You are the only friends I have,
and you are just a phone call away.
It's not the same.
I just don't think you should be running away.
Who's running ?
I'm driving.
Look, I just need a change of scenery.
I don't want to be reminded of him everywhere I go.
I know you're hurt, and, I'm, uh..
sorry about that.
Look, I'm losing you.
I'm gonna call when I get there, okay.
Dis you tell her about your dream ?
No, guess I'm too worried too much as it is.
You ? Worried too much ?
That is why I love you, baby.
Can I help you ?
No, but I can help you.
No, I'm not interested right now,
so if you're interested about my phone number..
Wait, I'm not lookig for a date.
What is that ?
I'm kind of in a hurry.
I didn't want to frighten you,
it'sjust that your brake lights are out.
I'm almost run into you back there.
Oh, God, I'm sorry..
Do you have far to go?
No, I just moved here,
I live a few miles up the road.
Well then you don't have to
drive much further than you have to.
You don't want to cause an accident or get a ticket.
No. I don't.
I'll get it looked at the first thing.
Well, if you like, I can follow you.
To get home safely.
Sure, thank you..
Marcus.
Marcus, I'm Heather.
Welcome to the Canyon, Heather.
Hello.
Who's there ?
You must be Heather.
I'm Mike, Mike Anderson.
Is everything alright?
Yeah, I'm sorry, I don't mean to stare,
I'm just, uh... thought you were gonna be a little older.
Oh, my father, he rented you this place.
We're both named Michael.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine, we get that all the time.
He rents out the places,
and I take care of them.
Speaking of which, your faucets, they fixed,
I added a few washers, presto, good to go.
And if I knew you were gonna be here earlier,
I'd finish it sooner, so, sorry about that.
No, it's okay, I just, need to
get out of the city.
I'm here once a week,
to fix the pool, clean up everything.
So, if you need anythig at all,
please feel free to call me.
Yes, I will, I mean,
I won't hesitate to call.
Okay.
Well, it's nice meeting you.
I guess there's other property to attend to,
so.. Enjoy your stay.
I will.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Think I'm gonna like it here.
Hello.
I'm here.
Finally ?
I'm starting to get worried.
I'm sorry, I was delayed.
Delayed ?
Delayed by what ?
It's not important.
What's important is that I'm here.
Well, how do you like it ?
I love it.
I can't wait to incite you to come for dinner.
And bring the kids, they're gonna
love the pool.
We can't wait to see the place.
You should see my landlord.
Pretty hot, huh ?
I'll say..
Who's hot?
Are you talking about me again?
Oh, please.
Is that Roger?
Yes.
We're busted.
Oh, don't go there, then I will
really be in trouble.
You got that right.
You know, it's good to hear you laugh again.
Yes.
Give Roger my love.
Okay, I'll call you tomorrow.
Hello.
I'm Heather.
Oh, yes.
You must be the new tenant.
I thought you're arriving this evening.
Yeah, I'm early.
I'm Marisa.
Michael let me use the pool
when no one is renting.
I'm sorry, you probably wanna get settled in,
I'll just grab my things.
No, that's okay. Stay.
I've got to get goind anyway.
My boyfriend's expecting me.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
Hello.
Marisa, right?
Yes.
You remembered.
This is Daniel.
Nice to meet you Daniel.
You all settled in?
Just about.
Well if you need anything, we're just atl 642.
Yes, anything at all.
In fact, if you don't have dinner plans tomorrow night,
maybe you'd like to join us.
We don't own a pool, but..
Then why don't we have dinner here ?
Please, I'll cook, I insist.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure, bring along your swimsuits, we
can hang out by the pool.
Sounds good, we'll gonna have a party.
You know, we're alone here,
so we appreciated the company.
Well, yes, I'm excited. That's why I moved,
to get away from it all.
Right, Daniel.
- So, 6 sounds good ?
- 6 it is.
Great.
- Great.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
Where is she ?
Feels great.
She's gorgeous, isn't she ?
I think I had one too many margaritas.
Or maybe, you need one more.
You kissed a woman before ?
Well, actually that was my first.
Not even in college ?
No.
You prove I'm right.
I'm not.
Yes you are.
Was not.
Well, you are not like Marisa.
She's exhibitionist.
Oh, really.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Can I have my bra back?
Here.
Well maybe I am.
Wasn't so bad, was it ?
What about Marisa?
What about her?
She's your girlfriend.
We have a very open relationship.
She's be out here any minute.
No, Marisa is probably inside,
passed out, right now.
Why do you like it here in Canyon?
You hiding out?
What makes you think I'm hidin out?
Well, that's why people moved here, right ?
To get away from everything.
Well, I just had to get away froom the city.
Oh, so you just woke up one day,
and said, "I'm gonna move to some secluded place all by myself?"
Yes.
I don't buy it.
What about you?
What about me?
Why are you here ?
Are you hiding from something?
The law?
No, Why ?
Why'd you hear?
Wanna know the truth?
Truth would be nice.
I.. hate people.
I.. moved here to get away from the city.
It's just... too many people.
Really.
Well, since you're being so honest.
I moved here to get away from my ex-husband.
Oh, the ex-husband.
Everywhere I went, he went.
Is he stalking you?
We're both writers.
We work in the same magazine,
the same editors.
We go to the same parties,
I just had to leave.
I see.
Well, I don't wanna bore you with my stories
about my exhusband.
I moved here so I won't think about 'em,
talk about 'em.
There you go, I'm rambling again,
I'm sorry.
It's okay, I love ramblings.
Would you uh, like another cup ?
No thanks, I'd be up all night.
Looks I gotta get myself home.
Yeah, you were right about her.
Thanks for tonight.
Bye.
Nice meeting you Daniel.
You all settled in?
Just about.
Well if you need anything, we're just at 642.
Yes, anything at all.
Well, then why don't we have dinner here?
Please, I insist.
Are you sure?
Yes, That's why we moved here, to get away from ..
Right Daniel?
So, is 6 okay ?
Well, see you tomorrow.
I think I had one too many margaritas.
Or maybe you need one more.
She's an exhibitionist.
Oh, really ?
Kissed a woman before?
What about Marisa?
Oh, good morning.
Oh, God.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
Has it been a week already?
No, but Marisa called me way too early this morning, asked me to heat the pool.
She did?
I didn't think she'll be up til noon.
You guys got a hangover fro the party last night?
How did you know?
Well, looks like it's gonna be a hot one today.
It's noon now, so..
Did you say noon?
S*it, s*it, my editor's gonna be here any minute.
Nice place.
Thanks, I'm glad you like  it.
Yes, but the drive Heather, it's making me nauseous.
You get used to it after a while.
Besides, I don't drive to town that often.
I can tell you one thing about this place.
It's doing you some good.
You think so?
I know so.
The last articles you sent me were really good.
Thanks Collin.
Hearing that from you means a great deal.
And you look great.
Seriously, you really had me worried.
Everybody worry about me too  much.
But I guess that's what's friends are for, huh.
Yeah.
So, how are you doing, really?
Good, actually.
Good enough to go to a party in a few weeks?
'Cos I got a lot of clients who's really interested
in your manuscripts.
Sure.
You know who'd probably be there.
You mean Michael.
Are you ready for that?
Is she still with that ??
Yeah, I hear she's a writer now, but with a tabloid.
She's no writer.
She just knows how to spread those legs of hers.
I ran to both of them at the party.
Man, she was drunk.
She was all over anyone who was anyone.
I'm pretty sure Carl was embarrassed.
He should be.
I think he realises he's made a pretty big mistake.
He sure did, and now he has to
live with the consequences.
He's got nothing on you, Heather.
Thanks Collin, I needed that.
Hello.
Is this the beautiful lady with the lovely breast?
Daniel, can I help you?
Or should I report this as a prank phone call?
Don't call the cops.
Listen, I heard it's supposed to be a nice day today.
Rather hot, actually.
So I've heard.
Well, a dip in the pool would be nice.
Are you inviting yourself over?
Of course, I'd love to.
See you in a few.
See you soon.
You're getting burnt.
No.
Manuscript you're working on, what's it all about ?
Well, it's about a woman,
who loses her husband to cancer.
And how she deals with her loneliness in
the years following.
Wow, how'd you get the idea?
Sounds depressing.
It was.
She was actually a friend of mine.
How's she doing now?
She's great.
She remarried.
Her story was so inspiring.
There is life, after the death of the loved one.
I'd love to read it some time.
When it's finished.
You'd be the first one.
Besides my editor.
I'd like that.
Why so serious, lighten up.
See you later.
When do you two meet?
Love at first sight?
Something like that.
She's very beautiful.
Yes, she is.
But it's not what attracted me to her.
Yeah, she's open-minded.
She doesn't try to change me,
she accepts me for who I am.
Who would wanna change you?
Most women are insecure.
I see.
Do you love her?
I care for her deeply.
But I'm not in love with her.
She's perfect.
I just don't see me spending the
rest of my live with her.
Does she know that?
Let's not talk about marisa.
Let's talk about you.
What about me?
You're beautiful.
You're perfect.
You are.
And you're shy.
I'm just not being used to
being talked that way, that's all.
Get used to it.
Glad you came.
Thanks for having me.
Here's the lovely ladies in the Canyon.
Thank you.
This calls for some music.
I love the song.
- Hello.
-Where were you last night?
What ?
I call you house several times,
I was worried.
I was out.
Out where?
With whom?
My friends were having dinner party.
It got kinda late.
I see.
So, did you anyone intsresting at this party?
No, just a party, my neighbours
Daniel and Marisa.
I told you about them.
Doesn't sound much like a party.
Oh, but it was.
Karen, I did something that I never dream
of when I was single.
What did you do?
I spent the night.
With Daniel?
With both of them.
I guess, if that's what they're calling it.
What was it like?
It was indescribable.
I think I'm falling for him.
Who?
Daniel.
What about his girlfriend?
That's why Roger and I never had a threesome.
I don't want some woman falling for my husband.
You don't have anything to worry about Roger.
He would never astray, he loves you.
He better not.
I'd kill him.
It's not like Daniel's married or anything,
they were only living together for a few months.
But that's not a woman scorned.
But it's meant to be.
I never had this feelings in a long time.
I think he has the same feelings for me.
I think you better chalked it up as fantasy fulfilled
and let it go.
I know.
You are right, again.
I know I'm right.
You don't want some crazy b*tch
running after you for stealing her man.
Besides, he sounds like he has
commitment issues.
Sounds like your ex.
He's nothing like Kyle.
I'm Heather, leave me a message.
Hey, it's Daniel.
Just trying to get a hold of you again.
Give me a call.
Bye.
You are calling her again.
Yes. I was.
Do you love her?
You're starting to get jealous, Marisa.
You have nothing to be jealous about.
Then why are you so obsessed with her?
I'm not obsessed with her
Am I not enough?
Babe, you know the answer to that.
Come here.
I don't wanna fight.
Hello neighbour.
Oh, Marcus right.
Good memory.
Thanks again about those brake lights.
No problem.
I'm sorry, I thought you were...
I didn't know.
It's okay.
It's nice to see you again,
but I gotta keep moving.
I'm sure we'll cross paths again.
Soon.
Oh, Hye Daniel.
Do you know that guy?
Nice to see you too.
Heather, do you know him?
Yeah, I met him before.
Well, stay away from him.
That guy is a creep.
What makes you say that?
I caught him following Marisa couple of times.
Until I scare him away.
You'rekidding.
I never seen her in while, but..
Until about a week ago, he was driving by
my house a couple of time.
Just to let me know he was still there.
Oh, God.
He knows where I live.
Just keep your doors locked, all the time, okay?
I will.
Let's go.
Thanks for jogging with me home.
You know, I called you a few times.
Yeah, I know, I've been busy.
Deadlines.
About the other night,
Are you okay with that?
Yes, of course.
Then why you didn't return any of phone calls?
You want the truth ?
The truth would be nice.
The truth is I never dated anyone since my divorce.
And it's been a while since I had any fun.
I like the both of you.
- But..
- But ?
Daniel, I can't stop thinking about you.
I can't stop thinking about you either.
It's not fair to Marisa.
It's not fair to me.
What do you mean?
I mean, I'm sitting at home, alone.
Thinking of you, sleeping with her.
I just don't wanna get hurt right now, that's all.
I think I should stay away for a while
until my feelings subside.
I'm still emotionally confused right now.
That's what you feel?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Daniel, I gotta go.
Daniel, what are you doing here this late?
I want to sleep with you.
I don't know why are you doing this.
She knows you.
I want you, Daniel.
You don't know me.
I want to know you.
I have needs.
I have desires that most women-
I know, I'm fine with  that.
Do you realise what you're asking me to do?
Yes.
Whatever you want.
I want you.
What's going on ?
I gotta talk to Marisa.
Right now ?
I've gotta let her know my feelings for you.
What are your feelings for me ?
I think you know.
I won't be able to see you for a few days.
You are so bad.
Don't, she knew I wasn't serious about her anyway.
Doesn't make me feel any better.
Listen, I'm not gonna let her stand in
ther way of me losing you.
I see you found my key.
It paractically had my name on it.
I miss you.
Daniel, I haven't of you in a week
No phone call, no anything.
I'm beginning to think you change your mind about us.
Never.
What took you so long?
- She's gone now.
- Where ?
It's not important.
What matters is that we're together now.
Daniel, I've gotta go.
I have meetings with my editor,
and some important clients.
I can't be late, this is very important.
Oh, Daniel.
You scared me.
You're home late.
What are you doing here sitting around in the dark?
take your blouse off.
What, now ?
Daniel.
How did you two celebrate ?
I don't know.
He's being so secretive.
he says he has a surprise for me.
Can you believe it,
we've been together six months.
You think it's a ring?
Karen?
You think ?
No, it's too soon.
Wouldn't that be something, though ?
Yeah, you sound so happy.
I am.
I love him, Karen.
What is it?
You'll see.
Would you give me a hint?
No.
But it'll get warmer.
Daniel, what is this?
You hire a prostitute on my birthday ?
Callgirl.
I thought you like her,
she's o beautiful.
You brought a whore in my house?
I'm leaving.
No, wait.
Please just stay.
Give me one minute.
Daniel, it's my birthday.
I know it's your  birthday.
And I thought you like the gift I got.
- Instead you've been acting like ungrateful..
- What ?
You heard me.
I thought we could use a little excitement around here.
Clebrate.
I thought it was just gonna be the two of us.
This is a very special day.
Well it's just the two of us.
Now look, I paid a lot of money for it.
So you either stay here and sulk,
or get back in and have a good time.
It's up to you.
Hey.
I forgot my suit.
Would you go in and make out?
No, I think we've already covered that.
I'm on my way out anyway.
But we should this again, some times.
Yes, I will give you a great reference.
Happy birthday.
I'm surprised you didn't ask her to move in.
What is wrong with you?
I just want you all to myself.
You have me all to yourself.
What more do you want?
Are you starting to get jealous?
Look ,you have me hooked.
But I have needs.
I know.
But I thought you love me and not want anyone else.
I do love you.
But don't try to change me.
You knew al this going into the relationship.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I said I was sorry.
Look, I'll only be going for a few days.
For what?
I have some business to take care of.
Some nuisance.
I'll be back before you know it.
Oh, it's you.
What do you want?
I've come to talk to you about your neighbours.
Daniel and Marisa.
Daniel already told me about you.
He said you were some kind of pervert.
Goodbye.
Is that what Daniel told you?
Did he also told you that I've been watching his every move since the disappereance of his last girlfriend?
You're lying.
Go away.
I'm gonna call the police.
I am  the police.
I'll be back withink the hour with a warrant.
It'll be much easier if you'll just let me in.
I'll just leave my card on your door..
Anyone can make those up.
Look Heather, Marisa is dead.
I believe Daniel was behind it.
When did this happened ?
Police found her body this morning at the Canyon.
What happened to her ?
I'm not liberty to discuss details.
But we know it was Daniel.
We just need to find him.
Do you know where he is?
No, business out of town.
When will he be returning to LA ?
I don't know.
Did he and Marisa had a fight ?
Is there anything you can tell me about their relationship?
I really don't know.
I know I can come on pretty strong some time.
But this is very serious.
We know Daniel killed Marisa.
As well as his last girlfriend, Laura.
Oh, my God.
Are you and Daniel intimate ?
Look, that's really none of your business.
I'm just rying to do my job.
I'd like to catch him before he kills again.
The why don't you just arrest him?
Believe me, I would if I could.
We just don't have significant evidence.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Do you know where he is ?
No.
It's obvious that you're ready to talk right now.
If you can think of anything,
give me a call.
Oh and lock your doors.
Heather, it's me.
Let me in.
I can't right now, I'm busy.
Baby, open up door.
Can you come back a little later,
I'm not feeling well.
No, Daniel.
What's got into you?
Stay right there.
Don't come any closer.
Marisa is dead.
They found her body at the bottom of the Canyon.
Look , I don't know what you've heard,
but you are wrong.
The guy you told me to stay away from,
he's a cop, isn't he ?
The guy's a liar, and I told you to stay away from her.
Tell me what happened to Marisa.
I don't know.
You're a liar.
No, let me go.
You're saved.
What am I doing here ?
You took a nasty fall.
Why am I not in a hospital?
Daniel may come looking for you.
I'm keeping you safe.
Don't worry about him.
You have me to protect you now.
And soon, we'll become lovers.
Just like you and Daniel once were.
Save your lungs, my dear.
No one can hear you.
Let me go, bastard.
It's not very nice.
I'll be back when you've learn some manners.
Hello neighbour.
Oh, Marcus right.
Good memory.
Hey, thanks again about those brake lights.
No problem.
I'm sorry, I thought you were...
I didn't know.
It's okay.
Nice to see you again, but, um,
I gotta keep moving.
We'll cross paths, soon.
Soon.
Hello Daniel.
Do you know that guy ?
Nice to see you too.
Heather, do you know that guy ?
Yeah, I've met him before.
he lives around the Canyon.
Well stay away from him.
That guy is a creep.
What makes you say that?
I caught him following Marisa couple of times.
Until I scare him away.
You're kidding.
I never seen her in while, but..
Until about a week ago, he was driving by
my house a couple of time.
Just to let me know he was still there.
He knows where I live.
Just keep your doors locked, all the time, okay?
I will.
Let's go.
Heather, it's me.
Let me in.
I can't right now, I'm busy.
Baby, open up door.
Can you come back a little later,
I'm not feeling well.
No, Daniel.
What's got into you?
Stay right there.
Don't come any closer.
Marisa esta muerta.
They found her body at the bottom of the Canyon.
Look , I don't know what you've heard,
but you are wrong.
The guy you told me to stay away from,
he's a cop, isn't he ?
The guy's a liar, and I told you to stay away from her.
Tell me what happened to Marisa.
I don't know.
You're a liar.
No, let me go.
Are we in a better mood today ?
What do you want from me ?
A little nicer.
Please.
What do you want from me ?
Simple.
Love me.
What?
And I will set you free.
Love you?
Is that such an unreasonable request?
I will treat you better than anyone.
Especially Daniel.
I bet he was a kinky bastard.
Wasn't he ?
Was ?
Where is he ?
Probably back with Marisa.
That's where he was, you know.
When he said he had to take care of business.
She's not dead ?
Muerto.
Dead ?
But they might as well be.
They were cheating on you, you know.
How dare you.
I was doing you a favor.
You can never have Daniel all to yourself.
He has his needs, and you couldn't
give that to him.
That's none of your business, you psycho.
If you are gonna be nasty,
I'm going to leave you alone again.
Wait.
I need to use the bathroom.
And some water would be nice.
That's my girl.
Marcus.
Yes.
Did you think you can get these cuffs off me now ?
No. It's too soon.
Haven't I change enough ?
We haven't make love yet.
That's not what our relationship is based on.
No.
Proof to me your feelings for me.
I do care for you.
Sweet Heather.
But it's not enough.
I'm making duck tonight.
Hope you like it.
Marcus.
- Yes.
I think I'm ready.
Ready for what ?
To make love.
Are you sure ?
Because I won't force you.
No, or course not.
Wait, how about some wine ?
Yes, that should loosen us a bit.
I'll be right back.
Some music would be nice.
Yes.
Any request ?
No, I'm sure whatever you have is fine.
How's that?
It's lovely.
Propose a toast.
To us.
Wait.
I wanna dance for you first.
Foreplay.
Could you undo my cuffs ?
Don't try to escape.
I'm faster, and stronger than you.
Besides,
You'll live to regret it.
I know.
Enjoy.
This wine...
Sleep forever.
I appreciate you letting me this.
You kidding me ?
You've been through enough already.
It's good that the psycho's walled up.
He wouldn't stalk anyone anymore.
It's too bad you're leaving.
Would have been nice to have as a  friend.
It's pretty lonely out here, you know.
Yeah.
So I've heard.
Welcome to The Canyon.
If you like, I could follow you,
to get home safely.
You're saved.
English Translation : i1chocolat @ Subscene.com
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org