filmeuy.com
Free Watch Online & Download Movies
[ORLEAN'S "STILL THE ONE"
PLAYS]
♪ WELL, WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
SINCE WAY BACK WHEN ♪
♪ SOMETIMES, I NEVER
WANT TO SEE YOU AGAIN ♪
♪ BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW ♪
♪ AFTER ALL THESE YEARS ♪
♪ YOU'RE STILL THE ONE
I WANT WHISPERIN' IN MY EAR
♪
♪ YOU'RE STILL THE ONE
I WANT TO TALK TO IN BED ♪
♪ STILL THE ONE
THAT TURNS MY HEAD ♪
♪ WE'RE STILL HAVING FUN ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE STILL THE ONE ♪
♪ I LOOKED AT YOUR FACE
EVERY DAY... ♪
HI.
SORRY I'M LATE.
I HAD THE NIGHTMARE AGAIN
AND OVERSLEPT.
OH, "THE MARCH OF
THE BRIDAL MERINGUES" ONE?
YES. PROMISE ME
IF I EVER
TRY TO SELL A WOMAN
A WEDDING DRESS
COVERED WITH PEARLS,
YOU WILL STAGE
AN INTERVENTION.
DONE.
OH! HEY, MY NIECE
GAVE ME THIS LAST NIGHT.
SHE SAID IT WILL
BRING YOU GOOD LUCK
WHEN YOU OPEN.
I WILL TAKE
ALL THE LUCK I CAN GET.
OH, I DROVE BY
THAT OTHER WEDDING
STORE THIS MORNING.
DID YOU SEE
THEIR WINDOW DISPLAY?
I DID.
THE BEADING ON THAT DRESS
MUST WEIGH AT LEAST 200
POUNDS.
I WONDER HOW THAT OWNER'S
GONNA REACT WHEN YOU OPEN.
OH, SHE'LL BE FINE.
I'M NOT TRYING TO
TAKE BUSINESS AWAY FROM HER.
I'M JUST PROVIDING WOMEN
AN ALTERNATIVE
TO THE TRADITIONAL
COOKIE-CUTTER STUFF.
LET'S JUST HOPE
THAT, IF WE BUILD IT...
THEY WILL COME.
OH!
IT'S PERFECT.
OH, I'M SO GLAD
YOU THINK SO.
I FEEL EXACTLY THE SAME WAY.
EXCEPT FOR THE NECKLINE.
I WAS JUST GOING TO SAY,
UM, I DEFINITELY AGREE
IT NEEDS TO BE... RAISED.
LOWERED.
LOWERED! AN INCH?
HALF AN INCH.
AND THE SHOES.
SEVEN AND A HALF NARROW?
EXACTLY.
WELL, THEY DON'T
CALL HER
THE "BRIDE WHISPERER"
FOR NOTHING.
[CHUCKLES] NO...
MOM?
MM?
I KIND OF WANT TO
HOLD OFF A MOMENT.
[SCOFFING LAUGH]
OH, HONEY, HONEY.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WE'VE WAITED SIX MONTHS
FOR THIS APPOINTMENT,
AND YOU HEARD
WHAT MRS. TAYLOR SAID--
YOU LOOK... BEAUTIFUL.
THE DRESS IS PERFECT.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL,
BUT I KIND OF WANT TO CHECK
OUT
THAT NEW PLACE.
"SO YOU SAID YES"?
OH, YOU DON'T
WANT TO DO THAT.
I SAW ON TWITTER
THAT THEY'RE HAVING THEIR
GRAND-OPENING PARTY TUESDAY.
THE OWNER'S TWEETS
ARE HYSTERICAL.
PLEASE?
I THINK, UH,
THESE ARE THE ONES.
OH...
I, UM,
JUST REMEMBERED--
I THINK THERE IS SOMEWHERE
THAT WE NEED TO BE,
BUT I'M SURE WE WILL BE
BACK.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH.
THAT'S A REALLY NICE SET-UP
YOU GOT THERE
WITH THE SHOP, KIDDO.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
THANKS, DAD.
YOU OBVIOUSLY GOT
ALL YOUR LOVE
FOR WEDDINGS FROM ME.
WELL, YOU DID
HAVE THREE OF THEM.
YEAH, AND THEY
WERE ALL A BLAST.
IT WAS THE MARRIAGE PART
THAT WAS TOUGH.
OTHER THAN THE ONE
WITH YOUR MOTHER,
REST HER SOUL.
YOU KNOW, YOU...
YOU LOOK MORE LIKE HER
EVERY DAY.
I SURE WISH
SHE COULD SEE THIS.
ME TOO.
SO YOU--
YOU READY TO OPEN TOMORROW?
I THINK SO.
I AM SORRY,
BUT I'VE HAD
THIS FLORIDA TRIP
PLANNED FOR A WHILE.
YOU GONNA BRING A DATE?
DAD, IT'S A NEW BUSINESS.
ONCE IT'S UP AND RUNNING,
I PROMISE, I WILL--
I WILL PAY ATTENTION
TO MY PERSONAL LIFE.
HONEY...
OBVIOUSLY, ALL YOUR HARD
WORK
AND SUCCESS AT THE AD AGENCY
ALLOWED YOU TO FINALLY WALK
AWAY
TO FULFIL YOUR DREAM
OF OPENING YOUR SHOP,
BUT...
YOU CAN'T KEEP HIDING
YOURSELF
BEHIND WORK FOREVER.
AND THAT'S...
THE END OF MY LECTURE.
GOOD.
BECAUSE ONE SERIAL-DATER
IN THE FAMILY IS ENOUGH.
TOUCHE.
YOU WERE RIGHT,
ANNABELLE.
THIS IS THE PERFECT DRESS.
WHO'S THAT?
[ANNABELLE]: OH, THAT'S
HERA.
SHE WAS THE GREEK GODDESS
OF MARRIAGE.
SHE WAS MARRIED TO ZEUS,
WHICH MAKES HER
THE QUEEN OF ALL WIVES.
I FOUND HER
ON MY LAST THRIFT STORE RUN.
AND THIS IS THE PERFECT HAT.
OH, I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
EVERY TIME
I WALKED INTO "EVER AFTER,"
I WOULD BREAK OUT INTO HIVES
JUST LOOKING AT THE TULLE.
WELL, I'M HAPPY
TO REPORT
THAT HERE, AT "SO YOU SAID
YES,"
WE ARE 100% TULLE-FREE.
I JUST HOPE
I ACTUALLY GET TO WEAR IT.
OH, REMEMBER,
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS,
OKAY?
JUST BECAUSE YOUR FIANCE
WANTS TO SPEND YOUR
HONEYMOON
SOMEWHERE HE CAN GOLF
DOES NOT MEAN
THAT YOUR MARRIAGE
IS HEADED DOWNHILL
BEFORE IT'S EVEN STARTED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M DOING THE
GLASS-HALF-EMPTY
THING AGAIN.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
YOUR CHILDHOOD.
IS THAT WHEN THAT STARTED?
MAYA'S GETTING
HER MASTER'S
IN PSYCHOLOGY,
AND THAT IS WHY
RATHER THAN PRACTICING
ON THE CUSTOMERS.
[DOOR CREAKS]
EXCUSE ME?
OH! UH,
SHE'S IN THE DRESSING ROOM.
IT'S REALLY GOOD THAT
YOU DIDN'T SEE HER IN HER
DRESS.
BY THE WAY, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO NIX THE GOLFING
ON YOUR HONEYMOON.
WELL, I JUST CAME IN--
OBVIOUSLY, THE KEY
TO A GOOD RELATIONSHIP
IS BOTH PARTNERS
MAINTAINING INDIVIDUAL
INTERESTS
IN ADDITION
TO WHAT THEY SHARE TOGETHER,
BUT IN THIS CASE,
SHE'S FEELING A LITTLE...
FRAGILE.
-I THOUGHT THAT MAYBE--
I WOULD THINK ABOUT--
...THINGS THAT YOU COULD
DO TOGETHER ON YOUR
HONEYMOON
RATHER THAN PLAYING A ROUND
OF 24 HOLES ON THE GOLF
COURSE.
-[CAR HORN HONKING]
-[GASPS] MY CAR!
THAT'S WHY I CAME IN.
IF YOU HURRY,
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO FIND
OUT
WHICH IMPOUND LOT
HE'S TAKING IT TO...
[SIGHS SYMPATHETICALLY]:
AHH...
SORRY ABOUT YOUR CAR.
I'M SAM.
IT WAS NICE
LISTENING TO YOU,
BUT I'VE GOT A VERY
IMPORTANT MEETING,
WITH A GOLF BALL.
OH, AND BY THE WAY?
A ROUND IS 18, NOT 24.
OOPS. SORRY, LADIES.
[♪♪♪]
HI, STEVEN. HEY!
-HI, SAM!
-OH, HI!
IF IT ISN'T WOODSON FALLS'
MOST TALENTED GARDENER.
YOU KNOW, NO ONE
CAN GROW AN ORCHID
LIKE YOU, BEVERLY.
AW, YOU'RE
A CHARMER, SAM.
SO HOW WAS YOUR DATE
WITH PATRICIA
JENKINS'S NIECE?
IT WAS GOOD.
SHE'S VERY NICE.
ISN'T THAT A GOOD THING?
IT IS.
SHE JUST ISN'T FOR ME.
ARE YOU
GOING GOLFING?
I AM, AND I GOTTA RUN.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
WELL, IF-IF
YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED
IN PATRICIA'S NIECE,
CAN I FIX YOU UP
WITH MY DENTIST?
[LAUGHING]
OKAY, OUR FACEBOOK "LIKES"
ARE UP TO 775.
THE MASSEUSE IS SET
FOR 10:00 A.M. ON MONDAY.
THE GROUPON
GOES OUT TOMORROW,
AND YOU ARE
GUESTBLOGGING
ON THEMODERNBRIDE.COM
ALL NEXT WEEK.
OH, THE TRAFFIC ON THAT
SITE'S
AMAZING, BY THE WAY.
[BUSTLING BACKGROUND
CHATTER]
HI. DO YOU MIND
IF I SIT HERE?
THERE'S
NO OTHER TABLES.
THANKS.
[CLEARS HIS THROAT]
YOU KNOW,
YOU COULD'VE
STOPPED ME
THE OTHER DAY,
RATHER THAN LET ME
JUST CARRY ON,
LIKE A FOOL.
OH, YEAH,
I WOULD HAVE,
BUT I JUST COULDN'T
GET A WORD IN.
[CHUCKLES DRYLY]
HERE, HAVE SOME.
CONSIDER IT
A PEACE OFFERING.
WELL, THANKS,
BUT I DON'T EAT SWEETS.
WELL, IT'S FRUIT.
IT'S JUST IN
THE FORM OF A CAKE.
[♪♪♪]
I'LL BUY YOU
ANOTHER ONE.
IT'S JUST THE STRESS
OF OPENING A BUSINESS.
[♪♪♪]
"MATRIMONY" IS "T-R-I,"
NOT "T-R-E."
OH, WELL, THAT HAPPENS TO
BE THE FRENCH SPELLING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY,
YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE THE KIND
THAT WOULD GO IN FOR ALL
THAT.
MATRIMONY?
NO, I DON'T.
NO. I MEANT AIDING AND
ABETTING
BRIDEZILLAS.
AW, THANKS.
I JUST, YOU KNOW,
LOVE BEING JUDGED
BY COMPLETE STRANGERS.
I HATE TO
BURST YOUR BUBBLE,
BUT I OPENED MY SHOP
FOR THE NON-BRIDEZILLAS.
I HELP BRIDES FIND A DRESS
THAT REFLECTS WHO THEY ARE
RATHER THAN WHAT A MAGAZINE
TELLS THEM THEY SHOULD BE.
THAT'S VERY NOBLE OF YOU.
YOUR WEDDING
DOESN'T NEED TO BE
AN IDEALIZED PRESENTATION
OF WHO YOU ARE
WHILE TOTALLY CUTTING OFF
THE CIRCULATION IN YOUR
TOES.
IT'S SIMPLY THE FIRST DAY
OF THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
WITH REALLY GOOD FOOD
AND PROFESSIONAL
MAKEUP.
MM! WELL.
BUT THERE'S AN INHERENT
FLAW IN YOUR ARGUMENT.
WHAT'S THAT?
THAT, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
ALL WOMEN--
NO MATTER HOW ACCOMPLISHED,
HOW INDEPENDENT--
ONCE THAT ENGAGEMENT RING
GOES
ON THAT FINGER,
THEY GO BRIDEZONKERS.
"BRIDEZONKERS."
CUTE. DID YOU COME UP
WITH THAT YOURSELF?
NO, I SAW IT
ON URBANDICTIONARY.COM.
-ARE YOU MARRIED?
-NO.
-BEEN MARRIED?
UH-UH.
-HAVE A SISTER?
-ONLY CHILD.
AH. OKAY.
NOW I SEE WHERE
ALL OF YOUR WEDDING
EXPERIENCE
COMES FROM.
BELIEVE ME, I HAVE
A LOT MORE EXPERIENCE
THAN I'D LIKE TO ADMIT.
AND WATCHING SAY YES
TO THE DRESS DOESN'T COUNT.
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO MY OFFICE.
BUT, UH, GOOD LUCK
WITH EVERYTHING.
AND, UM, IF, UH...
IF ONE OF YOUR CLIENTS
SUES, FOR, YOU KNOW,
A SLIPPED DISK
FROM SEQUIN OVERLOAD,
GIVE ME A CALL.
WE HAPPEN TO BE
A SEQUIN-FREE ESTABLISHMENT,
SO...
[♪♪♪]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[SIGHS] HEY, MOM.
NO, I DID NOT TELL BEVERLY
THAT SHE COULD SET ME UP
WITH HER DENTIST.
BUT EVEN IF SHE DID,
WHAT WOULD BE WRONG WITH
THAT?
I KNOW YOU JUST WANT
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME,
AND, MOM, AT THIS MOMENT,
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME
IS TO GET BACK TO WORK,
SO I'LL HAVE TALK TO YOU
SOON,
OKAY?
THANKS FOR THE CALL.
BYE, MOM.
OKAY.
YEP. BYE, MOM.
[♪♪♪]
[ANNABELLE]:
WELL, WHAT IF
WE RUN OUT OF FOOD
FOR THE PARTY?
UNLESS AN ENTIRE
SMALL COUNTRY CRASHES IT,
WE'RE GOOD.
[PHONE ALERT CHIMES]
OH. IT'S FROM THAT LAWYER
GUY.
HOW'D HE GET
MY EMAIL?
"THANKS FOR THE INVITE
TO YOUR PARTY.
"UNFORTUNATELY,
I HAVE A PRIOR COMMITMENT,
BUT IF I DON'T GET OUT TOO
LATE,
I'LL TRY AND STOP BY."
I-I DIDN'T INVITE HIM
TO THE PARTY.
I FOUND HIS CARD
ON YOUR DESK.
WELL, I'M JUST TRYING TO
FOSTER
GOOD RELATIONSHIPS
WITH OUR NEIGHBORS.
OKAY, MAYA.
TRY APPLYING TO THE
AMBASSADOR
POSITION SOMEPLACE ELSE.
YOU CAN'T AVOID DATING
FOREVER.
I'M NOT AVOIDING ANYTHING.
I'M STARTING A BUSINESS,
SO ALL OF MY ENERGY
HAS TO GO TOWARDS THAT.
YEAH, AND BACK WHEN
YOU WERE A STAR
AT THE AD AGENCY,
ALL YOUR ENERGY
WENT TOWARDS THAT.
IT'S LIKE YOU CAN'T WAIT
TO BE 70 ALREADY,
SO YOU'LL HAVE A VALID
EXCUSE
NOT TO DATE.
ALRIGHT, YOU DON'T HAVE
YOUR PSYCHOLOGY DEGREE YET,
SO, FOR NOW,
STICK TO SHOES.
AND SPEAKING OF SHOES...
[BACKGROUND CHATTER]
[♪♪♪]
IS THIS
A BRIDAL SALON
OR IS IT
A NIGHTCLUB?
HEY! THANKS
FOR STOPPING BY.
HE'S ADORABLE.
YOU SHOULD
COME BACK ON MONDAY.
I JUST SNAGGED A DRESS
ON EBAY LAST WEEK
THAT WOULD BE FABULOUS ON
YOU.
ACTUALLY, EDWARD
IS MY ASSISTANT--
OH!
AND EVEN IF
HE WERE MY FIANCE--
WHICH I'M DEFINITELY NOT.
I--
W-WHAT I MEAN IS--
I JUST...
I'M SURE THAT ONE
OF THE DRESSES
THAT I CARRY
IN MY BRIDAL SALON,
"EVER AFTER," WOULD
SUIT ME JUST FINE.
WOW! IT'S SO GREAT TO MEET
YOU.
IT'S LOVELY
TO MEET YOU.
A LITTLE "WELCOME TO
THE NEIGHBORHOOD" GIFT.
THAT IS
SO NICE OF YOU.
I DON'T REALLY EAT SWEETS,
BUT THEY LOOK DELICIOUS.
IT'S JUST AN HONOR
TO MEET
A FELLOW FEMALE BUSINESS
OWNER,
NOT ONLY ONE
WHO HAS BEEN SO SUCCESSFUL--
-OH, YOU'RE VERY KIND.
-I MEAN--
IT'S JUST AMAZING YOU KEEP
GOING
AND GOING AND GOING...
THAT DIDN'T COME OUT RIGHT.
I BETTER GET BACK TO
HOSTESSING,
BUT YOU KNOW, LET'S GET
TOGETHER
FOR COFFEE SOMETIME.
OF COURSE.
THANKS AGAIN!
I GIVE THIS PLACE
THREE MONTHS, TOPS.
NO COMPETITION.
OH, YEAH.
I LOVE THIS PLACE!
YOU ARE SO LUCKY
YOU JUST GOT ENGAGED.
IT MAKES ME
WANT TO GET MARRIED
ALL OVER AGAIN.
IT'S SO GREAT TO FINALLY
HAVE
A BRIDAL SALON IN TOWN
THAT'S NOT SO OLD-FASHIONED.
I KNOW.
"EVER AFTER" IS SO...
OUR MOTHERS' GENERATION.
[YOUNG BRIDE]: RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, SOME BRIDES
LIKE OLD-FASHIONED.
-EDWARD?
-YES?
NOT HELPING.
RIGHT.
[MAYA]: MAYBE SAM
GOT THE DATE WRONG.
MAYBE HE THOUGHT
THE PARTY WAS TOMORROW.
AND MAYBE YOU SHOULD LET IT
GO
AND WE SHOULD GET OUT OF
HERE
AND GO TO DINNER.
PLUS, EVEN IF
I WERE INTERESTED IN HIM--
WHICH, FOR THE RECORD,
I AM NOT--
HE WOULD NEVER GO
FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME.
-WHY?
-FIRST OF ALL--
...HE'S A LAWYER,
WHICH MEANS
THAT HE IS ALL LEFT-BRAIN--
ANALYTICAL, LOGICAL...
WHILE I, ON THE OTHER HAND,
AM ALL RIGHT-BRAIN.
OH! THAT'S WHY YOU WEAR
OPEN-TOED SANDALS IN THE
RAIN,
BECAUSE YOU'RE ILLOGICAL!
NO.
BECAUSE SOMETIMES
IT'S THE ONLY SHOE
THAT WORKS FOR THE OUTFIT.
AND SECOND OF ALL,
I'M NOT HIS TYPE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
I-I DON'T KNOW,
I CAN JUST TELL.
HE PROBABLY DATES WOMEN
WHO ARE THOROUGHBREDS,
WHERE I, ON THE OTHER HAND,
AM A MIXED-BREED RESCUE.
LOOKS LIKE I'M A LITTLE
LATE.
[MAYA]: NOT AT ALL.
HOW ABOUT A DRINK?
NO, THANKS,
BUT HOW WAS THE PARTY?
GREAT!
BUT ACTUALLY,
I WAS JUST GETTING READY
TO TAKE MAYA OUT TO DINNER
TO CELEBRATE.
[MAYA]: UH...
IF SAM DOESN'T HAVE ANY
PLANS,
THEN MAYBE HE CAN JOIN YOU
FOR DINNER.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
AS SOMEONE
WHO'S LIVED HERE FOREVER,
IT IS MY CIVIC DUTY
TO WELCOME A NEWCOMER TO
TOWN.
OKAY.
IN AN ATTEMPT TO BECOME
INVOLVED
IN MY COMMUNITY,
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD
ALLOW YOU TO DO THAT.
GREAT! BYE, GUYS.
GOODNIGHT.
[MAYA WALKS OUT]
I KNOW A GREAT RIB PLACE
THAT'S NOT TOO FAR FROM
HERE.
I'M A VEGETARIAN.
HOW ABOUT ITALIAN?
GINO'S HAS
THE BEST FETTUCCINE ALFREDO
THIS SIDE OF ROME.
I'M OFF GLUTEN AT THE
MOMENT.
HOW ABOUT YOU CHOOSE?
WELL, WE COULD STAY HERE.
I'VE GOT SOME GOOD
DALAI LAMA MOMOS.
WHAT ARE THESE
CALLED AGAIN?
DALAI LAMA MOMOS.
THEY'RE TIBETAN.
WITH A NAME LIKE THAT,
THEY-- THEY'D HAVE TO BE.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN?
NO. BUT I WOULD LOVE TO GO.
OH. TRY
ONE OF THESE.
MM! IT'S GOOD!
ALSO TIBETAN?
NOPE. IT'S A SAMBUSA.
IT'S A TRADITIONAL
ETHIOPIAN APPETIZER.
WOW. THIS IS QUITE
THE INTERNATIONAL MEAL.
THANK YOU FOR THIS.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
MINIM AYDEL.
THAT'S "YOU'RE WELCOME"
IN ETHIOPIAN.
I CAN'T SAY I'VE EVER MET
SOMEONE WHO KNOWS ETHIOPIAN.
OH, I DON'T.
I JUST LEARNED IT ON
ONE OF THOSE COMPUTER
SCREENS
IN AN ELEVATOR.
BUT YOU'D LIKE TO GO ONE
DAY?
OUI.
THAT'S "YES" IN FRENCH.
WOW.
WHO KNEW VEGETARIAN FOOD
COULD BE THAT GOOD?
I'M GLAD YOU LIKED IT.
NEXT TIME WE'LL ACTUALLY
GO TO THE TIBETAN PLACE.
NOT THAT THERE IS
GONNA BE A NEXT TIME.
I'D LOVE TO TRY
THE TIBETAN PLACE.
OH. THAT'S
A GORGEOUS CAR.
[SAM, SURPRISED]:
YOU LIKE IT?
IT'S ACTUALLY MINE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, IT IS.
REALLY? HUH!
WHAT'S "HUH"?
I DON'T KNOW...
YOU JUST DIDN'T
STRIKE ME
AS A "VINTAGE"
KIND OF GUY.
HA, WELL,
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT,
BUT IT'S NOT VINTAGE,
IT'S CLASSIC.
WHICH IS ANOTHER WORD
FOR VINTAGE.
NOT EXACTLY.
WHEN I THINK "VINTAGE,"
I THINK OLD AND DUSTY,
PAST ITS PRIME--
YOU KNOW,
THAT KIND OF THING.
I HAPPEN
TO LOVE VINTAGE.
IT'S KIND OF
MY WHOLE THING.
OH. CAN WE
CHANGE THE TOPIC
SO I DON'T PUT MY FOOT
EVEN FARTHER
INTO MY MOUTH?
YES. YES.
HEY, DID YOU KNOW
THAT YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO TOUCH
THE TOP OF
A TIBETAN PERSON'S HEAD?
THAT IT'S CONSIDERED
A SACRED PART OF THEIR BODY?
IS THAT EVEN MORE
ELEVATOR TRIVIA?
NO. I SAW IT
IN A DOCUMENTARY.
I WATCH A LOT OF THEM.
NOT THAT I, LIKE,
STAY HOME EVERY NIGHT
WATCHING THEM.
I TOTALLY HAVE
A SOCIAL LIFE.
I JUST...
I REALLY ENJOY THEM.
SO. I'M SORRY.
WERE YOU
SAYING SOMETHING?
UH, RIGHT, YEAH, WHAT
I WAS ABOUT TO SAY--
DO YOU SEE THAT?
THAT IS THE ROOT
OF CRASH-DIETING
AND UNREALISTIC EXPECTATIONS
ABOUT ROMANCE.
OH, I DON'T THINK
I'D GO THAT FAR.
THE OWNER CAME
BY THE STORE TODAY,
FOR THE PARTY.
TALK ABOUT FROSTY.
WHEN I SUGGESTED
THAT WE GET TOGETHER,
SHE LOOKED LIKE
SHE'D RATHER GET A ROOT
CANAL.
MAYBE SHE'S JUST
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
WHO TAKES A WHILE
TO WARM UP.
HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE
AN ICEBERG TO MELT?
I'M SORRY.
I GET CARRIED AWAY.
I REALLY AM-- AND I
COMPLETELY
INTERRUPTED YOU.
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I ALREADY FORGOT.
[♪♪♪]
MORNING, MOM.
DARLING. I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU IN AGES.
WELL, I WAS HERE
FOR TEA ON TUESDAY.
BEFORE WE EAT,
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
AND I CAN'T
WAIT TO HEAR IT.
BUT BEFORE YOU BEGIN,
HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS NEW BRIDAL SALON
THAT'S OPENED?
WELL, IF YOU CAN
CALL IT THAT.
"SO YOU SAID SOMETHING."
ACTUALLY, THAT'S--
YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT
THE OWNER IS TRYING TO DO.
IT'S ALL VINTAGE!
[LAUGHS]
I MEAN, WHAT BRIDE IS GOING
TO
WANT TO WEAR SHOES
THAT HAVE BEEN ON
SOMEBODY ELSE'S FEET?
WELL, IF THEY'VE ONLY
BEEN WORN ONCE,
I DON'T SEE--
I SWEAR, SHE TREATS
THE WHOLE PROCESS
OF GETTING MARRIED
LIKE IT'S SUPPOSED TO
BE FUN OR SOMETHING.
IMAGINE THAT.
SHE MUST BE
FROM THE CITY.
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT HER.
SO, WHAT WAS IT
THAT YOU WANTED TO TELL ME?
[STAMMERS]
ACTUALLY, I THINK IT CAN
WAIT.
YOUR DATE?
[STAMMERS]
OH, IT ISN'T A DATE.
IT'S AN OUTING.
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS
A "DATE"
HERE ON PLANET EARTH.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING
ON YOUR "OUTING"?
HE SAID ME TO CHOOSE
SOMETHING I LIKED,
SO I'M TAKING HIM
ON MY THRIFT STORE RUN.
YOU'RE KIDDING,
RIGHT?
THAT'S LIKE THE LEAST
DATE-LIKE THING EVER.
RIGHT.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT A DATE.
[DOOR OPENS, DRESS RUSTLES]
OH! LET ME SEE YOU.
[GUSHES]
OH, MY GOODNESS.
COME HERE.
LOOK AT YOURSELF.
[SHOP DOOR CREAKS]
-HI.
WOW!
WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE
TO SEE THE GROOM'S FACE
WHEN YOU WALK DOWN THAT
AISLE.
WELL, I HOPE
I'M APPROPRIATELY DRESSED
FOR WHEREVER WE'RE GOING?
YOU'RE A LITTLE
OVERDRESSED,
BUT YOU'LL BE ALRIGHT.
[♪♪♪]
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HAVE YOU CHANGED YOUR
POSITION
ON THE WHOLE VINTAGE THING?
WELL, YOU DEFINITELY
GET POINTS FOR CREATIVITY.
I CAN'T SAY I'VE SPENT
TIME WITH A WOMAN
IN A THRIFT STORE BEFORE.
WELL, WHEN I ASKED YOU
WHAT YOU WANTED TO DO,
YOU SAID
CHOOSE SOMETHING I ENJOY,
SO.
OH!
NOW, THIS IS A WEDDING
DRESS.
WHICH PART?
THE RIP ON THE SIDE,
OR THE MISSING BUTTONS?
WELL,
WHAT I SEE IS...
A WOMAN ENTERING
A GRAND BALLROOM.
1942.
A SOLDIER COMES UP
AND ASKS HER TO DANCE.
AND AS THEY DANCE,
HE TELLS HER
HE'S ABOUT TO SHIP OUT,
BUT THAT, WHEN HE COMES
BACK,
HE'S GOING TO FIND HER
AND MARRY HER.
AND DOES HE?
HE DOES.
WELL, I'M ALL FOR HISTORY
AND TRADITION,
BUT ALL THE BRIDES I'VE SEEN
LIKE "SHINY," NOT DULL.
THAT, MY FRIEND...
IS NOT DULL.
"I WILL LOVE YOU
UNTIL THE END OF TIME."
YOU MAY HAVE A KNACK
FOR TREASURE-HUNTING AFTER
ALL.
I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THAT.
HI, SAM!
I THOUGHT
THAT WAS YOUR CAR OUTSIDE!
OH, WE CAN GET ANYTHING
PAST YOU, CAN WE, BEVERLY?
UH, THIS IS
ANNABELLE BLANCHE.
SHE JUST--
...JUST OPENED
THAT NEW BRIDAL SALON
ON MAIN STREET,
BETWEEN THE TAILOR
AND THE STATIONERY STORE.
HOW NICE
TO MEET YOU.
NICE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
WELL, AREN'T YOU JUST
LOVELY?
WHAT AN INTERESTING VENUE
FOR A DATE.
OH, IT'S NOT A DATE.
IT'S AN OUTING.
[BEVERLY]: OH!
OH, SAM, I CAN JUST IMAGINE
WHAT YOUR MOTHER MUST HAVE
THO--
IT'S REALLY LOVELY
TO SEE YOU, BEVERLY.
ENJOY YOUR DAY,
HUH? OKAY.
SAM, IF IT'S
JUST AN OUTING,
MY DENTIST
IS STILL AVAILABLE.
OKAY.
SO THAT WAS FUN.
IT WAS.
AND DON'T THINK
I'M GOING TO FORGET
THAT I OWE YOU
A MUFFIN
AND A BROWNIE.
[LAUGHS] OH,
BELIEVE ME, I WON'T.
SO...
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO GET TOGETHER AGAIN?
MAYBE THIS TIME,
I COULD PICK?
OKAY.
I MEAN, OKAY,
IN THE INTEREST
OF EXPANDING MY HORIZONS.
[CHUCKLES]
-I BETTER GO.
-OKAY.
-GOODNIGHT.
DOES THAT
SEEM STRAIGHT?
YEP! PERFECT. NICE.
[ANNABELLE]: WOW!
THAT LOOKS PERFECT!
-NICE.
-GOOD IDEA.
[♪♪♪]
[SCOFFS]
IT'S "COUNTY," NOT
"COUNTRY".
[SHE SIGHS IRATELY]
[♪♪♪]
IT'S "ESPRESSO,"
NOT "EXPRESSO"!
[♪♪♪]
[ANNABELLE]: GOLF. WOW.
I'M HERE PRETTY MUCH
EVERY CHANCE I CAN GET.
I'M NOT SURE
I'M DRESSED FOR IT.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
DON'T I NEED GOLF SHOES?
[LAUGHS] NO.
YOU CAN GO BAREFOOT.
OKAY. STICK?
BALL? I GOT THIS.
[SAM CHUCKLING]
OKAY.
OKAY, NO,
HOLD IT, HOLD IT.
I'M SORRY, BUT I'M NOT GONNA
LET YOU OFFEND THE GOLF
GODS.
OKAY, WHAT
I WANT YOU TO DO...
IS JUST POSITION YOURSELF
RIGHT ALONG THE PUTTER.
JUST LIKE THAT. OKAY?
-LIKE THAT?
-YEAH.
EYELASH.
MAKE A WISH.
OH. RIGHT.
OKAY.
I'M PRETTY SURE
YOU ONLY GET ONE WISH.
I KNOW.
I'M JUST BEING SPECIFIC.
DONE.
I DID. IS THAT OKAY?
YES.
GOOD. BECAUSE IF IT'S OKAY,
I'D LIKE TO TRY IT AGAIN
SOMETIME.
I THINK
THAT COULD BE ARRANGED.
OKAY!
BACK TO WORK.
-YES.
-SWING AWAY.
OKAY.
[HOPEFUL GASP]
GO IN THE HOLE.
OH, GO IN THE HOLE!
[LAUGHS] WOW!
-HEY!
-NICE WORK!
[NEARBY WOMAN]: WOW!
SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
I USED TO BEAT HIM
ALL THE TIME.
[CHUCKLES]
HILLARY.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE BACK IN TOWN.
PROBABLY BECAUSE
I HAVE NOT RUN
INTO YOUR MOTHER YET.
HOW LONG
ARE YOU BACK FOR?
ACTUALLY,
I'VE MOVED BACK.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF
GETTING DIVORCED.
OH, SORRY
TO HEAR THAT.
UH, ANNABELLE,
THIS IS HILLARY JACKSON,
AN OLD COLLEGE
FRIEND OF MINE.
HILLARY, THIS IS
ANNABELLE BLANCHE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I LOVE THE HAT.
THANK YOU.
I BURN EASILY.
THAT'S WHY I WEAR A HAT.
REMEMBER?
WE WENT TO CANCUN
AND YOU GOT SUN POISONING
ON THE FIRST DAY!
OH! SO YOU GUYS
ARE REALLY GOOD FRIENDS?
YEAH, WELL,
WE DATED FOR--
WE DATED
FOR THREE YEARS.
AH.
REALLY, REALLY
GOOD FRIENDS.
YEAH, WELL, THAT WAS--
A LONG TIME AGO.
-NOW WE'RE JUST--
-[OVERLAPPING]: ...FRIENDS.
WOW. YOUR FRIENDS
ARE SO PUT TOGETHER,
AND TALL...
WITH SUCH WHITE TEETH.
[LAUGHING]
AND ACTUALLY OWN GOLF SHOES.
OH!
ANNABELLE JUST
MOVED INTO TOWN.
SHE JUST OPENED UP
A BRIDAL SALON.
INTERESTING!
I BET YOUR MOTHER--
WHICH YOU SHOULD
DEFINITELY
CHECK OUT
NEXT TIME YOU GET MARRIED.
AND, UM, YOU KNOW,
YOU PROBABLY HAVE
A TON OF PEOPLE
YOU WANT TO SAY
HELLO TO, RIGHT?
SO WE SHOULD
PROBABLY LET YOU GO.
OKAY!
WELL, NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE MEETING YOU.
[♪♪♪]
ON THE COMPUTER?
YES.
I'M TRYING TO FIND
THE "SO YOU SAID YES" PAGE
ON FRIENDBOOK,
BUT NOTHING IS COMING UP.
THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S CALLED FACEBOOK.
UH, MAY I?
I'LL LOOK THAT UP
FOR YOU.
[KEYS CLACK]
RIGHT THERE.
"MASSEUSE MONDAY?"
WHAT ON EARTH IS THAT?
THEY'RE OFFERING A 15-MINUTE
CHAIR MASSAGE TO THEIR
CLIENTS.
SMART IDEA.
OR NOT.
WHO NEEDS IT, RIGHT?
SPEAKING OF WHICH--
HAVE YOU COME UP
WITH ANY NEW
MARKETING STRATEGIES,
I HAVE.
I WAS THINKING WE OFFER
A FREE TRIP TO HAWAII.
AS A HONEYMOON, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, WELL,
I WAS THINKING OF
SOMETHING MORE
ALONG THE LINES
OF A CANDLE WITH
A $100 PURCHASE.
THAT'S A--
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
WELL, I WAS ALSO THINKING
THAT WE COULD TEAM UP
WITH AN ANIMAL SHELTER.
WE OFFER A FREE PUPPY
WITH EVERY DRESS PURCHASE.
-A PUPPY?
-OH, YEAH.
FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE
PLANNING A WEDDING?
OH, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT THEY NEED.
SO MAYBE NOT A GREAT IDEA.
AND WHAT ABOUT
OUR FRIENDBOOK PAGE?
"FACEBOOK."
WE ALREADY HAVE
35 FOLLOWERS.
AND THEY HAVE 775.
WOW.
THEY REALLY LIKE YOU.
USUALLY, THEY HISS
AT STRANGERS--
-THANK YOU.
-AND BITE.
AWW. SO JUST THE TWO?
YEAH.
WELL, THERE WAS
ANOTHER ONE I WAS FOSTERING
FROM THE SHELTER
WHERE I VOLUNTEER,
BUT MAYA SAID
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO HAVE
MORE THAN TWO CATS
BEFORE I'M 65.
AFTER THAT, ANYTHING GOES.
SO WHAT'S ON THE MENU?
WELL, I THOUGHT
THAT WE WOULD MAKE IT
A MIDDLE EASTERN NIGHT.
SO WE ARE GOING TO START
WITH
TURKISH RED LENTIL STEW
WITH MINT,
FOLLOWED BY MOROCCAN
CHICKEN POT PIE WITH
COUSCOUS,
AND, FOR DESSERT,
PURPLE RICE PUDDING
WITH ROSEWATER DATES.
WOW. YOU ARE A GOURMET COOK.
NO, NOT AT ALL.
IT'S ACTUALLY THE FIRST TIME
I'VE MADE ANY OF IT.
YEAH. [SNIFFS]
[BOTH SNIFFING]
AND... APPARENTLY
THE LAST.
[SMOKE ALARM BEGINS]
-I'M GONNA GO CHECK ON IT.
-OKAY.
[ALARM BEEPING]
OH! SHOOT!
[BOTH GROANING HUNGRILY]
WELL, THAT-THAT FEAST
YOU DESCRIBED,
I MEAN, IT SOUNDED GREAT,
BUT WHERE I'M CONCERNED,
NOTHING BEATS GINO'S PIZZA.
MM. WELL,
IT IS AMAZING.
-MM!
-I'M SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS.
THIS...
DATE?
OKAY.
THIS... DATE.
IT'S KIND OF A BUST.
WELL, AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED,
PIZZA, MOVIE, YOU.
CATS.
I, UH, I CAN'T THINK OF
ANYWHERE ELSE I'D RATHER BE.
♪ ...AND I CAN SEE
YOUR STAR SHINE BRIGHTLY ♪
♪ IT'S TIME TO LEAVE
YOUR FEARS BEHIND ♪
♪ SO GO ON AND
DON'T BE AFRAID TO SHINE...
♪
[BOTH LAUGHING]
CAN I ASK YOU
A QUESTION?
UM, WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH
THE COMMITMENT STUFF?
WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT COMMITMENT?
EVERY TIME I BRING IT UP,
YOU ALWAYS ANSWER MY
QUESTION
WITH A QUESTION.
WHY WOULD YOU...
SAY THAT?
OKAY, SCRATCH THAT.
I MEAN, I DON'T--
I DON'T GET IT.
WE PRETTY MUCH SPEND
ALL OUR FREE TIME TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW,
AND WHEN WE'RE NOT,
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU EVEN
ACCEPTED
MY ISCRABBLE REQUEST.
I KNOW, AND I'M VERY
PARTICULAR
ABOUT WHO I PLAY WITH.
YEAH! THAT'S WHAT
I'M SAYING.
SO WHY DO YOU GET
A LITTLE FREAKED OUT
WHEN I SAY THE WORD
"DATE" OR, UH...
[WHISPERS]:
..."GIRLFRIEND"?
I JUST DON'T LIKE LABELS.
OKAY, FINE.
AFTER MY MOM DIED
AND MY DAD FINALLY
STARTED DATING AGAIN,
HE ALWAYS HAD A GIRLFRIEND,
OR A WIFE...
AND AFTER A WHILE,
THEY DIDN'T SEEM VERY
SPECIAL.
YOU KNOW, SUSAN BECAME
ROBERTA,
WHO BECAME...
ANGIE, WHO BECAME COLLEEN.
IT'S JUST I'M AFRAID
IF WE PUT A LABEL ON IT,
IT'S THE BEGINNING OF THE
END.
I GET IT.
YOU KNOW, THERE MAY BE
ANOTHER WAY LOOK AT THAT.
HOW?
AS THE BEGINNING
OF THE BEGINNING.
I GUESS.
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE MAYOR'S DAUGHTER
IS GOING TO BE WEARING
ONE OF YOUR DRESSES.
WELL, OF COURSE SHE IS.
WHO ELSE WOULD SHE GO TO?
THE FAMILY'S ALWAYS BEEN
KNOWN
FOR THEIR IMPECCABLE TASTE.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
TRAFFIC WAS DREADFUL.
IT WAS. DREADFUL.
OH, LOOK. IT'S A... PARTY.
OH, CLAIRE...
I'M SO SORRY.
THERE WAS A MIXUP
WITH THE CALENDAR,
AND MY ASSISTANT
IS OFF TODAY,
SO I COULDN'T
FIND YOUR NUMBER
TO GIVE YOU A CALL.
I AM SO EMBARRASSED!
CAN WE RESCHEDULE?
WELL, WE'RE ALREADY HERE,
WE MIGHT AS WELL WAIT.
AND I'D LOVE TO SEE
ANNABELLE'S DRESSES.
SURE!
THAT'S FINE.
[♪♪♪]
THANK YOU FOR BEING
SO GRACIOUS, BOTH OF YOU.
SO... I KNOW YOU STUDIED
IN JAPAN IN COLLEGE,
SO I WAS THINKING
YOU MIGHT LIKE
THIS KIMONO-STYLE DRESS.
OHH! I LOVE IT!
GREAT!
AND I'M NOT A WEDDING
PLANNER,
BUT I DO KNOW THAT THERE IS
A BEAUTIFUL ZEN MONASTERY
ABOUT AN HOUR AWAY FROM
HERE.
MY FIANCE AND I MET
IN A BUDDHIST
MEDITATION CLASS.
I KNOW.
I READ IT ONLINE.
AND I WAS THINKING
YOU COULD KEEP WITH--
UH, THE JAPANESE THEME GOING
FOOD-WISE,
WITH SOMETHING LIKE
SASHIMI WITH BURDOCK ROOT--
-AND CREME FRAICHE
APPETIZERS.
-YEAH!
JAPANESE? [CHUCKLES]
FOR THE FIRST FAMILY
OF OUR TOWN.
HOW PATRIOTIC.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE
SOME OF YOUR CHOICES.
OF COURSE.
[SNAP]
YUP. LET ME JUST GET THAT.
NOW, I WAS THINKING
OF SOMETHING A LITTLE
MORE...
DOWNTON ABBEY.
OH! I LOVE THAT SHOW.
CAN'T YOU JUST IMAGINE
ONE OF THE CHARACTERS
WEARING SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
OH, DEFINITELY!
NOW, I'M NOT
A WEDDING PLANNER EITHER,
BUT WHEN I IMAGINE YOU
IN THIS DRESS,
I SEE YOU COMING DOWN
A GRAND STAIRCASE,
CARRYING
AN ENGLISH ROSE BOUQUET.
SOUNDS PERFECT!
I MEAN, THEME WEDDINGS
ARE FINE FOR SOME PEOPLE,
BUT FOR YOU--
YOUR FAMILY IS SO
RESPECTED--
WHAT BETTER WAY TO BE OF
SERVICE
THAN BY KEEPING WITH
TRADITION?
IF BY "TRADITION,"
YOU MEAN WEARING A DRESS
THAT'S
LIKE EVERYTHING ELSE OUT
THERE.
ACTUALLY, BY "TRADITION,"
I MEAN SOMETHING
THAT'S BEEN HELD IN
HIGH-ESTEEM
OVER THE YEARS
AND BECOME AN INSTITUTION.
WELL, FOR ME,
THE INSTITUTION
OF MORPHING YOURSELF
TO LOOK LIKE AN AD
IN A BRIDAL MAGAZINE
RATHER THAN BEING AUTHENTIC
SEEMS IN NEED
OF SOME RECONSIDERATION.
I CAN JUST IMAGINE
WHAT YOUR WEDDING WILL BE.
ACTUALLY, SHE DOES HAVE
A GREAT NEW BOYFRIEND, SO...
WELL, I'M SURE HE'S
CHARMING.
HE IS.
YES... WELL.
I JUST REMEMBERED
WE HAVE ANOTHER APPOINTMENT.
THANK YOU, LADIES, BOTH OF
YOU,
FOR DROPPING BY.
WE'LL BE IN TOUCH.
[♪♪♪]
I GUESS WE DON'T
NEED TO SCHEDULE
THAT COFFEE DATE
AFTER ALL.
I THINK
YOU'RE RIGHT.
[♪♪♪]
HILLARY!
-HI!
-HELLO!
I HEARD YOU WERE
BACK IN TOWN.
I'M SO SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT THE DIVORCE.
OH, LET ME GUESS.
YOU RAN INTO BEVERLY?
WELL, YOU LOOK
BEAUTIFUL, AS ALWAYS.
YOU'RE SO SWEET
TO SAY THAT.
BUT I MUST ADMIT,
WITH THIS NEW COMPETITOR
THAT'S OPENED UP,
I'M A LITTLE TIRED,
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN FORCED
TO BROADEN MY HORIZONS
WITH ALL THESE SILLY
SOCIAL NETWORK THINGS,
LIKE TWEETER.
[LAUGHS] IT'S "TWITTER."
YES. THAT.
ANYWAY, OTHER THAN THAT,
EVERYTHING IS WONDERFUL.
OH, SAM IS GONNA BE THRILLED
TO HEAR YOU'RE BACK.
ACTUALLY,
I ALREADY RAN INTO HIM.
-AND HE WAS WITH--
-YOU DID?
I WONDER WHY
HE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT?
UH, COMING UP WITH AN EXCUSE
AS TO WHY I CAN'T PLAY
BRIDGE
WITH MY MOTHER.
THE PARKERS ARE HAVING
THEIR ANNIVERSARY PARTY
AT MATTEO'S.
WHY NOT DROP BY?
-OH--
-OH, IT'D BE A GREAT
CHANCE--
...FOR YOU TO GET
BACK IN TOUCH
WITH EVERYBODY IN TOWN.
I DON'T KNOW--
YOU REMEMBER
WHERE IT IS, RIGHT?
ON MAIN STREET.
SO I'LL SEE YOU THERE,
AROUND 7:30.
CIAO-CIAO!
KNOCK-KNOCK!
I THOUGHT THE "KNOCK-KNOCK"
IS SUPPOSED TO COME
BEFORE YOU OPEN THE DOOR.
OH, YOU KNOW HOW
I HATE TO WASTE TIME,
DARLING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THIS EVENING?
-WELL, I--
-GREAT!
BECAUSE THE PARKERS ARE
HAVING
THEIR ANNIVERSARY PARTY
AT MATTEO'S, AND I'D LOVE
FOR YOU TO BE MY DATE.
ACTUALLY, I--
SO I'LL SEE YOU
THERE AT 7:30.
BYE, DARLING.
[DOOR SHUTS]
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
THIS IS LIKE THE FIRST
NIGHT IN FOREVER
THAT YOU HAVEN'T
SPENT WITH SAM.
WHAT'S HE DOING
TONIGHT?
I'M NOT SURE.
WHAT HE DOES
IS HIS BUSINESS
AND WHAT I DO
IS MINE.
IS THAT...
[♪♪♪]
MR. AND MRS. PARKER!
THEY'RE FOR YOU.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY!
YOU'RE A LUCKY MAN.
[BACKGROUND CHATTER]
SAM...
DARLING.
LOOK WHO I FOUND.
SURPRISE!
HI, HILLARY.
MOTHER, I'M SURE YOU HAD NO
IDEA
THAT SHE WAS GONNA BE HERE.
WELL, WE MIGHT HAVE
RUN INTO EACH OTHER TODAY.
MOTHER, UH,
MAY I HAVE A WORD?
EXCUSE US, HILLARY.
[INDISTINCT EXCHANGE]
IT IS SAM.
OKAY, MOTHER, LISTEN.
I KNOW YOU'VE ALWAYS
LIKED HILLARY.
I DO.
BUT THE THING IS,
I HAVE MET SOMEONE.
[QUIET WHISPERING]
I KNOW--
I CAN HEAR HIM.
SOMEONE REALLY SPECIAL.
WELL, SWEETHEART,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD ME
BEFORE?
WHO IS SHE?
WHEN DO I GET TO MEET HER?
WELL, ACTUALLY, UM--
-SHH-SHH-SHH--
-...YOU ALREADY KNOW HER.
[MAYA AND ANNABELLE
WHISPERING]
[LAUGHING]:
THERE SHE IS!
[DEFLATING SIGH]
[♪♪♪]
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT'S PERFECT.
IT LOOKS BEAUTIFUL ON YOU.
NOW REMEMBER--
AS MUCH TIME AND ATTENTION
YOU GIVE TO THE WEDDING,
GIVE 10 TIMES THAT
TO THE MARRIAGE.
[PHONE RINGS]
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS,
DON'T YOU?
IT'S HIM WASTING
A BUNCH OF MONEY
ON STUFF
HE KNOWS I WON'T EAT?
MM, ACTUALLY,
YOU WILL EAT IT.
BUT NO, THIS IS YOU
LETTING YOUR FEAR
GET IN THE WAY
OF YOUR HAPPINESS.
YOU ARE WRONG.
IT IS ME NOT WANTING TO
START
A RELATIONSHIP BASED ON
LIES.
HE DIDN'T LIE TO YOU.
HE JUST HADN'T TOLD YOU YET
WHO HIS MOTHER IS.
WHICH, SEEING
WHO HIS MOTHER IS,
AND HOW SHE FEELS ABOUT ME,
DEFINITELY FALLS
INTO THE CATEGORY OF LYING.
[SIGHS] MAYA!
I REALLY LIKED HIM.
I MEAN, MORE THAN I'VE LIKED
A GUY IN A REALLY LONG TIME.
I JUST FELT
I COULD BE MYSELF WITH HIM.
BUT OBVIOUSLY, HE DIDN'T
FEEL THE SAME WAY,
BECAUSE OTHERWISE
HE WOULD'VE TOLD ME THE
TRUTH.
PLUS, I TOTALLY TRASHED
HIS MOTHER TO HIM.
LIKE, A BUNCH OF TIMES.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
SHE WAS HIS MOTHER THEN.
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE HIM
A CHANCE TO TELL YOU THE
TRUTH?
APPARENTLY, IN THIS CASE,
MY SO-CALLED
"FEAR OF COMMITMENT"
THAT YOU'RE ALWAYS
ACCUSING ME OF
IS ACTUALLY
A GOOD THING.
SO, NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE
ME,
I'M GOING TO GO DOWNWARD-DOG
THE MEMORY OF HIM
RIGHT OUT OF MY SYSTEM.
[MEDITATIVE MUSIC PLAYS]
AS YOU BREATHE...
THINK OF
SOMETHING TO LET GO OF.
ALREADY HAVE.
ALL 6-FEET-2 OF HIM.
LET'S BEGIN.
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WE NEED TO TALK,
ANNABELLE.
[INSTRUCTOR]: LET'S DO
SOME "SUN SALUTATIONS."
YOU MIGHT AS WELL LEAVE,
BECAUSE I HAVE
NOTHING TO SAY TO YOU.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE UPSET.
EXCEPT FOR THIS.
HOW COULD YOU HAVE
LIED TO ME LIKE THAT?
-I--
-SHH-HH-HH!
I DIDN'T LIE.
I JUST HAD A DELAY
IN TELLING YOU
WHO MY MOTHER WAS.
SPOKEN LIKE A TRUE LAWYER.
NOT THAT IT MATTERS.
BECAUSE EVEN IF
YOUR MOTHER DIDN'T HATE ME,
THERE ARE A HUNDRED REASONS
WHY THIS WON'T WORK.
WHAT? NAME FIVE.
OKAY.
YOUR MOTHER HATES ME.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW YOU
WELL ENOUGH TO HATE YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
I WENT GOLFING
BAREFOOT.
THAT WAS MY SUGGESTION,
AND I'M WEARING KHAKIS TO
YOGA.
YOU DON'T LIKE VINTAGE.
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
I OWN A VINTAGE CAR.
YOU CALLED IT "CLASSIC."
YEAH, IT'S JUST ANOTHER WORD
FOR VINTAGE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHICH IS THE SALAD FORK.
IT'S THE SMALL ONE
TO THE LEFT OF THE BIG ONE,
BUT THE ONLY REASON
I KNOW THAT
IS BECAUSE
I HAD INSOMNIA ONE NIGHT
AND I STAYED UP
AND I WATCHED THE VIEW.
HILLARY.
[SIGHS]
THAT'S IN THE PAST,
ANNABELLE.
HOW MANY REASONS IS THAT?
ZERO. BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
HEARD A LEGITIMATE ONE YET.
DID I MENTION
THAT YOUR MOTHER HATES ME?
[EXASPERATED SIGH]
IT WASN'T LIKE
I WASN'T GOING TO TELL YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO...
MAKE SURE I FOUND
THE BEST WAY TO DO IT,
BECAUSE I REALLY
LIKE YOU, ANNABELLE.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT FROM
OTHER WOMEN I'VE DATED.
YOU CHALLENGE ME.
YOU HAVE OPINIONS.
YOU'RE 100% YOURSELF,
AND YOU INSPIRE ME
TO DO THE SAME.
I DO?
YOU DO.
JUST GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE.
I MEAN, I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I DON'T FEEL THIS WAY
VERY OFTEN.
YEAH, WELL, NEITHER DO I.
GOOD!
NOW THAT WE'VE SORTED THAT
OUT,
WHY DON'T THE TWO OF YOU
GIVE EACH OTHER THAT CHANCE
SOMEWHERE ELSE?
[♪♪♪]
AND MAYBE YOU COULD GIVE
MY MOTHER ANOTHER CHANCE,
TOO,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I KNOW THAT SHE COMES OFF
LIKE A HURRICANE,
BUT SHE'S MORE OF
A TROPICAL STORM.
AND SHE'S INVITED US
TO DINNER TOMORROW NIGHT.
I'M READY.
UH, WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHAT DID YOU DO
WITH MY ANNABELLE?
I THOUGHT
YOUR MOM WOULD LIKE THIS.
WELL, SHE WOULD.
BUT YOU'RE NOT HER.
WELL, I GOT THESE
AT A THRIFT STORE--
[PEARLS CLATTERING]
OHH!
GOSH. WHAT AM I THINKING?
I CAN'T DO THIS.
WHAT ABOUT ALL THOSE
HORRIBLE
THINGS I SAID ABOUT HER?
THAT'S
ALL IN THE PAST.
YOU TWO GET TO HAVE
A FRESH START NOW.
ANNABELLE, I NEED YOU
TO STOP LOOKING FOR EXCUSES
FOR THIS TO NOT WORK.
I'M NOT.
YOU ARE.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO LET
YOU.
BUT SHE HATES ME.
NO, SHE DOESN'T HATE YOU.
SHE'S JUST THREATENED
BY YOUR STORE.
SHE'LL GET OVER IT.
NOW, CAN YOU GO
GET CHANGED INTO SOMETHING
A LITTLE LESS
BANK-TELLER-ISH?
I'M STARVING.
[SAM]: BON APPETIT.
[♪♪♪]
MM...
THIS VEGETABLE GAZPACHO
IS DELICIOUS.
THANK YOU.
I THINK THE ANDOUILLE
SAUSAGE
GIVES IT A REAL KICK.
UH, MOM...
AS IT TURNS OUT, LIKE YOU,
ANNABELLE IS A REAL FAN
OF FOREIGN PLACES.
HOW WONDERFUL.
WHERE DO YOU LIKE TO GO?
WELL, I REALLY LOVE ASIA.
YOU KNOW, JAPAN,
VIETNAM, INDIA...
MY, HOW ADVENTUROUS OF YOU.
WELL, I HAVEN'T
ACTUALLY BEEN
TO ANY OF
THOSE PLACES YET.
I SORT OF PUT TRAVELING ON
HOLD
BECAUSE I WAS WORKING SO
MUCH,
BUT I'VE SEEN A LOT OF
DOCUMENTARIES ABOUT THEM.
WELL, I SUPPOSE,
FOR SOME PEOPLE...
EXPLORING A COUNTRY
THROUGH THE TELEVISION
SCREEN
IS THE NEXT BEST THING
TO ACTUALLY BEING THERE.
HER HOUSE IS AMAZING.
IT'S LIKE A SET
FROM A TRAVEL SHOW.
-WELL--
-HOW NICE.
I DO PICK UP SOME THINGS
FROM THRIFT STORES.
NOW THAT THE SHOP
IS IN THE BLACK,
I'M REALLY GOING TO MAKE
AN EFFORT TO START
TRAVELING.
WHERE DO YOU
LIKE TO TRAVEL TO?
I'M A REAL FRANCOPHILE.
MM!
I'VE SPENT A LOT OF TIME
IN PARIS.
PARIS IS AMAZING.
AH, WELL, THEN
YOU HAVE TRAVELED SOMEWHAT.
NO. I'VE JUST SEEN
A LOT OF FRENCH FILMS.
[PHONE CHIMES]
AHH. UH...
EXCUSE ME FOR JUST A SECOND.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I PROMISE.
OH!
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL
PICTURE.
IS THAT YOU AND--
SAM'S FATHER.
SO HANDSOME.
THAT WAS JUST BEFORE
HE WENT TO VIETNAM.
YOUR WEDDING DRESS IS...
BEAUTIFUL.
THAT'S SWEET OF YOU
TO SAY THAT.
LOOK AT IT.
IT WAS SO SIMPLE.
EXACTLY. THAT'S WHAT
MAKES IT SO LOVELY.
WELL, WE HAD NO MONEY BACK
THEN
FOR A REAL WEDDING.
WE WERE JUST YOUNG
AND IN LOVE,
AND WANTED TO GET MARRIED
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THAT'S WHY
I GOT INTO THIS BUSINESS.
SO THAT I COULD GIVE WOMEN
WHAT I WASN'T ABLE TO HAVE.
THEY'RE LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
[♪♪♪]
SO, THAT WASN'T
SO BAD, WAS IT?
GUESS NOT.
EXCEPT FOR
WHEN I SPILLED RED WINE
ON HER WHITE SOFA.
[CHUCKLES]
I FORGOT HOW
NERVE-WRACKING IT IS,
FALLING IN LOVE.
DID I JUST SAY "LOVE"?
YOU DID.
I THINK
THAT WORD CAME OUT
BECAUSE I WAS
THINKING ABOUT
HOW MY DRESS
IS CREAM-COLORED--
AND THAT MADE ME
THINK OF CREAMSICLES,
WHICH I HAPPEN TO LOVE.
MM. WELL,
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
YOU LOVE
CREAMSICLES, TOO?
NO. THEY GIVE ME
STOMACHACHES.
WHAT I MEANT WAS...
I LOVE YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I... THINK
I KIND OF/SORT OF
LOVE YOU BACK.
KIND OF/SORT OF?
OH, SCRATCH THAT.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
GOOD. I'M GLAD
THAT'S SETTLED.
[♪♪♪]
HEY. DAD!
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE
COMING BACK FROM FLORIDA
TILL NEXT WEEK.
WELL, A MAN CAN ONLY SIT
ON THE BEACH FOR SO LONG.
HUH? [CHUCKLES]
"BECAUSE IT'S WEDNESDAY,
WHICH MEANS I LOVE YOU
MORE THAN I DID ON TUESDAY."
SOUNDS SERIOUS.
LET'S GET SOME COFFEE.
DO YOU LOVE HIM?
YES.
GOOD!
TELL ME, ANY TALK
ABOUT THE FUTURE, OR...?
ISN'T THE WHOLE
POINT OF LIFE
TO STAY IN THE MOMENT?
LIKE YOU ALWAYS SAY,
"THERE'S NO TIME
LIKE THE PRESENT."
[HE SIGHS]
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY,
EVER SINCE
YOU WERE A LITTLE GIRL,
YOU WERE ALWAYS--
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN FEARLESS.
EVERY TIME
YOU WANTED A NEW CHALLENGE,
YOU'VE CHUCKED WHATEVER
SECURITY YOU HAD
AND YOU WENT FOR IT.
AND THOSE RISKS HAVE
ALWAYS WORKED OUT FOR YOU.
BUT WHEN
IT COMES TO LOVE...
YOU'VE ALWAYS PLAYED IT
SAFE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I HAVEN'T PLAYED AT ALL.
BE FEARLESS IN ALL
PARTS OF YOUR LIFE,
ANNABELLE.
ESPECIALLY THE ONES
THAT INVOLVE YOUR HEART.
I PROMISE YOU,
PAYOFF'S A LOT BIGGER
WHEN YOU DO.
KNOCK-KNOCK.
[SIGHING] HUH.
I GUESS MY HEARING'S GOING,
BECAUSE I DIDN'T HEAR A
KNOCK.
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
WORKING SO HARD,
NOT TO MENTION SPENDING ALL
OF
YOUR FREE TIME WITH
ANNABELLE,
SO I THOUGHT
I'D BRING YOU LUNCH.
THAT'S VERY SWEET OF YOU.
AND SO YOU DON'T GET LONELY
EATING ALL BY YOURSELF,
I BROUGHT YOU
A DINING COMPANION.
HEY, YOU.
HI, HILLARY.
SWEETHEART, AS SMITTEN
AS YOU MAY BE WITH
ANNABELLE,
I DO THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
TO REMEMBER YOUR OLD
FRIENDS,
AND I'LL BET
THAT HILLARY WOULD
APPRECIATE
A SECOND LEGAL OPINION
ON HER DIVORCE AGREEMENT.
MOM, I'M SURE
HILLARY'S ATTORNEY
IS COMPLETELY COMPETENT.
BUT DID HE GRADUATE AT THE
TOP
OF HIS CLASS LIKE YOU DID?
PROBABLY NOT.
SO, HAVE FUN!
[BOTH START LAUGHING]
OHH.
I RAN INTO HER
AT THE HAIR SALON.
I TRIED MY BEST TO STOP HER,
BUT--
AS WE KNOW,
THAT'S LIKE TRYING
TO STOP A FLOOD
WITH A PIECE
OF CARDBOARD,
BUT AT LEAST
WE'LL BE WELL-FED.
SO, SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
TO GETTING SERIOUS
WITH ANNABELLE?
WELL, I'D SAY I'VE
ARRIVED...
[SHE GASPS]
OH, WOW!
OH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
THANKS, HILLARY.
I KNOW IT'S PRETTY FAST,
BUT, UH...
BUT, HEY, WHEN YOU KNOW,
YOU KNOW.
IN MY CASE, THE KNOWING
STOPPED AFTER FIVE YEARS,
BUT I'M LOOKING TO EXTEND
THAT
THE NEXT TIME AROUND.
NOW I JUST NEED
TO FIND A WAY TO PROPOSE
THAT'S, YOU KNOW, ROMANTIC,
BUT NOT OVER-THE-TOP.
YOU KNOW,
SOMETHING THAT'S IN LINE
WITH HER WHOLE APPROACH
TO WEDDINGS.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME HELP?
AM SO GLAD YOU WERE UP
FOR MEETING FOR COFFEE.
OH, PLEASE. HAVE SOME.
I BROUGHT AN EXTRA FORK.
OH, NO, THANKS.
I DON'T EAT SWEETS.
I WAS REALLY HOPING
YOU WOULDN'T THINK
THIS WAS WEIRD,
YOU KNOW, WITH ME
AND SAM, AND THE PAST.
OH! NO. NOT AT ALL.
I MEAN, THAT WAS
FOREVER AGO.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU GUYS
STILL HAVE FEELINGS
FOR EACH OTHER. RIGHT?
OF COURSE NOT.
HE'S AN AMAZING GUY, THOUGH.
TOTAL MARRIAGE MATERIAL.
THIS MIGHT SOUND WEIRD,
BUT I'M ACTUALLY ONE OF
THOSE
WOMEN THAT FANTASIZES MORE
ABOUT THE PROPOSAL
THAN THE ACTUAL WEDDING.
OH, YES!
I LOVE THE ENGAGEMENT
STORIES FROM MY CLIENTS.
SO WHERE
WAS YOUR GUYS'S FIRST DATE?
AT A THRIFT STORE.
OH!
THAT IS SO ORIGINAL.
WELL, TECHNICALLY,
IT WASN'T A DATE.
IT WAS AN OUTING.
-THERE'S A DIFFERENCE?
-OH, YEAH.
WHERE WAS YOUR FIRST DATE
WITH SAM?
A HOT-AIR-BALLOON RIDE.
OH? WOW!
THAT'S ROMANTIC.
I GOT TOTALLY FREAKED OUT
BY THE WHOLE HEIGHTS THING.
IT WASN'T PRETTY.
-UH-HUH.
-ANYHOW, MOVING ON.
WHAT'S A TYPICAL
SATURDAY NIGHT?
WE LIKE STAY IN
AND EAT PIZZA AND WATCH
MOVIES.
THAT IS THE BEST WAY
TO SPEND A WEEKEND.
SO, UM... WHAT DID YOU AND
SAM
USED TO DO ON THE WEEKENDS?
OH...
OH, GOSH, UM...
GO SAILING?
SAILING?
MM-HMM.
LET ME GUESS.
PROBABLY AT SUNSET?
MAYBE?
UM, I'M SORRY,
I JUST REMEMBERED
SOMETHING I HAVE TO DO.
BUT THIS WAS GREAT!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT WAS REALLY ENLIGHTENING.
OKAY, THAT DID NOT
GO AS PLANNED.
[CLAPS RING CASE SHUT]
OKAY, I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
A QUESTION
AND I NEED YOU
TO TELL ME THE TRUTH.
ARE YOU STILL
INTERESTED IN HILLARY?
WHAT? WHY WOULD YOU
EVEN THINK THAT?
OH, I DON'T KNOW...
MAYBE BECAUSE I JUST SPENT
THE LAST FEW MINUTES
LISTENING TO ALL
THE WONDERFULLY ROMANTIC
THINGS YOU GUYS USED TO DO
WHEN YOU WERE TOGETHER.
-HEY, HOLD ON.
-NOT THAT I BLAME YOU.
I REALLY, REALLY DON'T.
I MEAN, YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE,
THE J. CREW VERSION
OF THE PERFECT COUPLE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING A--
HOT-AIR BALLOONS, SAILING?
AND WHAT DO I GET?
ANNABELLE...
FOR GOOD OR FOR BAD,
WHEN I AM WITH YOU,
I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I HAVE TO IMPRESS YOU,
OR WIN YOU OVER.
BUT IF YOU WANNA GO ON
A HOT-AIR-BALLOON RIDE,
LET'S GO UP IN ONE!
WHY WOULD I
WANT TO DO THAT?
AND THAT SAILBOAT
BELONGED TO MY OLD
ROOMMATES,
SO IF YOU WANT TO GO
SAILING,
THEN I HAVE TO GO RENT ONE.
WE CAN GO RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO TAKE DRAMAMINE
WHEN
I WATCH A MOVIE ABOUT
SAILING.
FOR ME...
I COULDN'T THINK OF
A MORE ROMANTIC EVENING,
SATURDAY NIGHT,
THAN EATING PIZZA
AND WATCHING A MOVIE
WITH YOU.
ESPECIALLY WHEN I GET TO
WIPE THE CHEESE OFF YOUR
CHIN.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
SO, IF YOU'RE UP FOR IT...
I THINK I'D LIKE TO SPEND
EVERY SATURDAY NIGHT
TOGETHER
FOR THE REST
OF OUR LIVES.
[GASPS]
YOU WOULD?
I WOULD.
YOU'RE SURE?
[CLOSES THE BOX]
I'M SURE.
ANNABELLE BLANCHE...
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
SAM TAYLOR...
YES, I WILL.
[♪♪♪]
HELLO.
OH! CLAIRE.
I WAS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
SO I THOUGHT I'D STOP BY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE
DOING
RESORT WEAR AS WELL.
THAT'S SMART OF YOU,
THINKING OF THE HONEYMOON,
TOO.
IT'S ACTUALLY
HER WEDDING DRESS.
I GOT IT ON ETSY.
IT'S FROM MOROCCO.
HOW INNOVATIVE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT,
IN MOROCCO,
AFTER THE WEDDING,
THE BRIDE ARRIVES
AT HER NEW HOME,
HER MOTHER-IN-LAW IS THERE
TO
WELCOME HER WITH DATES AND
MILK?
GUESS I SHOULD STOCK UP,
THEN.
WELL, I'VE NEVER CARRIED
CAFTANS IN MY STORE MYSELF,
BUT I THINK SOMETHING LIKE
THIS
WOULD GO WITH IT WELL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
IT'S NOT TOO OVERPOWERING
FOR THE DRESS?
WELL, WE'VE DECIDED
ON THIS ONE.
I PICKED IT UP
IN LITTLE INDIA.
WITH A DRESS LIKE THIS,
IT'S "GO BIG OR GO HOME."
AND YOU DECIDED
TO GO BIG.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
WITH YOUR HAIR, DEAR?
PROBABLY DEFINITELY UP?
WAVES CASCADING DOWN HER
BACK.
I THINK
I'LL JUST LEAVE YOU TO IT.
WE'RE ALL DONE.
I'M SORRY,
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE BUSY,
SO...
BUT I JUST-- I WANTED
TO TELL YOU THAT, UH,
WHILE I AM AVAILABLE
FOR WHATEVER YOU MIGHT NEED,
I KNOW THAT YOUR VISION
IS VERY STRONG,
SO I'M JUST HERE TO SUPPORT
YOU.
THANKS,
I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT I WOULD LOVE YOUR HELP.
MY MOM DIED
WHEN I WAS A KID,
AND I'VE ALWAYS ENVIED
BRIDES
WHO COME IN WITH THEIR
MOTHERS.
SO I-- I WOULD...
I WOULD REALLY LIKE THAT.
AND I'D BE HONORED.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I DO HAVE A FEW IDEAS.
[♪♪♪]
[CLAIRE]:
THIS IS THE SEATING CHART.
NOW, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT 200.
200 PEOPLE
AT THE WEDDING?
WELL, THEM,
AND HOWEVER MANY OTHERS
YOU WERE
THINKING OF INVITING.
MOM...
WE REALLY APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU HAVE DONE.
OH, HONEY,
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING!
BUT WE CAN'T EXPECT
SOMEONE AS BUSY AS YOU
TO DEVOTE SO MUCH
TIME AND EFFORT
TO OUR WEDDING.
WELL, OF COURSE YOU CAN,
SWEETHEART!
IT'S TRULY MY PLEASURE.
TECHNICALLY,
I'M BOOKED
FOR THE NEXT
YEAR AND A HALF,
BUT BECAUSE
IT'S YOU, CLAIRE,
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION.
AND I'M SO
GRATEFUL TO YOU
FOR DOING
THIS FAVOR FOR ME.
WHAT IS ALL THIS STUFF?
WELL, THIS "STUFF" HERE
IS SHRIMP-AND-LEMON SKEWERS
WITH A FETA-DILL SAUCE.
THAT SOUNDS WONDERFUL.
IT IS. SO I'LL ADD IT
TO THE APPETIZER MENU.
-AH! YES.
-BUT I'M ALLERGIC TO
SHELLFISH.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT, DEAR.
AND WHAT'S THIS?
FILET MIGNON IN
A BALSAMIC REDUCTION.
THAT'S A MUST-HAVE.
THAT IS
JUST FANTASTIC.
I'M A VEGETARIAN.
AND RIGHT OVER HERE
IS MY SPECIALTY--
FOIE GRAS WITH ARUGULA
AND CHANTERELLE MUSHROOMS.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
A GOOD IDEA. I KNOW--
AND ALSO--
IT JUST ALL LOOKS
SO ELEGANT.
[OVERLAPPING CONVERSATION]
WHENEVER I'VE BEEN TO AN
EVENT
THAT YOU'VE CATERED,
PEOPLE JUST TALK ABOUT IT
FOR DAYS AFTERWARDS.
I CAN'T SAY ENOUGH
GOOD THINGS ABOUT THIS.
SHE'S GOT ME EATING SWEETS.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
I MEAN, THIS MORNING,
SHE TOLD ME
SHE WAS TRYING TO TRACK DOWN
A DOZEN WHITE DOVES
TO RELEASE WHEN WE KISS.
WHAT DID
YOU TELL HER?
THAT I'M A BIG FAN OF BIRDS.
OH!
I'M NOT A WIMP, I SWEAR,
I JUST DON'T WANT TO
DISAPPOINT HER.
WELL, IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER,
SHE HAS ALWAYS BEEN LIKE
THIS.
IT DOESN'T.
OKAY, WELL, AT ANY RATE,
THIS YOUR DAY,
NOT HERS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I JUST NEED TO SET
SOME BOUNDARIES.
-MM-HMM.
-I CAN HANDLE HER.
-YOU'LL SEE.
-MM-KAY.
FOR FORTIFICATION.
THEY'RE BOTH ABSOLUTELY
LOVELY
ON YOU.
YOU CAN'T GO WRONG
WITH EITHER DECISION.
OKAY, WELL...
THEN LET'S GO WITH THIS ONE.
OKAY.
WAIT. NO. NO!
NO. THIS ONE.
THIS ONE, I THINK.
IT'S MY MOTHER.
SHOULD I GET THIS?
OR I COULD-- I COULD
CALL HER BACK WHEN I GET
HOME?
TAKE IT. PLEASE.
OR I GUESS COULD CALL HER
FROM THE CAR.
[SNAP]
ANNABELLE.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU TWO
HAD PLANS TODAY.
OH, WE DON'T.
I JUST CAME TO SAY HI.
OH, CLAIRE'S JUST OVER THERE
WITH A CLIENT.
GREAT. THANKS.
BRAVE WOMAN.
COME WITH ME.
EVERY TIME
I HAVE A NEW BRIDE,
I LIKE TO GIVE HER
A LITTLE PIECE OF ADVICE
ON MARRIAGE.
SO HERE'S ONE
OF MY FAVORITE PEARLS--
"LISTEN MORE THAN YOU TALK."
HMM. I LIKE THAT.
GOOD GIRL.
ANNABELLE.
HOW NICE TO SEE YOU.
IF THIS IS A BAD TIME,
I COULD COME BACK.
OH, NO. NOT AT ALL.
MY NEXT CLIENT WON'T BE HERE
FOR ANOTHER HOUR.
TO WHAT DO I OWE
THE PLEASURE?
THERE'S JUST SOMETHING
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
OKAY. WHAT IS IT?
CLAIRE--
I THINK THIS DRESS RIGHT
HERE
IS VERY NICE.
REALLY?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE SAYING THIS.
BECAUSE-- NOW, I KNOW
THAT YOUR TASTES
ARE VERY ECLECTIC,
BUT THE TRUTH IS,
AS SOON AS I SAW THIS DRESS,
I THOUGHT OF YOU.
OH, I DIDN'T--
I MEAN, I KNOW THAT YOUR
TASTE
AND YOUR VISION
IS SO SPECIFIC,
WHICH IS WHY I DIDN'T
BOTHER TO SUGGEST IT.
CLAIRE?
YES?
I GUESS
I SHOULD TRY IT ON THEN.
OH!
EDWARD?
FITTING.
[CLAIRE GASPS]
OH, IT IS--
TOO BIG?
TOO SMALL?
TOO SOMETHING?
IT'S PERFECT.
AND YOU ARE GOING TO
LOOK SO BEAUTIFUL
WALKING
DOWN THAT AISLE.
[ANNABELLE]: CLAIRE--
IT'S SAM!
EDWARD, HELP.
HE CAN'T SEE YOU
IN YOUR DRESS.
THIS ISN'T MY DRESS!
-HOW ARE YOU?
-GOOD TO SEE YOU.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
HEY. WHERE'S, UH...
WHERE'S ANNABELLE?
SHE IS IN
THE DRESSING ROOM.
-OH, OKAY.
-SWEETHEART.
I THINK THAT ANNABELLE AND I
HAVE HAD A REAL BREAKTHROUGH
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
REALLY?
SHE TOLD YOU
WHAT WAS ON HER MIND?
SHE DID.
GOOD FOR HER!
AND I AM SO GLAD.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW HAPPY IT MAKES ME.
I MEAN,
IT FEELS LIKE
WE'RE IN
A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
PLACE.
YEAH. BETWEEN A ROCK
AND A HARD PLACE.
JUST LET ME DEAL
WITH THIS CLIENT.
OKAY.
[EXHALES, RELIEVED]
MY MOTHER JUST TOLD ME
THE GREAT NEWS.
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU
FOR HAVING THE COURAGE
TO BE DIRECT
AND CONFRONT THINGS.
-SAM, I--
-I KNEW--
...IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF
TIME
BEFORE THE TWO OF YOU GOT
ALONG.
OKAY! [SIGHS]
THIS ENGAGEMENT PARTY
IS GOING TO BE GREAT.
[♪♪♪]
[PIANIST PLAYS
AS GUESTS CHAT AND CHUCKLE]
[♪♪♪]
OOH. NICE SPREAD, HUH?
HIS MOTHER
HAS OBVIOUSLY GOT CLASS.
YEAH...
[CLAIRE]:
ANNABELLE, DEAR,
I'D LIKE
TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO SOME OF OUR DEAREST
OLD FRIENDS, THE BURDETTES.
I FIND THAT
HARD TO BELIEVE.
EXCUSE ME?
WELL, YOU'RE WAY TOO YOUNG
TO HAVE OLD FRIENDS.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
NICK BLANCHE.
I'M ANNABELLE'S FATHER.
OH!
DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE THIS ONE'S MOTHER?
I AM.
SHUT THE FRONT DOOR.
I BEG YOUR PARDON?
OH, IT'S A PHRASE.
YOU KNOW.
UM... "GET OUT OF TOWN."
MAYBE IT'S A MILWAUKEE
THING.
THAT'S WHERE I'M FROM.
EVER BEEN?
I'M AFRAID
I CAN'T SAY I HAVE.
MOVING RIGHT ALONG.
SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
CLAIRE HAS TOLD US
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
SO... WHEN DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL HAVE KIDS?
CONDO OR HOUSE?
PRIVATE OR PUBLIC SCHOOL?
CHANGING YOUR NAME
OR HYPHENATING?
[PARTY CONTINUES
IN THE DISTANCE]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DOES IT LOOK
LIKE I'M DOING?
I'M STRESS-EATING.
DO YOU WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT?
-NO.
-OKAY.
DO WE KNOW WHAT STOCKS
WE'RE GOING TO INVEST IN
WITH OUR RETIREMENT FUNDS?
I CAN'T EVEN
BALANCE MY CHECKBOOK.
I THINK HE WAS JUST
MAKING CONVERSATION.
AND WHAT ABOUT
THAT COUPLES THERAPIST
WHO HANDED ME HER CARD
AND SAID "JUST IN CASE"?
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT TO HEAR
AT YOUR ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
THAT'S FREYDA.
YEAH, SHE'S ALWAYS
BEEN A LITTLE NUTS.
AND THE KICKER IS,
YOUR MOTHER,
INSTEAD OF
CHANGING THE SUBJECT,
SHE ANSWERED
THE QUESTIONS FOR ME.
OKAY.
IT'S TIME TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS.
[♪♪♪]
ANNABELLE,
LET'S START WITH YOU.
I'D LIKE YOU TO TELL MY
MOTHER
HOW YOU'VE BEEN FEELING
IN REGARDS
TO THE WEDDING PLANNING.
THE THING
OF IT IS--
NOT ME. HER.
I REALLY DO APPRECIATE
YOUR HELP WITH THE
WEDDING...
BUT I FEEL THAT THERE HAVE
BEEN
A FEW OCCASIONS
WHERE YOU'VE JUST
DISMISSED MY IDEAS
WITHOUT EVEN PRETENDING
TO CONSIDER THEM.
I'M SORRY
YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
THAT CERTAINLY
WASN'T MY INTENTION.
ANNABELLE, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SHARE SOME EXAMPLES WITH
US?
OH. YEAH.
THREE PAGES?
THERE USED TO BE FOUR.
I HAD HER EDIT IT DOWN, MOM.
NUMBER ONE.
[CHUCKLES]
WHEN WE WENT
TO GO TASTE THE CAKES,
I BROUGHT UP
THE IDEA OF TIRAMISU
AND YOU MADE A FISH FACE.
WHAT'S A FISH FACE?
YOU'RE MAKING IT RIGHT NOW.
I HAPPEN
TO LOVE TIRAMISU.
JUST NOT FOR WEDDINGS.
IT'S THE FIRST
DESSERT
SAM AND I SHARED TOGETHER.
[SAM]: IT WAS.
-NOT THAT--
-...SHE HAD MUCH
BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T
REALLY EAT SWEETS.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
I THINK IT'S WONDERFUL
YOU'RE SO CREATIVE.
OH! THANK YOU.
THAT'S THE ONLY NICE THING
YOU'VE EVER SAID TO ME.
AND IF YOU CAN
FIND CLIENTS
WHO DON'T HAVE AN ISSUE
WITH THE FACT THAT,
YEARS FROM NOW,
THEY MIGHT END UP REGRETTING
THE IMPULSIVE DECISIONS
THEY MADE
WITH REGARDS TO THE MOST
IMPORTANT DAY OF THEIR
LIVES--
"IMPULSIVE"?
BUT SEEING AS
THIS ISN'T JUST YOUR
WEDDING,
BUT ALSO MY SON'S--
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR SON'S. NOT YOURS.
WELL, THEN MAYBE
YOU OUGHT TO CONSIDER THE
FACT
THAT-- HAH!-- YOUR FLAGRANT
DISMISSAL OF TRADITION,
IT ISN'T EXACTLY A ROUSING
SIGN
OF SOMEBODY WHO'S
COMFORTABLE
WITH COMMITMENT.
NOT THAT ANYONE
COULD BLAME YOU.
I MEAN, I'M NOT A THERAPIST,
OBVIOUSLY...
BUT A FATHER
WHO'S BEEN MARRIED FOUR
TIMES--
THREE.
...MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
OKAY.
I HAVE TRIED
TO GET ALONG WITH YOU.
I HAVE HELD MY TONGUE,
I HAVE BITTEN IT,
I HAVE SMILED,
I HAVE CAVED,
I HAVE DONE ALL OF THIS
BECAUSE I LOVE YOUR SON.
BUT IT IS OBVIOUS TO ME
THAT, NO MATTER WHAT,
I WILL NEVER, EVER
BE GOOD ENOUGH FOR HIM.
[BLURTS OUT CRYING]:
SO, I'M SORRY. IT JUST--
I CAN'T DO THIS.
[♪♪♪]
THAT YOU TRY
AND STAY POSITIVE.
OH, I AM POSITIVE.
POSITIVE
MY RELATIONSHIP IS OVER.
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
I THINK I'M GOOD.
HI!
WHICH ONE OF YOU
IS ANNABELLE?
OH. YOU LOOK...
DIFFERENT THAN YOU DO
ON THE BLOGS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW EXCITED I AM
TO FINALLY GET TO
COME HERE AS A CUSTOMER.
YOUR WHOLE APPROACH
TO WEDDINGS IS AMAZING.
YEAH, WELL,
I HAVE A NEW APPROACH.
WHAT'S THAT?
DON'T DO IT.
WHAT SHE MEANS IS--
DON'T DO IT
UNTIL YOU'VE WEIGHED
ALL YOUR OPTIONS,
OF WHICH WE HAVE MANY
HERE AT "SO YOU SAID YES."
SO WHY DON'T
WE GO LOOK AT SOME?
"I WILL LOVE YOU
UNTIL THE END OF TIME."
THAT'S SO ROMANTIC!
IT IS, ISN'T IT?
THE THING IS,
PEOPLE HAVE
DIFFERENT DEFINITIONS
OF WHEN TIME ENDS.
IS IT WHEN YOU DIE?
OR...
IS IT WHEN
YOUR MOTHER-IN-LAW-TO-BE
DECIDES YOU'RE NOT
MARRIAGE MATERIAL
BECAUSE YOU DON'T LIKE
STRING QUARTETS?
I-I THINK
I'LL COME BACK LATER.
THAT WENT WELL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
YOU DON'T HAPPEN
TO SELL DINNER DATES
HERE, DO YOU?
HEY, DAD.
HEY...
YOU WASHED YOUR HAIR
SINCE WE WERE FACETIMING.
[CHUCKLES WARMLY]
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
I'M ACTUALLY WEARING PANTS
INSTEAD OF PAJAMA BOTTOMS,
SO.
HAH.
I EVER TELL YOU
THE, UH, COUCH STORY?
NO.
IT'S ABOUT
YOUR MOM AND ME.
SHE AND I GOT ENGAGED,
AND IT WAS TIME
TO MOVE IN TOGETHER,
AND WE HAD THIS
BLUE-AND-ORANGE
PLAID ULTRASUEDE COUCH
IN OUR FRATERNITY HOUSE.
YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
YOUR MOTHER'S REACTION TO IT
AS WELL.
IN FACT,
SHE HATED THE COUCH SO MUCH,
THAT WHEN SHE REALIZED
THAT I WAS PLANNING
ON MOVING IT IN
TO THE NEW APARTMENT,
WELL, WE, UH,
WE GOT INTO A BIG FIGHT.
YOU NEVER WERE
MUCH OF A DECORATOR, DAD.
WELL, THAT
MAY BE TRUE,
BUT THIS COUCH
WAS IMPORTANT TO ME.
HOWEVER, YOUR MOTHER
COULDN'T
GET PAST HOW UGLY IT WAS.
AT SOME POINT, THE FIGHT
STOPPED BEING ABOUT THE
COUCH
AND BECAME
ABOUT EVERYTHING ELSE.
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
THE WAY SHE, UH...
SHE LEFT THE CAP
OFF OF THE TOOTHPASTE,
OR I PUT THE DISHES
IN THE DISHWASHER
WITHOUT RINSING THEM FIRST.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
TO RINSE THEM,
OTHERWISE THAT DRIED FOOD
NEVER COMES OFF.
YEAH, I KNOW,
SHE SAID THAT.
SO BEFORE LONG...
WE DECIDED TO CALL THINGS
OFF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'VE NEVER HEARD THIS STORY.
NO, IT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SHARE
AT AN ANNIVERSARY TOAST.
ANYWAY, I HEADED
FOR THE DOOR,
AND I TURNED TO HER
AND I ASKED HER,
DID SHE REALLY KNOW
WHY THE COUCH
WAS SO IMPORTANT TO ME?
IT WAS BECAUSE
THE VERY FIRST TIME
I LAID EYES ON HER,
AND KNEW I WAS LOOKING AT
THE WOMAN I WAS GOING TO
MARRY,
SHE WAS SITTING ON IT.
OH, THAT'S SO ROMANTIC.
WELL, WE--
WE GOT RE-ENGAGED,
SHE LET ME KEEP THE COUCH,
AND WE RECOVERED IT WITH
A NICE NEUTRAL TAUPE
SLIPCOVER.
[GASPS] OH!
I REMEMBER THAT COUCH.
YEAH?
WELL, YOU SHOULD.
I USED TO ROCK YOU TO SLEEP
ON IT WHEN YOU WERE A BABY.
LISTEN.
I KNOW I HAVEN'T BEEN
THE BEST ROLE MODEL,
IN TERMS OF
WHAT COMMITMENT LOOKS LIKE,
BUT AS A SALESMAN...
SWEETHEART, I KNOW PEOPLE.
AND SAM...
IS GOOD PEOPLE.
AND I'M WILLING TO BET
AWAY FROM
ALL THIS WEDDING STUFF,
YOU'D FIND THAT
SHE'S A GOOD EGG AS WELL.
DAD, YOU'RE TOO MUCH.
SWEETHEART,
THIS WHOLE TRUE-LOVE THING
DOESN'T COME ALONG OFTEN,
SO BEFORE YOU LET IT GO...
WHY NOT GIVE HIM-- AND HER--
ANOTHER CHANCE?
IT'S NOT WHERE
THE TWO OF YOU COME FROM
THAT MATTERS.
IT'S WHERE YOU'RE GOING
AS A COUPLE.
YEAH.
[♪♪♪]
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
YES, BUT IF IT'S TO TRY
AND CONVINCE ME TO BLERGH--
"BLOG."
...THE ANSWER IS STILL NO.
OKAY.
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH BUSINESS,
SO I REALLY
DON'T HAVE ANY RIGHT
GIVING YOU MY TWO CENTS
ABOUT SAM AND ANNABELLE,
BUT I'M GOING TO GO OUT
ON A LIMB HERE
AND SAY THAT, CLAIRE,
YOU ARE WRONG.
DID I JUST SAY THAT OUT
LOUD?
YOU DID.
OKAY. ANYWAY.
I'VE SEEN MANY WOMEN
WALK THROUGH THIS DOOR
AND NONE OF THEM
HAVE THE CHARACTER, CHARM,
OR THE PERSONALITY
THAT ANNABELLE HAS.
AND EVEN IF
SHE WASN'T SO FANTASTIC,
SHE STILL LOVES YOUR SON,
JUST LIKE
YOU LOVED YOUR HUSBAND.
SO WHAT IF SHE WANTS TO WALK
DOWN THE AISLE WITH
WILDFLOWERS
INSTEAD OF ROSES.
IT'S STILL GONNA BE
BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S JUST GONNA BE
DIFFERENT.
[SIGHS QUIETLY]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[PUTS PHONE DOWN]
[KNOCKING]
COME IN.
[SIGHS]
YOU KNOCK NOW?
[SHE SIGHS]
YOUR FATHER
LOVED YOU SO MUCH.
HE LOVED BOTH OF US SO MUCH.
YES, HE DID.
YOU KNOW, WHEN HE DIED...
EVERYONE SAID
I'D MEET SOMEONE ELSE,
AND, SURE,
I DATED, BUT...
I ALWAYS KNEW
THAT THERE WAS NOBODY
WHO WAS GONNA REPLACE YOUR
DAD.
BUT THAT WAS OKAY,
BECAUSE EVERY TIME
I LOOKED AT YOU,
I SAW HIS EYES AND HIS
SMILE...
AND I KNEW THAT A PART OF
HIM
WAS STILL HERE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
I REALIZED IT UNTIL TODAY.
IT'S NOT THAT I WANTED YOU
TO MARRY THE PERFECT GIRL.
IT'S THAT I WAS AFRAID
YOU WOULD AND...
THEN I'D LOSE YOU, TOO.
[SNIFFLES]
LOOK AT HER.
SHE'S WEARING A 1950s DRESS
WITH A 1970s JACKET.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'D CALL THAT HAIRDO.
WHAT IS IT?
A KIND OF A BEDHEAD-BOB?
I'M SORRY, SAM.
YOU TWO ARE OBVIOUSLY
PERFECT
FOR EACH OTHER
AND YOU NEED TO GET MARRIED
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
YOU REALLY MEAN THAT?
I DO.
MOM...
YOU'RE NOT LOSING ME.
YOU'RE JUST
GAINING A DAUGHTER,
AND...
I THINK
SHE COULD REALLY USE A MOM.
NOT TO MENTION
I'VE NEVER MET A WOMAN
WHO HAS YOUR LEVEL
OF SHOPPING STAMINA.
WELL, I LOOK FORWARD
TO EXPERIENCING THAT.
HOPEFULLY AT THE MALL,
AND NOT IN ONE OF
THOSE VINTAGE STORES.
OSED--
HOPEFULLY AT THE MALL,
OH.
I HAVE THIS ONE BRIDE,
AND, UH...
SHE'S LOOKED AT
EVERYTHING IN MY SHOP
AND CAN'T FIND
ANYTHING SHE LIKES.
I WAS THINKING
THAT THERE MIGHT BE
SOMETHING HERE THAT, UH...
I COULD FIND FOR HER.
DO YOU MIND IF I JUST
POKE AROUND FOR A BIT?
SURE.
DID I EVER TELL YOU
ABOUT THE FIRST TIME
THAT I MET MY MOTHER-IN-LAW?
NO.
PROBABLY BECAUSE
I SPENT THE LAST 30 YEARS
TRYING TO BLOCK IT OUT.
WELL, IT WAS THANKSGIVING,
AND THERE WERE ABOUT 20
GUESTS,
AND FOR SOMEBODY LIKE ME,
WHO'D NEVER SEEN FINE CHINA
OR TABLECLOTHS,
EXCEPT IN THE MOVIES,
I MIGHT AS WELL
HAVE BEEN IN BUCKINGHAM
PALACE.
SO WE'RE SITTING
AT THIS LONG TABLE,
OF WHAT TURNED OUT TO BE
ABOUT EIGHT COURSES...
AND, UH...
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I JUST BECAME
COMPLETELY OVERWHELMED.
SO WHAT DID YOU DO?
WELL, I HANDLED IT IN
THE MOST GRACIOUS WAY
POSSIBLE.
I EXCUSED MYSELF,
WENT TO THE BATHROOM,
AND BURST INTO TEARS.
OBVIOUSLY,
THE RELATIONSHIP WAS DOOMED.
THESE PEOPLE WERE
WAY TOO SOPHISTICATED.
COMPLETE OPPOSITE
FROM THE APARTMENT IN QUEENS
WHERE I GREW UP.
YOU GREW UP IN QUEENS?
OH, SURE.
YOU CAN TAKE
THE GIRL OUTTA QUEENS,
BUT YOU CAN'T TAKE THE
QUEENS
OUTTA THE GIRL.
SO, I'M IN
THE BATHROOM AND, UH...
FIXING MY MAKEUP,
AND THIS KNOCK ON THE DOOR--
SAM'S FATHER.
HE ALWAYS HAD THIS SIXTH
SENSE
ABOUT WHEN I WAS UPSET.
AND WHEN HE ASKED ME
WHAT WAS WRONG,
I TOLD HIM THAT I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF WE JUST CUT OUR LOSSES
AND WENT
OUR SEPARATE WAYS.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE SAID,
"WELL, I HATE
TO TELL YOU THIS, CLAIRE,
BUT IF YOU EVER LEAVE ME,
I'M GOING WITH YOU."
AND THEN HE SAID
THAT IT WAS JUST AS UNFAIR
FOR ME TO JUDGE THEM
BASED ON WHAT THEY LOOKED
LIKE
AND HOW THEY ACTED
AS IT WAS FOR ME TO THINK
THAT THEY WERE JUDGING ME.
YOUR HUSBAND SOUNDS LIKE
HE WAS A VERY WISE MAN.
HE WAS.
AND THEN WE WENT
BACK TO THE TABLE,
AND I DISCOVERED
THAT THEY WERE ACTUALLY
LOVELY PEOPLE.
AND I WENT OUT THE NEXT DAY
AND I GOT MYSELF
A COPY OF EMILY POST,
AND THAT WAS THAT.
[CHUCKLES QUIETLY]
ANNABELLE,
I OWE YOU A HUGE APOLOGY.
I HAD NO RIGHT TO TAKE OVER
YOUR WEDDING LIKE THAT.
SINCE HE MET YOU,
SAM HAS NEVER BEEN HAPPIER.
THIS IS YOUR WEDDING,
AND THE ONLY THING
THAT IS IMPORTANT TO ME
IS THAT I GET TO HAVE
THE BEST SEAT IN THE HOUSE
WHEN YOU
WALK DOWN THE AISLE.
YOU GOT IT.
GOOD.
UM...
IT'S NOT--
IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT...
YOU DID MENTION
THAT YOU LIKED IT--
BUT THAT'S
YOUR WEDDING DRESS.
[UNZIPPING]
I WAS HOPING
THAT YOU MIGHT CONSIDER
USING THIS AS, UH...
YOUR "SOMETHING BORROWED."
REALLY?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY, YOU CAN
DO WHATEVER YOU NEED TO
TO MAKE IT YOUR OWN.
OH, NO. IT'S...
PERFECT,
JUST LIKE THIS.
[♪♪♪]
[KNOCKING]
OH, YEAH, OF COURSE!
OF COURSE,
I CAN GET YOU A CAFTAN.
-HI.
-SURE! NO PROBLEM.
YES, AND I WILL CALL YOU
LATER.
OKAY.
WHO'S THAT? MAYA?
NO. YOUR MOM.
MY MOTHER WANTS A CAFTAN?
YEAH. WHY?
THAT'S FUNNY.
I NEVER THOUGHT OF MY MOTHER
AS A CAFTAN KINDA WOMAN.
WELL, THERE'S A LOT YOU
DON'T
KNOW ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
APPARENTLY SO.
SO HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
AMAZING.
WE HAD BREAKFAST
AT CAFE DES ARTISTES.
OH, NICE. YOU AND MAYA?
NO. ME AND YOUR MOM.
DID I TELL YOU
SHE'S TEACHING ME FRENCH?
I'M SO EXCITED.
TERRIFIC.
WELL. UH...
AND HOW WAS YOUR AFTERNOON?
AMAZING.
FACIAL AND A MASSAGE.
NICE. YOU AND HILLARY?
NO. ME AND YOUR MOM.
I'M SORRY.
ENOUGH ABOUT ME.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
-[PHONE RINGS]
-WELL, THIS MORNING WAS--
ACTUALLY,
HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
YEAH, CLAIRE?
OOH, YOU'RE KIDDING?
THAT'S AWESOME!
THAT'S GREAT!
OH, AMAZING.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
YOU'RE ON FIRE!
[BOTH TALKING EXCITEDLY]
[♪♪♪]
[MUSIC OVER CONVERSATION]
[LAUGHING]
[CLAIRE]: WHAT DID YOU SAY
THIS BREAD WAS CALLED?
[ANNABELLE]: "INJERA."
-OH! IT'S DELICIOUS.
-IT'S ETHIOPIAN.
MM!
OKAY. SO...
RINGS?
UH, MAYA'S GOT THEM.
UH, FOOD?
ALL SET.
I'M STILL FULL
FROM THE FINAL TASTING.
OH, BY THE WAY,
DID YOU GUYS
HAPPEN TO TRY
THOSE FLORENTINE COOKIES?
THEY WERE AMAZING!
NOT THAT I--
[SAM AND CLAIRE]:
"...EAT SWEETS OR ANYTHING."
SO, I'VE TALKED TO
THE CHAIR RENTAL PLACE,
AND EVERYTHING WILL
BE SET UP BY 3:00.
THE GUESTS
ARE SCHEDULED TO ARRIVE
BETWEEN 5:00 AND 5:30...
MM-HMM.
AND THE SUN IS
GOING TO SET AT 6:23,
WHICH MEANS
THAT WHEN YOU TWO
SAY "I DO,"
YOU'RE GOING TO LOOK
LIKE A POSTCARD.
WHAT IF IT RAINS?
WE HAVE BEEN CHECKING
THE WEATHER SITES
EVERY DAY FOR THE LAST WEEK,
AND THERE IS NOT A DROP OF
RAIN
IN THE FORECAST.
BUT IF IT DOES,
WE'VE GOT A BACKUP.
THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY
HAS BEEN GENEROUS ENOUGH
TO LET US USE
THEIR BUILDING.
OH.
SEE, BETWEEN
THE TWO OF US,
WE HAVE MANAGED TO PLAN
THE PERFECT WEDDING.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
THEY SAID
IT WOULDN'T RAIN!
OHH! WATCH
YOUR MASCARA.
THEY LIED.
NO, RAIN ON
YOUR WEDDING DAY
IS GOOD LUCK.
-WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT?
-FROM YOU.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE
THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY
FOR YOUR RECEPTION.
IT'S A REALLY
BEAUTIFUL BUILDING.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS.
I MEAN,
I WAS REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
SAYING MY VOWS
ON THE PUTTING GREEN
AT THE GOLF COURSE,
BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE
WE HAD OUR FIRST KISS,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHERE THE CEREMONY IS--
I JUST WANT TO MARRY SAM.
AND CLAIRE THOUGHT AHEAD
AND INSISTED
THEY SET UP THE TABLES
AND CHAIRS
AT THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY,
IN CASE WE HAD AN EMERGENCY.
AND THEY DID...
BUT THERE'S A SLIGHT
PROBLEM.
HOW SLIGHT?
ABOUT A FOOT'S WORTH OF
WATER.
THERE WAS A FLOOD.
WITH ALL THIS RAIN,
THE CEILING CAVED IN.
SO UNLESS WE WANT TO HAND
OUT
RUBBER RAIN BOOTS AT THE
DOOR,
THAT ISN'T GOING TO WORK
EITHER.
IT WAS ALL
GOING SO WELL,
AND NOW EVERYTHING'S
FALLING APART.
OH, NO, DARLING,
IT ISN'T.
DON'T WORRY.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
WE'LL MOVE THE RECEPTION
TO MY HOUSE.
WHAT ABOUT THE CEREMONY?
I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA
FOR THAT.
[♪♪♪]
DO YOU--
ANNABELLE BLANCHE.
...ANNABELLE BLANCHE,
TAKE THIS MAN--
SAM TAYLOR.
YOU TWO
ARE IN A HURRY.
...SAM TAYLOR
TO BE
YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED
HUSBAND?
I DO.
AND DO YOU TAKE THIS WOMAN,
ANNABELLE BLANCHE,
TO BE
YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED WIFE?
I DO.
THEN BE THE AUTHORITY
VESTED IN ME,
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
♪ YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL
LIKE A STAR-FILLED SKY ♪
♪ IN MYSTERIES
FOR YOU TO FIND ♪
♪ AND I CAN SEE
YOUR STAR SHINE BRIGHTLY ♪
♪ IT'S TIME TO LEAVE
YOUR FEARS BEHIND ♪
♪ SO GO ON ♪
♪ DON'T BE AFRAID TO SHINE ♪
♪ EVEN IN THE DARK ♪
♪ LISTEN TO YOUR HEART ♪
♪ IF YOU BREAK DOWN... ♪