Downloaded from
G2G.fm
We all have stories to tell,
our own paths
to faith in Christ.
Some are kookier than others
like finding Jesus in a piece
of drift wood,
yeah more on that in a second,
but for me I didn't see it
coming.
I thought I was looking for a
guy
to stick a ring on my finger,
my Mr. Right.
And along the way something
wonderful happened.
I found Him.
That's Him with a capital H.
street light got that perfect
glistening,
touchdown I fall into your arms
right where I belong your
everlasting arms.
And where would I be
without yo u
I'd be packing my bags
when I need to stay.
I'd be chasing every breeze
that blows my way.
I'd be building my kingdom
just to watch it fade away.
It's true.
That's me without you, that's me
without you
that's me without you.
Don't know where I'd be without
you,
that's me without you, that's me
without you,
that's me without you, without
you.
Don't know where I'd be without
that's me without you, that's me
without you,
that's me without you, without
you.
Yeah? It's real good.
I actually took a
trip to Franc e
a couple years ago. Oh, the
wine!
Have you ever been to France?
Ryan?
Oh sorry.
Yeah France. No I haven't been.
But I hear it's great.
Love the accents.
It is better than great, I
don't know how
but you can eat anything you
want there and
not gain a pound, that is my
kind of
country.
And the wine is just to die for
even the
cheap stuff oh and the Fermat
of course.
That cheese right?
I love stinky cheese, it clogs
the pipes but
still.
You know they say the best
cheese comes from
between French framers toes.
Yup that's probably why it's so
stinky.
Incroyable.
That sounds great.
Listen Gwinny, a friend of mine
just walked in.
I'm just going to go say hi
real quick.
OK? This is great. I'll be
right back.
-Sure. -OK hold on.
-Sounds good.
And it's Gwyneth not Gwinny.
It's so rude, the guy couldn't
keep eye
contact with me for 10 seconds.
Is it me?
No sweetie, it's just dumb
stupid guys.
Ryan is definitely not stupid
he's a leading
gastroenterologist.
Which is why he is so full of...
Gwyneth he just texted me.
He said he's sorry.
It was his high school
sweetheart.
He hasn't seen her in years.
High school sweetheart. Is that
the one
that's half his age and
half his weight?
We're running out of guys, our
husbands are
running out of guys.
Babe, if you're not careful
your going to be
the last one standing.
No, Ann Marie will be the last
one standing
guaranteed.
I am losing here you guys, I
feel like it's
one of those movies where the
guy in
a little boat just drifts off
into the
horizon and then he just
disappears.
Poof!
I don't want to spend another
Christmas
under the mistletoe alone.
I just want to meet a guy that
will look at
me for 10 seconds and smile.
Sold.
Let's go.
Dad.
I'll be in the car.
Hey Speedy.
What are you going to eat all
this in one
day?
Now you can get it in one.
Stop it!
Stop being poor!
Now buy my book and join
the one percent.
Cheesy.
One Minute workout, one
Minute a day a new
you.
Check out these results.
One minute a day.
It's not even the same girl.
One minute a day a new you.
This is our first Christmas as
husband and
wife.
We met on ChristianMingle.com.
From our family at Christian
Mingle, we'd
like to wish you a Merry
Christmas and a
Happy New Year.
Yea right.
Joining is easy and free.
Joining Christian Mingle.
No, no, no.
Ann Marie will be the last one
standing
guaranteed.
You've got to be kidding me.
30 years old and only a couple
lousy short
term relationships under my
belt, pathetic.
But, it wasn't for a lack of
trying I dated.
Boy did I date.
But most of the time I was
thinking, get me
out of here before the
appetizers arrive.
And I don't know maybe it was
me.
Either way I was convinced that
it was
now or never.
Seriously. And you know what I
lied.
I didn't just want guy to look
at me and
smile.
I wanted more than that.
I, I wanted a genuinely decent
guy.
And I knew he was out there.
But, if I was going to find
him , I'd had to
do something different, totally
different.
Happy New Year Ms. Hayden.
Hey Gwen.
You look terrible.
I'm done.
New year, new me.
I'm buying a dog or joining a
monastery, or
both if they'll let me bring a
puppy.
Ladies, everyone on the bridge
in 5 minutes.
Got big news big, big,
big news .
Pamela, the coffee has
that foul taste
again, dish water.
Not the day for stinky Joe.
I want you to fix it ASAP.
Please, pretty please.
Rodger that admiral.
Oh, and Happy New Year
everybody.
Not today, I cannot play
battleship with him
today.
You ever think if it's the guy
your picking
to go out with?
Maybe your knocking on one door
hoping
another will open.
Oh, thank you Oprah.
Don't call me Oprah.
Have either of you heard of
Donny De Bona?
Is that really a name?
He is the biggest name in
direct response
for male beauty.
Oh, you're talking about the
infomerical guy
with, with the weird goatee.
Oh.
I am talking about the
infomercial king, and
he is coming here today on his
private jet.
He is coming in at O-1100 hours
to meet with us.
To discuss if he wants us to
single-handedly
market his newest product.
Hair.
As in wigs?
Transplant?
Hair.
Hair!
The real thing.
He has found a cure for
baldness.
He found a secret solution and
he puts it in
a little capsule.
This is ridiculous.
There's no secret solution.
You take that back.
I mean it.
Okay fine, I take it back but...
No buts. This is the
real thing .
I've done my research, I'm not
an idiot.
We are done here.
I want you to assemble the
troops.
Clear the decks.
I want a reception fit for a
president.
Now hurry up!
Dismissed.
I can take almost anything,
spin it into
gold and fool some of the
people some of the
time.
But, I don't care how you brand
it, package
it or sell it.
If God didn't give you hair,
you aint
getting hair. End of story.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Donny De Bona.
I'm sure you don't need any
introduction to
Mr. De Bona.
You know him as the man who has
revolutionized the way modern
men live their
daily lives.
Now Mr. De Bona is at it again,
bigger and better than ever.
And from what I understand he's
here for a
few days to kick our tires and
if we pass
the test we will be the lucky
firm to brand
and market Mr. De Bona's newest
product
and if that day comes,
then you , me, we,
all of us will be a part of
history.
The story.
A man.
Let's meet the troops.
They're all yours.
let's chat.
Good to see you Rex.
Donny.
Hello there. Donny De bona.
Okay let's review.
So no Mr. Right
and now I've gotta make bald
guys
believe some magical potion
they buy on TV
is gonna solve all their
problems.
At this point I'm like "God, if
you are out
there, this is Gwyneth Hayden
calling and uh
help."
You're single.
You're Christian and you're
looking for a
meaningful relationship.
Find God's match for you at
ChristianMingle.com.
The leading site for Christian
dating.
It's the largest community both
nationally
and where you live of
like-minded Christians
seeking a partner for their
spiritual
journey.
It's easy and it's free.
In minutes you can start
browsing millions
of profiles and discover easy
low-pressure
ways to start meeting other
Christian
singles.
Worn out with blisters on your
feet.
To anyone with a heart that's
shattered.
Doing your best to hold it
together.
With no prayer to pray and no
song left to
sing.
Whatever pain you're dealing
with.
Let me offer this.
Come however you are.
Come with all your
heart breaks .
Come with all the mistakes,
you've made.
Lay them down at the cross.
Give them to the God who loves
you.
Hurt, scarred, falling apart.
Come however you are.
To the girl who never had a
father.
To the guy who thinks he'll
never amount to
much of anything.
To those of us who feel
unwanted, unneeded,
unloved, and desperately
incomplete.
Come however you are.
Come with all your
heart breaks .
Come with all the mistakes
you've made.
Lay them down at the cross.
Give them to the God who loves
you.
Am I bad?
You're right this is wrong.
-This is wrong.
-What's wrong?
-Hi, I'm sorry.
-No, no I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
Hi, I'm, I'm Paul Wood.
Gwyneth Hayden. Hi.
I wish that I had an excuse for
you but
honestly I'm just terribly with
time
management.
I mean Papa warned me it would
be my
undoing.
-Papa?
-Oh, My dad.
Oh.
-Should we?
-Yeah sure.
What?
Nothing.
It's the photo isn't it?
Yeah I don't really look
like my picture.
I kind of cheated on that part.
Who doesn't?
Mine was from like 10 years ago
back when I
was on my way to rock stardom.
Yeah!
You were going to be a rock
star?
Well, you know, an entertainer.
Oh, an entertainer.
That's interesting.
This is weird isn't it?
It's a weird way to meet
somebody.
What a strange new world.
It is.
It's like click, meet, marry,
die, done.
It's a very strange new world.
But the stuff between never
really changes.
Family, joy, a love for the
Lord.
Yeah gotta love Him.
The Lord.
Well hey do you want something
to drink?
Hey, how about a cookie?
Oh no I don't do cookies.
It's a double chin coming
quicker than a
freight train.
How about a cookie?
Sold.
What?
Nothing.
You're great.
Yeah well you're awesome.
I would've been okay with okay.
Coffee would be great though.
Black, no sugar.
Uncomplicated and a believer.
That's me.
I like that.
Believer or not.
Thank you.
Dear Lord, yes, we just want to
thank you
for the coffee and the cookie,
and really
most of all the coffee and the
talent of the
baristas that prepared it.
Although I am just drinking
black so I guess
that really doesn't take a lot
of
barista-ing.
But um.
We also just want to say a
huge , super huge
thanks for bringing Paul and I
together
because he is just, he's very
cool and - you
really did good thank you - and
I just want
to thanks for old photos.
Yes.
-Amen. -Amen.
I have never prayed over coffee
before.
I mean you can't pray enough in
this click,
meet, marry world.
That's it?
You're stopping there now?
No more die and done?
No I might wanna, I don't know
wanna have a
few laughs or something before
that.
Sounds good to me.
So, what do people call you?
Gwinny?
Not if you want to
see tomorrow .
Sixth grade summer camp didn't
end well.
You can just call me Gwyneth.
Gwyneth it is.
I like you.
You got spunk.
Spunk?
It's a little 'Brady Bunch'
but , I don't
know; it might grow on me.
This is a guy you met online!
I know, but it's not like that.
It's a very popular and legit
dating
website, not to mention it's
Christian.
Which brings us to problem
number two:
You're not Christian.
Says who?
I believe in God and stuff.
I mean I was baptized, I
went to Sunday
School, I read the Bible when I
was a kid...
you know, the one with all the
pretty
pictures...
and I go to church sometimes.
When?
When is the last time you
stepped into a
church?
Last month.
You went to church last month?
I did.
And?
Okay, so it was a wedding.
Whose wedding?
I don't know, but it was so
beautiful.
Oh, you crashed a wedding.
No!
I just peaked inside.
It's not like I
followed them to the
reception and chowed down on
free shrimp.
And that was the last time you
were in a
church...
peaking in a wedding?
Yeah.
It was so beautiful.
This is so sad.
Okay, that doesn't count.
You're not Christian or
whatever this guy
thinks you are.
That website is for real
Christians looking
for other real Christians.
Do you see the problem here?
Okay, you are making this
a much heavier
religious issue than it
needs to be, and
besides, I think I'm at
least 50 percent
that kind of Christian anyway.
I'm pretty sure it's either/or,
not just a
slice of the pie.
Ladies.
Gwyneth, you are up.
Well she's all yours, God help
her.
Actually I'd like a few minutes
alone with
Ms. Hayden if I might.
Well then I'll just leave you
two to it.
You don't bite, do you?
Nah.
What do we have here?
Gwyneth Hayden, BP, Brand
Management.
That's me.
What's brand management, in
your own words?
Well I think I take the story...
the good, the bad and the ugly
of it all.
I mix it in a bowl, I add some
sugar and I
make it taste good.
And you're good at that?
I think I am.
You're not a believer, are you?
uh....
I'm sorry, what?
You don't believe that I can
grow hair.
Oh.
Oh, that.
um...
I just...
You mean with these?
Well I can.
I can, and I can prove it to
you.
Before and after.
Before, after.
Pictures don't lie.
Scout's honor.
Scout's honor then, I'm good.
And it's all right there.
Before and after.
Yes, we're going on a second
date.
I mean he's a little like
out of 'Leave it
to Beaver' but you guys, he was
so charming.
Oh honey, switch the channel.
This can only end badly.
End?
What do you mean?
It's just beginning.
Sweetie, you're desperate and
you're
grasping at straws.
You guys, no, stop.
He is fantastic.
I mean isn't this what we've
been trying to
do...
get me a fella and get me
hitched?
My family has been in the
construction
business for generations.
Papa's papa, he was a big
development guy so
he sort of turned it into a
bigger deal.
Now papa has taken it to
a whole 'nother
level.
So do you work a lot with your
hands?
Oh no, gosh, I wish.
No, I'm kind of stuck in the
office.
Oh, really?
Doing what?
Analysis, mostly.
Feasibility reports on
potential projects.
Oh, so you basically sniff out
the stinkers.
Yeah, I guess that's one way to
put it.
Sushi up.
Oh, thank you.
Looks delicious.
Okay.
Dig in.
You're not really a fan of
sushi, are you?
Is it that obvious?
Yeah.
You know that funny thing
you're doing with
your nose, your stinker
detector?
It's kind of a dead giveaway.
I mean you look like you just
smelled dog
poop.
Not really helping the
situation here.
Well why didn't you just
tell me that?
Because I kind of wanted to try
it.
You know, it's the in thing,
right?
This red one here,
this is tuna,
and this here, the yellow one,
is
yellowtail, which is
technically a different
kind of tuna.
The brown one is eel, and then
this orangey,
mushy-looking one is uni, which
is sea
urchin.
It is delicious.
It's my favorite.
Well maybe I'll try that one.
Looks interesting.
You know what?
On second thought, no.
Let's pass on that.
Sea urchin is not
gateway sushi .
Just take your chopsticks,
right, and let's
just start right here.
Okay, that'll work.
Here, you can dip it in the soy
and...
uh huh.
Here it goes.
Mmm.
You are gonna actually have to
swallow at
some point.
It's coming.
Here it goes.
Oh!
Not exactly sure what just
happened.
You just chewed that poor tuna
to death is
what happened.
I guess I'm just more of a
chili cheese dog
kind of guy.
Someone's gonna get hurt.
Do you have any idea what
happened at a
Bible study?
What?
to gas.
Got to get away from here fast.
Enemies breathing down my neck
and trying to
grad a hold and make me wreck.
Hot on my tail trying to
make me fail and
trying to take the wind up out
of my sail.
Trying to roll me
off this road .
Don't look at what's behind.
There you are.
Thought you got lost.
No, no, no.
Here I am.
You look great.
Come in, come in.
Meet everybody.
Everyone, this is Gwyneth, and
whatever you
do, don't call her Gwinny.
Ah ha ha ha.
Okay, let's see.
First that's Jimmy and Jessie
McKenzie.
They're happy newlyweds.
Met on Mingle.
Turned me onto it, praise the
Lord.
Praise the Lord.
And this is their beautiful
home.
And that's Tommy and Gabby
Huntley, who are
having a baby.
My belly!
Praise the Lord.
Indeed.
And that's Kel-Kel.
Hi, hi.
Kelly.
Heck, you want to talk about
summer camp
stories, we got a few of our
own.
Bible camp.
Believe me, it's nothing.
Okay, let me see if I have it.
We have Jimmy and Jessie
McKenzie, Tommy and
Gabby Huntley, who are having a
baby in your
belly, and summer camp Kelly.
So you should just call me
Gwinny.
Really?
Sure.
This, This place is great.
It's all so inspirational and
marriage,
marriage that's just, I mean,
it actually
reminds me of one of my
favorites.
Yeah I think the passage is
from Galatians.
Because of the temptation to
sexual
immorality each man should have
his own wife
and each woman should have her
own husband.
You know what, my bad, I think
that was
Corinthians.
Yep that was Corinthians.
So sorry.
Do you have any water?
Sure.
Thank you.
C'mon.
Hi how ya doing buddy.
I'm sorry, I'm not really good
with you
people.
Well you seem pretty good with
Pauly.
He's just so different.
He's the last of the good ones,
that's for
sure.
I hope things work out.
I haven't seen him this
happy in a while.
Really?
Well I must be doing something
right then.
So great to have
everybody back .
Jessie, Jimmy, thank you
guys so much for
your hospitality again, once
again.
And Gwinny it's just awesome to
have you
with us.
So, uh let's pick up where we
left off last
week, Romans 7 we were uh,
Verse 14.
Now everybody's familiar with
the story of
Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
You know what I think?
No, what do you think?
You should stick to Gwyneth.
Just be you.
Whoever that is.
The trouble is with me for I am
all too
human, a slave to sin.
Well the pressure's
bleeding in .
Giving me some blurry vision.
Fogging up my intellect.
Where love and hate they
intersect.
Keep the path of the mission.
Never going to lose
my ambition .
Got my eyes up on the prize.
Eyes forward.
Don't look at what's behind.
Don't take your eyes off the
prize.
I told Mom about that raw fish.
Oh you did?
Boy did she get a kick out of
that.
So what's the deal
with Kel-Kel ?
Who?
Kelly from Bible Study.
Oh that?
Oh no nothing.
Honestly.
We, she's practically like a
sister.
We grew up together, our
families.
Although if mama had her way?
You and Kelly would be about 3
kids and 2
dogs deep right now?
The barking kind.
oh, the next stop, the
deliciou s train.
I like it around here.
It's funky.
Funky spunky.
Okay so I told you I wanted to
be a rock
star.
So what about you?
Did you have any other dreams?
Um...
yeah, I always actually wanted
to be a
teacher.
Wow that's noble.
What happened?
Well I went to school and
graduated and
needed a job and looked for a
meaningful job
and there just wasn't one so I
kind of faked
my way to a living until I,
funny enough,
ended up in a line of work
where faking it
is actually part of the job
description.
So, how long have you been a
believer?
You know, it's, it's just
such a long and,
you know, personal story.
Maybe it's for another time if
that's okay.
Oh yeah absolutely.
Though you have peaked my
curiosity.
You know what they say about
curiosity and
the cat.
What about you though, if you
don't mind me
asking?
No, no not at all.
I was kind of born into it, I
guess.
All the men on mama- my
mother's side were
pastors going back forever.
So, my papa's- my dad's side
different
story.
He was a crazy kid my dad
growing up in the
60's and all.
Drifting through life.
Then as the story goes he was
walking on a
beach one day, and he came
across this piece
of driftwood and he saw
something in it.
So he took it home and he
studied it and he
studied it, and he ended up
carving a statue
of Jesus out of it.
Next thing you know, spirit
fills him,
changes his life forever.
Just like that.
Lights off, lights on.
Flick of the switch.
Let me get this straight.
You're telling me your dad, who
was a
drifter as you say, and whose
last name
happens to be Wood
finds a piece of
driftwood on the beach and
finds Jesus in it
and bam, he's born again?
Wow, I've never seen that angle
before.
Are you kidding me?
It was laying right there.
No seriously!
Snap!
That is so creative.
How do you just come up with
that all so
quickly?
It's kind of what I do.
Well anyway, my driftwood
moment actually
happened when I was 13.
I entered the science fair at
school and I
built this maze for mice to run
through.
I had them in 2 cages,
the mice .
In one cage I had flashing red
lights and
head banging music going 24/7
and in the
other one I had soft blue light
and
classical music.
My hypothesis was that,
the mice in the
tripped out cage would run the
maze faster
because they're all hyped
up and the mellow
mice would just wander through
without
really caring.
And then right before every run
I would give
each mouse a sniff of this big
chunk of
Swiss cheese that I had at the
end of the
maze, their prize.
This is actually me but I'm
fascinated, I
want to hear more.
Oh, Ok.
It was somewhere in the middle
of it all,
none of that mattered anymore
because I got
so fixated on the notion of the
cheese.
That prize that both sets of
mice had a
scent of and ultimately were
drawn to.
Each had their own path,
but the goal was
the same.
Don't tell me you saw Jesus in
the cheese.
No, no um..
But, it reminded me like so
much of what I
had been doing as a kid.
Searching for something that I
had a sense
of but couldn't quite put my
finger on.
suddenly it all clicked.
The cheese.
Jesus' love was waiting for me.
So that weekend I won the
science fair, and
found my prize.
A love in Christ.
Well sweet Cheesus.
Sweet Cheese!
Sweet Cheesus.
You find the funny in
everything, don't you?
I'm sorry.
No I like funny.
The world could
definitely use a little
funny right now.
Are you happy?
You know, are you content?
Yeah I think so.
Wow.
Big question.
I'm happier now that I've met
you, that's
for sure.
Flatter.
You working overtime for that
goodnight
kiss?
No.
Well then no kiss.
Okay.
Are you serious?
Absolutely.
Worn out with blisters on your
feet.
To anyone with a heart that
shattered, doing your best to
hold it
together.
with no prayer to pray.
You're not going back to 1950s
sweetie
you're going to church.
You know I want to scare his
parents right
out of the gate.
Keep shopping.
I think I can make this work.
Yeah, if you're playing
Margaret Thatcher.
Aren't you a little worried
about all this
pretending.
I'm not pretending I genuinely
like him.
I do, and you know what?
That is so cute I just want to
be
respectful.
And dressing like Julia
Child is being
respectful.
Or apparently any other
character recently
played by Meryl Streep.
Thank You that is so sweet.
Nice to meet you.
What am I doing.
standing at an open door
this is your life
never live twice
step through to the other side
Gwyneth.
Oh, I'm sorry.
How do you feel about that?
It's just so big.
Hundred and twenty seven by
forty five and
sixty three feet closer to the
other shore.
Steak and cake.
I'm sorry what?
How do you feel about steak and
cake?
We're all going there.
Don't tell me you've never had
steak and
cake.
Oh are you in for a treat.
Amen.
Have you met our Kelly.
I have hi nice to
see you again .
Well alrighty then.
Let's steak and cake it.
Your mother doesn't like me.
What are you talking about of
course she
does.
She doesn't even know you, and
speaking of
which is it just me or have you
always
dressed like my grandma.
I just didn't want to stick out
cause
sometimes.
She likes you.
I promise you are reading way
too much into
it.
Paul.
Coming.
Gwyneth we would all be so
honored if you
would say Grace.
Of course.
Dear Lord, thanks a bunch for
new friends.
It's really not often in life
that we get
such a gift.
People that are just kind and
generous, and
so thank you
and, and for this food golly
I mean steak and cake it's kind
of hard to
know which to eat first.
But, I guess it's all going to
the same
place so we are just very
thankful for that.
And, we thank you for the
abundance of all
of it.
There is just so much, and we
thank you for
the cows who are
willing to give up
themselves.
And that this food is going to
nourish our
bodies, and we really just sit
in
awesomeness, and really
I have a great
amount of gratitude.
So, yes Amen.
In Jesus' name Amen.
Oh yes in Jesus' name I
mean all of that of
course was in Jesus' name Amen.
Alrighty to the almighty lets
dig in.
Paul, have you told Gwyneth
about our
mission trip?
Yeah, we're just all so blessed
and excited
last year when we were
vacationing on the
Mayan Riviera.
The Yucatan Peninsula the
Caribbean side.
Right.
Well, we took this fantastic
day trip to see
some of the ancient sites the
Mayan pyramids
and all.
We came across this beautiful
little town
called San Luis De Piscopo.
Oh, just a stone's throw from
where we were
staying.
A stone's throw.
Yeah, well the town is
almost in ruins.
Evidently they haven't really
recovered
since hurricane Wilma struck
there.
Three years ago, category 5
just blew this
little place to bits.
Grace, let the boy finish.
Sorry.
Well really.
go on.
Really that's it I mean most of
the people
just, left you know, abandoned
the place,
sort of just lost their way,
gave up.
Faith an all.
That's right.
Door to door we shall restore.
Bill, who needs to hush now?
Door to door was real good,
take a note of
that.
Anyway, right there smack
in the middle of
it their church crumbling, it's
symbolic
they haven't opened their door
since.
The bell literally fell to the
ground and
that's where it sits.
So tragic.
But, with the help of Papa's
company and the
good Lord's grace.
We are going to fix it.
Door to door, we shall restore.
Oh yeah.
So, I'm, I'm just curious
exactly how long
does it take to re-hang a bell?
Long as it takes.
We will be there
till she rings .
Not a ding or a dong sooner.
Papas got it all pretty
keyed in down there.
So, we're thinking maybe a
month at most.
Or, until the bell rings.
It's cake time.
I want Chaco Latto, please.
Wait, I'm sorry you're going to
Mexico for a
month?
It's going to be awesome.
So wait, when do you leave?
Like tomorrow, night.
Praise the Lord.
I'm sorry but I, I thought you
would have
told her.
I was going to, and I should
have but,
you know we just met and to say
that
I was leaving for so long I, I
just...
I understand, I understand
really and
honestly I'm sorry that I made
things
difficult for you.
But, I did think that
you wouldn't have told her.
Paul, you know I only want
what's best for
you.
Of course.
Well, don't you think there is
something
just a little off about her.
Off?
Out of place, peculiar.
I mean don't get me wrong.
I'm sure she's a sweet
girl and , and I'm
sure she means well but.
But what?
Forgive me, but there is
something not
genuine going on there.
Alright now there I said it.
How so?
You really don't see it.
See what?
Oh sweetie you are just being
blinded by
love.
I'm really not following here.
Paul, she is hiding something.
No she isn't.
You know what I think?
I think this is you with
all due respect,
Mom stepping in the way.
You like to trying to control
the situation.
Please don't do that, not here
not this
time.
I like Gwyneth I really, really
like her and
I think she's awesome.
Admit it she is a little
different, but
that's what I like about her.
I think she does mean well and
she is
genuine, and I'm going to prove
it to you.
How is that?
I don't know but I will.
I'm buying a dog.
Oh well, I mean he was a really
nice guy.
He was but, he was kind of
goofy.
And between his mama and his
papa it
probably wouldn't work anyway.
What about a Bulldog?
Onward and upward.
Onward anyway.
You know I just he would have
given me a
heads up.
It's so unfair.
Has he tried calling?
Yeah about a hundred
times but I am not
answering I'm gonna let him
sweat it out.
And they say romance is dead.
There was something about
it al l though I
gotta say.
Everyone just seemed so happy.
Surprise inspection.
De Bona is here.
He wants to see some ideas now.
I guess he's keeping us on our
toes.
But, I...
No buts! Just genius.
Pamela, cup of Joe.
Quick.
Thank you.
I don't know.
Maybe I should start with them,
or oh no.
This one.
Yeah, this one right here for
sure.
Ok, so this is gonna be a
little out there.
So if you kinda just
go with me .
Hang on.
Alright, so we are going
to kill baldness
with the blue bullet.
Most men I know view their
follicly
challenged head as a life-long
nemesis.
And men being men, they want to
destroy the
enemy, right?
So how are we gonna do that?
We are going to kill it.
That's right.
With a blue bullet.
Right?
Do you see where I'm going with
this?
You know we can even have,
like , a little
dispenser, that's actually
shaped like a
gun.
You know?
Shoots out the blue bullets, or
we could
call it the Bald Bullet, even
better.
Or just Bullet.
You know, we could get a really
good looking
bald Steve McQueen-type male
model.
You know, Bullet?
The movie?
No?
I'm gonna pass on that.
That's mixed messages and in
this current
environment.
And with all the gun issues
right now.
It's, It's toxic.
Toxic.
Yeah, toxic.
Too toxic.
Okay.
You know what?
Absolutely.
We are just gonna - shifting
gears here.
Going in a whole new different
direction.
Ah, literally.
Everyone wants someone to blame
for their
deficiencies, especially men.
All due respect.
So sorry.
But when men look in the
mirror , and you
know what?
Also women.
We cannot forget that there are
plenty of
bald women out there.
Boy you can say that again.
My mother was bald.
Mamma Debona had alopecia.
Bald as a baby's butt.
Very tragic, very tragic.
What?
Sorry about that.
Okay.
Yeah so, when we look in the
mirror.
I mean when we really
see who we are.
Who we really are.
Sometimes we just don't take
responsibility
for it.
So, we want someone to blame,
right?
And who are we going to blame
for our
baldness?
I think naturally we blame the
thing that
created us.
That's right.
We're going to blame God.
Right up there.
God.
Blaming God.
Looking at God, going 'you know
what?
Why me?
Why me, God?
Why can't you just help me God?
You know what?
God hears your cries.
He hears your cries of
desperation.
And he has mercy because he
is a loving God,
and he has given us Heaven's
Rain.
Heaven's Rain?
Yes, he made it.
And with a little faith and
Heaven's Rain,
he can re-make it.
Water.
Wow.
You know what?
Can't you take a hint?
Alright, alright.
Hey.
You know, I'm trying to be mad
at you.
I think, I think I owe you an
apology.
No, you don't.
No, that wasn't the coolest way
to tell you
I was leaving for a while.
Paul, listen.
This is hard to say, but I just
don't know
if we're really, I mean you are
such a sweet
guy, you really are, but...
You should come down here.
What?
Mexico!
Come on down.
Gwyneth?
Yeah, I'm here.
I just, wow.
That's - I mean, I mean, when?
Now.
I can't.
I mean I really can't.
I mean we're in the middle of
something
really huge here at work.
Oh, one second please?
Heaven's Rain!
God!
Little blue bullets from a gun?
What planet are you living on!
Voodoo guru?
Listen, you'd better shape
up or ship out
missy.
I told you not to blow this!
I'll pay for that.
Are you still there?
You're on.
Wait please, where are you
taking
my stuff?
It's all good.
That's my stuff.
Hey, it's okay.
Welcome to Mexico.
It's all good.
Buenos Dias, stranger!
Hey!
Ha ha, there she is!
Listen, you want something for
the trots,
just let me know.
I got something for ya.
Great.
So what do you think?
It's...
Well
Buenos Dias senorita!
It's...
awesome.
I kinda packed more beach, sand
and
surf-ish...
You're fine.
That works!
Don't worry.
You look pretty.
Well, I'll just take some
vacation time.
I mean I have three years'
worth.
I have worked through every
holiday known to
man to make these deadlines.
He owes me.
You're in Mexico?
On a mission trip?
It's not like I'm not doing
something good
down here.
I mean we're all wearing the
same shirt and
making a difference.
I'm going to knock these sticks
together,
bang bang bang, slap on some
paint, brush
brush brush, and then Paul
and I can head to
the Mayan Riviera.
Where we can have
margaritas and gulp and
gulp and gulp and watch the
sunset, into the
Caribbean.
It's a win win for everyone.
Except for the poor suckers who
paid a ton
to watch the sun sink into the
Pacific,
which is what it normally does.
Oh, okay so sue me Pam I'm bad
at geography.
I don't care, listen, I am so
sick of
normal.
I just want paradise.
His version of paradise.
And if the sweet Lord is my
ticket to that,
then so be it.
All the better.
I mean I'm here two weeks, life
goes on.
There you are.
uh, uh, uh.
I'm losing you!
No, no.
It's a really bad connection.
I know that's you you... no,
come on.
I'm sorry, thank you.
Everything okay?
Yeah, just checking in.
She did not just hang up on me.
Oh my.
yon city.
Holding up the wall?
Your dad has a beautiful voice.
Yeah he does.
I see where you got your dreams
of being a
rock star.
It's amazing.
What's that?
Just given everything that's
happened.
The devastation.
Everyone just seems, so okay,
so just happy.
When your peace comes from God
no storm can
take it.
Yeah, I spill a drop of wine on
my carpet
and I have a heart attack.
Go bonkers.
Okay.
The temperature really drops
here at night
huh?
Yeah.
Savior.
down.
Let us love one another for
love comes from
God.
Everyone who loves has been
born of God and
knows God.
Whoever does not love does not
know God,
because God is love.
Anyone who does not love does
not know God
because God is love.
1st John 4:7-8.
Would anybody like to say
anything about
that?
Maria.
That's a very good question
Gwyneth.
Would you like to take a crack
at it?
I'm, I'm sorry, I just, my
Spanish.
I don't - I don't think I
understood the
question.
Maria wanted to know why, if
God loves us so
much, he let happened to their
village what
happened.
If God is love, why did he let
this happen?
Well, that is a very good
question Maria.
And not an easy one to answer.
But I know there are many
wonderful answers
in here.
Let me see.
How about James 1:7-8?
I think that addresses it
beautifully, don't
you?
Yes.
That is exactly what I was
thinking.
You are exactly right.
Let's see.
And that was the end of the
road.
They knew.
I knew they knew.
And they knew I knew they knew.
Perfect.
Now the only question was how I
was gonna
get out of there with any trace
of dignity.
Hey.
I was just hunkering down with
the men folk
about tomorrow.
Lots to get done?
Yeah.
But we will get 'er done.
I'm sure you will.
I mean God willing of course.
God willing, right?
You hungry?
Not really, no.
Can I talk to you a minute?
You're not enjoying this are
you?
What?
you seem lost.
Are you lost?
I don't - kind of.
You know what I think?
Straight up.
You're pretending.
Pretending to be something
you're not.
Why would you say that?
Just a hunch.
Am I right?
Not, completely but...
You're not really a
believe are you?
There's that word again.
Wow.
I guess I'm confused.
I like you a lot.
There's nothing confusing about
that.
And I like you.
A lot.
So?
Being a believer what does that
even mean?
I'm Christian, I believe
in God , I was
baptized, all of that stuff.
Are we really that different?
You gonna figure all that out
with this?
Where did you find that?
Did someone go
through my stuff ?
Because that so not...
One of the kids found it
when they were cleaning out the
bunk house.
It was under your cot.
They gave it to my mom, and she
gave it to
me.
Tell me if this sounds about
right.
All your life you've done some
searching for
something.
Something bigger.
Every now and again maybe you
can call
yourself a Christian.
Why not?
It's easy, gives it a name.
So you say, "I believe in God".
And for the most part it works.
Covers the bases, satisfies
that underlying
need to understand it deeper.
You kinda go with the common
flow.
And then something bad happens
and you look
around see all the terrible
things in the
world.
Compound that with the general
negative spin
on religion and you just get
turned off to
it.
God, faith, all of it.
So you, toss it all out.
Back and forth, accept it,
reject it.
How's that sounding?
About right.
Honestly, some of the stuff out
there, you
would not be human if you
didn't question
it.
So help me out here.
When you went online, Christian
Mingle.
What exactly were
you expecting ?
Honestly, I don't know.
I just saw the website and, all
of these
happy people.
And the guys just seemed, I
don't know.
All of the guys that I have, I
have been
dating were just so full of
themselves.
And I saw your pictures.
And your smile and you just
seemed like a
genuine guy.
But, then you lied about
yourself.
Why?
Well isn't it obvious?
Because if I hadn't, then, then
you.
What does it matter because in
the end, we
did meet.
And, Paul I really like you,
and according
to you, you really like me a
lot.
So.
I do like you.
But whoever I am with I gotta
feel totally
comfortable sharing what's
important to me.
And having a relationship with
Christ
through the good and the bad,
that is, that
is more important to me than
anything.
And I, I can't, I can't share
that with you.
Not if it's not true for you.
That's who I was looking for.
So, what are you saying?
I'm not sure, I'm, I mean I'm
confused
myself.
Because I do like you.
I really like you.
Well okay.
Then, unless you are under some
contractual
obligation please your
mother by being with
a gal, that she thinks you
should be with,
i.e., Kel-Kel which is not me.
Then maybe you could slowly
help me get to a
place that works for you.
That works for both of us.
I would like that!
Maybe, you could help show
me my driftwood.
I don't think it works like
that.
Not for me anyway.
I just wished that you hadn't
lied.
Maybe if you didn't-mm.
I don't know.
So, should
I just leave?
I like you so much.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, Me too.
Me too.
That was just about one of the
worst moments
of my life.
But, things were exactly as
they were meant
to be.
I think it is called Grace.
Don't say I didn't tell you.
Yeah.
Christians looking for other
Christians.
I really liked him.
I know.
Yes, come in.
Hey, Hey um..
How you doing?
I'm glad you are back.
That was pretty fast.
You, are, are you feeling
better?
Ah, what?
I know you want to keep it
between us.
But, the strep throat.
Oh, oh yeah the strep throat,
yeah,
it's a little scratchy but you
know what I
am doing so much better.
Thank you!
That's good.
That's good and, and so you're
back at it?
With, with the De bona thing?
Yes, yes.
That's splendid, splendid.
Well, then as you were.
Thank you.
Thank you, but strep throat
really?
You could of just said the a
cold or the
flu.
You had to go all dramatic with
strep
throat?
Hey, you said a couple of weeks
so that's
what I bought ya.
news lie admit-ion .
I got my eyes on the path.
My eyes on the path.
We are in here!
Oh I used to love this program.
Never miss a day of it.
I keep it on for her.
OK, it's a little catchy.
You know these people never to
seem to leave town.
Or get older, evidently.
Alright Gwen, What's going on?
Is it chain again?
Yeah, it clinks.
Clinks?
Or maybe it's more of a clunk.
Sure it's not a clank?
Like last time?
No, it's definitely a clink.
It's like clink, clink, clink,
clink.
I got, I got it.
I got it.
Thanks dad.
You're single.
You're Christian and you are
looking for a
meaningful relationship.
Find God's match for you at
ChristianMingle.com.
Oh, it's a different day, huh?
Yeah.
I meet my wife in high school.
I married her right afterward
and loved her
till the day she passed and oh,
no.
Eleven years ago.
You ever think about getting
back out there?
You know, dating?
Da-da-dating?
Me?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
She was my one and only.
ChristianMingle.com is the
ideal...
I think I got your coin
figured out here, just
give me a minute.
-within the faith.
Join today as part of your free
membership
you can take a journey of self
discovery
with a color coded personality
test.
If you are hoping to meet
someone special
log on to ChristianMingle.com
today.
Sometimes we wait for God to
make the next
move when God is saying, "It's
your time to
act", "your time to act", "your
time to
act".
We have had a lot of
opportunity walk
through our door.
Some better, some worse and
ninety-nine
percent of the time I have been
able to doll
it up.
Give it a makeover, and make it
the queen of
the ball.
Correct or incorrect?
I would say that's a fair
evaluation.
But, that's not 100% is it?
Douglas, I have to have an
ounce of belief
in something.
A half an ounce.
Just a drop of it to do what I
do.
To find the angle, the magic.
This De Bona stuff, all of it,
it's
just...
Stop!
Don't say that word.
If you say it, it becomes truth
and you
can't go back on it.
You're the one who made that
rule!
I can't do it.
It's false.
Look, Gwyneth, this isn't the
first time
you've had to make the leap.
But I can't do it this time.
That's what this is about.
On the record, I want to say
that I think
this hair thing is the real
deal and I think
it is going to grow hair, not
just because I
want it to.
I'm sorry Douglas but I just
can't do it.
Not this time.
Not with this.
Not, with any of it anymore.
I think I've just pushed the
boundary so
far, and bought into the dung
for so long.
And suspended a sense of
belief , and what we
do here.
And in, my life that I don't
even know
what's true or real anymore.
I've gotta believe.
I just needed to start at the
beginning.
Everyone welcome?
Pam was right.
I had been knocking on one door
hoping
another would open.
Give it all back to me.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
Give it all back to me (That's
what the Lord
said).
Give it all back to me (What
I've done for
you).
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
Give it all back.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
Give it all back.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
I won't share my glory.
With no one else (I won't share
with no one
else so don't you try).
Don't you try to keep it.
For yourself.
Don't you ever take the credit.
You didn't earn it, you
shouldn't get it.
Don't you know that pride comes
before every
fall.
Give it back, back, back, all
back.
Give the glory back.
Give it all back to me.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
Give it all back.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
Give it all back to me.
Give it all back.
What I've done for you.
What I do through you.
It is so clear.
I am so clear and there's no
going back.
No more.
I need truth.
Okay, and how exactly did you
come to this
sudden epiphany?
I think it was my driftwood
Jesus.
Say what?
It's a long story but for the
first time, in
a long time in my life it just
felt true.
True feels good.
It feels really good.
And I don't know where this is
gonna go.
But I know I just have to go
with it,
whether it takes me there or
not.
But it's not about the cheese,
it's about
the journey to it.
For everyone who asks receives
and the one
who seeks finds, and to the one
who knocks--
it will be opened.
Matthew-7-8.
Wait, you?
Right under your nose huh?
What?
Pam I've known you for
years and how did I
miss that?
And why didn't you say anything
through all
of this?
Oh no it's not my style.
You don't wear a cross or
anything?
Really not my style.
Huh.
But you seemed like you were so
against the
whole Mingle thing.
I wasn't against anything.
I told you it was for
Christians looking for
other Christians.
Who wanted to share a true love
for Christ.
And no matter what you may
think, you're not
quite there yet.
Yeah.
I've got a lot of work to do
but,
I want to do it.
And not for Paul.
I mean, if he were a part
of the deal that
would be fine.
But, I want to do this for me.
I want a relationship with him.
I, I want him in my life.
Who?
Him.
I didn't hear you.
Jesus.
I couldn't hear you, what'd you
say?
Ok I want Jesus in my life.
There we go, I said.
Can you say it louder?
I want Jesus in my life!
There you go.
Hey it's Paul here.
I'm back from old Mexico.
Leave me a message and I will
get back to
you.
Knock knock.
Oh wow!
This is a surprise.
Let me catch up with you guys.
Do you want to come in here?
That'd be great.
Knock knock you never said
who's there.
Okay, who's there?
Heaven.
Heaven who?
Heaven you missed me?
Cute.
It's really dumb I know.
I really wanted to tell you I'm
sorry.
I'm so sorry, for everything I
did.
Lying to you and deceiving you
which by
definition is the same thing.
I'm sorry.
And I hope with all of my heart
that you can
forgive me someday, no strings
attached.
I just wanted to say that.
Gosh of course.
Forgiven.
That is really thoughtful and,
and very
sweet.
I appreciate it.
And I, also wanted to say thank
you, for
opening my eyes.
And my heart to all of this.
You woke something up in
me that had just
been, I guess it had been there
all along.
But I don't know, maybe
that was his plan.
Maybe that's the reason we met.
Nothing more.
Right.
I don't know where it's going
but, for the
first time I just, I have this
sense of
purpose in my life.
That's awesome.
The heart of a man plans
his way but the
Lord establishes his steps.
Wow, you have been doing your
homework.
Yes I have.
Do you mind us coming in?
Oh Gwyneth, what a lovely
surprise.
Hi Gwinny.
Hi.
Gwyneth was just telling me
about this
amazing journey she's on.
Oh?
That's wonderful.
Yeah, you know, it's kind of
more of a
weekend getaway.
Really I wouldn't actually call
it a journey
yet.
I'm just kind of cutting that
baby path
through the jungle to Jesus,
you know?
But just my, my sights are on
the Lord, and
just yep that good ol' pathway
to heaven.
Right there.
That's where I'm going.
Okay.
Bye.
Gabby had her baby.
Did she?
Down in Mexico?
Right there in the square.
Just like she wanted without a
hitch.
That's awesome, and so public.
Yeah it's a beautiful, healthy
baby boy.
Praise God.
Alright you look like you're
chomping at the
bit to say something, so go on
just say it.
You think you can handle it?
We'll see.
Okay.
On one hand I'm really
happy for you.
I am, just like I said.
But, on the other hand I'm kind
of
disappointed in you too.
You're disappointed?
Okay look I know I messed up.
I wasn't truthful with you, and
I am paying
the price for that.
But, I'm kind of wondering what
your
deception is costing you.
Kelly?
If you're really happy, I'm
happy, but isn't
it just a little obvious?
Actually I think it's pretty
amazing that we
practically grew up together,
and then one
day I turn around and there she
is.
It's like driftwood.
You're not your dad, you
are not your mom.
You're you, and Kelly's a great
girl and,
you know what, God is probably
gonna like
unload about 40 days and 40
nights of rain
on me for saying all of this.
But, I just feel like you are,
you play it
so safe.
When does Paul get to just be
Paul?
Like this church I've
been going to.
Totally chill and laid back.
Does that make it any less
Christian than
the one you go to?
No, it can't.
But it does make it more me,
and it doesn't
make it right or wrong but it's
the way I
can relate to God.
Chill and laid back.
Not exactly how I would
describe you, but go
ahead.
I don't know if Kelly is
on your path.
She may be, but it's like your
life has been
planned and laid out for you,
by everyone
but you.
Just locked, stock and Jesus.
It's your turn Paul.
Take some chances.
Give safe a break, and be your
own man.
Just be you.
You finished?
Yeah.
Yeah I guess, I guess I am.
Good.
I don't think it's a good idea
that we see
each other anymore.
I'll pray for you, I will.
But you are so off base here.
Starting with Kelly.
No, I wasn't trying to be rude
about Kelly.
You spend 5 minutes carving
your way through
your jungle to Jesus, and you
think that you
have it all figured out.
I like you Gwyneth and I'm not
gonna lie
about that, and you are
definitely one of a
kind, and I have no doubt
of the incredible
journey that you're on.
Or that Jesus is waiting
for you with open
arms.
But I.
like I said, I'll pray for you
but beyond
that.
I was kidding about
the 40 days .
You don't even have a sense of
humor.
Okay that was wrong of me.
I'm sorry.
Please hear me.
I realized it wasn't enough to
talk about
God.
I needed to know God
personally .
So we started a conversation.
Leave me alone!
Really?
You're so obvious.
I remembered at my church the
preacher
saying that Jesus died for my
sin on the
cross, and he told me if I'd
turn from my
sin and ask Jesus into my life,
he would
come in.
I know, a little heavy, but
through all my
tears that night I finally
understood what
that meant.
Maybe you're knocking on one
door hoping
another will open.
I knocked on one more door, his
door, and
boy did it open.
You're 3E right Hayden?
I've got your mail right here.
Dear Senorita, me sorry for my
English not
so good.
I want to say 'Hi and thank you
very much
for coming to San Luis'.
My village, it looks so pretty
again, almost
like it was before.
It is like what you
taught us in school.
When bad things happened.
God made us stronger.
Just like you made our new
church stronger.
I made a photograph of it for
you.
It look beautiful.
It is beautiful.
Sorry again for my English.
I hope you like the photograph.
God bless you, Maria.
I want to visit many places.
I would like to see snow and
make a snow
angel from heaven.
I think the world is a
beautiful place.
But the most beautiful is here
because I
live here and it is my home.
And my family is here with me.
The end.
That was excellent, Maria.
And there is so much for
you all to see and
do, and I'm sure you'll all get
a chance to.
Senorita, senorita!
Es necesario que vay a la
iglesia ahorita.
English, please, Eduardo.
And slow down por favor.
You need to go to the church.
It's very important.
You must go now.
Hurry, hurry!
Jose, llama para me.
Did someone call me?
No se, no se.
I did.
Paul?
Wow, look at you, you look
great!
What are you doing here?
Truth?
I'm not really sure.
If you're looking for Kelly
she's not here
with me.
Not here or here.
There only one thing more
difficult than,
playing it safe.
You know what that is?
Admitting you're wrong.
And I was so wrong to let you
go, Gwyneth.
I came here to tell you that.
We get good cell service here.
I mean, a text message would've
been
cheaper.
But you can't do this with a
text.
So you maybe still
like me then ?
Truth is I never stopped.
Me neither.
I think we're being watched.
Do you want to meet
my kids?
I like the sound of that.
Come on.
So your papa, I've gotten to
know him on a
little on his visits down here.
And he is just an awesome guy.
And your momma, well,we're
going to have to
work on her a little.
She's definitely an acquired
taste.
Speaking of which, I don't
suppose we can
score some sushi around here?
Don't even try it.
You got me.
Hi!
You guys, wanna say 'hi' to
Paul?
Hey!
Hey you wanna show him
around?
Show me the hamster!
Yeah!
Hello!
The love of God
and love is never blind.
You see all the wrongs I've
tried to hide.
But you stay right by my side
when all the
world does not.
You're the one safe soul I've
got.
Man's greatest fear is being
alone and his
You'll still love me when I
start getting
old and wrinkly, right?
As long as you love me if I
start going
bald, right?
Start?
Really?
I used to think I knew it all.
I had all the answers and I
could spin a lie
with the best of 'em.
Now I'm pretty sure I
don't know anything
except Jesus is there for us.
All we have to do is call his
name.
And Mr. Right?
He's there too.
You just have to reach into
your heart and,
discover what's true.
done wrong.
We already know, I think it's
time for us to
find the freedom and the trust
of letting
go.
Let's take some time to thank
Him for the
blessings let's go big tonight
with all our
hearts adore Him.
With joy unspeakable let's get
on our feet
movin' to the beat.
Wave our hands high in the air.
Celebrate His love, grace that
is enough.
Give Him all of our cares
with joy unspeakable Joy
unspeakable.
Let's raise our voices to the
one because he
is worthy of all of our praise.
He's given us a second chance,
turned our
sadness into dance.
We have been changed.
Let's take this time to thank
Him for the
blessings.
Let's go big tonight with all
our hearts
adore Him with joy unspeakable.
Let's get on our feet movin' to
the beat.
Wave my hands high in the air,
air, air
Celebrate his love
Grace that is enough
Give Him all of our cares
With joy unspeakable, joy
unspeakable
You and I were made for more
Can't imagine what's in store
We were meant to soar like an
eagle
Leave religion at the door
Raise the roof and shake the
floor
Let's get loud and let's
explore
Joy unspeakable
Unspeakable
Let's get on our feet
Moving to the beat
Wave our hands high in the air
Celebrate His love
Grace that is enough
Give Him all of our cares
Joy unspeakable, unspeakable
We've got to celebrate
Joy unspeakable
Hey, hey, hey
Adios amigos!
For more new Movies go to
G2G.fm