SUBTITLES BY LUIS-SUBS
Jamie.
Hey.
I need you to read this.
Can you believe he texted me this?
In the middle of chem class.
So are you gonna do it!
No.
Maybe.
Well, what about you?
You and Danny have any naughty plans
for your one year celebration?
He's probably just gonna take
me to dinner or something.
Yeah, is that what
you're hoping for?
So what are you doing,
are you heading home?
Soon. I'm gonna go say
goodbye to Ms. Cohen first.
Oh, teacher's pet?
All right, I'll see you
after practice, okay?
Okay.
- Bye.
You are lucky.
I know.
Jamie!
I was hoping I'd get
to see you before I left.
This is for you.
Oh, you didn't have to.
Just a little something
for the baby.
Besides, you've helped me
a lot this year.
Jamie, you are gonna do great.
Your marks are excellent,
and if you just keep working
as hard as you have,
you can get into whichever
college you choose.
Even Whittendale?
Even Whittendale.
What about the new teacher?
Oh, Miss Matson, don't worry,
I've heard she's great.
I'm sure you'll really like her.
Let's go, man, you got it.
Our school has always taken pride
in our extracurricular activities.
Music, drama, but the
real feather in our cap...
is our baseball team.
For eight seasons straight,
we've won the state championships.
Wow.
Still though, it doesn't mean these
boys get any special treatment.
They're all expected to
maintain a passing grade.
If not, they're cut
from the team.
Now, I'll be emailing you your
class list by the end of the day.
And if there's anything else?
No, I don't think so.
Hey, dad.
Hey, Jamie.
M, honey, how was school?
Okay.
How did dad's job interview go?
Uh, not so good.
Can you do me a favor and make
sure he gets some dinner?
I gotta go to work.
So I guess this means I'm not getting
my cell phone back anytime soon.
Jamie, you know we'd like
to be able to get you that.
I know, we need
to cut back on expenses.
What's that?
My application to Whittendale.
Jamie, I need
to tell you something.
Your father and I,
well, we had to borrow from the
college funds to pay for the house.
And the taxes
were six months overdue,
and the bank was threatening
to take the house.
I don't believe this.
Jamie, I'm so sorry, but I'm
doing everything I can,
by taking the two jobs
and your dad's out of work.
So what, I don't get
to go to college now?
No.
No, no, no, I promise you
we'll make back the money.
How, mom?
Where are you going?
Over to Danny's.
Danny, stop.
What?
You know I'm not ready.
I know.
Just promise me that when you
are ready, I'll be the one.
I promise.
Okay.
You could knock first.
I don't need to knock
in my own home.
Besides, shouldn't you two be
studying at your own house?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Good night, Miss Campbell.
Good night, Jamie.
That's the third time she's
been here this week.
Yeah.
Look, maybe you
might want to think
about starting to cool
things off with her.
You guys fire her dad and now you
want me to brake it off with her?
Your father had no choice.
We had to downsize.
Danny, look at me.
You father and I have always expected
that you would go to Stanford.
But you are not going
to get into any decent college
if you spend all of your days playing
baseball or looking after Jamie hall.
You're not. You need
to get your grades up.
And that needs to be
your only focus.
Okay?
Yeah.
No wonder your real
momma didn't want you.
That's a lie.
No, it's not.
Don't say that, mommy.
No, I am not your mommy.
She's dead!
- No, be quiet!
- Dead!
Who'd want a sad
ugly freak like you?
Shut up!
Hey, how's it going?
Hello.
Looks like I won't be
skipping class anymore.
What?
Just kidding.
Hey.
Whats up, brother?
Good morning, everyone.
My name is Miss Matson.
I'm filling in for Mrs. Cohen
for the rest of the year.
Now, it's not my intention to come
in here and undo her curriculum,
but to pick up
where she left off.
So I had a chance to look
at some of your papers
on the meaning and impact of
your favorite literary quotes.
I have to say, I was
intrigued by a few of them.
Um, one being Trent Davies.
"Romeo, Romeo,
where for art thou, Romeo?"
- Hey, Romeo.
- Hey, babe.
And Jamie hall's "love never
claims it ever gives."
Jamie?
Who...?
Oh. Gandhi,
if I'm not mistaken?
Now, it's not a literary quote,
but it's lovely all the same.
How about...
"He who love touches not
walks in darkness."
Plato's symposium, and one
of my personal favorites.
Now, before you all
start groaning
about how you ended up
with such a mean teacher,
the following quiz is one
that Mrs. Cohen prepared...
before she left.
I'm just following
her curriculum.
Besides, you guys
should know this.
It's pretty easy, I think.
Take one, pass it down, please.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you.
Uh...
Uh, Danny...
Can I see you for a moment?
Uh... yeah.
I was speaking with the principal and she
mentioned that if you're going to stay
on the team, you need to maintain a 3.0.
How's that working out for you?
Not great.
Mm-hmm.
Well, um, the team
needs their captain,
and I'm here to get you out
of high school hell,
and to help you move on
to where you really wanna be.
So, why don't you
see me after school.
But I promise
I won't take long.
Um, yeah, all right.
That test was ridiculous.
Okay, which is a form of conflict?
A, man versus man?
B, man versus himself?
C, both of the above?
A?
All right, let me
ask you a question.
Um, do you have a girlfriend?
Uh, yeah.
All right, so let's say
you meet another girl and
she rocks your world...
Hmm.
But you love your girlfriend,
so what's going on
inside with you?
Conflict.
Exactly.
Man versus himself.
Ah.
This, this paper really has
a lot more promise now.
Yeah?
Thanks. Honestly,
you're the first teacher
who's ever given me
a second chance.
Aww.
You're pretty cool.
Thank you, Danny.
That really means a lot to me.
Yeah.
Thanks again.
Well, sure.
Hey, I'm free after
school on Thursday
if you need more help.
Uh, midterms are coming up.
Ah, actually, Jamie and I, our first
year anniversary is Thursday.
Oh.
Okay, so you already have plans.
Um, how about this, why
don't you, um, give me
your cell number and then I
can help you with your paper.
You know, find a topic.
Um, yeah, okay, cool
thanks again.
Anytime.
Here you go.
And I'll be right back
with refills of your tea.
Thanks.
Hello?
Lauren, it's me.
Hey, Phil.
How bad is he?
Really bad.
All right, well, I can't
do anything about it now,
but I'll take care
of it during my break.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Aww.
Hello!
Jamie, is your father home?
No. Why?
Well, Phil called, and he was in the
bar going off about Mr. Campbell.
He tried to stop him, but
he left in pretty rough shape.
I'm just worried that he
might be headed over there.
Okay, I'll go get him.
Hey, you pig!
What in the world?
It's the big bad wolf coming
to blow your house down.
What are you doing here?
You're home.
Of course I'm home.
I just want to talk.
What do you want to say?
I was there with you on
the ground floor, Brad.
18 years I gave you.
18!
And for what?
For nothing.
Do you even know
anything about loyalty?
Dad, come on.
It's time you went home, Steven.
To what?! To my house, the
house that gonna lose because
my 18 years of service with
your company are not valuable?
Gwen, go call the police.
No, please, I'll get him home right
now, okay? Dad, come on, please.
Let's go.
18 years, and look at you.
Who'd hire you now?
You don't need to beat him down
more than you already have.
Come on.
Ahh!
What have you done?
What have you done?!
Who's ugly now?
You're the first teacher who's
ever given me a second chance.
You're pretty cool.
Oh.
Very nice.
Great job.
Thank you.
All right, great job, guys.
Most of you did very well.
I was very impressed.
Um, Miss Matson?
Yes?
I was just wondering,
this is the first time
I've gotten a "C" on anything,
and I really need a good grade to
get a scholarship to Whittendale.
Whittendale.
Well, that's impressive.
My dad's been out of work
for over a year,
and anyways, I don't want
any kind of special treatment.
I just, I wanna know
what I can do.
Can I make it up somehow?
Was there something I didn't
understand about the assignment?
Not at all.
In fact,
you nailed
the assignment right on.
See, that was the problem.
There was nothing
personal in the paper.
Nothing showed me
that Jamie hall wrote it.
Oh. Well, I didn't realize.
My teachers always expect
a lot of references
and footnotes.
Well, I'm not
any of your other teachers.
Listen, I'm also
not a mean teacher,
so here's what we can do.
How about you pull
together another paper
by tomorrow, same topic, just
inject more Jamie into it,
and I'll mark it as your first.
By tomorrow?
Yes.
Is that a problem?
No, I just... I had
some important plans.
More important than college?
I'll cancel them.
That a girl.
All right, see you tomorrow.
You guys were so great
last weekend, honestly.
Let's go out and
do it again, guys.
- Hey.
Hi.
You excited for tonight?
Um, actually, I can't go out.
What do you mean?
We've...
We've been planning
this for weeks.
It's our anniversary.
I know.
I need to redo my paper.
It's just one "C."
But it counts for 10%
of my final grade.
I'm not lucky like you are.
My parents don't have the
money to send me to college.
I need a scholarship.
So this is my dad's fault again?
No, that's not what I said.
I gotta go.
Here.
Happy anniversary.
Hey!
Sorry you guys lost tonight.
Are you okay?
I heard that coach Braun
can really dole out
quite an earful.
Yeah, yeah, especially
to the team captain.
Aww.
Well, at least you have
your anniversary
to look forward to.
I would,
but Jamie bailed on me.
Oh, that's right.
Sorry, I just wanna give her
a chance to redo her paper.
No, no, that's cool.
Well,
do you have any other plans?
I was gonna go over to Trent's.
Well, if you're interested, I've
got a sure way to cheer you up.
Oh, yeah, what's that?
Hop in, and I'll show you.
I can't do this anymore.
I cannot keep holding
down the fort
while you go around
feeling sorry for yourself,
and drinking, and racking up
the credit card debt.
What do you want me to do?
I have over 18 years
of engineering experience
and I'm not just
gonna throw that away.
You know what,
maybe your problem is
you go down there and put
your confidence to your ego.
I have confidence.
Then go paint a house.
I've been out there every day
looking for a job.
I'm sick and tired
of hearing "you're too old."
You're on that
computer every day.
"You're too qualified,"
I'm sick of hearing it.
I understand your...
So what is this place?
It's exactly what you think it is,
a hole in the wall
in Chinatown.
Ooh, is it important?
No, it's nothing.
Okay.
So...
I found that the best cure
for anything is beer.
And a little MSG.
You sure that's okay?
It's just one beer.
I won't tell anybody
if you won't.
So, um... What were your
plans tonight with Jamie?
Were you guys gonna have dinner
and then a little
sex in the back seat?
What? I know what
it's like to be a teenager.
You can't exactly do it when
you're still living at home.
Yeah, right.
Maybe for those
that are actually doing it.
Aww.
Hello?
Hey, Heather, it's Jamie.
Do you know where Danny is?
Ah, yeah, he was
supposed to come over
to Trent's after the game.
Hey, did Danny ever show up?
No, I haven't seen him.
I guess he didn't show up.
That's weird.
Look, well, uh, if he shows up,
can you tell him to call me?
Yeah. Sure, I'll tell him.
Okay, thanks.
Okay, Danny,
here, if you ever need any extra
tutoring, here's my address.
Whoa.
My door is always open.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Oh. You know, ah,
I must've forgot my phone.
I'll be right back, okay?
Okay.
Ugly little girl.
You okay?
I just need
to get something, sorry.
Here it is.
I should probably
get back to my car.
Mm-hmm.
Hey. Hey.
Hi.
So, I called you last night.
Where were you?
I just went over to
Trent's after the game.
Hey, Danny!
- Whats up, man?
- Hey.
Hey, you guys going
to the big bash tonight?
- I don't know. Where is it?
- It's at Gil's.
His parents are going
to Tahoe for the weekend.
Nice. Yeah, I'm in.
What about you, Jamie?
She's probably got
to study or something, right?
No, I'll go.
Sounds like a party.
All right, babe, I'll see you.
- Danny.
- Hey.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hey. You made it.
Yeah, I said I was coming.
Look, I'm sorry
about cur anniversary,
and I want to make it up to you.
Come here.
Danny, stop.
I said stop!
Screw it.
Hey.
Do you know where Danny is?
No, why?
You guys doing okay?
I don't know.
Well, look, I've come to find that
when you're having boy troubles,
the best way to get over them
is by having a little fun.
Bottoms up, babe.
All right, let's see here.
Let's see here.
Oh. You know, it's
your battery terminal.
My what?
- This is your negative battery terminal.
- Uh-huh.
It's usually connected here.
Ohh.
Oh, no,
look how dirty your hands are.
Oh.
It's no big deal.
Oh, come inside and I'll
clean 'em off for you.
The movie I was gonna see
already started anyway,
so it's the least I could do.
Come on.
Okay.
Do you have a lot of car problems?
Well, my car's what do you think?
Give me your hand.
If you need a good mechanic,
I know one.
Do you know Tony's auto body?
They only take cash,
but they do a good job.
Are they, are they
like a chop shop?
- Something like that.
- Mm-hmm.
Um, I don't know if this is
doing that great of a job.
I don't know,
what do you think?
Sorry, I don't know
what I was thinking.
No, no, it's okay.
You're 18.
You can do whatever you want
with whomever you want.
Hey, it's okay.
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
It'll be our little secret, okay?
Where have you been?
God, Jamie, what...
What are you doing here?
It's one o'clock in the morning.
And what are you
just doing getting home?
Have you been drinking?
Don't turn this around on me.
I know you were
with someone tonight.
- I wasn't-
- Who is she?
- I wasn't with anyone.
- Liar!
Were you with her the night you
were supposed to be at Trent's?
Tell me, Danny.
Tell me who she is!
Hey, hey, what is going on here?
Are you drunk?
Why won't you talk to me?
Okay, Danny, go in the house
and call her a cab, please.
Go.
Do you have any idea how irresp...
Jamie, where are you going?
Jamie hall, do not
get into your car.
Jamie!
You're not going with her.
Hey, Jamie, come on.
Don't... don't-
what are you doing?
Jamie, don't drive off.
Pl...
Okay, all right, great.
Thanks, Gwen.
Jamie?
Where have you been?
I've been worried sick.
I was at a party.
Well, I just got off the phone
with Danny's mother.
She said you've been drinking?
I had like one drink.
One?
Jamie, you're 18.
You're not supposed
to be drinking at all.
And you're driving?
Whats wrong with you?
God, mom, can't you just
leave me alone
like you normally do?
Today, we're gonna
start reviewing
in preparation
for your midterm exam.
Mike, stop talking.
Today we've got a lot
to cover, guys.
Let's get started.
I can't believe she gave me a "c."
I did exactly what she wanted.
I rewrote the entire paper.
It's like she has
something against me.
Maybe you should try
talking to her again.
Look, there he is.
Are you gonna talk to him?
No.
Have you even seen him
since the party?
I tried calling him all weekend,
but he wouldn't answer.
Are you sure he's fooling around,
and he's not just brushing you off?
Heather, he's been lying to me.
Why else would he unless
he has something to hide?
I'm gonna go get
a frappuccino on the way home.
Are you coming?
Maybe later.
All right.
What?
There's nothing to say.
I don't believe it.
Coach Braun has
actually threatened
to kick me off the team.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure he's just
blowing off steam
so you'll do what you have to
to get your grades up.
With my help,
it's already happening.
Do you think it's enough?
Straight A's is
definitely enough.
Add your midterm grade to that, which I'm
sure you'll pass with flying colors,
and you're golden.
If you're going to stay on the
team, you have to maintain a 3.0.
Why don't you see me
after school?
Great job.
If I don't get into Stanford, my parents
are going to be so disappointed.
Do you want to go?
Of course, yeah.
I mean, it's a great school.
I just don't know
if I can hack it.
My-my dad's always been
so successful
at whatever he does.
I guess he just assumes
I'll be the same.
Sometimes mothers and fathers can
drive us to do things
we feel we have to do.
Are your parents like that?
I never knew my parents.
I... I had a foster mother.
She was something.
She was the only
mother I ever knew.
It's too bad she...
It's too bad she died
when she did.
It's such a horrible way...
To die by your own hand.
What have you done?!
Is she...
She killed herself?
Insulin overdose.
She was diabetic,
and they concluded that
she made a mistake...
A terrible, terrible mistake.
Who are you texting with?
Oh, just Trent.
What?
Nothing.
I guess I'm just...
I'm just stressed
with school and everything.
Miss Matson.
For some reason, she keeps
being extra hard on me.
What do you mean?
She keeps giving me lousy grades
when I know the work is good.
I mean, why would she do that?
How should I know?
- Look, I gotta go.
- Wait, Danny.
Can we talk?
Ah. Sorry, I've got
some stuff I got to do.
Like what?
Just running
some errands for my mom.
Can I talk to you later?
Did you miss me?
I just saw you in class.
Are you... are you failing
Jamie on purpose?
What is she telling you?
Nothing.
Really, I was just asking.
No, silly.
She's just being paranoid.
What the hell?
Oh. Oh, wait,
wait, wait!
I'll make sure that
she doesn't tell anyone.
No, I gotta go.
Jamie!
Jamie.
Jamie, please, wait.
Hey, Jamie.
Jamie, please-
how could you?
It's not what you think.
Are you serious?
I know what I saw, Danny!
You're making too big
a deal out of it.
You're having sex
with our teacher.
Jamie, listen, you know how
much of a hard ass my dad is.
If he found out about this,
he'd kill me.
He'd just--
He'd cut me off.
Miss Matson's flunking me out of senior
lit while you two are messing around,
and I'm supposed to protect you?
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Well, it did.
No, ple-- I will take care of this.
I promise.
Just... just please
don't say anything.
Jamie, is everything okay?
Danny?
Yeah.
Yeah, Mrs. hall,
everything's fine.
Jamie, whats going on
with you and Danny?
Didn't you hear him,
everything's fine.
It didn't seem that way to me.
Look, I'm sorry I got caught up
with everything going on,
but I am here.
Everything's fine, mom.
Answer!
Who'd want a sad
ugly freak like you?
Shut up!
He's mine!
Jamie? Jamie,
can I have a minute?
I had another look at the
paper you re-did for me,
and although I don't
do this very often,
I have to admit,
I believe I made a mistake.
If you think this is
how you're going to get away
with what you're doing,
you're wrong.
What?
Hey.
So, how'd the stake out go?
Did you catch him
doing anything or what?
No. No, I didn't.
See, I told you,
Danny's not the type of guy
that would fool around.
I gotta go.
I didn't want to say anything,
but Jamie's behavior has been
a little disrespectful lately.
How so?
Well, she became
very belligerent
the other day when I gave her a
poor grade on one of her papers.
She stormed off in a huff.
Do you want me to talk to her?
No, no, no,
I've got it under control.
I just thought
I'd share that with you.
She's going through a lot
of family problems at home,
and I just want to be
really supportive
and encouraging, you know.
She's one of our best students.
She certainly is.
Well, you let me know
if you need anything.
I will.
You're doing
a wonderful job, Molly.
Keep it up.
Thank you, Mrs. Jenkins.
Jamie.
How's it going?
Miss Matson gave me an "A."
Obviously, she was
failing me on purpose.
I'm sorry, I really am.
Thank you for not saying anything.
And I'm gonna end it tonight.
Do you mean it?
I swear.
My parents will be out later.
You can come over to the
house and we'll talk.
Okay. Later.
Of course he still wants me.
Oh, just look at ya.
Who'd want a sad
ugly freak like you?
Huh? Ugly...
Ugly... freak!
Freak!
All right, I'll be home later.
Wait just a second.
- Where are you going?
- To meet Jamie.
You have midterms in a few weeks.
You need to be studying.
I just have something I gotta
take care of, all right?
I'll be home soon.
What do you need
to take care of?
- Nothing.
- Danny, are you and Jamie breaking up?
Hi.
Nice spot.
Dark, secluded.
What do you have in mind?
Back seat?
Okay.
Whats wrong?
I... I just don't like the way
that you've been treating Jamie.
I gave her an "A."
What, is she still
bitching about it?
No, she's not bi...
It's not about that, Molly.
It's about this.
I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
Wait, wait, wait, she' been
talking to you, hasn't she?
She's trying to scare you.
There's nothing to worry about.
She's not gonna tell anybody.
She doesn't have any proof,
and besides,
we'll just deny it.
That's enough.
I gotta go.
Where are you going?
To see Jamie.
Why?
Because she's alone, Molly.
What... what's she
gonna do for you?
We both know she's not
gonna give herself to you.
That's enough.
I know that you want me.
No, I don't!
Stop, stop it!
I don't want you anymore.
Yes, you do.
Stop... God!
You're such a freak.
No...
Oh, no!
Danny?
Dad.
Hey, sunshine.
What are you doing out here?
Nothing, I... I just...
I thought I heard something.
No, it's just me.
You okay?
Yeah.
Did I scare you?
- You did scare me.
- Sorry.
Hi, I know it's almost over,
but can I get a ticket
to the 8:00 show?
Sure.
Thanks.
Danny, what do you want
for breakfast?
Danny.
Sweetie, I'm opening...
You have reached your destination.
Hi.
Hi. Can I help you?
Uh, yeah, can you-
can you fix this?
How'd that happen,
you ding it on the way
to the mall buying some new shoes?
Does it matter how it happened?
Easy.
I'm not your husband, lady.
Okay, uhh, is there somebody else I
can talk to, somebody more qualified?
Hey, I'm as qualified
as they get.
Carla, go pump some air
in some tires or something.
What can I do you for?
How fast can you fix this?
There's blood here.
- What?
- What happened?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I hit a deer.
How fast can you fix it?
Express service'll cost you extra.
I'll give you what you want
as long as you can
guarantee discretion.
I don't need a receipt.
Discretion'll cost you
a little extra, too.
How much?
Teenager, 18 years old,
and didn't come home last night.
Wow, that's a new one.
Yeah, his name is Danny Campbell.
Father's name is Brad Campbell.
Now, apparently, he's a big
mucky-muck friend of the mayor's.
They have just called,
and they want us
to move on this right away.
Right, because boy
with a silver spoon
- has got to get back by dinner.
- Yeah.
So did they order
a trace on the cell!
- 20 minutes ago.
- All right, let's go.
All right, I'll drive.
Hey, it's Danny.
Leave me a message
and I'll hit you back.
How long before you
get rid of the old one?
Salvage truck comes by on Monday.
And then what?
Then it gets shipped off
to a yard in Fontana.
Then it disappears forever.
Well, it should
for $2,000.
Don't worry,
your little secret is safe with me.
So is yours.
All right, here we go.
Text sent at 7:21 pm.
To an unidentified number.
Fantastic. It says here
to meet me at Bellevue Park.
Lover's Lane.
- Yeah.
- Great.
It's Peters.
Need a team to meet us
at Bellevue Park.
Got it.
Lets go.
All right.
Thank you, sir.
Someone didn't make much of an
effort to him or his wheels.
Yeah, it looks like they were in a bit
of a hurry to get out of here, huh?
What's forensics say?
Not a hell of a whole lot, actually.
But whoever did this
is one sick son of a bitch.
I mean, look at this poor kid.
You want me to call the family?
No. No, I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
Yes, we'll be right there.
Thanks.
I'm done with my homework.
What's wrong?
Honey, sit down.
That was detective Allen
from the police department.
They're at Danny's house.
Danny's house?
Why?
They don't have
all the details yet,
but they need us to come
down to the station.
Mom, just tell me what happened.
Honey,
Danny's dead.
What?
They found his body
in Bellevue Park.
- What did you do to him?
- Excuse me?
Danny said he was gonna
go see you last night.
Were you drunk, is that it?
Just so angry with him that
he was gonna end it with you
the you ran over him with your car?
Is that what you did?!
Is that the way you raise your daughter?
Why am I not surprised?
Calm down.
Hey, hey, hey, calm down.
Listen, I'm detective Allen.
This is detective Peters.
We talked on the phone earlier.
If you wouldn't mind just
following me over here.
Yeah, if you wouldn't
mind having a seat
right here, I'll have somebody
get you some water.
Just right here.
Just for a few minutes, okay?
Jamie, when was the last
time you saw Danny Campbell?
At school.
Um, around three.
Did you talk to him?
Yeah.
Well, what did he say?
He said he was gonna come
by, and he never showed up.
And that's it?
He also said that he was gonna
take care of something.
What was that?
It's okay, honey.
Go ahead.
He said he was gonna
break up with his girlfriend.
Jamie, I thought
you were his girlfriend.
He was seeing someone else.
Any idea who?
Our teacher, Miss Matson.
What?
Jamie, do you have
any proof of that?
He told me, and I
saw them together.
Okay, where?
At her house.
Mr. and Mrs. hall,
you knew nothing about this?
- No.
Hey, Jamie, so you never mentioned
any of this to your family,
to your parents,
or to any high school officials?
No.
Why not?
He didn't want me to.
It's just-that's
such a horrible thing to say.
I-I just... I can't believe it.
So, Miss Matson, there was
nothing inappropriate
about your relationship
with Danny Campbell then?
Oh, absolutely not.
I would never do anything
to hurt any of my kids.
Just the thought of
that is-is just so vile.
So why do you think Jamie hall
made this accusation?
I don't know. She's one
of my best students.
Although, I will say that
she has had a change in
behavior the past couple weeks.
Such as?
She's become
increasingly belligerent.
We had an episode a few days ago.
Go on.
She got a bad grade on a paper,
and... she almost threatened me.
Sort of. She said you will
never get away with this.
And did you discuss this
with anybody?
Yes, I did, principal Jenkins.
And we decided not
to do anything about it.
We thought, you know,
it's due to stress.
You know, family problems.
Her father's out of work.
Danny.
Miss Matson,
if you could be so kind
as to tell us about
her problems with Danny.
Oh, I-I I don't know.
I obviously don't pay attention
to the teenage dramas that
swirl around high school.
But I did overhear that
Jamie was accusing Danny of,
um, seeing someone else.
Who knew it was me?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Miss Matson,
where were you Friday night
between the hours
of 7:30 and 10:00 P.M.?
Friday?
I was at the movies.
Oh yeah?
What did you see?
I saw BlackBerry Winter,
actually, down at the
Broadway palace downtown.
You know, because
I love those old theaters.
You wouldn't happen to still have
that ticket stub, would you?
I don't know.
I think I might, actually.
Yep, BlackBerry Winter,
it says here.
And the time is there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it does.
Okay, well, she was
acting a little weird.
I mean,
Danny was blowing her off,
but she was taking it like he was
cheating on her or something.
Was he?
No, not that I know of.
She even followed him
home one day.
And I told her that
was crazy, and I was right.
She said she didn't
catch him doing anything.
So she admitted to you that she
never saw him with anyone else?
Yeah.
What was her general disposition that
day at school, the day Danny died?
I'd say she was sort of
pissed off.
I'm just saying,
I'm not buying the fact
that he was sleeping
with his teacher.
Well, it's Jamie's word
against Molly's.
But we do know that Jamie was angry at
Molly for giving her the bad grade.
Okay,
what do we have here, right?
The key to this whole case is
this prepaid cell phone, right?
If we can find out who Danny sent
that text to, we got our killer.
Well, I say we start with Jamie.
She's the only one
with a clear motive.
And the only one
who can't prove to us
her whereabouts between
eight and ten P.M.
On the night of the murder, right?
Right.
Think we got enough?
- Yeah, just enough.
- Yeah.
- Calling it in?
- Yep.
- Lieutenant Ryan.
- Gonna need a warrant.
Location?
The hall residence.
Nice to see you again.
We have a search warrant.
- What?
- Yep.
No, you can't just come in here
and start searching my place.
No, Jamie didn't do anything.
She's been really cooperative.
She's told you everything
that she knows.
Mom, whats going on?
The detectives brought
a search warrant.
Why?
That's exactly
what I want to know.
Folks, please,
let's just calm down, okay?
This is just part
of an investigation.
Now if you're telling us the truth,
we'll be out of here in no time.
And you could really help us out
if you gave us your cell phone.
I don't have one.
Yeah, that's right,
we took it away
- a couple months ago.
- Uh-huh.
- I think I'll check the car.
- Good idea.
- Excuse me.
- I'll check the living room.
Jamie, are you telling us
everything you know?
Mom,
I don't know what's going on.
You know what, I'm gonna
call our lawyer.
Hey, check this out.
Yeah?
What you got?
This, right here.
Ken. Ken.
Yeah.
There's something
you should see.
What do you got?
Check out the front bumper.
This is your car,
isn't it, Jamie?
Yes.
That looks like you got some
dried blood on your bumper.
I don't know
how that got there.
Jamie, what happened?
What is that?
- Did you hit something, honey?
- No.
- Ken.
- Yeah?
I've never seen that before.
- Where was that?
- Jamie, did you buy a phone?
No, I didn't.
That's not mine.
We got what we need.
Bag it.
- You're under arrest.
- What are you doing?
Hold on, detective.
- Mom?
- Anything you say can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
Mom?!
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you can't afford one, it will be
provided to you at the public's expense.
Mom!
Jamie!
- Mom!
- Jamie!
Good.
Get some sleep,
and we'll see you tomorrow.
Danny's got a girlfriend.
I know. What was that
about the school teacher?
- There he is.
- How is she?
She's fine. They're gonna hold her over
night until the bail hearing tomorrow.
Will she be safe?
They'll put her in a private cell.
She won't have to mix
with the general
population.
I made sure of that.
Can-can we get her
out tomorrow?
Well, the D.A. Has
a compelling case.
The blood they found on Jamie's bumper
was positively identified as Danny's.
Oh, my God.
Couldn't have someone
planted it there,
- and the phone?
- Yes.
And these are the arguments
I'll be making tomorrow.
Along with the fact that
she's an honor's student.
She's got no priors.
I think there's a good chance
the judge'll grant our request.
Don, how much will all this cost?
For manslaughter,
this statute is 100,000.
And so you'll need
50 grand to make bail.
Okay?
Okay.
Thanks, Carl.
I'm sorry to call you so late.
It's all right.
But you know what we're up against.
Yeah.
All right, so I'll see
you in the morning.
- Take care.
- I really appreciate it.
Bye bye.
What happened?
Thank God for my brother.
Between him and my parents, and whatever
we can borrow off our credit cards,
I think we can come up
with the 50k.
Thank God.
Hall was arrested
in connection with the hit and run
death of what we have since learned
was her boyfriend, Danny Campbell.
And while police are saying
very little about the charges,
we have learned that a bail
hearing has now been set
for 11:00 tomorrow morning.
We'll of course be here
and have a live report for you.
For now though,
from Wilfred High School,
I'm Rick chambers.
Let's go back to the studio.
Look at this thing.
I feel like a dog on a chain.
Yeah, well, according to don,
we're lucky the judge
let you out at all.
So I think that's
a small price to pay.
So, I-I can't leave the house,
at all?
Not until the trial.
But that could be months.
Your mom and I are doing everything
we can to get you out of this.
Did they question Miss Matson?
Apparently so.
And?
She's got an alibi.
Well, she's lying.
Danny told me he was
gonna go see her that night.
She's the one who killed him.
No, honey, we believe you,
it's just the police have nothing
to connect her to the crime.
Did they check her car?
I don't know.
Well, there has to be some
sort of evidence in it.
And if the police won't look,
then maybe we should
look ourselves.
Okay.
Miss Matson.
Yes, may I help you?
I'm Lauren hall.
Jamie's mother.
Oh!
Are you here to, uh,
pick up her homework?
Something like that.
How is she?
Not good.
She spent the night in jail.
Oh. I heard about that.
I'm so sorry.
- Miss Matson...
- Mm-hmm?
Someone's trying to frame
my daughter for murder.
Really?
Who would do such a thing?
I don't know.
Maybe you.
Uh, Mrs. hall,
I really resent that.
The police have investigated this,
and I have been completely exonerated.
She saw you with Danny.
Your her mother, of course
you're gonna believe her.
I can assure you,
she's making that up.
You know, I never held Jamie's
accusations against her.
Even after Danny told me the
trouble that they were having.
And you know why?
Because I know about
love, young love.
And that makes people say
and do crazy things.
So Danny confided in you?
No.
He was looking for
someone to talk to.
Oh, and lucky for him,
you were there.
Or was it luck?
Mrs. hall, I have
a faculty meeting right now,
so I'll have her homework ready
for you to pick up tomorrow.
See you then.
Sure.
Your destination.
Hey.
Um, are you Gino?
Yeah.
I was wondering
if you could help me.
Was there a car
that was brought in,
sometime this week,
it was like a silver jeep,
a license plate "4D0Q67B"?
Sorry, don't ring a bell.
Are you sure?
A woman,
dark hair, attractive?
She may have brought it in
with some damage
to the front end?
Told you, I don't remember.
Look, my daughter
might go to jail
for a hit and run that she didn't commit
unless I prove that she didn't do it.
And I am sure that you
have the evidence here-
look, I don't need any cops snooping
around my place. You got it?
So like I said,
I don't remember.
Hey.
- I know the chick you're talking about.
- You do?
Yeah, skinny bitch
with hot pink lips,
came in here with a broken grill.
Do you still have it?
Not any more.
It went to scrap three days ago.
So is it true, this chick
really hit someone?
A young man.
My daughter's being blamed for it.
Are you sure you can't help me?
You think you can talk to the
police and tell them what you know?
If I talk, I'm out of a job.
I got kids, too.
She was there, Steven.
The owner, Gino, he didn't
want to talk about it,
but his mechanic, she was
telling me everything.
She confirmed that
Molly dropped her car off
Saturday morning.
The grill on her car, that's the
only evidence we would have,
but I guess that was hauled
off, what, three days ago.
Other than getting her
to confess,
there's nothing we can do.
Then let's do it.
Do what?
Let's get her to confess.
I mean, if I confront her,
maybe she'll...
No, no, no, I don't want you
anywhere near that woman.
And besides,
you can't leave the house
with that thing on your ankle.
The police'll track
you down in 10 minutes.
I did that.
I'm so stupid!
Okay, what am I gonna do?
What do I do? I mean,
I have to cover my tracks!
You idiot!
Okay, where are you?
Where are you?
I'm here. Okay.
My head hurts.
What did I do wrong?
Stupid!
Shut up!
Ugly little girl.
Ugly! Ugly! Ugly! Ugly!
Shut up!
We could go back to Brad,
I don't know.
We could get money from Brad.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I mean, I could try him.
Okay, but still, it all takes money,
honey, and we don't have the money.
We have to think of other options.
I don't know
what to do anymore.
Look, we know that she's innocent,
and we just have to keep fighting.
This is one of those surreal moments
you think this has got to be made up.
I know, I know.
Jamie.
What are you doing?
Hey.
We need to talk about
your good friend Gino.
You know, the one
who runs the chop shop.
What?
We have the grill.
You know, the one you replaced
the day after you killed Danny?
Oh, I don't...
They didn't haul it off
like they told you.
They kept it.
That's not true.
Gino gave it to my mom.
She's on her way
to the police right now.
I'm sure there's plenty
of evidence on it.
No, there's not.
I didn't do anything.
Why, did you wipe it off?
The same way you wiped
the blood on my bumper?
Okay, I-I I'm not gonna listen to this.
You need to go.
You put that blood on my car, and stashed
the phone in the glove compartment.
No, I didn't. You're crazy!
Get out of my house.
Why did you kill him,
Molly, huh?
- What?
- Was he gonna tell on you?
Was he gonna get you
fired from your job?
If you have the grill,
why are you telling me this?
You're trying
to get me to say something.
What, are you trying
to trick me or something?
What is this?
You were.
Yah!
You're trying to record
my confession?
Get out of my house!
He didn't want you.
He used you like a whore he used you
to get what he thought he needed.
Uh-huh.
He told me what he
really thought of you.
He said you were a crazy old
lady, that you disgusted him.
And how long did you think
he was really gonna be with you?
Look at you.
You're pathetic.
That's not true.
Danny wanted me!
You think because you're
so pretty and so popular
that you're better than I am?!
You-you think who would want
to be with poor, ugly Molly?
He wanted to be with me!
But because you interfered,
he's not with me anymore.
You stupid, selfish little-
oh, you cut my face.
Oh, look who's pathetic now.
Don't like that, do you?
You know what, I can't believe
that Danny made such a
stupid mistake, for this?
Danny got what he deserved.
And now, you...
Oh, God! Detective!
I'm go glad!
She broke into my house... Stop!
Listen, she's telling the truth,
and I heard everything
you said about Danny,
- so stop it, okay?
- No, this is her fault!
- She cut me!
- Miss Matson, I need you to calm down.
Please, calm down, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
Now, are you all right?
You're not hurt or anything?
Don't move!
You don't know what
to do with a gun.
Wanna bet?
Hey, it's okay.
I can handle it.
We were worried.
Here she comes.
Well, apparently,
this wasn't the first time.
She admitted to being involved
in a student affair back east,
but the district covered it up.
And she was able to move to L.A.,
and just get a job like
nothing ever happened?
She had the credentials.
That's all she needed.
What kind of sentence
will she get?
Manslaughter, and attacking a police
officer, I'd say 20, 25, easy.
Detective, I wanted
to ask you something.
Sure.
Why'd it take you
so long to get here?
My dad said it would
only take 10 minutes.
I was kinda counting on that.
You know what, Jamie,
the next time you wanna jump in,
I suggest you do it before
rush hour would be good.
Oh.
Let's go.
Down 17, the Nasdaq down 38...
- Hey, mom.
- Hey.
Is dad home yet?
Nope, but he promised he'd be home
from work in time for dinner.
Oh, by the way,
you got some mail today.
So...?
"We are happy to offer you
admission to Whittendale
University
and are delighted to have
you as our new student."
Oh, honey, I am so proud of you.
The day after Molly Matson
was sentenced to prison
for manslaughter,
we asked a variety of
students how they might react
if confronted
with a teacher temptress.
Here's what John Ludlow from Litton
High School had to say. Take a look.
Well, if she looks anything
like that Miss Matson,
hell yeah, I'd let her
have her way with me.
I mean, look at her, she's hot.
If that were my teacher,
I'd never skip class.
Oh, that's sweet.
John.