* time is a stealer
* a stacked deck dealer
* deals you time
* then takes time away
* you learn if you're lucky
* you never waste a day
* time is a racer
* a comet chaser
* stops for no one in its quest *
* and thinks nothing of it
* to pass you by
* leave you stranded
* with all the rest
* what about that bride tomorrow? *
* all those best laid plans
* what about the time you counted upon *
* the time that was in
* now is gone
oh, Bob, we picked upa little
eight-unit dealout there in Taylor.
Yeah?
You need some work, though,
if you can get to it.
Okay, I'll take a look.
Good to see you.
See you, Mr. McHenry.
Tommy.Hi, dad.
Get the stick.Get the stick.
Good boy.
You got him trained? Sort of.
It just must be the center of our concerns,
but we will not permit those
who fire upon us in Vietnam
to win a victory
over the desires
and the intentions
of all the American people.
Smells good, Ruth.
They only got a few yearsto
go to end this war
before Tommy's old enoughto go.
Mr. McHenry, it'll just aboutend
about then, I'm telling you.
I don't see itlasting till 1970.
Do you, Ruth?
Lord, I hope not.
Are you going to be here
forsupper tonight, Mr. McHenry?
No, I've got to go into town.
I'll pick up something.
* if you're lucky that love is a thing *
* you don't save for a rainy day *
* you don't save love for a rainy day *
excuse me, are you Mr. McHenry?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, hello.How do you do?
My nameis Carol fritzsimmons,
and I just wantedto congratulate you
and your new store.
I think it's really goodfor the town.
Oh, thank you.lt was kind of handed to me.
Well, actually, do you know,
I'm a seamstress myself,
and I'm a very good one,
and I was just thinking
that if you'd recommend
meto any of your customers
who might needsome alterations,
I'd be very happy to give youa
percentage of whati charge them
because I'm... well, anyway, I'm
raisinga daughter by myself,
and I'm just... I'm
trying to make ends meet.
Fucking sack of shit.
Typical... typical raise.
Oh. Anti up.
Name was Clayton,
Clayton fritzsimmons.
Crazy son of a bitch,
real sharp lookingpiece of shit.
Drunk all the time.
Fuck anything.
Had what he had at home,
go out and fuck anything.
Wild temper.
Wild man.
Could play cards with you.
Drove like a maniac.
It finally killed hima few years back.
I didn't ask about him.I asked about her.
I dated her once.
She went out with you?
Fuck you, yes.
Well, wasn't exactly a date.
We had coffee in a diner.
She was sitting therewith a cup of coffee.
I sat down.
Highly attractive.
Jay, she's too prettyfor you.
Oh...
You the big winner?
Tonight I was.
You always win.
Nobody wins all the time, joleen.
That's whythey call it gambling.
It's too early to go home.
Where are we going?
Look. Louis is going to bewalking
out the doorany second now.
Now, come on. Why don't you
just getout of the car
and go on home with him.Okay?
I'd rather not.
Get down. Get down.
Joleen.
I got a feeling here.
I can't keep going onwith you.
Why not?
It's not right.
God's going to punish
you'cause of your wife?
Yeah, maybe,
and your husband.
Honey, she is nevergoing to know.
And she's never comingout of that home.
You know it.
I'm going to tell louisall about us.
That's right.
All about us.
How do you like that?
You think that you can justuse
me like some dish rag
and then toss mewhen you're finished?
Like I got no feelingsabout this,
no say in the matter?
Well, I can be a bitterand
a vengeful woman, reece.
You have misjudged me.
I don't think I have.
That wife of yoursis a
perfect shield against me.
Isn't she?
Against Carol Fitzsimmons.
What do you know about Carol?
I know that she's beencoming around you
and insinuating herselfinto your life.
But you want to be free.
Free? I'm not free.
Oh, yes, you are.
Nobody's figured that
out yetbut me and you,
and that's the beauty of it. Isn't it?
You can cat around
without having to reportto anybody.
But if somebodystarts getting too close,
you have gotthe perfect excuse,
the perfect responsibility,
just lying up therein that hospital bed,
and you can't deny it. It's the
truth, and you know it is.
Look, let's getsomething straight.
All right?
I am not leavingthe woman I married,
even if she laysin that hospital bed
for the rest of my life.
What a waste, reece.
You're younger than me,
a lot younger.
And I'm not burdenedby pesky traits
like moralityand strength of character.
Yeah, I've got a lot of those, obviously.
I'm here withanother man's wife.
Where you going now? You going
to go bythe little shop?
I might.
You might?
You might? You might see Carol.
Tell me something, reece.
Have you sleptwith the poor widow already,
or are you justworking up to it?
Audios.
Are you going to buythis outfit?
Oh, my... what are you...
oh... I'm sorry.
Excuse me. What are you going here?
I brought my boy down herefor the weekend.
Your boy.Yeah, I've gota 15-year-old son.
Oh, I... I havea 13-year-old daughter.
Is that right? Yeah, I do.
Well, where is she?
Oh, she's around heresomeplace.
I brought her up herefor the weekend.
Look, why don't we find her,
and we can all go havelunch together?
Oh, actually I... she's
at the lake swimming,
so I...
So is mine.
Really? Yeah.
Why don't I buy you lunch, then?
Oh, well, I... come on.
You're not going to buythis outfit.
No.
No, no, not this.
I could make this thingin an afternoon.
Where... you all stayingat the cabins?
Um, yes... oh, actually,
yes, I'm staying at...
I'm cabin five.
Really? Mm-hm.
I'll be darned. I'm in seven.
No, are you really? Mm-hm.
Coincidence.How did that happen?
Thank you.
Um... Hot dog?
Sure, I'd love a hot dog.
That would be good. And also a beer.
Couple hot dogs? Yeah, and a beer.
I always said words funny.
You did? Mm-hm.
What do you mean?
I thought that bouillabaisse
was pronounced "boolabase."
I thought it was a soup, boolabase.
Boola.
I had no idea what"boola" was, "boo-ah."
Boola, boola.I don't...
What... what becameof your husband?
Oh...
Well, he was killedin a car wreck
off the highwayabout four years ago.
Mm, sorry to hear that.
Yeah.
Your wife?
Um...
She... do you wantanother beer?
Mm-hm.
Oh, do know who vin Scully is?
Baseball guy?
Yes, sports announcer.
I thought his name
waspronounced Vince kully.
Vince kully.
Oh, dear.
It's hopeless.
I can understand.
Are you having any luckwith that?
Turned out to be little
bittougher than I thought it was.
Really? I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked you.
You didn't ask.
I volunteered.
Really, no. No, I should've
calledthe plumber.
No, I can... I can fix it, but...
You can?
Uh, plumber would probablyfix it right.
Yeah? What?
Wait, you knowi'm still married.
I mean, you knowthe
circumstances.I'm still married.
What, are you afraidyour wife's
suddenlygoing to wake up?
No. Things are going to beback to normal?
She's going to walk in on us
or something like that?
No, but... What?
To have a steady girlfriend,
you think that'sthe right thing to do?
Oh, wait a minute. Have I
missed something here?
Who asked you if you
wanteda steady girlfriend?
I just thought it wasin the air.
Don't try and read my mind. Okay?
I'm sorry.
You should be.
You should be really sorry
because I have a boyfriend.
You do?
You don't.
Oh, he's so surprised.
You can't believe it, huh?
No, I mean I...
that's right.I have a boyfriend.
I didn't know.
Well, now you know.
And I don't need you to makeany phone calls
for me either
because I can callmr. Quillet myself.
You see, I'm not helpless. Right.
Because you know what?
We're not livingin the dark ages.
This is the 1960s,
so you better wake up
because women can calltheir own plumbers
and women, too...
can enjoy themselveswith
their... you know, their...
their boyfriends and...
Somebody who isn't their...
what are you doing? Their boyfriends.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
I mean, what the hell's going on?
Your boyfriend hereor something?
I have company, yes.
Carol?
What? What aboutthis afternoon?
You know, the plumbing and every...
what are you talking about? I mean, I...
you know whati'm talking about.
No, I don't knowwhat you're talking...
vin Scully and...
We had sexon the bathroom floor.
You barely said a word to me.
You left.
I had no ideayou were coming over here.
Well, I'm here now.I'm here now.
Well, you're here, and I have a guest.
Okay? Excuse me.
Hey! No. I mean it. Good-bye.
Ah!
Getting wet? Oh! Oh.
Look, is there any reasonwhy
we can't be friends?
I just... Well, no. I'd like that.
Well, I mean, there, for a while,
you were coming around, and...
I don't you know... you stopped and...
I thought we had a
fight.Well, that was a...
A fight is when youand your
husband exchange blows,
when the house is destroyed,
when the horrible wordsyou
scream at each other
echo years and years later,
when he gets into a carand
drives it off into the night
to burn to deathoff some old highway,
and your only daughterforever
has screamingnightmares, reece.
That's what a fight is.
What did we have then?
We had a few words.
Well, here's a few more.
I don't particularly likegene Hamlin.
I recognized his car.
Gene Hamlin happens to bea very nice man.
Don't tell me about him.You play poker with
a man, you get to know him pretty fast.
Well, I'm sorryif you don't approve, so...
Look, I don't wannaargue with you.
Well, anyway, look, I should be going.
So... friends or...
Look, it's Wednesday afternoon,
it's raining, and I already let my girl go.
Why don't I just close shop,
and we could, uh, take a little drive?
What do you say?
Do you evergo to the movies?
No. I never do.
Do you know that one ofmy
favorite things in life
is to go to the moviesin the afternoon?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Especially if it's raining.
What was I saying?
Sex.
Oh, yes.
I was hoping you'd forgotten.
Um...
Well, we just had do you see
that couple? A pretty
good sex life, you know?
It just was very...
I just...
I enjoy sex. It was nice.
We were pretty wild, Martin and me.
Tell me what you mean by that. What
do you mean you were pretty wild?
Well...
We had a good sex life.
Come on.
Reece, what are you doing?
Nothing.
You were waitingto see them, weren't you?
No, no, no. Yes, you were.
No. Look, aren't you curious?
Do you wanna stayand see who they are?
I think we should tellthe manager that
if wewanna see that kind of thing,
we can just goto the drive-in.
We were young once.
Okay. Okay, we forgive them.
We won't tell the manager. Okay.
Now, do you thinkthey're gonna
stayand see the whole movie?
Yes, if they didn'tsee it the first time.
Oh, lookit. You see that? You
know what that is? What?
No. What is that? That is
a sonybetamax machine.
Uh-huh. What's it do? Well,
it shows you moviesat home.
Home movies? Yep.
Wow.Well, no.
You have a motion pictureon
a videocassette tape.
And you stick it in that thing, and it
shows you the movieon your t.V. Screen.
I don't understand that. Why
would you wanna do that?
It's like... it's like...
no, I mean,
it's like a recordof a song.
Where are yougonna buy a movie?
You can buy them now.
You can rent them.
I really don't understandwhat
you're talking about.
It's in the future. It's coming.
If I wanna watch t.V., then I watch t.V.
If I wannago to the movies, then I do that.
But thiscombines them both.
Why? Why?
Tell me why.Come on, reece.Tell me why.
Thanks, Phil. Yeah.
I'm good to go? Yes, sir.
All right.Thank you.
See ya.
You know, one of these days, they're
gonna discontinuethe Wednesday matinees.
Why would they do that?
'Cause nobody comes.Well, we do.
Yeah, but we're not enough. Oh, yeah.
And how wasthe movie today?
It was good. We enjoyed it.
Yes. She was really good, I thought.
Thank you, Mike. You bet.
Uh, I can't stay long today
because I have a thingback at the house.
You don't workon Wednesday afternoon.
I know, but this girlis getting married,
and this was the only timeshe had, so...
Wait a minute, wait a minute. Mm-mm.
George segaland glenda Jackson. Oh.
Okay. Oh, God. A touch of class.
Hmm.I got one.
Oh, wait a second. No. All right.
I know. I got a better one.
All right. Okay. Okay.
Steve mcqueenand Sharon Farrell.
All right. Uh-huh.
Wait. This iseight or nine years ago.
You're so... no. Wait a minute.
Sharon Farrell... sad. Sad.
Um, the reivers, they called it.
You're good. Okay. You're very good.
I'm just tryingto keep up with you.
Hey, Mike,
have you ever heardof this machine
that plays movies at home?
What do you mean, like a
little movie projector?
No. This is different.
We had a bell & howell.
See what I mean? No...
Mike, this is by Sony.
Hell, I don't knowwhat
you're talking about.
Never.lt'll never work.
Because that just worries
me, you know what I mean?
Oops. Looks like they're here.
What do you mean?
Oh, no. They're waiting on me. All right.
Okay, you going backto the store?
Oh, look at her.
Hmm? Yeah, I thinki'm gonna go back there
and move things arounda little bit.
Do you want some supper? Sure.
Okay. Well, I'll come by,
and we'll go out, okay?
Sounds good. Like we've doneevery Wednesday
for the past 12 years.
You complaining? No.
You know thatronnie's older sister...
yeah? Got married seven years
agoin San Francisco, California,
out of doors, in the nude?
Oh, Mary Anne, I wouldn't go
aroundtelling people that.
But why not?
Oh, all right.
Where's the... I'll be right back.
Let me look at you.
You're fabulous. Yes.
It looks good. Hello?
Oh, dottie, hi. What...
I don't understand.
Honey, what's the matter?
You don't sound goodat all.
Would you excuse mefor a minute?
It's my sister from Canada.
She lives there, of all places.
What is it, dottie? What?
Oh, boy.
Nipples.
Lisa freelander. Lisa freelander?
Nipples? You always saidshe had no nipples.
Well, she had very, very
smallnipples, that's right.
I said best nipplesof all time.
But Lisa hadenormous tits.
I'm not talkingabout the whole tit.
Well, something aboutthose enormous tits
made those tiny nipplesvery special.
Oh, I see.I understand.
Now, those nipplesby themselves...
no, I don't think they'd
doanything for you.
But in context... world's best nipples.
Right. Mm-hmm.
Feet.
Jennifer schneiderfrom law school.
Small, beautifully done, immaculate feet.
Great-looking toes.
Nails polished just right.
Oh, I used to beg herto walk
on my backwith those feet.
Now, uh, tell meabout the girl you met.
Well, it's the craziest thing.
Her mother and my dadbeen
friends for years.
But you never met?
Well, once years and years
ago, but she doesn't remember.
Just the one time?
Guess I was awayor she was
awayor we were both away,
but I never forgot her.
Now you're both in townand you hook up.
What'd you do?
Well, I took her to lunch,
caught an afternoon movie.
Touchy-feely.
Of course, we got all worked up.
Took her backto somebody's place?
I took her home, and I dropped her.
She shot you down?
No, Eddie.
I just didn't feellike
closing the deal yet.
Well, why not?
Oh, I guess the motherand
your father thing?
Yeah, some of that.
And I liked her.
You liked her?
Yeah.
So, show some respect.
A little. Yeah.
I see. I understand. Next time.
Next time, maybe, yeah.
Which is tonight, 'cause
I'm going over there.
Not wasting any time.
No.
I understand.
This time, she's had it.
This time, she's gonna
getwhat's coming to her.
Any potentialfor this one?
Yes, lots of potential.
For a body part award?
Well, it's early yet, but I think so.
What's her name?
Katherine fritzsimmons.
Don't know her. Good.
**
That didn't take long. No.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Something's the matter.
Boy, can I just be readlike a book?
Well, I can read you.
You know, the motherof
this bride-to-be told me
that her daughterhad not been promiscuous
because men like girlswho are chaste.
So, of course, I get this picture
of this pack of roving men
chasing this girlall over the place.
"Chaste"... c-h-a-s-t-e.
I know. It's c-h-a... I know.
I finally figured that out.
And "bouillabaisse." Yeah, right.
But you know mewith the words. Mm.
Reece?
Hmm?
I got a phone callfrom
my sister up in Canada.
And, well, her healthhas fallen to pieces,
and she's... she's desperate.
For what?
For somebody.
Who?
Me.
I'm the only personshe's got.
Well, how sick is she?
She's sick. She's very sick.
So you might have Togo up there for awhile?
I might have Togo up there to live.
You mean forever?
Well, she's notgonna live forever,
but for as long as she does, she needs me.
Wait. You're gonna moveup
to Canada to live?
Reece, you asked mewhat was the matter.
Well, isn't there somebody
elsethat could be with her?
I'm her only family. A friend or something?
She needs morethan a friend dropping by.
She needs somebodyfull time.
Well, she can't ask youto
change your whole life.
She didn't come right outand ask me, but...
maybe youmisunderstood her. No. No.
I know what the situation is.
So, I mean, how soondoes she need somebody?
Now.
You mean, I'm gonna lose
my best friendin the whole world?
Is that what I am, your best friend?
Yeah, you are.You're the
best friendi've got.
Well, maybe you're justgonna
have to pack right up
and move on upto Canada, too, reece.
I'm not moving to Canada.
It's cold up there.
You can't either. I don't know what to do.
Well, don't move to Canada.
They ice fish up there.
Well, I'm not gonnaturn
my back on my sister.
Mm-mm.
You're not mad at me, are you?
No. Of course not.
I'm racking my brainstrying
to figure out what to do.
Oh. Louis.
What are you doing openthis afternoon?
Hi, Louis.Well, actually,
I'm not open, Lou.
What'd you two do, go to the movies?
Mm-hmm.
You two and yourwednesday matinees.
Whole town knowsabout you two.
Knows what?
Aw, hell with them.
Don't misunderstand me, reece.
Nobody blames you.
People understand.
They do?
What brings you in, Lou?
You wanna sell these?
Or make a tradefor a suit, reece.
Carol? Mm?
You remember thisyou made for me? Oh.
For joleen. God, yes, I do remember that.
Oh, look at that.
Well, I guess I could
give youabout five bucks.
Is that fair?
That sounds fair.
And what kind of suitdid you have in mind?
Dark. Black, I guess.
You're, uh, 44 long?
Uh-huh.
I used to havea black suit once.
It might still be in heresomewhere, reece.
What do you wantwith a black suit for?
Who died?
Joleen.
What?
What are you talking about?
Joleen died.
What... what happened?
She died yesterday at noon,
straight up and down.
How?
Her heart.
She had a defect in therefrom birth.
Oh, Louis.
I didn't know.
Uh-huh.
She diedat the ironing board.
Ohh!
She was ironing mea shirt.
She just fell.
Her heart stopped.
Didn't make a big deal about it.
It just... quit.
Oh, my God.
You two are beingawfully kind to me.
Well...
Well, especially you, carol.
I mean, after some of the
thingsjoleen said about you.
What?
Huh?
Well, you know.
No, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I don't know whyshe
didn't care for you.
She probably saw youwearing
a dress sometime
that she thoughtwould look better on her.
She didn't like me? I
mean, everybody likes me.
I got a big mouth.
Excuse me.
Uh, another round, please. Thank you.
I'm sorry that hurtyour feelings.
Well, a personlikes to be liked.
It's funny, isn't it? I mean,
we assumeeverybody likes us,
but maybe they don't.
Well, I like you.
Please don't say thatto
me again, all right?
Mmm.
You remind meof Kenneth Meade.
I don't know who that is.
You don't know him.Why should you?
He's a young man I dateda few
years backin San Francisco.
Don't tell me I remind
youof some guy you dated.
Why not? You do.
Yeah, but don'ttell me I do.
What, you wanna be uniquein all the world?
Yes. What an insensitivething to do.
Oh. I didn't realize.
No? What if I told you
you had lipslike Gretchen Miller?
What if you did?
How do I remind youof Kenneth?
Forget it.
How?
You said you didn'twanna know.
Well, is it the wayi look?
No.
Well, what then?
I wonder what ever
happenedto Kenneth Meade.
Was he a magnificent loveror something?
I don't remember.
All right.I'm gonna tell you.
Sometimes,
your eyes get really bigall of a sudden,
and you swallow hard.
Like a little boy.
Like Kenneth.
It's sort of likean involuntary expression
of innocence.
I like it.
You have great ears.
I do?
They're beauties.
Hmm.
The greatest earsof all time?
Huh?
Why'd youask it like that?
Why'd you usethose words?
Like what? "The greatest earsof all time"?
Oh. You thinki don't know how men talk?
I think I do.
Oh, my God, the things men say.
They just kill me.
They absolutely kill me.
I'm right, aren't I?
I can't tell you the detailsabout
her yet, Eddie.Why not?
Well, what if she's the one?
What does that mean? The one.
What if she turns outto be the one for me?
Oh, and then you told meall her secrets?
That's right.And I wouldn't like that.
I understand. But tell me anyway.
What if it turned outi married her?
Aw, don't even mentionthat word to me.
Well, then you'd knowall
these secretsabout my wife.
You met this girl24 hours ago.
What the hell'sthe matter with you?
I've been looking for herall my life.
What has shedone to you?
I think she'sthe end of the prey.
Stop. Stop. I'm... I'm ill.
All right.Just tell me...
just tell methe area between...
between the naveland the pubes.
Her tummy? Yeah. Below the tummy.
Below the naval? But above the pubes.
It's real white.
Ooh.She got great skin.
She must take afterher mother, I guess.
Her mother's got great skin.
You leave the lights on?
For awhile.
So she's white, totally milky?
No tan there at all?
Not below the navel, above the pubes.
Come on. Tell me more.
No.
Okay. Come on, chick!
And to thinki called you friend once.
How long have you knowncarol fritzsimmons?
Oh, about 12 years, I guess.
And in all that time, why didn't you
everintroduce me to her daughter?
Why should I unleash
youon Carol's daughter?
Well, we met yesterdayat the
markettotally by accident.
Now, don't fool aroundwith
her daughter, all right?
Why not? Because you go
through womenlike water,
and I don't want youto
hurt her or her mother.
Now, wait a minute. I'm not kidding.
Hi, tom.
Why haven't you everintroduced
your daughter to me?
I don't know. They met
yesterdayby accident.
Oh. Yeah, we went out.
I really like Katherine. Uh...
you went out already? Yeah,
we had a couple dates.
What do you mean? You just met her
yesterday, and you already had two dates?
Yeah. I took herto the
moviesyesterday afternoon.
Then we got togetheragain last night.
You took her to the
moviesyesterday afternoon?
Yeah.
Oh, come on. What?
Okay, wait a minute. What did you see?
Well, we saw that thingover
at the Baker.Oh, my God.
Yesterday afternoon? Yeah.
Were you sittingdown there
in front, on the left there?
Now, don't lie to me. There was
only four peoplein the theater.
We... we thoughtwe... we were alone.
Well, that wasgrossly apparent.
Uh-huh.
Why can't your sistermove down here?
Because she can't, reece.Why not?
Because she's dying, and I don't want
to put herthrough that kind of ordeal.
How longhas she got, Carol?
How long does anybody have? I don't know.
All I know is I'm healthyand she's not,
and she should bewhere she wants to be.
Besides, I ordered herto come down here,
and she said no.
Well, I just thoughtmaybe
you hadn't thought of it.
Did you drive all the wayover
here at 10:30 at night
to ask me that?
Well, what if wehired a nurse, okay?
And she could stay herewith her all day
and all nightand holidays.
I know it'd be expensive,
but I'll pay for it.
You'd do that for her?
Well, I'd do thatfor you and... and me.
So... I don't know.
Look, I don't know how manymore
ideas I can come up with.
Yeah.
Were you sleeping? Mm, watching t.V.
What's wrong? Nothing.
Well, good night.
The late show is on at 11:00.
You gonna watch it?
**
Now, see, this is a movie,
but we're watching t. V.Not... reece...
yeah, like that machinei showed you.
Movies should be seenin the movie theaters,
where the screen is big, there's no
ads, you have aisles and ushers,
and that's my opinion.
Can't you see that? I finally thought...
Reece? You're right.
Reece? Huh?
How badly do you notwant me to move?
Well, you could leavetonight if you want.
Do you know somethingi'd always regret?
What? That...
that we neverwent away together.
Do you know?
You mean on vacation, or what?
Oh, a weekend.A long weekend away.
We never did that. No, thanks.
Well, how come you
nevermentioned this before?
Why didn't you? I'm not a traveler.
Well, I didn't knowhow to mention it.
How difficultcould it have been?
Very.
Don't sing that, please.
You know what I would liketo see one
of these daysis a good old Western.
Oh, yeah. They're not makingthose anymore.
I'd love to see a Western.They're not.
I know. You know, like, uh,
the outlaw Josey wales a couple years ago.
You see yourselfas a bit of an outlaw.
What? Yeah, you see yourselfas
a bit of an outlaw.
I have no ideawhat you mean by that.
Oh, the renegade.
Yeah, and the personwho doesn't do
thingslike the way they're done.
I'm a solid citizen.What do you mean?
Okay. Most menget up in the morning,
they go to work at a job,
and 5:00... yeah?
...they go home.
You've never done that, reece.
I've got the store.That store is a toy.
Oh, I know. Butch Cassidy
and the Sundance kid.
You know the one.Where
they jump off the cliff.
And they say, "oh, shit."
Shit!
Shit. It's too embarrassing.
It's kind of embarrassing, but we're alone.
So what do you think?
I don't know.
I bet they're togethersomewhere,
those two. Hmm.
Maybe.
It's not movie day.
They'll be backin awhile, I guess.
I wouldn't worry.
This place is amazing.
You see anything you like? Everything.
You neverbeen in here before?
No. I've only driven by.
Well, you should'vecome by years ago.
I might've been here.
I never knewit was such a candy box.
My mother never told
memuch about this place.
Wow.
Our parents must be in
love, don't you think?
Mm. I'm not sure.
Besides, my dadwould never use that word.
Well, did he use itwith your mother?
I don't know. I doubt it.
I can't believeshe might go to Toronto.
She might neversee him again.
And if she were to go, you
know what the reason is?
Her sister.
Yeah. But not only that.
She's testing him.
She's testingtheir relationship.
That'd bea dangerous thing to do.
I wanna watch youundress and dress.
Pervert.
You can make mea pervert.
That's a lovely thingto say.
Hello, Louis.
Where's your daddy?
Uh, he's not here today.
Or he's gone. We're not sure.
Louis, I heardabout your wife.
I'm awfully sorry.
I picked me outa suit yesterday.
I need it for tomorrow.
Here it is.
Ta-da!
Uh, Louis, this iskatherine fritzsimmons.
What you got on?
Uh, it's a dress.
Why you wearing it?
Well, usually, it's easier to meet
someonewhen you have clothes on.
Get that dress off! Aahh!
What the hell'sthe matter with you?
Are you okay? Yeah.
He didn't hurt you, did he? No.
The dress... Joleen...
Was that joleen's dress, louis?
All those years,
I was living with somebodyi didn't know.
Hey, Phil. Hello, tom.
Hey, did you seemy dad today? Uh, yeah.
Came in this morning to fill up.
Him and the fritzsimmons woman.
Did they saywhere the were going?
Cabin somewhere.Oh, that
cabinup in hill country?
Yeah. They were goingto
hill country.All right.
All right.Be cool, Phil.
Okay. I'll see y'all.
Take me to my truck.
Well, I knowwhere they are,
Louis.I can drive us up there.
Just take meto my truck.
Reece? Yeah?
Oh, wait. Look. You see the ducks?
Ducks?
Wait. Let me get this.
Okay.
Hey, what are you doing? Quit. What?
What?
I've never hadmy picture taken.
What are youtalking about?
I've never hadany pictures taken of me.
Since when? Ever.
I don't understand. What
kind of a lieis that anyway?
No, no. I'm not kidding
you.I've never had a picture.
What aboutyour family album?
There is no family album.
Okay, well, then, you
were in the army. Yeah.
Three years in the pacific.
So, they took your picturein
the army, didn't they?
No. They missed me.
Reece, you're pullingmy leg, huh? Uh-uh.
Well, then, what didyou look like,
reece, when you were a little boy?
I don't know. I've got no idea.
I don't care. I'm doing it. No. Come on.
No. Quit it now.Cut it out.No, wait.
Please, let me justtake one. No.
Reece... no, please. No.
I'm gonna get a pictureof you. I am. No.
I am. What if we separateor
something happens to us?
I'm gonna have a picturewhere
I can look back on.
You don't need it. Yes, I do. I need it.
Hey, Alpha! Zeus!
Come on, Zeus!
She here? Yeah, she's inside there.
Amanda McKay?
No.
Louise Duffy?
Well, who do you knowaround here?
Well, I don't remembernames much.
Yeah.
Now, Katherine...
Tom herethinks he likes you.
And that's all welland good.
But it's my jobto make sure
that if he likes you, he
knows what he's doing.
I understand. Do you?
I think I do.
You think you do?
See,
tom and I know women.
You know what I mean? It's what we do.
I can see this situation
so much more clearlythan he can.
Look, if you and ihad a thing,
he would be the oneasking the questions.
Well, of course. See,
what I'm looking for
is an ulterior motive.
I don't have any motives,
ulterior or otherwise.
Well, what the hellyou doing here?
I'm just alongfor the ride.
Is it your planto cut tom
off from other women,
and by doing so, sabotage our friendship?
No.
This manwas once a marine.
He fought gooksin the jungle.
You care to comment on that?
No, I'd rather not.
Miss, uh...
fritzsimmons.
Fritzsimmons.
Is there a specificpart of your body
that is perhapsthe greatest of its kind?
My ears.
May I see them?
All right.
I haveno further questions.
How do you work this? No. Here. Lookit...
no.
Here. Let me get youcoming off the canyon.
Come on. No, I don't wanna.
Such a cute hat.
Every age I hit
seems youngerthan it did before.
I'm 54.So I remember
when I was 20, 30,god, even 40,
I thought 54was really ancient.
54's not that old.No, no.
It doesn'tseem like it's
old, but it actually is.
I mean, I knowwhat you're talking about.
But it's old, and you know it.
I rememberwhen I was 35,
I really pitiedthose poor
old peoplewho were 40.
But when I was 45,I would've
killedto have been 40.
40?Mm-hmm.You're 56, right?
So wouldn't it be greatto be 45?
Well... it would.
Are you bushed?
No. I'm fine. No?
You didn't sleep muchlast night.
Neither did you.
What does that mean?
Look at this. Oh, my God!
Oh!
Please don't.Oh, reece, don't. Don't.
Get away from there.I'm all right.
It's kindof thrilling, actually.
Whoa.
Aahh! Oh. Oh. Better hold me. Come here.
Don't do that. Don't do that.
You know what?
You're the only thrilli need. Mm.
You are.
You two! What?
Louis!
You two can be hard to
findwhen you wanna be.
Louis, what's the problem?
I tracked you down.
Huh?
Lou, what the hellare you doing up here?
Ohh!
Louis, get away from there!
Come on, Louis. Don't.
I'm not gonna jump. No, but you could fall.
Louis!
Lou, come on.
Aahh!
You know, I heardby the year 2040,
there's not gonna bea single
tree lefton this planet.
Lou... I wonder what peopleare
gonna do without trees.
Lou, what did youcome up here for?
Yeah, Louis.
Get away from there.Come on.
Come on.
Why'd you do it, reece?
Do what?
I was looking throughsome
of joleen's things.
I found this.
What is it?
It's a letter she wrote, never mailed.
Look, Lou, come on awayfrom
the edge there, would you?
I'll read youthe letter.
Lou...
"Dearest reece,
"as long as I live,
I will never forgetwhat
you have done for me."
Lou, would you please... "I was yours.
"I came to you.I wanted you. I was yours.
"But you said no,
"you would not have me.
"Not even for one night.
"In your kind rejection, yet understanding,
"you have taught me honor.
"Thank you, reece.
Love, joleen."
Like I said, why'd you do it, reece?
There were many timesyears back
when I thoughtshe was fooling around on me,
but I never knew for surewho with.
This letter clears you, of course.
Doesn't it?
I owe you.
Lou...
I'm selling my house, reece.
I'm going to my sister's.
**
I'm dancing with her.No,
I'm dancing with her.
Hey, isn't thisa little unethical,
Eddie... you and Lola being here?
What wouldn't be ethicalabout it?
Hi. How are you?
Well, the obvious. I mean, you represent
her in divorce, and now here you are.
Yeah, but divorceis final and everything.
Tom, because I choosea certain profession,
certain people are
suddenlyoff-limits to me in life?
I hope that is not howour
judicial system works.
Listen, I wouldn't, like,
have gone out with him
while the casewas still in progress.
Of course not.I can see how
certainsmall-minded individuals
could misconstrue.
Except that one timeand everything.
What time was that, Lola?
Should I tell them?
Admit nothing.
We had a sexual encounterin his office
first day I, like, came in
to see himand everything.
How'd that happen, Eddie?
Uh... remind me.
On your desk!
Like you don't remember.
Mwah!
Now I remember.
* I'm sitting on a bar stool
acting like a darn fool *
* that's what I'm a-doing today *
* and I'm a-sitting here drinking,
trying to keep from thinking *
* I'm a-boozing my troubles away *
* so pour me another one, I'm
finished with the other one *
* I'm drinking my baby good-bye *
* I said pour me another one, I'm
finished with the other one *
* I'm drinking my baby good-bye *
* I said pour me another one, I'm
finished with the other one *
* I'm drinking my baby good-bye *
**
Whew!
Thanks.
I got a call today... From a director.
He's directing a play, and he wants me
to cometo Tennessee and be in a show.
Oh, yeah? When?
Tomorrow.
He wantsyou to come tomorrow?
Yeah, somebody got firedand
he needs a replacement.
Well, I hope you told him
you had other thingsin your life.
Like what?
Me.
I'm going, tom.
Aw, come on.
Yeah, I leave first thing.
Well, I thoughtwe had something
developing here, katherine.
Look, it's a good partin a play.
You knowi enjoy doing that.
I'm going.
It's a dinner theaterin Tennessee.
Sounds likea real career move.
It's only for three months. Two months.
Well, that couldbe worse.
And then it toursfor six.
Oh, you can't go.
I mean, you absolutely can't go.
Look, don't tell Mei can't do a thing...
all right?
I can't stand it. I'm
like a child that way.
Well then I'll gowith you.
Tom, you're such a sweet guy.
And you know I'm attractedto
you, obviously.
But, I don't wantyou
trailing along behind me.
Well, I won't be trailingalong behind you.
I'll beright there with you.
Let me be with you.
No.
Why not?
Because.
I like beingon my own.
How can I explain that?
Why should I have to?
I've got you.
You're hereand I've got you.
What the hellwould I do without you...
for eight months?
Come on.
You've lived this long.
You'll be fine.
Don't be so flipwhen I'm trying to tell
you how I feelabout you, damn it.
Lola wentto powder her labia.
Where's yours?
Tennessee.
All right.
I know you're dying.
Lola... her neck.
World-class neck.
I just wishi could get
her whole neckin my mouth.
It took you a while, but you finally came.
Well, now that I'vegotten
up here to visit you,
when are you gonnacome
back home and see me?
I don't know.
Did you see, uh...
which one, now?
Well, listen, here's what...
I'm not gonna go see smokey and the bandit.
No.
Can I justsit over there?
Oh...
you all right?
Yes...
Thank you... oh, good.
It's buttered.
Huh?
Oh, what?
It tasteslike styrofoam.
Well, it has a littlestyrofoam taste.
Canadian popcorn.
Do you wantto take off your coat?
Nope.
You're justa big baby, aren't you?
The heater's brokeor something... you know?
You're still punishing
mefor leaving, aren't you?
What?
You hardly ever call me.
Now you come up here,
you act likeyou're freezing
to death.Go ahead, reece...
You made mepay for... hey,
you wannaget into this?
You wannaget into this?
You couldn't possiblythink
I could have moved
up here with you, huh?
You knew you werebreaking us up.
No, I didn't.
Oh, you didn't? I thought...
what did you think?
I... well, I thought...
That some miraclemight happen?
Dare I say this? Dare I say this?
Yeah. Dare.
I thought you mightrealize
that you love me.
All right. Okay.
Uh, just forget it. We'll watch the movie.
Let's watch the movie, reece.
Okay?
Reece?
Do you rememberthat hill country weekend
before I moved?
Hill country?
Nope. Doesn't ring a bell.
Yeah.
I'm going go to my lawyer'sand have lunch.
Okay. I'll be back later.
Sure.
Sally?
Is he here?
Counselor?
Oh...
I thought you were goingto close the deal
on that store at the mall.
I've got 4,0oovideo cassettes
sitting aroundwaiting to get
into that space.
What did she say to you?
Who?
Sally.
Outside.
She didn't sayanything.
We're havinga silent row.
A row, huh?
You know, under the surface.
We're... we're at pizza hut...
and, uh, she comes in... she comes in
with this asshole.
Wait a minute.
Who's at pizza hut?
Uh, me, Bonnie, and, uh... me,
Bonnie, and the kids.
So, you're at the pizza hut
with your family...
We're atthe pizza hut
and she comes inwith this asshole,
and they sit at the table
right next to our booth
and they're allkissy-face
and holding handsacross the table.
She's doing thisjust to aggravate me.
You've got a wifeand four kids.
You're poppingyour
secretary, who is single.
And you see her outon a
date and you get jealous.
Don't try to make me outlike
some sort of freak.
Any man would feelthe same way.
What about this leasein the mall?
What about it?
Hey, Greg.
Hey, tom.
You should let meget somebody in here
to cleanthis place up.
Well, Ruth wasmy housekeeper.
Yeah, well... Ruth's long gone, dad.
Besides, she'dhave a fit at this mess.
Would you liketo go out
to the hill country, dad?
And spend the night?
What?
You used to liketo go out there,
and you haven't beenout there in years.
I don't careanything about it.
I'd like to see youget out of this store
every once in a while.
Why?
You've gottenso damn sedentary, dad.
There's nowhere to go.
Well, there's lotsof places to go
and I just toldyou one place...
I don't careanything about it.
You know, I'm not sure, but I
think I sawkatherine fritzsimmons
downtown on the street today.
You remember her?
Little bit.
At least I believeit was her.
Wonder what in the worldmight
bring her back to town.
Hello?
Yeah. Hold on a second. I'll go get him.
Yeah, I remember her.
You two came in hereevery Wednesday.
Yeah, after the matinees. Mm.
And she moved away.
Yeah, she did.She moved to Canada.
Mm-hmm. Mm.
Is she back now?
Apparently so.
Have you two kept upover the years?
No, no, we haven't.
So you haven'tseen her in...
Uh, ten years.
Well, my goodness, reece.
You two used to beinseparable, didn't you?
Yes, sir.We were good friends.
Oh, reece.
Well, hello.
Oh.
It's our table. Yeah.
Well... What?
Oh, reece.
What? oh.
Do you remember me? Mike.
Oh, Mike.
Yeah. See? She's still a regular.
She drops by every tenor 15
years just like clockwork.
What'll you have?
Oh, I'm gonna havea glass of white wine.
Make that two.
All right.
Thanks, Mike. Mike.
Well...
I've been reading abouthow
to write a mystery novel.
Why?
Oh, I don't know. I thought that I
might try and write one.
Agatha christie? Oh, well, she wrote 200.
I might write one.
You still sew? Sure.
So you're gonnawrite a mystery and sew?
Well, I like to keep busy, don't you?
No, no. I don't like to keep busy.
I like to hardly do anything. Thank you.
Well...
What do you do, reece?
Nothing.
Huh. You still goto the movies?
Mm. Hardly ever.
I watch them on tapes.
Huh.
My son ownsten video stores.
Tom? Yeah.
He brings me bagsfull of tapes.
Well, that's convenient.
So you watch them at home?
No, at the store.
I don't go home much. The store is home.
I spend mostof the time there.At the store.
Yeah. More comfortable.lt's smaller.
I like a smaller placeto live in, you know.
You still dogood business?
No, no. I'd be lyingif I said I did.
It's slacked off some.
Really?'Cause I would've thought
that the used clothingpart of your
businesswould've skyrocketed.
Why is that?
'Cause the times.
I mean, you know, used
clothesare really popular.
New clothes havethese holes in them.
Well, you can't leta business go,
and I kind of let mine
goover the millennium.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Reece.
When I first met you, you drove a Cadillac.
Yeah. Yeah.
You were really expansive. Yeah.
By the time I moved, you'd gotten smaller.
Well, I only likedbeing around the store
'cause that's whereyou were, you know.
Me? I somewhat scaled down.
So now you're smaller still.I'm tiny now.
I got ridof almost everything.
So, how long do you think
you're gonna livein that hotel?
Well, until I can findthe
right apartment to buy.
Well, maybe I can help
youlook for an apartment.
I'd like that. Yeah.
You still knowjust about everyone there is?
No. Hardly anybody.
Your, uh, sister
hung on a long time, didn't she?
Well, not as long as some.
You gave up a lot for her.
I didn't really feelas
though I had a choice.
You're a very good person.
Tell me something.How was Tennessee?
Tennessee? Yeah. The play.
I don't knowwhat you're talking about.
Well, the last time I saw
you, you were getting ready
to go to tennesseeand act in a play.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I remember.
Every timei thought of Tennessee,
I mean, over the years,
I would think of you.
I was Tennessee to you?
That's funny.
Nah, I was only therefive minutes.
Five minutes?
Well, yeah. I got up there, and, uh,
the theater went broke, something.
I don't know. Anyway, I
went outto California.
Lived with some girlfriends, got married.
So what do you mean, the
theater closed or something?
I mean I was in tennesseefor five minutes.
I went up thereto see you in that play.
To surprise you.
Well, then, you know.
You bastard.
I was never in that play.
I wasn't rightfor the role.
You persistent little swine!
God.
By mutual agreement, I left...
And I went to California.
So by mutual agreement, you
weren't right for the role.
That's right.
They fired you.
So how longwere you married?
First time?
Two years.
I married a cokehead.
And I divorced him.
And then I marriedhis dealer.
So you did you havea bout
with drugs yourself?
"A bout with drugs."
That's a pretty compactlittle
way to put it.
Yes, I had one.Yes, I did.
The '80s were a, uh, world
championshipbout with drugs.
How come you never married?
You.
You knew me a week.
What can I tell you?
That's the craziest thingi ever heard.
Don't tell mewhat I saw.
I'm telling you... I got eyes, Buster.
What you got is likea
mother-daughter envy thing.
I don't know. What? How dare you?
It's normal. Hey, you two.
You remember Lola?
I don't thinki can stay,
Eddie.You better take me home.
Uh, what's going on?
Too embarrassed to tell you. Uhh...
Eddie comes to pick me up.
While I'm getting ready, I'm come out.
He's, like, on the couchwith
my 15-year-old daughter.
I didn't know I wasn'tsupposed to sit down.
I saw what you were doing.
I met the girl20 seconds before.
Like, you know, I work that fast.
Oh, hi. Oh, it's you two.
Gosh, it's been awhile.
Didn't we go out one night? The four of us?
Yeah. It wasa long time ago, hon.
Right. How ya been?
There she wasin the phone book,
and her name just sort
ofjumped off the page at me.
I want y'all to knowi do not
go outwith married men.
Why didn't you tell meto bring a suit?
I'd love to go swimming. Well, go swimming.
You don't need a suit. Yeah, right.
I'll make usall some drinks.
Well, I'll help you.
Oh...
She comes into my officefor
her first divorce.
You know, way back. I boff her on my desk.
And now she needs a suitto go swimming.
She still lookspretty good, though, huh?
Yeah, looks good. Yours looks good.
You don't mind uspopping
in like this, do you?
Yeah. But what am igonna do about it?
Well, we won't stay.
Good.
You know, I used to own this place.
You did? Yeah. Built it.
It was all rental unitsback then.
Been remodeled a bunch.
I don't know whyi'm so surprised.
I mean, I hardlyeven knew you, reece.
You showed me just enoughto
keep me interested,
and then you... you just kept me out.
You told me nothing.
Well, it's a pretty good view.
It'd be a nice place for you.
Good price. Mm-hmm.
Awfully high up.
Yeah.
In Canada, you were on the ground floor.
I'm surprisedyou remember.
Well, at leasti came to visit.
Once.
One time.
How come you nevercame
back down to visit me?
Well, I wasn't a
schoolgirlhopping on airplanes
every weekendto go see my boyfriend, reece.
I had a responsibility. "Boyfriend"?
What about your responsibilitytoward us?
What "us"? There was no "us."
I realized that pretty
soonafter I moved away.
"There was no us." You're lying.
Now you're really lying.You moved.
That's what happened.
We had a life, and you left it.
What kind of a lifedid we have?
A pretty darn good one.lt was casual, easy.
Casual? Oh, brother, was it casual, yes.
I don't remember youhating
it so much way back then.
I did.
Oh, you did? You hated the...
yes, I hated it! I hate
somethingthat starts out good,
and just stays there, reece,
and it doesn't move
forwardinto something better.
Casual and good... reece, that
just wasn'tgood enough for me.
Well...
I didn't take youout dancing every night.
Not every night, no.
Why didn't you expressyour grievances...
why didn't youexpress your grievances?
Because that's notsomething I do.
I'm not very expressive.
Well, I was the one who saidwe
should go away for a weekend,
because we've nevereven gone
awayfor one weekend, reece.
And when you did, what did I do?
I took you.
Yes, but where wereyour ideas?
My God, you were young, you were vital.
You could've hada thought.
"Young and vital"... yes.
You were young.You were vital.I
don't know when it ended.
Well, it's ended.
Yeah, I can see that.
I'm just sayingi don't know when it ended,
because I wasn't thereto see it end, reece.
I wasn't thereto see you end.
It started to endwhen you left.
I shouldn'thave to tell you that.
Go ahead and tell me.
Just rub it in my face.
Go ahead.
Well, look, it's nobody's fault, I guess.
You couldn't have itboth ways forever.
You couldn't have mesort
of on the side forever,
and I should've said thatpoint-blank.
I should've come right out, and
I should've spoken my mind.
Yeah, you should have.
You're speaking it now.
Yeah.
I mean, everything is easier to do
when you do it too late.
Basically, what happened was you...
Left the country.
Not believing thatyou wouldn't let me go.
You said you had to go.
There was no other way.
What was I supposed to do, chase after you?
I expected youto leave her, okay?
Oh.
Her life was over, over, over,
the day she satat that red light.
Years beforei even met you,
reece, her life was over.
Damn it! Damn you, reece!
I expected youto face that.
I expected you to face me.
And... I don't know. One
place, another place,
both places, we'd be
togethersomehow, some way.
Reece...
Oh...
Look, we can arguetill
we're blue in the face,
and it's not gonnabring back those
years, so I should just... shut up.
When I firstwent up there
to live with dottie,
do you know I used tolie
in bed at night thinking,
how did this happen?
Yeah, I had nightslike that too.
You knew howi felt about you.
I know. There was me,
but there wasjoleen quillet too.
Yeah, I knewabout her, reece.
I could tell when louiswas
reading his letter,
because I was readingyour face.
The letter didn't fool me.
She must've loved you... Very much.
Look, I was with hera couple of times.
She was very lonely. She
threw herself at me.
Oh, didn't we all?
Then I met you, and that
was the end of that.
You mean you weren'tfooling around
with both of usat one time?
No, I was not.Well, I didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
Back then on that hill,
when we took that little trip, you know?
When you, uh...
Made it up in your mindthat
you were gonna move...
You weren't thinking
that... that I was carrying on
with joleen as well as youat the same time?
All those years?
Partially that, yes.Oh, God, Carol, no.
God almighty.
I'm gonnaask you a question.
Reece... reece... reece...
reece...
Who was the loveof your life?
Who was she? Please, who?
You know what I want youto
say to me, so say it.
Who was the love of your life? Tell me.
Who?
M... my wife.
Mmm? Yeah.
Thank you.That helps.
We're almostour parents' age.
What the helldoes that mean?
Well, when they met, they were our age.
I mean, we'rea little bit younger, but...
Yeah. Wow.
Well, there's somethingyou don't know.
What? About them?
About us.
We met a long time ago.
Well, yeah. I know.
Right beforemy Tennessee debut.
Uh-uh. Before that.
What are youtalking about?
We were in our teens.
I was 15.
I don't remember that.
I know you don't.
Well? Tell me. What?
You lied to me.
Well, I can't deny thatuntil
I've heard the facts.
Well, we met one summerout at the lake,
and you told me your
namewas Sharon childress,
and that you werefrom
Washington, d.C.Oh, my God.
And that your dadwas a foreign agent.
Oh, my God!
And it was very,
veryhush-hush and secretive.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Oh, I was sucha screwed-up little girl.
Wait a minute.
We went out in the woodsthat afternoon,
and we made outlike a couple of banshees.
Then it turns out our
folkswere together for lunch.
Wow. That was you? Seriously?
Well, why didn't youtell me
this before, when we met again?
Well, I was going to. I was
gonna tell youone night in bed,
but I decided... ah, I decided to wait,
or maybe you'd remember or...
I don't know. I just waswaiting
for the right momentor something.
But then, you got gone so fast.
I was wild.
What's changed?
Well, I still docrazy things.
I always have.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm trying to picture youliving
in my houseas my husband,
being a fatherto my kids. Uh...
Like telling themabout how we first met.
Wouldn't give themtoo many details though.
Would you bea good husband to me?
A good daddy to my kids?
We'll never know.
Wh...
hey, let's go swimming.
Well, if you'd just told
meto bring my suit...
Well, it doesn't matter. Come on.
Come on.
Who wants to go swimming?
Fine.
Ohh.
Oh, it's warm.
Come on out, Katherine.
You're gonna swim naked, aren't you, Eddie?
I'm a man.I don't swim naked.
The women swim naked.
You're sexist.
You figured me out.
You better changeyour ways, Buster.
Lola, the seasons may change,
the world may change,
but I will never change, my darling.
Hallelujah.
He's gonna change.
You're not gonnastay around here, are you?
No. I can't.
You know me.
But I'll be back though.
Come on in the water,
tom.You know you want to.
Come on! Do it!
Whoa!
You made it!
They're not coming.
They're coming. They'll be here.
How'd they knowwhich exact placeand so on?
Well, I wasvery specific.
Where'd you get the beer? I brought them.
Give me a beer.
You quit drinkinga long time ago.
Yeah. I quit drinking, I quit smoking,
quit working.
I quit just about everything.
Now just give me a damn beer.
And a cigarette.You got a cigarette?
I quit smoking.You did?
A very long time ago.
Twist-off.
I can't rememberanything anymore.
Well, hell, dad, I'm in my 40s,
and I don't rememberanything either.
And you say that kidding.
See, but I'm not kidding.
When was the last timei saw Carol?
About six years ago.
She was...
she was gonna move into a
condowe were looking at.
What ever happenedwith that?
What do you mean, "we were looking at"?
I was helping herfind a condo.
Oh, you weren't goingto move in with her?
What do you mean, "move in with her"? No.
Why not?
What's the matterwith you?
There's nothingthe matter with me.
Well, her daughter, katherine,
moved down to the Gulf,
and Carol went with her.
Yeah. Seems like I canremember
something like that.
Well, she sent you postcardsfor awhile.
Who did? Carol.
I don't rememberif she did or not.
Well, she did, dad, and you know it.
Yeah. She was a funny woman.
What was funny about her?
Well, you never knewwhat
Carol was thinking.
That works both ways.
What... what's it been,
five, six years?
Seven?
Oh!
Well, she thoughtshe could make it up here,
but after the ride overfrom the
beach, she's not up to it.
She wanted me to ask you twoif
you'd meet up at the hotel,
follow me up there.
Something wrongwith her?
Well, sir, to tell you the truth,
mom's gotwhat her sister had.
Uh, she's had it for years
and never let on.
Of the two, my motherwas
never one to complain.
Dad?
How bad is she?
She's dying?
Yeah.
You give my dad one of
thosewhen he comes back?
Yeah. Sure.
So, you wake up every
morninghearing the ocean?
Yeah. Walk on the beach,
bundle up in winter.
Mom used to go with me,
but she can't anymore.
Yeah, I like the beach.
I'm kind of like my dad. I...
Could never liveanywhere but here, I guess.
Yeah, sure. I know.
But I don't think of youas
much like your father.
Maybe you are.
You kind of growinto being like your dad.
So, who's your latest lady?
Nobody, really.
You should be married, have
a big old family by now.
Yeah. There's this, uh...
there's this oldrobert mitchum movie.
It was on t.V.And he's some detective
or something, and, uh,
the woman he's withis talking
about her familyand her husband.
She drones on, and finally
she stops talking.
He sort of looks at herand says,
"I never married."
I don't know. But, wow, did
that linepack a wallop to me.
I mean, maybe nobody
elsein the world got it.
Who's your latest?
You.
Me, huh?
Yeah, I'm herewith you right
now, so I'm your latest.
Same old Katherine.
No. No.
I mean, you grow up some,
whether you want to or not.
I always went for you.
I just couldn't stoplong enough...
To love me?
Well, yeah.
I just couldn't stoplong enough.
You have always loved me, haven't you?
Since I was 15.
God!
What a sucker.
I didn't mind.
There you are.
How is everything. Oh, fine, thanks.
Oh...
Oh! Oh!
Oh, God!
You're the loveof my life.
You are.
Oh...
You left early.
Where's Katherine?
Ah, she's headedback over to the beach.
What do you mean?
That's where she lives.
I thought you twohad finally hooked it up.
Well, I didn't wannapush her.
You didn't wanna push her?
Huh?
You push her, boy! Goddamn it!
You push her! Now go on, get in that car!
Get in the car!
What the hell'sgotten into you?
Let's take my car.Get in the goddamn car!
Well, let me drive.
Jesus, dad, I'm not even in the car yet!
Goddamn!
What the hell'sthe matter with you?
What the hellare you doing?
What do you think I'm doing? Let me drive.
I'm driving! Let me drive the car.
I'm drivingthe goddamn car!
Jesus, dad, did you see that stop sign?
How much head startshe got?
It doesn't matter. You're gonna
kill usbefore we catch her.
I cannot believethat you let her go again.
What the hell's wrongwith you?
Well, I told you.
It's all gonna work out.Just
a little more time.
How would you know anything? Things
don't work outby themselves.
You gotta make them work
out.Watch the road!
Time is laughingat you, boy.
You want things to turn around,
you gotta turn them around!
Turn around.
If I gotta lead you by the
nose, I'm gonna lead you.
I said turn around.
Tom, don't bea goddamn fool.
I'm not gonnalet you be a fool
the second halfof your life.
She's backat the service
stationfilling up with gas.
We just passed her.
Aw, come... come on, dad.
Have you lost your mind?
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Stop it, dad.I'm not a little boy.
Son, that is the point!
That's exactly the point!
What?
I love you.
Don't go away. Stay here with me.
This is a toyfrom Kodak, dad.
I think you'd be surprised.
What does it do?
Watch. It puts your pictureson the t.V.
I don't get it. You see your
photographson the screen.
That's a slide projector.
No, no. This is different.This
is a photo c.D. Player.
Just watch.
Who the hell is that?
Huh? Who's that?
That's Eddie.You remember Eddie.
Who's Eddie?
He got caughtin a motel room
with judge Harlan's wife.
Sells cars now.
No, dad, I'm not gonna show
youjust pictures of our wedding.
Mother treasuredthese photographs, reece.
She just loved themmore
than you'll ever know.
Well... That's enough for now.
Come on, chick.
**
* love never tasted
* is love that's wasted
* leaving regret to haunt your way *
* you learn if you're lucky
* that love is a thing
* you don't save for a rainy day *
* you learn if you're lucky
* that love is a thing
* you don't save for a rainy day *
* you don't save love
* for a rainy
* day
**
* time is a stealer
* a stacked deck dealer
* deals you time
* then takes time away
* you learn if you're lucky
* you never waste a day
* time is a racer
* a comet chaser
* stops for no one in its quest *
* and thinks nothing of it
* to pass you by
* leave you stranded with all the rest *
* what about that bride tomorrow? *
* all those best laid plans
* what about the time you counted upon *
* time that was endless but now is gone *
* love never tasted
* is love that's wasted
* leaving regret to haunt your way *
* you learn if you're lucky
* that love is a thing
* you don't save for a rainy day *
* you learn if you're lucky
* that love is a thing
* you don't save for a rainy day *
* you don't save love
* for a rainy
* day
**