(GRUNTS)
(DISTANT SIRENS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Where you been?
Sorry, Jerry.
Is Sal still here?
You were supposed to
be here an hour ago.
Now he's at the produce.
When Sal tells
you to be somewhere,
you fucking be there.
Think you could
give me a ride?
Fucking A, Nicky.
Go!
- Go! Go!
- All right.
(LIGHTER CLICKING)
(ENGINE IDLING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(SIGHS)
Man,
I need my own fucking wheels.
Yeah, you do.
You should have kept
that Chrysler, man.
That was a good car.
Hmm.
My brother needed
some money for school,
you know?
Will you please
leave it on one station?
Fuck you.
(MUSIC PLAYING
SOFTLY OVER RADIO)
$86.
Fuck, I told Vito I'd stop by
with some dough.
Man,
we need a good fucking rip.
You got anything?
Things been kind
of cold lately.
I got a vic up north.
It's a home invasion.
Like a drug deal or something?
Nah. Straight guy. He owns
two sports bars up
in New Hampshire.
Wife, two kids.
250K in his mattress.
I got a tip from
his financial advisor.
Financial advisor?
Yeah, I sell
the guy coke and steroids
from time to time.
That sounds like
a guy you can trust
with your money.
- No. What else?
- (CHUCKLES)
I got a...
I got a number for a bookie,
big fish kind of guy.
Figured I'd throw
in some high numbers,
see what happens and...
With your fucking Irish luck,
no fucking way.
-That has nothing
to do with luck.
-Next.
- What are you talking about?
- Next!
Jesus, Nicky,
let me see what else I got
on the fucking lot for you.
(CHUCKLING)
Uh, Big Victor. I've been
waiting for that to get
ripe for a while.
Probably get him for
25 grand this week.
Big Victor.
I don't know, man.
We'd have to
give him a beating.
So what?
What we need is
our own fucking crew.
- Our own crew...
- Come on, man.
...and we won't be up
against the ropes
all the fucking time.
You know what? You watched
the first half of
Goodfellas too many times.
- (CHUCKLING)
- Those days are dead, man.
Nowadays,
a crew makes you hot.
Your friends in the North End?
Just a bunch of old guys now
that fucking play gangster
so they can fucking sell ziti
and fucking cannolis
to tourists.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Sal fucking
runs the North End.
Sal ran the North End
20 years ago.
Have you looked
around recently?
It's like a guinea
minstrel show over there.
It's like a dago Disney World.
Trust me.
Those guys are geriatric rats
on a fucking sinking ship.
You don't know what the fuck
you're talking about,
- all right?
- (CHUCKLES)
Will you please hurry up?
Sal's gonna kick
my fucking ass.
Fuck Sal.
DOCK WORKER 1:
We load and lock.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
This one's filled up.
Yeah, why don't you grab it?
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
DOCK WORKER 2:
You send me that number?
DOCK WORKER 1:
Yeah, we're good.
(MACHINES CLANKING)
Hey, Angelo.
Hey, Nick, how's it going?
GINSBERG: Okay. Well, can you
let me know by next week
which way you want
to go with this thing?
Otherwise I just
got to proceed.
Wait here for me. All right?
Come here.
- Sal, I...
- Get over there.
I'm so sorry
that I'm late, Sal.
Why?
I could smell
the pussy coming off you
halfway down the hallway.
I got a call last night
from Tony Matazano.
(SIGHS)
What happened?
I get a call
yesterday afternoon
from my cousin Eric.
Something about
Tony's daughter
chewing him out
at the hair salon
that he works at.
She was bitching about him
smoking too close to the door
or something stupid like that.
Anyway, he called her a name.
She got pissed.
Tony sends his
fucking goons down there
to rough up my cousin.
He's a kid, Sal.
He was shitting in his pants.
So I call Tony,
try to calm things down.
Did you tell him
you were going
to track him down
and put a bullet in his eye?
He started in on me
with all this tough guy shit.
Like, "I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna kill your family."
I mean...
Eric is a kid.
And he's family.
Tony is a prick.
All I was trying
to do was apologize.
That's it.
Well, now you have to
go down there and apologize.
In person.
And to his daughter.
Tony's protected. Nick.
He makes us a lot of money.
You know that he's
holding out on you.
He's running all
this shit on the side
you don't even know about.
I bet he never even...
SAL: Hey, Mickey Mouse.
Wait outside.
You really want to associate
with people like that?
He came out of
his mother's ass.
I never would have survived
them three years up in
Shirley without George.
Get your ass
over to his place.
And watch your
fucking mouth with me.
If you want in,
you better listen more
than you don't listen.
And don't take everything
so fucking personally.
You got a lot of heart, Nick.
Don't let it go to your head.
Whatever I got
to do, I'm ready.
You know, Ginsberg,
the lawyer that just left...
- You know...
- Sure. Good guy.
Listen, Nick.
With the old timers dying,
one by one,
and the Feds and the rats
and the chinks and the fucking
Albanians up my ass,
I got no choice
but to go legit
or be the last man standing.
We're like an island.  Capisce?
There's not many of us left.
Whatever you want
me to do, I'm ready.
I never was one of those guys
who just let anybody in
who'd come through the door.
But I paid the price. I know.
I see something in you.
The day you see it yourself
is the day things will go
right with this family.
You're a good boy, Nick.
Your time's coming.
And bring
the girl some flowers.
NICK: Vito.
What's up, Nicky?
How are you, brother?
What's up, Georgie?
GEORGE:
Vito, when are you gonna do
something about that haircut?
The pompadour died with Elvis.
Fuck you.
What's up, Eric, you dumb ass?
You know I got to go deal
with your shit right now?
What shit?
You're the one with
the big fucking mouth.
Bitch wanted to fuck
and I just wouldn't play.
This kid couldn't get pussy
from a dead whore. Shut up.
ERIC: Suck a dick, Vito.
What trouble? What do you got?
Don't worry about it.
Here you go. Take this.
No. Nick, you're not
even supposed be here.
Where is he?
He's in the house.
I can't take that.
What, you don't got to eat?
You don't want
to go to college?
He gets a fucking job,
he can bitch about
getting free money.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
No, he don't want you here.
You cause problems for me
every time you come.
- I got to deal with him.
- Hey, hey, hey.
This is my house, too.
Ma would want me here.
It's 80 fucking dollars.
Take.
Relax, will you?
It's gonna be beautiful.
All right,
don't let that big fat cock
-scare the neighbors,
all right?
-(CHUCKLES)
- King Kong.
- All right.
Hey, Nicky,
can I have some money, too?
Pearls before swine,
you fucking pig.
You're fucking pitiful.
(ENGINE STARTING)
It's gonna be beautiful.
Let's get out of here.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BLOW DRYER WHIRRING)
-WOMAN 1:
Here, let me borrow that.
WOMAN 2:
Yeah, just give me a second.
(SPRAYING)
Hey, Tony,
what's with the spandex?
Don't you want
the back of your
ball bag tanned?
(LAUGHING)
(TONY CONTINUES LAUGHING)
TOMMY: What's up?
Who's there? Who's that?
It's the guy Sal sent over.
Oh, the big mouth.
Hey, big mouth.
You better hope my
kid don't catch cancer
from your dumb fuck cousin's
cigarette fumes.
Come here.
Come on, a little closer.
- Don't be shy.
- I'm fine right here.
Come back, finish me later.
I'm going mobile with this.
Pretty girl gives you
a tan in your home...
(SPANKS)
...and sucks you off.
Good idea?
Sure. Whatever you say.
Whatever I say?
Whatever I say.
I say
you're a dirt bag.
That's what I say.
What do you say?
- I say you're right.
- You're right I'm right.
Say, aren't you here
to get down on your knees
and suck my dick?
Is that right?
I'm just kidding.
Not really.
I'm here because you and I,
we got mutual friends.
And out of respect
for those friends,
I've come here to apologize.
So there you go.
There you go.
Okay, pretty boy. One...
(LAUGHING)
We don't have mutual friends.
You,
you're just a wannabe punk
for Salvatore Vitaglia.
You don't got your button,
so quit pretending.
Not yet.
Not... Not yet?
I think I heard the sound
of a little piece
of shit talking to me
without a sincere apology.
Sincere... You hear
a sincere apology, Joe?
This is Joe.
Joe don't talk much,
except with his eyeballs.
(SNIFFS)
What his eyeballs say,
blow your mind.
You ever have your
mind blown, Nick?
Ever?
Look, Tony, I come
here to apologize to you.
All right?
What else do you want from me?
You know,
I like cocaine very much.
I like ladies with big tits
rubbing them all in my face.
I like Italian cars.
I like Irish whiskey.
I like things all men like
but are afraid to admit
to their girlfriend
or their wife
for fear she'll make
him sleep on the couch.
I like the couch.
It's relaxing.
I don't need a man cave
in the basement
with flat screen TV,
video game,
hiding out like
some fucking mouse.
I don't need a fucking
man cave because
the whole fucking world,
that's my man cave.
You have a man cave, Nick?
No.
Nick, come here.
Come on, come on.
Just come on.
I want you to tell me
what you think of me.
The truth. You seem like a guy
who tells the truth. Come on.
Come on, Nick. Blow my mind.
The truth?
I think...
I think today if you're
rich and you're Italian,
that makes you a gangster.
Like on some TV show.
(LAUGHING)
What?
You mean, I'm a TV show?
I'm a TV show?
Apologize for insulting me,
you fucking asshole!
Mr. Matazano,
I am sincerely sorry
for acting so out of line.
I meant you no disrespect.
Please accept my
sincerest apology.
Get out of here. Go on.
You tell that
dipshit mongoloid
cousin of yours,
if he fucks with my
daughter again, I'll rip
his fucking throat out.
(SCOFFS SOFTLY)
(LAUGHS)
You... Hey! I fucking
saw that, cocksucker!
(ENGINE IDLING)
(DOOR OPENING)
All right, let's go! Let's go!
Start the fucking car, George!
- Come on, George!
- What?
We gotta fucking go!
What the fuck is
the matter with you?
-They're right behind me.
Can we go?
-(MEN YELLING)
-Who them? Man, I'm fucking...
-Drive the fucking car!
Do your fucking job!
When you fucking bug out...
Fuck you!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Why are we stopped?
(SIGHING)
Swear to God, George.
Why are we fucking stopped?
You know, Nicky,
you're the only guy I know
who goes into a titty bar
to suck a fucking cock.
What? You think that
I wanted to go do that?
I had to, all right?
You didn't have to.
You fucking chose to.
Look, you wanna be
a part of that whole thing
and eat a plate of shit
every time these guys fucking
serve it up to you?
Go right ahead.
Just don't expect me to be
sitting there with a fork
and knife next to you.
And I'll tell
you another thing.
If that fuck crosses me again,
-I'll fucking bury him.
-All right,
all right, all right.
- Fucking apple face.
- All right, all right.
Look, I know. All right?
But don't worry about it.
Sal's gonna make...
Sal's gonna what?
Is that your new mantra?
"Sal's gonna"?
You know,
I don't gotta join a club
to know who my friends are.
It's not about
fucking friends.
It's about business.
All right?
No, it's about
business with me.
With you, who knows
what the fuck it's about?
You got all these
fucking big ideas.
You know what I got?
I got little ideas.
And they keep me
fed and not dead.
(CHUCKLES)
Can you please get me
the fuck out of here?
(SLOW ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey.
Ali here?
What can I get for you?
Let me get a whiskey sour.
(ICE CLATTERING)
$6.
Keep the change.
You Ali?
Who's asking?
I'm Nick.
Okay. What's up?
I heard from your father
there was some kind of
problem with my cousin
at the hair salon you
were at the other day.
I'm here to apologize for him.
You're apologizing for him?
Well, I don't have
a problem with you.
It's your little shit cousin
that called me a cunt.
And who cares, anyway?
I care.
The person I
work for, he cares.
It was an insult to
you and to your father.
I'd like to try
to make amends.
My father's insultable.
What are these?
NICK: They're for you.
They're flowers.
What am I
supposed to do with them?
I don't know.
Put them in water.
(BUCKET CLANKS)
Wait. Look. Okay. (CHUCKLES)
I know there are
better flowers.
Oh, really?
Why didn't you
bring them, then?
Next time.
What was your name again?
Nick. Nick Tortano.
Okay, Niccolo.
You go back and
you tell your boss
that everything's fine.
You'll live to
see another day.
Whoa, whoa...
Just... Hang on. Hang on.
You gotta let me
do this the right way.
Miss Matazano,
I am sincerely sorry my cousin
was acting so disrespectful
and out of line.
It was
completely inappropriate.
I hope you can accept
my sincerest apology.
Okay.
Thank you.
That was really nice.
And thank you for the flowers.
Hey.
You wanna go out with me?
(SIGHS)
Not in a million years.
(BUZZING)
(MUSIC PLAYING IN APARTMENT)
What's up, brother?
(SNIFFS)
I thought you
were coming alone.
You gonna bust my balls?
I'm not allowed to have
a friend in the world?
It's me. Let me in, Victor.
All right, come in.
Fucking asshole.
Victor, you know Nick? No?
VICTOR: Yeah, yeah,
we met a couple of times.
- How you been?
- Good.
VICTOR: Yeah?
You wanna line of coke?
No, thanks, I'm good.
VICTOR: Are you sure?
This shit's cut
with creatine, man. It's fire.
(VICTOR SNIFFS)
Well, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna do a line.
(SNORTING)
(GRUNTS)
Ooh. (COUGHS)
(SNIFFING)
Hey, Victor, where's Blackie?
He don't live
with you no more?
What was that? Huh?
GEORGE: I said,
where's Blackie? He don't
live with you no more?
No, no. Not since
he got sent upstate.
It's all right, though.
He's too into himself,
you know what I mean?
A real narcissist.
I can't be surrounding myself
with people like that anymore.
Fuck! Where are my manners?
Do you guys want
a beverage or something?
I'm good, I'm good. Thanks.
But Blackie,
you should've seen him
when he got arrested.
The fucking guy
started crying
like a little bitch.
Fucking idiot.
Now, he's in the union.
Fucking union job.
Who wouldn't want a union job?
Like I don't want a union job?
(CHUCKLES)
I'd love a union job.
Making 1,800 a week.
I'd never fuck that up.
He's full of it.
Always talking big talk.
I fucking...
I never understand
guys like that, you know?
They go on and on and on
about nothing at all.
It's crazy.
He's in the union.
Shit don't make no sense.
What am I doing?
It's all good, right?
Of course it's good.
Of course this shit's good.
I know it's all here.
I'll be right back.
(VICTOR SNIFFING)
You know what else?
Like, what's he thinking?
The cops ain't
gonna fucking bust him
'cause he's banging hammers
and pounding nails and fucking
running wires on the weekends?
(COUGHS)
Fucking crazy.
Like,
"Oh, I got a W-2, Officer.
Please, leave me alone.
Don't arrest me."
He got sent upstate
to Shirley for, I think,
two years or something.
I haven't talked to him.
(SNORTING)
It's crazy how you can be
best friends with someone
and then five minutes later
you're fucking enemies. Right?
It's crazy because...
What the fuck, George?
-Nicky, are you serious?
-GEORGE:
Get down on the floor.
Fuck, Nicky.
You heard the man.
On the floor.
Victor, you know I'll do it.
Get the fuck down.
VICTOR: What are you doing?
What the fuck, man?
Jesus Christ.
I thought we were friends,
Georgie.
GEORGE: I been setting this up
since I've known you.
George, we met two years ago.
Exactly. (LAUGHING)
He's good, huh?
(GRUNTING)
VICTOR: Fuck!
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
- Fuck you!
(GRUNTING)
You fuckers!
Cocksucker.
(GROANING)
It's fucking frozen.
Guess I know
where he hides it.
MELISSA: Hey, Nicky.
When are you gonna take me out
and do something?
How old are you?
MICHAEL: Hold on, Nicky.
Melissa, I don't pay
you to talk. All right?
Go get dressed.
We open in an hour.
You hire relatives, that's
what you get. All they wanna
do is chit-chat.
She's a good kid.
I'll see you.
Whoa, Nicky.
Where are you going?
What's your rush?
I got to go. I'm late for Sal.
I'll talk to you later.
Sal and Jerry were
in here last night.
The place was packed.
Yeah. Yeah, I noticed.
You're doing real
well for yourself.
You're really expanding here.
On that note, um, I hate
to bother you with this,
but do you have
that grand you owe me?
I'm sorry, Michael,
I don't have it.
Things been pretty slow.
You know?
Slow. Yeah, I hear you.
You know, if you want,
I can get you
a job down at the deli
or I can give you
a couple of hours
over here in the kitchen.
You could pay me back,
work it off.
Don't bust my balls,
all right?
I ain't that guy.
You ain't that guy?
Which guy?
The guy who doesn't pay?
The guy who doesn't work?
Or are you the guy
that wants to make trouble?
Do me a favor, Nicky.
Give me the money
when you have it, please?
And say hi to Sal for me.
You got it.
- Thank you, Nick.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Hey. Nicky, how are you?
I'm here to see Sal.
Oh, yeah.
(PAPER RUSTLING)
(KEYS JANGLING)
You got an address.
Now, take care of it.
You got to know,
there's a guy on that paper,
ain't gonna show up
nowhere never again.
Capisce?
Yeah.
JERRY: Get this shifted.
Just move the boxes
onto the trolley there.
All the boxes. Okay?
Hey, Nicky.
When you're young,
you got options.
Later on, you don't.
Enjoy the sunshine, Nicky.
Be winter before you know it.
What's going on
with my chatty
friend over there?
I never heard you so quiet.
(SNIFFS)
GEORGE: You want some air
or something? You want me to
roll the window down?
Yeah.
(SIGHING)
You know,
you don't have to do this
if you don't want to.
We can go get
something to eat.
The first one is hard.
After that, it's...
(STARTS ENGINE)
I'm just leaving
the office right now.
I'll be home in
about a half an hour.
I love you, too.
- GEORGE: Excuse me.
- (HORN HONKS)
(GINSBERG STRUGGLING)
(HONKS HORN)
Easy.
(GEORGE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT)
MAN: Good to see you.
(CHUCKLING)
- Sal.
- Nick.
A big day for you.
Yes, sir.
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
ANGELO: Excuse me.
In honor of the family,
the family is open.
I, Niccolo Emilio Tortano...
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
SAL: ...want to enter
into this organization...
(NICK CONTINUES
SPEAKING ITALIAN)
SAL:...to protect
my family...
...and to protect my friends.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
SAL: Our thing
you wish to be a part of,
it's a wonderful thing.
The greatest
thing in the world.
Do you feel this way as well?
Yes, I do.
And wish to be a part of it
for the rest of your life?
NICK: Yes.
SAL: You agree
to be a soldier,
follow the rules
and obey our code of omerta
until your dying breath?
Yes.
Jerry, will you be
Niccolo's  compare?
Proud of you.
As this saint burns,
so will my soul burn.
I live and die
by the gun and the knife.
I swear never to betray
the secrets of this
thing that we have
and to obey with
love and omerta
the Sicilian code of silence.
(SIZZLING)
JERRY: This family,
we help each other
because our people
became outlaws.
What took place here today,
only the Ghost knows, by God.
SAL: He who is blind,
deaf and mute
lives 100 years of happiness.
Which finger do you use
to pull the trigger?
(APPLAUSE)
(PASSING TRAFFIC)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
NICK:  Mr. C.
Hey, Nicky.
Thank you for seeing me, sir.
Hey. My pleasure.
Got those credit card numbers
we talked about?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I wanted to tell you,
it was a stroke of genius.
Coming up with this idea.
- You want a drink?
- Sure.
MR. C.: Mikey,
get him a drink, please.
These numbers
ain't never been
run by you, right?
No. That's the way
you wanted it, right?
Yeah, that's the way I
wanted it, but you had these
over a month, right?
Nicky,
I double-check 'em myself.
If I say they're over a month,
you can go to bet on it.
I'll see you next time.
- Thank you, Mr. C.
- Okay.
Nicky.
Congratulations.
GEORGE: Thank you.
Don't forget,
you're in to Michael
for a grand, too, right?
-Oh, that fucking prick.
-You owe a lot of
people money, man.
-Fuck that cocksucker.
-You gotta chill
with that shit.
I work in his
fucking deli, my ass.
What a bitch.
So go get him.
He knows everybody by name.
He knows everybody
in the neighborhood.
He'll go crying to Sal
like a big fucking baby.
So what? You're a made guy.
This guy's a fucking blowjob.
What am I missing?
Oh, yeah.
Listen, no more free
ziti with meatballs
and Italian subs. All right?
What's going on here?
What's the problem?
The problem is you've opened
four of these stores
in the last three years.
How much money can you really
be making selling fucking
mortadella and prosciutto?
- Seriously? You're serious.
- What else are you doing?
Why are you asking
all these questions?
You're driving around
in a brand new Mercedes.
You wouldn't fucking
lie to me, would you?
I see.
You got your button now.
You bring your baby gorilla
here to scare me?
(CHUCKLING)
You know what? Why don't you
tell Jerry to give me a call.
We'll settle this, okay?
Hey, wait. That's not...
That's not how it's gonna go.
That's no way to talk to me.
You're a gangster now?
No disrespect,
Nick, but fuck you.
I ain't paying you shit.
- (GROANS)
- NICK: Shh, shh, shh.
NICK: All right?
How many accounts
receivable you got?
How many people
haven't paid you?
- You're asking me this?
- I'm asking you.
Ten, 20, too many.
NICK: Stand up.
Come on, get up.
Stand up.
Listen to me. All right?
Listen to what this is.
I take care of you.
You take care of me.
Anybody who don't
take care of you
is also not taking care of me.
MICHAEL: I gave
your brother Vito a job
when he was a little kid.
NICK: And now it's
time to repay the favor.
Yeah, let's go take
a look at your books.
I'm gonna take care of
everything, all right?
(LAUGHTER)
MAN: What are you
fucking busting my balls for?
It's 32 grand in there.
I got 12 coming in
from Freddy Charles
in Lynn.
Also, you know, Tony's running
them Slavic girls on the side.
Don't worry about Tony.
And don't worry about
his daughter either.
Call isuckcock.com
if you get lonely.
MAN: No, you can't call them.
The Feds know about that, too.
What?
- MAN: Suckcock.com?
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
(BASS THUMPING)
(SNORTING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the fuck do you want?
(CHAIR SCRAPING)
We, uh...
We heard you been
running Ukrainian girls
out of here.
Pimping them out
to high-end clients.
(SNIFFS)
Yeah?
You better start feeding
your rat some better
fucking cheese. All right?
'Cause there ain't no
Ukrainian broads here.
These are local girls.
- Hmm?
- Oh, yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
Where're you from, sweetheart?
(SLAVIC ACCENT) Rhode Island.
(CHUCKLES)
We know from
a certain hotel off Boylston
these girls are making
$1,000 a night
outside the club.
(SOFTLY) Can you
believe this motherfucker?
Look, kid.
Tony ain't
gotta give you shit.
All right?
Just 'cause you're made,
that don't mean nothing to us.
- NICK: Really?
- Yeah, especially me.
Really.
Tell Tony we
just want our cut.
It's that simple.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
Flowers again, huh?
What do you want?
It's next time.
Better flowers.
Thank you.
What...
What are you doing now?
Going home.
I could walk with you.
I'm okay. I can walk myself.
It's just a few blocks away.
I can walk with you.
My car's in the shop,
but I like to walk.
It's a Cadillac.
- What?
- My car. It's a Cadillac.
Three hundred horsepower.
Leather seats.
It's a real comfortable ride.
I could give you
a lift home sometime.
Yeah. Sure. Leather seats.
What, you don't like
leather seats?
What's wrong
with leather seats?
(TEASINGLY)
"You don't like leather seats?
"Who don't like leather seats?
Leather seats."
-That's how I sound?
I sound like that?
-(CHUCKLES)
That's the way I sound to you?
You know what?
I'm gonna keep my mouth shut.
I'm not gonna say nothing else
the whole walk home.
Oh, yeah. I bet.
Okay, then.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You may speak now.
Okay.
(LAUGHS)
Vow of silence still?
Okay.
Good night.
You wop greaser.
Good night, you stupid guinea.
Open your yapper.
Okay.
You just gonna keep
bringing me flowers, huh?
Are we gonna go to the prom?
Oh.
I see. Ahem!
You're embarrassing yourself.
Come on, say something.
Tell me...
Tell me some more about
your horsepower
and your gold chains
and your Virgin Mary.
Tell me...
Tell me how much you love
your I-talian mother.
(SIGHS)
I'm a woman you can love.
Be careful.
TONY:  And you
couldn't see this coming
a mile away?
It's a setup.
Look at the patterns
he was rifling in.
Nickel A and R.
Dime, dime, dime, dime tease.
Maxes out every bet.
Bets every game.
One day,
hockey and basketball,
the next day football.
Come on!
He takes
the favorite in every game.
We pay this guy for
the past three weeks?
- Yeah.
- How much?
- 10,000.
- 10,000!
And he's down now, what?
25,000?
And you didn't cut him off?
I thought he was good for it.
TONY: Okay.
Mmm-hmm.
Who is this guy?
All I have is a phone number.
You're letting
people take action,
and you don't even
know their faces,
you fucking moron?
What the fuck are you
doing about it, Joe?
What am I supposed
to do about it, huh?
If I knew who the guy
was or where he was,
- I'd break his fucking legs.
- TONY: Mmm-hmm.
I call him. He says
he ain't got the money.
And he fucking hangs up, Tony.
What do you want me to do?
-It's this
fucking punk's fault.
-TONY: Joe...
JOE: Get him
the fuck out of here!
We have no idea
who this guy is.
Why not?
All I got is a number.
What do you mean,
you just have a phone number?
You're the fucking agent!
This is a fucking setup
and you're all in on it.
Jesus. Fuck!
I'll do it myself.
What's the number?
Come on,
give him the fucking number.
What are you doing?
- I just texted it to you.
- (SPUTTERS)
Why don't you
just fucking tell me
the fucking number?
Jesus! Fuck!
Get out there.
Waste more of my time.
Come on.
Come on, you fucking moron.
Get out of here.
What are you,
a fucking dickhead?
You trying to get me
in fucking trouble?
TONY: Seriously?
Hey.
Go make a buck.
What do you think,
this is a dumb slut
convention?
My God!
You two are depressing.
Is this F-4?
Come on, man,
don't be such
a fucking jerkoff.
You owe me 25,000.
It's been three weeks.
I'm gonna beat you.
I'm gonna fucking
rape you in a body bag.
Oh. Oh...
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I had no idea your life
was so fucking hard.
Yeah.
Yeah. I know the place.
Do you got my fucking money?
Okay. I'll meet you there now.
Fuck you, by the way.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Joy Luck Club,
go shake your rice cakes,
I got bills to fucking pay.
Yeah, don't think
I didn't see that.
I see everything!
NICK: Hey.
Nice hat.
Yeah? You like it?
I do, I do. I like the hat.
Thanks. Just got it.
So, what do you want to do?
You want to go to
the movies or something?
It's freezing.
How do you know my father?
What?
I don't talk to him.
He's an asshole.
Nick.
I stay away from him
and the people he
hangs out with. So...
Really?
'Cause he seems
like such a sweetheart.
Look.
I like you. All right?
ALI: I didn't like you at all.
(MOANING)
Hey.
- See you.
- Bye.
(SIGHS)
Vito!
Hey.
You know, you don't
got to smoke out here.
Mom ain't here to
tell you any different.
Are you gonna say hello to me?
"Hey, Nick.
How are you, Nick?"
If you're not
gonna talk to me,
give this to Vito
for me, will you?
You're a big shot now.
Big tough guy, huh?
Excuse me?
VINCENT: What do you got?
What do you got here?
Wow, look at that.
Throwing it around.
Hey, who wants a hundie?
There's a 50
right there for you.
Take a 20, huh? Big shot.
(SNIFFS)
Smells like blood to me.
It's college money.
It stinks.
NICK: You haven't had
a job since Mom died.
Take the money.
If she knew what
you were doing...
If your mother knew
what you were up to,
she'd be sick.
You'd kill her all over again.
There's 2 grand right here.
Get it out of my sight.
I think Vito could use it.
Don't you?
Over my dead body.
(SOFTLY) I'm begging you.
What do I got to
say to you, huh?
What do I got to do?
What do I got to do
to get through to you?
My boy. Beautiful boy.
If your mother
were alive, she'd say,
"Tu aviadu morde."
You say that to me?
I'm your son, Pa!
I have a son.
Get that out of my house.
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
NICK:  Jesus Christ, George.
What the fuck?
I missed, like, nine calls
from you last night.
I stayed over at
Tony's daughter's house.
Sal's gonna be pissed,
so keep your fucking mouth
shut about it, all right?
Anyway, I got your message
with some fucking
address up in Lynn.
I guess I'll be there
in, like, an hour.
(BARKING)
(GEORGE LAUGHING)
NICK: Fuck! Tony.
Hey! Look who it is.
Merry fucking Christmas.
Look at this guy, huh?
- What the fuck?
- GEORGE: Yeah.
He got fucked up.
What the fuck
did you do, George?
GEORGE: I couldn't
avoid this here.
- NICK: What the fuck?
- A bit complicated.
-NICK: What the fuck?
-He looks fucked up,
doesn't he?
(CHUCKLING)
It's fucked up
how it happened.
You want to hear the story?
(SCOFFS)
(CHUCKLES)
I was rifling
into this big book
that a friend of mine
had put me on with
a few weeks back.
I think I told you about it.
Anyways, must have
been beginner's luck.
Because right out
of the fucking gate,
I'm hitting everything.
I won 10 grand.
First couple of weeks.
(SIGHS) But what do I
know about football?
I don't know
shit about football.
Eventually,
I started missing some bets.
Actually, the third week,
I fucking missed everything.
I mean, I got fucking buried.
I was losing
everything I put in.
Went down 25,000.
So I tried to be scarce.
Fall off the radar a minute.
I tried to avoid these pricks.
Honest to God, I did. I did.
But they kept
calling
and harassing
and calling
and harassing my friend,
until eventually he caved in.
He coughs up my phone number.
So, yesterday I'm sitting
at the house, I'm waiting
for this broad to call me up,
and I see
a number I don't know.
I think it must be her.
And I pick up the phone.
(SCOFFS)
You know whose voice
I hear on the other line?
My handsome friend,
right here.
(LAUGHING) I mean,
what are the fucking chances?
It was fucking unbelievable.
I couldn't believe it.
I mean...
We just saw this prick
a few weeks ago.
Fucked me all up.
Of course, right away,
he starts with the tough talk.
The beatings and
the body bags and the...
(MIMICS SHOOTING)
Real fucking wise prick.
I mean, this is one
disrespectful fuck!
I gave him a bullshit story.
I told him
I have half his money.
"I got half of
your money, Tony.
"I got half."
Comes into my neighborhood.
And once he got
out of his car,
I fucking tased him.
Threw him in
the back of my car.
Well, I think you can
deduce the rest of
the story from there.
You set him up?
What are you? Fucking stupid?
You're gonna get
us both killed.
You got to let him go.
I don't got to do shit!
George.
I didn't even
know it was his book
until I heard his
fucking retarded voice
on my phone.
(BREATHING HARD)
I do know one thing, though.
See, to me, you know
what this seems like?
It seems like fate.
I mean, Nick,
I think they call it kismet.
- (GRUNTING)
- Fucking stop, George!
Oh, shit!
JOE: Hey! Hey! Hey! Jerry!
Jerry. What's up, huh?
You don't return
our fucking calls?
You can't leave a voicemail?
Cut the shit, man.
Tony's missing.
JOE: Yeah, he don't
return our calls either.
That's not like him.
Something's up.
You know where he is?
What do I look like,
the fucking lost and found?
Hey, you don't want me
to tell you what you
look like. All right?
You better not know
where my fucking boss is.
I know what I'd like
to do to your boss.
But we got money on him.
Whoa. Wait a minute. We?
What do you mean, "we"?
(CHUCKLES) All I see
is one guy standing in
a fucking empty loading dock.
There ain't no more "we."
Okay? It's us.
All right? From here on out.
Don't think I don't know
what the fuck's
going on around here.
Hey. You know why they call me
"daylight," right? Hmm?
You wanna find out?
(COCKING GUN)
Hey, get out of here,
you fucking project trash.
Fuck you!
(BARKS)
(DOGS BARKING)
Uh...
I didn't mean
for this to happen.
I'm sorry. All right?
You got to believe me.
I'm sorry.
They're fucking
with Sal's business.
You got no idea
what you're into.
(WHEEZING LAUGH)
You're in so far
over your head.
Hey, hey, hey.
(TONY PANTING)
That mark, got you made,
he was on the up.
He was just in our way.
(CHUCKLES)
You clueless... Fuck!
You don't talk to me
like that. All right?
I'm a fucking made guy.
You might be protected,
but Sal made me, all right?
So shut your fucking mouth.
Mr. Made Guy.
(LAUGHS MOCKINGLY)
You got no idea
the wrath Sal's
gonna bring down.
GEORGE:
Fuck this greaseball, Nick.
Fuck this greaseball fuck.
NICK: Untie him, George.
We're letting him go.
What?
I said untie
the motherfucker, now.
I ain't fucking untying him.
What's done is done.
What do you think is going
to happen when Sal sees him
like this anyways?
Let him go, George.
Can't send him
back to Sal like that.
Look at him.
(CHUCKLING)
- Hey, listen.
- Fuck.
(SOFTLY)
You're gonna die
out here, you fuck.
George.
You're gonna die ugly.
You're gonna die, you fuck.
You hear me?
You're gonna fucking die.
George!
(GRUNTING)
I said let him go now!
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
TONY: Yeah.
- That's how it's gonna be?
- That's how it's gonna be.
That's right, Nick. Shoot him.
Shut up!
Kill him, Nick. Shoot him.
Go ahead, shoot me.
Kill him.
Go on. Shoot him, Nick.
Let me tell you
something, Tony.
Nick here, he ain't a shooter.
It ain't in his DNA.
Don't you fucking
test me, George.
Yeah,
Sal was gonna kill this fuck
no matter what.
Huh?
Save yourself, Nick.
Shoot him.
Shoot him. Come on, kill him.
Go ahead, shoot me, Nick.
Hey, did you tell Tony
about you and his daughter?
- George. Shut your mouth.
- Oh! (CHUCKLES)
- NICK: George.
- Oh, you didn't know?
Shut your fucking mouth.
GEORGE: Oh, he didn't know.
-This is beautiful.
It's fucking beautiful.
-NICK: Shut up.
- Yeah. Hey, Tony.
- Shut up.
-Guess who's
fucking your daughter?
-NICK: Fuck you, George.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That apology,
- it went real well.
- Kill him.
She accepted it,
I think. Yeah.
- Shoot him.
- Shut up!
TONY: Do it!
- He's fucking piping her.
- NICK: I swear to God, George!
-Fucking do him.
Shoot. Dead already.
-NICK: Shut up!
NICK: Shut up!
TONY: Kill him!
-Why don't you tell
Mr. Matazano...
-TONY: Kill him.
- ...how you got made?
- TONY: Nick.
GEORGE: Why don't you tell him
how you got made?
You know how he got made?
Who do you think
made that hit for him?
- George.
- Who did it for him?
I fucking did
that hit for him.
He was too afraid
to pull the trigger.
It's not in him.
(YELLING) I fucking made you!
I made you!
Shoot him, Nick.
Kill him, Nick. Do it.
You don't have
it in your heart.
TONY: Shoot him.
Kill him. Shoot him!
You know what?
Maybe we should untie him.
- Nick. Nick.
- Maybe we should untie him.
'Cause I want Sal
and everybody else
to know...
- What?
- ...exactly who you are.
- Nicky.
- What?
Look, my daughter...
I could give a fuck, man.
Okay?
Your secret, don't worry.
- Your secret's safe with me.
- You ain't a shooter.
- NICK: Shut your mouth.
-Shoot him.
-You don't have
the fucking heart to do it.
- Shoot me! Go ahead.
- Nick, shoot him.
Come on, please.
You ain't a shooter.
- TONY: Shoot him. Nick.
- You're not a shooter.
Do it! Yeah, shoot him.
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Shoot him. Shoot him.
(GUNSHOT)
(CASING CLATTERS)
That's the fucking spirit!
I knew you had it in you.
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
How's that feel?
(NICK SWEARING SOFTLY)
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
This is your mess to clean up.
I brought
the fucking contracting bags.
It was that kid
from Dorchester.
Nick's boy. Georgie Mullins.
You sure that's the guy
that owed Tony the 25?
Yeah. We finally found
that agent. The one that's
running the books.
He said it was Mullins.
Tony went to go talk to him,
and that's the last
time I heard from him.
I mean, add it up.
Nick don't answer.
Look, we've been looking
for Tony everywhere.
I know those two motherfuckers
know something.
I'll look into it.
Look, Sal.
We've been good to you.
You know?
I'll decide whether
you've been good to me.
I told you I'll look into it.
- Tried his cell.
- Let's go find this prick.
Tried his cell phone,
house phone.
Even called his father.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Yeah?
Nicky, where the fuck
have you been?
I've been...
- I've been busy.
- (LIGHTER CLICKS)
Where are you right now?
What?
Sal's looking for you, Nicky.
We need to see you now.
Tony's missing
and they got wind
that crazy mick of yours
was the last one
that seen him.
They've gone over
to your folks' house,
looking for you.
Nicky,
do the right thing here.
Nick here?
No. Nick don't live here.
Who are you?
You his brother?
Look, Nick's in deep shit.
Where the fuck is he?
Why don't you
go fuck yourself?
Come back later.
What? Hey! Hey, hey.
Don't fucking
close the door on me.
- What are you doing?
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- I got this. Dad, I got this.
- Just calm down.
- Get in the house. Please.
-Come on,
what are you gonna do?
-Get in the house.
- You got a problem here?
- Yeah. Fuck you! Look...
VINCENT:
This is private property.
- Get the hell out of here.
- JOE: I don't give a fuck.
You tell your brother
Joe came by.
Okay? And I'm gonna find him,
so you might as well
tell me where he is.
We wouldn't tell
you where he was
even if we knew. Let's go.
Come on. Get... Get off...
-Get off my...
-Don't put your
fucking hands on me.
VINCENT: This is
private property.
Get your fucking
hands off me.
Don't put your
fucking hands on me.
- Fuck you!
- This is private property.
What are you gonna do?
You got a fucking problem?
Get out of here!
Don't put your
fucking hands on me again,
old man. You hear me?
Listen, your son's
a fucking punk, all right?
He did the wrong thing
to the wrong fucking people.
You're a punk.
I'm a punk?
He's gonna pay
the fucking price.
Vito, no!
Hey, Vito!
Get back!
Vito! Get out of here!
Go home, guys! Vito!
JOE: Get the fuck off me!
VINCENT: Just go home!
JOE: You want to fuck with me?
Here you go!
- Motherfucker!
- VINCENT: Vito!
- No!
- JOE: Come on!
(GUNSHOT)
Dad?
JOE: Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Come on! Get in the car!
Let's go! Tom, get in the car!
What the fuck?
My brother's gonna
fucking kill you!
(ENGINE REVVING)
-You're okay.
Come on. You're okay.
-(GROANING)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
Please, Pop.
NICK: Can you hear me, Pop?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Pop?
Get him in the car.
Help me get him
in the fucking car.
-Help me get him
in the fucking car!
-Nicky, Nicky. Nick. Nick.
(WEEPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
NICK: Fuck!
Fuck!
I gotta talk to Sal.
Where is he?
He ain't gonna see you, Nicky.
Don't fuck with me, Jerry.
Where are they?
I'm gonna fucking kill him!
That Joe is
a fucking dead man.
No, no. You're not.
We're gonna take
care of things now.
You need to
fucking relax, Nicky.
They killed my father, Jerry.
I'm sorry, Nicky.
Things are a mess right now.
They found Tony up in Lynn.
In a fucking bag.
And that guy in
the parking garage.
He was straight,
though, wasn't he?
He got in the way.
People get in the way.
NICK: In the way.
In the way of what?
Doesn't matter.
You didn't kill him,
did you, Nick?
I told Sal to bring you in.
I put myself on
the line for you.
Your own father didn't care
if you was alive or dead.
- It's not fucking true.
- Here's what's true!
Get out of town.
Forget this girl.
Forget Sal. Forget this.
-Forget this,
this thing we have.
-Jerry.
Jerry.
(BANGS DOOR)
Look...
Hey, man, I'm so sorry.
Look.
This is what we gonna do.
We find them all one by one
and then murder those fucks.
No reaction to that?
What's the matter?
- No emotion?
- Shut up, George.
Nick, they killed
your fucking father.
I said shut
the fuck up, all right?
You having second thoughts
about what needs
to be done here?
Why?
Is it because you're
banging that whore?
That clown's fucking daughter?
Or is it because your boss,
Sally Jane Fungulo,
might get mad?
You're afraid of that?
Nick, we had to kill Tony.
How many times
did he disrespect you?
Disrespected your friend?
You listen to me.
What happened the other night
never happened, all right?
I know you, George.
You got a big fucking mouth.
A few weeks go by.
You get 10 deep in some bar.
And suddenly
everyone in Southie
gets the idea
that what never happened,
happened.
Who are you talking to?
You talking to me?
I run my fucking mouth?
You're an ungrateful fuck.
It wasn't enough
that I saved your fucking
pretty ass in Shirley?
That's not enough?
It ain't enough that I'm
fucking cutting you in
on all my action
just so you can kick it back
to these filthy
fucking guineas?
It ain't enough?
It ain't enough that I
gotta drive you around
to suck all
the dicks you gotta suck?
Guys like Joe?
That's what bullets
were invented for.
Kill that fucker.
You gotta kill him.
You ain't like me.
You ain't nothing like me.
You're a fucking wannabe.
A fucking wannabe.
Talking about all that
"restoring order to
the North End" shit.
You never had it in you.
You're a fucking poser.
You never had it in you!
You're a fucking fraud.
You shut your mouth.
Everything you say is a lie.
Everything you think
is a fucking delusion.
You shut your fucking mouth.
Everything you believe
is a fucking delusion.
I said shut
your fucking mouth!
You hear me?
You know who knew
you were a fraud
more than anyone?
Your old man.
(GRUNTS)
Nice fucking friend I have.
You know who your friends are?
Big fucking mafioso man!
Look at you.
You're a made man now.
You're a made man!
- (ENGINE STARTING)
- Where are your friends now?
Where are your friends now?
Where are your
fucking friends now?
I can count
mine on one finger!
(LOCKS CAR)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
Hey.
I've been calling you.
Can I come in?
(SIGHING)
I have to go to work soon.
You all right?
Yeah.
(SIGHING)
Listen, some guys came around
asking where my father is.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Do you know
anything about that?
-I have to go
away for a while.
-(SIGHS)
What do you need?
Do you know
where my father is?
Nick.
Would you go away with me?
(SIGHS)
Nick.
Would you?
Where's my father?
(WEEPING)
Fuck you!
What the fuck is
wrong with you?
Why did you do that?
(SOBBING) Why did you do that?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(SOBBING)
He's with the girl?
(SIGHS)
Get rid of him.
(MUFFLED GUNSHOT)
(SHORT SCREAM)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED GUNSHOT)
What are you doing?
I'm dropping this off for you.
That's for you.
Where you going?
I gotta take
care of some stuff.
Let me go with you.
That's for you.
Hey!
Fuck you.
(VITO SNIFFLING)
Don't fucking follow me.
(SNIFFLES)
(RADIO PLAYING)
(SONG PLAYING ON RADIO)
(CHOKING)
Move over.
Let's take a drive.
(GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANING)
I'm not surprised
to see you, Niccolo.
It's done.
This thing
that you have.
This
family.
It's all I ever wanted.
But it's done.
Why don't you put that down?
You destroyed
everything I ever cared about.
And now, I'm going
to fucking kill you.
What the fuck have you done?
What have I done?
I've done what I needed to do.
Yeah?
You let those guys
go over to my house.
My fucking house.
Killed my father. My girl.
Your father didn't care
if you was alive or dead.
You might as well
have been an orphan.
I gave you something
and you threw it away.
You do all that,
start killing people
in cold blood
so he finally approves of you?
Like he's looking down
from heaven all proud?
Let me tell you something. Oh.
He ain't looking down
on you from nowhere.
You're gonna have to
kill all of us, Nick.
There ain't many left.
But there's enough for you.
Let me ask you
a question, Sal.
You ever been in love?
Of course.
Who hasn't been in love?
(GUNSHOT)
(GUN CLICKS)
(DIALING)
Sal. I need a pick-up.
(STRIKING MATCH)
Need a lighter.
(GUNSHOT)
(GUNSHOTS)