[ Ambience ]
We're at the beginning
of something...
Crazy... And historic.
This will be
the hardest thing I ever do.
But there's nothing else
I'd rather.
If dad were around,
I think he'd be proud.
Welcome
to you your new office.
- Only six outlets.
- Oh, we can do
something about that.
We'll power from a different
circuit in the house.
Gonna need to do
a lot more than that.
Yeah, I like it.
It's good, clean, simple.
I mean,
it could be a lot worse.
Right, guys?
Kids.
It'll work just fine.
Here's the way I see it...
Main control panel over here.
Processor's back here,
And our pedestal
right in the center.
Okay, I'm just telling you now
I think we're gonna need
at least two storage towers.
All right, so spread them out.
Toss one
on each side of the table.
Where do you want me
to set up my chem set?
In your room.
We don't want contamination.
In that case, I'm...
Gonna be in the master, right?
We'll see.
Okay, so, everybody clear?
All right.
Project has officially begun.
Let's get to work.
[ Camera beeps ]
This is Perry Frank.
I'm the head scientist
and theorist
On the project entitled Phoenix.
Over the course
of the next few months,
We will be working
on breaking ground
And overcoming mortality.
These tapes will serve
as a personal log
Of all the participants
of the project.
Regular reports will be
mandatory.
Preliminary work is
going smoothly.
We have a basic timeline
and a strategy,
And we know how much rope
we have to work with...
five tests.
And we'll use them wisely.
I'm ready to get this rolling.
For real this time.
Okay, so,
everyone on the team seems like
They're getting along
really well, which is great,
And I like everyone on the team,
Which is good 'cause we're gonna
have to live together
For the next couple months.
And I mean, I just...
I really wish it were longer,
But it's probably about as far
as our grant money will last,
Which is what Perry says is
what we're gonna go on,
Which means we're gonna be
moving fast,
Working real hard, and, yeah,
I just hope it doesn't go by
too quickly.
So, I'm just supposed to talk?
Yeah.
It's for the grant organization
To be able
to track our progress.
And you want me
to talk to myself?
Well, no, not to yourself.
To the camera.
Right. So, to myself.
I don't... I don't know
what the guys have already said.
I-I don't know
what I'm supposed to say.
Honestly, this feels like
a complete waste of my time.
I'll have something to say
once we've actually had a test.
I have to get back to work.
I think the guys
are waiting on me.
[ Camera beeps ]
[ Machine whirring ]
Killing susie.
[ Machine powers down ]
Killing Jenny.
- Table clear?
- Yeah, it's clear.
Priming susie.
[ Switches click ]
Priming Jenny.
[ Machine whirring ]
Here we go.
[ Camera beeps ]
[ Electricity humming, popping ]
Oh, no. Cut the camera.
[ Camera beeps ]
[ Devices beeping ]
[ Switches click ]
[ Beeping stops ]
So, was that it?
- So we got nothing.
- Nothing.
Okay, plug in the girls.
[ Machine whirring ]
I'm sorry.
It really should have worked.
Probably gonna be
something stupid.
It's all right.
That test was
mainly a control.
So, let's see where we're at
And make sure
we nail the next one.
So...
What... Went... Wrong?
We juiced the hell
out of the thing.
Of course we did.
That's the point.
Well, it didn't work.
Let's talk specifics, boys.
Focus.
There's too much power coming
from the top down.
It doesn't match
with our outputs.
It's not supposed to.
Why can't we just turn it down
a bit?
- And by "we," you mean me.
- No, I mean, why can't we
Just regulate the...
no, no, it's fine.
Amps is just gonna
fix everything. Good.
No, that's not what I meant.
- Guys, we're on the same team.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Exactly.
Let's pull up the charts
and get some numbers up.
- So it's no more tests
for today, then?
- Only on paper.
It's gonna be a while
before we can go again.
Pasta and chicken?
- That'll do fine.
- Okay.
I don't think
we were off by that much.
No, we weren't.
It has to be a problem
in the theory,
Not the practice.
Amps wouldn't miss that badly.
I wouldn't go that far.
You carry a digit
to the wrong place,
You end up with a fire.
All right, here.
All of these numbers are
correct.
All right.
See, look,
I-i think we have a problem
With instrument accuracy
and margin of error.
See, look...
Look at these connections here.
The load can fluctuate
too easily.
So let's quit messing around
with the crickets
And get out
from under the microscope.
The larger the subject, the more
room we've got for error.
No, we... we... we got to take
one step at a time.
If we skip steps,
it makes it that much harder
To get up the stairs.
Just hear me out.
And we need a successful test
before we can move on.
Hear me out, Perry. Come on.
Look... From the beginning,
Our theory's been built around
the warm-blooded mammal.
That's how it was conceived.
That's how it was built.
Am I right, amps?
It should be able to cope
with anything.
Right, but I'm saying
it was built for mammals.
Yeah.
So... And I know this seems like
We're getting way ahead
of ourselves,
But why don't we at least start
on the right track?
Amps.
I'll go make some changes.
Catch a mouse.
All right, then. Moving on.
Wire cutters.
Hold on. Ah. There you go.
Thank you.
So, how's it going under there?
Pretty good,
from what I can tell.
Is there anything
I can do to...
Help you out right now, or...?
Yeah,
make sure I keep working.
So...
How'd you get a name
like ampersand?
How did you get a name
like Carter?
Well, um...
I was born
in a really small town,
And my... my grandfather was
the only doctor there.
And he had this dog...
This little Jack Russell terrier
That used to follow him around
all the time.
And, uh, the only problem with
having a-a dog for a best friend
Is, I mean,
they only live about 10 years.
So... One day,
that dog, Carter, passed.
And a week later, I was born.
Carter watts...
After the, uh... after the dog.
I was the second son born.
My parents always wanted
a daughter.
They wanted no more
than three kids.
Sense of humor.
Joke's on them, though.
I got a little brother.
[ Chuckles ]
Crescent wrench.
[ Tools shuffling ]
Do you want to see
how this thing goes together?
Test 1 went about as well
as could be expected.
We only have four left,
but we won't rush.
We'll... we'll make
the remaining tests last.
We'll make them count.
We'll get it done.
I think Perry and I did
a really good job
Hiring amps and Devin.
They're talented, hard-working,
driven.
[ Chuckles ]
It seems like they want
this project to work
even more than we do,
Which is
really saying something.
We're heading
in a good direction.
I think Perry and I are
working together well.
Uh [Chuckles]
he's... A complicated man.
Uh, not quite the same shape
as the rest of the world.
He doesn't know how to fit.
I started a bit of a fire.
Not really that big of a deal,
though.
I mean, it's not like
the guys can get mad at me.
I am building their new toy.
Um, Devin, uh, is getting us
to move on to mice.
Uh, it's... it's fine.
We were going that way anyways,
eventually.
Um...
[ Sighs ]
But, yeah, now I don't have
to deal with bugs, which...
I-I hate bugs.
Um, mice aren't so bad, though.
[ Squeaking ]
This is just depressing.
Why can't we use a trap
to kill it?
'Cause it'll break
the thing's spine.
You can't revive an animal
that's physically broken.
Well, we could.
No, no, no, no, no.
W-why don't we use some
poison pellets or something?
No, the poison would
still be in its system.
If the machine works, it just
wakes up and then dies again.
Well, clearly,
we're not doing that.
Poison dissolves
when it's dead?
Into what? Its tissue?
That's even worse.
So when he wakes up,
has some side effects,
We can't tell if it's
from the experiment
Or from the fact
that we poisoned him.
No, we got to do it the only way
that won't screw us over.
Suffocate it.
Put it in a box and seal it.
That'll work.
Fun conversation, guys.
Guys.
Come on!
Come on.
[ Squeaking ]
How... Long do you think
it'll take?
I have no idea.
- Do we have to keep it
in a see-through container?
- Yes.
Can we at least put it
under the table or something?
Fine.
And now we wait.
The thing is basically
a neurological jump start.
And, uh, now that we're working
with an animal,
The whole restarting
of the neurological process
Could lead to some very
interesting results.
Um, see, the... the animal's
commands start in the brain,
And, uh, these commands are
carried from neuron to neuron
By these rapid, uh,
electrical firings of synapses.
And these firings...
They have different patterns
And different lengths,
Which create mental function
and create impressions.
And similar firings help us
to remember,
Which begs
an important question...
Will this creature re-live
its own birth
Upon resuscitation?
It's too bad we can't ask it.
I... Thought I'd be ready
to start testing
On... on larger subjects,
But I just really, really feel
uncomfortable
Taking a mouse and killing it
For the purposes
of its possible re-animation.
Like, we don't even know
If this machine is gonna
work or not, and I...
I mean, can't we buy
some dead mice or something?
I just... Perry wouldn't even
let me name it.
He wouldn't even let me name it.
"Not gonna be around
for long enough."
I mean, I-i feel like
if we named it,
We have a better chance of
bringing it back to life, right?
The mouse traps worked.
So we have our test subject.
Machine is
up and ready to go again.
I've got the girls primed,
instrumentation recalibrated.
I think... I think...
I-i can't see any reason
Why this is not gonna work.
I remember seeing the notice
and thinking that,
"They can't be serious.
"This is something
that nobody does.
This is... Fantasy."
I forgot about it for...
10 minutes.
I-I just couldn't get it
out of my head.
I kept coming back to it because
what if... what if, like...?
Perry says this isn't about us.
I don't know.
It's important to note
the change
From crickets to mice...
Very important.
"After a failure in the first
test with the cricket..."
"From here on to be referred to
as subject 'a'..."
"The decision has been made
to change the organism
in question."
Size, blood, so on.
And make... make sure
that you mention
it's a mouse, specifically.
Yeah, I'm... I'm...
I'm getting there.
Don't... don't worry.
"The following test will be
conducted on an organism
"Of a greater size
"And with a warm-blooded
circulatory system...
A common mouse... subject 'b.'"
You know, you probably could
have written this without me.
But if I did,
no one would read it.
You keep my head straight...
Write what I mean and can't say.
I need that.
Just remember that when
you're in the history books...
"The great Perry Frank could
never have been published
Without Carter watts."
[ Machine whirring,
switches clicking ]
Did we check him?
I checked him twice.
'Cause zapping a bug is
one thing.
I just really don't want that
to happen to the mouse.
He'll be fine.
What are we gonna do,
kill it again?
Killing susie.
Carter?
Yeah, sorry. Killing Jenny.
Table clear?
Clear.
Priming susie.
Priming Jenny.
[ Machine whirring ]
Here we go.
[ Camera beeps ]
Killing power.
[ Machine powers down ]
[ Devices beeping ]
[ Switches clicking ]
[ Beeping stops ]
That's a no-go.
[ Clicking continues ]
Clear the table.
[ Device beeping ]
Did that register?
[ Sustained beep ]
P-Perry, did you get that?
Yeah, we got something.
It's just not much, but...
did it work?
Is he gonna make it?
Yeah, it worked for a second.
Devin, come look at this.
Devin.
What?
Come look at this.
[ Laughs ] L-look.
Yeah, yeah. We got all of it.
This is good.
Oh, this is really good.
This is... this...
I know what to do... Maybe.
[ Chuckles ]
Then we run it again.
Right now. We just run it again.
No, we can't.
Why not?
Look... th-the same mouse.
We can just run it again.
Of course.
Why didn't I think of that?
Okay, "a,"
the coils need to cool down.
"B," one test, one subject.
And that was our only mouse.
And, "c," the wiring melted
from the increase in voltage
From bugs to mammals.
Should I keep going?
All right, so, when can we, uh,
Be up and running again, huh?
I-I got to...
Got to take it down a few steps.
We got to re-wire it,
let the girls cool off,
Charge them up again,
and get another mouse.
Thursday. Thursday.
Thursday. Thursday's great.
Thursday's fine. This is good.
This is progress, right?
But we killed it.
But we brought it back to life
again.
Now we just have to figure out
somehow how to sustain it.
And... and that's all
we have to do.
That's it. Simple, right?
I'll get to work on an autopsy.
Yeah, record everything.
Write down everything and...
and preserve it.
Uh... Great work, amps, huh?
We're getting there.
I'll run analysis.
You get this
up and running again, okay?
Copy.
[ Door closes ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
Nice night.
Yeah.
Peaceful.
On nights like this, my...
Sister and I used to climb up
on our roof
And watch thunderstorms
in the mountains.
That sounds nice.
Yeah, it was.
My dad wasn't around much.
It was mostly just us.
That's understandable.
The, uh, scientific profession
asks a lot.
Did your father ever isolate
that protein sequence?
You know about my father?
Ah, I research.
That's what I do.
No.
No, he never did.
That's too bad.
I know.
He was a great man, my father.
He did his best
to raise us right.
That's all you can ask for.
Wish I had been afforded
the same.
What did your father do?
Nothing.
So, how long until we're ready
for the next test?
When we're ready.
We can't afford
to throw away any tests.
Right, no. Of course.
But... How long
do you expect this to take?
Well, we have enough money
for a couple months
Of waste and haste
with no results,
But, uh, if we slow down
and make each test last,
We might actually have
something.
But the...
The goal of this is...
To apply this work to humans,
right?
This endeavor is about
scientific advancement,
Not practical application.
You know, I think
my father's biggest regret
Was watching other men finish
the work that he started.
And I think about that
every day.
[ Camera beeps ]
The last few weeks have been,
uh...
Rough.
We... we keep getting
the same results.
Carter is, uh, staying positive,
as always.
And, uh,
Devin is getting frustrated.
But he works hard.
And ampersand...
Ampersand is is the one
I'm really worried about.
He's not himself lately.
His confidence is dropping.
And every time the machine
fails, he takes it personally.
I... well, I-I'm doing,
and I'll continue to do my best
To try and keep the team
and the project together.
I haven't slept
in a couple days,
So hopefully I'll be able to,
if I can...
If I can get some of this
off my mind.
Hopefully.
Yeah,
that doesn't look very safe.
What do you mean, "safe"?
The mouse is dead.
Yeah, I know,
but I just don't think
That looks like it's gonna work,
And I just don't want
to torture it.
It is dead.
And it's not supposed to work.
I just need to make sure
the skull cap transfers
Electricity more evenly.
Well, what does that have to do
with anything?
Carter, would you plug
the mouse in, please?
Not until you tell me
what you're gonna do
with this mouse.
Fine.
I need to make sure
I don't kill any cells
Or damage a portion
of the brain.
I need to make sure
I don't melt it.
- Melt it?!
- Give me the mouse.
Wait, hey! Hey!
You guys ready to go in here?
Hold that thought.
[ Machine whirring, pops ]
[ Sighs ] No.
Perry, a word, please?
Yeah. Sure.
Uh, amps, run a ground wire
from the cap to the table.
Tell me if that works.
[ Sighs ]
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
So, uh, are we set?
The synthetic adrenaline
And the oxidizers are
separating.
We can't wait any longer
Or I'll have to put together
a new blood strain.
So, how long will that take?
I can mix it together
with four hours' work,
But it'll take another five days
to bond and settle.
That's no good.
We're gonna waste so much
of our money on small tests,
We'll risk losing a real one.
We can try pushing the old mix,
But I think
it'll take too long to react
Once it's in the system.
Okay.
Well, if we're
not completely set now,
Let's ride the levels low.
Maybe we can save some wear
and maybe go two for one.
Ready to work. Let's go.
You sure?
Sure as I'm gonna be.
Third time's charm.
Let's hope so.
[ Camera beeps ]
Okay. Here we go.
[ Machines whirring ]
Cutting power.
[ Devices beeping ]
[ Machines powering down ]
And again, boys, that's a day.
[ Sighs ]
I'll go put some dinner on.
That'd be nice.
P-Perry, I want another te...
Let me... let me have
one more test, Perry, please.
I-I-i have another...
I have another...
I have another mouse,
and just...
Just one more test, Perry.
I-i-I'm sorry.
God, I'm sorry.
You've got nothing
to be sorry for.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no. It's not you.
It's all of us.
This is not an easy thing
we're doing, so just calm down.
I know. I know. I know.
Yeah, I-i know.
L-let's just try again, okay?
Just five minutes.
Five... five minutes... Perry.
Five... Uh... I think...
I think I know what's wrong.
It's basically all that I...
all that I haven't changed,
um...
No, I mean...
Five minutes, Perry.
Let's... let's go again.
Just you and me, okay?
Please.
Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Okay.
I think we have enough power
for one more pull.
60%. That's reading fine.
Fine.
[ Switches clicking ]
[ Machines whirring ]
Okay.
That's what I...
That's what I can do.
Okay.
Here we go.
[ Machine thuds ]
[ Machine whirring ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
Killing. Killing.
[ Air hisses ]
[ Devices beeping ]
[ Machine powering down ]
Sorry.
That was...
No. No, I...
Sorry, Perry.
I'll... I'll do better.
No.
Take a break, hmm?
We need the rest.
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Clock ticking ]
[ Knock on door ]
Go away.
Go away!
[ Door opens ]
I saved you some dinner.
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Wind chimes ringing ]
Guys?
Guys?!
Guys! Guys!
Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up!
Wake up, Perry! Perry!
Come on! It worked. It worked.
Stop screaming.
Some of us need sleep.
The mouse moved.
What happened?
Uh, I came here to check
on the girls and...
And the the table was empty
and...
And that mouse is on the floor.
Go... go...
Go check the record.
See if there's anything abnormal
about our last test result.
Perry!
I-I don't think
anything is different.
I think...
i think everything's the same.
No, no, no.
Uh, amps and I ran another test
last night.
It was
after everybody else left.
We didn't have anybody here
to record it.
I know what changed.
I can build off this,
recorded or not.
What's all the shouting?
What did I...?
Why is that mouse on the floor?
We're back in business.
Carter entered the lab
last night
And found our test subject
across the room.
Amps has
something to work with now.
Yeah, finding
that mouse on the floor was
About the best thing
that could have happened to us.
[ Chuckles ]
The team is motivated.
We've got our miracle.
This is the thing I needed.
This is gonna
let us do something big.
There's no way Perry can say no.
Not now.
He... he's just gonna want to go
bigger and better.
And then we're there.
I was
at the hospital last night,
And... and she's...
She's not getting better,
But she's stable.
There's still time.
We got lucky.
Uh, hopefully,
it helps me out quite a bit.
I-I-if this is accurate,
then I-i-I've got some things
I can try, pieces I can...
I can build with.
Um, I think... I think
we're running into an issue
With cell oxidization,
which I...
Which I need to talk
to Devin about,
But if it made it off the table
and no further,
It's definitely an issue
with cell functionality,
Uh, but luck or not,
I am glad this happened.
I am... I am really glad.
What did we do?
We've only been changing
The amount of power
we've been using
And playing around
with the pieces we already have.
And I guess
there's a lot going on
That's a bit over my head,
but still, I mean,
I'm not complaining.
This is progress.
This is amazing progress.
I just... I just can't seem
to understand
What could have caused this,
unless...
Unless somebody...
You finished with the camera?
We should get this on tape.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
What do you mean?
We document everything.
The mouse moved.
Yeah, but maybe it didn't.
Well, I'm not sure I follow.
Maybe somebody moved the mouse.
Maybe... To make the machine
look like it was working?
I'll keep it in mind.
Thank you for looking out,
But don't worry about it
too much, okay?
I don't want it
affecting your work.
Okay.
I just was going through it,
And I don't really see
how it would be possible.
I mean,
we didn't really change
anything.
Well, Devin's blood strain was
getting old, separating.
Perhaps the separation
kicked the oxidizers first
And the adrenaline second.
And, uh, we only ran half surge,
not even half,
So it could have created
a more natural pulse,
Which we didn't account for.
Our distribution system's
at its best yet...
Completely revamped,
twice as efficient.
Any one of these would have made
the difference.
Yeah, of course.
If there's a problem,
I'll handle it.
Sorry to bother you, Perry.
Carter.
Thank you.
Overall voltage output ranges
from 100 volts to 3,500 volts
At maximum output.
We have
the capacity for anything.
No. No, not anything.
Anything up to a human
and a bit beyond.
Anything useful.
But it gets more difficult
the smaller the subject gets.
Tougher on the machine.
Easier on the general public.
Nobody minds us working
on a mouse,
But the second we move up
to household pets,
People start to get nervous.
And we know we can get
our organism up and moving,
But we can't sustain it,
and there's a delay.
And I have an idea
why this might be happening.
Now, once a cell dies, it is
difficult to bring it back.
And even then,
there's no telling
If it'll be able
to function properly.
But even dead cells contain
enough genetic information
To make a copy of themselves.
I see
where you're going with this.
It's not something I can do.
No, I know.
I'm not asking you to.
Yeah, I-i rea... I really
don't see where you're going.
He's talking about inducing
cell generation,
But only where necessary.
Exactly.
Activating the existing cells
isn't enough.
We need to start helping.
We need to catalyze
The regenerative processes
exponentially.
We'll know we've done our jobs
if the rabbit stays alive
And sheds about 40% of its mass
over the first day.
Uh, rabbit?
Where are we getting rabbit?
They're transported frozen.
It'll preserve more living cells
and make my job a lot easier.
An enzyme.
Yes.
I'm already working on it.
From what cells?
Some of my own.
Just a small skin sample.
Human cells?
Yes, that... they're
the most readily available.
It shouldn't cause
any genetic complications.
How long do you need?
Three or four days.
Take a week. Get it right.
[ Sighs ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Wind chimes ringing ]
[ Ringing continues ]
[ Typewriter clacking ]
[ Chuckles ]
It's a...
Funny system those two have.
It works.
They make a good team.
I guess.
I'm not sure
what Carter brings to it.
He's a good kid.
You should... Get to know him.
Talk to him. Give him a chance.
[ Clacking continues ]
Were you out of bed last night?
Uh, I'm out of bed every night.
Did you see anything
or hear anything unusual?
What do you mean?
Oh, I thought I heard noises
coming from outside.
Thought I heard the front door.
Huh.
No, I didn't hear anything
that bothered me.
And I was up
pretty much all night.
Hmm.
Creatures in the night.
[ Chuckles ] Yeah, I guess so.
[ Clacking continues ]
Are you busy?
Not really. What's up?
I just wanted...
To thank you...
For not asking where I was
the other night.
Of course.
I mean...
It's not really
any of my business.
Just as long as you're doing
your work...
Yeah.
You know, I... Never asked you.
How... how'd you end up working
for Perry?
Um, I was doing
my undergraduate
When he was doing his doctorate,
And he was one of my professors,
And I just kind of became
his understudy.
And what did you study?
Uh, engineering, same as Perry,
But he was doing his doctorate
in mathematical physics.
Yeah, he's a...
He's a smart man.
Yeah.
It must have been hard
sometimes, though.
What do you mean?
He's not the most...
Compassionate man I've ever met.
I mean, that's just his way.
He's just...
He's just practical.
Practical.
Yeah, sometimes
he's a little too practical.
He's just stressed out.
He just...
We only have so many tests left.
He doesn't want
to come up empty-handed.
You don't want
I was
at the hospital last night,
And she's not getting better,
but she's stable.
There's still time.
[ Click ]
I'll tell you what.
I'll call up the grant committee
in the morning
And see if they can help us out.
Yeah, anything to...
Buy us more time.
[ Sighs ] Yeah.
I'll call them in the morning.
Devin. We need to talk.
Yeah, sure.
[ Crickets chirping ]
You know we're not doing this
for personal reasons, right?
This is about something
much bigger than that...
Much bigger than us.
I know that.
Okay.
It seems like
you got someone in mind.
In fact, I know you do, Devin.
You got to tell me this.
You don't think
I'm committed enough?
No, no,
I think you're plenty committed.
I just want to know why.
Are you doing this for somebody?
Who is it?
Perry.
Tell me. Who is it?
- It's my little sister.
- Oh, God damn it, Devin.
There was a car accident. I...
I tried to stop,
but I-i couldn't.
And now she's...
and now she's dead, okay.
No.
She's unresponsive.
Okay,
so, here's why that's a problem.
It means that everything
we're doing now means nothing
Unless we get the result
that you want.
So we're fighting time.
We're fighting money.
And now we're fighting you.
I-I'm not gonna
do anything to you.
No, no, I don't care.
You don't bring something
personal into this.
You don't make it
a goodwill mission.
Are we clear?
No, Perry, we aren't.
I-I-i can pretend
to move past this,
L-lie to your face
again and again
And say it's out of my mind,
but it's not.
It's never gonna be.
Then why are you wasting
my time?
'Cause this is
the only hope that I have.
When the time comes,
I know that you are gonna do
the right thing.
I'm...
"The right thing"?
Hmm? Where are we gonna
go find a body, huh?
How long is that gonna take?
How easily is that gonna derail
this whole project?
Maybe there's another way.
No, there is no other way.
What we're doing here is
Something that most people
don't want or even understand.
Now... now, the other guys...
They understand that this is
not for us, but you... you...
You're Miles ahead of us, hmm?
Now, tell me
if that sounds productive.
I'm sorry.
But now that you know
why I'm here,
Do you think I'm gonna do
anything to hurt this project?
All this means is
that I have regrets.
And, what, like...
Like, you don't?
You don't have mistakes
that you would want to fix?
Do you?
[ Sniffles ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Breathes deeply ]
I, um...
I've been doing some thinking,
and... You're right.
I'm sorry. I should have
told you about her.
All right.
Uh, there's some things
I want to run by you...
Things I think
we've been missing.
Yeah.
Okay, let's hear it.
[ Footsteps approaching ]
Don't!
Carter. Carter.
[ Door opens ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Carter, you can't just go
through my stuff like that.
What are you doing?
Talked to some people today,
Perry,
Down at the university.
Told me something interesting
about your grant.
What's that?
Nothing.
Get back to work, please.
Carter,
can I speak to you in private?
There is no grant.
It doesn't exist.
That's not what you said.
I said that I have
the finances covered, and I do.
They have a file on you.
Were you even aware?
What's in the file?
Nothing.
Please, get back to work!
No, Perry, I think I have
the right to hear this.
[ Drawer opens ]
[ Drawer closes ]
What's in the file?
It says
that he's done this before,
Or at least you've tried.
Tell him. Tell him.
No?
Okay.
Once, in your second year.
You almost burned down
the science building.
Sent a guy to the hospital.
Then you tried to make it
your dissertation.
And then you blow out the power
in the lab.
He electrocuted two teammates.
They barely made it.
Is that true?
[ Drawer opens ]
I heard it
straight from the source.
It's more than just
your project, Perry.
This is your...
This is your obsession.
- I want to get it done.
- Yeah, I've gathered that.
You'll get it right eventually,
right?
And until then, what?
What, you'll just...
You'll lie to everyone involved.
You lied to me
from the very beginning.
Say it's... it's...
It's legitimate.
It's financed.
It's legal.
You said everything is...
Is okay. It's all right.
"Don't worry.
"Nobody's almost died
working on it.
Don't worry.
Nobody turned me down twice!"
Twice!
Carter. Please.
You know, you know what?
I think...
I think I'm done with this.
What do you mean?
This project is
not for me anymore.
Carter, come on.
Carter, hey. Look.
Fine.
You're... you're...
You're right, you know,
But you can't just leave.
Why not?
This whole thing is insane,
Perry.
This project is so...
So selfish, and you know it.
What else are you?
What do you...?
What do you have?
What have you...
What have you given up for this?
Like, I-i-i thought
you valued our friendship,
but clearly, I was wrong.
We're just the crew.
No.
That's it.
I'm done.
Carter, come on.
I'm done. I quit.
I can't work for a liar.
Get back here!
What you did is...
[ Sighs ]
You're leaving, too?
No.
I don't like being lied to,
either.
Just... I don't have
any other options right now.
I guess I can understand
your situation.
You don't know anything
about my situation.
Don't pretend like you do.
I'm not still here
because I want to be.
I'm still here
because I have to be.
Don't forget that.
Whatever the reason.
[ Buzzer ]
Where's Carter?
He is taking some time off.
I think
it got a bit stressful for him.
Will he be back?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I, uh... I hope so.
The enzyme's done.
Let's power it up.
Let's, uh... let's double-check
it with the system first,
Make sure the deployment
mechanism is all set.
Amps has been on it, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
Uh, every...
Everything checks out.
Okay, well,
we should check it again.
We've made
some significant changes.
Well, all the changes we made
will work.
We should go for a test now.
I don't think
we're ready for the test.
Amps has been working on this
for days.
And we don't want to bleed
any more grant money.
Amps?
Everything should work.
Amps is ready. I'm ready.
We're ready.
Let's get in the lab.
I don't appreciate that.
You don't have to.
Killing susie.
[ Switches clicking ]
Killing Jenny.
Table clear.
Here we go.
[ Electricity hums ]
[ Door opens, closes ]
What the test did was
fry the main connection,
Which caused a surge
in the rest of the machine.
Uh, it's fixable?
It is fixed.
That's all it was.
So we're up and running again.
So we can keep going.
If we're careful.
So, we're careful,
but we keep going.
We try the rabbit again.
No.
No, we need
to check everything first.
I did. I-i-i already checked.
I double-checked,
and I re-checked.
I've been up all night
fixing this machine by myself.
We're checked.
Okay, great.
So let's pull the cables.
No.
We look at it again
and not just the machine.
We look at the math.
We look at the enzymes.
We look at the oxidizers.
We look to make sure
our specimen is ready.
no one is going to get hurt.
I want to see it.
I want to sign off on it.
We don't move on
till I'm convinced.
Something happen
between you two?
Just a disagreement.
[ Device beeps ]
Perry?
Perry!
That mouse... the first time
off the pedestal...
It never moved.
Sorry, what?
You moved the damn mouse,
Perry.
I know you did.
The numbers prove it.
It never would have moved at all
with the system I was using.
- Look, amps...
- No, no, no, no.
Don't you, "look, amps," me.
I am not a kid.
All right, I-i get it.
I was frustrated, and instead
of talking to me about it,
You just... you went ahead,
and you cheated, Perry.
All right, look.
I did not cheat.
This project couldn't afford
to have you freezing up.
A decision had to be made,
and I made the right one.
I am not a machine.
At the end of the day,
it worked.
you moved the mouse.
It didn't walk anywhere.
You moved it, Perry!
I have been basing
hours and hours of work
Upon the pretense
that what we were doing
Made the mouse move and that...
It's... it's...
It's completely false.
Yeah,
but you've got it right now.
And you can do this.
I'm taking some time off.
First Carter, now this.
It's too much.
It's... it's too much, Perry.
[ Sighs ]
[ Knock on door ]
Yeah?
It's time for a test.
Has amps finished
checking everything yet?
Yeah. He's done.
All right.
Um, let me wrap this stuff up
while he does the pre-test,
And then I'll...
actually,
amps is sitting this one out.
It's just you and me.
I see.
Need your help.
All right.
Okay.
Killing Jenny.
Killing susie.
Board is up.
How are the levels?
Susie's at 94. Jenny's at 97.
Let's put the specimen on.
Live.
Clear the table.
Table's clear.
Priming susie.
Priming Jenny.
You ready?
Yeah.
Here we go.
No way.
Killing power.
[ Machine powers down ]
What are you doing?
Working.
I built the machine.
You can't just run it
without me... without asking me!
We moved forward.
You had no right
to move forward!
[ Monitor beeping ]
[ Chuckles ]
Goddamn.
[ Telephone ringing ]
Carter.
Hey, I-i-i know you're mad.
Perry, I -
- you have every right to be,
but, hey, we... we did it.
- What?
- The machine. [ Chuckles ]
The... the machine works.
Oh, my God.
I don't even know what to say.
I-I congratulations.
[ Laughs ]
We're gonna publish,
and I want...
I-I, you know, I need you here.
- What?
- Please.
Perry.
[ Laughs ]
I'm really sorry.
[ Sighs ] I know.
Yeah, okay.
[ Birds chirping ]
See, it wasn't
just cell oxidation
That was fouling us up.
We also needed
the rapid regeneration
In order for it to work.
So what we essentially did was
we gave the system a jump start,
Forcing the rabbit's cells
into a rapid mitosis
And causing them to multiply
at an extremely
accelerated rate, a-and, um...
Uh, and it worked.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, you don't care how it...
It just worked.
Well, it worked.
I didn't get to see it.
Um, so I guess what happens now?
We... we're...
Or, I guess...
I guess we're done, right?
[ Sighs ]
It's... it's alive.
The rabbit...
The rabbit's alive.
I...
I'm just so proud
of everybody here.
Everyone.
I'm so happy Perry called.
It's really good to be back.
[ Laughing ]
[ Breathing deeply ]
This is it.
I know what I have to do next.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Leaving.
No, you can't.
Why not?
There's nothing else to do.
I might as well
just get out of here.
No, we're...
We're not finished.
Well, Perry is, okay?
And ultimately, it's his show.
We got a living subject.
What's left?
Human test subjects.
[ Scoffs ]
Right. Humans.
Yes. M-make this project mean
something.
Make it worthwhile.
- Do you have a body?
- No.
Then stop talking,
and get out of my room, please.
Amps, look. I know you.
You aren't satisfied.
You want the machine
that you designed,
that you built,
That would not exist
without your hard work
To do more than this,
to be more than this.
Perry's gonna publish.
And someday, someone else will
Finish the work
that you started.
Can you honestly tell me
that you are okay with that?
Don't be a stepping stone, amps.
You are better than that.
And I am better than that.
And this project deserves
to go all the way.
Get me a body,
and then we'll talk.
Perry's gonna shut us down.
I will get you a body,
but we need to start work now.
Okay, just...
Just remember, we get...
We get one test per subject,
and you need to listen to me.
I need you to listen to me.
Yes. I will.
Remember,
you and I are on our own now.
Okay.
We're gonna need
a bigger test area,
A stronger current,
and work on the jump system.
We're gonna need
a rapid oxidation system...
Something new. Something better.
Now, I know
what makes the thing tick,
But I don't have
the technical skill you have
to make it happen.
So tell me what you need,
and I will get it for you.
It's only a matter of time
till we're discovered,
so we need to move quickly.
Let's get this done.
[ Drill whirs ]
How's it coming?
It should be just about up.
Okay, great.
Perry and Carter are
pretty deep into writing,
But be careful with the sound.
There's a certain amount
of noise
That comes with construction.
No, I know. Just do your best.
I'm gonna take a glass of water
And some work
in the living room.
If one of them heads
for the garage,
I'm gonna drop it.
You listen for the break.
All right.
All right. Okay.
You're doing great work, amps.
We're almost there.
And, um, to this point,
All the rabbit's vitals are
normal...
Blood pressure,
et cetera, et cetera.
We'll put the data as a...
As an appendix.
Attagirl.
You're up late.
Yeah.
Still writing.
Taking a break?
Just grabbing some things
from the kitchen.
You know...
You're right.
It is on my mind.
The implications of the machine,
what it could become.
Maybe not like you,
but I-i do think about it.
I know.
You gonna get some sleep?
Soon.
[ Metal clanks ]
What was that?
What?
I heard something
in the garage.
Really?
[ Glass breaks ]
Damn it,
will you grab me a towel?
Get it yourself.
Hey... Perry.
Amps.
What are you doing in here?
I was just, you know, uh...
Devin!
Yeah?
What exactly is
going on in here?
- We made it better.
- Excuse me?
You want
to run that by me again?
I got you what you needed.
You have to let me try.
No, you went behind my back.
See, that's it. You're done.
This is my room now.
Testing is over.
Perry, this project needs to...
No, I don't think
you seem to understand.
See, this machine has already
Successfully re-animated
an organism.
It's in the next room right now!
- Yeah, but it can...
- The project is over!
Perry!
Perry.
Perry, stop.
Come on, this isn't right.
You want to push the parameters
of this project exponentially
And... and... and ethically?
I'm telling you
we simply cannot!
No, no, no, no, no.
You will not.
Look, this is possible.
You're just putting limits
on what we can achieve.
You just don't get it.
This project has never been
about human mortality
Or... or self-preservation.
No, but this could be...
Look, what we have discovered
is astounding.
A-and maybe someday, there will
be human implications.
- Someday!
- But if we try
to push it there now,
It will never happen, ever.
Perry.
We might as well
just throw it away.
- Look, you owe me this.
- Your sister is dead!
- No!
- You can't save her!
I'm sorry, but that's life!
You try to bring a body
in this house,
I'll have you arrested.
Aah!
[ Sobbing ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Camera beeps ]
I'm sorry for what
I'm about to do to you all.
I don't have any other choice.
[ Sighs ]
Katie passed two days ago.
If this works,
she's the first... Okay?
It's been an honor
and a privilege
To work with each of you.
Perry, you put together
a hell of a team.
[ Sighs ]
I know you didn't plan
on making it this far, but...
I'm not gonna give you
a choice.
I'm in the bathtub.
Hurry.
[ Footsteps running ]
[ Cries ]
One, two, three.
[ Both grunt ]
Amps, where are you?
- Making changes.
- You know what are you doing?
Get this other strap.
[ Sobbing ]
[ Machine whirring ]
You know something?
You know it's gonna work.
You must have known.
How's it coming, amps?
30 seconds.
You're gonna thank me
when you wake up.
Amps, what should I do?
The electrode panels in
the back of the converter box.
Administering enzyme.
All right.
We're gonna have to go
with rolling power on this one.
Carter, you're gonna
have to count us up.
Ch-charge at 37%.
We've only got
one shot at this.
Amps, are we ready?
42%.
Perry, I don't know.
Yes, you do know.
Think. Are we ready?
71%.
Yes.
No, no, no, no!
I don't...
I've never done this before!
- Listen to me.
- 86%.
This is not a life
on that table.
This is another test.
You got to think through this.
Break down the problem.
Think through the steps.
Charge at 100%. Ready to go.
Drop the power down to 12.5%!
It's ready. It's ready.
God, I hope so.
[ Machine whirring ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
Killing power!
[ Devices beeping ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Let's get him off of here.
- Devin.
- Devin. Devin.
- Can you hear me?
Devin, it worked.
[ Laughing ]
I knew you knew it would work.
We did it.
It works, huh?
- I knew you knew.
- We did it.
- [ Chuckles ]
Devin, come on.
- Say something.
- Devin.
Devin. Hey.
D-Devin?
Perry, what's wrong?
What happened?
Devin, s-say something.
[ Crying ]
Can you say something?
Carter.
No, please, say something.
Say anything.
Carter,
he doesn't remember how to talk.
No! He knows how to talk!
This is a brilliant man!
He remembers how to talk!
Say something.
Devin is gone, Carter.
It's over.
Devin.
Take it all down.
No! [ Sniffles ]
Take it down!
The human brain is
a fragile instrument.
We are all machines.
We run processes.
We recall files that are
stored away in our memory.
We...
We're not immune
to reformatting.
And that's scary.
That's sad...
To know that fact
for certainty.
To stare it right in the face.
Yeah, our memories are
what make us special,
Make us different.
Without them, we're nothing.
The project is over.
We have failed.
I...
I have failed.
[ Birds chirping ]