- (groans)
- (men shouting)
Robb!
(wailing)
- (roars)
- (screams)
(men cheering)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
(screeching)
Season three begins with us
very much heading
in the right direction.
(screeches)
The dragons have got
a bit bigger.
And you're starting to see
what they'll end up becoming.
We're headed to Astapor because we've
got our ships and now we need an army.
Some say the Unsullied are the
greatest soldiers in the world.
The greatest slave
soldiers in the world.
She debates
whether the Unsullied
would truly be behind her
because she's paid them to.
Once I own an army of
slaves, what will I be?
Pyat Pree has sent a warlock
to try and kill me.
And I'm saved by
Ser Barristan Selmy.
The honor is mine, my queen.
Clarke:  He pledges
allegiance to me
because he was head
of the Kingsguard
for my father.
I have been searching for
you, Daenerys Stormborn,
to ask your forgiveness.
I will not fail you again.
Ygritte's taking him
to meet Mance Rayder.
And this is going straight
into enemy territory.
He doesn't rate his chances
of survival particularly high.
Don't look so grim, Jon Snow.
If Mance Rayder likes you,
you'll live another day.
And if he don't...
When Jon first walks into
Mance's camp, he meets Tormund.
What do we want
with a baby crow?
This «baby» killed
Qhorin Halfhand.
Harington:  Mance is
a legendary figure.
He used to be part
of the Night's Watch.
Why do you want to join us?
I saw Craster take
his own baby boy
and leave it in the woods.
I saw what took it.
And why would that make
you desert your brothers?
I want to fight for the side
that fights for the living.
Do you know how long it's going to
take us to get to King's Landing
- walking through fields and forests?
- Yes.
One thing Jaime
is very good at,
he's very good at sniffing
out people's weaknesses.
- Move.
- He wants her to lose it with him
so that he will get
the opportunity
to get out of his chains
and get rid of her.
And then they reach this bridge
and finally
he gets the opportunity.
Ah!
And unbelievable. He goes
from one bad situation
to a horrible situation.
So we have the wonderful
Locke appear.
Let us go, my father will pay
you whatever you want.
Enough to buy me a new head?
Season three starts with Robb really
just wanting to fight someone.
And they get to Harrenhal and,
again, he can't fight anyone.
And worse than that,
the people loyal to him
have been slaughtered
in the most horrific way.
Find her a chamber
that will serve as a cell.
Talisa:
She's your mother.
Robb:  She freed
Jaime Lannister.
The Lannisters robbed
them of their sons.
And she robbed them
of their justice.
When we arrive,
I get the message
that Winterfell,
after being taken by Theon,
has now been
burned to the ground
and it looks like Bran
and Rickon may be dead.
By the time Bolton's bastard got to
Winterfell, the Ironborn were gone.
They massacred everyone and
put the castle to the torch.
And Bran and Rickon
have not been found.
Bran and Rickon
have fled Winterfell
and no one has heard from them.
But there's a brother
and a sister that come.
I'm Jojen Reed.
This is my sister Meera.
We've come a long way
to find you, Brandon.
Fairley:  They realize
he has this power,
but he doesn't know
anything about it.
And we have much farther to go.
So it's about educating him so that he
can actually become what he becomes.
Theon may have taken them back
to the Iron Islands as hostages.
Have you heard anything
from Theon at all?
- What's your name?
- Theon Greyjoy.
What is your name?
Reek.
My name is Reek.
Maisie Williams:  First of
all, they're in the woods
trying to find her family.
Not necessarily home,
just somewhere
where she thinks
her family may be.
And they come across
the Brotherhood.
They don't know who she is.
They don't really want
anything to do with her.
You can finish your meals
before you go.
- You'll free us?
- I give you my word.
Rory McCann:  The Hound had
been drinking too much.
We know he's an angry man
and a bit lost.
I mean, where's
the Hound gonna go?
So I think he was found
drunk under a tree
with not all his wits
about him.
Just as she's this close
from the door,
- the Hound recognizes who she is.
- Girl.
Then tells the rest of
the Brotherhood who she is.
What in seven hells are you
doing with the Stark bitch?
Sansa finds a new friend
in season three. Margaery.
It is my honor
to present my grandmother,
the Lady Olenna
of House Tyrell.
Pretty much as soon
as she's introduced to them,
they talk about Joffrey.
I want you to tell me the truth
about this royal boy,
this Joffrey.
Sansa tells them
what he's really like.
- He's a monster.
- Ah.
That's a pity.
- Tell me what you think of her.
- Who?
- Margaery.
- She's an ideal match.
With the Tyrells beside us,
we'll crush the northerners.
The new relationship
between Margaery and Joffrey,
I think, scares Cersei a lot.
Cersei's really threatened
by Margaery.
She's younger
and she's more beautiful.
She's very smart.
But Cersei sees all that.
She knows she's a game player.
She married a traitor
and known degenerate
like Renly Baratheon
for a reason.
She married Renly Baratheon
because she was told to.
That's what intelligent women
do — what they're told.
This is what these seasons
are becoming about —
is her loss of that one
thing that kept her sane.
Because she believes him — you
know, he's gonna be the next king
and she would reign
through him.
The Lord of Harrenhal will make a
worthy suitor for the Widow Arryn.
For which I am
extremely grateful to you.
You will leave for the Eyrie
soon as possible
and bring Lysa Arryn
into the fold.
Peter Dinklage:  Tywin wants
to secure everything.
And he figured Littlefinger
would be a great person
to go up there and take charge.
Littlefinger: Lady Arryn and I have known
each other since we were children.
She has always been
positively predisposed
toward me.
Tyrion:
But Lord Baelish's absence
would present certain problems.
The royal wedding may end up
being the most expensive
event in living memory.
Not a good time to leave the
crown's finances unattended.
Which is why I'm naming
you new Master of Coin.
Dinklage:  They sort of don't
really recognize Tyrion
as being so instrumental
in saving King's Landing.
The rebels came
for Joffrey's head.
They lost their own,
thanks to Father.
Thanks to Father.
The Unsullied,
who are fundamentally
a slave army,
do exactly as they're told.
When she meets the Unsullied,
she realizes that she will
take the Unsullied
if only to save them.
There's a small amount
of bartering that goes on
until she kind of pulls out
the ace of spades.
I have dragons.
I'll give you one.
When she hands over the dragon,
she swaps the dragon
for the whip,
which means
that she's the master.
So she tells them they need
to kill all of the slavers.
(speaking Valyrian)
Dracarys.
(screaming)
(screeches)
Tormund:
Orell.
Harington:
Orell is a warg
and he can look
through the eyes
of his animal,
which is an eagle.
He reports back that
he's seen dead crows
at the Fist of the First Men.
When we reach
the Fist of the First Men,
we discover that there's
a kind of horrific pattern
of dead horses
that's been made.
And Mance is quick to point out that
this is the work of the white walkers.
Always the artists.
Mance decides
that Jon should go
with the climbing party
over the Wall
for the basic reason
that Jon knows
more about the Wall
than anybody else.
If he's useful, good. If
not, throw him off the Wall.
See if crows can fly.
These men, all these soldiers,
they've been on the road
for God knows how long.
And now suddenly
they have this woman.
Jaime knows what's going to happen.
He knows before it happens.
But then when it does happen,
he, for some reason —
I think it surprises himself —
he can't just stand by,
so he makes up this story.
Her father
is Lord Selwyn Tarth.
Lord Selwyn would pay
his daughter's weight
in sapphires
if she's returned to him.
Coster-Waldau:
So Locke thinks about that
and his greed is stronger
than his lust, I guess.
So he takes it out
on Jaime instead.
(screaming)
Madden:  We get the news
that Robb's grandfather
is dead at Riverrun.
Robb's very much aware
that he needs the army
that his mother's
family command as well.
So they set off
to go to Riverrun
for the funeral
of his grandfather
and to discuss
what happens next.
And when we get there,
Robb meets again the Blackfish
and Edmure, Catelyn's brother.
Edmure has come up with
two Lannister prisoners.
Edmure: Willem Lannister.
Martyn Lannister.
Willem and Martyn Lannister
are 14 years old.
Lord Karstark
takes it upon himself
during the night to slaughter
these two young boys
chained up in a prison cell.
Robb understands
why he's done it,
but as a king
and a just leader,
he can't allow that
to go unpunished.
Rickard Karstark,
I sentence you to die.
(grunts)
When Robb carries out
the sentence on Lord Karstark,
Robb loses half his army.
The Karstarks are gone.
They need more men.
They need help.
He needs to make amends with people
he's betrayed, which is the Freys.
But because of Robb's
breaking of his promise
by marrying Talisa
when he had been promised
to one of
Walder Frey's daughters,
they are very skeptical
about approaching Walder Frey.
And rightly so.
He sends two sons as an envoy.
And Walder Frey has said,
«Yes, we will help you.»
But the sting in the tail
is that Edmure
must marry one
of Walder Frey's daughters.
- Could I see her first?
- You want to count her teeth?
He's disgusted because
everybody in the land
knows that nobody
in any right mind
would want to marry a Frey.
The Brotherhood take her
to see their leader.
His name is Beric Dondarrion.
Williams:  She's not
particularly happy about it,
but they're not hurting us,
so it could be worse.
You know, he's a knight, but
he's with all these guys in rags
and they look like
a bunch of swineherds.
If you mean to murder me, then
bloody well get on with it.
You'll die soon enough,
but it won't be murder.
For some bizarre reason,
they choose a trial by combat.
(grunting)
Williams:  Beric gets a
sword down his shoulder
and topples over
and «dies».
But somehow Beric Dondarrion
is born again
with the help of Thoros.
It's really
pretty spooky stuff.
How many times have you
brought me back?
It's the Lord of Light
that brings you back.
- How many times?
- This makes six.
What are you
going to do with me?
At first light
we'll ride for Riverrun.
Your brother's there now.
What have we here?
Frozen crows?
- We can talk inside.
- Can we?
Harington:  Mormont and a
depleted group of other rangers
make it back
to Craster's Keep alive.
You feed that pig
better than you feed us.
Pig's got value to me.
(woman screams)
- What is it?
- (crying)
It's at this point
the rebellion starts.
(shouting)
I shall have your head.
We have to go now!
I now am a woman on a mission.
I've saved 8,000 slaves
and I've got a thirst for
wanting to save more people.
So we move on to Yunkai.
The Yunkish train bed
slaves, not soldiers.
- We can defeat them.
- But they won't meet us on the field.
Jorah:
They have strong walls.
(speaking Valyrian)
So I then set up camp
and hear the slavers of Yunkai,
and I kind of lay down
the law for them.
You will release
every slave in Yunkai.
Reject this gift,
and I shall show you no mercy.
You are mad.
We are not Astapor or Qarth.
We are Yunkai.
Those who survive, we
shall enslave once more.
Perhaps we'll make
a slave of you as well.
(screeches)
Now get out.
Clarke:  I give them a little bit
of a fright with the dragons,
And then I decide
- that I'm going to kill them.
- (purring)
Harington: Before Jon, Ygritte,
Tormund, and Orell climb the Wall,
Ygritte sort of coerces Jon
into a secret
place she knows...
Ygritte!
...and decides to really test
A) whether he's a crow,
and B) whether
he loves her.
I don't ever want to leave
this cave, Jon Snow.
Harington:  And Jon
does betray his vows.
I think it's at that point that
he falls in love with Ygritte.
It's a rare moment in the story
where we have a purely happy
moment between two characters.
When Jon and the others
are climbing the Wall —
which is 800 feet
of ice —
a part of the Wall breaks off,
leaving Jon dangling
on the end of a rope
as well as Ygritte.
And it's only
right at the last minute
that Jon manages
to save them both.
(horse whinnies)
Finally they get
to Harrenhal, the castle.
Lord Bolton, I give you
the Kingslayer.
We have a dinner
with Roose Bolton.
Roose:  I will allow you
to go to King's Landing
as restitution for the
mistakes my soldiers made.
And you will swear
to tell your father
that I had nothing to do
with your maiming.
- My lady.
- She won't be going with you.
Jaime leaves Harrenhal. He leaves
with a bad taste in his mouth.
I'm leaving her with Locke.
Don't you worry
about your friend.
We'll take good care of her.
But then on the road,
he finds out
that it's only a matter of time
and they're gonna kill her.
And he again surprises himself,
the way he so wants
to just not care.
- (crowd cheering)
- (roars)
But he does and he goes back.
I'm taking her to King's Landing.
Unless you kill me.
Well, let's be on our way.
Spotted a Lannister
raiding party.
- How far?
- Less than a day's ride south.
Time for a lion hunt.
They say: «oh, we're gonna go
and kill some Lannisters
and then we'll take you home.»
- I swear to you, this isn't —
- You're a liar!
They're all distracted getting on
their armor and things like that,
so she sees her opportunity
and she goes for it.
- Anguy, bring her back.
- Come back, girl.
Williams:  Then gets
stopped by the Hound.
(muffled screaming)
Kick all you like, wolf girl.
Won't do you no good.
He sees a chance of using Arya
as a bargaining chip.
Is that the Blackwater?
That's the Red Fork.
I'm taking you to the Twins.
Your uncle is marrying
one of the Frey girls.
Your mother and brother
will be there
and they'll pay me for you.
So a great road trip begins.
Littlefinger comes along
and he says to Sansa
he's got a ship and he could
take her with him.
Please, Lord Baelish, tell me what to do.
Tell me when.
She yet again thinks
she's gonna get out of here.
You must see Highgarden.
I don't think the queen would
let me leave King's Landing.
Margaery wants to marry
Sansa off
to her brother Loras Tyrell...
Once I marry Joffrey,
I'll be queen.
And if you were
to marry Loras...
...which Sansa is over
the moon about.
She's getting married to
a guy that's actually nice.
The Tyrells are plotting
to marry Sansa Stark
to Ser Loras.
We need to find Sansa Stark
a different husband.
He tells Tyrion he's gonna marry
Sansa, which I find hilarious.
Then, kind of within
the same breath,
lets me know that I'll be
marrying Margaery's brother.
Tyrion will do as he's
bid, as will you.
- What do you mean?
- You'll marry Ser Loras.
- I will not.
- Yes, you will.
This arranged marriage to Sansa
doesn't go over very well.
She doesn't like
that news at all.
She wasn't gonna go
on Littlefinger's ship
because she was being
married to Loras.
Now Littlefinger sailed away,
she's getting married
to Tyrion,
who she didn't want
to get married to.
So, am I invited
to your wedding?
Shae is pretty gutted
about this marriage to Tyrion.
Especially now that
she's Sansa's handmaiden.
Listen to me, my lady.
I'm not your lady.
I'm your whore.
Dinklage:
He's vulnerable, Tyrion.
And that's very
frightening to him.
The wedding to Tyrion,
in Sansa's eyes,
it was the worst day
of her life.
He's a Lannister.
She's not gonna trust him.
Joffrey, of course,
takes great glee
in this new relationship
and torments both of them
as he usually does.
Time for the bedding ceremony.
There will be no
bedding ceremony.
There will be if I command it.
Tywin: I'm sure Tyrion did not
mean to threaten the king.
Your uncle is clearly
quite drunk, Your Grace.
Stop.
But your father —
I won't share your bed.
Not until you want me to.
What if I never want you to?
And so my watch begins.
(screeches)
Only one old man
and eight good horses.
Let's carve him up.
We just take the horses and go.
The old man's no threat.
There's a storm coming.
(thunder rumbles)
It's as good a place
to shelter as any.
- I yield.
- Wildlings.
Harington:  Bran and
Rickon and Osha and Hodor
are in the windmill
that is just by where Jon is.
Their paths
just miss each other.
Neither of them know
that they're there.
Cut his throat or he'll tell
the crows we're here.
Harington:  The man, you
know, has to be killed
and Orell suggests that it
should be Jon who does it
to prove that he's one of them.
- Kill him.
- (grunts)
Orell and Tormund
are about to kill Jon
when two direwolves attack.
It's Bran who goes into
his warg mode
and into Summer to attack
the wildlings and save Jon.
- (growling)
- (screams)
- (grunts)
- (groans)
(screeching)
Madden:  When we
arrive at the Freys',
Lord Frey wants to make sure
that this wedding happens
here and now
before we go back to war.
Or so that's what
we're led to believe.
If you think the time
is right, Lord Walder,
by all means, let us bed them.
As the bedding party exits,
the lights dim.
Then, literally,
as the door closes,
the band strike up.
And that is what makes
Catelyn turn around
and think,
«What is going on here ?
Something is about
to happen.»
(playing «Rains of Castamere»)
Arya completely believes
that she's going home.
She's with one of the most
powerful guys she's ever met
and he actually
is trying to help her.
This was our chance
of getting into the wedding
by using the salt pork wagon.
Turn this cart around
and get the hell out of here.
Lord Walder then stops
the proceedings.
Fairley:  Roose Bolton
comes over to the table
and sits beside Catelyn,
and that's when
the enormity of
the situation strikes her.
Robb!
(groans)
This sea of arrows
come at them.
And Walder Frey is basically
enjoying every moment of this.
Just as we're coming in,
everyone was killing each other.
Williams:  She realizes
everything is going wrong
and she doesn't even know why.
So it's time to change the plan.
Plan B.
Get the hell out of there.
It's too late.
McCann:  The Hound,
at the last minute,
manages to just grab her
from behind
and knock her out.
At the same time, Catelyn is
trying to say to her son,
«Get out», but he won't
leave his dying wife.
Mother.
Fairley:  Roose Bolton
walks up to Robb
and whispers something in
his ear and then stabs him.
The Lannisters
send their regards.
- And she just loses it.
- (wailing)
Gleeson:  When Joffrey gets
the news of the Red Wedding,
this is the best day
of his life.
I walk into
the small council chamber
and everyone else sort of knows
what has happened.
I don't.
Killed a few puppies today?
Robb Stark is dead.
Joffrey loves
every second of it.
Command Lord Frey
to send Robb Stark's head.
I'm going to serve it
to Sansa at my wedding feast.
She's no longer
yours to torment.
Everyone is mine to torment,
you little monster.
Tyrion:
Monsters are dangerous.
And just now kings
are dying like flies.
She finds out that her brother
and her mother
have been killed.
- Sansa.
- Turner: It's very unexpected.
All her hopes are dashed,
like, every single time.
She is pretty bitter.
The usurper Robb Stark is dead.
Betrayed by his bannerman.
Gleeson:  Despite his
loss at Blackwater,
the threat of Stannis
is still present.
Davos:  It's from Maester
Aemon of the Night's Watch.
Their Lord Commander is dead.
What he saw beyond the Wall,
it's coming for all of us.
Gleeson:  Stannis appears
to be more determined
in his desire for the throne.
This war of five kings
means nothing.
The true war lies
to the north, my king.
Death marches on the Wall.
Only you can stop him.
Harington:  So Sam and Gilly
head towards the Wall
together to go back
to the Night's Watch.
The Nightfort's closest
to Castle Black.
It's got a secret sally port.
It leads through the Wall
right down into the Nightfort.
- Meera: It's empty.
- Let's find a place to sleep.
So they come across
Bran and Hodor.
Come with us. We'll walk
straight to Castle Black.
Take us north of the Wall.
Why in the world
would you want to go —
I don't want to.
I have to.
Now he comes back
to King's Landing
and, of course,
no one recognizes him.
Step aside, country boy.
He makes it up to Cersei.
And then he sees her.
They just look at each other.
This is really the moment
where he really realizes
that «I'm no longer
the same man.»
She's ecstatic
because she's got
the one person she trusts back.
But he comes in
missing the thing
that makes him
who he is as a man.
They're both a bit like,
«Who are you ?»
A lot happened since they
haven't seen each other.
After Jon escapes,
Ygritte catches up to him.
I have to go home now.
I know you won't hurt me.
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
(grunts)
Jon survives and we find him
right at the end of season three
collapsing off his horse and
being dragged into Castle Black.
Carry him inside.
And we leave him, not knowing
whether he'll be safe or not.
Under the cover of nightfall,
they send my best men
in through a side entrance
to the city of Yunkai
and have them murder
all of the slavers.
And so that then they can
release all the slaves.
When she finds that
they've been successful,
they come back to wait
outside the gates of Yunkai
to see what the fallout
will be.
And then the slaves come out
and the person
they see is Dany,
the woman who's saved them.
- Mhysa!
Clarke:  The word that comes
out of their mouth is «mhysa»,
which means «mother».
And it's this moment
that Dany for the first time
sees what her new dream
is going to be
and she realizes the possibility of
how many more there are to save.
And it's this wonderful moment of
them looking to her as a mother
and her kind of accepting
their love
and becoming a leader.
(screeching)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com