- All right, Slate. Show time.
- You sure you don't wanna
go for a swim?
- Tariq told me to tell you
come back with the gold
or don't come back at all.
- Well, I don't think we gotta
worry about Tariq.
- No one's ever found anything
down there before.
What makes you think
you're any different?
- Well, the Blue hole is a
bottomless pit.
Not even Cousteau can
swim the bottom.
But I can. And he
didn't have these.
- Sonars, guns, and C4.
You're gonna bury yourself
underthe sea floor and silt.
- Well, then I won't have to
deal with Tariq, will I?
You'll have to face him alone
and without the gold.
( heavy breathing )
- Hey, mon, it's getting
cold over here.
- Let's keep going. The
shelf's straight ahead.
( Sonar pinging )
- It's not working.
- All right, let's head down.
- I don't like this at all.
- How much farther?
- I'm gonna look for a spot
to set the charges.
It's where it's buried.
Cortez should be right
underneath it.
( static )
- Okay, come here. Bring
me the charges.
I'll plant a few charges here.
You guys set the perimeter.
I need you goin' off
to the left.
- Let's go.
All right, mon. we are
set over here.
- That's what I like.
( chuckles )
( beeps )
( explosion )
( shouts )
( screams )
( growling )
- Whoa! What the...?
( roaring )
( gunfire )
( screams )
( reggae music plays )
Whoa ♪
Whoa-ho ♪
Como te llamas ♪
I want to know your name
what's your number ♪
Girl, I really, really
wanna get to know ya ♪
Baby girl, I want to
know your name ♪
Sexy lady ♪
Como te llamas ♪
I want to know your name
what's your number ♪
Girl, I really, really
wanna get to know ya ♪
I want to know your name ♪
Sexy lady ♪
I want to feel your body
Close to mine ♪
Romance is in there air so
let's not waste no time ♪
I'm feeling hot, hot, hot ♪
Yes, you blow my mind Baby,
don't stop, stop, stop ♪
Giving me them sweet wine ♪
Como te llamas ♪
I want to know your name
what's your number ♪
Girl, I really, really
wanna get to know ya ♪
I want to know your name ♪
Whoa ♪
Girl the way you move it
drives me crazy ♪
Feel as if I could
touch the sky ♪
The way you shakes your waist,
it hypnotize me ♪
Gimme this wine girl ♪
( chattering )
- Aha!
- This place is so gorgeous.
- What'd I tell you? Just wait.
- Just wait for what?
- Yeah, I may or may not have a
little surprise in store.
But it's perfectly safe.
Trust me.
- Why do I need to be
reassured that it's safe?
- Come on. Can you
just chill out?
Relax and enjoy the view.
Look where we are.
This is amazing. It's gorgeous.
- We are gonna have
so much fun.
- I know. Come on. Let's
get checked in.
- Sarah!
- Hi, Henry. How are you?
- Good, good.
- Good.
- Today is going to be a
beautiful day.
You heading back out to the
barrier reef today?
- Um, it depends.
You available?
I need some samples
for the lab.
- I'm actually takin' a couple
out here in the boat an hour.
Just snorkelin', though.
But I'm free for diving
this afternoon.
One p.m. work?
- One p.m. is perfect.
- Good. See you then.
- Babe, let's go!
- I'm coming.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
So why didn't we spend the week
on the mainland again?
- You didn't like the
Mayan ruins?
- No, I liked it.
It's just seven days of
nonstop hiking is not
my idea of a vacation.
- You helped me plan this trip.
Okay, fine.
You get to choose all the things
we do next time.
- Oh, what makes you so sure
there's gonna be a next time?
We ought to stay here and hang
out with the locals.
- Really? You're hilarious,
you know that?
Are you ready to
snorkel or what?
( fog horn blares )
- Henry, right?
- Rod, yes.
- Hi, I'm Jane.
- Hey, nice to meet you guys.
- Nice to meet you too. I
hope we're not late.
- Not at all.
So you guys ready to go
snorkel at the Blue Hole?
- Yeah, man, yeah. We're
both really excited.
- The Blue Hole?
- Yes, the Blue Hole.
Welcome on board.
- Thanks.
- Yes.
- So who here has gone
snorkeling before?
Not like this, you haven't.
Snorkeling at the
Lighthouse Reef
is unlike snorkeling
anywhere else on earth.
And if you're really daring,
you can swim across
the Blue Hole.
Most people are not.
Now the ride to the reef is
about an hour from here.
So I suggest you just relax
and enjoy the ride.
- What is the Blue Hole?
- It's a huge sinkhole about
three foot five feet across.
And six down.
- And you knew about this?
- You're gonna love it.
You're gonna love it.
- Turn on some music, Jibuti.
( reggae music plays)
- Going to be a lot of fun.
I want to know your name
what's your number? ♪
Girl, I really, really wanna
get to know ya ♪
Baby girl, I want to
know your name ♪
Sexy lady ♪
Como te llamas ♪
I want to know your name-- ♪
- This is insane.
I've never seen
anything like it.
- This hole is huge.
- Is that a shark?
- Just tiger sharks,
then bull sharks.
- Rod?
- I'm just kidding.
( chuckles )
Those are nurse sharks.
They're totally harmless.
- Then what's that spear for?
- Customers who don't pay.
( chuckles )
- Henry! Help!
- Henry!
- Hurry! Come quick!
- Henry, there's a body
in the water!
- Look at that.
- Come here! You're not
gonna believe this!
Come on, come on! Hurry up!
- There's someone over there.
- Here, take these.
Saw a body out there floating.
One guy.
I don't know if he's conscious,
unconscious or what.
- We gotta get him out
of the water.
Start the engine.
There he is.
Give me a hand with this.
- Is he alive?
- He's breathing, barely.
He's got a pulse. It's
kind of weak.
He probably had a concussion,
maybe even the bends.
We probably better get
him to a hospital.
- No, no hospitals.
- We can take him back
to our place.
- Well, shouldn't a professional
come and look at him?
- I know someone we can call.
- Oh. what do you make of that?
- Why them boy take so long?
They should have been
back by now.
Find out what happened.
Slate double-crossed me again.
This time, he must pay
with his life.
- Let's go.
( groans )
- Hey, guys, he's waking up.
- Where am I? Who are you guys?
- We found you out there by the
reef barely breathing.
We gave you CPR.
But wasn't sure if you
were gonna make it
for a second there.
- You gave me CPR?
- You woke up just long enough
to say ''no hospitals''.
So we brought you back
here to this hotel.
I'm Sarah, this is Henry.
He called me from the
boat to meet you.
And this is their place.
They were on the boat with Henry.
Thanks, you guys. I'm Jackson.
Most people just call me Jacks.
- All right, Jacks.
How's the head?
- Drink the local fruit wine,
you'll figure it out.
I think I'll survive.
- So you wanna tell us what
happened out there?
- Uh, not really, no.
- What about this? You wanna
tell us about this?
( grunts )
- Now I am going to ask
you one more time.
Where is Tariq's money?
- I don't know.
( grunts )
Oh, man, you been workin' out.
I actually felt that one.
Ah!
( gunshot )
Hey! Hey!
- Now I'm going to ask
you one more time.
Where is Tariq's money?
- We didn't find anything,
all right?
We went into the jungle. There
was no Mayan gold.
No nothing, just death.
- I tell you what I think.
I think that you found exactly
what you were looking for
and decided to keep it
for yourself.
and kill our men!
You better start making sense.
Then where is it?
- It's at the bottom of
the Blue Hole.
- What the hell are you
talking about?
- I'm talking about
Spanish gold.
( laughter )
- He's talking about Mayan
gold, the gold that
the Governor Cortez stole from
the native people.
No one has found it. No one
knows where it is.
- I know where it is.
- All right, but I warn you.
You try anything, Slate,
anything at all,
I will put a bullet
in your head
and bury you in that
hole myself.
- Okay, I get it, I get it.
I found it snorkeling.
It's amazing what people
leave behind, huh?
- You mean, like the Mayans?
- I dove to the bottom of
the Blue Hole.
- You went to the bottom? what
else did you find?
Hey, look, man.
You don't have to tell us
anything you don't want to.
But I'm sure the police
will find this
all pretty interesting.
- Well, I don't wanna
involve you guys
in anything too dangerous.
But if you really wanna know...
Get me a beer and let's go outside.
( phone rings )
- Yes, boss?
- Any sign of them boys?
- No, boss, but the port here
around the Blue Hole shut
down and are locked.
The Coast Guard in there. They
find a boat missing.
Wreck smashed off the rocks.
Passengers presumed dead.
What else you want me to do?
- I want you to keep looking
until you find them,
or their bodies.
- Yes, boss. Raul, let's go.
- So you're saying you owe this
Tariq guy a lot of money
and you were gonna pay him
off with the gold?
- Oh, forget Tariq.
As far as he knows, I'm
already dead.
That gold's still out there.
Tell you what.
I'm willing to cut you in if
you guys help me find it.
- Aren't you
forgetting something?
Someone out there did
kill those men.
And if it wasn't you, then we
should be worried
about who or what.
- What do you mean, or what?
- I mean, right now we
don't know anything.
But Dr. Jones here has been
setting off charges
in Blue Hole.
So who knows what the hell
he's unearthed?
- What exactly are you saying?
- I'm saying I'm in.
I don't care about
the Spanish gold
or lost treasure.
I just wanna know what's
out there.
- I care about the gold.
- Yes, me too. - Rod?
- Count me in.
Listen, we came out here to
dive that hole anyways.
And now I see more reasons
to go...a lot more.
I say we go for the gold.
- The police will be
patrolling the air
between here and the reef.
- Well, we'll have to go the
long way around.
Half Moon Key, huh?
Help me with the rest of this.
( phone rings )
- Any sign of Edric
and the others?
- No, boss, only Slate.
And he's going out with some
different people.
None of we people.
- That bastard has
double-crossed us
for the last time.
You know what to do!
- Yes, boss, and the
rest of them?
- No witnesses, not one
to tell the tale.
- Yes, boss.
When they curl Half Moon Key,
we're gonna wait for them.
Let's go.
- Rod? A word?
Are we seriously going
through with this?
I mean, I don't wanna die on
some wild goose chase
for some lost treasure.
Did you forget the part
where some gangsters
are trying to kill him?
Or, like she said, there
could be something
out there that's even
worse than them.
Stop acting like you're
in "The Goonies".
( chuckles )
- "The Goonies"?   Listen.
I think that you need
to calm down.
Change your mind and
come with us.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
- No, Rod, I want us to
stay together.
Otherwise, I'm gonna go
back to the hotel
and you can have your little
adventure on your own.
- Listen, I hear you.
I just think it's a little bit
too late for that.
We're already set, loaded up,
and ready to go.
There could be a lot of
gold out there.
- Look, if you go on that dive,
I'm gonna be really upset.
- I'm gonna go.
We'll see you back at
the hotel, okay?
- Is it just me?
The woman doesn't look too
happy with you.
- Yep.
- Don't worry.
She'll be a lot happier when
you bring back the gold, huh?
- That's the plan.
- Raul, here they come!
See them there?
Get ready for the shot!
Now remember, when
they get close,
we'll pull up side of them.
I say hello and then goodbye.
( rumbling )
- Whoa!
- Something out there!
Something big!
( growling )
- Start up the boat, boy!
Start up the boat!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on, boy! - I'm trying!
( gunfire )
( screaming )
- Hurry, boy, hurry!
( gunshots, screaming)
- Hey! You guys see
that up ahead?
There!
- Hey, there's some wreckage
out there!
Check that out, take me to it.
- Just like before.
Another wrecked boat with no
sign of survivors.
Not even any bodies.
- What the hell is goin' on?
- This is the Coast Guard.
Remain where you are!
- Damn!
- Great.
We got visitors.
- Prepare to be boarded.
You people wanna tell me what
the hell you're doing out here?
You got a name?
- Who's asking?
- Cut the bullshit.
I wanna know who you people are
and what you are doing at
the Blue Hole.
- Blue Hole?
- Don't play dumb with me.
That boat of yours had a
registered dive
out at the hole at nine
this morning.
And then there's this.
You fancy yourselves some kind
of treasure hunter?
- Look, you can't keep us here.
We haven't done anything wrong.
- Where do you think you are?
You think this is the U.S.?
I've got two boats destroyed.
Covered in blood.
Maybe you did find something.
And maybe you killed your
friend over it.
- Okay, look. My name's
Jackson Slate.
I was diving the Blue Hole to
see what I could salvage.
The last thing I remember,
there was an earthquake.
When I came to, these
people rescued me.
We decided to come back out
here and investigate.
And that's when we found this.
- Look, we've got a
real problem here
and I think you know damn
well it isn't us.
- In all my years
working these parts,
I have never seen
anything like this.
- Oh, my God!
- Let alone twice in one
goddamned day.
Not even drug runners.
- This wasn't drug runners.
This was bitten off by
something big,
something really big.
- Whatever it is, it's big enough
to tear a dive boat to shreds.
- We need to have an advisory
and tell the people to stay
out of the water.
- We need to go into
that Blue Hole.
Think about it.
This all started after he
went down there.
Maybe he disturbed something.
We need to khow what
we're dealing with
while we can still do
something about it.
- All right, Slate.
Look like you get to go
back and hunt
for your lost
treasure after all.
- Yeah. What about.. .
- Sorry. Property of Belize.
- At least you know
where there's more.
- Any word from Rafa and Raul?
- Nothing yet, big man.
- If they are not back by sundown,
I'll find Jackson Slate myself
and skin him and his friends alive!
( cocks gun )
- So, Jackson, you left
out a few details
when you were talking
to the police.
What do you think really
happened down there?
- Honestly, I think Tariq's
guys blew the charges early
and left me for dead.
But somebody came back and
took care of them.
I'm sure you got a
different theory.
- Yeah. All I know is there's
something out there
destroying boats.
And we just happen to
be on a boat.
- These guys got plenty of
gun power and sonar.
Anything comes at 'em, I'm sure
they'll take care of it.
- Tell me, how did
you get involved
with those low-life
gangsters anyway?
And were you really gonna pay
them back the gold?
- Of course...probably.
- Probably not.
( chuckles )
- Well...
I put my hand
around your waist ♪
Girl, you're
feeling so nice ♪
When I look into your eyes ♪
Girl, you got me hypnotized ♪
There's just something
about you, girl ♪
Whenever I'm around you,
girl ♪
Como te llamas ♪
I want to know your name
What's your number ♪
Girl, I really, really
wanna get to know ya ♪
- What's goin' on, beautiful?
- Hello, sweetheart.
- Hey, what's up, guys?
- Oh, nothin'.
We're just down here in Belize
for training right now.
Just kind of drinkin', relaxin'.
Kickin' with the locals.
I don't know if
you're interested.
But my buddy, he's got a boat
right down the beach.
You wanna join us? - A boat?
- Yeah. Would you like to see it?
- Uh, no, I shouldn't.
- Aw, come on. You can lay out.
And we'll drink tons of
champagne, have some caviar.
- You guys are full of shit.
- You'll never know unless you go.
- All right, yeah.
So what kind of boat is this?
- Sure you boys don't
wanna go for a swim?
- Ha! I don't get paid enough
to do anything this crazy.
- All right.
Well, just keep a lookout,
will you?
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
You afraid of the dark?
- Not of the dark. Just
what's in it.
- I told you what's in it.
Spanish gold.
- Woo-hoo! Yeah, baby.
- Or in some people's opinion,
Mayan gold.
Gotta tell you, it's
not what's in it
that you gotta be afraid of.
When you get down to
about 200 feet,
the pressure's gonna be so bad
it's gonna make your chest
feel like it's gonna explode.
Get down to 300, nitrogen
narcosis kicks in,
you're gonna feel dizzy.
You're gonna think that you might
be seeing some things.
But it's nothing compared to
when you get down to 400 feet.
- You know what, Jacks? why
don't you save it?
- You panic and come up too
fast, you're gonna die.
So just breathe normal
and don't panic.
If any of you guys feel like
you need to back out now,
now's the time to tell me.
( chuckles )
- Jacks, I'm not really one to
back out of things ever.
But I think it'd be a good idea
to keep a man onboard
and keep an eye on things.
Make sure you guys are safe
while you're down there diving.
So I think I'm gonna sit
this one out, huh?
- Yeah, sure.
- Hey, hey!
I'll still get my cut, though,
right?
- Yeah.
- All right. You're a good man.
Good luck, man.
( sonar pings )
- Shelf's right up ahead here.
Get ready to go down.
Is everyone all right?
- Getting deeper now.
( static )
- There's the Cortez in
her final glory.
Okay, you guys follow me,
all right?
Let's go forward.
- Okay, I'll follow you.
- See those?
- These are dinosaur
footprints, I think!
Look at the eggs!
We've got to take one
back to the lab!
- Okay.
I've seen enough. Let's
get outta here.
( screams )
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Relax.
You all right?
Okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
- You guys all right?
You were down there for a
long time, ma'am.
I thought we lost you.
- You nearly did.
- Yeah.
We ran into my old crew down there.
They were torn apart,
trampled or something.
- What else did you guys
see down there?
- We saw footprints, big ones.
- Well, did you see what left them?
- No, but we found this.
- What the hell's that?
- It's what I intend
to find out.
- The advisory is still in effect.
Stay out of the water.
- I better go try to find Jane.
She's probably worried about me.
- I still give you guys a
ride to the mainland
once he opens up the harbor.
- Hey, Jacks.
Wanna come back to the lab with me?
I could use an assistant.
- Uh, sure.
- Great.
- Hey, you still owe me a
refund for that ride, man.
- Hey, I did take you guys out.
You know where to find me.
- Yes, boss? It's me.
I found Slate.
He's with the Marine Biologist.
I'll keep an eye on them.
- I'm not crazy, that's a
big ass egg, right?
- You're not crazy.
But it's time we
should look inside.
( beeping )
- God, what are we lookin' at?
- No, it couldn't be.
This has all the traits of being
some kind of dinosaur!
An ancestor maybe?
I don't know.
- You mean, like the extinct kind?
- Well, not entirely.
I mean, technically
crocodiles are dinosaurs.
Birds too.
- So you're sayin' there's more
of these out there?
- It would seem so.
- And how big do you
think it might be?
- I mean, based on the size
of the footprints
and the fact that it tore
apart two dive boats
like it was nothing, I'd say at
least 40 to 50 feet tall.
But to learn more, we're gonna
have to crack her open.
- Okay. You need some
help with that?
- Just don't break anything. -
Hey, you got any beer?
- Right in the
fridge over there.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- It's your beer.
- I mean, from before.
We would have died down there
had it not been for you.
- You wouldn't have been out
there unless it was for me.
- Well, that's true.
Now I want you to make
yourself useful.
Put this on.
- Do you really think all
this is necessary?
- And these gloves.
You've seen "Alien", right? Can
never be too careful.
- Okay, what do you
want me to do?
- That'd be great.
Now I want you to hold it
just like this.
Nice and straight. Very, very,
very gentle.
Nice and steady.
I'm just gonna chip the top.
- Oh, God, that's awful.
what is that?
- It's hydrogen
sulfide and methane.
A bit pungent, but nothing
you can't handle.
( hisses )
Careful. Not too close.
- Come on, it's eyes are closed.
I'm just gonna--
Whoa! Whoa!
- Oh! Oh!
- Bring me the--
- ( growling )
- The what?
- Right behind you.
It's a sedative.
Right behind you.
- Which one?
- It's the one with
the green top.
- Okay?
- Give me three cc's.
- How much is that?
- Just fill it up. Hurry, hurry!
Come on, Jacks!
- Okay, okay!
- Okay, set it down.
- Okay.
- Grab the forceps. One, two,
three.
- Oh!
- Where is it? Where'd it go?
- I don't know.
- Do you see it?
- Jacks, look in the corner by
the file cabinet!
- Where? Where?
- Oh, my God. Just be careful.
- I got it.
- Careful.
- Careful !
- I got it.
- Oh, my God.
I'll get it.
Open the freezer, Jacks.
Open the freezer!
- Okay.
( panting )
- Oh, my God, that was close.
- See, babe? I'm an
honest soul.
- Yeah, right.
Could be worse, though.
- Couldn't get much better,
though, could it?
It's not that bad, is it?
- What are you doing?
- What, babe? I thought you
came here to party.
- I did. I just need
another Mimosa.
- All right, babe. I'll
be right back.
- Thanks.
( reggae music playing )
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Hey, can we stop
for a second?
- What? What's wrong?
Hey, if you wanna go downstairs
to be more private, we can.
- Look, dude, it's just not
gonna happen, okay?
I have a boyfriend. I think
this party's over.
- Party's gotta end sometime,
doesn't it?
( screams )
- Help! Help!
- Oh, great.
- ( screams )
- I guess I'll go.
- Forget it, man.
( screams )
( shouting, screaming )
( shouting )
- Hey, what's goin' on?
Hey, did you see what happened?
Hey, hey, excuse me. Hey,
can I see these?
Thank you, thank you.
What the--?
- It's coming!
- Go, go, go!
( screams )
- Here. Henry!
Man, I need you to get
me out there!
- Sure. Yo, unchock the
boat real quick!
- See the wreckage out there?
The boat?
Get us out there wide open.
Let's go!
Hey, when we get out there,
man, you keep your eyes peeled.
- Look at that.
- Predator X?
- 50 feet long and 100,000 pounds.
Four times more powerful than
the Tyrannosaurus Rex.
But this one had flippers.
It's not our guy.
- Yeah, our guy didn't have flippers.
( shouting )
( screams )
- Hey, take it easy!
Take it easy!
- I blow this bitch head off.
- Slow down!
- I said don't move.
- I never knew you had the
brains for science, Slate.
( panting )
- Where is my gold?
( gasps )
- It's not what you think,
Tariq.
- What I think?
What I think is you got greedy,
diveman.
You saw that gold
and you thought you could just
cut me out of this deal.
Again!
- It's not like that, okay?
A lot of weird stuff's
been going on.
A lot of people have
been dying lately.
- You're right about that.
Tell me where the gold is.
and I might let your woman
live for a while.
( shrieks )
- It's in the fridge.
- Check it!
Careful. It might be a trick.
( growls )
( screams )
( gunfire )
( shouting, growling )
- Kill it! Shoot it!
Kill it!
Damn you, Slate!
You'll never make it off
this island alive!
( growls )
( screams )
- Go, go.
- Go!
- Do you see her?
Do you see her?
Jane! Jane, Jane?
Oh, my God!
You'll be all right, Jane.
Jane?
Goddamn it!
- Sorry, man, she's gone.
She's gone.
- I'm sorry about your girlfriend.
We should be safe enough
here at the docks.
But we're dealing with something
pretty lethal out there.
- I saw that thing's arms and
head sticking out of the water.
It's a goddamned monster.
So what do we do now?
- I don't know.
Those little ones are like
gremlins from hell, though.
- And they won't stay
little for long.
You're right.
We should have destroyed those
eggs while we had the chance.
- How many of those eggs
were down there?
- Two dozen.
- Oh, my God.
If just one of those things can
do that to a sailboat,
can you imagine what two
dozen are gonna do?
- Yeah, or how long before they
become 200 or 200,000?
- We gotta do something
right here right now.
Or else we're gonna be
dealing with--
- A new apex predator, the top
of the food chain.
And the end of our time
as a species.
- We gotta destroy those eggs.
All right, guys. We're headed
back out to the hole.
Let's go!
- Hey, guys, get ready.
- So how come we never seen
this thing before?
- I think we have.
Nautical tales of sea monsters
are as old as humanity itself.
Who khows what's out there?
I mean, for all we know, a
Poseidon Rex could have
been hibernating forthe
past 400 years
or even the last 400,000.
Maybe nobody ever saw
it and lived.
Like the crew of the Cortez.
- Wait. What did you call it?
- Poseidon Rex,
the 'King of the Ocean'.
Just like the T-Rex was
king of the land.
P-Rex ruled the sea, only
bigger and stronger.
- So you get to name it?
- Perk of the job.
- King of the sea, huh?
We'll see about that.
- Make no mistake.
P-Rex may have been one of the
most fearsome creatures
to ever walk the earth.
Or swim the earth anyway.
- Okay. So how do we
kill this thing?
- Well, even P-Rex is
just an animal.
It bleeds like anything else.
- So we get guns, right?
- Uh, I'm picking up something.
Jacks.
- It's probably just the reef.
It means we're getting close.
- There's something coming up
beneath us!
Something really, really big!
- Look alive on those guns!
- It's coming in fast!
It's almost here.
- Where is it now?
- It's underneath us!
- Full reverse!
- Hold on!
( growls )
- Open fire!
- ( gunfire )
- My God.
- Fire at its head!
( gunfire )
- Amazing.
- I'm out!
- Reload!
- I'm not seeing anything.
- Well, I think we got him.
- I think we just pissed it off.
- There's no way it survived
all that.
- I've got something. I think
it's back!
Oh, my God, Henry!
Henry!
- Spare me!
No!
- No!
( growls )
- Jesus.
- Take us over there!
( roars )
- Guys, that's not
gonna kill it!
- Yeah!
- Yeah! I hit it!
- Great job, Jacks!
- Well done! Good job!
- Yeah, man!
- Whoa!
- Jacks, we're being dragged!
Pull the lever!
- Jacks, get on it!
- It's gonna pull us under!
Pull the lever!
Hold on!
( shrieks )
Oh, God! Oh!
- Let's get back to the dock!
- Oh, that was close.
- Let's get off the water, huh?
- This place looks like
a ghost town.
- Yeah. That tends to
happen when people
see a prehistoric monster come
out of the water.
- They got to get the hell
off the island.
- So you're gonna call in
the cavalry, right?
- We'll bring enough fire power to
send it back to the ice age.
- Cretaceous period, actually.
It, uh--
( sighs )
Never mind. It doesn't matter.
Just don't forget those eggs
are still out there.
- We'll nuke the goddamn
hole if we have to.
- What about us?
- I suggest you people hide.
- Just be careful.
- I think he knows better than
to come after us again.
Okay, guys, let's go.
( roars, screaming )
( shouts )
- Guys, let's get the
hell outta here.
- Don't worry, guys.
This is the one place
we're safe.
I mean, P-rex rules the water,
not the land.
- You sure about that?
- On second thought, maybe
we'd better run.
Definitely run.
- Run! Come on, let's go!
Move, move, move!
Everybody run!
Get out!
- Hey, here!
- Come on, go, go, go.
( roars )
- This is unbelievable.
- Oh, my God!
Upload the footage.
People need to know what's
happening here.
Someone must have signaled
for help.
It should be coming, right?
- I don't know.
I kinda think we're on our own.
We need to get outta here
before that thing comes back.
- And go where?
- At Henry's boat. It's
just on the dock.
- It's 40 miles to the mainland.
You wanna take that chance?
- Guys, there's an old
military base
on the other side of the
island past the town.
We could hide there.
- All right. I'll try
and distract it.
You guys make your way to
the car, okay?
- Good luck.
- Hey!
Hey, over here!
Hey, ugly! Come and get me!
Come on, you old reptile!
( roars )
Go! Go, go, go!
- Okay, come on, come on!
- No keys!
- What?
- Look for keys.
- Check the body!
- Keys, keys.
Got 'em, got 'em!
- Got 'em? Let's go, let's go!
- No. We're not leaving
without Jacks!
No. He'll be back any minute!
Jacks? Jacks?
Jacks, let's go!
- Slate!
- Tariq? You're, uh...
- Alive?
No thanks to you, Slate.
Where is my gold?
- We're goin' to get
it right now.
- Yeah?
Now I get my gold and my revenge.
But before I do,
I want to kill you!
( crunching )
- Get in, let's go, let's go!
Come on, drive!
That was close.
Nice driving for a
marine biologist.
- We just follow this road for
a couple more miles.
- Yeah. I just wanna make
one more stop.
- Where?
- Guess we'll find out.
- What is this place?
- Compound of Tariq's.
- You mean the guy that just
tried to kill us?
- Yep.
- So why would you
take us here?
- Oh, shit.
- That's why.
- Man, now that's more like it.
- I don't think we've seen the
last of that thing.
I don't know about you, but I'm
not much for hiding.
I say we ought to kill that
thing or die trying.
- Oh, we're gonna kill it.
( roars )
- We got company!
- Shoot it!
- Oh, my God, get it!
( gunfire )
( screams )
( tires squeal )
- Everybody out! Let's go!
- Run! We can lose him
in the woods!
( gunfire )
( growling )
- Go, go, go, go!
Go, go!
- Jacks! What the hell
are you doing?
- Do what I ask and go!
- Let's go! We gotta move!
- Careful !
- We're not gonna outrun it!
It's too fast, too big!
Just keep going!
In here! In here! Let's go,
let's go, let's go!
- Come on!
- It's coming.
- Quiet.
- Don't move a muscle.
( growling )
- It's gone.
- How much farther do you
think that base is?
- Not more than a mile or so.
- Come on. Let's keep moving.
Let's go.
( growls )
- How old is this place?
- I don't know. It doesn't matter.
Hopefully, we can get a
signal out from inside
and call for help.
- At the very least, a
place to hide.
- This place should be running
on its own grid.
- Oh, this place gives
me the creeps.
- Well, safer in here than
out there, right?
- I guess.
- So what are we looking for?
- Power.
Jackpot.
- You think you'll get it
up and running?
- We'll see.
- I'll be back. I'm gonna go
check things out.
- Where'd you run off to?
- Found the armory.
- Did you find anything?
- Oh, yeah.
Grenades, rocket launchers,
you name it.
( gasps )
- You did it!
- I'm not sure how
long it'll last.
Let's see if we can
find a radio.
- Great.
- Okay.
- This thing looks ancient.
- It is.
This is Jackson Slate on
the Ambergris Key.
We are alone and we're
in trouble.
Anyone out there, please
respond. Over.
Anyone out there read me? Over.
Anyone out there? Over.
This is Jacks Slate of
Ambergris Key.
We are alone and in trouble.
Anyone out there copy this,
get back. Over.
I gotta assume we're still alone.
Found a two-seater airplane in
the hangar next door.
If no help comes in the morning,
I'll fly that thing outta here.
- What if it comes back before then?
- Well, then we'll give it hell.
Get some rest. I'll keep watch.
- Sure you wanna stay out
here all by yourself?
( chuckles )
( giggles )
- Let me know as soon--
Got it? I don't care
what it takes.
What's goin' on, Private?
- Sir, something's strange.
I received a transmission on an
old military band,
one that hasn't been used
in over 30 years.
- That is strange.
- Actually, that's not even
the strange part.
- Where did it originate from?
- Ambergris Key, the old
military base over there.
- That outpost has been abandoned
for decades.
What did it say?
- Actually, sir, you
won't believe this.
- What the--?
- So how does one get
in the business
of treasure hunting?
- I think getting in is easy.
It's the getting out part
that's hard.
- Oh, I've noticed.
( chuckles )
- And how did you end up
mixed up with a guy
like Tariq anyway?
- Tariq?
I don't think you can say what
I do is exactly legal.
So sometimes you need somebody
that knows
the ins and outs of a country, right?
- And I take it you probably
won't be turning
any of that gold into the local
government or museum?
- Would you?
- Hmm.
- So what about you?
If you're not motivated
by money,
I mean, you're obviously not
motivated by danger.
- Hey, there's plenty of
danger in what I do.
( chuckles )
Jellyfish sting, you know.
- A jellyfish, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, the Immortal Jellyfish,
to be exact.
They live in the Blue Hole.
I've been studying them for
the past three years.
Do you have any idea
what you've done, by the way?
By setting off those explosives,
you've done irreparable damage
to their habitat.
- Hey, slow down, okay?
I think finding a ship
that's been missing
for over 400 years is a
little more important
than some jellyfish.
- Oh, these jellyfish
live forever.
- Forever?
- As in immortal.
They never die.
They may hold the key
to unlocking
the secret of human immortality.
Oh, I was just scratching
the surface of
all the secrets the Blue Hole
may have been hiding.
- So you don't think that thing,
that Poseidon Rex, is
immortal as well, do you?
- I don't really know
at this point.
( radio static )
- What are you doing?
- This place is so old.
I figured they'd have this
stuff laying around.
And I was right.
- What is it?
- A telegraph.
- Morse Code? Who you
trying to reach?
- There.
- The jungle?
- No. It's a U.S. Army base.
- How do you know it's there? -
Trust me. It's there.
- So now what?
- Now we wait.
- Okay. Well, what'd
you tell 'em?
- I told them that a 50-foot
sea monster
was attacking the island,
killing everybody
and that they needed to do
something about it.
- Yeah, I'm sure they're gonna
take that seriously, huh?
- Well, it was worth a shot.
( static )
- Wait a minute.
What's that sound?
- ( beeping ) - Shh!
You're not gonna like it.
They got your message last night.
They have satellite imaging
of the creature
and are tracking it now.
We have to be off the island
in 20 minutes.
- Why? What happens in 20 minutes?
- It's gonna be an all-out
aerial assault.
They're gonna level
the whole thing.
- What are you talking about?
There's still people here!
- What are we gonna do?
- The airplane.
- But it only fits two people.
- Yeah, well, only one of
us is going up.
You guys get down to the pier.
I'll try and distract it.
- One, two, three, four.
- You still have eyes
on the creature?
- Yes, sir.
It's still rampaging the
entire island.
- Bring it up on the monitors, please.
Zoom. Closer.
My God!
- Sir, you won't believe this.
I just received a message from
the civilians at the base.
The ones from last night.
Morse Code.
They're still alive.
- I hope you told them they got
less than 20 minutes
to get out of that area before
I glass the whole damn thing.
- Sir, we have to give them
time to escape.
- I can't let that thing
get off the island.
Let's hope your friends can.
Proceed.
- Come on, give me a hand!
Slide it open.
That's it.
( panting )
- Come on, come on, come on.
- It needs fuel!
Grab the stepladder over there!
Try on top.
Right on top, right up here,
right up here!
Okay!
All right, give me some slack!
All right. Once he gets it in,
just pump, okay?
- Okay, ready? Ready?
- Go, go.
Come on!
Come on! We need more!
- I'm pumping as hard and
fast as I can!
( growls )
- Guys? Guys? It's back!
That's it!
- All right, get out of here!
Get out of here!
- Be careful, Jacks.
- Get off this island!
( growls )
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, get
the bow line!
( roars )
- Come on, you bastard,
follow me.
- Come on, come on, come on!
( growls )
- T minus five minutes
to destination.
- Copy that, Gold Leader.
You are weapons free if you can
make visual contact with the target.
- Go! Light it up, light it up!
( gunfire )
- Keep shooting! Keep shooting!
- The son of a bitch won't die!
- Pilot, please identify yourself.
- Hey, it's Jackson Slate.
Who's this?
- You are ordered to leave
this airspace at once.
- Now listen here!
I'm the one that called the S.O.S.
The goddamned monster's been
attacking the island!
- Come here! Take the wheel !
- Get it, Rod! Get it!
Be careful, Rod!
( roars )
- Whoa!
- You are ordered to
immediately leave the area
before aerial
bombardment commences.
- There's still people
on the island!
The creature's not on
land anymore.
It's in the water.
- Lieutenant, have 'em
paint the target.
- We're tracking your position.
If you continue to paint the
target, we can get a lock.
Do you understand, Mr. Slate?
- I do.
- Gold Leader, the Cessna 22
will paint the target.
Lock onto his transponder signal.
- Affirmative.
( roars )
- Oh!
( screams )
- No!
- Raptor's are nearly in
visual range, sir.
T minus 30 seconds.
( growls )
- Direct hit!
The creature is down!
- Yes!
- I repeat, the creature is down.
- I want a cleanup team in
there immediately.
Good job, good job.
- What about Slate?
( growls )
- Sir, it's back!
- No! No, it's impossible!
- Look!
- Yeah.
( screams )
- Woo!
- Yes! Yes!
( pants )
- Hey, there.
- You're alive.
Jacks.
- How would you like a vacation?
- How about a different island?
- Sounds good to me.
- Aren't we forgetting something?
- The gold?
- No. I mean the eggs.
( rustling )
( growls )