*
(Prisoners murmuring)
Fucking faggot!
(Screaming)
Mother fucker!
Don't ever fucking
touch me!
Fucking kill you!
I'll fucking kill you, Puta!
(Man)
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Smart, Rodriguez.
Real fucking smart.
90 days, man.
Get on in there.
(Slow breathing)
*
I can't do it if you
keep moving, coño.
Coño, shut up.
Testy.
No, mama,
you look fierce.
(Giggling)
*
What did I tell you about
bouncing that ball in here?
Angie, honey, nobody could
pick him up?
No Ma, I told you,
the car's in the shop.
Is this thing straight?
I can't do
that right now.
(Baby giggling)
Hey, yo, E.!
E.!
Is that you?
Yo fellas...
Look what
the cat drug in, kid!
Yeah, oh!
What's up?
(Man)
Watch it, watch it,
stop the traffic!
Look who here!
Woo...
What up, kid?
Michael, puñeta,
no lo toque.
Let me get $20?
What for?
I'm going out.
Okay...
But you're going
to wait for Papi, right?
(Man)
* Ya llego
Enrique llego *
Nah, but my freestyle is like...
* Where are you tonight
my love *
Hold up, hold up,
hold up.
How come
you got so big?
You been eating those
hamburgers.
This man got a big butt, son.
Look at the bun,
look at the bun!
I gotta break out.
Wait, wait, what
the fuck is that, E.?
No, no, hey, your family
right here.
(Man)
He ain't even got a piece
yet and he...
All right, all right,
all right.
(Woman)
Look who decided
to show up.
(Mother)
At, ay dios mio!
Ay dios mio.
My son is home.
Oh, thank the Lord
for bringing you home safe.
Jeanette, can you help
me with a couple of things
In the kitchen please?
Angie... Angie.
I would like to thank God
for bringing Kike home safe.
Okay, Mami.
Vamos niño.
Niño?
(Woman)
Sorry, bro.
You see this shit,
right?
You're lucky Michael's grown
already, huh?
Hey.
Come here, papi.
Man, you're big.
I bet you hitting them
out the park now, right?
Hey, Mr. Rodriguez.
It's a pleasure to
meet you.
Nice to meet you.
(Baby)
Papi!
Hey, who's that...
Come here!
Look at him!
You miss your uncle, right?
Un besito, un besito, muah.
(Woman)
Grandma is coming.
Ma, I'm leaving.
Okay.
Bye, mi amour.
Bye.
You going, Mike?
Where you going?
We're late...
We gotta go
(Door closing)
Coming to the stage,
from the BX.
(Cheering and clapping)
Please welcome, the one,
the only...
Vanessa!
(Cheering and applauding)
It cracks and clicks and the
glass it rips to pieces,
Too sharp.
I sometimes slip between
the creases
I been
building out your weakness.
(Woman)
Wow.
Brow and bone structure bent
to your likeness.
I like this.
Live in the middle with
a piece of mind.
Make like a mirror
and turn me lovely.
Face to face, and say
you love me.
(Woman)
Yes!
(Crowd cheering)
(Woman)
Aw ma, you did your
thing up there.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
Let me talk to you
for a second?
Okay, you have one
second... go.
So I'm saying,
I think you look mad sexy.
You here with somebody?
Yeah.
All right,
that's cool, ma.
I'm kidding.
I'm here with my friends.
Got you, got you.
So what's up?
Let me get at you.
You want my number?
Yeah, I want it.
I want to take
you out.
I could treat
you real good, you know?
Oh, word?
Yeah.
(Whispering)
Trans what?
Transsexual.
Oh, for...
For real?
Hold up, you know,
that's cool, ma.
So, like, it's... it's
gone, right?
No, um...
I still have a thing.
You real freaky
with it?
What?
Like... you suck dick?
Um...
I mean...
No, I'm sayin', like,
you like that?
You suck dick?
You don't even know
my name.
It's Vanessa, right?
(Door closing)
(Man)
What do we got here?
' 95, two years grand
larceny.
'01, a year on arms
possession, resisting arrest.
Last bid's a three
out of five.
Drugs,
possession and selling.
Model prisoner for
the most part
Except a little
hiccup at the end here.
Okay, Rodriguez, you
tell me.
What's different this time?
I ain't going back.
You have to obtain and secure
gainful employment
Or you're
going back up.
Any police contact, you're
Drug test
come back positive,
You're going back.
What am I telling you
this for?
You know all
this shit, right?
Yeah...
I mean, yes.
I don't know
if I believe you.
Do you believe you?
That's what
matters, right?
All right, get out my face
and go get a job.
See you next Tuesday.
Thank you, sir.
Yo, let's go kid,
you taking forever.
Ay mama, y este pajaro?
Ay metamelo alli,
hay asi.
Jalame El pelo, macho!
Mas duro harder,
ay Si, haci es, papi!
Yo, don't forget your
panties.
Dame ese salami, campe...
Faggot!
(Woman)
I just want to know if he
violated.
(Woman)
No, he ain't violate.
So what,
you love him?
I mean, he do be calling me
his wifey and shit, so...
You lying.
I mean, he better.
I let him bust.
In your mouth?
Oh, you nasty ho.
You a ho!
Like you ain't.
How it taste?
I sucked on a pineapple
candy before I did it.
That's how
you get the taste out.
He is still nasty.
So?
(Schoolbell ringing)
No, no, mama.
Where do you think
you're going?
Where are we going?
No Te preocupes.
This is for the Morris Avenue
companies, okay?
Okay.
Thank you, sweetie.
(Man)
Come on, let's go, let's go.
Let's go!
We gotta get these plates out.
Come on we got table
four waiting.
Let's go!
Jesus.
Work, work, work, work,
work, work!
Ah, yes, hey!
Pussy, pussy.
Ow, ow, ow, hey!
Ow, ow!
Pussy, pussy.
Down... ow!
I feel like...
Yes, bitch.
(Playful chattering)
Here you go, papa.
Mmm, baby,
you killing it.
Thank you.
This food is amazing.
(Phone ringing)
Michael...
Do you mind
not doing that at the table?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
I got a surprise for you.
Next week, me and you.
I got tickets
to the game, papa!
You know, at the new stadium.
Look at how close those seats
are next to like, home plate.
Check it out.
What's the matter, you don't
like the baseball no more?
It's okay, I guess.
Just okay, huh?
You wouldn't understand.
Okay, then tell me, Mike.
Talk to me,
make me understand.
You don't like baseball
no more?
Fine, I get that.
What do you like, Michael?
Football?
Basketball?
You like school?
Oh, I love it.
(Angela giggling)
Yeah?
What'd you
learn in class today?
I don't know...
the usual.
Yeah?
You weren't
learning how to cut class
With your little faggoty
little friends?
Enrique!
It ain't like I never
cut class before,
But don't lie to me.
Enrique!
You can't follow me
around, Papi.
Sit down.
I don't go following
you around.
What's up
with your hands, man?
Put your hands
down and talk to me like a man.
I didn't raise you to be
like that.
You didn't raise me!
You can't just come in here
and try to be "Papi" now.
Well, I am your papi, I am!
Dejalo, Kike.
(Phone ringing)
"Creating a vagina
approximately
"Seven centimeters
deep in seven days,
Although it can be
more than this."
I'm sure it will be.
Ooh, this one
is mad pretty, Vee.
Look, you circled this
one here.
It look like a flower
That's one dusty
ass flower.
Hater, ew.
Don't turn the page yet,
I'm looking.
All these is nasty.
No, they not,
they beautiful.
Taste good, too.
Whatever!
Michael ain't never even
felt a pussy before.
Probably ain't
seen one neither.
That true?
Wanna feel mines?
That's so OD...
She gonna cut yo ass!
Get your ass away
from me.
(All laughing)
Sup with old boy from
the club?
Y'all do the nasty yet?
No, bitch.
Y'all so crazy.
He might not want you to
cut your pee-pee off.
That nigga playing
the trade.
You told him?
Yeah.
He plays the trade!
(Girl)
Shut up, Antoine!
He ain't after your ass, so
why you worried about it?
How he gonna want her
After she told
him she got a dick
If he ain't playing
the trade?
Cause she's
a bad bitch!
(All laughing)
(Knocking)
(Woman)
No, Mami, no.
I cannot be bothered this week,
I told you Saturday.
I'm not being
fresca, you know I love you.
(Phone vibrating)
Hello?
Who's this?
I can't believe I'm this
fucking stupid.
You're not stupid.
Hector, no, come on.
How's my little man?
He's good.
So go ahead.
Tell me to go fuck
myself.
Tell me what
a fucking bitch I am
Because I don't know what
a good man I'm losing.
That's not what I was
gonna say.
I will tell you this...
I wish we had more time.
Somebody needs to go there and
stomp that nigga, son!
Entiende?
Yeah, he lives up on
Webster Ave,
Right by my cousin Tina.
Just say the word,
E. Man, okay,
And it's done, we got
you, man, we got you.
You don't have to worry about
shit, entiende?
(Man)
We gonna
fuck him up, E.
I'll handle it.
Oh, shit, this
mother fucker's gonna do
Some Lone Ranger type shit.
Come on, man... talk to this
motherfucker, man.
Hey, you sure, E.?
Yo, I got it.
What the fuck, man?
I don't know, B.
Mira, Mira quein esta alli,
Mira Que chulita!
Ay yi yi...
Tu viste eso?
Her daughter, son?
What are you doing,
Angie?
I'm getting ready
for bed.
Don't you miss me?
Enrique, please not now,
I'm tired.
Yeah, what
you tired from?
Life.
Life, huh?
I thought you were tired
from going
With that new
boyfriend of yours.
What are
you talking about?
I don't got no
boyfriend.
No?
No...
what are you, deaf?
Don't lie to me,
Angie.
I ain't fucking stupid.
Look, I don't expect
anybody to wait three years.
That ain't natural.
I was up north.
You had to do
what you had to do.
But I'm home now.
I don't want to see
no dudes.
I don't
want to smell it.
That's it.
If you want me,
it can only be me.
Okay.
You know
I missed you, Enrique.
You sure?
Of course, stupid.
Hold me.
(Heavy breathing and moaning)
*
(Danny)
Uh-oh, back that shit up.
Enrique mento!
Hey, Mike!
Want to bat?
Come on, Mike!
Yeah... Yeah!
Remember how we used
to do it?
Hey, he's gonna mess up
the whole flow of the game.
Dejalo, dejalo...
Come on.
That's gonna throw
everything off.
Danny, just
throw the ball, dude.
Man, he's gonna take
my spot.
All right.
Remember how we used to do it
in little league, right?
Choke up on the bat,
put your shoulder into it.
Come on, throw him a nice juicy
one so he can smack it!
Yo, what if he hits
a home run?
Yo, just shut up
and throw the ball, B.
Okay.
Ponsela, ponsela!
Come on, Michael!
Esta seria, aqui.
Go, go!
Go, run it out!
Run Michael, run it out,
run it out!
Run!
It's okay, that's okay.
You want to take another
at bat?
No, it's okay.
(Cell phone ringing)
Ma, I'm gonna run,
okay?
Okay, mi Amor.
Where's he going?
I don't know...
with his friends?
(Woman)
You can keep it up.
One, two, three, four,
five, six.
Why you let him play with that
shit for?
Let him be, Enriquito.
He's a little man, why don't you
put a ball in his hand?
Get him out there with
the other kids?
Do me a favor, E.,
Don't worry
about raising my kids.
They have me for that.
Worry about your
own kid.
What's that supposed
to mean, huh?
I'm just saying, be a father to
your own kid, that's all.
Cayense,
cayense la Boca.
Be nice.
Igualito a papi, no?
Callate la Boca!
What you talking about
papi for?
That nigga was never there.
Yeah, E., and how are
you any better?
Stop it, puñeta!
What are you saying to
me right now?
What the fuck, Karina?
I told you not to curse
in front of the fucking kids,
You fucking fuck.
*
You said your mother
was upstairs?
Yeah, but she don't
bother me though.
Why don't you sit down?
Make yourself comfortable,
know what I mean?
You did that?
Yeah.
Why you ain't talking?
I'm talking.
Why don't you come
a little closer
So you can
hear what I'm saying?
Know what I mean?
Damn, you look sexy.
Wait.
What, they ain't real?
Not yet.
What you mean, not yet?
I mean not yet.
They gonna be real soon.
It costs mad guap I just
don't got right now.
Well how much
it cost?
$400 a month.
Ma, I got you, that
ain't nothing.
Just like that?
Yeah.
Just like that.
You got me?
Yeah.
You... you got a candy?
Come here.
What?
What do you mean, "what"?
You see what time
it is?
What you got that shit on
your head for?
Take it off.
Take what off?
I said, take that
shit off!
Pa, papi, stop!
Take it off!
(Angela)
Enrique, no!
My hair!
No!
What?
Pa...
Angie, this shit ends now.
Stop it...
Enrique, no!
Leave it alone, he's not
hurting anybody!
Papi, no, stop,
I'm sorry!
You don't disrespect
this house.
Sit the fuck down,
right now.
Don't do this,
he's not hurting anybody.
Put your fucking hands down.
You're a fucking man, Michael,
You're not a woman!
No, no!
Get your fucking hands...
Why you doing this?
Why are you defending
this shit, huh?
Don't you understand...
this can't happen.
You're supposed
to have my back, Angie.
Kike... Kike!
Stop it...
just stand still.
Papi!
Stop it!
Papi, please stop!
Shh.
Papi!
Stop, stop.
I fucking love you.
I'm not going to let you
do this to yourself.
Be strong, be strong.
There you go.
There you go...
beautiful man.
Viente nueve, trienta.
You got 30 pills
here.
And you got
the testosterone blocker.
Okay?
Otherwise you be growing
a beard with tetas.
You don't want that.
That should take
care of you for the month.
Anything else?
Um...
Oh, you wanna get
pumped... huh?
You got the coins?
Yo, damn,
that needle's big.
I can't believe you
doing this shit.
The price you pay
for beauty.
You want some, too?
I'm just here for moral
support, mama.
You want anything
on top?
No, Papi would kill me.
Okay, just the culo?
Okay.
Here... you can hold me
if you want, mama.
Oh, hell, no.
Try not to move.
Can you pass me
that, please?
This?
Thank you.
What the fuck?
It is the fastest way.
Does it look good?
You gonna
look hot, mamita.
Yo, wait till you see
this place, E.
It's like
an amusement park.
They got like a butcher
shop in there.
They got a club in there.
Yo, they got these like plush
brand new seats, kid.
I don't even know how
they play baseball in there.
It's like a hangout.
What's up, bro?
What the fuck
are the chances, bro?
You should see the way this
nigga walks around
Waving his arms and shit.
That's wild, B, but come on
don't worry about it.
When Angie
was pregnant, right,
She had this...
Um, they did the thing,
you know where...
Sonogram.
Yeah, sonogram.
They told me it was a boy,
I was like wow.
I gave that nigga
my name.
Enrique Michael Rodriguez.
That's my name, son.
Bro, I don't know what
to say, man.
I mean, I hear
you, bro, I hear you.
But the fuck, bro?
What if that's
his life, man, that's him.
That's his life?
That's my life...
That's my boy, you understand?
You know, he took that
from me.
He took
that shit from me.
Yes, Mr. Rodriguez?
Can I use the bathroom?
Come on, Michael, just go.
You don't
have to interrupt.
Oye, papa, ven!
What's up?
Damn.
What happened, huh?
Damn!
Rodriguez?
Does this look
like a beet salad, hmm?
This just came back.
My best salad just came back
looking like that.
Yo, I don't know...
This is unacceptable.
Fix me a new one...
now.
Is there a problem?
All right, where do you
think you're going... Come on...
*
You know, it doesn't
look that bad.
I actually think
it looks kind of cute.
What?
I'm not pretty no more.
You are beautiful.
You hear me?
Why did he have to
come back?
I wish he could
have just stayed up there.
You could have married
Hector.
You're just saying that.
You're just
saying that, okay?
*
You all right, B.?
Huh...
oh, yeah.
I'm shakin', I'm
shaking.
Nah, I'm just
getting started though.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You ain't won nothin'
all day.
Come on...
That's what
I'm talking about, yo.
What's good?
How you doin', can
I get in?
My money good?
Yeah, fuck it.
All right.
Cuanto?
$100. a game, man.
$100.?
Man, roll 'em, man,
roll them dice, dude.
Shaking them down ain't gonna
make no difference.
(Man)
All right, watch me.
Come on six... here
we go, baby, here we go.
Four, five, six...
Cee-lo!
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, that's me,
baby, that's me!
What's up?
Oh, shit.
It's like that?
Oh, hells yeah, it's
like that.
Yo!
Run your pockets.
And I like that watch.
Que Te pasa.
Take it off.
Just chill, all right?
(Man)
Yo, E.!
Who said he could
play, man?
You!
You did that shit, E.!
Yo, money was shitting
in his pants, son.
You did good, E.
*
Stop.
I'm sorry, baby.
I just don't want
you pulling on it hard...
That's all.
So now I'm "baby" now?
You don't like that...
Baby?
It's whatever.
Come on,
don't be like that.
Don't be hitting me, I'll smack
that fat ass of yours.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Stop.
Fresco.
Hold up, hold up.
I do something wrong?
Nah.
I'm saying I want
the whole thing tonight.
Oh.
Wow.
You cool with that?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I don't want to see
shit, a'ight?
You won't see nothing.
Okay.
Damn.
(Gasping)
Can I ask
you something?
What's up?
Well, you know when
we met,
How you said you
were gonna take me out?
Yeah.
Well, how come you don't
take me out?
How come you only
ask me to come to your room?
What, you don't
like coming over here?
No, of course I do.
I'm just saying, like...
How come we
don't we go out?
You know like, to the movies,
or to eat?
Cause that shit
is whack.
I don't think its whack.
Whatever.
*
That's pretty good.
Mm-hmm.
Asi.
Papi, hi!
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Damn.
Excuse me, young man.
May I?
Let me show you how it's done.
*
(Laughing)
I got something
for you.
What, for me?
What is it?
Go ahead, open it.
E., it's beautiful...
You can't afford this.
Baby, Papi got paid...
You like it?
I heard you did a good job
taking care of them
When I was gone.
Yeah.
Hey, you wanna
see something cool?
Watch this.
All right, you see
the guy right there?
Watch this.
Watch him come for
my finger.
Thinks it's food.
Watch, here he go.
Ah, shit!
(Laughing)
You try it.
Come on, Michael, it
don't hurt.
Give me your hand.
Mete Tu mano right there.
Watch that, the water.
Yeah, just like...
Hold it right there.
Wait for him, wait
for him.
Ah!
You see that?
Yeah.
Bites.
Told you.
Hey, um...
And thank you too, for sending
me those pictures...
While I was up north.
I don't know if I thanked
you for that.
You're welcome.
Stop.
Just make sure you don't
ride the clutch too much.
You want to give her a break
every once in a while,
So she can last.
You pay for all this.
Otherwise you'll be back
spending your money.
(Angela)
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(Hector)
Manny, it's okay, papa, I'll
close her out.
You sure?
Yeah, esta bien.
(Radio playing music)
(Dance music on television)
*
Man, them sorry ass cats
can't play no ball.
You catch
the game last night?
Nah, just the lowlights.
Yeah, you didn't
miss much.
(Toilet flushing)
I don't want that shit.
Slap that bitch
right there.
Everything
going all right?
Everything is everything.
You got pay stubs
for me?
Yeah.
Hey, what's up?
Any police contact?
Hey.
Nah, nah.
All right.
Everything's looking on
the up and up.
Stay away
from the bullshit.
You're doing all right.
I'll see you next week.
All right.
(Women giggling)
(Angela)
Enrique?
Yeah, in the bathroom, ma.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Isn't tonight Michael's
school thing?
Yeah, but I didn't think
you were going.
Now you got a hot date.
It's not that big a deal.
You're not embarrassed,
are you?
Of course not.
I just thought you were
working, that's all.
I took off.
For this?
Yeah.
Didn't your father ever teach
you how to tie a tie?
No, he didn't.
You know...
I didn't mean to make you
do anything
You didn't want to do.
I'm chillin' yo.
Oh shit, my dude...
That's a nigga right there.
No gas, no gas!
Oh!
You just
gonna stand there?
You're not gonna say
anything?
Yo, what you want me
to say, yo?
It ain't
like they lying.
You know,
you're fucked up.
Yo.
Yo, you ain't my girl.
You need to chill
the fuck out, a'ight?
Oh, so I'm good enough
for you to fuck
And for me
to suck your dick,
But I'm not your
girl?
Well, then fuck you...
fuck you!
Yo, you good?
I'm good, yo.
Wait, Chris.
Get the fuck off
me, man!
Then go, go!
Get the fuck outta
here, maricon!
So Michael is one of my
favorite students.
Rodriguez.
Sorry?
Michael Rodriguez is
our son.
No, yeah,
I meant Michael Rodriguez.
He's got a knack
for poetry.
He writes
beautifully, you know.
It must be difficult
for you, though.
How so?
Well, I mean with the issues
Michael's having.
You know, the...
His refusal to
use the boy's bathroom,
The eyeliner in class,
et cetera.
You know, all
the things you and I spoke of
A month ago Mrs. Rodriguez...
You made me look like
a fool in there.
It isn't like that,
Kike.
Listen.
No, I have been listening.
You been keeping a lot of
shit from me.
I'm supposed to
find out from his teacher?
How the hell you think that
makes me look, huh?
He's walking
around out here,
Going to the fucking
girl's bathroom?
What the fuck's
that say about me?
I'm sorry, I thought this
was about Michael.
Don't fucking start,
Angie!
You don't need
that shit anyway.
Like, not at all.
Wait, check you out.
Girl, you ain't all
churchgoing goody two shoes.
Look at that frumpy
old church.
It moved, God moved.
Shut up, puta.
Kike, please!
What the fuck.
What the fuck
is this?
What the...
Oh...
Enrique.
That's my son.
No...
not my boy.
Kike, listen.
No.
You didn't notice your
shit was missing?
Don't blame me for
this, E.!
What the fuck were you doing
this whole time?
I was working, pendejo!
Where were you, huh?
Tough guy?
No.
Where were you?
Angie, you don't
get it.
The shit that...
Goes down
behind those walls.
You can't understand.
And here, my son wants
to be like this.
(Music playing from club)
(Woman)
All right!
So we ready to keep
it going?
Let's welcome up to the...
She needs no introduction.
Vanessa from the Boogie Down!
(Cheers and applause)
Show 'em how it's done.
I'm trying something a little
bit different.
I am standing right here.
Tucked in the mess of
my own fear.
Far from fine.
In your eyes I seem to fall
farther and faster
Than you have
time to catch me.
From a boy balanced on
his shoulders
Who can take on the stars.
Where were you from bedtime
to dawn?
Tucking me in,
instead of ducking out.
Where are your arms when
I just need them
To wrap around and hold me?
I am standing right here,
just as you left me.
I am begging
right here for you to see me.
I will try and I will try.
I'll try to be whoever
you need me.
See me.
(Cheering and applauding)
Right there in front of your
fucking boy,
I don't give a shit.
Papa!
Vente.
Ven aca.
Vamanos.
Where we going?
We're going
for a little ride.
(Woman)
Entra.
You can sit down.
Not me, Michael.
Have a seat.
Este es Tu hijo?
Si, ese es...
hagale un hombre.
Mira.
No Te preocupes.
Él no habla español
muy bien.
¿Ah, no habla español?
That's a pity...
(Door opening and closing)
You have
pretty eyes.
Anyone tell you
that?
Shh, shh.
It's okay.
I'm not gonna
hurt you.
Give me that.
Aqui.
Ay.
Ay, that's it, papi,
Mira, asi.
It's okay, papito.
Shh, shh, shh.
Sweet, sweet boy.
Shh...
Shh, shh.
(Crying)
Tate tranquilito,
shh, shh...
(Micheal crying)
*
(Crying)
Where is he?
Kike.
Did you hurt
my baby?
No, I...
You son of
a bitch.
What did you do, where
is he?
Where is he?
I don't know!
You're going to
find him.
As God is my witness,
you are going to find him.
Yes... yes, you!
I'll call the police,
I swear to God.
I swear to God I will throw
you back in that cage
If you don't
bring my baby home.
Baby, how the fuck
am I supposed to know
Where he is?
I don't give a fuck!
I don't give a fuck.
I don't give a fuck,
you will figure it out.
Go, go, go!
Okay, okay.
Fuck, I'm ready to go inside
and get in shape.
I think my baby girl is in
for a treat tonight.
(Man)
Yo, that's the shorty that
wanted me to wifey it up,
But she let the next nigga
hit it.
I was like, "How you want me to
wifey it up"
And you let dude hit?"
Shit, that's why you can't trust
these bitches, man.
(Pete)
Can't trust
niggas, neither, man.
Yo, she even got the name
"Danny" tattooed on her pussy,
But I don't know if it
was for me,
'Cause that
nigga's named Danny, too.
(Laughing)
Nah, that shit ain't
funny, Tico.
A'ight!
Yo, I don't think
Michael's around here.
Yo, just
keep driving man.
Yo, stop the car.
Yo, Pete, let me get
that ratchet...
You all right, B.?
(Club music playing)
Yo, come with me.
You all right?
Where y'all going?
What you want, man?
Yo, just get back
down there.
Yo, what the fuck man?
Just shut the...
Shut the fuck up.
Right there, turn around.
Look at me.
*
Open your legs.
Open your fucking legs!
I got
a wife and kids, man.
Yeah, you got wifey?
Yeah?
Open your fucking legs!
You like to touch wifey?
Huh, huh?
Motherfucker!
E., E.!
Come on, lets go.
Come on, man.
E.!
Huh?
You good, B.?
Yeah.
Come on, man, let's go.
Come on.
Come on, we gotta go,
we gotta go.
(Club music thumping)
(Cell phone vibrating)
Hello?
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
He's at Hector's.
It's not me he's running
away from.
17 years, Kike.
I gave
my life to you.
It was hard, but
I did it.
I put my trust
in you because I knew
You would take care
of us.
But now my baby's
out there.
E., I don't know
what happened to you up there,
But it has nothing to do
with Michael.
The boy loves you.
He needs you.
We need you.
*
(Knocking)
(Door creaking open)
(Manny)
Hold it, hold it.
Right there, right
there.
I just want my family.
Can I talk to him?
Son.
Um...
I know I've made a lot
of mistakes.
I still don't know
what I'm doing, you know.
I never meant to
hurt you.
My son.
My boy.
My baby boy.
My flesh and blood, pa.
But you ain't no baby
no more.
You can make
your own decisions.
We want just want you
back home, son.
Just come back home.
All right?
(Whispering prayer)
*
Get the fuck off!
Get the...
Wait up, wait up!
Michael... Michael!
Michael... Micheal!
Micheal!
*