[WATER HISSING]
[WATER ROARING]
No fish ladders...
I thought they all had
to have fish ladders.
Wonder how they got
around that one.
But they got to have vacuums.
Well, shoot 'em out into
the back of a truck...
[BIRD TWITTERING]
Whoa.
Think that was an oriole.
I didn't know we had those.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Wait here.
[DOOR RATTLES]
[PEACEFUL PIPE MUSIC]
You didn't wait.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Where's Josh?
He took a walk.
The disaster we see is
happening everywhere
at the same time.
The clock is ticking.
It has been ticking
for 150 years now,
since the dawn of
industrialization.
We are a culture hooked
on profit, production,
and perpetual growth,
but at what cost?
The disaster is happening
to our farmlands.
It is happening to our oceans,
our forests, our wildlife.
It is happening to our climate.
How long will it be until
humanity understands
that everything is interconnected?
How long until
multinational corporations
understand that they can't make
a profit off a dead planet?
So let the revolution begin,
all around the globe.
An army of individual citizens
must rise up and take a stand
for the future, for the people,
and for the planet.
[APPLAUSE]
Thank you.
Thank you all for coming out.
And as you know, we have
the filmmaker here tonight,
Jackie Christianson from Eugene.
That was tremendous, amazing work.
Thank you so much for
sharing that with us.
Now if you have any questions,
she's ready to take them
if you've got them.
- Is that right, Jackie?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I just want to
thank you, Jackie,
for that uplifting,
hopeful vision there.
It was really awesome.
I feel like if you bombard people
with too many horrific images,
it just feels like it's too
late or too much to take on.
It fulfills the end-of-world vision.
Well, you're not going
to get anywhere
with those people anyway.
Dena?
Yeah, I mean, end of the world,
what's there really to lose?
But, Jackie, I'm curious...
What you think it is exactly
that we're supposed to do?
Do you have some sort
of big plan or...?
I think this one big plan thinking
leads to a lot of the
problems we're facing.
Part of the idea for
me, is not thinking
there's just one big thing.
I'm not focused on big plans.
I'm focused on small plans.
A lot of small plans.
I think just by us coming together
and sharing our concerns in one...
[JACKHAMMER CLATTERING]
What time are we meeting your guy?
We said 11:00.
11:00.
We're not gonna make it.
The guy didn't really seem
like he had a lot going on.
I could give him a call, though.
No, no.
I don't want to find a
pay phone right now.
Breathe, Josh.
Okay.
We'll be there soon.
All is well.
Got a inboard 5-liter V-8 engine.
Well, it looks really nice.
Yeah. It's a great boat.
- Kind of hate to get rid of her.
- I'm sure.
Lot of good skiing,
I can tell you that.
Yeah.
But, you know, time for a change.
Both kids off to college...
lot of good skiing though.
May I use your bathroom?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Through the garage
there, up the stairs.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
I'm a nurse. He works
at a supermarket.
Ah. What one?
You definitely want those
brake lights working.
All right, we're good.
All right.
Well, we've always wanted a boat.
Can't believe this is
happening, right, honey?
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
No, not hungry.
Are we almost there?
We must be in Wyoming by now,
coming up on the Dakotas.
I don't know. Half an hour, maybe.
He's pretty out there.
I thought you said he lived close.
He does.
This is close.
We've already gone like this.
Are we going like this?
You can tell me, if we are.
It's close for here, okay?
This isn't Connecticut.
- It's not?
- No.
Shit, I must've got off
on the wrong train.
What is that?
Deer.
You're stopping?
It's half in the road.
It's warm.
What does that mean?
It's a doe.
She's pregnant.
The baby's alive in there.
Oh, my God.
[GRAVEL RUSTLING]
[CHUCKLES]
Where'd you get this thing?
Medford.
[LAUGHING] Medford.
- Party barge.
- Yeah.
You must be D.
You're the infamous H.
Nice to meet you.
At your service.
Night Moves?
Slick.
We could've had Gone
Fishin' or Wet Dream,
but those sounded kind of lame.
There was Makin'
Waves, Reel Wild...
Get it? Reel, two Es.
Pretty awesome.
Jamaican Me Crazy,
Gone With the Wind,
looked at all those.
All right. So what do you think?
Size-wise, is this gonna work?
Uh-huh.
You got a key?
Yeah.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS OUT]
[SNIFFLES]
Good. Good space.
We'll take all of this out.
Yeah.
How much this set you back anyway?
It wasn't cheap.
I bet.
You paid cash, right?
No, I gave the guy my
credit card number
and then told him to check out my
webpage, and then I posted it on Facebook
so everyone else could see it too.
Cash,
the poor people's money.
So it looks all right?
Oh, yeah.
She'll do.
It's a shame.
It's not a bad ship here.
It's got years left in her
if you treated her right.
If I was keeping her,
I'd say there are some
easy repairs to do.
But, uh, I guess we don't give
a shit about longevity, do we?
Nope.
[GRUNTING]
Good to see you, brother.
Yeah, you, too, Harmon.
It's been a while.
Well, you never come around.
Well, neither do you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um...
Why don't you just park
your rig over there, okay?
Yeah.
And then let's head
back inside, all right?
'Cause there's narcs
everywhere out here,
and don't trust the
raccoons at all!
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Hot off the presses.
Cary Taylor.
Looks like I've gained a
few pounds, but, whatever.
Cary Taylor. Really?
Cary Taylor.
Fucking idiot.
Tomorrow this is who
we are, all right?
No exceptions.
Joseph Macca, 10-30-81.
Here.
I'll call you Joey.
You always looked
like a Joey to me.
These look really good, man.
Nice work.
I'm Edward, just so you know.
You can just call me Ed.
Ed.
Ed McMahon, Ed Sullivan.
Joe... McCarthy.
[GIGGLES]
You see the new golf
course on the way in?
Is that what that was?
No, we just saw dump trucks.
Yep.
Just the latest outpost
of the Portland empire.
And taxidermy,
gourmet food,
$8 coffee...
Sounds pretty cool.
Yeah, fuck cool.
Keep your fucking cool to yourself.
You know how many golf courses
there are in Bend already?
- No.
- Guess.
I don't know.
Guess.
5.
15.
29.
It's the high plains desert.
Where's the water?
Right?
Absolute bullshit.
Okay.
So how's everything else going?
Are we on schedule?
[SIGHS]
Mm...
Yeah, real close.
Close? What do you mean close?
We could use another couple
hundred pounds of fertilizer.
[SPUTTERS]
Sorry, I thought you said that
you had it all under control.
I mean, it's not that easy.
I can't go in that often.
And I have to work.
Right?
Those greens don't mow
themselves, you know?
So how much... how
much do you have?
Mm, 1,000 pounds, give or take.
And how much do we need?
500 pounds would be nice.
500 pounds?
Look, we can go with what we have.
I mean...
it's probably all right.
God knows that dam
wants to come down.
There is a serious tonnage of water
just pushing up against her walls.
Everything in the world is telling
her to give up and let go.
But still, I mean,
we should just help her
all we can. Right?
So what... what are you
saying that we do?
Let's go to the feed store
in the morning, that's all.
They're not gonna
sell us that much.
There's just one way to find out.
No, anything over 10 pounds
sends up major red
flags for these guys.
- That's not necessarily true.
- It is true.
We should've known
about this earlier.
Yeah, one second, let me just...
Okay, no, if that's
what we got to do.
Yeah.
All right, we'll go
out in the morning.
Then we'll come back here
and stuff the turkey.
'Kay?
We'll put in Sunday.
We'll move into
position Sunday night.
Monday morning, we'll all go to
work like nothing happened, okay?
[METAL CLINKING]
He knows what he's talking about?
Yeah.
Yeah, he was trained by the best,
the United States Marine Corps.
You trust him?
Definitely.
All right. I'm going to bed.
You think she's all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, she's done some shit.
She's good.
She did that thing in Eugene
with you... the cell towers?
Yeah. Yeah.
She bankrolled that.
That's what I heard.
What do you mean,
that's what you heard?
Well, you told me
that, you dumb-ass.
That's good. You're paranoid.
Healthier that way in the long run.
She paid for it.
Mm.
How much was that boat?
10 grand.
Rich daddy.
I don't see why she has
to be here, though.
She's done plenty already.
It's part of the deal.
I don't see why she
just doesn't go home.
We can take her down to the
train station tomorrow morning.
Mm-mm.
This isn't the same
as those other shows, my friend.
This is on a different level.
You know that.
You think I don't know that?
- No, you know.
- Okay.
You definitely know.
This is gonna be big.
Yeah, it's got to be big.
If people are going to
start thinking anyway...
Killing all the salmon
just so you can run
your fucking iPod every
second of your life.
And that's what's gonna happen.
People are gonna start thinking.
They have to.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SIGHS]
- You ever see Randy anymore?
- Mm.
No, not for a while.
He was squatting in Eagle
Creek, last I heard.
Slipping back out into the wild.
- Lucky man.
- Hmm.
I thought it opened earlier.
I'm sorry.
It won't take that much longer.
- Don't worry.
- I'm not worried.
- All right.
- No, we got to eat.
It gives Dena a chance
to do her homework.
[CHUCKLES]
I've got it.
How are your eggs?
They look dry.
I like them this way.
You should have some.
Mm, no.
I only eat oatmeal in the morning.
Girl, you need protein.
It makes your brain fire better.
Believe me. You should
have some eggs.
My brain fires just fine,
mister. Oats are the best.
- They're a perfect food.
- Okay, Okay.
So what are you gonna say
if he asks why you want it?
For the broccoli.
For all the goddamn broccoli
that needs its nitrogen.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried about it.
Harmon.
Hey, man. How you doing?
Keeping my nose clean, you know.
Glad to hear it.
Well, you have a good day, brother.
- You too.
- Take it easy.
- Yep.
- See you around.
The hell was that?
I thought you said you don't
know anybody around here?
I barely know him.
How do you barely know him?
We served time together.
What?
I thought you said you
didn't have any priors.
What the hell is your deal?
When were you gonna tell us that?
Calm down.
It's so long ago,
it doesn't really count.
It's gone, expunged.
Your friend is really
something here,
Mr. Ed... or is it Harmon?
Things are kind of getting
mixed up already,
and we're, what, an hour in?
You think your record is gone?
You think anything is
ever gone anymore?
You need to join
this century, dude,
and realize that your
record is not just sitting
in some filing cabinet somewhere.
They don't just burn it.
Nothing is ever gone anymore.
You need to know that.
Just take it easy, because
it's not that big a deal.
It is a big deal.
I think we all should know
what we're dealing with here.
Oh, could you please shut up?
- Okay.
All right.
Now remember, just
be as forgettable
as possible, all right?
The cameras are on the
edges of the store,
so stay to the middle aisle
as much as possible.
Keep your hat on, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, hey, remember,
ten acres, okay?
You got ten acres of land.
Hey, I'm looking for
your larger bags?
Your 50-pound bags?
Oh, they're outside,
out that door and over in the shed.
Cool, thanks.
When she was in... in Manila,
she shared a room with ten sisters,
and she gets here.
She looks at the house,
and she says, "The
house is too small."
All right, hasta luego,
all right, Goose?
All right. Have a good day.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
I'm looking for ammonium
nitrate fertilizer.
Do you have that?
Did you look around?
A little.
Yeah?
Nope, we don't have it.
None at all?
Well, you can... you can
ask in the front office.
Where's that?
In the trailer.
Thanks.
[KNOCKING]
Can I help you?
Yeah, I think so.
Looking to get some fertilizer.
Sure, you know what
you're looking for?
Yeah, the ammonium nitrate.
Hope you've got it.
How much you need?
500 pounds.
What are you growing with that,
if you don't mind my asking?
Oh, beets, carrots, onions,
parsnips, broccoli.
I wonder if you've tried
our new sodium fertilizer?
It's good stuff by all reports,
fast uptake, just like ammonium.
Yeah, I think I'll probably
stick with what we're used to.
- Thank you, though.
- All right.
How much you say you need?
500 pounds.
And how many acres you covering?
Ten.
All right.
I need your signature, your ID...
Coming up.
Yep, no problem.
And your Social Security card.
I don't think I have that.
I don't usually carry
that around with me.
Well, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna need to see
your Social Security card
before I sell you ammonium
nitrate, you understand?
I could tell you the
number, no problem.
No, I'm gonna need to see it...
controlled substance and all.
Okay. All right.
Well, let me... let me
go check in my truck.
I'll be right back.
What's up?
He wants a Social Security card.
What?
Bullshit.
Complete and utter bullshit.
Just a power trip.
He's making shit up.
Who carries around their
Social Security card?
That's what I said, but I told
him I'd check in the car.
All right, let's just go. Come on.
We'll find it someplace else.
No, no, no, no.
- Just split you mean?
- Yeah.
What, you don't think so?
I'm just thinking
that's the easiest way
to get remembered out here, right?
You probably ought to go
back in there, I'd say.
No, no, no, no.
Just go back in, tell him
you left your card at home.
See what happens.
Worst case is, he
doesn't make the sale,
but you can't just leave
him hanging, right?
Go on.
[DOOR RATTLES]
Yeah, I don't have that with me.
I don't carry that
around on me usually.
Well, that's inconvenient.
Yeah, it is.
I don't even really
know where it is,
but I really do need that load.
So I don't know if there's
something we can work out,
or some way to get around this.
Well, you could go home,
take a look, come back later.
We're open till 5:00.
Yeah.
We're up near Pine Hollow,
so I wouldn't be able to
get back for another week.
Well, I wish I could help.
Well, how much can I get
today without the card?
None.
I can't leave you some
collateral or something?
I'm afraid not.
Look, sir, the winter went
extra long this year,
so we're already late getting
that stuff on the ground,
and the broccoli
really needs it now,
or it's not gonna be ready in time.
Well, I'm real sorry.
The forage production is
a big deal for us too.
We've got a 120 milk cows that
need that grass and clover.
Look, you come back here with
the proper identification.
I'm sure we can work something out.
But until then, I can't help you.
I'm sorry. That's just how it is.
You'd sell it to me if I
looked like these guys.
I know these guys.
Lucky you don't look like us.
[MEN CHUCKLING]
All right, look, sir.
If you want to, you can call my uncle.
Nature's Harvest is our name.
We grow carrots, onions,
beets, parsnips, broccoli,
and we have 120 milk cows
that supply for Wilber Dairy.
You probably drink our milk.
I do drink the milk
if it's on sale.
[FLY BUZZING]
[MACHINERY CLATTERING]
[GRUNTS]
[HEAVY MACHINERY RUMBLING]
[WATER HISSING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CHIMES TINTINNABULATING]
[GIGGLES SOFTLY]
[MOANING]
[GRUNTS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING AND BUZZING]
You want to go around
and grab this?
Sure.
- Got that?
- Yeah.
So, uh.
I'm thinking we'll put
in upstream a ways.
Closest place is Lake of the Woods,
not too many spectators
this time of year.
Yep. How far upstream?
Uh, the boat launch is
six or seven clicks
from the reservoir.
We'll put the boat down first,
then take the truck further
down the mountain.
All right, that sounds good.
You good with this?
Yeah. I'm good.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES WHINING]
Easy.
Heavy load.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[AGGRESSIVE ROCK MUSIC]
You want to just follow me?
Wait, I thought you said
no one would be here?
This is nothing.
You should see it in the on-season.
All right.
Come on. Follow me.
[KIDS CHATTERING]
You're almost right
dead in the middle,
just a little below the very
center of the price range.
Let's see if you are on your
way to Miami for six nights.
Is she right?
You got it!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
You're going to Miami!
I've been walking
for, like, 11 miles.
I can't go any more.
My ankles are breaking.
We'll be fast.
Let's find a safe place to
park the trailer, all right?
And careful where you park.
The lot has cameras now, okay?
Got it.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Now what should we do?
That's a big guy.
Should I shoot that?
Bam!
That guy has a broken arm.
That guy has arms.
Let's shoot his arms!
Boom, Boom.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
[JET SKIS THRUMMING AND WHINING]
Which way are you going back?
Uh, 26, across the mountain.
It's out of the way, but
there's more traffic.
We can blend in.
When we split up, we
shouldn't talk on the phone.
Yeah, no way.
Yeah, no contact. No contact.
- No contact.
- Yeah.
- Howdy.
- Oh, shit.
How are you guys doing today?
Not bad.
Beautiful day.
Don't mind me. I'm just
out walking around.
Got to keep walking all the time.
My legs are killing me.
Nerves are messed up.
You don't want to hear about it.
Anyway, awesome spot you found.
Yep.
Yeah, they fixed it up real nice.
Oh, yeah, I used to come
here back in the '80s.
[CHUCKLES]
Back in the '80s...
man, those were wild times...
wild times.
Take care.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
How deep is this lake anyway?
Uh, 200 feet this time of year.
What kind of fish are in it?
Cutthroat trout, mainly.
It's all I've ever seen.
That's an oily fish.
Good omega-3 fatty acids in trout,
good for the heart.
Good for depression too, they say.
All I know is, they're fun to catch.
What makes them fun?
They like to fight,
they like to jump.
Sometimes they break free,
and I respect that in a fish.
I've never fished.
No, never? Not once?
- Nope.
- Not one time?
Nope.
Mm.
Saw a lot of paintings of
fish when I was a kid.
Those were our family vacations,
just looking at paintings
of places we'd rather be.
Someday you'll fish.
No.
I'm not fishing now.
In 2048, the oceans
are gonna be empty.
Yeah? Who says?
Science.
Science? Maybe science is wrong.
No.
29% of edible fish
have gone down by 90%.
More people are moving
to the coastlines,
means more pollution, more waste.
Situation is getting
"geometically" worse.
It'll all go fast in the end.
Once the marine biodiversity
goes, everything goes with it.
You know a lot.
The one good class
I took in college.
Really? That's it?
I hate to hear that.
I wasn't there very long.
Just a bunch of poseurs
shooting up for four years
before they took their
media jobs in New York.
It was a joke. I couldn't
wait to get out of there.
You should go fishing some
time before it's all gone.
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
[GRUNTS]
[CRACK]
[CLICKING]
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[CAR BEEPING]
[WHISPERS] That's not a good spot.
[WHISPERS] No.
[CAR BEEPING]
Yeah, I got a flat.
Yeah, well you know,
I'm gonna need your help.
Yeah, yeah, I got...
no, I got... yeah, this...
yeah, it's right here.
Yes, I do have a jack.
[METAL CLATTERING]
Babe, I wish you could see this.
Yeah.
I'm looking pretty manly right now.
Okay, car is in the air.
- How far am I going with this?
- [WHISPERS] Hey.
- Can you stop it?
- Okay.
Not a great idea.
[GRUNTS]
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
Oh!
[METAL CLATTERS]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
[BEEPING STOPS]
[METAL CLATTERING]
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[PANTING]
Hey, we're good.
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
[TENSE AMBIENT MUSIC]
[ALL PANTING]
[ALL GASPING]
[ENGINE GRINDING]
Shit.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Okay. Okay.
[PANTING]
Whew.
[EXPLOSION BOOMS]
[CHUCKLES]
[RUMBLING]
[SIGHS]
[HITCH THUDS]
Later, brother.
See you, D!
[SIRENS WAILING]
Okay.
We just got to get home,
show up for work tomorrow morning,
just get back to normal, okay?
Hey, are you listening to me?
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Shit.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Put your seat belt on.
[SEAT BELT CLICKS]
Good evening, I'm Sergeant Snook
with the Talent Police Department.
We're just checking
the area right now,
identifying everybody
coming through.
I need to see your license.
Yeah, of course.
How are you guys doing tonight?
Oh, we're doing good.
Good. How about your passenger?
I need to see some ID for you.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Joseph, would you mind stepping
out of the vehicle for me?
I'd just like to talk
to you over here.
Yeah.
Why don't you lift
up this tarp here?
I need to see what's
underneath there.
Can you lift that up for me?
Yeah.
How about the box?
Could you slide the box over here?
Do you mind if I
take a look inside?
Do you mind if I look inside?
No.
That's just, like, um, a CSA box.
It's, like, community
supported agriculture
for home delivery, just vegetables.
Okay, Joseph.
You didn't see anything
coming through, did you,
that looked out of
the ordinary to you?
- No.
- No, okay.
Here's your guys' IDs back.
- Thanks, and have a good night.
- Okay.
Good evening.
Hi.
I'm Sergeant Snook with the
Talent Police Department.
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
[SHIVERING]
[LAUGHTER]
You wouldn't have the
organization skills
to pull off something like that.
You don't have good
interrogation skills.
Well, clearly, these people have
some organizational skills.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
I didn't know you were back already.
Oh, yeah, yeah. I got in late.
Nothing local on there, you know.
Unless you want to see what's
happening in Beverly Hills
every five seconds of
the day, then cool.
But if you want to
see what's happening
in your own river, sorry.
What's going on?
Somebody blew up the Green
Peter Dam last night.
Big story, national news.
And this guy was downriver,
sleeping on the bank.
Now they can't find him.
I am never going camping again,
well, unless I'm uphill.
God, what a bummer.
Can you imagine that?
It's like, "Dude, quit snoring.
"Wait a minute.
"There's an entire
lake coming for us.
- Holy shit!"
- That's so funny, Dylan.
You have, like, no feelings at all.
Oh, I'm sorry that my sympathy's
with the water on this one.
Wow, okay. Now you're insane.
No, come on.
Like, of course, if something
happened to that guy,
that's awful.
I hope they find him. I do.
I'm just saying...
someone's got to start
somewhere, you know?
Seriously.
What, Sean, you don't agree?
No, they're idiots, that's all.
Yeah, but you don't
think they had a point?
Yeah, sure, they had a fine point.
But one dam? Who cares?
That river has ten dams on it.
The grid is everywhere.
You need to take down, like,
12 dams to make a difference, 100.
Doesn't do anything.
And, what, you want a nuke plant?
Because that's your only other
option when you get down to it.
No, no. I'm just saying I
want everyone to use less.
I mean, is that so much to ask?
I mean, it's something, you know?
Yeah, it's a statement, right.
I'm not interested in statements.
I'm interested in results.
Seriously, you don't
call that results?
No, I call that theater.
All right, well,
what's your solution?
Look out the window.
It's a lot slower, but it
makes a lot more sense to me.
You have a good time?
Oh.
It was Portland.
I looks like you had a good time.
I'm just... I'm tired.
Where'd you stay?
I stayed at this friend's house.
The guy just moved to town.
Come on, you two,
we start mass today.
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING AND ENGINE REVVING]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[FAN HUMMING]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[FAN WINDS DOWN]
[DOORS SLAMMING]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
Oh, no!
Almost lost it.
There we go.
Okay, that's good.
Whoa.
I feel something.
Look at that!
Whoa!
Mom, look at my aura!
Beautiful. Okay.
I want to try that!
Okay, give me a second.
Yeah, that means he's spiritual.
Hey, Felix!
No, your aura level just went down,
- Let go, let go.
- Ow!
Hey, Josh.
You want me to read your aura?
- Oh?
- It works.
Okay.
- Have you seen this thing?
- Hey, Corser.
- What is it?
- It's my aura reader.
Oh, I've seen it. It's all black.
- Yeah, okay.
- Sorry.
Now it's time to see who
you people really are.
[GROANS]
Hey, Josh.
Hey, Corser.
What's up, man?
Not much. You?
Well, I burned my cheese license.
- I heard about that.
- Well...
Yeah.
Was there any fallout?
- Not a peep.
- Hmm.
I know the F.D.A knows, by now...
but I haven't heard a word.
So what do you think will happen?
[SIGHS]
No idea.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Shit.
- Uh, could...
- Oh.
Hello?
It's me.
Hey.
What's up?
Have you talked to Dena?
No.
No, I thought we weren't
talking right now.
Yeah, well that's
what I thought too,
but she's been calling me a lot.
Why is she calling you?
I don't know, but she is.
And she doesn't seem like
she's doing so good.
Okay, but no one should be talking.
We... we shouldn't even
be talking right now.
Yep, I know,
but it's happening.
So what do you mean,
she's not doing so good?
You read the news?
Yeah.
She's upset.
Yeah, well, me too.
He'll turn up.
You watch.
Well, you don't think she would,
like, do anything stupid, do you?
I don't know. That's
why I'm calling you.
Okay, so...
So maybe I should go talk to her.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Yeah.
What, you don't think I should?
I don't know. I don't know
how it is between you two.
If you think it would help, you
should definitely talk to her.
If not, I don't know.
I just wanted you to know.
That's all.
She isn't doing that great.
Okay.
So how... how about you, though?
Are you... are you okay?
I'm okay.
Sure.
[LINE CLICKS]
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
Good night.
[LIGHTS CLICK]
Hi.
I thought we were gonna
stay away for a while.
Yeah, I just wanted to check in.
Come on in.
Harmon called you, didn't he?
Yeah. We talked for a second.
He said that you were worried.
That's all.
Worried.
Yeah.
Do you want to talk about it?
What am I supposed to say?
Have you seen the website?
What website?
Of course you haven't seen it.
Why would you care?
I don't know what website
you're talking about.
The one for the missing camper.
No.
You should see it.
All of his friends are posting,
his wife, his kids, his mother.
I can't believe this.
Okay, look.
It's not what anyone wanted,
but the guy is probably fine.
We don't know anything.
You said no one would get hurt.
But they did.
We don't know that, but...
but it's natural for
you to feel so upset.
There's nothing natural about this.
We could have done
this in the winter
when no one would be there.
What did you think
was gonna happen?
Wow.
[SNIFFLES]
So...
so what are you gonna do?
What do you mean?
I mean, are you going
to do anything?
Or are you going to be
able to get through this
and keep on going?
Is that why you're here?
Do you mean, am I
gonna call the cops?
Am I gonna go visit
the Halter family
and tell them what really happened?
I don't really know, so
just leave me alone.
Hey, Dena.
Let me go.
You're hurting me.
Sorry.
I bet the salmon did it.
Like, suicide salmon,
they, like, organized,
got arms from the sturgeon
or something, you know?
Did you hear about those
artichokes at Trillium?
They're so good, man.
They're amazing.
They had some on
samples for last week.
Yeah, yeah, I heard about that.
I heard they were better
than last year's.
That's for sure.
[DOORS RATTLING]
[FOOTSTEPS THUDDING]
We don't open until 10:00.
I'll be... I'll be five minutes... less.
If I make an exception for you...
I can't hear you.
I have to make an
exception for everyone.
Okay, I'll be two minutes, okay?
I'll be two minutes.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
[METAL CLATTERING]
Bye.
Later, man.
You talk to Dena again?
Yeah.
And what's happening?
She's taking it hard.
Yeah, well, join the club.
Yeah, well, there's
hard, and there's hard.
So...
is she talking?
It's just a matter of time.
One person.
Okay?
That's all it takes.
Yeah.
So?
I don't know.
Something's got to happen.
Oh, you got ideas?
Nope, but jail don't
sound too good to me.
The time for this...
try life plus 300 years.
Shit.
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
[CAT YOWLS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
[MUSIC FADES]
[BIRDS TWITTERING]
[TEAPOT WHISTLING]
Hey.
[BIRDS TWITTERING]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING
AND ENGINE REVVING]
[GOAT BLEATING]
Hi, Josh.
Hey. How's it going?
Good.
Hey, Josh.
Okay, let's go.
Come on, guys. Come on.
- Hey, come on.
- Come on.
- Scout, let's go.
- Scout.
Scout, let's go.
- Hey.
- Scout.
Here.
Hey, Josh, can I talk
to you for a second?
Now?
Yeah, now would be good.
[SIGHS]
What's up?
Now, I don't know exactly
what's going on.
What you do is your own business,
but people are talking.
You know that?
Who's talking?
You know, just tell me.
Tell me who's talking.
Dena and Anne talked last night.
And what did she say?
I don't know.
She didn't have to say anything.
Anne knows her too well.
Anne's not stupid.
And who else is Dena talking to?
That's not the point.
Now, I don't know
anything, all right?
All right.
I don't know what happened.
I don't ever have to know,
but I can't be an
accomplice to this.
You're not. You don't
even know anything.
You're not getting it,
Josh. We live here.
That means I'm abetting.
My whole family's abetting you.
Don't you get it, man?
We could lose everything.
Okay.
This is not gonna blow over, man.
Do your thing, whatever
you have to do,
but don't take us down, all right?
[SIGHS]
You know how long it took
for us to make this?
[COINS CLANGING]
[LOW MUTTERING]
[UPBEAT FOLK MUSIC]
Hey, Josh.
Josh.
Yeah.
Oh, hey.
What's going on?
I hear you're taking off.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
for a little while, At least.
Right away?
Yeah.
Are you, um...
are you gonna go up to Portland?
'Cause I think I'm gonna be
going up there soon actually.
Oh, no.
I'm heading east, so...
- Oh, bummer.
- Sorry.
Well, it's a good time to
be getting out, anyways.
Why? What do you mean?
Did you hear about Corser?
Well, yeah.
The Feds knocked on his door
and took away his computers.
Why?
Burning the license, they said.
But Corser says that's bullshit,
that they're on to something.
It's out of this world, right?
So what did he do?
He gave them the computers.
You know, this is not the
food inspectors, man.
He's not gonna mess
with these guys.
Surprise, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll meet up with you in a second.
God, it's like, "Go away," right?
So have you talked to Dena lately?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
- I haven't seen her in a while.
- Yeah.
I heard she was kind
of down or something.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Mm-hmm. That's what Sarah said.
Mm-hmm.
I just... I thought you
would know something.
I don't.
Okay, well...
if you talk to her,
tell her to give me a call, okay?
Okay.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER]
[BOISTEROUS FOLK MUSIC]
Good night.
That was amazing.
Thank you.
Hope you don't get
in trouble for this.
No, Audrey's cool.
This play just takes it out of me.
I feel much better.
Good. I'm glad.
You should really
treat yourself too.
Oh, it's just hives or
a rash or something,
whenever I'm stressed.
Well, try to take care of yourself.
If anything happens this
weekend, give me a call.
See you.
[PEACEFUL PIPE MUSIC]
[REGISTER DINGS]
[GASPS]
What the fuck, Josh?
What are you doing here?
Get out, Josh. Go home.
I just wanted to make
sure that you're okay.
Because I've been,
personally,
not so good.
And if I'm not good,
and you're not good, then...
- No, I'm fine.
- No, no, no, I just...
I just think it's important
that we know what we feel.
Yeah, yeah, I get it. I got it.
Whoa!
Good, okay, now stay
off the fucking phone.
Stay off the goddamn computer.
Don't open your mouth at all.
Go somewhere else.
Get out of town if you have to.
[GRUNTS]
Ow!
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
[STEAM HISSING]
[SHRIEKS]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[GAGGING]
[STEAM HISSING]
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]
Yes, I went to see her last night.
And, yeah, there was
kind of like...
like an accident, and...
Are you talking about D?
You're telling me D isn't
in the picture anymore?
Is that it? She... Did
she quit on this?
Yeah.
Yeah, she quit.
Don't tell me anything.
I don't want to know.
Yeah, but, I mean, it was an
accident, though. I mean, she...
I know. I know man.
Just calm down. I know.
She quit by accident. Okay.
I don't know.
Like, I was thinking, maybe, like,
you and I could go somewhere,
like, kind of quiet,
like just out in the middle
of nowhere or something.
I got a lot of stuff.
And I could come and get you.
I can come and get you now.
I don't know where you are.
You got to get real lost now.
You got to get real
lost and stay lost.
Okay.
That's it.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
[LINE CLICKS]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[UPBEAT CLASSIC ROCK MUSIC]
♪ All the nasty weather ♪
♪ And something part of you ♪
♪ I'll be part of you and me ♪
You need any help?
No. No, I'm good.
Okay.
No, actually...
Actually I'm here about that job.
Oh, okay, cool.
- Hey, Tim!
- Hmm?
This guy's here about the job.
Oh, great.
- Hi, there.
- Hey.
Why don't you come to
the front desk with me.
We'll have you fill
an application, okay?
Okay.
Do you have any retail experience?
Yeah.
Great, great.
You from around here?
Yeah.
And do you have a car?
Mm-hmm.
Great.
Well, here you go.
If you want to just fill that out
and tell me when you're done,
I'll fill in the parts I need to fill out,
and we'll just take
it from there, okay?
- Okay.
- Great.
[RELAXED POP MUSIC]
[MELANCHOLY AMBIENT MUSIC]