[TOOL WHIRRING]
Excuse me. I'm looking
for Glenn Hunter.
Excuse me. I'm looking for Glenn...
You must be Dad's latest stray.
Can I come aboard?
Uh, Owen Powers.
Donna, Glenn's daughter.
Him and my brother Joe
will be back any minute.
Is there anything you need me
to help you with while I wait?
Jonas.
All this stuff needs to be stowed
before we set out tomorrow.
Jonas will show you what's what.
All right, yeah, you got it.
Yeah, I'm on it. I'm on it.
Hey. Owen.
- Welcome to The Black Drum.
- OWEN: Thanks.
- She always that friendly?
- Rumor has it
her blood runs colder than
the Bering Sea itself.
Generally prefers
family to outsiders.
Considers us a necessary evil.
You got any tips for me on
how to get on her good side?
Not sure she has one.
- That's all right. I like a good challenge.
- Good luck with that.
Come on, let me show you around.
What do you make of
the new deckhand?
Been here five minutes,
done more than you.
Nicest thing you've ever said about a
new hire. Trying to get in his pants?
Don't start, will you? I hired him
because he's highly motivated.
Let me guess, alimony, child support,
witness protection program? Ex-con?
Knock it off. I've gone over the
claim with the metal detector,
but I want eyes on it down there, just
to be sure. Can you handle that?
Seems like a little midnight
prospecting's now in order.
Get off me.
DONNA: Why are we so far north?
JOE: I know how to navigate.
DONNA: From what I remember,
cave is south of here.
JOE: All right, all right.
GPS marks the spot.
[SIGHS]
- What's with the excitement on this claim?
- Virgin claim.
Full of rich gold sediment
from the glacial melt.
State is auctioning
it off tomorrow.
- Rights to work it could be worth millions.
- OWEN: Nice.
- Who says you're diving?
- I'm not gonna be the boat bitch, okay?
Any of you know how to run the
smart end of the dive equipment?
- No, I don't.
- No problem.
Heads, I dive. Tails, you dive.
Fine. Flip it.
Would you look at that? Oh,
my goodness, what is that?
Let me ask you one question.
- That guitar, can you play it?
- Ha-ha-ha.
Or is that just a chick prop?
Ha-ha-ha.
- You'll see.
- Okay. All right, all right.
Chick prop, it's done
me pretty well, so.
- You certified, newbie?
- I'm willing to learn.
Not tonight. It's your lucky day.
No problem.
Sit back and watch, John Cougar.
[CREATURE ROARING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
Help! Help! Help!
- Help!
- OWEN: I got you, I got you.
- DONNA: You okay? You okay?
- Jonas is dead.
Jonas is dead.
Joe, that's not funny. Stop joking.
I'm not joking. Something got him.
I think it was a shark.
DONNA: I see a fin.
Owen, Owen, weigh
the anchor. Go. Go.
Here, come on, Joe. Get up.
Get up. Guys, hold on.
Good. Get in. Get in, guys.
Hold on tight. Unh!
JOE: It's still behind us.
It's following us.
[CREATURE SNARLS]
[SIGHS]
I'm glad you're okay.
I wish the same could
be said for Jonas.
You know, after the auction,
I'll get ahold of Jeb Stuart
and we'll go out there
and search for Jonas.
We find that shark, we'll kill it.
I think we should keep
it to ourselves for now.
[SCOFFS]
I'm for breaking rules
but I draw the line
when it comes to covering
up someone's death.
- We're not covering anything up.
- Keep this on the low before the auction.
We'll be screwed.
How come all of a sudden
I'm the voice of morality?
Just delay saying anything until
after the auction. We'll find Jonas.
No one's gonna be looking.
We're his only family.
All the more reason not to treat
him like yesterday's garbage.
- What if somebody finds his body?
- It's a risk we'll take.
- I'm not okay with it.
- It's an accident.
- It's not like we murdered him.
- He died on our watch!
Okay, fine. Family vote.
Why even bother?
You two share a brain.
All right, calm down. It's
terrible what happened.
But come on, Joe. Donna's right.
I'll keep my mouth shut,
but I don't have to like it.
I guess anyone who isn't a part
of this family is disposable.
That's the only reason
you're still around.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey. So has anyone notified
the authorities yet?
Not yet.
I'd appreciate it if you don't say
anything until after the auction.
I don't wanna create a panic
among the other dredgers.
We'll find Jonas.
Yeah. Yeah, whatever
you feel is right.
Claim 42.
Wow.
What's this little baby worth?
Two thousand dollars.
Live for the gold.
Die for the gold.
[ALARM BUZZING]
[SCATTING]
[GASPS]
Oh...
They've moved up the food chain.
Do I have 85,000?
I have 85,000.
Eighty-five thousand is the new bid.
Eighty-five thousand, going once.
GLENN: When we start the bidding,
we'll use an anonymous bidder,
so not to reveal our interests.
JOE:
Dad has a sixth sense for the gold.
If people knew what
Claim 42 was worth,
it'd drive the price
right through the roof.
Hope we're not after the
same claim today, Glenn.
Because if I gotta compete
against you, I'll win.
I'm sure you'll get
everything you deserve.
I always do.
I'll win.
Who's that?
Resident bloodsucker.
Currently up for bid, claim
number 42, opening at $35,000.
I have 35,000.
Do I have 40? Forty thousand.
Do I have 45,000?
Forty-five. Do I have 50?
Fifty thousand.
Do I have 55? Fifty-five thousand.
Do I have 60? Sixty thousand.
Do I have 70? Seventy thousand?
I have 70,000. Do I have 75,000?
Seventy-five thousand?
Seventy-five thousand.
That's it, our ceiling.
I can't go any more.
- Seventy-five thousand, going once.
- Sell it. Take the bid.
- Seventy-five thousand, going twice.
- Eighty thousand.
AUCTIONEER: I have $80,000.
Do I have 85?
That's it, we're out.
- AUCTIONEER: Do I have 85,000?
- Dad, I can get us another 10,000.
- You save your money, kid.
- No, Dad.
AUCTIONEER: Do I have 85?
Do I have 85,000?
I have 85,000. Eighty-five
thousand is the new bid.
Eighty-five thousand, going once.
- Eighty-five thousand, going twice.
- One hundred thousand.
AUCTIONEER:
One hundred thousand dollars.
Son of a bitch.
Son of bitch knew what
claim we were after.
- I did everything to keep him in the dark.
- New guy sold us out.
The new guy? He doesn't
know enough to sell us out.
So, uh, what now?
- We dredge.
- Without a claim?
I did homework in case this didn't go
our way. After a claim is auctioned,
there's a seven-day holding period
before Thorne takes ownership,
which gives us a whole
week to dredge out gold.
That's my girl. Any gold out of Thorne's
pockets makes this twice as sweet.
Good job.
DONNA: Thanks, Dad. Let's go.
I've made arrangements with Jeb Stuart.
I'll be going outwith him. Do a good job.
The least we can do for Jonas.
We don't have time for this.
I know you're under pressure, but
work together. Work as a family.
Hey, Mr. Hunter. With all this commotion,
I haven't had a chance to thank you
for the opportunity to work
on your boat this season.
Three things to remember
to do a good job:
Common sense, an affinity to
bust your ass, and teamwork.
If you're anything like your
old man, you'll do a good job.
That's all I can hope for, sir.
MEGAN:
I'm looking for The Black Drum.
- Found it.
- I'm sorry to be the one to tell you this,
but I discovered the body
of one of your divers
washed up on the
beach this morning.
Who are you?
I'm Megan Arthur, professor of
marine biology from the U of A.
- How do you know it was our diver?
- Diver's suit had your logo on it.
Where's the body?
- In my lab.
- Excuse me?
If I let the coroner collect the body
before I could properly research it,
his report would
claim shark attack.
I believe this to be something
other than a shark.
Something other?
I've been tracking
this unknown predator
responsible for this large amount of
seals washing up along the coast.
- Is that unusual?
- It is.
Only because they've
been exsanguinated.
- What the hell does that mean?
- Entirely drained of blood.
And your diver is the first
human casualty I'm aware of.
Damn sea vampires.
Sea vampires?
Don't listen to him.
They're a local legend.
And the key word being "legend."
Care to enlighten me?
I think I remember a little
bit from elementary school.
It dates back to the 1800s, started by
a wounded fisherman who washed ashore.
Locals say before he died
the fisherman claimed to have
been attacked by a sea vampire.
A fanged, blood-drinking beast
born beyond the icy depths.
I need to learn as much as
I can about this legend.
Tourist center should have
all the info you need.
All right. You can call me tomorrow
about collecting the body.
Be careful out there.
Up until now, the great white shark
was the worst thing known to man.
Whatever this is, it's even worse.
Oh! Hey, here we go. Oh!
Get ready to bring it around!
Got her on the line, she's
a big son of a bitch.
- Hang on.
- You hang on.
All right, back it down.
Back it down.
I'm not driving a cab.
Take it easy, Jeb.
- Watch the line, man, watch it.
- Let it out!
I am letting it out.
Back down a little bit.
I am backing it down.
I'm coming around.
Oh! Whoa! Hey! Hey! Hey!
The safety belt snapped! Glenn!
Glenn, get down here! Glenn! Glenn!
Glenn! Glenn! Glenn!
Glenn! I need a...
Glenn, help! Aah!
Jeb!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
- I'm okay.
- Come on.
Jeb!
[SHRIEKS]
[SHRIEKING AND HISSING]
Son of a bitch.
- I'm not as petty as you are.
- Petty?
You're so irresponsible. I can
handle this better than you...
Is there any compromise
that can be made
so we can stop wasting
time, get back out there?
- This is family business.
- Stay out of it.
- Heads, I dredge. Tails, you dredge.
- Why do you always get to pick first?
Give me that. Two heads?
My own brother.
You know me. I'll do
anything to better the odds.
I'm in charge, not by default,
by your dumb-assery.
JOE: Yeah, whatever.
Dig with the excavator.
Everything from here goes
into the grizzly over here,
tracks into the sluice box, and this is
where we separate the gold and dirt.
Move! We got a distress call
from Dad! He's in trouble!
Let's take the launch.
It's at the ramp. Let's go.
- Go. Let's go. Joe, are you driving?
- Yeah.
DONNA: Go, Joe, drive.
DONNA:
Did he say anything? What happened?
JOE: I don't know. He sounded
like he was in trouble.
DONNA: Go, go, go! Come on.
OWEN: Let me get it untied.
Come on, Joe. Faster. Come on, Joe.
He's right there.
- JOE: Hold on, let's get closer.
- OWEN: Looks like it's drifting.
JOE: Do you see him?
- Oh, my God.
- Go, go, go.
- Dad!
- Go, go.
- Dad, Dad, Dad.
- Is he alive? Here.
- Check his pulse. Check his pulse.
- All right. Donna, is he okay?
- What you got? You got it? Is he alive?
- DONNA: What do I do?
- Gotta get him to a hospital.
- Get him to the hospital.
- Hurry up! Hurry up! Come on!
- Dad, wake up!
DONNA: Joe, come on! Drive faster!
Hold on, Daddy.
- Right there. Get him up. Get him up.
- Go, go, go. Come on, Joe. Unh.
- Get the back. I'm gonna put him there.
- OWEN: Got it. All right.
- Joe, you're driving.
- OWEN: Just set him right here.
- Put him right here. Put him...
- Got him?
I got him. I got him. Right here.
I got him. Pull him back.
- DONNA: Drive. Get in the driver's seat.
- OWEN: Ready?
DONNA:
Get in the driver's seat. Go.
- OWEN: Push.
- DONNA: Unh!
Come on, Dad. Come on, wake up.
We did good on the gold today, Dad.
Gosh, Dad. He's awake.
- Where are we?
- It's okay.
- Where are we? What happened?
- You're gonna be okay.
- Glenn, it's okay. It's okay.
- Unh. Ow!
- What the hell's wrong with him?
- Oh, no! No!
OWEN:
Hold him down. Hold on. Come on.
- No, Dad. Dad. You'll hurt him! Don't!
- OWEN: Stop. Come on, Glenn.
He's freaking out. He's freaking out. Hold
him down. Hold him down. Hold him still.
- JOE: What's going on?
- I don't know what's going on with him.
- What's going on?
- OWEN: Come on.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
Whoa.
- What the hell is that thing?
- OWEN: Get down. Get down.
[SCREAMING]
Come here. Donna. Get back here.
[CREATURE & DONNA SHRIEKING]
Oh, no, no, no. Go to the front.
Out the door. Out the door!
Go, go. Get out.
Get out. Get out.
What the hell is that?
I swear to God, I don't...
What the hell is that thing? Joe.
- Let's kill it!
- What are you doing? No!
- I gotta save my dad!
- No! Not yet! Listen to me!
Do you wanna die? You wanna die?
If you open that door,
that's what's gonna happen.
- What if he's still alive?
- He's dead.
Now that we know there's
more than one out there,
you and me and every other dredger
on the Bering Sea's at risk.
All I'm saying is we gotta figure out what in
the hell that thing is before you kill it.
- No.
- Aah! Aah!
How in the hell are we
supposed to do that, huh?
Joe.
[SOBBING]
MEGAN: I've been tracking
this unknown predator
responsible for this large amount of
seals washing up along the coast.
DONNA: Is that unusual?
MEGAN: Only because they've
been exsanguinated.
Entirely drained of blood.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- JOE: This is Joe from The Black Drum.
It's your lucky day. We
caught you a sea vampire.
How did it get in there?
- DONNA: Came out of our father.
- JOE: Be careful.
DONNA: Be careful. Watch.
[CREATURE SNARLING]
Told you.
Thanks. I was afraid it might
use a host to sire offspring.
You did whatever you could to
warn us. We didn't wanna listen.
- How fast was the incubation?
- I don't know. A couple of hours.
- Incredible.
- Sorry if we don't share your enthusiasm.
I didn't mean to sound insensitive.
Look, whatever. I need you to figure out
whatever it is that makes this thing tick,
- so that no one else winds up dying.
- You want me to find a way to kill them?
Yeah. Smart cookie, professor.
I am sorry about your father.
I am a scientist, not an exterminator.
I have a profound reverence for all life.
This is an undiscovered species.
- It needs to be researched.
- That's why we brought you here.
Research it, pull its guts
out, but we're gonna kill it.
Yeah, we are.
- We'll need to get it to my lab.
- How are we gonna do that?
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
- Here.
- All right, you ready?
- Yeah.
- All right, on three.
One, two.
Let's go. Let's do this.
[CREATURE SQUEALING]
- MEGAN: Great.
- Sure it's gonna work?
Yes. There's enough chloroform in there
to take down a pack of elephants.
- It's right there.
- Right there.
- Oh, my gosh. Give me that thing.
- Be my guest.
Wait, we gotta wait till
the gas clears out.
Here, I'm gonna open up the door
just a little bit and let it out. Ready?
- MEGAN: All right, move.
- It's right there. Get it, ready?
OWEN: Get it... Come...
[CREATURE SQUEALING AND HISSING]
- Get it.
- I got it. Got it.
- OWEN: Put it in.
- Guys, it's awake. It's coming.
- Close it. Close it. Close it.
- We got it.
Oh...
- MEGAN: Oh, my gosh.
[CREATURE SQUEALING]
So I would appreciate it if
one of you could come with me
while I conduct my examination.
I'll go. It would give you two
time to be with your dad.
I'm going to need him too.
- What?
- Excuse me?
Well, it gestated inside him. His body
will tell me things I need to know.
You want me to do this
right, don't you?
- You're not touching my father.
- Let me examine him.
Otherwise, one of us could
become the next incubator.
No. I said no.
If I can learn one single thing about
this sea vampire that will help us,
he wouldn't have died for nothing.
We'll take care of Dad and
then we'll warn the others.
Fine.
They're not even gonna
believe us anyway.
JOE: I'm not kidding. The legend
of the sea vampire is real.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
They're fish by day
but at night, they walk on two
legs, thirsty for human blood.
- This is a matter of life and death.
- Sea vampires can be tasty
battered and fried, served up
with a side of tartar sauce.
But be careful. I hear when you
bite into them, they bite back.
Looks good. I'll take them.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
THORNE: Mm.
Hello there, Donna.
Thorne.
I've known you since you
were a little girl.
You think it's about time you
started calling me Travis?
Thorne, have you heard about
the legend of the sea vampire?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Well, it turns out there's
some truth to it after all.
You putting me on?
I know it sounds ridiculous, but
regardless, the water's not safe.
I suggest you guys stay on
dry land for a couple days.
Your daddy put you up to this?
Hm? Little practical joke for
me outbidding him on his claim?
Wish it were a joke.
[SIGHS]
Wait, how'd you know
it was our claim?
Sorry, what was that?
The claim you bid on, how'd
you know it was ours?
I saw him storm away, it was easy
enough to put two and two together.
Can I offer you a little
piece of friendly advice?
- Stay off my claim.
- It's not your claim for another six days.
- I beg to differ.
- Cool, well, take it up with the state.
You heard about what happens
to people who steal from me.
- Are you threatening me?
- No.
God, no. Of course not.
This is not a threat. This is
more of a business proposal.
Yeah, well, coming from you,
they're one and the same.
Look, I got the best claim.
You got the best rig.
You know as well as I do how profitable
this claim can be if handled correctly.
That's why I need for you
to talk to your dad.
Convince him to sell his
entire operation over to me.
That way, he can retire in
comfort and you and your brother
can come work for me.
It's a win for everyone involved.
Dredging is my family business,
and you are not my family.
Baby girl, I would get down on my
knees and propose this very night
- if I knew it'd sweeten this deal.
- Shut up.
Jimmy.
Get the boys together.
It's time we put those
Hunters out of business.
Permanently.
Everyone thinks we're a joke.
Even I can't wrap my
brain around this.
But whatever. We warned them.
That's what Dad would've done.
- To Dad.
- I still can't believe he's gone.
- Me neither.
Taught me everything
I know about everything.
Thorne was telling me something
strange after the auction...
MAN [OVER RADIO]: Sluice Goose to
Black Drum. Come in, Black Drum.
Ahem. Sluice Goose,
come in. Black Drum.
Hey, little lady.
Just wanted to tell you
I didn't see any of your sea vampires
out there on the water today.
But what I did see was
a ton of cave gold.
And they were all on the
new claims. Ha-ha-ha.
[CREATURE ROARS]
[SCREAMS]
- He's screwing with us.
- But how do you know?
Come on, let's go.
Joe, come on. Come on.
[SHRIEKING]
[DONNA GASPS]
He wasn't kidding.
[SHRIEKS]
- Quick, get down. Joe. Down.
- Thanks.
- Gotta get away from the water.
- Run.
- They're gonna attack.
- How do you know?
Because they're diving
to gain momentum.
There. There. There. Go, go.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
Go, go, go.
[WHISPERING]
Turn off your flashlight.
[WHISPERING] Now what?
I don't know. I was just trying to
buy us time before our next move.
Great.
[CREATURES SHRIEK IN DISTANCE]
- Did you hear that?
- No.
- What about now?
- I wish I didn't, but I did.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING AND THUDDING]
- Oh, my God.
- Okay.
OWEN: Is this what you
dug up on the legend?
MEGAN: Yeah, not much to go on.
"The legend originating from a
dying fisherman washed ashore"
off the coast of Nome
in the late 1800s
"has proven to be of interest
to locals and visitors."
An account of a man claiming to have
survived an encounter with a vampire,
as well as the record of a fishing vessel
that was discovered off the coast of Nome.
"Despite the fact that
the weather was fine,
the crew had been experienced and the
ship remained entirely sea-worthy."
I mean, wouldn't you think the
discovery of this ghost ship,
and this fisherman, it would
connect these two events?
Well, most myth are
based on some fact.
I don't understand, why is it that we're
just finding out about these things now?
You were lucky enough to survive a
face-to-fin encounter with a sea vampire.
I mean, who could you tell that
wouldn't think you insane?
- You?
- Other than me.
Fair point.
I don't even wanna believe
these things exist.
From what I can glimpse
of their anatomy,
they resemble most
bottom-dwelling sea life.
Before diving, the only way a
human could encounter them
would be if a sea vampire got caught
in the net of a fishing trawler.
Virgin claims.
- A virgin what?
- The virgin claims.
There's an entire stretch off the coast
that's never been dredged before until now.
I think we were the ones
that stirred them up.
What do you mean?
Joe, Donna and I, we were on a dive
there the night Jonas got killed.
Important fact to
leave out, you think?
It wasn't my decision.
I'm telling you now.
Like kicking a hornet's nest. We invade their
territory, they defend their territory.
But come on, you really think
that these things are responsible
for that ghost ship?
You saw it in action, you tell me.
And this is a newborn.
Imagine what a full-blown
adult is capable of.
All right, one of
us has to cast off.
I'll flip you for it.
All right, heads, I win,
tails, you lose. Let's go.
No, I'll go.
Really?
Yeah, I got this.
Okay. Hurry.
Hey, Joe?
Be careful, please.
Yeah.
[CREATURE SHRIEKS]
- DONNA: Come on. Hurry.
- Aah!
Joe.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Someone up there likes us.
[GRUNTS]
Glenn's cells are ravaged.
They look like broken eggs.
It's as if it were feeding
on him from the inside out.
Take some blood. Oh, wow,
this isn't going to work.
- You're not gonna get him.
- It's moving.
This is going to require a different
approach. Can you pass me the camera?
Sometimes photos reveal things you
can't see with the naked eye.
Okay.
- A good one.
- I'm gonna go download these.
Yeah, yeah. Wait.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Wait. He's not moving.
What'd you do?
- Oh, great.
- He's just sitting...
- Help me get it up to the exam table.
- What if he's playing possum?
I mean, the gas didn't last
very long, remember?
[GRUNTS]
JOE: Let's get to Megan's lab.
It's really close to here.
Maybe she's figured something out
about these things. Come on.
Wow, it has soft tissue on
the underside of its fins.
Yeah, that's right
where its teeth are.
Well, it's a soft spot, though
less than ideal place to attack.
- What's going on?
- Whoa. I think we pissed it off. Back up.
Back up. Back up. Back up.
Oh, no, no, no.
[SHRIEKING]
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go. It got loose.
We need to stay on dry land.
[ROARS]
OWEN: Look, they're coming this way.
We gotta get out of here.
[HISSING]
- We gotta move, you guys.
- We're sitting ducks out here.
- Come on, come on!
- Come on!
- OWEN: Faster, they're gaining on us.
- JOE: Run faster.
[ALL PANTING]
OWEN: Come on.
Come here, come here.
Over here, over here.
Go under there. Go. Here, come on,
let's go under here. Come on.
- All right.
- Come on.
They're a triple threat, able to
hunt on land, sea, and in air.
You realize we are the
things they're hunting?
Well, they can't help it.
To them, we're just blood bags.
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
- Joe!
- I got this.
- DONNA: No, you don't. Stop it.
- Joe!
- Joe.
- DONNA: Get back.
- Joe, get back here.
- JOE: I got this.
Go, go, go.
OWEN: Here.
Here.
Here. Here. Here.
Right here, right here.
- Duck down. Duck.
- Communal hunting.
They're working
together to trap us.
Well, I refuse to get
outsmarted by these things.
Owen, where are you going?
- Guys, go. Go, go!
- Come on, let's go!
What the hell's going
on out here, huh?
- Huh?
- Calm down, man. Just calm down.
- What's going on?
- Calm down.
We don't mean any harm.
Calm down. Just calm down.
- What's going on? What you looking at?
- Calm down.
[SHRIEKING]
[GUN COCKS]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
Ugh!
[GASPS]
- They're not so hard to kill after all.
- Its engorged state made it vulnerable.
Oh, come on. Dead is dead.
You got lucky. It was a
one-in-a-million shot.
[SHRIEKING]
Oh, here we go again.
Any ideas, guys?
Bet you wish we killed them
when we had the chance.
[SQUEALS]
[BOTH SIGH]
- DONNA: Quick thinking.
- JOE: Managed to kill one.
It's where the blood came
from. Sorry I missed it.
Well, there's more.
Let's get to my lab.
- Any chance I'm dreaming?
- Feel that?
- Damn.
- Maybe we scared them off.
- I have a theory.
- Hey, another theory?
Skin can't handle extensive sun exposure
outside the protection of the water.
Would explain why they
only appeared after dark.
- Like real vampires.
- There are no such thing.
- After today, I wouldn't be so sure.
- The flash.
- The flash is what stunned the infant.
- They would have sensitivity to light.
Shocked the nervous
system, caused a seizure.
- Can we use that to our advantage?
- Let's turn the tables. Hunt them. Go.
- Let's do that.
- Let's go.
All right, guys,
you know what to do.
All right, let's get going.
Come on, go.
He knows what he's doing, right?
With the charges? He knows?
All right, I'm going in.
- Hand me the charges.
- You got it.
Got it.
[BEEPS]
- Got that one. Another one. Thanks.
- All right.
[CHARGE BEEPS]
- I got them set.
- All right. Let's go.
[CREATURE GROWLS]
What was that?
What is what?
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLING]
Good God.
Go. Go! Get going!
Oh, my God.
Sea vampires.
[PANTING]
JOE: What do we do now?
OWEN:
Well, obviously that didn't work.
We've got to regroup,
come up with a plan B.
I think I got some ideas.
[MAN SIGHS]
[CREATURE GROWLING THEN SHRIEKING]
[YELLING AND GROANING]
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]: Weather
service has issued a storm warning
for all of the mid and southern
coastal areas of Alaska.
Warnings for south, St. Matthews and
Nunivak are at life-threatening levels.
Preparations are made
for rescue operations,
expected to be in epic proportions.
Everyone is advised to
prepare for the worst,
and listen for
emergency broadcasts.
Storm to the south is preventing
anyone from getting to us.
We're on our own for 48 hours.
I suggest we sit tight, stay off
the water and away from the beach.
I'm not sitting tight. Those
things killed my father.
- Don't make it personal.
- This is beyond personal.
Those creatures are simply doing
what they were born to do.
Breed and feed, it's primal
instinct, survival of the fittest.
You invaded their turf.
They're defending it.
You're saying we started this?
No, I'm saying that up until now, they
were feeding off of one thing: seals.
Your diver came, they got a taste of human
blood, now they're thirsty for more.
We only have five days until this claim
is off-limits and it's Thorne's claim.
I intend on taking full
advantage of them.
Is it worth risking your life for?
- Dredging is my life. Joe, Owen.
- She's right.
It's a mistake to go
against Mother Nature.
I mean, she always bats last and
she always bats a thousand.
Are we supposed to just sit here and wait
for the cavalry to ride in and save us?
Father taught us not taking matters into
your hands is how you get taken down.
And who's to say that the
Coast Guard can do any more?
Right now, if anything, we are
the sea vampires experts.
I never agree with my sister, but I'm not
letting anything take us off the gold.
I really wish you would listen to me.
What you all are doing is suicide.
Thank you, but I'm not
asking your permission.
Come on, Joe, let's go.
JOE: I'll meet you at The Black Drum.
There's something I have to take care of.
Back so soon.
You settled one debt.
Wouldn't think you'd be so eager to
get behind the eight ball again.
My father's dead,
which makes me 50 percent
owner of The Black Drum.
Yeah? My condolences.
Don't pretend to care.
Okay.
- What is it that you want from me?
- A promise.
Half my stake in future
profits from The Black Drum.
Nice of you to be so
generous to yourself.
Quote me and I'll
deny I ever said it.
But you and I both know my
sister's the best dredger.
Her haul is better than
mine or anyone else's.
And what do you want in return?
All my debts paid in full,
and you and your men help
us with our little problem.
You hear that? Heh.
Boy thinks he can quit cold turkey.
Son, you live for this action.
You're gonna be back in here
making your bad bets in no time.
- Well, that's my problem.
- Until it becomes my problem.
- Then don't take my action anymore.
- Well, that right there, that's just...
That's not in my nature.
You have five seconds to
take the deal or it's off.
I don't want half of your action.
I want half your boat.
No way in hell.
Then you're right back
where you started,
on your own and in over your head.
Guess it's better to go
with the devil you know.
[SIGHS]
Half my boat.
Half the boat.
DONNA: Well, at least
something's gone our way.
Where is my brother?
He's never on time.
OWEN: We finally have one thing
in our favor: storm's gone.
Now, do you wanna hear my plan B?
DONNA: Uh, yeah, sure. What?
We're gonna put a net at
the back of the harbor.
Shrimp boat's gonna come
in, pulling the net over.
We're gonna trap them so
that nobody's gonna get out.
We'll bring the lights in.
Lights...
Where have you been? Excuse me.
I need a second with my brother.
We could use as much help as we could
get, regardless of the source.
- What did you do?
- What I had to do.
Joe.
THORNE:
I want all the equipment taken out.
- I need you to trust me.
- That's never worked out.
- You are a two-headed coin.
- There's always a first time.
Dad went out of his
way to keep him out.
He wouldn't take anything from Thorne,
he knew what a predator he was.
Believe me, I know what he is.
We need his help.
Any collateral damage is on me.
- I got your back, baby sis.
- Yeah, I sure hope so.
Have no fear, the cavalry is here.
I don't know what's worse,
Thorne or the freaking fish.
Didn't expect you.
I have a moral obligation to make
sure you don't die a horrible death.
Much appreciated. We can use
all the help we can get.
Flash kits, explosives,
chicken wire?
You planning on
building a fish disco?
What we're gonna do is fence
off the harbor, lure them in,
trap them, stun them with the
lights, and we're gonna kill them.
Kill every single one of them.
And how are you so sure
this is gonna work?
- You a hundred percent certain it won't?
- Nothing's a hundred percent.
Then I say we cut the friendly
chitchat and we get to work,
because what's happening here, it's
not making our odds any better.
Okay, come on. Let's go.
I want them to have an accident
of the permanent nature.
You understand me? All right.
- OWEN: Almost there. Hold on.
- DONNA: Right, good. Let's hurry.
- Right. Ahem. Tell me when to go.
- All right.
Good. Hold on. Let me start it up.
[ENGINE REVS]
All right, go. It's hot.
It's hot. Go.
- Got them on there? Got it?
- Yep.
- Good. Let's go. Go.
- DONNA: Don't really have time. Come on.
- Right.
OWEN: Hold on. Let me get the boat.
Let me get the boat.
Good.
All right, there we go.
Testing out!
- Okay. All right. Let's go.
- Good, good. Go, go, go.
All right, let's go. Are you ready?
All right, let's go. Owen.
- We all set? We're good?
- Yeah.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
It's working. They're
coming. Be ready.
- There they are. There they are.
- Oh, my God.
- Here we go. Unh.
- Okay, do it.
[CREATURES SQUEALING]
Go get my rifle.
- Nice.
- You see that?
- Yeah.
- Give me that. Get the hell out of here.
- Yes.
- Nice.
- Nice. Nice. Good job.
- I counted six!
[GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
- No, no, no. Go.
- We gotta go. We gotta run.
- Run! Go!
- Go!
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
[MAN GRUNTS]
[YELLING AND GROANING]
[CREATURE GROWLING]
You stupid son of a bitch.
You're gonna look real
nice mounted on my wall.
[GRUNTS]
- Come on. Ugh, freaking door.
- Come on. Come on.
- Got it. Got it.
- Go, go, go. Open it.
- Open it.
- Yeah. Go, go, go.
DONNA:
The door, the door, the door.
- Is it locked?
- Yeah, yeah.
I don't know what that would
do, but whatever. Okay.
- Ugh. Smell that?
- Whoa. He's growing pot.
- That's where he gets all his money.
- JOE: You have no idea.
- DONNA: What is that supposed to mean?
- JOE: Don't worry.
DONNA: Don't worry about it? Do
you know something I don't know?
- Shut up.
- Shut up?
Annoying.
Guys, get down. Get down.
Joe, get down. Get down.
[SHRIEKING]
[SQUEALING]
Guys, stay down.
Aah.
[BOTH GASP]
- Okay, what just happened?
- We just got very, very lucky.
I didn't think it would work.
- I was trying to find a way to fend it off.
- JOE: Explain.
Growing lights use an intense
and isolated UV wave
- naturally shielded by the atmosphere.
- In other words. English.
We found the sea
vampires' kryptonite.
Regular light stuns them, but
high-intensity light kills them.
- This is good.
- Yeah.
Owen, you've been pacing back
and forth for, like, an hour.
Sit down. Relax.
Joe and Megan are on watch.
Come on.
[MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY]
[SIGHS]
Okay, I'm going around the corner.
If you hear anything, warn them.
I've got it.
I'm just...
I'm just amped up.
It's like that feeling I used
to get after a big game.
Football?
Yeah.
Yeah, after college, I was
supposed to go pro, but I, uh...
I hurt myself...
and I didn't handle it too well.
Tough break.
Yeah. Football was
everything to me.
I didn't know what I was
gonna do after that.
Then the phone rang,
and it was my ex-girlfriend. And it
turns out I had a 1-year-old son.
And she couldn't take care of
him anymore so I stepped in
and became a single father.
That's amazing.
It scared the hell out of me.
I bet.
You know, but the reality is,
you know, my son saved my life.
And I owe him everything.
That's why I'm here.
I need to make as much money as
I can so I can give him the life
that he deserves.
He's the best thing that
ever happened to me.
Yeah. Sounds like my dad.
Family's the best thing that
could ever happen to anyone.
You know, I can't
agree with you more.
Listen.
I think we're in a good position.
We know their weakness.
They're gonna be on our
turf till the sun comes up.
So I think that gives us a pretty sizable
home-court advantage, don't you think?
What did you have in mind?
- Craziest thing I've ever done.
- Not even in my top 10.
- Show-off. Come on, let's go.
- Get them. Aah.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
- I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
- Would Cousteau run from danger?
- No.
- Turn his back on what is the greatest
evolutionary discovery
of the millennium?
- Jacques Cousteau couldn't handle this.
- I guess you're in luck, then.
There's one. Right there. Right
there. Right there. Get him.
Yeah, good, good, good.
- Get him. Right over there.
- Right.
There's another one over
here. Get them. Got them.
- Did we get them?
- Nice.
[CREATURE SNARLING]
[WHOOPS]
- Yeah. Nice.
- Technical difficulties. Please stand by.
There's nothing going on.
It's really quiet.
- Joe, you see anything in the front?
- It's unusually quiet right now.
[GASPING]
- What is that?
- Where? Where?
Over there. No, that's not...
We're good.
Don't scare me like that.
Yeah, I know. I think we're...
I think we're good. That's...
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
No, no, no. Come on. Come on.
Joe, what are you doing?
Come on. Move this thing again.
- Go! Come on!
- Come on. Come on.
DONNA: Pick up the speed.
What are you doing?
OWEN: Come on, we gotta go faster.
- Do something. Do something!
- Come on. I'm trying! I'm trying!
OWEN: No, no, no.
- DONNA: What's going on?
- OWEN: Come on. No, come on.
[CREATURES SNARLING]
Come on, come on,
come on. Please, please.
Come on! Come on!
MEGAN: Do something!
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
- OWEN: We gotta go faster.
- DONNA: Joe!
- Bail out!
- Aah!
- DONNA: Joe? Go.
- OWEN: Go, go. Get out. Get out. Get out.
DONNA: You unhooked? All right,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
OWEN: Whoa!
[ROARS]
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[CREATURE SQUEALS]
My gosh, neat little trick.
- I like to keep something up my sleeve.
- Can you make more of those?
Yeah, and now that I know they
work, I got a few other ideas.
- I'd like to help.
- Why the change of heart?
- Being on the wrong side was sobering.
- Glad to see you come around. Come on.
Damn things did me a solid.
What did he have on
you anyway, Joe?
Whatever it was, doesn't
matter now, does it?
[SIGHS]
I guess not.
How do you wanna play this?
Take it to them. Let's
kill them where they live.
That's what I hoped you'd say.
Looks like a giant jigsaw puzzle.
Where'd you learn
how to do all this?
My old man and I used to restore
classic cars when I was a kid.
Taught me everything I needed to
know about electronics and engines.
All the dos and the don'ts.
Let's just say I had a lot
more fun with the don'ts.
Taught me how to blow stuff up. Made
me popular with the neighborhood kids.
Got to have my own fireworks
show any day of the week.
Bet you never thought
you'd be using it for this.
Never in my wildest dreams.
What about you?
At what point did
you say to yourself
you wanna dedicate your
life to the study of fish?
Well, I spent a lot of time with my
grandparents when I was growing up
and they lived about a mile away
from one of the nicest
beaches you ever wanna see.
I used to spend hours
with my grandpa
collecting crabs and snails
and starfish in buckets.
So as I got older, it only seemed
natural to move on to bigger fish.
Well, be careful what you wish for.
Wow, looks like a first-class
battleship. Good job, brother.
- More like a death ship.
- Even better.
- Megan and Owen are here. Let's go.
- OWEN: Come on, let's do this.
DONNA: What do we have? Oh, wow.
Nice. All right. This isn't gonna be pretty,
but now we know what makes them tick.
We'll be coming at them
on their home turf.
But Murphy's always
part of the equation.
- Murphy?
- Murphy's Law.
- If anyone wants out, speak up now.
- I got nowhere else to be.
I gotta get us on that gold.
- Let's do this before I change my mind.
- Let's go.
- OWEN: Get the big one right here.
- DONNA: Help me, Joe.
- Take one to the bridge, one to the back.
- You got it.
OWEN: Hey, buddy.
It's Dad.
What am I doing?
Well, I'm, uh, hunting monsters.
No, I'm not teasing you.
These are... These are
real live monsters.
Well, because they're protecting the
gold, and we gotta fight them for it.
They live at the bottom of the ocean,
in caves, and that's where the gold is.
Exactly.
Just like the dragon in your book.
Buddy, listen.
I don't have much time,
so I just, uh...
I wanted to call and see how you're
doing and tell you that I miss you.
Yeah, well, when I get back,
we're gonna go on a trip.
So I want you to start thinking
about places you wanna go, okay?
All right.
All right, I love you too.
Bye-bye.
Seems like a great kid.
Yeah, he's...
He's the most important
thing in the world to me.
My dad was a single dad too.
I don't know how he did it.
I can't imagine raising a
kid in this day and age.
I have enough trouble getting
myself through the day.
It's the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
Harder than hunting sea vampires?
You know, I'm gonna have to
get back to you on that one.
- Okay, we're here.
- Right back where we started.
There you go.
- Let the games begin.
- Thanks.
[ENGINE STARTS]
This is for you, Dad.
I'm coming for you, suckers.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
Teach you not to
mess with my father.
[GRUNTS]
How did that feel?
That's what you get for
touching my father.
[SPITS]
- You ready? Grab it. Grab it.
- I got it.
Get rid of it. There you go.
Watch out. Watch out.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Okay, ready?
- Boom!
- Nice.
[SHRIEKS]
[SQUEALS]
Got one!
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
[GRUNTS]
[SQUEALS]
Got another one!
Joe! Donna, what's going on?
I'm losing power up here!
- Joe, generator.
- Got it!
- Here. Owen, take this.
- All right.
Oh, damn.
Damn, damn, damn.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING AND SQUEALING]
[SHRIEKING]
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Owen!
- Yeah!
- Catch!
- Thanks.
[SHRIEKING]
[MEGAN YELLING]
Owen. Owen, go. Megan.
[YELLING AND GROANING]
Owen, help me! Please!
Owen! Help me, please!
Owen, help!
Hold on.
[MEGAN SCREAMING]
Suck on this!
[CREATURES SNARLING]
Come on!
[SHRIEKING]
Yeah!
[SIGHS]
I got your back.
[GRUNTS]
That's it.
- We're done. The Black Drum is sinking.
- That's bad.
I know. There's no way
we can fix this out here.
I'd rather put a bullet in my brain
than let those things get me.
Drum's going down, no matter what.
Let it go down with a purpose,
let it go down with a bang.
- What did you have in mind?
- I can rig it to explode.
I can put together a UV combustion
bomb and I can blow it sky-high.
All right, let's do it. Joe,
cover us with the UV cannons.
JOE: Let's go, let's go, let's go!
All right, okay, right here.
Here we go. Here we go.
These are gonna blow them up.
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
It's gonna be nice. Okay,
give me these. This goes here.
- All right.
- There. Good, good, good. Good job. Go.
Let's do this. Come on.
Okay.
It's now or never, people. Come on!
- This is as good as it's gonna get.
- Come on, let's move.
- Come on. Hurry.
- Hold on, hold on.
- Go, go, go!
- DONNA: Come on. Go.
- DONNA: All right.
- OWEN: Go, go.
DONNA:
Let me know when the boat's untied.
OWEN: Come on. Come on.
- DONNA: What's taking so long?
- OWEN: All right. Go, go, go!
Any second now.
Come on, come on, come on.
- Come on.
Something must be wrong.
It's taking too long.
Uh-oh. That's the
least of our worries.
[CREATURES SNARLING]
- Guys. Shoot.
- Come on, come on.
[GRUNTS]
Come on, come on, come on.
- Yes.
- Whoa! Yeah!
[CHUCKLES]
Even in death, The Black
Drum puts up a fight.
Always has.
I sure hope this thing doesn't die.
I don't have it in me to paddle back in.
[SHRIEKING]
Whoa, watch out!
- Joe!
- Whoa, Joe.
- DONNA: My gosh, are you okay?
- Is he okay? What's wrong with him?
- Kill it. Kill it.
- I am. I am. Joe, are you okay?
- Joe. Just keep...
- DONNA: I am. I'm killing it.
- Kill it.
I'm trying. I'm getting it.
Hold on.
[CREATURE SQUEALING]
- Joe. Joe, look at me.
- DONNA: Are you okay?
Die already!
I think it's dead. I think it's dead.
Joe, are you okay?
- Look at me. Look at me.
- Are you okay? Let me see. Let me see.
It's not that bad. Okay. All right.
Yeah, you're good. You're good.
I mean, same old, same old.
Always wind up carrying your ass.
Not true.
Yeah? Well, name one time you
ever had to carry me. Huh?
Halloween, 1992. You twisted your
ankle and you didn't want to go home.
So I carried you piggyback
the whole night.
Yeah, I didn't wanna go home
with a weak candy haul to Dad.
He used to weigh out our candy.
- Traded candy for gold ounce for ounce.
- Double ounces for Snickers, remember?
I take it back.
You have carried me.
You know, I'm gonna
turn over a new leaf.
- Hopefully it's a gold leaf, right?
- I'll get us back on the gold. I promise.
I'm taking your word. Can you
try not to bleed to death
- before we make it back to shore?
- Yeah, I'll try.
And, Owen, after everything
you've done for us,
you have a place in
this boat for life.
That is if you still want it. Heh.
I knew I'd get on your good side.
- Hey, hey.
- Ha-ha-ha.
Think we got them all?
If not, at least they'll think
twice about coming back at us.
- Live for the gold.
- Die for the gold.
- But not this time.
- Hear, hear.
You know, after everything,
Name's a pretty beautiful place...
- when it's not trying to kill you.
- All right, let's get the hell home.
- What do you say, huh?
- Yes, please let's go home.
Can we just go home?
Let's go.