LEFT BEHIND
Hello.
Hi Mom!
Chloe, welcome home.
You're going home, right?
Yes, safely.
Your brother has been running to and fro.
Oh, I can not wait to meet her
.
So are all ready for a surprise party for dad
?
Um, dear, I'm afraid your father would not
be here when you were Bernie dir.
What?
Why not? Mom, what happened?
He got the call to work.
Did you tell him I was coming? ./
Yes dear, I said it, but...
call this morning and
The flight  what?
That Flight London 335...
Tell
Romeo I'll come home for a while longer.
You must have never seen this all
You always berbada the disaster.
Every time I see the news.
Oh what good is it? The important thing is
I got a good job.
Can I ask you something, Mr. Williams?
Yes, of course.
Do you read the Bible? ./ Well...
I think I do not like
you expect.
In Matthew 24: 7. no explanation about hunger, food shortages
, and earthquakes in various places.
All the same, they are all disasters
signs.
You always think that the end will occur.
Unfortunately, God knows everything.
So why did not he do something?
I mean, he was the Lord, he can block the sending
flooded with light rain
It is one of us. God created a perfect world
and we are destroying it.
Who is destroying it? I?
You? He?
All humans.... / By
mysterious ways, I know.
But somehow continue to build and
He ​​loves them. And it's a new mysterious.
Everything for you now.
Good morning, Rayford.
I enjoy your words.
Yes, I'm sorry about that ../ Do.
That was very nice.
I assume it's not the first time.
Well, the first time in front of the public
. / Cameroon Lindsay.
My Buck
I Chloe Steele.
Chloe to friend
So you go to college.
Wow, your investigation capabilities
very frustrating.
I just wanted to say thank you to you for saving me
from the strange woman.
Oh, equally.
He was alive to do it.
True once he was so.
Dirty?
Actually
I just want to go home this morning, I decided with Wacko
Wacko? ./ Hmm hmm.
I love that word, wacko
Can I buy you a cup of coffee?
No, no, I'm doing okay
Come on!
What if I add a box of strawberries...
Oh my God. Well, it's new seductive.
Yes? ./ Hmm hmm.
But I'm waiting for someone, and he
should be coming soon
My father.
I have prepared a surprise for her birthday, but...
something is happening.
We have a safe flight
O dear! ./ Hi!
What are you doing here? ./ I go home, to give
day of your birthday surprise
Unfortunately I just got a call,
I could not just walk away
Yes, the mother has been telling me I ../
hope you tell you to come
Oh you, you're Williams, geez.
So you two? / Oh, we just met.
Hi, nice to meet you captain. / Ray.
I'll let you two. And
well, nice to meet you. Chloe
You look incredible ../ Thank you.
Let's talk
How was school? ./ Good.
Good, yes...
What?
You know what the first thing I think of when I
home
It is your laughter
I really mean your laugh Then pack your bag,
slammed the door, get in the car and go.
Your mother and I are fine, Chloe.
It's okay, I do not blame you
you do not blame me for what
? ./ To walk away
But I do not just leave you
that said I went away
Who the girl? ./ girl what?
Flight attendant, Beautiful, and blonde
Stewardess, I worked on dozens of flight attendants
.
I do not even remember his name
If this happens  last year, you know before
mother drank, you'd be home now
We all have at home, such as family or something
.
Chloe, I think you know that your mother and
I got married at a very young age...
and there is always a change for between 15-20 years
He always did what he thought was right without
never give me a chance.
I... How about you?
When you go to London
You are a person who does not come home for Christmas.
I ../ school and I work.
I just feel that you always want to exaggerate something
.
Look, I know that the past
years, sauatu assessment, but
She is your mother, and would be very nice if you
, no, we're both...
mutually support each other.
But you miss ../ Yes,
I miss him.
But hey, he will not be so happy to see me home right
.
Where is your baggage?
In my car, I will never forget when
fly
Chloe, she is my world, I'm not going to
do something that makes him angry ok
But I have to go, we
'll talk when I get back .
I will not be at home when you go home.
Oh but you'll be home soon, right?
This...
The car is in the usual place, and
try not to fight mother,
I love you.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, I'm fine.
I was a journalist, do you remember?
True ../ Yes.
So...
I just feel a little disappointed, that's all.
This is a big problem for me, all of us have the time
fun
Oh I'm sure you'll survive if you can.
It comes with both hands on the floor.
And the stewardess said...
"I'm sorry..."
You may only carry one luggage
I'm sorry, Captain
And he thinks I'm funny
Oh if you have no job
try come see me
Hey Marcus, you can take care of the computer ?
Negative, to the Peacon,
there perlaatan in the deck
Yes, I will be heading east, in
6 hours, I would be older 9 hours
Thank you.
Sounds like it is your mother talking
Sometimes it looks like it.
There is someone who saw the earthquake on the news and
try to convince people it's good news.
Does that make sense to you?
Death by Tsunami,
it beyond your shadow.
Children
dragged into the sea before they were aware.
It's hard to imagine the baby in hand.
And he was so sure I
save her baby.
But he mengikhlaskannya.
He ​​is grateful.
She thanked him for killing others?
He has a chance, that night he refused
in the evacuation, and he felt God was watching.
And.... / Then...
And he tries to
How people see things like that, and...
If you look close enough, you'll see what
you're looking for.
And I've got a lot of work to it.
One of them
might be the truth.
And what about you?
Do you have seen the village?
I see everyone
not care about the small things.
And if he asks why?
I know why.
Tsunami.
I know what I think
Not. No, I do not do it.
If you want an amazing thing
as it happens, and...
Do you mind if it is
a stranger at the airport?
Oh...
Why laugh? ./ Oh, no.
What?
Oh, just thinking about that joke.
The man makes me laugh.
Ray !. / You mean Captain Steele?
Just in front of others.
Really?
So he is?
No, not yet.
But, we would spend time together
in London.
True?
Why do not you tell me?
Chloe, where are you going?
Ah, how many details I beg
I really need someone to talk to today in
Thank you.
I'll call you from London
true? / Right
I will make sure you will not forget me
, ok. / Right, right.
What every woman you meet at the airport
, what do you call it?
No, if I do not like them.
Chloe.
Ok. Jim.
I got something for your dad
That's for tomorrow night.
You too. Waw.
It is not easy to obtain.
You tell me.
It took two weeks for me to get this thing
Two weeks?
Chloe, I'm sorry...
Mr. Williams, please
I'm coming, sorry
Chloe, I ..
What
you can give this to my dad? I beg
course.
Well, you...
Excuse me, is he / Thanks
Mr. Williams, please ../ Sorry
Excuse me Captain
Chloe asked me to give you
You are CW & G
CW & G, It is me.
Recommend, Chris Smith ../ Hi, nice to meet you
.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome
Peacon flight 257 to London
Flight
will take as much as 6 hours 30 minutes.
Thank you, and enjoy Your flight
So, did you get her phone number?
Come . / I see you in the queue last 1 hour and
you are the last person to go up to the plane.
Try you think, I spend time with
I do not know why you are concerned with her
.
Probably because we do not want to travel with pakian
ugly
You're right on that.
I will be grateful for it, first class flights
No need to thank a friend
Look at the man sitting in the back there.
How can you be sure?
I know you!
See, George. It was Frank Sinatra!
What? ./ It is Frank...
Oh!
Listen , George.
We're home
We have not been home
Sometimes he's a little confused.
Good afternoon, this is Captain Rayford Steele, who led
Peacon flight 257, and sunny weather report
So we will fly smoothly, towards London
, / Please sit back and enjoy our waitress
Soon we will airs,
calm and relax.
No Jonny, you do not need to throw anything else
, just do what you think is best
Tom, man.
If you say one thing about this acquisition,
say it all.
Listen,
I went to Houston with Jet. I'm going to
in London, before they realize I've gone
We'll go, see you later, do
Chloe, Chloe!
Hey! Come on!
My God, Oh My God
You are so great!
Ok.
Did you take anything from its airport?
Well, you'll have to wait and see.
Well, take a look at what's there.
New baseball gloves
I ask for it
No way! Mother!
Chloe is here!
Mother, Chloe is here!
She is here, mom!
Hi! ./ Hai...
geez
Oh, you look beautiful.
Waw.
So,
Um, can I get you you
something to drink?
Yes ../ course
Chloe baseball gloves buy a new one for me. See?
6 hours to London.
I do not think going for it.
Super jet engine has been changed segelanya
Oh yeah? Why so?
Department of defense.
Are you saying the Department of defense? ./ Yes.
We will have a new general,
ok? We carry about 300 passengers,
Towards London, 6 minutes.
6 minutes? ./ 6 minutes.
It was very fast  ../ Personally,
I think there is still another.
Yes, I guess it's a good guess
It is still in the development stage
, and I expect
That's about mechanical engineer or something else
Probably something from Area 51
Yes .
Please drink.
So, what surprised your father?
Yes. I think he was surprised.
I talk to him
He ​​looks very upset because he had to go.
I have to say to him.
So, how was your flight?
It was fun. Yes, it was fun.
School?
Well okay
Hey, you would not think
whom I met at airports.
Buck Williams.
Sorry, Camden Williams.
From broadcast news? ./ Yes!
True? ./ Hm-hmm.
Were you a chance to talk to him?
Yes. Actually,
And, he...
Violent Men
Hmm, it seems he just
should be friendly.
Yes...
I told him that you like him.
Oh!
Yes, and anyway, you're not the only one who thinks
earthquake is the end of the world.
There is a mad woman who thinks like that.
Not so true.
After all, Hmm...
He is a great guy.
Chloe dear...
I do not intend to force.
I know how to taste like that
I just want you to understand.
It's important to me.
So also with you.
I just want you to be prepared.
Ready for what?
You know...
Forget it.
Can we talk without you interrupting?
Mom, I just got here.
I'm not really prepared to talk tough
.
Yes, of course, now listen to me.
Few.
I pray that you come home, and I'm sure
is why God brought you here.
What are you saying?
Lord take me home?
God did not take me home, I
carrying myself.
I bought the tickets, I was on a flight
,
God has nothing to do with it.
And let me ask you something
If God takes me home for dad's birthday,
Then why did he fly to London?
Maybe it's important for us to talk
I do not like the taste of it
One thing I am sure, God is the reason why now
father is not here now
Chloe!
I'll be right back ../ Yes.
What I can help put your bag?
What I ask for help?
I, I can put it on for you.
Yes? I can too!
What do you see?
Want to ask me something?
Want to know how I drive?
Maybe where I buy my clothes?
How can I reach the urinal?
What is a urinal?
This is my father.
He plays football.
That's good, son.
Tomorrow
if he would play his hand was healed.
Your father played baseball on television?
Tim what?
Jets!
Oh. What's wrong with her?
Cosmo. He was my dog.
He hit the father.
Oh, really?
Father very angry. He pushed Cosmo.
What I say unto
about the other passengers?
Sorry...
So, you're a bad man.
Yes.
You're going to give it to the child?
His father is a famous person.
I'm not sure he needs the money.
Do you want to go where?
Go out . / What can I join
I do not mean now
I beg.
Right. Take your things ../ Cool!
What we could go to the mall? ./ Yes, we can.
I heard 8% of the
Americans like to go to the mall.
Do you think it's crazy mother.
What?
Not.
No, I'm just annoyed
Father says pastor Bruce has brainwashed her.
Oh, it's just a joke.
True?
I do not understand.
So did I..
So this is a little annoying.
What is it? ./ Do
flight when's your birthday?
Well, but you have to pay your bills right?
So how long Chloe in the city?
Well, it looks like he
You know I straighten my legs.
Go see how the other crew members
Raymie, what are you doing?
I'm scared to death!
What was that?
Come ../ Can I have it?
Not. ../ you can not think that a few hundred dollars
?
I know.
Hello, girls.
I will find a way to repay you.
What's the problem? ./ No... I...
I just think this should put the date.
You want coffee? ./ Yes.
I'll be fine.
Huh?
Mother.
You were just a waste of time to keep
with me, you know what I mean?
He never took me away.
So why not go alone, do not you think?
Hmm? Yes, yes of course.
Dad just has to work, it is
things that should do it, ok?
Dad tell you about my game?
Are you kidding me?
About hath all that we are talking about.
He said that you were the best baseball
puz worldwide.
And you know what? ./ What?
He was right.
I love you.
I miss you,.
No, it is not possible.
Where is the police?
Kathy?
Do you see where her daughter
I go?
Bruce! Let me in!
Do you hear me?
Raymie!
Where is he?
Everything sat.
No, everything sat!
Sit! Everything!
Hey, what actually happened?
What happened?
No, let's go. This is serious.
I want to see the captain!
Hey, I want to see your captain.
Hey, I want to see the captain!
Off me.
Attention, this is your captain.
This is the captain. all others please
immediately sat where you guys soon
Hey, back off ../
I want to see the captain!
Tell us what just happened?
We are experiencing low air pressure.
Please go to your seats,
and wear air masks.
This is so crazy.
Come on!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop!
It pencon 257 we have an emergency.
Emergency! Emergency! It pencon
257 please identifiable.
The cabin
has not in the low pressure, it is not anything.
Everyone in this plane
already terrified.
I really need to do your job
.
Can you do that? ./ Yes.
If you know something strange
, immediately let me know.
Hello. I'm Captain Steele!
I want you to stay seated and wearing a seatbelt,
but now you can unplug your air mask.
What has happened?
Children I... Where's me.
I know you all want answers,
but believe me, I'm also the same.
And I'll do the best I,
to lose you, but now
I have to do my job so we can all survive.
Happy? Congratulations on what?
Sit!
If you are constantly paranoid,
Currently, it is the biggest threat on this plane
.
Now I'm going to ask the flight attendants to calculate the amount of your
Whatever happens to them,
we will find them.
I still have not been able to reach
anyone, so I do not know if this.
This incident has occurred in all planes
or just here alone, but I promise...
Immediately
I get something for you guys to tell
I'll tell him
That's it?
Maddie?
Kimmy...
My God .. Kimmy...
Kimmy has gone.
Ray what is going on? ./ Honey...
Honey... you have to brace yourself ../
Please hug me.
Look at me, look at me.
We trained for daruat circumstances.
So we will do our work.
Look, I'm doing all of this
So, I really need to focus
, ok?
Ok? ./ Ok.
Now listen to me...
I want to go back and check their
.
Let us find out who they are.
And we're going to land, ok? ./ Ok.
Ray...
I'm afraid.
You will let me go?
I will soon let you go
, as soon as possible.
Please, please help me, I'm really scared
.
I'm sorry...
I Williams, reporting from flight 257
We are in the waters of Atlantis, towards London, but
3 hours from JFK Airport
Something. / Mushail. here are so tense in the plane
Tell me what you see.
I do not know.
I can not see it clearly.
Then what happened?
Not happen.
I just sit here and very frightened.
I scream scared, I do not know.
Although this sounds impossible, but it's all real
.
I'm not aware of all this.
Hey!
Return the bag to me!
Not!
Are you okay?
I... I hear...
Hear what?
Not...
I know what happened here.
What do you know?
Right.
It's a bad trip.
You must move on.
This is not be the last.
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
Hey, hey.
It's okay.
Now sit down.
Wear your seat belt.
You'll be fine.
All of this does not really happen.
That's okay, we'll get through this.
Why do not you relax, just relax.
Try to sleep.
Can you tell me what you see?
All it would not make a difference.
Listen...
Did you ever see the
disappear just like that?
Not.
What is next to you?
Who is it?
I do not know, a stranger.
Is there anything unusual about the
is not it?
There are strange to us all here.
Get that camera out of my face.
Hi, this is Christy O'R usell
please give me your number.
Sam...
Mother, please pick up the phone,
I do not know what happened.
Ramy, if you receive a call.
I need you to listen, understand?
I know that you fear
and I'm too scared.
But I need you to pick up the phone
.
I want to know that you're okay.
I need to hear your voice.
I love you.
I think, we should pray
for what happens here.
It is the same prayer...
A prayer?
Prayer to whom?
To God.
Who is God?
Ye God, or God I?
Only God.
You know what I think?
No,
This is the captain speaking, we
halfway again to New York.
Hopefully we can get through this.
Pak...
Raymie ../ Back off.
Hi this is Chole Stlee
You okay?
Can you calm the passengers?
I'll try it, but I do not know how the outcome
.
They must be terrified.
We all fear.
I know, I'm going to land this plane
whatever happens.
What is it?
Aircraft in 1581, this aircraft
257, did you hear?
Aircraft in 1581 you should be
to change lanes.
Tampakanya we get the problem of emergency, prepare everything.
Now!
Hello passengers, please return to your seats and place
wearing a seat belt.
Chloe  15.81, did you hear? Please replace
at 10 thousand feet altitude.
Damn!
Emergency!
This is Peacon 257
We were involved in a collision.
5.81 Charlie fell.
Our Coordinated
4-7, this is an emergency situation.
There is a plane that crashed,
We need a rescue team
Repeat, this is an emergency situation.
Come on, there must be someone out there.
What is wrong with you?
You do not believe me?
We are not talking about a bomb.
If this is a gun, it
is not from this planet.
What are you talking about?
I'm just saying, maybe they were abducted.
Alien?
Come on.
Can you believe this guy?
Is everything okay?
What about the other plane, what he also lost passengers
?
I do not know.
Your camera, I want you to photograph the plane's wing
captain.
Wendy.
Be careful.
Hey.
Here's the picture.
Looks like we got a problem.
6 inch gap in the aircraft wing. And spoiler disappeared
That's the problem.
What does that mean?
This will be a difficult journey.
We will get problems during this trip.
I think this it is a lucky day I
They've disappeared
They all have brought the children.
Are you sure?
I'm looking for my son.
I'd been talking to a doctor.
This is not just about suffering.
It occurs where where.
Virtually all parts of the world.
None
even one child is not disadvantaged over this incident.
We rely only on this computer tool.
Camera, I lose
Auto pilot can you check the back of the wing of this plane?
Listen
Makusdmu fuel.
We are at an altitude of 3000 feet, we
can not refuel granted.
Perfect.
Look, we have to go back.
We must return.
We will return safely. No, I mean,
I want to go back home to see my baby.
We have lost a lot of fuel,
how we can survive this problem?
We should be able to return safely ../
Calm down, nothing will happen.
Oh, look at that fire.
Now you know, that we will die.
Back off!
Hey, everybody, listen to me!
No one will be dead, you hear me
? ./ Everything back seat.
True captain Now
I want you all to remain calm.
There was fire coming out of the
side of the wing of this plane.
Is that fire burning wings,
or simply remove the fire alone?
Removing the fire, and the flames were huge.
It was bound to happen due to a fuel leak.
What? ./ It is derived from
leaking fuel.
That's what caused the fire was out.
Let's go back  ../
We must look at the situation first.
It could happen here or here.
So what will we do?
Let it burn.
Only that we can do.
The flames had dimmed.
Fuel level will not change.
Do it marked
we've run out? ./ We do not know.
And I ../ What a loss ladder?
The elevator. It seems we have reached the New York
two hours late
I could not move it.
You're going to try to do that?
At least I will try.
I've tried.
We will do another plan,
because that part has been exposed.
You have to talk to the passengers
what is going on.
I do not know about the passengers.
But I know this.
I am the person who flew it.
Excuse me. I was just thinking,
Where's disappearance?
What?
I mean ..
Why do we not get to see it all?
Like, you know, it's not visible.
It was an annihilation.
Is not this more crazy than annihilation?
Hello, this is an automated message service.
You must be mengevakusikan themselves.
You must immediately leave the house...
(Pray)
How close did you know him?
What?
How close did you get to know him?
Not too close. She's just a friend.
Look goods goods goods goods ../ what?
Whatever. Find just what you get and
can bring to me.
I beg. / Ok
We have a problem anymore with the flight.
Please fasten your seat belts, we
at an altitude of 1000 feet with a latitude 1000
What did you get?
What did you get? Quick take here.
Why do you need all this?
It's all crazy, and the whole world thinks
crazy.
What are you talking about?
I think I know the cause.
How can we know where its existence?
What do you mean?
What if we pass through holes caterpillars,
and into a space of time, we could be in
different time dimension of human existence.
What if that happens?
It was crazy!
Stop! Enough is enough, all of you!
I know what happened here.
Do you know?
How much are they paying you?
What are you talking about?
I can not believe he
do this, I'm her daughter!
Ok. Miss, I do not know what do you think happens
here...
Backward!
Where did you get it?
You! ./ Yes...
How much are they paying you? What?
Where are you taking her? ./
I do not know, what do you mean where?
Husband I.... / Miss, I beg you!
Shut up, shut up!
Mom, who's your husband? Just tell us that.
Why are you doing this? ./ Listen to me...
I promise you, I've never met your husband
.
What is going on?
Mrs , look, I do not know what this is...
But why did not you.... /
What if I shoot it?
Not!
Ray, what happened to you?
Why are you talking like this?
You've never talked about God before.
Where does the  this?
From...
My wife
Miss, I beg you!
Forget about him, ok?
Calm down,
In no part of any of this.
Todongkan weapon on me alone
I did not do anything,
what about him?
Miss, I beg you!
Todongkan arms to me!
Yes  so.
That's good, ok?
Now, just tell me what you think would happen
?
He tried to take my daughter from me.
He thought he would be
do that, right?
He took my daughter, then...
I fell asleep,
someone must have put something in the drink
I, I should have known he would do this.
He ​​can not do it when you fall asleep.
Not possible.
The aircraft landed while I was asleep,
he picked it up and pay you
all to lie to me.
I can not lose him, I could not.
You need to relax.
I'm always awake.
This aircraft has not landed.
No one got out of this plane.
Then where is he?
I can not lose him, I
can not, just that I've got him!
You're thinking I'm crazy,
what should I say?
If he disappear?
I know where he is.
Pastor Barnes?
Chloe...
Hey.... / Oh, no...
Oh, thank God you're still here.
I was so scared, when I saw
they're gone I'm afraid...
He does so, like
promise, just a blink of the eye
What?
Is true...
Then why are you still here?
It is in the Bible.
My parents sent me to
camp in the summer time,
everyone is talking about this.
They say that one day
millions of people will just disappear.
Millions?
Moreover, they say?
I do not remember.
It's been a long time.
What did you say, this act of the devil?
Not.
It is the Lord.
Do not tell me you believe this.
It does not matter what I believe.
Where are they? Where did they go?
Go to heaven.
Kim  true
What do you mean?
Maybe I was really mad.
No you're not.
Maybe he's better off without
I ../ Do not say it.
No, do not!
Please, do not!
Maybe he's better off without me.
You have to listen to me now, do not do this.
You can not give up.
Do you have any children, Mr. Williams?
No, I do not have.
But I have a mother.
ill, father
I've tried everything, doctors, drugs.
But it was all to no avail.
I came home from school one day,
and I found him.
He just lay there,
silent, do not you do that to Katie.
I may not know what is happening
these days, but this is not the fault of Katie,
what do you hear me?
Yes.
If he's out there right now,
see us.
Yes, that's good.
Give me that.
Hey, this is not about us.
It's about the truth.
You have to focus on the truth.
That actually, Ray?
Are you serious? lya.
This is not about the past
us, it's about this time.
What happened to this plane today.
Could happen in everywhere, now also
So they are all in heaven, the conclusions.
Without talking to anyone else outside of this plane.
You will follow the explanation that comes to your head.
I already knew this would come.
In all details
How is it possible
But the way it happened,
how they disappeared,
Even the way their clothes are still there.
The details are perfect.
How can he know that?
Think about it.
Why did not you think about this?
You lied to me about your wife,
Do you lie to your wife about this flight.
You even lied to his own daughter.
Seems that you can lie to everyone in your life,
and now you're asking me to seek God.
Hattie.
You do not understand.
You're here every day.
You work here, preaching here.
Not what counted.
What do you mean?
I know all the words, I could
cite all the chapters, but it was not enough.
You have to believe.
Believe?
Believe in what?
In God who killed my father?
God who took me from my mother and sisters of this world?
God who crashed the plane and destroyed the city?
He took them to protect them.
From what?
From the darkest period in the history of this world.
Murder, war...
And 7 years of darkness, they took him
And what we are all that's left?
What about me? What should I do?
This is not about what we do, it's about
requesting amnesty and surrender our lives...
Stop it!
God the mother I'm talking about,
will not ever do something like this.
Chloe, I beg...
Listen to me.
Dengarkanmu?
Why should I do that?
You do not even listen to yourself.
Are you okay Marshal?
Yes.
Good, I'm glad to hear it.
Peacon 257  This is the control tower
This is Peacon 257,
call control tower
257  This is
Peacon marcus, are you there?
Marcus, I'm 20 minutes outside of JFK,
I have to spin. Where are you?
You're a loss how many victims?
So it happens everywhere?
The whole planet friend
No one knows how many
, but millions
seems to be no way out.
What about my family?
I need you to call
Irene, make sure they are safe
How are you feeling?
Critical. I would be very lucky if achieving
Listen, all aircraft landing everywhere,
is not possible if you're landing at JFK
How Werdia Luke?
Sorry, Ray!
So where do I go?
You should land.
Marcus, I could not land
We'll let you know, when it's ready
It is not possible, you have to talk to them
. clear the way for us.
Marcus?
Marcus!
JFK tower, this Peacon 257, I'm in the emergency fuel shortages
, I need a foundation, I repeat, I need grounding.
So...
Is there a backup plan?
We do not have it.
We're not just a shortage of fuel, but gas as well.
JFK is the nearest airport, we
will be lucky to get there.
We only have one choice,
I hope they clean up the runway
and they do it quickly.
What about the sea? ./ I do not know.
We hit the water, I do not know what
this plane will survive.
We can not, we can not
harm these people.
Hey...
Are you okay?
You probably do not remember me,
In your father's office you sit at a table
yellow.
I remember thinking, this guy definitely
wants everything the best.
They have a small plastic table.
But when you're on the table, the table becomes a table
as the best among others.
Sometimes I also think like that.
Well...
At least he tried.
And I have a daughter too.
I mean, he's big now, he's married now
,
she never existed in my office desk.
To be honest, I was always too busy,
I hardly ever see him again.
You know, before all this happened, I
never even thought of him.
I wish I could say now that I do,
but I think about money, and jobs.
Maybe this is the best .
I'm sorry...
You know what he said about heaven
?
Although I really wanted to see it,
time I came home I
hope he was not there.
I need you to look for me.
I'm trying.
I'm sure this is uh... ended more fun than in the
plane.
I can understand that.
Jim to the tower, do you hear me?
We are leading towards the beach.
Our fuel is almost exhausted.
I need a path to a clean landing.
I repeat, I need
path to a clean landing.
Listen to me...
I control the plane with many passengers here.
I do not have nothing, not
no flag, no elevators.
And if this run correctly,
occurrence can not be repeated.
I need to refuel.
Oh...
Damn...
There reply?
He who controls consolenya.
What else? What can I say.
He turned.
I should not leave him today.
You do not know.
All I know, he came to meet me and I
go.
I left it alone.
Only God knows what he went through
down there.
He loves you, right? He will understand.
I can not let this be the last
thing for us.
I just can not.
I must tell the truth to him.
And I have to tell him that this is not the fault of his mother
, everything is my fault.
Every time I call God, I turned.
Mother...
I do not know if you can hear what is not...
But there is what I'm saying.
This morning
I feel we as a family will be destroyed.
And I blame you.
And I know that I hurt you.
Father, forgive me
I'm so sorry.
Hello?
Who is this? ./ Chloe...
This is Buck. / Thanks
Thank God, you're alive.
Where is my father?
He is here.
Chloe, honey, are you okay?
Dad...
I think you've died
Are you okay?
Yes, yes... I think so.
Mother and Raymie, they both disappear
I, I told you about this.
Yes, and he also had to tell me.
I love you very much.
I love you more than anything in this world.
I, father. I also...
I'm so sorry, I lied to you this
day and I'm not there with you today.
I just want you to know how much I love you
.
No matter what happens.
Well, dad... Why
do you talk like this?
What happened? Where are you?
Well... we still are in the air. We
the way, but there is a problem.
All electrical path outages...
What?
And I do not have enough fuel.
Chloe...
Dad...
The passengers...
We are entering the New York area.
Good...
All its airport closed.
And I want you to keep on kuris you
Fasten your seat belt,
and try to remain calm
But I have to be honest...
This is a very serious situation.
We talked on the tower controllers, and we
try to alternate landing area
But very little fuel us
Please note well our flight crew.
And if you believe
with the power of prayer.
Perhaps now is the time
Do you want to pray with me?
Yes, of course. Course.
No nothing.
Still not getting the signal.
Keep on trying.
I'll do it.
Well, now you have to put it down.
Put?
Where? ./ Aquatic...
But you said...
I know...
I want to fly in the JFK long as I could, but
I can not fly there without there are landing pads
This all happens in all airports
By flying there, it is impossible
We flew 4,000 times
JFK tower is 257 Peacon we need airstrip immediately
Continue to try
Well everything,
I need you to pay attention because we enter the emergency procedures.
I need you guys
Listen to instructions from the flight crew
JFK tower is Peacon 257, we need
emergency landing, now.
JFK tower. JFK tower is Peacon 257,
I need emergency landing now.
Come on...
right.
Buck, can you hear me?
Chloe
Biarakan I speak in speakers
I think I found a place where you can land
.
In the highlands in the west, there is a large
lane and I was cleaning the track.
Nothing is guiding us, we
can not land in the dark.
Hey, check your phone and open the application compass...
Well, wait a minute.
Well, I've got it.
Well, see the below screen is no sequence of numbers.
I need you to read it to me.
North West... 40.66.34 73.78.32
I got
Chloe, how long
path that we have a foundation?
Uh... There is about half a mile, father.
And there's more...
How much longer? I need at least 1 mile.
Well, wait a minute.
Chloe... Chloe, what are you still there?
Around 17:10
18...
Buck... Buck, can you hear me?
Hello?
Come
You've got to be kidding on me
Come on.
We need a vision or something,
so we can know when the landing would begin
you want me to sit here shortly
? ./ Yes... Yes...
Do not stop praying, and
all will be fine.
We're running out of fuel.
What?
Not.
This can still be used for landing
at least we should try to land
Or we will hit the ground quickly.
Is not nothing we can slow down, just brakes alone.
I need you to seek the best for us
Father...
Chloe...
About 9/10 mi. This is the longest track
I can try.
I mean 9/10 is enough?
But you need something
sign up so I could see the runway being
right.
I play my car lights, what do you see?
No, we were too far away for that, we need
bigger and brighter as a beacon
We ran out of time, I
have to land now.
Chloe...
I just need my lighter...
What we are going through there?
If no, I do not want him to think it was a mistake
he
This is it, we're going to land.
Did you see something?
No.... / Keep looking,
about 3 miles.
We only have one chance,
we must know when to start
Still nothing whatever
Come on darling
There!
Try opening wheels for landing.
Dad, you're going to hit me.
Oh...
We're home
All right, get out of the plane, now.
Come on, hurry.
We should fast. Let
Come...
You can get down, I beg
away from the path, / Come away
Hey, hey
Hey!
Buck.... / Chloe.
Thank you.
You've done an incredible job.
You also
Patty!
I'm sorry.
I know.
Dad...
I should be there with you.
With the mother, and Remy.
I'm not supposed to leave you.
I'm quite happy you okay
I thought you might want to keep it.
Could this be the end of the world?
Not. Still yet.
I'm sure, is just the beginning
GOSPEL Mark 13:32 But of that day or hour
no one knows