♪♪
- Mr. Twain!
Can we come in?
- Sure!
- Look, Mr. Twain, what we
found in the newspaper.
(clears throat)
It's a picture 0f a ship.
A big Mississippi steamer
that has your name on it.
Does this boat belong
t0 you, Mr. Twain?
- Oh, my, no.
This don't belong
t0 me, boy.
- But then, why does it
say your name on it?
- Mama told me that you
had been working on a boat
like that when
you were young.
Can you tell us
about it?
I also
want t0 travel
on a big steamer.
- Well, better g0 pretty
quick, little princess,
'cause there ain't
many more 0f these left.
- What do you mean, there aren't
that many anymore?
- Well, son,
the time was when
there used t0 be hundreds
0f these steamb0ats--
mighty, mighty steamboats
going up and down
the mighty Mississippi.
But, with the invention
0f the railroad,
many 0f these are gone now.
But that's a...
(clears throat)
whole other story
in and 0f itself.
- Can you tell us
a story?
- Yes please,
Mr. Twain!
Tell us
your story.
- All right.
All right, pull up a chair
and sit a spell.
All right, here we g0.
This story took place
way before you two
were ever even born.
But I still remember
just as it happened
way back in those days.
♪♪
(steamboat chugging)
Mark Twain: Once a week,
the "Paul Jones," the mail-boat,
would chug upstream
and dock right here.
And all the kids had
only one simple
but honorable wish...
t0 be the steamboat captain.
Sure, we entertained
the idea 0f becoming
a clown in the circus,
or maybe even a pirate.
But, no desire was so strongly
anchored in our hearts
as the one t0 be
a steamboat captain.
And one 0f us kids
was Tom Sawyer.
- Girl: "Columbus departed
from Spain with three ships.
"The 'Santa Maria,'
"the 'Pinta,'
and the 'Nina.'
"Columbus first sailed
t0 the Canary Islands
"on September 6th,
"for what turned out
t0 be a five week voyage
"across the ocean.
A man looked out--"
(clatter)
- Thomas Sawyer.
Stand up,
Thomas Sawyer,
and let the class know
the reason you are
so tardy today.
- Well, sir...
the reason that
I'm so late today
is because I was having
an intense conversation
with my best buddy,
Huckleberry Finn.
- Thomas Sawyer, that has got
t0 be the most amazing
confession I have ever,
in my entire l ♪♪e, ever heard.
An action 0f this sort
is deserving
an extra-special penalty.
This! ls! Big!
- Please, sir...
punish me as you
see fit,
just don't send me t0 sit
over with the girls, please.
- Not t0 the girls, huh?
(students whispering
and giggling)
Hmm.
- Student: He's gonna get it.
- Huh! Immediately g0
t0 the girls' side
and no talking back.
Let this be a warning t0
you, Mr. Thomas Sawyer.
(whispering continues)
teacher: Keep on reading.
(thwack)
girl: "And spotted land
"at about 2:00
in the morning,
"and he immediately
alerted the rest 0f the crew
"with a shout.
"Then, the captain
0f the 'Pinta,'
(stammering)
"Martin Alonso Pinzén,
"ver ♪♪ied the discovery
and alerted Columbus
"by firing a Lombard.
"Columbus later said
that he himself
(chair creaking)
"had already seen a light on the land
"a few hours earlier,
"and he claimed
for himself the money
"promised
by King Ferdinand
(chuckles)
and Queen Isabella t0 the..."
- Mark Twain: Already one day
later began a chain
0f events that would result
in undesirable consequences.
♪♪
(frog creaking)
(birds chirping)
(sighs)
- S0, uh, what'cha
doing down here?
- Psh, nothing.
(Spits)
You know, I'm just--
just spitting.
(chuckles)
- Hucky, you got a good l ♪♪e.
You don't need t0
g0 t0 school.
You can do what you
want when you want to.
I wish I had a father like
yours who was a drunken bum
and didn't make me
do stuff.
- Yeah.
Yeah, well,
it turns out, um...
my old man ain't that
bad after all.
- D0 you mind  ♪♪ I
take a pull?
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
You're my buddy.
G0 right ahead.
- Hey, Huck,
what's that?
- Oh, this?
Uh, well, that's her.
That's my mom,
my true mother.
- But, Huck,
you ain't got a mom.
Everybody knows that.
- Tom, I do have
a mother.
She's out there.
See that?
Mississippi's my mother.
She was there when I opened
my eyes for the first time.
She was there when
I was growing up.
She's there
when I get lonely.
Sometimes I come out here
when I'm alone...
and I talk t0 her.
It's weird, you know?
- Hey, Hucky, what you got
in the pouch?
- Nothin'.
Just a--
just a dead cat.
- That crittefs st ♪♪f
as an ironing board.
Where'd you get it from?
- I bought it about
two weeks ago from Ben Rogers.
- And, uh, what does something
like that cost you?
- Ah, it ain't worth
talking about.
- Okay, and uh,
what's the dead cat good for?
- It banishes your warts.
. OKW-
H0w-- how does
that work, exactly?
- You really want t0 know?
- Yeah.
- All right, well...
you g0 to
the cemetery.
Now, you gotta go to where
some dead guy's laying
about six feet under,
and at the stroke 0f midnight,
the devil's gonna
show himself.
Now, when that happens,
you're gonna hear a sound,
something like a hissing
or the wind
or maybe even words.
Anyways, when you
hear the sound,
you take the dead cat
and you gotta throw it
in the direction you heard
the sound coming from.
But, after you do that,
you gotta say this...
"Devil gets the cat,
cat gets the corpse,
warts get the cat,
and that's not where I'm at."
Then the warts g0 away.
- Okay, so when are
you gonna try this?
- Oh, I don't know.
I figure tonight,
they're gonna be coming t0
get good 0l' Ross Williams,
so probably then.
- Would-- would you mind
♪♪ I tagged along?
- Yeah, sure.
Just better not get me
busted like last time.
Old man Hopkins
sent a whiskey bottle
flying right past our heads,
you remember that?
(crickets chirping,
frog creaking)
Meow!
Meow? Meow!
(quiet scraping)
♪♪
(hay rustling)
- Think old man Ross Williams
hears us talking?
- Well, I sure as hell
ain't been dead before.
Either that or his ghost can.
- Damn it.
(chuckles nervously)
l-- I meant t0 say
"Mister Williams."
- Huck: You oughta be careful what
you say about dead people.
(distant howling)
- Uh, hey, Huck, would you mind
♪♪ I were t0 call it night?
After all,
they are your warts.
- What?
I ain't got no warts.
- You ain't got
no warts?
Then what the devil
are we doing down here?
Just think, Hucky.
What would you do  ♪♪
these ghosts don't exist?
I mean, for me, it'd--
it'd be as though
something were missing.
(branches snapping)
- Did you hear that?
- What?
- Over there!
- What is that?
(rustling)
You saw that, right?
You saw that!
- Yeah.
- I'm tell-- I'm telling
you they're real, look!
I ain't bluffing,
those are the devils!
They're at work right now!
- They're coming
straight towards us.
Uh, uh...
Come on,
come on!
♪♪
- man: Now, I gotta look nice.
I got a job on top 0f
everything else.
- Tom, am I going crazy, or is
that the voice 0f Muff Potter?
- Man: The crap you do
when times are hard.
- That's him, isn't it?
- Can that be?
- Yeah, I know Muff's voice.
Drunk or sober,
that's him.
- All right, this is it.
- The 0ther's Doc Robinson,
and the 0ther's--
- lnjun Joe.
- Muff Potter: Come on, hurry.
The moon can show itself
any minute now, gentlemen.
I suggest you
get a move on.
Start digging-
♪♪
(tools scraping earth)
(distant howling)
- Oh, yeah.
Ah, that's good enough.
(scraping continues)
Muff Potter: Open it.
(creaking)
- Mark Twain: Even up t0 this point,
Tom and Huck had not even
the slightest idea
0f what was going on.
The fact that
Doc Robinson wanted
the corpse 0f Ross Williams
for studies 0f the anatomy
was discovered later.
- S0, good doctor,
think you can
throw another five
for the trouble for us
t0 keep our trap shut?
(Spits)
- Now, may I remind you
that we had an agreement?
Your payment upfront,
which I gladly did.
It's called an
agreement, Mister Joe.
- He's right, Joe,
let it g0.
(Qrunts)
- Joe: His father arrested me once
and punished me in front
0f all the people.
D0 you think
I'm gonna forget that?
(grunting)
" Uhh!
Take it easy, Joe!
Come on,
don't hurt me.
Oh, Christ.
God damn lnjun.
- Joe: This might hurt.
(Qrunts)
♪♪
(panting)
- Huck, what do you
think's gonna happen?
(sighs)
-  ♪♪ Doc Robinson don't
wake up in the morning,
s0me0ne's gonna
get hanged.
- You really think so?
- I'm as sure as an
amen in church.
- Well, who do you think's
gonna tell 'em? Us, maybe?
- N0,  ♪♪ any0ne's
gonna say something,
it's Muff Potter.
- Huck, Muff Potter don't
know nothing about this.
How's he supposed t0
say something?
- Tell me why
he don't know nothing.
- 'Cause he just happened
t0 get clunked out
as lnjun Joe did it.
- Oh, damn!
- Huck, are you sure you
can keep a lid on this?
- Now, Tom, you know we got
to keep a lid on this.
We have t0.
♪♪ the devil lnjun Joe finds
out that we ratted him out,
he don't get hung,
he'll snuff us out for sure.
We don't want that.
- Huck, we need t0 swear
not t0 tell a soul
a single word.
- I swear.
- S0 just repeat after me.
Huck Finn and Tom Sawyer...
- "Huck Finn and
Tom Sawyer..."
- ...s0lemnly swear t0 keep
their traps shut...
- "...s-- uh, s0--
solemnly swear
t0 keep their
traps shut..."
- ...and not t0 tell a
single, solitary soul...
- "...and not t0 tell a
single, solitary soul..."
- ...a single word.
- "...a single word."
- Unless they want t0 die
in their tracks and rot.
- "Unless they--" Well, that
last part's kind 0f rough,
- don't you think there, Tom?
- Needs t0 be.
♪♪
(gasps)
- Finally, I caught you.
Young man,
this deserves punishment.
You will paint the
picket fence tomorrow.
- The whole fence?!
- Yes, picket by picket.
(door closes)
♪♪
(imitating steam whistle)
- Starboard! Starboard!
(continues imitating)
Hey, buddy.
Hey, my friend, heh.
That's a pretty
tough job, huh?
S0... I'm going
swimming, you know?
Wouldn't you not
like t0 come along?
Nah, what am I thinking?
Tom Sawyefd
prefer t0 work.
- You calling that work?
- S0, are-- are you
saying that...
that's not work,
what you got
going on right there?
- Maybe.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
But, I do know that I'm
having the time 0f my l ♪♪e.
(scoffs)
- Come on, Tom Sawyer,
cut it out.
You're really trying t0 tell
me that you're having fun?
- Well, believe it or not,
I'm having a lot 0f fun.
You know, you don't
get the opportunity
t0 paint a picket fence
every day.
You just don't have
the chance t0 have this much fun.
You know what I mean,
booga-bean?
- Ha, Tom.
My good, good friend.
L-- could l, uh, think I--
think I might, uh--
Mind  ♪♪ I give it a try?
- Nuh-uh, Ben,
buddy man.
Auntie Polly is
real particular
about how it's done
and about who do it, too.
She is proud 0f her
picket fence.
This is precision
work right here.
This white picket fence
is out here through thick
and through thin.
I really don't think that
there is one in 1,000
who can do this job the way
it's meant t0 be done.
Well, maybe one
in 2,000, maybe.
- Now, come on,
give me the brush.
I'll give you a piece
0f my apple, 'kay?
- Now, come on, Ben.
What kind 0f fair
sportsmanlike is that?
What is an apple against
a whole picket fence?
- Okay, then,
I'll give you my shirt.
- N0, Ben, I do not
want your shirt.
I do not want your shirt.
- Okay, Tom Sawyer.
I'm gonna make you an offer
that you can't squawk at.
I know just how much you
want a switchblade kn ♪♪e
just like mine.
S0, you know what,
Tom Sawyer?
I'm gonna give you
my switchblade kn ♪♪e.
That's right.
Pretty good offer.
Come on.
Thanks, man.
This is pretty fun.
- Yeah, it's very fun.
♪♪
- Mark Twain: Even having
won Ben over,
Tom took advantage
0f the opportunity to acquire
- a set 0f marbles from Billy Thatcher.
- Okay.
- John Miller got in
through his offering
- Okay.
- 0f a harmonica in excellent condition.
- Yeah.
- And so on it went.
Without his even knowing it,
- Tom learned a very important
- Okay.
- Nah.
- human law having t0 do
with transfer and trade.
T0 raise the desire 0f
another individual,
then there is nothing
more necessary than t0 make
that object 0f desire
d ♪♪ficult t0 reach.
(overlapping chatter)
(loud tapping)
Mark Twain: By mid-day,
the awful news
had spread throughout
the entire town like lightning.
A murder had taken place.
At the murder scene,
a bloody kn ♪♪e was found
next t0 the victim
that was ident ♪♪ied
t0 belong t0 Muff Potter.
(overlapping chatter)
(chatter continues)
- man: They got him! Over there!
(crowd murmuring)
- man: They're bringing him.
Hey, it's Muff Potter.
Hey look, they're
bringing him out.
(chatter begins anew)
(chatter stops)
- l-- I didn't d0 it, folks.
I swear t0 God.
All 0f you.
(crowd murmuring)
- ls this your kn ♪♪e?
(murmuring continues)
- man: That crook.
- You tell them, Joe.
- Joe: What should I say,
except how it happened?
I saw it all.
I didn't say nothing till now
'cause Muff's my buddy.
There was argument,
pretty hot.
Don't know
exactly about what.
All I do know is that Muff
pulled that kn ♪♪e out
and rammed it
into Doc's guts.
(overlapping shouting)
(crowd shouting
"Hang him!")
(overlapping shouting
intens ♪♪ying)
(gunshot)
- woman: Now, just hold your horses!
For your information,
and it's nothing new,
but we just happen t0 have
a judge in this town,
and we also have laws!
Even though I see
that some 0f you folks
want t0 take it into
your own hands.
But what  ♪♪ he
happens t0 be innocent?
(crowd murmuring)
You all know
Muff Potter for years.
He is entitled t0
a fair trial
which he is going t0 get.
S0, Sher ♪♪f,
what are you waiting for?
- Take him t0 the jail.
(overlapping chatter)
- man: You got lucky, Muff Potter!
- Take him!
- Sooner or later, you're gonna hang!
- Man, Tom, you were chattering
away in your sleep.
I didn't get
t0 sleep a wink!
_ whafd you say?
- Tell me, Tom,
what's troubling you?
- Auntie Polly,
just dumb stuff.
- Dumb stuff?
I heard words
like, "Blood.
Blood.
That's blood!"
I heard that a lot.
You moaned and
said, "Please...
please, don't torture me.
I won't tell!"
- It must be that
awful murder.
I've been having
nightmares myself.
- You see, Aunt Polly?
We're all having
bad dreams.
♪♪
(birds chirping, splashing)
- Here you g0, Potter,
little bit 0f bacon,
some bread, and
a pack 0f cigarettes.
- Wow.
Thanks, Tom.
You and Huck
are good boys, I gotta say.
- Yeah, Muff,
it's okay.
Tom: You know what me--
you and me
gonna do?
- What?
- We're gonna
bust him out.
- Tom, you
losing your marbles?
- Yeah.
N0, I'm not
losing my marbles,
and, yeah, we're gonna
get him out 0f there.
- Say we do
get him out.
What the heck then?
- "What the heck," Huck?
We get him out 0f the joint,
out 0f the town,
out 0f the state,
out 0f the country.
He's gonna make
tracks t0 Europe
where he can't be hung.
(sighs)
- Well... Okay, okay, say we
get him t0 Europe.
What's he gonna do
over there?
Or better yet, how is
he gonna get over there?
- Well, you're just
gonna have t0 trust me
'cause I got a plan.
♪♪
(tapping)
- Huck: Tom, look!
We got the tools right here
t0 do the job!
I say we bust a hole
through this here wall
and then just get him out.
- Would you
please hush, Hucky?
How am I supposed
to concentrate
and come up with
the perfect solution
with you chatter-boxing
the entire time?
Hold the lamp.
I got an idea.
We're not gonna g0
through the wall.
N0, we're gonna
g0 under the wall.
Yeah, that's how
we're gonna do it.
Just like I've read it's been done
in lots 0f my books.
Here we g0,
right here's the spot.
- What the heck
are you doing, Tom?
- Hucky, can't you see that
I'm digging a tunnel
under this confounded wall?
- Well, how long you reckon
that's gonna take, Tom?
- There was this
guy held, locked up
in a cellar or dungeon
in a castle
near the ocean or
something like that,
somewhere over in France
or something like that--
you know, somebody
0f importance--
and so, this count
started digging.
And how long do you think
he needed t0 get through
the solid rock
0f that castle?
- I don't know.
I figure about
a month or so?
- N0, incorrect, wrong.
He needed 37 years.
- Well, I don't think
we got that long.
I mean,
by the time we do that,
Muff Potter will be
either hung high
or probably be dead from
old age or something.
- Now, come on, do you
honestly and truly think
that we're gonna need
37 years t0 get through
this little bit
0f earth, huh?
He was sitting on solid rock
and he only had one kn ♪♪e.
We got two.
And, Huck, for someone
who can't read and write,
you're pretty smart.
(laughs)
But, I have read practically every topic
that's ever been printed
on this book.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I don't care
how the counts
are doing it
in France.
All we need is a shovel
and a pickaxe
t0 get the job done.
♪♪
(grunting)
(Muff snoring)
(sn ♪♪f5)
He is pretty drunk.
Hope we don't gotta
carry him out like this.
- Don't worry, Hucky.
He'll be okay by the morning.
Let's get outta here.
- What?
Well, I thought we came here
t0 break him out today.
- Yeah, Hucky, we will,
but not just yet.
♪♪
Let's make tracks.
(sighs)
- After all this hard work,
we're losing precious time.
I mean, what happens  ♪♪ we
come back tomorrow?
They're gonna hang
an innocent man.
That poor guy'll be
strung up for nothing.
- Huck, we're gonna get him
out in the morning.
A break like this needs
t0 be planned t0 detail.
Otherwise,
they're gonna get Muff
before he even notices
that he's on the run.
(Qrunts)
Now, let's get outta here.
- Oh, better tum
this light off.
♪♪
(whispering)
- Potter! Potter, wake up!
- It's empty.
There's nobody in there.
Hucky, you hear me?
♪♪
. Hyah!
- Damn it, Huck.
Potter's gone.
- He is gone.
I can't believe it.
What are we
gonna do now?
- T0 be honest,
I don't know.
But I do know that, without us,
he's not getting too far.
- Man: All right, boys.
It's right up here.
- Damn, damn, damn!
We gotta cover
our tracks!
G0! G0! Go!
- Man: Get up, Potter!
Come on!
Time to go!
- You know we's
here, Potter!
HE'S gone!
- Man 1: Crawled through it
or something.
- Man 2: He ain't in here!
- I don't know where he is.
- Let's get him!
- Man 1: Come on, let's g0 get him.
- Man 2: Well, he can't be far.
Come on, boys.
Come on!
- Hyah!
Come on! Hah!
(crickets chirping)
- Mark Twain: Now, there was
l ♪♪e in this small town.
Muff Potter was found about
two miles outside 0f town
in a dilapidated
one room shack.
But, before he was sent
back t0 jail, he was memorably
tarred and feathered.
(overlapping chatter)
- Tom: I can't watch this.
I'm gonna be sick.
- Come on, Tom.
(gavel banging)
- Order in the court.
- Yeah, and I saw Muff Potter
washing in the creek.
- Yeah, but that is not so
out 0f the ordinary,
someone bathing
in the creek.
- It dam tooting is,
'cause everybody in town
knows that Muff
rarely washes.
("Qht laughter)
- prosecutor: ls it possible that
Muff Potter washed himself
after the act 0f murder,
removing all traces 0f blood,
after the brutal stabbing
0f the good Doc Robinson?!
(crowd gasping)
And are you sure that
this is one 0f the kn ♪♪es
that you sold from
your store?
- Objection!
- Objection taken.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
N0 further questions.
- The court calls the defense.
We have no further questions,
Your Honor.
(overlapping chatter)
- Now, what in God sakes
is going on in here?
Can you not even try t0 do so,  ♪♪
you would defend this poor man?
- Mark Twain: Towards the end
0f the second day 0f trial,
word went around that
lnjun Joe's testimonial
is rock solid, and he has
no shadow 0f a doubt
about how the decision
0f the jury will lean.
- Y'all know there's no visitors.
This better be good.
- Just want t0 bring
Muff some smokes.
- All right.
- And you better know that
this is a high profile,
high security zone.
- Hey, Potter,
you got visitors.
- Hey, Muff,
how's it going?
Uh, we brought you
something.
- Wow.
Thank you, fellas,
you're real chums.
- Uh, Muff, are you
all right?
- What am I supposed t0 say?
When you sit here
and wait
and you're
so close t0 dying
an unnatural death for something
you didn't want t0 do,
then you know
how good l ♪♪e is.
And Joe, bless him,
meant well,
but he'd be better off
t0 let it g0
so he don't get
pulled in deeper.
- Let it g0?
Let what g0?
- The break-out.
That just made
things worse.
Just realized that
I had a real friend.
And-- and I'm happy.
I've got three.
You guys and Joe.
(sn ♪♪fs)
Mmm.
- Several 0f our most
upstanding citizens
have sworn witnessing events
so out 0f the ordinary
that any question 0f doubt
can immediately be erased.
This horrible crime committed
by the accused, Muff Potter,
has been shown
t0 be his and his alone.
(crowd murmuring)
The prosecution requests
on behalf 0f
the citizens 0f this fine town
against the accused
Muff Potter
death by hanging.
(crowd murmuring)
- Your Honor,
members 0f the assembly,
at the start
0f this trial,
due t0 the overwhelming
evidence
and inf0rmati0n's detrimental
t0 the name 0f the accused,
we attempted t0 plea
for a less harsh sentence
based on his, in the past, reputation.
We no longer wish
t0 take this stand.
Because, from this moment on,
we are dealing with
a completely new situation.
The defense wishes
it t0 be known
that it now has the fullest intention
t0 save our client
from the untimely demise at
the end 0f a hangman's noose.
(crowd gasping)
Let it be noted
that new evidence,
shortly t0 be presented,
will beyond a shadow 0f a doubt
free Muff Potter from all
burdens and charges.
The defense wishes t0 call
t0 the stand a new witness.
Please call t0 the stand
Mr. Thomas Sawyer.
(crowd murmuring)
♪♪
- judge: Put your hand on the Bible.
D0 you swear t0 tell
the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
- Yeah--
uh, yes, sir.
L-- I mean t0 say,
I swear t0 tell the truth.
- Very good, Tom.
Very good.
Now, take a seat, son.
- Thomas Sawyer, where were
you on June 17th at midnight?
Now, Tom, just tell us.
Where were you on
the before-mentioned night?
- At the graveyard, sir.
- Okay, Tom, now, for those
in the back row
who may not
have heard you,
please repeat that
a little bit louder.
- I was at
the graveyard, sir.
- At the graveyard.
And where in
the graveyard were you?
- Uh, I was near t0
Ross Williams's grave.
- Were you alone?
- Yes, sir.
I was alone that night.
- Young man, was there
anything else
that may have been
out 0f the ordinary
that we absolutely should
be made aware of?
- Uh, yeah.
There was a sound,
and, well, that made me unsure
0f what should be going on
at that-- like you said,
that untimely hour,
and for just that
reason, Your Honor,
I was obliged t0 keep
a discreet cover,
and so I stayed
in the shadows.
- Defense attorney: You stayed
in the shadows?
Are you trying t0 tell us
that you were hiding?
- Yes, sir, I was hiding
behind the tree.
The-- the elm next
t0 Williams's grave.
- And about how far from that grave
is that wise old elm?
- The distance is about the same
between you and me right now.
- Well, let me
get this straight.
You were alone
at midnight in the graveyard
and you heard sounds,
and you hid.
Did anything
else happen?
♪♪
(crowd gasping)
(shattering)
(overlapping shouting)
(gunshot, crowd screaming)
(horse whinnying)
' Hiyah!
♪♪
(gunshot)
(overlapping shouting)
' G0!
(horse whinnying)
- Mark Twain: A mute Spaniard had
been hanging around the town
for a few days.
He had long white hair
and he was wearing dark glasses.
N0 one knew where he came from
or what he wanted.
(thunder crashing)
♪♪
- N0!
Please, no!
Huck!
What the fudge you
trying t0 do t0 me?!
You scared me out
0f my wits!
- Tom, you broke
our pact!
Remember, the one
that we agreed to?
Now, you know lnjun Joe ain't
gonna take this lightly, don't you?
- Well, I didn't say a word about
you, so you're still in the clear.
- That don't matter.
There's a killer on the loose.
You're in danger
and I'm scared.
I'm getting outta here.
- Huck, where you gonna g0?
(thunder rumbling)
- I don't know.
But, I'll tell you one thing,
I'm getting far away from here.
- Huck, I know
where we're gonna g0,
and I'm gonna be with you.
Come on.
See that old wreck?
- Tom, there's no way
that boat's empty.
We should g0 back.
- Never! You'd have t0 be
out 0f your mind
t0 be on a wreck like that.
(thunder crashing)
- It looks like me.
(laughing)
- man: I caught you,
you little snake.
- Hucky, where are you?
- Man: You thought that
I didn't see you.
I don't want you
talking t0 them.
- Tom?
- They could be onto us.
- Man 2: Oh believe me, I did not
talk and nobody was there.
I was all alone.
- Tom, we ought t0
get outta here.
This ain't smart.
Come on. Come on.
- Man 2: I was on the other
side when it happened.
- Yeah, Huck,
maybe you're right.
- Man 1: You're a real filthy rat.
What, you thought you could
get away with
all the dough?
(laughing)
They don't know
what's going on.
♪♪
(metallic clanging)
- Windy.
- I'm gonna put a piece 0f lead
- in your head.
- Windy, I swear.
I ain't gonna
spill the beans.
Not a single,
solitary syllable.
Please, let me g0.
- Put your piece away,
Windy.
Don't kill him.
At least, not now.
- Thank you, Joe.
- In less than a half hour,
he'll be resting 0n the ground,
and a drowned corpse is always
less incriminating
than a corpse
with a hole in it.
- Please, I won't
say a word.
Please, I swear.
- Windy: I'm sure you
won't say nothing.
- TOrnQ
- Come on, Hucky, let's get
outta here, like now!
G0, g0, g0!
G0!
- Tom, the boat!
"'5 gone!
- Come on, Hucky,
we gotta get outta here!
G0!
(gflSps)
- Over there! The raft!
- Huck!
- Quick, it's going down! It's sinking!
- G0!
- G0, g0!
- Come on.
Agh!
Come on, Hucky.
(grunting)
(boat creaking)
(metal groaning)
(light water splashing)
♪♪
- Mark Twain: Just three miles
from Saint Petersburg
at a spot where the Mississippi
is a little over a mile wide,
and where an excellent
hideaway exists 0n an uninhabited thin
and woodsy piece
0f free-floating land,
was the Jackson Island.
♪♪
- Hucky, wake up.
Wake up!
- Come on, Huck! Wake up!
- Okay.
- Let's g0 catch
some game.
(duck quackinq)
(sizzling, fire crackling)
(distant boom)
- I'd sure like t0 know
what that sound was.
- It sounded
really awkward.
(two booms echoing)
- Well, it ain't thunder,
that's for sure.
- Come on, Hucky.
Somehow, I know
that sound.
♪♪
- man: Just stay
close t0 the embankment!
- Got any idea what
that might be?
- William, you got
anything?!
- Huck, I know what's going on.
- Nothing here!
- I know exactly
what's going on.
(boom)
Tom: S0me0ne's drowned.
- Huck: Oh yeah!
- That's what's happening.
Yeah, n0w-- now I know.
Like last summer,
they did the same thing
- when Bill Turner died.
- Yeah.
- Man: Might have got hung up
on that sand bar!
- Huck: I'd like t0 be
over there right now.
Give an arm and a leg t0 know
who they're looking for.
- Man: It gets real
shallow here. Yeah.
- Huck!
- Yeah.
- Man, 0h man, Huck!
- Man: How's the west bank?
I bet I know who
they're looking for.
I bet I know whose drowned.
- Huck: What makes you
so sure you know?
- 'Cause 0f the circumstances
the last couple 0f days.
- Man: You might look
through them bulrushes!
- I ain't following you, Tom.
- Think, Huck, think.
- They're looking for us.
- Well, we're right here.
- Man: Yeah, let's just do that!
- Sure we are, Huck.
And we know that,
but they don't.
- Now, after all that,
the curiosity and temptation
0f hearing what was being
said about his postmortem
was just too tantalizing
not t0 follow up on.
Now, Tom had no
intention 0f abandoning
his best friend, Huck,
but he just had t0 know,
would he be missed?
Would he even be missed
or wept over?
S0, he waited until Huck
was fast asleep.
Just before midnight,
he left Jackson Island
and waded over
t0 the shallow water
on the Illinois side
0f the river.
And then, he waited till
just the last ferry 0f the day,
what was called
the night ferry.
And he jumped on
and stowed away,
and he crept into
one 0f the dinghies
so he wouldn't be discovered
as a stowaway
or a presumed dead man.
And then he made his way
back t0 Saint Petersburg.
Mark Twain: For the return trip,
he borrowed the canoe
from Joe Harper,
naturally without telling Joe.
♪♪
(water splashing)
- Huck, man! Huck! Wake up!
- What?
- Wake up, Huck!
- Yeah?
- While you were sleeping,
I was out and about
figuring out what
the world is up to,
and I gotta tell you,
this coming Sunday's
gonna be our day--
yours and mine.
This coming Sunday,
everyb0dy's gonna be praying
and crying, and rejoicing, redeeming,
and doing whatever else they do t0
set a soul on the right path.
And the things I heard.
You know, when you're alive
and kicking, nobody cares.
But, when they're dead,
everybody just loves you.
(bell ringing)
(crowd murmuring)
(floorboards creaking)
(coughing)
- Brothers and sisters
0f the congregation,
we are brought here today
t0 mourn the loss
0f one 0f our own.
This is a day 0f great sadness,
due t0 the untimely departure
0f one 0f our most
g ♪♪ted young people.
The spirit 0f good.
Because I am the power,
and the eternal l ♪♪e,
and any mere mortal
who would doubt
the resurrection,
who would doubt...
(gasps)
What?
(overlapping murmuring)
- Oh, Tom.
My God, Tom.
Oh, Tom.
- Come on, Aunt Polly,
s0meb0dy's gotta be happy
that Huck's still around
other than me.
- Well, 0f course we're all
happy that Huck is here.
Please, let me give you a hug,
poor motherless boy.
(overlapping chatter)
- man: Where's he goin'?
- Becky.
♪♪
And he travels
all over the world,
he stays in the best hotels.
I'm gonna be a musician
when I get bigger.
- Oh, that sounds
just wonderful, Tom.
- Oh yeah, and they
get good pay, too.
Almost a buck a day.
At least that's what
Ben Rogers told me.
Hey, Becky, mind  ♪♪ I ask
you a personal question?
- N0, Tom Sawyer,
I don't mind.
- Have you ever--
ever been engaged?
- N0.
Of course not.
Never.
Um, Tom?
What's that mean, anyway?
- Oh, you gotta
try it out.
- Oh, 0h,
l-- I don't know, Tom.
How does that work?
_H0W?
Uh, well, it's as
easy as nothing.
All you gotta do is
say t0 a guy like me
that you'd never,
ever take another guy,
and then you kiss each other
and then that's it.
Everyone can do it.
- Kissing?
- Why on earth w0uld--
- Uh, yeah.
Uh, kissing is for...
0h, you know, 'cause they
always do that.
But first, you gotta say
that you love each other.
- Oh.
I d0n't-- I don't think
I want t0 be engaged.
- Y0u-- you don't
have t0 say it too loud.
You could even
whisper it real soft.
(whispers)
I love you.
Now, you whisper it
t0 me just like I did.
- Now, you tum
your face away,
and don't you say a word
0f this t0 anybody.
- Of course not, promise.
- I love you.
(giggles)
♪♪
- And from now on, you love
me and only me, okay?
And we can walk
t0 school together,
and we can walk home
from school together,
when no 0ne's looking,
0f course.
- Oh, how romantic.
- Sure is. What do you
think it was like
back when me and
Amy Lawrence was engaged?
(chuckles nervously)
Uh, here, Becky.
H0w'd you like
t0 have it?
Hey, Hucky.
S0, is this where
you've been hanging out?
- You know, Tom...
lnjun Joe was
a murderer,
but I imagine how
desperate he must have been
once he found out
the jig was up.
Man, he was probably
in a bad state.
- Yeah.
Who knows, someday...
we might turn out
t0 be murderers.
Yeah.
S0 where you been hanging
out the last couple 0f days?
I've been looking for you
high and low.
- Just been squatting
at the haunted house.
It's the only
dry place I know.
Besides, ever since
lnjun Joe's been gone,
pretty safe, too.
Hey, you see, Tom?
It ain't all
that bad in here.
Come home, hang up my stuff
in this wall closet.
And then, retire upstairs
t0 the bedroom at night.
Come on, I'll show you.
(chickens clucking)
- Wow.
This place is
a real home.
(men chattering)
Shh.
- Man:  ♪♪ you need t0 l ♪♪t 'em,
we'll get a mule or something.
- Huck: That's the deaf mute Spaniard.
- I told you no.
I don't like it and
I ain't gonna do it.
- Shut up, Windy.
- Mark Twain: The voice...
exactly that voice
took their breaths away
and sent chills down the spines
0f Tom and Huck instantly.
Simultaneously.
And, as a matter
0f fact,
there was no doubt in
a million that this voice
belonged t0 only one.
- You're right.
- Mark Twain: lnjun Joe.
- But, I'm telling you,
this time, leave it be!
- Injun Joe: What are we gonna do
with all that cash leftover?
- Don't know.
Windy: We leave it here.
Don't make sense
taking 'em out
before we're heading south.
650 is a lot
0f weight.
- Yeah, but you listen t0 me.
It could take a while
before the time is right.
(whispers)
- Get down. Get down.
- Injun Joe: This spot here
isn't right.
We need t0 bury it right,
and I mean deep.
(stones and dirt clattering)
(scraping)
(grunting)
(kn ♪♪e hitting wood)
I'm hitting a rotten
piece 0f wood here.
Nah, it's a crate, I think.
Come here and
give me a hand
so we can see just
what's down here.
- Windy: Wait, Joe.
- Joe: Ohh!
- Let me do it.
Come on, Joe.
Here.
There's money in it.
(laughing)
Look at it! Money!
- There's gotta be $1,000 dollars in there.
- Now, you don't have
t0 do that last job.
(laugl15)
(gflSps)
- That goes t0 show you don't
know anything about me,
and at least not enough.
I don't like it when s0me0ne's got
the upper hand on me.
I got a job t0 do before
I can leave this place.
- Windy: What are we gonna
do about this here?
Bury it back like
it was before?
- Joe: Let's get outta here.
- Windy: Wait.
(clattering)
- Joe: Time t0 move.
(rustling)
(chickens clucking faintly)
(Qrunts)
(chickens clucking)
(gunshot)
Get outta here before
they pluck our eyes out.
(coins jingl ♪♪lq,
Tom laughing)
(grunting,
st ♪♪led screaming)
(cougl15)
(Whispers)
- Hucky?
Hucky?
(whispers)
Huck!
- Howdy, Huck.
- Huh?
- Hucky.
_ Hm?
(grunting)
Howdy, Tom.
- You know, Huck,
that treasure rightfully
belongs t0 us.
- Yeah, now you're
really dreaming.
- Could be, but, uh...
we was there first,
and that's why it
belongs t0 us.
- You should tell that
t0 lnjun Joe.
- You know, Huck,
I don't know why
I didn't come up
with it before,
but uh...
down in the caves.
I'd have t0 say that
that's where they took the loot.
- Well, I ain't
going down there.
- Well,  ♪♪ you don't
wanna g0, that's fine,
but you at least
gotta cover me.
- Yeah.
Yeah,
I can do that.
All right.
- Now, you're being
sensible.
Now, you don't
lose strength
and I won't lose
strength neither.
♪♪
(creaking)
(sn ♪♪fing)
- Meow! Meow!
- Dam it!
Come on, Huck, let's get
outta here, come on!
- Mark Twain: Next day was the annual
archeological school outing.
This excursion would bring
the kids from Saint Petersburg
up t0 the McDouglas caves.
- S0, students, can you guess
what the name 0f the cave is?
Look up,
and you will see
these amazing big eyes.
Yes, the name 0f the cave
is the Big Eyes.
Please.
From this point on,
I will lead you,
and... Tom,
and you, Becky,
bring up the rear.
I'm counting on you two.
And remember what
I told you all.
Stay together.
(students whispering)
- "And remember what I told you:
stay together."
' Hm!
(giggles)
- Becky?
- Yeah?
- Oh, I gotta show you something.
Come over here.
- All right.
Follow me, my lady, into
the bowels 0f these caverns.
(laugl15)
♪♪
- Oh, isn't this
wonderful, Tom?
- Yeah, Becky,
it sure is marvelous.
(giggles)
(wings flapping)
(shrieks)
Come on, Becky, over here.
Come on, come on over here!
- TOrnQ
- Tom: It's okay, Becky.
I'm here.
Nothing can happen.
- Tom.
Oh, my God.
Group.
Our class,
they'll be looking for us.
- Yeah, Becky, you're right.
It's time t0 g0 back.
- D0 you think you can
find the way back out?
I don't have
the slightest clue.
- That is the least
0f our worries.
We should find
a d ♪♪ferent way out
so that we don't have t0
g0 through that again.
Come on over here.
- All right.
You know Becky, I think it'd be
better  ♪♪ we just light this torch.
- All right.
- Hold this.
(screaming)
(bell ringing)
(overlapping chatter)
- Mark Twain: On Sunday morning,
alarming news spread through
the first 0f the congregation
and then the town,
and eventually the country,
demanding the attention
0f both young and old.
Tom Sawyer and
Becky Thatcher did not return
with the rest 0f the group
from McDouglas caves
and have not been
heard 0f since.
- But they must
still be in the cave!
- Yes, they're still in there!
They have t0 look for them!
- Yes, my darling.
And that's exactly
what they did.
(overlapping chatter)
- Oh, my God.
Without light, we'll
never get out 0f here.
D0 you think that they're
looking for us, Tom?
- Yeah, Becky.
I know that someone's
looking for us.
(qying softly)
What are you thinking,
Becky?
- What day it is and  ♪♪
it's day or nighttime.
- Man 1: Becky?!
- Man 2: Let's split up
in three groups.
- Man 1: Tom!
- Man 2: You guys check out
Big Eyes.
- Man 1: Hello?!
We're staying down
in the lower quarter.
- Hey, stay together.
- Be careful 0f
them cl ♪♪fs!
- Becky! Tom!
(overlapping shouting)
- Hello?
- Where are you?
(crying)
And...
we're never
gonna get out 0f here.
- Sure we are. Look, I'm gonna
feel my way over there.
And you're gonna stay right
here until I get back, okay?
- N0, please, please,
don't leave me alone in here.
- Becky, I have t0.
I'll be right back.
You stay right here.
- Don't move.
- Please!
- Man: Hello?
- man 2: Tom, where are you?
- You over here?
- Come on out!
Becky,
where are you?
- Man: Stay together!
(overlapping shouting)
- man: There's footprints
over this way!
- Man 2: They must have gone
up t0 the forbidden caves.
- Becky Thatcher's hair band.
' Becky!
- Stay together!
(men continue shouting)
- Hello? Hello?
Hey, hey, hey!
We're over here!
S0, this
is number two.
♪♪
Come on, Becky.
We gotta get away!
- All right.
- Come on!
Tom: Come on!
This is n0t-- n0t--
Over here.
This is the way.
- Come on, Becky.
- Okay.
(screams)
♪♪
Tom: Come on, Becky.
Come on.
Through here.
G0! Quick!
Hurry!
(grunting)
- Mark Twain: Some believe that
those missing youngsters
aren't even stuck
in the cave,
but rather that they
would have somehow drowned
and have been flushed
out onto the river.
That's the reason for
all those floating lights.
They were meant t0 aid
in the search effort.
(bird calling)
♪♪
Mark Twain: There she was again,
that mighty Mississippi.
Wide, endless,
powerful as always.
Oh, that was without a doubt
one 0f the nicest nights
that town or any town
would ever experience.
Long into the wee hours 0f
the morning, the town ate,
drank, danced,
and was merry.
All but the two guests
0f honor were present,
since the ordeal 0f the last
few days took their toll
on their stamina.
They were safely
and soundly fast asleep
in their respective beds.
A day and a night
under those conditions
were not so easy
t0 shake off.
(water splashing)
- Tom: Start turning.
Start turning.
(laughing)
- See that there, way up high?
- Yeah.
- On the mountain where
the landslide was, that's it.
Where it's white and rocky,
that is the opening
t0 our brand-new world,
buddy.
Yippee!
- Let me tell you,
Huckleberry buddy,
from this spot, we can reach
the hole that saved Becky and me
from a certain demise.
And not everybody
can fit in it,
and it's so close,
you can spit on it.
See, Hucky,
didn't I tell you
that this is the most
hidden cave opening
in all 0f
the United States 0f America?
♪♪
(whooshing)
(gflSps)
- L00kie there.
- What's that?
- S0meb0dy-- s0meb0dy's body.
- That's gotta be Windy.
- Yeah.
Can be pretty sure that he didn't
die 0f natural causes.
- Injun Joe.
- Injun Joe and that
treasure.
It's just plain,
old-fashioned greed.
Come on, Huck.
- Mark Twain: And that is
exactly what it was.
- And over here, Hucks,
we're gonna see number two.
- Lookie there.
- Well, you best get in there.
- Yeah, hold this.
Right there.
(Huck grunts)
Tom: Wow.
Whoa, look at that,
Hucky.
(cocks gun, gun clicks)
(chuckles)
Where are
the saddlebags?
Hey, Hucky,
lookie here.
Hand prints and drops 0f
tallow on this one side,
but nothing on the other.
(scraping)
(kn ♪♪e hitting wood)
- What is that?
- You hear that, too?
One second.
(Qrunts)
(laughing)
Hucky.
Tom: The saddlebag!
(laughing)
We're rich!
- We're rich!
- Come on, let's get it and get out 0f here.
- Yeah, yeah!
(laugl15)
Come on,
come on, Hucky.
(match striking)
- Let's see what
we got here.
Mr. Thomas.
Smarty Pants Sawyer
and his worthless buddy.
What have our Boy Scouts
found on their journey?
- Nothing. Just a lamp.
Take a look for yourself.
- What'cha gonna do
with the lamp?
- Uh, well, first--
first, you gotta rub it,
you know, t0 make it work.
Use your hand
or a cloth or a towel.
Whatever works, really.
But after you rub it,
a genie'll come out.
The whole place will
fill with smoke
and you
can't see nothin'.
Um, but the genie'll give you
almost anything you want.
Gold, silver,
rubies, cigarettes.
Whatever you want.
Matter 0f fact,
Tom's got a book on it.
Don't you, Tom?
- Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Uh, it's--
it's all in there.
- Yeah, yeah.
What's the-- what's the name
- 0f the book you got there?
- Uh...
Uh... uh...
- Uh, "Aladdin"!
"Aladdin and the Magic Lamp."
Yeah.
That's the name 0f it.
(gunshot)
- You little fish heads
could have had a future
♪♪ you would have kept your
nose out of my business.
But too bad.
Now, not even Aladdin
can help you.
(clicks)
♪♪
' Hey, Joe!
- Tom: Grab the saddlebags!
♪♪
(grunting)
(overlapping chatter)
- All right, Mrs. Douglas.
Be careful.
Up you g0.
- Mark Twain: The widow Mrs. Douglas
opened her heart and her home
t0 offer Huckleberry
the best possible future
and everything that
goes along with it.
- Hey Becky,
you wanna see what I got?
Then just ask me
for the time.
- Boys: Whoa!
- Judge Thatcher: Hey, Tom.
How is our treasure
chest finder doing?
Anything, uh, interesting
at the McDouglas caves?
- Uh, no, Mr. Thatcher.
Should anything
be going on?
- Exactly that.
Should anything
be going on?
Now, Tom, from now on,
nothing will be going on there
because we've, uh, taken some
special safety measures.
- Safety measure--
what kind 0f safety measures?
- Uh, well, indirectly,
thanks t0 you,
the safety measures
include, um,
guided trips with constant
accounting 0f participants.
In addition, we've locked
the entrance t0 the cave
with a triple closure
made 0f steel.
Uh, that means
no more entry
without the permission
0f my office.
And... I personally
have the key.
- Well, sir,
I think that somebody
still might be in there.
- Who on God's earth
could be in there?
- Injun Joe.
- G0 first.
(overlapping chatter)
- man: Careful fellas,
he might be armed.
- Man 2: Yeah, he's killed before.
- Open the door.
- Ready?
- He's in there.
- What's happening there.
- Mark Twain: Tom was moved
with what he saw
because he knew
from his own experience
how that troubled man suffered
in those final hours.
He felt sorrow,
but the feeling 0f relief
and the safety was
even stronger,
because lnjun Joe was dead.
♪♪
Mark Twain: Vacations have begun,
and Tom was traveling
with Aunt Polly and Sid, just as it
happened each and every year,
t0 their relatives down
the river in Saint Louis.
- Aunt Polly: Steward?
Steward, could you help us
get our luggage on board?
Aunt Polly: Tom!
Come here!
It's time for you
t0 come on board.
- I'm coming, Aunt Polly,
just a minute.
Now look, Huck...
I know that it's
been hard,
but it ain't
that d ♪♪ficult, huh?
And even though the old widder may
give you some problems,
she only
means the best.
And, when I get back,
we're finally gonna form
a Sawyer-Finn gang.
- Aunt Polly: Tom!
- Just a minute,
Aunt Polly, I'm coming!
Dagnabbit.
(ship horn blowing)
- All yours now.
The widder was gonna
confiscate it anyways, so...
ain't no more use t0 me.
- Okay, but just until we
form the gang, okay?
- Tom Sawyer!
- Just a second,
Aunt Polly!
Take care, Huckleberry.
See you.
(ship horn blowing)
♪♪
- Mark Twain: Then suddenly,
just like that,
the day t0 day mundane,
barren, and empty ritualistic l ♪♪e
returned t0 this lonely
part 0f the world
here on the west shore
side 0f the Mississippi.
When one day Huck's
long lost dad showed up in town
and demanded his share
0f the fortune,
he realized that money
doesn't equal happiness.
Huck managed t0 escape his father,
the Widow Douglas,
and what's even more important,
so-called civilization.
That didn't really work for him.
Together with
runaway slave Jim,
he decided t0 let
the Mississippi take them
t0 a place far away
where you can leave
in freedom and without
the restraints 0f
civilized society.
- Jim: Widow Miss Douglas
didn't really wanna sell me.
Brotha, she was wailing
the whole day.
But, she didn't
have much choice.
Times are hard and she
really needed the money.
You can't get that kind 0f
money together.
Besides, I'd-a never again
get t0 see my w ♪♪e and kids.
- Well, Jim, now you
can't see your w ♪♪e
and kids neither, 'cause
a, well, runaway slave
ain't got too much
chance for surviving.
- This might sound funny,
but I got me this here.
This...
this is a map.
And the ticket
t0 freedom.
My freedom.
Now, here we are.
- Right here?
- Mm-hmm.
Now, we take this
down here.
♪♪ I can make it
down here near the cable
where the Ohio River
and the Mississippi River flow,
then I can make it up here.
Then I could make it
up t0 the free states.
And once I get there,
brother,
I'm gonna
get me a good job
and make me enough money
t0 buy my whole family back.
(ship horn blowing)
- Mm-hmm.
Jim! Jim! Jim!
Steamboafs coming
straight for us!
- Whoa, whoa, don't you worry,
Mr. Huckleberry.
He ain't gonna touch us.
You just pass me the tiller.
Here.
♪♪
- girl: What happened
t0 Huck and Jim?
- Oh, those two?
Well, they floated
down the Mississippi
toward the town 0f Cairo.
There, they were
t0 board a steamboat
t0 get t0 the free states,
but carelessness
was responsible for them
t0 override that entry
and regrettably
send them even deeper
into the southern states--
and 0f course,
deeper and deeper
into the slave regions.
- Has Tom ever seen
Huck again?
- N0.
N0, they never saw
each other again.
♪♪