Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Wake up!
Wake up! Yee-ha!
- Oh, it is.
- Wake up!
Yeah!
Get back in the house. Hurry up.
Patty, Elizabeth! You get in here!
Now!
Wake up!
I told you it was
that damn new kid again.
Don't make me come up
after you there, boy!
Wake up!
Excuse me.
Either of you boys have any gum?
I got it.
Well, thanks a lot for the ride, fellas.
Thanks a lot.
Easy, easy, chief.
What's the matter?
Sheriff didn't feed you a banana?
All right, boys.
Nobody said to stop working.
That's right, boys, hard work works.
Mornin', Mr Benedict.
- One, two, three.
- Twenty-seven.
- Twenty-eight.
- One, two, three.
- Twenty-nine.
- Thirty.
All right. Sit-ups. Hit the deck.
And ready.
Up... down.
Up... Come on, Mr Blaine.
You can do better.
Keep it up.
Up... down.
Let's go, let's go! Up!
Come on. You think this is hard? Up...
...down. Life is hard. Up.
- I can't do it.
I will not tolerate you quitting on me.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- All right.
You got yourself an extra half hour
of callisthenics after the boys go in.
Look at me. I got 30 years on you.
He ain't you, Benedict.
I know that's what you want,
but he ain't you.
You just got yourself another hour.
Make it two and you got a deal.
Welcome home.
Mr Benedict.
Billy, bring that ladder.
- Bradley.
- Huh?
Who is that?
Who?
Sara.
- What's she doing here?
- It's summer. Back from college.
That's not Sara.
That's too big to be Sara.
- She has...
- Tits.
Place looks great.
Doesn't it?
All right, Mr Tucker. That's enough.
Wait a minute.
Take these bags into the house, please.
Watch it! Hey!
- I have some fragile things in there.
- Mr Tucker, please be careful.
Get it into the barn right now!
- Who's that?
- He's the new boy. A handful.
Look at you, honey.
You light up this whole house.
I gotta get that.
Mr Tucker, take the bags upstairs.
Hello.
This is Eugene.
Yeah, well...
Look, would you please be careful?
Oops.
Mr Tucker, get these things picked up.
- What happened out there?
- Nothing.
If he gives you any trouble
just let me know.
I can take care of myself.
Of course you can.
Excuse me.
How about a whiskey, Junior?
Good song.
Hey, Molly,
come here and dance with us.
You wanna dance?
Sure.
- What are you doing, man?
- What?
I said, what are you doing?
No nigger music in here.
What's that in the juke for?
It ain't.
Let her go.
- You say something?
- Come on, be cool.
Cool?
- What kind of word is "cool"?
- Too many syllables?
Come on, Travis, leave him alone.
You're not from around here,
are you, boy?
You need a ride to the bus stop?
No thank you, sheriff.
Just here for a job, that's all.
- Music teacher, Benedict's place.
- Benedict expecting you?
Yes, sir, he is.
You enjoy making me look like a fool.
You do a pretty good job
of that yourself.
Let's go.
Y'all come back now.
I was hoping you'd come out.
I keep telling him we're old news
but he never was one
to keep up on current events.
Look, I run a club on the other side
of the tracks, so to speak.
- How's the booze?
- Terrible.
Step in sometime. Ask for Molly.
Hey, Molly.
How come that record was on the juke?
I slipped it in
when nobody was looking.
I'll see you around, Molly.
I'll definitely see you around.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You're more than qualified
for this job, Mr Cabe.
You're gonna find these kids
are damaged goods.
Some of them are orphaned,
others are sent here by their parents,
by the juvenile authorities,
a great pity.
A strong hand is what they need.
Discipline.
They need role models, Mr Cabe.
You don't have to worry about me.
You need somebody to get the boys
ready for the 4th of July concert.
I'm your guy.
I saw your sign when I
walked through the gate
and I agree with it.
I'll work hard with these boys
and I'll teach them their music.
Wake up.
- What are you gonna do about it?
- Do about what?
About what? About her.
Go over there and talk to her.
She wants to talk to you.
- No she doesn't.
- Yeah she does.
- No, really?
- You really think so?
- I know so.
You look fine. Go talk to her.
OK.
Go.
Wonder what he's thinking about.
I saw you looking gaga
at that girl in church.
No I wasn't.
Yeah, sure you weren't.
Oh, Alan! Oh, Alan!
Come fondle my massive milkers.
One, two, three and...
Quarter note, sharp attack.
Good.
Bradley, you've got to loosen up, man.
You're playing like a robot.
Try without this.
- I can't play without music.
- Try it.
I can't.
Jesse, you gonna joins us?
No.
- No?
- No.
Play chords with your left
and pick with the right.
- Pick with the right?
- Pick with the right.
Kinda like this, huh?
That's just the right look for you.
I know you better than you think.
If he don't want to participate,
I've got a job for him.
Mr Tucker.
Thanks.
Come on, let's go.
And one, two, three and...
- What is your problem?
- Excuse me?
You've taken some disliking to me.
Well, I don't much like you either.
So why don't you stay in your hole and
I'll stay as far away as possible, OK?
# Look at old Jesse there down in a hole
# He acts real tough
but he looks like a mole
What's your problem?
# His punishment was digging
in the mud and the sand
# When he could've been playing
with the boys in the band
Dick.
Come on, let's go.
- Get the lead out.
- Come on, come on.
Let's go.
Shut up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Jeez Louise.
What's wrong with you guys today?
You were bad before
but you're stinking up the place now.
- What was that music you were playing?
- We'd like to play that.
Yeah, it gave me a boner.
- Will you teach us?
- No.
- Why not?
- Mr Benedict wouldn't appreciate it.
Keep going, Jesse.
Everybody join in.
Toby, quarter notes on that.
- Quarter notes on that.
- Straight quarter notes?
One and three on the bass drum.
Add a backbeat.
Good.
Bradley.
Just play the...
It's not on here.
You'll get used to it.
Big boy, just play the bass line.
Like this:
Da-da-da-da.
Good.
It's called rock and roll, boys.
Only a select few
know about this right now,
but I'll tell you something,
in the not-too-distant future
it is gonna burn through this country
like a prairie fire.
You think you can handle it?
- You got the guts?
- Dang straight, man.
Well, you can't.
Not yet. You gotta get better. OK?
Now this is the deal.
You practice real hard
and you learn your music
for the show, and then...
...then we'll talk about rock and roll.
You guys gotta practice.
I hope you taste better than you look.
Come here, you stinkin' bird.
Get over here!
Let's go. Let's go up there.
Move out of the way, boys.
Coming through.
- Let's get it and go.
- Come on, hurry up.
Excuse me.
Hey, you guys,
know what would be great?
What?
- Start our own rock and roll band.
- Easy.
- Could we do that?
- We could.
Jesse, wanna join
our rock and roll band?
No.
- Beautiful.
- Most beautiful girl I ever saw.
- Only girl you ever saw.
- I'll kick your butt.
- Try it, blimpo.
- I'm gonna nail her.
What?
I'll light up Benedict's precious
daughter like a pinball machine.
What do you mean?
What do you mean what do I mean?
What do you think?
Yeah, sure you are.
You wanna bet? Huh?
Come on, you boys must have
a little chore allowance saved up.
Put your money where your big mouth is.
OK.
- I'll bet.
- Me too.
- How much, two dollars?
- Wait.
- We shouldn't bet about this.
- What's the matter? Chicken?
No, I'm not chicken,
I just don't think...
You shut up.
- You what?
- It's not right.
- She's a nice girl.
- So marry her.
Are you kidding me?
Look at her sitting back there.
That's Benedict's little pride and joy.
This'll teach him.
Fine, you don't want in? No problem.
- How about the rest of you guys?
- I'm in.
Psst.
Hey, Jesse. Jesse.
Hey, Sara.
How you doing?
Did you have a good ride?
- Nice legs. On you too, Sara.
- I've had enough.
Oops.
- Shut up.
- Regular Cary Grant.
Smooth move, ex-lax.
Hi.
You're not supposed to be in here.
No, it's OK,
I get invited in here quite a bit.
My father will be back.
- Do you want me to go?
- Do what you want?
- OK, I'll go.
- No, don't.
Listen, Sara, I'm really sorry
that I threw dirt on your feet.
You're the first pretty girl
we've had around and...
...I guess I got a little flustered.
- What are you doing?
- Just writing a letter for my father.
Is this a picture of you?
- Yes.
- Really?
Yeah.
I got a little picture too, actually.
- Are these your parents?
- Yeah.
Handsome couple. Where are they now?
They died.
- Oh.
- Yeah, in a car crash.
- I'm sorry.
- It's OK, it was a long time ago.
My mom died when I was eight.
I remember that she had this one freckle
on the end of her nose.
She would call it her kiss button.
Whenever I would touch it
she would give me a kiss.
Hey, what's the matter?
Nothing. Just hadn't
thought about it for a while.
Look, I should go.
Why?
I'll see you later.
- Try it without the sheet music.
- I can't play without the music.
I wanna see you after class.
OK, guys, and one, two, three...
- You scared?
- Yeah.
Yeah, me too. Stay there.
Stay there. Stay there.
All right. Go from there to here
without walking. No running either.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- I don't know.
Just use your imagination, man.
Come on. Come on.
Yeah, that's it.
- Now something else.
- What else?
I don't know, something else.
- Like what?
- Anything.
Walk like a monkey,
cluck like a chicken. I don't care.
- Monkeys don't cluck.
- Come on, just do it.
Come on.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Good, man.
- How long should I do this?
- Till you get it right.
Now come on. Come on, man.
Yes, yes, yes.
- What's up?
- Pork chops for dinner.
What a dick.
Hi.
- Hi.
I got something for you.
- It looked a little worse for the wear.
- Thanks.
It's an old frame of my mother's.
- You didn't have to...
- I...
OK.
Well, I'll talk to you later.
- Don't sleep much, do you?
- Uh-huh.
What are you running from?
What makes you think I'm running?
You're a runner all right.
- Morning.
- What are you doing up so early?
- Couldn't sleep.
This is what I was looking forward to
most about coming back here.
- Do you ride?
- No, we aren't allowed to ride them.
Pretty good at cleaning up
their crap, though.
Did you like the picture?
Yeah.
Listen, there's something
I need to tell you.
I never did get to thank you.
For the picture.
I love this time of morning.
Would you like to kiss me?
Now walk like a monkey
and cluck like a chicken.
You know, I've been thinking.
I've never done it before.
Maybe you could teach me.
- Teach you?
- Yeah.
'Cause it's going to be
a long, hot summer.
Mm-hmm.
Do you ever let other people touch it?
- You mean my guitar.
- Of course.
What else would I be talking about?
That's it. Just go. Let it go, man.
All right, now play it. One...
They are doing so much better.
They're starting to sound like a band.
It's your methods, Mr Cabe...
...in the classroom.
And those silly, stupid dances you're
teaching Kroft and Blaine in the field.
- I'm trying to make it fun for them.
- You didn't see them when they came.
Delinquents running around with gangs.
Control got them this far.
I am so sure everything you've done
for these kids is great.
Thank you.
I just feel there are other ways
of getting results.
Mr Cabe, I'm not gonna argue with you.
I can always get another music teacher.
- What do you want?
- Wanna hear some tunes.
No. No more records.
- Why not?
- You heard them all.
- We'll listen to them again.
- I can't.
- Why can't we?
- I just can't, OK?
It's Benedict, isn't it?
He found out.
It's OK. He gets to everybody
sooner or later.
Wait a minute.
- All right!
- Yes!
- OK, any of you guys got a radio?
- No. Why?
- Forget it.
- What?
What? I'm not gonna get you
cranked up over nothing. Forget it.
Come on, tell us.
All right.
There's this DJ I know about.
- What's a DJ?
- Don't you know nothing, man?
Tell him, Mr Cabe.
A DJ's a disc jockey,
a man who spins platters on the radio.
There's this one fella in particular,
out of Memphis I believe,
and he plays the hottest rock and roll,
I mean real scorchers.
Strictly underground stuff.
Now, he calls himself
the Midnight Rider.
Everybody has tried to shut him down.
Parents, school teachers, government.
President Eisenhower tried to
shut him down, but nobody could.
He's always one step ahead of the law.
Nobody can stop the Midnight Rider.
How can we hear him?
Well, like I said, you need a radio.
You probably even need a short wave
all the way out here to pick him up.
Now beat it.
I can fix the radio in the garage.
There's a book in class about radios.
- All we need is the pieces.
- Let's do it.
- Sure you don't want me to do this?
- No, I gotta do it.
Keep your eyes peeled.
Bradley! Bradley, come on!
What are you doing?
- What's that?
- This...
...is a project for science class.
We're getting extra credit for
taking apart radios and examining them.
You can do better than that.
We wanna listen to a radio show
that Mr Cabe told us about
and I need one of these to build
a short wave radio.
- What show?
- Midnight Rider.
Come on, he's coming!
Come on.
Go on, take it. Take it.
We listen to Midnight Rider in college.
Yeah?
Thank you, Sara.
You sort of cradle the neck
with your left hand.
And you rest this on your knee.
All right, let's say like a D chord.
- What?
- Nothing.
You put your first finger
in the second fret.
- Put this one here, that one there.
- Mm-hmm.
Now with your right...
You've got to hold on tighter here.
- OK.
- OK?
All right, now strum.
- That's good.
- That's bad.
- That was good. It was good.
- You know it sounds bad.
I've got it. In the bridge coming off
the verse, you play like before, right?
And then I'll answer you.
And we'll do it four times, right?
- It'll be perfect.
- Shut up, shut up, shut up.
Why don't you just
keep doing it? D chord.
I've got a problem.
- I guess Jesse's gonna win that bet.
- Shut up.
- Hi, Sara.
- Hi, Bradley.
- Did you get that radio working?
- Yeah. Thank you for that.
You OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What's wrong?
There's something I have to tell you.
A bet? A stupid bet?
Well, come on,
let's win that bet for you.
Come on, here I am.
- That's what I thought.
- Sara...
It started out as a bet,
but it's not about that anymore.
That's almost as good
as that lie about your parents,
or whoever those people
in the picture were.
You were using me
to get at my father, weren't you?
That what this was all about?
Well, I'm not my father, Jesse.
Now, let's start off with...
- Find the Midnight Rider.
- I'm trying to.
Are you out there,
brothers of the night?
- That's it.
- Are you listening?
Flying to you
on night-silent black wings.
Getting inside you, urging you,
telling you that tonight anything,
anything can happen.
Are your ears open?
Because the ears and not the eyes
are the windows of the soul.
Listen, my children.
Listen.
Jesse.
- Where are you going?
- Him.
- Why?
- I want my money.
Jesse.
I thought you were gonna nail Sara.
Did you chicken out?
- Yeah, you chicken out?
- We had a bet.
- Pay up.
- That's right. Put up or shut up.
Jesse, wait a second. Jesse.
Jesse.
What happened?
- Where are you going?
- Out.
Bradley. Hey.
What if Benedict catches us?
Let's go.
- This is it. Come on.
- Sure we can get in?
How do they know about...?
Hello.
- You know what you're gonna say?
- Shut up. Let me talk.
- How do we get in?
- I don't like this.
- Yeah.
- It's all right.
Hi.
We're friends of Cabe's.
Come on.
Hi.
Shut up!
What did you call me?
Take your time.
Hey.
It was me.
- What?
- I told Sara about the bet.
What did you do that for?
'Cause you're an asshole.
You don't make a bet on a girl
about something like that.
You like her, don't you?
- Huh?
- Yeah.
But she's in love with you.
You're blowing it, man.
What are you doing, boy?
Take it easy on that stuff,
it'll make you blind.
- How you doing?
- You brought the troops with you.
Better not make a habit of this,
we'll both get in trouble.
How you doing?
- I don't know, man.
- You got it pretty bad, don't you?
She ain't nothing
like what I thought she was.
They never are.
Why don't you get up there tonight
and jam with the rest of them?
- Why don't you?
- Maybe I will.
Come on, sugar, let's dance.
As long as you're here
have a good time.
I'm gonna do this.
- You did good tonight, Jesse.
- I did, didn't I?
Yeah, you were good. You were hot.
Well, well, well.
What have we got here?
- A little after hours action, huh?
- Travis, you're drunk.
Just you and me.
What's the matter with you?
It's you and me.
Completely off the record. No badge...
- Sleep it off, man.
... no gun.
Hey! Hey!
Cabe, man,
come on, that's enough.
- Stop.
- Let go. Let go.
- Jesse, get him out of here.
- Let me at him!
Just get him out! Are you crazy?
He's a goddamn sheriff!
I don't know. I've never felt like that,
never played like that. It was amazing.
I know, but I don't think running away
is a good idea.
Well, I'm not going back in there.
- Can't beat these sons of bitches.
- You can.
- It's a rigged game.
- It's a rigged game if you run away.
They automatically win that way.
I wouldn't do it.
I wouldn't do it if I were you.
If you're gonna go I'd go now.
He'll be up anytime.
I'll cover for you as long as I can.
- You got bucks?
- Yeah, I got some.
- I'm gonna miss you, man.
- Same.
All right, you know where to get me
if you need me.
You know, I want to give you something.
I wanna give you this.
- No, man, I can't take that.
- Yeah.
A good friend of mine gave me this...
...and I want to give it to you.
So please, take it. Go ahead.
Thanks.
I'd learn how to fix it 'cause it costs
an arm and a leg to get it repaired.
Glad to have you back.
You young people are coming to a time
when difficult decisions must be made,
as is our country.
There is a moral decay
eating away at our land.
In books, on television,
in the movies...
- Pass...
... in our own government.
And now in this new music.
It is a foul, black music,
godless and profane.
I implore you to say no to it.
Shout no to it.
And now let's bow our heads
in a moment of silent prayer
and ask God for the strength
and courage to fight this evil
that threatens the very foundation
of our American way of life.
Sara.
Sara, I'm sorry about last night.
About the bet and everything.
I got no excuses.
Except that you scare me. I mean...
That first day you showed up
I remember thinking,
"This is the kinda girl that would never
want to have anything to do with me. "
So I guess
I must've known already that...
...I liked you... and it scared me.
You were right about the picture.
It came with the wallet.
They just looked like the kind
of folks a guy should have and...
...I just sort of adopted them.
So who were your parents?
Who were my parents?
My father was a wildcat
and my mother was a waitress.
Or maybe she was a salesgirl
and he was in the service.
Or maybe they were just two
teenagers who met behind a bar.
You heard about the trouble
we had at the Lizard Lounge.
I have. I'm sorry, Travis.
You were right.
I should've fired the guy.
- I'll do it as soon as I get back.
- I don't want you to do that.
I've been checking around
like we talked about.
I'm expecting a phone call from
the sheriff in Biloxi, Mississippi.
They had trouble there a couple years
back and the description could be Cabe.
I ain't sure that it's him.
But if it is I don't want you
to spook him, so sit tight.
I want this man
just as bad as you, Eugene.
Just as bad as you.
We're cookin' now, daddy.
Who is responsible for this?
I am.
No he's not, I am.
It's me.
You know who it is.
All right, everybody
back to the dormitory.
You, come with me.
I've been easy on you long enough now.
This is your new bed.
Get used to it.
Jesse.
- You OK in there?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I thought you guys were heading
to the girls school.
We decided not to.
Why?
You know...
Look, you like her, don't you?
- I can't stop thinking about her.
- Then go down and see her.
OK. Thanks, Jesse.
Wait up. Come on, man, wait up.
- Come on, slowpoke.
- Guys, keep it down.
What are you doing?
Be careful.
- What's he doing?
- Lame-brain, what's it look like?
They're coming.
- There she is.
- Listen, maybe we should go.
- Come on.
- Yeah, we should go.
- Shut up, wuss.
- Come on.
Come on, let's go...
- Turn the radio on.
- Yeah, I'll be right there.
Are you leaving?
Come on, come on, come on. All right.
This is the Midnight Rider
on KCWR,
riding on the silver waves
of this moonlit night.
Are you out there?
Are you listening?
Do you wanna dance?
OK.
What are you boys doing here?
- What's your name?
- Rebecca.
My name's Alan...
...and I love you.
- I can't stay.
- Why not?
My father, he'll know I'm gone.
- He's gotta know someday.
- I know.
Don't you want to get away?
Don't you everjust want to go
and keep on going?
- Sure.
- I know I do.
I don't want to see nothing but blacktop
for a couple thousand miles.
Where would you go?
There's this place. They've got this
little bar and a stage in the corner.
On Friday nights everybody comes down
and gets to drink and makes noise
so you can barely hear the music.
But I wouldn't care, I'd just play.
And keep playing till there
wasn't anything left to play
and then I'd play
until they dragged me out.
Where is it?
I don't know.
You'll find it.
Go!
Hey, what gives?
He's gone.
What's going on?
- What are you doing out here?
- I wanna know what happened?
Your Mr Cabe is a wanted man.
He's a murderer.
What's the matter with you guys?
- Don't let Benedict see you like this.
- How are we supposed to act?
- You believe what they're saying?
- I suppose the cops made it up, huh?
- I don't care what the cops say.
- Then where is he, Jesse?
- Where did he go?
- He'll be back.
He'd be back if he was coming back.
You guys can go to hell.
Jesse? Where are you going?
Go, Jesse!
Yahoo!
There's this friend of mine,
a coloured guy.
We were playing gigs in Biloxi,
Mississippi.
All coloured clubs.
And then this one night this guy
who owned a white club came in.
He heard us.
He thought we were pretty good,
and he offered us a gig at his club.
He said that he didn't really care
what colour the musicians were
as long as they were good,
and we were good.
Josh tried to talk me out of it.
He said he didn't think it was worth
making the trouble over.
There was something about the idea
that they didn't want us there
that made me want to play that gig
more than anything else in the world.
So we played.
At least we started to play.
Got eight bars through the first song
and then all the troubles started.
Someone threw a beer bottle
at Josh's face.
And someone had a knife.
I tried to stop it with my hand.
But it went through my hand
and into his gut.
I swear my hand was stuck to his belly.
And I looked up and...
...there was this...
this kind of puzzled look on his face.
And I picked up this broken beer bottle
and I went after the son
of a bitch who got Josh.
So I got away.
And I ran, and I ran...
...and I'm still running.
Maybe it's time to stop.
Don't throw my words back at me.
This is different.
- How is this different?
- Get serious.
- You didn't do anything wrong.
- I killed a white man
in order to help a coloured man,
and in Mississippi
that is as wrong as you get.
Fight them.
I'll help you.
Come on, get out. Get out.
Get the hell out of here, man!
- One, two, three.
- Twenty-four.
- Twenty-five.
- One, two, three.
- Twenty-six.
- Twenty-seven.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-nine.
Thirty.
Mr Benedict...
...can I come back?
What was that, Mr Tucker?
Can I please come back?
I won't cause you anymore trouble.
I just wanna come back.
Hi.
Hey.
You OK?
I'm fine.
- I waited for you after band practice.
- I had to work in the yard.
I left a note with Alan.
Yeah, I know, I got it.
What's the matter with you?
People been asking me that
my whole life.
I wanna see you.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
Why not?
- Jesse?
- 'Cause your father, that's why.
Since when do you care
what he thinks about anything?
- I'm gonna be leaving soon.
- Yeah, I know, and I'm not.
You'll go off to college and I'm gonna
stay and dig ditches for your old man.
I just wanna put in my time
and get out of here.
And go where?
There's a great spot with a stage...
You don't get it, do you?
You don't get it.
Every time I hit,
they hit me back harder.
- When I start to trust somebody...
- You can trust me.
And you're leaving, aren't you?
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention.
Always a great pleasure
this time of year
to introduce the Benedict Home
for Boys Band!
I'll be back.
All right.
Cuff him.
- I'll see ya.
- Let's go.
One, two, three, four. Whoo!
Alright!
What the hell's going on?
Come on, get up!
- You hear that kid?
- Yeah, I hear him.
All right, that's it, kids.
- Where are you going?
- Let me go.
Yeah!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org