A QUEDA DO PODER
- The Magnificent Ambersons -
This way.
Good evening.
Yes, of course.
- Yes, directly over here.
- All right.
The invitations.
- Eugene Morgan is back in town.
- Hello, Sam.
- Good evening. Eugene Morgan.
- Welcome, sir.
Yes, thanks.
Let's go.
It's Eugene. Eugene Morgan.
He's a childhood friend of mine.
- Remember you very well indeed.
- Nice to meet you.
Isabel.
Remember you very well indeed.
- Isabel.
- Eugene!
- Is this your boy?
- Yes. George, this is...
Remember you very well indeed.
George, you never saw me
before in your life, but...
from now on you're going
to be seeing a lot of me. I hope.
I hope so too, Eugene.
Where's Wilbur?
He's off in the game room
with the others.
He never was much for parties.
Remember?
Yes, I remember.
I will come back for a dance.
Please, do.
Eugene Morgan, Major.
- Remember you very well indeed.
- Of course...
of course!
I heard you'd come back to town.
Are you thinking
of settling down here?
- I plan to, Major.
- Hello, Eugene...
It's good to see you!
You look terrific!
Come on,
let's go to the game room!
Remember you very well indeed.
George, you don't remember her either
though of course, you will!
Ms. Morgan is from out of town.
Perhaps you'd like to take her dancing.
You've pretty well done your duty here.
I'd be delighted.
May!
Who is that?
I didn't quite catch his name
when my mother present him to me.
You mean the queer looking guy?
I mean the aristocratic guy.
That's my uncle George.
The honorable George Amberson?
I thought everybody knew him.
It looks as if everyone ought to know
him. It seems to run in your family.
I suppose most people do.
Out in this part
of the country specially.
Besides, Uncle George
is in Congress.
The family likes to have
someone there.
Why?
Lt'll make it pleasant when the rest
of the family wants to go traveling...
or things like that.
I myself expect to do a great deal
of traveling when I leave college.
I suppose he will be too,
when this time goes.
Oh, is this Lucy Morgan?
Ms. Morgan, Ms. Sheffield...
this is my aunt,
Ms. Fanny Minafer.
And this is Ms. Johnson,
my friend Charlie's mother.
You must favor your mother, dear.
I never knew her.
- Hello, Lucy.
- Hello.
Lucy, can I have the next dance,
please?
Yes, yes.
- It's Geoffrey.
- Geoffrey.
Lucy, my name is Edward,
and I would love to dance with you.
And how about one
for Fred Kinney?
- Ok. Hi, Fred.
- Hi.
Give me the next one.
And the one after that.
And give me every third
for the rest of the evening.
Are you asking?
What do you mean "asking"?
Well, it sounded to me
as if you were just telling me...
to give you all those dances.
Well, I want them.
What about all those other girls
that is your duty to dance with?
They will have to go without.
Look here...
I want to know:
Are you going to give me those?
Good Gracious.
Yes.
- My name is William.
- William.
- Alfred.
- I would love to dance with you.
- Right.
And...
I can't believe that fellow.
He just sweeps in here...
and takes that girl right away!
Eugene, you're so funny!
How is that for a bit of freshness!
What was?
That queer guy waving at me
like that.
He meant me.
Oh. You seem to know
too many people.
Papa does. You know,
he used to live here in this town...
before I was born.
Where do you live now?
We don't live anywhere.
What do you mean
you don't live anywhere?
Well, we've lived all over.
Why did you keep moving around for?
Is your father a promoter?
- No, he is an inventor.
- What's he invented?
Lately, he's been working
on a kind of horseless carriage.
Look here, who sent you those flowers
you keep making such a fuss over?
What?
- He did.
- Who's he?
- The queer looking guy?
- Him?
I suppose he is some widower.
Yes, he is a widower.
I ought to have told you before.
He is my father.
Well, that's a horse on me.
If I had known he was your father...
of course, I would not
have made fun of him.
I am sorry.
- Nobody could make fun of him.
- Why couldn't they?
I wouldn't make him funny,
it'd only make themselves silly.
Well, I am not going
to make myself silly anymore, then.
I don't want to take
chances like that with you.
Thank you.
"Damas y caballeros".
Ladies and gentlemen,
directly from New York and Europe...
the forbidden dance.
Hello young namesake!
Life lingers on the languid
heels of the dancer!
She is around here,
waiting for me somewhere.
See, who is this fellow Morgan,
auntie Fanny was dancing with?
He is a man with
a pretty daughter, Georgie.
It seems you have spent the evening
noticing something of the sort.
Never mind!
What sort of man is he?
Your question is purely
mercenary, I take it.
If you want to know
his true worth...
before proceeding further
with his daughter...
I can not inform you. Thou
I noticed signs of considerable...
prosperity in that becoming dress
of hers.
Oh, dry up.
He seems at home here, by the way
he is dancing with aunt Fanny.
I am afraid
your Aunt Fanny's heart...
was stirred by ancient
recollections, Georgie.
You mean she was silly on him?
She wasn't considered singular,
He was...
he was popular.
Do you take the same
passionate interest...
in the parents of every girl
you dance with?
Oh, go on!
I only wanted to know.
Eugene Morgan!
- Wilbur.
- I heard that you were in town.
Twenty years!
Make some difference in the face...
but more in behavior!
My own behavior began
to be different about that...
long ago,
quite suddenly.
I remember.
Well, life is odd enough
as we look back.
It will probably be odder still
as we look forward.
Tom, I heard you were in the
conservatory dancing like an Indian.
I leave that to my boy Fred.
He is competing with young Georgie...
for the prettiest girl I have seen
here for some time.
Those boys had a row as kids...
and there's still a bitter feud
between them!
And between him and others.
Does young George
dislike people generally?
I don't know about "generally".
But there are a lot of people who'd be
glad to express their opinion about him.
What is the matter with him?
Too much "Amberson", I suppose,
for one thing.
And then for another, his mother just
worshiped him from the day he was born.
He acts the high tin God, yet this
intelligent, high-spirited woman...
can't see the truth of it.
What does she see
when she looks at him?
She sees an angel.
If she sees an angel, she's a funnier
woman than I thought she was!
Perhaps.
But that's what she sees.
Mothers see the angel in us
because the angel... is there.
What? You mean if a son cuts
somebody's throat...
then the mother can only see that
it is possible for a misguided angel...
to act like a devil.
And she'd be entirely right
about that!
What you are saying
is Isabel is always right!
No, no.
But in her mind,
she always has been!
Some people might think
she was wrong once, you know!
No. No, no.
- My Lord.
- No.
This is like old times
starting all over again.
Old times? Not a bit!
When times are gone...
they are not old, they're dead!
- There aren't any times but new times!
- Here, here!
- So what are you studying in school?
- College.
At the University, yes,
what are you studying there?
Lots of useless guff!
So why don't you study
some useful guff?
What d'ya mean, useful?
Something you would use later,
in your business or profession.
I don't expect to go into any business,
or profession.
- No?
- Certainly not.
Why not?
Take a look at them.
That's a fine career
for a man, isn't it?
Businessmen, lawyers, politicians...
I mean, what do they ever get
out of life? What do they ever know?
Where do they ever get?
What do you want to do?
A yachtsman!
- Come on, come on!
- George!
Come on!
Excuse me!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
- Thank you.
- Will you come again?
Excuse me.
How lovely your mother is!
I think she is.
She's the most graceful of women,
she dances like a girl of 16.
Most girls of 16 are bum dancers!
Anyhow, I wouldn't dance
with one unless I had to!
The snow's fine for sleighing.
I'll be by for you tomorrow
in a cutter a tad after two...
Tomorrow I can't possibly go.
If you don't, I'm going
to sit outside your gate...
and if you try to go out with anybody
else, he's going to have to whip me...
before he gets to you.
- Major, thank you so much.
- Eugene.
Thanks so much. A tremendous party,
a pleasure seeing you looking so well.
Thank you.
Are you ready, Lucy?
- Good night, Ms. Minafer.
- Good night, Lucy.
I hope we see much more of you!
You'd better take
this scarf Lucy dear...
- Thank you, Ms. Minafer.
- You're welcome.
Lucy?
- I'm coming out too!
- Fanny, you'll catch cold!
Lf we're going to ride in that thing
tomorrow I want to make sure it's safe!
- Good night, Isabel.
- Good night, Eugene.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Hello!
Pop...
Poppa, do you think George is
terribly arrogant and domineering?
Oh, he's still only a boy!
There's plenty of fine stuff in him.
Can't help but be!
He's Isabel Amberson's son.
You liked her pretty well once
I guess?
Yes! Yeah, I still do.
She's lovely... lovely.
I find her...
What?
How did she happen
to marry Mr. Minafer?
Oh, Wilbur's all right!
Lt seems pretty much like squandering,
but when you see that dog out...
walking with Miss Isabel,
it seems worth the money.
I don't know
as I know how to put this...
but she's kind of a delightful
looking young lady.
Eugene!
- Come on over here, Eugene!
- Come on, Eugene!
Hey, give it back!
Eugene! Give it back!
A poem.
I am of old and young,
of the foolish...
as much as the wise...
Regardless of others,
ever regardful of others.
I can't...
Eugene!
The band
is going to sound better now!
My hearing's going to be...
Is Miss Amberson at home?
No, Mr. Morgan,
Miss. Amberson is not at home.
Thank you, Sam.
Dear Isabel...
You seem to care a great deal
about double bass's.
I promise never to break another.
No sir, Miss Amberson's
not at home to you Mr. Morgan.
- Thanks, Sam.
- Mr. Morgan...
this time she really is out,
with Mr. Wilbur Minafer.
Yesterday they were row boating.
Thanks, Sam.
Getting married, getting married!
Isabel!
Good.
Push harder, push harder!
Yes, yes, very good!
Now, that is it.
Good.
Push.
Push!
Very good!
Gentlemen, please!
Mrs. Minafer will not be able
to have any more children.
I'm sorry. Good day!
Giddy up, giddy up!
Move out! Come on!
Get out of my way, get out!
By golly! I guess you think
you own this town!
I will, when I grow up. I guess
my grandpa owns it now, you bet!
I'll pull off your vest!
Don't have to!
Doctor says it ain't healthy.
But I'll tell you what I'll do!
I'll pull down my vest
if you'll wipe off your chin.
Well! I'd like to know if young
George Minafer isn't spoiled enough...
for a whole cartload of children.
Look, it's the girlie curls!
Get out of my way!
Say bub! Why d'ya steal
your mother's old sash?
Your sister stole it for me.
Stole it off her own clothesline
and gave it to me.
I haven't got any sister!
I know you haven't at home.
I mean the one that's in jail.
I dare you to get out of that cart!
I'll get him, don't worry!
- I dare you to come over here!
- Yeah?
I dare you, half way her
Here I come!
Take that, Fred Kinney.
Boy! Boy!
Here boy!
Now that will be enough of that!
You will...
You stop that! You...
I guess you don't know who I am?
Yes, I do know...
and you're a disgrace
to your mother!
You shut up about my mother!
She ought to be ashamed.
A woman who'll let a bad boy like you...
Pull down your vest
you old billy goat you!
Pull down your vest,
wipe off your chin...
and go to hell!
"Pull down your vest...
wipe off your chin,
and go to hell".
- Did you say what he said you did, dear?
- Which one?
- Did you tell him to go to...
- Listen here, mom...
Grandpa wouldn't wipe his shoe
on that old storyteller, would he?
- Georgie, don't!
- I mean...
none of the Ambersons would have
anything to do with him, would they?
Come here.
That's not
what we're talking about!
I bet if he wanted to see
any of us...
he'd have to go round
to the side door.
George...
- Please, Major.
- No!
Yes, he would, Mom!
That kind of people, I don't see why
we can't say anything we want to them.
No Georgie, those were terrible
words that you used!
- But he's just riffraff!
- You mustn't say so!
Just promise me
you'll never say bad words!
- I promise.
- All right.
Go!
Unless I get mad at somebody...
- Careful!
- Slow down!
Slow down, boy!
- Got any sense?
- Watch it now!
See here, bub!
Does your mother know you're out!
Pull down your pants,
you would be dude!
Raining in dear old money!
Get off the earth!
Welcome, friends of the Ace!
Take your seat in the secret square.
We will now proceed to...
Look here, Charlie Johnson!
What's Fred Kinney doing
in the President's chair?
Didn't you all agree I was
to be President just the same...
even if I was away at school?
All friends of the Ace
will take their seats!
I'm president of the F O T A
now, George Minafer.
- This meeting will now proceed to...
- No, it won't.
You put down that gavel!
Lt belongs to my grandfather!
- I was legally elected here!
- All right...
you're President:
Now we'll hold another election!
We will not!
We'll have our regular meeting,
and then we'll play Yuker.
And Nick in the corner.
That's what we're here for!
Who's the founder of the F O T A,
if you please?
Who got the Janitor to let us have
most of this furniture?
Do you suppose you could
keep this clubroom a minute...
if I told my grandpa I didn't want it
for a Literary Club any more?
I'd like to say a word about how
the new members have been acting too.
That's what you want?
You can have it!
All in favor of having
a new election say "l"
"l".
All in favor of me being President
instead of... Fred Kinney...
- say "l".
- "L".
The "Is" have it.
I resign!
Old redhead Fred will be back
around next week.
He'll be around bootlicking to get us
to take him back in again!
Now I don't suppose there's any more
business before the meeting?
Anybody who's game
for a little quarter limit poker...
or any limit, as they say...
I'd like to have them sit
at the President's card table.
Your face looks like...
it looks like a snowflake
on a lump of coal.
Perhaps you'd better
look at the reins!
'Cos there's too much pink
in your cheeks for a snow-flake.
We're going pretty fast,
Mr. Minafer.
Well, you see,
I'm only here for two weeks...
I mean the sleigh!
I suppose your father thinks
he can build a horseless carriage...
that can go that fast!
Lt can go that fast already
sometimes.
All of this land, 200 acres of it,
my grandfather developed.
He built the streets, set up statues
and fountains.
It's called the Amberson Addition.
And that there is Amberson Boulevard.
It must be from the soot.
Somebody ought to see
that these statues are kept clean.
There are so many houses
around here!
My grandfather sold most of the lots,
there aren't any vacant ones left.
And there used to be heaps
when I was a boy.
Many people built houses, and then the
price of the land kept getting higher...
and, people sold part of their yards and
the people who bought 'em built houses.
The way it used to be...
it was like a gentleman's country state.
That's the way my grandpa will keep it.
These people do anything
they want to!
But how can you stop them, if you sold
them the land, it's theirs, isn't it?
He ought to have all the trades-people
boycott them!
All he'd have to do is say they wouldn't
get any more orders from the family.
The family?
The Ambersons.
I see.
What are you laughing at now?
You always seem to have some little
secret of your own to get happy over!
Always? What a big word
when we only met last night!
That's another case of it! One of
the reasons I don't like you... much...
is that you've got this way of seeming
quietly superior to everybody else.
I have?
Oh, you think you keep it,
sort of confidential to yourself!
I don't believe
in that kind of thing.
- You don't?
- No.
I believe the world is like this...
There are a few people where their birth
and position puts them at the top...
and they are to treat each other
entirely as equals.
I wouldn't speak like this
with everybody.
You mean, you are confiding
your deepest creed to me?
Go on, make fun of it then!
Well, if you don't like my seeming
quietly superior...
from now on
I'll be noisily superior.
We aim to please.
I had a notion before I came to get you
today that we were going to quarrel.
No, we won't!
Lt takes two!
Go on!
When we get this far out, we can see
the smoke hanging over the town.
Poppa says it used to be nicer here
when he lived here.
From the way he talks, you'd think
that life here then was just...
one long mid-summer serenade.
There always seemed
to be gold dust in the air!
I think the gold dust he thinks was here
was just being young that he remembers!
Still, it is pretty pleasant
to be young, isn't it!
I wonder if we really do enjoy it
as much as when we look back and...
You're a funny girl.
But your voice sounds pretty nice when
you think and talk along like that.
Hey! Look at that
old sewing machine!
Hey, that's father's car!
And there's your mother,
Miss Minafer, and Mr. Amberson!
Go on! Get on!
Get a horse, get a horse!
Look out!
There's a ditch on the right!
Georgie!
Lucy!
They're all right!
The snow's like a feather bed. There's
nothing the matter with them at all!
George!
- Lucy!
- Georgie!
Georgie! Lucy!
Lucy, dear, are you all right?
- Don't make a fuss Mother!
- Let me see you! When you fell like...
- Let me get the snow off you!
- No! Leave me alone, Mother!
All right, you mustn't catch cold!
Mother...
- I was worried you had broken your neck!
- Stop it. Stop it!
That darn horse!
I wouldn't bother about the horse!
He'll be home a long time before we are!
All we've got to depend on is Eugene's
broken down chafing dish yonder.
Here we go!
All aboard!
- Stop doing this...
- Come on, Mom, get in...
- You will catch a cold!
- Just get in the car!
I walk along with a pot of gold
And an independent wealth
And you can hear the girls declare
He must be a millionaire
He was very sad
And he wished to die
And to see in a blink of an eye
The man who wrote the card
He was very sad
And he wished to die
And to see in a blink of an eye
The man who wrote the card
Look here...
How about this man Morgan
and his old sewing machine?
Doesn't he want to get grandfather
to put some money into it?
Isn't that what he's up to?
I bet he borrows money
from Uncle George!
He strikes me
as that sort of a man!
He was a fairly wild young
fellow 20 years ago.
He was a lot like you, Georgie.
He spent too much money...
only he didn't have a mom, to get money
out of her grandfather to help him...
so he was usually in debt.
But, I believe he's done fairly well
of late years...
so I doubt he needs anybody's money
to back his horseless carriage.
What's he got her here for then?
People who own elephants don't take
their elephants when they go visiting.
- What has he got it here for?
- I am sure, I don't know.
Why don't you ask him?
While strolling through
The park one day
In the merry month of May
I was taken by surprise
By a pair of roguish eyes
In a moment my poor heart
Was stolen away...
They seem to be getting along
a lot better than they did at first...
those two children.
They seemed to always be having
little quarrels of some sort at first.
At least Georgie did, always being
cross with her over nothing.
Cross with her? My Georgie? Why I
have never seen a more angelically...
amiable disposition in my life!
That's all the side of him
you happen to see!
I immediately raised my hat
And finally she remarked
I never shall forget
That lovely afternoon
I met her at the fountain
In the park
- Would you join me in a drink, Eugene?
- Oh, no, thank you, Major.
Oh, that's right! You don't! Not since
a certain run-in with a double bass!
Well, hardly anybody
drinks nowadays...
Almost.
- Perhaps it's just as well...
- Thank you!
Things used to be livelier.
The fact is...
if you hadn't broken
that double bass...
Isabel would never
have taken Wilbur.
That may be the only
reason Wilbur got her!
By Jove! I think she's blushing!
Who wouldn't?
Well, the important thing is,
that Wilbur did get her.
And he not only got her,
he kept her!
There's another important thing!
Well, that is for me!
Lt's the only thing that makes me
forgive that double bass...
for getting in my way.
What is it?
Lucy.
To Lucy!
For heaven's sake!
What's the matter?
You're going away.
Well, I'll be back,
don't you suppose?
I never could bear to see you go,
that's most of it.
I'm a bit worried about
your father as well.
Why?
Lt seems to me that he looks badly.
Everybody says so!
Nonsense!
He is not much different from the way
he's looked all his life. I can tell!
He's been worried about his investments,
and I that worry affected his health.
What investments?
He hasn't gone into Mr. Morgan's
automobile concern, has he?
About three years ago...
he and your Uncle George put almost
everything they could get together...
into some stocks of some rolling mills.
And those mills haven't been doing well.
What of that?
You and I will look after him.
We'll build him a little stone bank
out the back...
and every morning
he can put pennies in it...
and we'll keep him
as happy as he's ever been!
I look out on the campus
from my many paned window...
and things are different with me from
the way they were back in freshman year.
I can see now how boyish I was
in many ways back then.
I believe what has changed me as much
as anything was my visit home...
and meeting you.
And so I sit here
with my faithful briar...
and dream all dreams
over as it were.
Dreaming of the waltzes
we waltzed together...
and of the last night
before we parted.
And the good news you were going
to give to me there.
And that I would find my friend
waiting for me...
when I got home next summer.
That telegram came this morning!
Not bad news?
My father!
As you see,
I've got to go home!
Yonder is where I room
when I was here.
I don't know whether George
would allow my admirers...
place a tablet
to mark the spot, or not.
He thinks he owns all of
these buildings now, you know!
Didn't you!
When you were here?
Like Uncle, like nephew!
I wonder if I was like that?
Oh, look at the swell!
You don't suppose every Amberson
has to go through it, do you?
At least half of it is the combination
of youth and good looks and college.
And even the noblest Ambersons
get over their nobility...
and come to be people in time.
It takes more than time,
though.
You should say it did take
more than time!
Lt's charming, isn't it?
They're so eager and confident,
all these boys.
It's touching.
Of course, youth doesn't know
that it's touching!
Do you know what I think whenever I see
all these smooth, triumphal young faces?
I always think: "Oh, how you're
going to catch it!"
Oh, George!
Yes, life is most ingenious...
It has a special walloping
for every mother's son of them!
Well... maybe some of the mothers
can take the walloping for them!
Not any more than she can take
on her own face the lines...
that are bound to come
on her sons.
Well, maybe times will change
and nobody will have to wear lines!
Times have changed like that
for only one person that I know.
The serenest brow is the one
that believes the most.
In what?
In everything.
I believe.
I believe I do.
Isabel,
you're a foolish person!
There are times when you look
exactly like 14 years old.
Gracious!
What'll your crowd be
doing after graduation?
Don't you think that being things
is rather better than doing things?
Rather better?
What are these things that are
so superior and beautiful to be?
Family and all that.
Being a gentleman, I suppose.
Where have the children got to?
Yes, where is the exact proprietor
of the universe?
Well, it's never becoming
for your mother to look pale.
- What did you say, Aunt Fanny?
- Nothing.
I suppose your mother's
been pretty gay, going out a lot.
How could she?
I mean, in mourning all she could do
was just sit around and look on.
That's all Lucy Morgan could do
either for the matter of that.
I suppose so.
How did Lucy get home?
Well, she came
on the train with us, of course.
I didn't mean that!
I meant from the station!
She drove home
with her father of course.
Oh, I see, so...
Eugene came to the station
to meet you?
To meet us? How could he?
I don't know what you mean. I haven't
seen him while your mother's been away.
Naturally.
He's been East himself.
Did you see him?
Well, naturally, since he made
the trip home with us.
He did?
He's been with you
the whole time?
No. Only on the train
and the three days before we left.
Uncle George got him to come.
You're a fine housekeeper.
You know how to make things look
dainty as well as taste the right way.
- I shouldn't be a bit surprised if...
- It's real odd...
What is odd?
Your mother not mentioning that
Mr. Morgan had been with you.
Didn't think of it, I suppose.
I'll tell you something
in confidence...
What?
Lt struck me that Mr. Morgan was looking
pretty absent-minded most of the time...
I shouldn't be surprised if
all the young fellow was waiting for...
was to know that he had
an assured income before he proposed.
What young fellow?
This young fellow Morgan.
I shouldn't be a bit surprised to have
him to request an interview with me...
and ask my permission
to pay his addresses to you.
Good heavens!
I was only teasing!
Let me alone!
Please, Aunt Fanny!
Please!
I said: Let me alone!
I didn't mean it!
How can you eat?
In the name of God! What does
grandfather mean by doing such things!
My private opinion is: He desires
to increase his income...
by building these houses to rent.
In the name of God! Couldn't he find any
other way of increasing his income...
other than building
them in the front yard?
In the name of God...
it would appear he couldn't!
Lt's beastly!
Lt's a damned degradation!
Lt's a crime!
Your mother said not to tell you
until we got home...
so as not to spoil commencement.
- She rather feared you'd be upset.
- Upset?
- I should think so!
- Your mother knows you rather well.
And your mother was right!
She is right!
Oh, be careful!
Heavens, oh, my!
My, it's noisy!
All this noise seems
to be good for you!
Perhaps you ought to tour a factory
every time you get the blues!
She doesn't get the blues, George!
I've never seen a person with
a more even disposition in my life!
I wish I could be like that!
Eugene!
Lt makes us all so happy.
Dear old Eugene!
Fanny, take his hand.
There.
Now if George was here, Eugene would
have 3 of his oldest and best friends...
congratulating him all at once.
It's just beautiful, Eugene.
- Did you like it?
- Of course I did.
You know, I used to write verse,
if you remember...
Yes, I remember.
I don't recall that I have written any
for 20 years or so...
but I'm almost thinking
that I could do it again...
just to thank you...
for making a factory visit
such a...
such a kind celebration.
Goodness!
Aren't they sentimental!
People that age always are!
They get sentimental
over anything at all!
- I quite enjoyed part of that tour!
- The assembly of the engine?
No.
- You whispering to me!
- Blarney!
- No, don't.
- Don't?
I know when you let us drift like this
it's to give all of your attention...
to proposing to me again.
Lucy.
Dear, what is the matter?
You look as if
you are going to cry!
You always do that whenever I get
to talk to you about marrying me.
Everything is just so...
unsettled.
If you aren't the queerest girl!
What is unsettled?
Well, for one thing,
you haven't settled on anything to do.
At least, if you have, you've never
spoken to me about it.
You really don't mean to have any
regular business or profession at all?
I certainly do not!
I was afraid so.
So that's it, is it?
Lt's your father's idea
that I ought to go into business...
and that you oughtn't to be engaged
to me until I do.
No! No, I've never once
spoken to him about it. Never.
But you know without even talking to
him that that's what he feels about it.
Yes.
Lucy.
Don't you know that I love you!
Yes, I do.
Don't you love me?
Let me tell my mother when I get home
that we're really engaged.
- No. No.
- Because of your father!
- Because it's better!
- Isn't it your father?
Lt's his ideals I'm thinking of.
Yes.
I know what you mean.
But I daresay I don't care
for your father's ideals...
any more than he does for mine.
It's so nice of you to always dress
for the evenings, Georgie.
Uncle George used to, and so did father,
but they stopped a long time ago.
There are a great many
more automobiles than there used to be.
Eugene is right about that.
Why?
I've begun to agree with George...
about them being more of a fad
than anything else, like roller skates.
They're probably a mistake.
I don't believe we'll see so many
next summer as we do right now.
Besides, people won't permit
the automobiles to be used.
You can see how
they spoil the bikes...
People seem to hate them.
I should be sorry to see
such a thing happen to Eugene.
I shouldn't be surprised
if there was a law...
forbidding the sale of automobiles.
Just the way there is with...
Summer's dying.
How quickly it goes
once it starts to die.
Isn't it queer how your mother
can use such words?
What words you talking about?
Words like..."die and dying".
I don't see how she can bear to use
them so soon after your poor father...
- It seems you are using them yourself!
- I? Never!
- Yes, you did.
- When?
Just this minute.
You mean when
I repeated what she said?
That's hardly the same thing,
George!
I don't think you'll convince anybody
that my mother's unfeeling!
I'm not trying to convince
anybody of anything!
I mean,
that merely in my opinion...
well, perhaps
it's just as wise for me...
to keep my opinion to myself.
There's just one thing I hope.
I hope at least she doesn't
leave off her full mourning...
on the very anniversary
of Wilbur's death!
Beautiful!
Of course you are.
Riffraff.
- Who is going?
- Not I.
Summer's gone
and I've hardly seen Lucy!
- I've missed my best girl.
- We all do!
Well, Lucy's spending some time
with a school friend, Major.
Eugene, I hear someone's
opened another automobile shop...
somewhere in the suburbs.
I imagine they will either drive you
out of business...
or else the two of you will drive
all the rest of us off the streets.
Well, if we do,
we'll even things up...
by making the streets five times
as long as they're now.
And how do you propose
to do that?
Well, it isn't the distance from
the centre of a town that counts...
it's the time it takes to get there.
This town's already spreading...
and automobiles are going to carry city
streets clear out to the county line.
Dream on fair son!
But if people are going to be
moving out that far...
the real estate values in the old part
of town will be stretched pretty thin.
So, you and your automobiles
will ruin all your old friends, Eugene.
Do you really think that they're
going to change the face of the land?
Oh, they're already doing it,
Major...
and it can't be stopped.
Automobiles...
Automobiles
are a useless nuisance.
What did you say, Georgie?
I said, "all automobiles
are a nuisance".
They are never going to amount
to anything more than a nuisance...
and they had no business
being invented.
Of course you forget that
Mr. Morgan makes them...
and also did his share
in inventing them.
If you weren't so thoughtless,
he might think you rather offensive.
That would be too bad!
I don't think I could survive it.
Well, I'm not sure he's wrong,
about automobiles.
For all their speed forward, they may
be a step backward for civilization.
Maybe they won't add to the beauty of
the world, to the light of men's souls.
I am not sure.
But automobiles have come...
and almost all outward things
are going to be different...
because of what they bring.
They are going to alter war
and, they are going to alter peace.
And I think men's minds are going to be
changed in subtle ways...
because of the automobile.
But you can't have the immense
outward changes that they will cause...
without some inward ones,
and it may be...
that George is right...
and that the spiritual alteration
will be bad for us.
Perhaps 10 or 20 years
from now...
if we can see the inward change
in men by that time...
I shouldn't be able to defend the gas
engine, I'd have to agree with him...
that automobiles...
had no business being invented.
Well, Major, I hope you'll excuse me.
I have a prior engagement and...
much as I prefer to linger.
I'll bid you all a good evening.
Good evening.
- Good night.
Georgie dear, what did you mean?
- Just what I said...
- Well, he was hurt.
I don't why he should be.
I didn't say anything about him.
Anyway, he didn't seem hurt to me.
He seemed perfectly cheerful.
- What makes you think that he was hurt?
- Because I know him.
You didn't mean him, you say,
Georgie?
By Jove, but you're puzzlement!
In what way, may I ask, sir?
Well, thank you. It certainly is
a new way to court a pretty girl!
For a fellow to go out of his way
to try to make an enemy of her father...
by attacking his business.
That's a novel way
to win a woman!
Eugene would never be
anyone's enemy. He just couldn't.
Last of all, Georgie's.
Well...
it certainly wasn't
a successful dinner!
I've come to say good night.
Good night.
You needn't look so worried,
old lady.
I won't be tactless
with Morgan anymore.
After this, I'm just going
to stay out of his way.
Darling, tell me something.
Why don't you like Eugene?
I've had the feeling from the very first
that you never liked him...
and now I know
that feeling's right.
That seems so queer to me...
given how you feel about
his daughter!
How do I feel about his daughter?
You've certainly never looked at another
girl since Lucy Morgan came to town!
And surely,
you've been best friends.
What of it?
Lt's like what was said
by your grandfather.
I can't see how you can feel so
interested in a girl and not be...
pleasantly disposed to her father.
Well, I admit. There may be something
in what you say, but...
the truth is, up until recently, I've
only ever thought of Lucy as Lucy...
and Morgan as Morgan.
I've never really thought of her
as somebody's daughter.
Probably you've got plenty of friends
that don't much care for your son!
Not at all! And if I knew anyone
felt like that, I would...
There, there Mother!
I really want to go to bed,
Mother.
Good night.
But George... you would like him
if you just let yourself.
Let's not talk of it any more.
Good night, old lady.
Good night.
Why... hello, George!
How do you do?
I...
I trust...
I trust you had a pleasant time.
I hope you are extremely...
I beg your pardon?
Nothing
of the slightest importance!
Good afternoon.
Riffraff!
Riffraff! Riffraff!
George! George!
Now what on earth do you want?
Oh, for the Lord's sake!
What in the world is wrong with you?
I don't think I can stand it!
You wouldn't treat anybody in the
world this way, except for old Fanny.
"Old Fanny," you say...
"lt's nobody but old Fanny...
so I'll kick her.
Nobody will resent it!"
And you're right! I haven't got
anybody or anything...
in the whole world
since my brother died.
Nobody!
Nothing!
- Nothing!
- My Lord!
I would never, never...
in the whole world have told you...
had I seen that somebody else had told
you, that you'd found out by yourself.
Somebody else had told me what?
I'd found out what for myself?
How people are talking
about your mother!
- What did you say?
- Of course...
I understood what you were doing.
It puzzled other people at first...
when you began to be rude
to Eugene.
They couldn't understand how
you could behave in such a way...
when you were so interested in Lucy,
but I knew...
you'd give Lucy up fast if it became
a question of your mother's reputation.
Because you said that reputation
is the most important thing!
- What are you talking about?
- Everybody knows it!
Everybody in town knows...
that your mother has never cared for
any other man in her life except Eugene.
Poor Wilbur...
he was the only man alive
that didn't know it!
You say that they believe that
my mother is in love with that man!
- Of course!
- Just because he came over here?
And they went out driving?
That they think that she was in love
with him, before my father died?
Why George... don't you know
that's what they say?
You must know...
that everybody in this town says that
they are going to be married very soon!
God knows
I'm sorry for you George.
I wanted to say so...
but I'm only poor old lonely
Aunt Fanny so whatever she says...
even if it's in sympathy,
pick on her for it.
It's only poor old lonely
Aunt Fanny.
Someone must have told you!
- Who told you?
- What?
Who told you there was talk?
Where is this talk? Where does it
come from? Who does it?
Sorry... I suppose
pretty much everybody!
- Who said so?
- I... heard.
Where did you get hold of it?
Answer me!
I hardly think
it would be fair to give names.
One of your most intimate friends
is that mother of Charlie Johnson's...
- has she ever mentioned it to you?
- She may have intimated...
I said... has she ever
talked about it with you?
She's a very lovely
discreet woman, George...
but she may have int...
I saw two talking
about it on the street.
- Do you deny it?
- I...
Do you deny it?
No.
What are you going to do,
George?
George!
What are you going to do?
I didn't...
where are you going?
Mr. Amberson!
I mean, Mr. Minafer.
I'm really delighted!
Mrs. Johnson! I've come
to ask you a few questions.
Why certainly...
anything I can do to help...
You were talking with my Aunt
Fanny about my mother this afternoon?
Lf we were discussing your mother, it
must have been a pleasant conversation.
I don't intend
to waste time, Mrs. Johnson.
You were talking...
You were discussing a scandal
that involved my mother's name.
Mr. Minafer!
My Aunt said that you
repeated the scandal to her!
I don't think your Aunt
could have said that.
We may have discussed matters that have
been topics of conversation around town.
Yes! I think you may have!
That's why I'm here
and that's what I intend to find out!
Don't tell me what you intend,
please!
And I would prefer that you keep your
voice not quite so loud in this house...
which I happen to own.
Now... if I discussed
this matter with your Aunt...
you can make sure that
it was in the most charitable spirit...
and without sharing people's disposition
to put an evil connotation to it.
Other people!
That's what I'd like to know
about... these other people!
I beg your pardon!
You say that other
people talk about this?
- Well, I presume they do.
- How many?
- What?
- How many other people talk about it?
Really, this is not a courtroom
and I am not a defendant in a lawsuit.
You may be.
I intend to know just
who dared to say these things...
even if I have to force my way
into every house in this town.
I'm going to make them
take every word of it back.
I intend to find out the name of every
slanderer who spoke of this to you.
I mean to know!
You'll know something pretty quick!
You'll know you are out on the street.
Now
please to leave my house!
Now you have done it!
What do you mean?
What have I done
that wasn't honorable and right?
Do you think these riffraff can go
around bandying my mother's name?
They can now!
What do you mean by that?
Gossip is never fatal, Georgie,
until it is denied.
Gossip almost never does any harm...
until some defender
makes a controversy.
See here! I didn't come
to listen to philosophies.
You asked me what you have done,
and I'm telling you.
People who have repeated
a slander either...
get ashamed or forget about it.
Challenge them...
and in self-defense
they believe everything they've said.
What do you think I've been doing?
Nothing helpful! The more you do,
the more harm you'll do.
Didn't you understand me
when I told you...
that these people say that
my mother means to marry this man?
I don't see anything
precisely monstrous...
about two people getting married when
they are free and care about each other!
What's the matter
with them marrying?
Lt would be monstrous!
Don't be so theatrical!
Come back here!
George, you mustn't speak
to your mother about this.
Get out of my way!
And I tried on this ridiculous dress...
You should've seen it, it didn't fit me.
It was so funny.
I laughed for hours.
Here you go, sir.
- You should've seen the shopkeeper...
- So, what are you going to do?
I don't know,
but I'll think of something...
Can I get you anything else?
- We want another couple of beers.
- All right. Beers.
One...
- two.
- Now, eight.
Turn, turn.
One, two.
Ok.
One, two, three, and...
- Turn.
- One, two...
Heavens! Oh, I'm sorry!
Yes?
Oh, it's you.
Oh, indeed I should!
Of course!
Then I'll expect you around noon.
Yes! All right! I'll see you then.
Good-bye, Eugene.
You needn't mind, Mary! I'll see
who it is and what they want.
- Probably it's only a peddler!
- Thank you, sir, Mr. George!
How do you do, George!
Mrs. Minafer expects to go driving
with me, I believe, so...
Would you be kind to sand her
the word I'm here?
No.
I beg your pardon?
- I said she's, she...
- I heard you.
You said you had an engagement
with my mother, and I told you no!
What is the... the difficulty?
My mother will have no interest
in knowing that you came for her today.
Or any other day.
I am afraid
I do not understand you!
I doubt that I could make it
much plainer, but I'll try!
You are not welcome
in this house, Mr. Morgan.
Not now, or at any other time.
Perhaps you'll understand this!
Georgie!
Dear, I waited lunch almost an hour
for you, but you didn't come!
Did you lunch out somewhere?
Yes.
- Did you have plenty to eat?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
Wouldn't you like Maggie to get you
something from the dining room?
They can bring it to you here
if you think it would be cozier.
No.
Gracious, Georgie,
you have been investing!
That was very nice of you, Georgie.
I ought to have had it framed myself
when I gave it to you.
Isabel?
I'm sorry to disturb you...
but I have got to speak
to you... upstairs!
I don't mean to be mysterious.
But, recent events compel me...
to have to speak to you about
a very, very serious matter.
I can guess what that was about!
He's just told her
what you did to Eugene!
- You go on back to your room!
- You're not going in there!
George! George!
You get away from that door!
George! You listen to me!
- Let go of me, you!
- Come here.
Here, look...
We are going upstairs...
you are going to go up those stairs
and leave them alone for a change.
- This is ridiculous!
- Ridiculous is squabbling at that door.
You sit down and you hush up!
There.
I thought you knew about everything!
Lf I even dreamed you'd go out
making a big tragedy of it all...
Look here! Lt seems to me you've
been taking a pretty different tack.
I know! They haven't done
anybody any harm.
Isabel was really a good wife to Wilbur
and she was always true to him.
I'm not doing myself a bit of good...
going around and ruining them...
I suppose you think I'm doing that.
Yes! Yes I do!
On the contrary!
I'm trying to save my mother
from a great calamity!
I think there is something
you ought to know, George.
I'd leave your mother alone,
if I were you.
I don't think she is very well.
It's nothing! Lt's nothing at all!
Well, she's trying to keep it from you,
but she goes to a doctor regularly.
You stay here!
You stay here and let them alone.
Don't go down. Let her alone.
One thing you can never doubt,
beloved boy...
I could never care for anything in the
world as I care for you. Never!
- Never.
- I know...
No matter what happens.
I want you to read this.
Dearest one, yesterday I thought
the time had come...
when I could ask you to marry me,
and you were dear enough to say...
some day it might come to that.
But now we are faced,
not with slander...
and not with our own fear of it,
because we haven't any, but...
with someone else's fear of it...
your son's, and...
dearest woman in the world,
I know what your son is to you...
and it frightens me!
I don't think he will change.
Forty can't tell twenty about this.
Twenty can find out
only by getting to be forty...
and so we come to this, dear.
Where you live your own life...
your way...
or George's way?
I'm saying too much
for wisdom, I fear...
but oh my dear,
won't you be strong?
And such a little, short,
strength it would need.
Don't strike my life down twice,
dear.
Because this time,
I've not deserved it.
The worst of it is, he thinks
he's been such a hero...
and Isabel does too.
She goes about,
overseeing the packing...
and pretending to be perfectly
cheerful about what he's making her do.
And all the while,
it's almost killing her.
What he said to your father!
Now...
you must come and see me.
After they've gone of course!
I'll go crazy if I don't see
something of people.
I'm sure you'll come
and see me as often as you can.
I know you well to think you'll be
sensitive about being reminded of George.
You're much too well balanced to let
anything effect you deeply about that.
Oh, that monkey!
Where's your father? I should say
good-bye to him before I go.
He's just stepped out, I'm afraid.
Good afternoon, Mr. Minafer,
Mr. Johnson.
- Hello, Suzanna.
- Hello, Charlie.
- How are you?
- How is your mother?
- Well, she is the same.
- I hope she is on the mend.
Well, we hope so too,
the doctor's into see her.
Well, that is good.
- Look what I bought.
- It's lovely!
- Hello, George!
- Lucy, I want to tell you something!
Well, I hope it's
a lively something then!
Poppa's been so glum today,
he's scarcely spoken to me.
- I'd be glad to hear a funny story!
- Well, it may seem one to you!
To begin with, you went away
and you didn't even let me know.
- Not a word! Not even a line!
- I know. I trotted off for some visits!
- At least you could've said something!
- I know.
Don't you remember, George?
We had a terrible quarrel and...
hadn't spoken to each other
all the way home, from a long drive.
And, well, as we couldn't play
together like good children...
of course it was plain that we
ought not to play together at all.
- Play?
- Yes.
Well, what I mean is...
we had come to the point
where it was time to quit playing...
whatever it was we were playing.
At being lovers, you mean,
don't you?
Something like that! Lt was absurd!
- It needn't have been!
- No, it couldn't help but be.
The way I am and the way you are,
it could never have been anything else.
Well, this time I'm going.
That's what I wanted to say!
I'm leaving tomorrow night
indefinitely!
Well, I hope you'll have
ever so jolly a time.
I don't expect to!
Well then if I were you,
I don't think I'd go!
Lucy! This is our
last walk together!
Evidently, if you're
leaving tomorrow night!
Lucy! This may be the last time
I'll ever see you, in my life!
Well, you're not going
away are you, to live?
- No.
- And, well, you'd be back for visits.
I don't know when I'm coming back.
Mother and I are leaving tomorrow
night on a trip around the world.
Your mother's going with you?
Good heavens! Doesn't it make
any difference to you that I'm going?
Of course! Will you be gone long?
I've made no plans
at all for coming back.
Well, that does sound like a long trip!
Will you be traveling all the time,
or will you be staying in one place?
- I think it would be just lovely if...
- Lucy!
I can't stand this any longer!
I can't stand this!
I'm just about to walk into
this drugstore here...
and ask the clerk to give me something
to stop me from dying in my tracks.
It's quite a shock!
What is?
To see how much you've cared
for me.
To see how much of a difference
this makes to you!
George! Surely you don't want me
to do pathos on a downtown corner?
I can't stand this any longer!
Good-bye, Lucy.
It is good-bye.
I think it's good-bye for good!
Good-bye. I hope you'll have
the most splendid trip.
Give my love to your mother.
Please, let me have a few drops
of aromatic spirits of ammonia...
- in a glass of water.
- Yes ma'am.
- Look out!
- God, are you sick, miss?
- Are you all right?
- Lucy!
The Major had one painful
satisfaction this spring.
He had his taxes lowered!
How did he manage that?
I said it was
a painful satisfaction, Fanny.
The property has gone down
in value...
and they assessed it
lower than they did 15 years ago.
But further out I hear they...
Oh yes, prices are
magnificent further out.
We just happen to be the wrong spot.
That's all.
Not that I don't think
something could be done...
if father would let me
have a hand. But he won't.
He's always done
his own figuring, he says.
And its his life-long habit
to keep his affairs and just...
hand us out the money.
Heaven knows!
He's done enough of that.
It does seem as if there's a great deal
of money to be made nowadays.
I ran into Frank Rohnson
the other day and he told me...
Even dear old
Frank has got the fever!
- Yes, and he told me...
- He told me about...
this invention he's going into.
Some new electric headlight...
- Yes, electric headlights, that's right.
- Headlights better than anything yet...
Yes, he was telling me about it,
yes.
He's putting half
he's laid by into it.
- Half?
- Half.
And he's almost talked me into
getting father to finance me enough...
for me to go into it.
At any rate,
I've been thinking it over.
So have I!
He seemed to be certain it would pay
25% in its' first year.
And I'm only making four
on my little principal.
It does seem as if enormous
fortunes are being made...
out of anything to do
with motorcars these days.
So, I told him I would
think it over seriously.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
- Really?
- Yes.
You must be careful to leave
yourself a margin of safety, Fanny.
Now I'm confident that this is a pretty
conservative investment of its' kind.
And all the chances are with us.
But it is prudent...
to leave yourself enough
to fall back on.
In case anything should go wrong.
- Nothing will go wrong.
- We seem to be partners all right.
Now let's go and be millionaires before
Isabel and young George come home.
Well, if they ever do come home!
Fanny.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
My dearest George,
thrilled by your news!
I'm so looking forward to your visit!
Dear, dear Fanny, we are
so happy to have George with us.
Dear Father! What fun to be
in Venice with Uncle George.
I wish you were here with us.
I trust this finds you well.
I miss you. Isabel.
Dear Frank Rohnson, we have offered
prayers here today for father's health.
Fanny, my dearest! How we all
wished you had been here with us.
I shall be so sad to see George go.
Well, he seems to have recovered.
I beg your pardon!
Your grandson! He was inclined
to melancholy on certain days...
but he seemed jolly
enough when we parted.
What was he melancholy about?
Not getting remorseful about
all the money he's spent in Europe?
I wonder what he thinks I'm made of.
Gold! And he's right
about part of you, father!
- What part is that?
- Your heart.
I suppose that accounts for how heavy
it feels sometimes nowadays.
This town is rolling right over
that old mansion, George.
Rolling right over it
and burying it under...
Never mind, father!
Don't think of it!
Lf things are a nuisance, it's a good idea
not to keep remembering them.
I try not to.
I try to keep remembering that I won't
be remembering anything very long.
Not so very long now, my boy.
Not so very long.
Has this been a good holiday
for you, dear?
Oh, I suppose so, why?
Lt's pleasant for people my age to know
that people your age see they're happy.
People your age?
You know, you don't precisely
look like an old woman, mother.
No?
But I suppose I feel about
the same as you do inside.
But time really does fly.
Perhaps it's more like
the smoke and sky.
What do you mean?
Time being like the smoke and sky.
I mean the things that we have
and we think are solid are like smoke.
And time is like the sky
the smoke disappears into.
You know, how really the smoke curls up
from the chimney, it seems all thick...
and black, busy against the skies as if
it would go on and do important things.
And then you see it
getting thinner and thinner.
And then in such a little while
it isn't there at all.
Nothing is there but the sky and the sky
just keeps on being the same forever.
I don't see much resemblance
between time and the sky...
but I do see why you like
Lucy Morgan so much.
You two talk the same wistful,
moony way sometimes.
We do?
I don't mean to say that I mind it in
either of you, 'cos I like to hear it.
Anyway, I've got a lot to read
while you romance.
- Au revoir, Madame.
- Au revoir.
Welcome back!
I wonder if history is going on
repeating itself forever.
It's the Amberson Mansion again, only
it's your father who's built this one.
Oh, you're pretty refreshingly
out of the smoke up here.
Yes, until it comes up
and we have to move out farther.
No, somebody else
will move out farther...
you'll stay here.
I found Isabel as well as usual...
only I'm afraid "as usual"
isn't particularly well.
What do you mean by that?
I'm afraid she hasn't been really well
for several years.
She's rather alarmingly
short of breath.
For a slender person of course
she makes nothing of it...
but it seems rather serious to me.
I told her I thought she ought to
make George let her come home.
Let her? Does she want to?
Well, she doesn't urge it,
George seems to like the life in Paris.
He's quite a swell.
In spite of anything she said,
I know she does want to come.
She'd like to be with father,
of course...
I think she's...
well, she intimated one day
that she feared...
she wouldn't get to see him again.
I thought at first she was referring
to his age and feebleness.
Later it struck me
she was actually thinking of her own...
state of health.
I see.
And you say he won't let her
come home?
Oh, I don't think he uses force,
he's very gentle with her.
I doubt if the subject
is mentioned between them.
And yet...
knowing my interesting
nephew as you do...
wouldn't you think that was
about the way to put it?
Knowing him as I do?
Yes.
Yes, I should say that is
about the way to put it.
She is very sick.
It seems to me that
you should return to America.
To be around
the things that she loves.
It's changed.
It's so changed.
You mean the town!
You mean the old place
has changed, don't you dear?
Yes.
It'll change to a happier place
now that you are back in it!
Oh, dear!
You're going to get well again.
When are they going to let me
speak to my daughter?
They told me to stay out of the way
when they carried her in.
Said it might upset her!
I wish they'd let me go on in there
and speak to her! She wants to see me!
You must get something to eat, Georgie.
I know she'd want you to.
I have things ready in the kitchen.
I know she'd want me to.
You'd better go on down.
I don't want anything to eat.
I never thought this thing that's the
matter with her could be so serious.
Mr. George will be right down,
Mr. Morgan, sir.
Thank you, Sam.
- I've come to see your mother, George.
- I'm sorry. No.
Not this time, George.
I'm going up to see her.
The doctor said
she has to be kept quiet.
- I'll be quiet.
- I don't think you should, Eugene.
The doctor said she's going to...
Fanny's right, Eugene.
Why don't you come back later?
All right.
Darling!
- Did you get something to eat?
- Yes, mother.
Oh, you need it.
Yes.
Are you sure...
Are you sure you didn't catch cold
coming home?
- I'm all right.
- Oh, God!
Oh, that's sweet. It's so sweet.
What is?
I get to feel my hand on your cheek.
I can feel it.
I wonder if Eugene
or Lucy know we've come home?
I am sure they do.
Did he ask about me?
Yes, he was here.
Is he gone?
Yes, he is gone.
I should like to have seen him...
just once.
I feel that old familiar
sinking feeling...
that's attended all my previous efforts
to prove myself a business genius!
Well, it looked so right. We saw
how perfectly nicely they worked.
Yes, it was perfect. In the shop!
The only thing we didn't know...
was how fast an automobile
has to go to keep the light going.
I don't understand, just how fast
does it have to go?
Lt is computed, by those enthusiasts
who bought our product...
and subsequently returned it to us
and got their money back.
That people have to go 50 miles an hour
and above to have a real headlight.
Unfortunately,
many people don't care...
to drive that fast, at all times,
after dusk...
- and especially in traffic!
- But isn't that man going to remedy it?
- Can't he at least try?
- Yes, he can try, he is trying!
I'm standing in the office
while he is trying.
George, you startled me!
I can hear you walking up and down
in your room.
You're at it almost every night.
I know your mother
would want you to rest.
I wanted to tell you once more,
that what I did was right.
- About what?
- About everything!
I think she was happy in her life,
and it is my only consolation.
She had a good husband...
and all the comforts and luxuries
that anybody could have had.
Do you deny that what I did
was right?
I don't intend to judge, Georgie,
I know you think what you did was right.
What else was I to do?
How else could I protect her
from the talk?
Lt would've died out before long.
If I hadn't acted as I had,
that slanderous old Mrs. Johnson...
would still be slandering
my mother today!
- No, no, no... she's dead.
- Ok.
- One of the others, they would have!
- No, things are so changed, Georgie.
Other people... one hardly knows
what's become of them.
You mean to tell me...
that if I'd just let things go on,
it would all have turned out fine?
- I'm not saying so.
- You're afraid to!
Lt's not all my responsibility!
Lf you were so sure
that you were wiser than I...
you could've stopped it!
No, Georgie!
No one could've stopped you.
You were too strong and...
And what?
And she loved you too well.
It must be in the sun.
There wasn't anything here but
the sun in the first place.
The earth came out of the sun...
and we came out of the earth.
So, whatever we are...
it must have been in the sun.
We go back to the earth
that we came out of.
The earth will back
to the sun that it came out of.
Time means nothing.
Nothing at all.
So, in a little while...
we will all be back in the sun...
together.
I wish...
Did you want anything, grandfather?
What?
Would you like a glass of water?
No, no I don't want anything.
I wish...
somebody could tell me.
This is the Last Will and Testament
of Major George Amberson.
"I, Major George Amberson,
being of sound mind and body...
do hereby declare,
as I am a gentleman...
that the following expresses
my true desire and sincere wish...
for those of my family
as named herein.
And also I hereby bequeath those items
as mention hereafter...
the said items being rightfully
due from myself, George Amberson".
So much for the great Amberson estate!
I guessed it!
As an expert on prosperity...
my career is disreputable.
But, as a prophet of calamity...
I deserve a testimonial banquet!
We'll survive, Georgie!
You will especially.
I'm too old and accustomed to falling
back on somebody else to survive...
to start a big fight with life.
But an ex-Congressman
can always be pretty sure...
of getting a Consul-ship.
I'll live pleasantly enough.
A pitcher of ice under a Palm tree.
And I'll manage to send you
fifty dollars every now and then.
Yes, I can appreciate that they are all
fine objects, but I am afraid that...
- You understand, right?
- Yes, I do.
Just sign here.
Right this way.
Mother?
Forgive me.
There was this bad Indian chief
that lived in a grove.
He was the worst Indian
that ever lived.
And, his name was, it was Vendona.
It means "writes down everything".
I see.
Vendona was so proud,
he wore iron shoes.
He walked over people's faces
with them.
At last, the tribe decided that it wasn't
a good enough excuse for him...
that he was young and inexperienced.
He had to go!
So, they brought him down to the river
and they put him in a canoe...
and they pushed him off from
the shore and he never come back.
- So, Georgie, I mean, the chief...
- Vendona.
No, they didn't want him back,
of course...
the tribe had lived such
an exciting life under Vendona...
they wouldn't settle down to anything
tame. Couldn't help feeling that way.
Well, I see, so that's why they named
the place "They couldn't help it".
It must've been.
So you are going to stay here
in your garden...
growing to look like a penciled
garden lady in a Victorian engraving.
I suppose I'm like the tribe.
I had too much unpleasant excitement.
It was unpleasant,
but it was excitement.
And I don't want any more.
In fact,
I don't want anything but you.
What was the name of the grove?
- "They couldn't help it".
- No, the Indian name.
Mo-wa-ha-ha.
- That wasn't a native sound.
- I've forgotten.
Well, perhaps you can remember
the Chief's name better?
I don't.
I hope someday you can forget.
Porter!
I may not see you again, George.
It's an odd way for us
to be saying good-bye.
One wouldn't have thought it,
but here we are...
two gentlemen of elegant appearance
in a state of prostitute.
We can't ever tell
what will happen at all, can we?
- Please, take my dog.
- Once I stood where we're standing now...
to say good-bye to a pretty girl...
only it was in the old station,
before this one was built.
They called it the "Deepo".
I was wild about her
and we were to be married.
She had to go abroad first, and when
we came to say good-bye to each other...
we knew we wouldn't see
each other again for almost a year.
I thought
I couldn't live through it.
I don't even know where
she lives now, or if she is living.
If she ever thinks of me,
she probably imagines I'm still...
dancing in the ballroom
at Amberson Mansion.
Whisky, twice.
Life and money.
Both behave like loose quick-sliver
in a nest of cracks.
And when they are gone
you can't tell where...
or what the devil you did
with them.
I believe what I'll say now.
I've always been fond of you, Georgie...
but I can't say
I've always liked you.
But you've received a pretty heavy jolt
and you've taken it pretty quietly...
- and I...
- All the passengers to Washington...
With my train coming into the shed,
you'll forgive me for saying...
there have been times when
I thought you ought to be hanged.
On plaftorm two...
- Washington D.C.
- But I've always been fond of you.
And now...
I like you.
Just for a last word. There is someone
who's always felt about you that way.
Found of you, I mean.
- You might try to...
- All aboard.
- Well, I must run.
All aboard!
Ladies and gentlemen...
this is the last call!
All aboard!
I'll send back the money
as fast as they pay me.
So...
good-bye!
God bless you, Georgie.
By this time tomorrow
we'll be in our new home, Georgie.
I'll make a nice home for you.
Even out of a three-roomed
kitchenette apartment.
You'll see!
Lt'll be good to be among nice people,
people who know who we are.
It's about this new apartment
that I wanted to speak.
What?
I'm sure it's
just what you like, but...
I've decided on another arrangement
for myself.
- You're going to leave me in the lurch!
- Get up, Aunt Fan.
I can't! I'm too weak!
You're going to leave me in the lurch!
For heaven's sake, get up! Stop sitting
with your back against the stove.
No, it's not hot, it's cold...
we ran out of coal a long time ago.
I wouldn't mind if it was hot...
- I wouldn't mind if it had burned me...
- For heaven's sake.
- Get up, come on!
- No! No!
I'd be a burden on you.
I'm to get eight dollars a week.
You'd be paying more
of the expenses than I would.
I'd be paying, I'd be paying,
I'd be paying.
Exactly! You'd be,
you certainly would!
- But you'd be using more of your money.
- Money? I've got 28 dollars!
That is all!
Until the interest is due.
And no, there's no interest 'cos
there's no more principal.
But, but, Uncle George
said you had more money!
Uncle George said you had
enough money to fall back on!
He said you'd bought some stocks
you shouldn't have but that's all...
I lost it all! I lost it all!
Lt seemed a sure way...
of making a fortune out of
a little bit of money.
Good Lord! Did you have
to wait until now to tell me?
I couldn't tell it until I had to!
Lt wouldn't have done any good.
Nothing does any good
in this old world.
I can't. I tried, I tried.
I was trying to look
for a place for us to live.
I knew you didn't want me!
I knew it!
And what of you, you shouldn't
be left alone in this world...
I knew your mother would
want you to be looked after...
and have a home.
I walked my heels down looking
for a place for us to live.
I didn't...
I walked and walked all over this town.
I wouldn't take a streetcar,
no matter how tired I got.
Because I didn't want to spend...
and now,
you want to leave me...
in the lurch.
You want to leave me in the lurch.
Sr. Minafer to see you, sir.
George! The real flair!
The real flair for the law.
That's right!
Couldn't wait till tomorrow
to begin, eh!
I'm delighted that...
- I wanted to say...
- Wait just a minute, young man.
I've prepared a little speech
of welcome, and, I mean to deliver it.
I think you'll find an honest pleasure
in our industry and frugality.
- The law is a jealous mistress, but...
- I can't do it.
What?
I can't take her for my mistress.
I've come to tell you, I have to
find something quicker.
I have to find something
that pays from the start.
Well, sit down, my boy.
- What's the trouble?
- Well, you see sir, it's Aunt Fanny.
She has her heart
set on this apartment.
She's got some old cronies there
and...
I guess she's been looking for
the games of bridge.
But she has her own resources.
No! Lt all went
into the headlight company.
I got her into that.
I feel a certain responsibility
I'm taking the responsibility.
She's not your Aunt, you know!
Sir!
I'm unable to see that
a young man is morally called upon...
to give up a career in the law...
to provide his Aunt with a favorable
opportunity to play bridge!
I feel as if...
I have one or two pretty important
things in my life to make up for.
Well, I can't!
I can't make them up to...
to whom I would.
So it struck me that I might be decent
to somebody else... perhaps...
so that's what I've come
to see you about.
I have an idea, you see!
Well, I'm glad of that!
I can't think of anything, just at
the minute, that pays, from the start.
I suppose that I am about as ignorant
of business as anybody in the world...
but I've heard they pay very high wages
to people who work in dangerous trades.
People who handle touchy chemicals
or high explosives.
I thought I'd see if I couldn't
find something of the kind to do.
As soon as possible!
All right!
You promise not to get blown up...
and I'll go with you to see
if we can find the job!
There you go, George.
- Good morning, Sr. Averson.
- Good morning.
- How are you?
- Fine!
Are you all right, Georgie?
You seem a little down.
- I'm fine.
- Excuse me.
- Really? Are you sure?
- Can I join you?
You seem a little down.
Do you want some cream?
4th of July reminds me.
Have you heard what that
George Minafer is doing?
No, I haven't.
Well, sir, it beats the devil!
My boy Fred told me about it yesterday.
Seems young Georgie is working
for the Acres Chemical Company.
- What does he do?
- He's a nitro-glycerin expert.
He is what?
Doesn't that beat the devil?
Seems to me I heard the average life
in that sort of work is around 4 years!
Agents can't write any insurance
at all for nitro-glycerin experts.
No, I suppose not.
I suppose it would be pass around
the hat for old Fanny, if he blew up.
They say she hasn't got
anything else to depend on.
I suppose not.
I was wondering why you couldn't find
something around your works for him.
He used to be such a tremendous friend
of the family, I thought perhaps you...
No, no.
I haven't anything to offer him.
I don't know that I would myself!
Well... we'll probably see his name
in the paper some day...
if he stays with that job.
Here it is, our Civic History, sir.
The latest version.
Please let me know
if you need anything else.
This old town of ours
is really getting enormous.
I shouldn't mind knowing who he is!
Well, I don't know who he is...
but from his looks,
I know who he thinks he is!
He thinks he's
the Grand Duke Cuthbert.
Riffraff.
Lucy? Lucy?
Lucy?
- Look out!
- Will you get out of the way!
Look out!
- Look out!
- Get out of the way!
- Oh, God!
Now, just stay calm.
- Be careful with him.
- Let's take him to the hospital!
Now, stay calm.
Do you want me to take
you to a private hospital?
No!
Take him to the city hospital
Take me to the city hospital.
He was just standing right
in the middle of the road.
- That is right! I saw it!
- We all saw it!
Stand back, stand back.
Give us some space, please.
- Stand back.
- He was right in front of us!
Some would call it progress,
I would call it shame.
Those darn machines shouldn't be allowed
on the street, as far as I'm concerned.
Funny what he says to the little cuss
that done the damage.
That's all he did call him.
Nothing else at all.
The cuss that broke both his legs
for him and God knows what all.
What was it?
"Riffraff".
What's the prognosis?
We don't know yet.
It's critical.
Nurse.
Do you want something?
There's nothing
in this family business.
Even George Washington...
is only something in a book.
I'll not go home now, Harry,
drive to the City Hospital.
Yes, sir.
Miss Lucy's there. She said she expected
you to come there before you went home.
- She did?
- Yes, sir.
I suppose Mr. Minafer
must be pretty bad.
Yes, I understand he's
liable to get well though, sir.
Fanny?
Eugene!
Where is he?
He is right here.
I will take you.
You must have thought my mother
wanted you to come here...
so that I could ask you
to forgive me.
No! Just to take your hand.
Dearest, Isabel...
Your boy was hurt a few days ago
in a street accident...
run down by an automobile.
At first, I thought I wouldn't go
to see him at the hospital, but...
of course I did.
I thought it would be
hard not to be bitter...
but I found it was easy, he looked
so much like you, dearest one.
As I came in, he said...
"You must've come because you thought
my mother wanted you...
to forgive me".
Lucy sat beside him, radiant.
But for me, another radiance
filled the room...
and I knew
that I had been true at last...
to my true love.
And that through me you had brought
your boy under shelter again.
Done by (c) dCd / February 2014