OK, so, my name's Danny.
And it'd be good
if you had long hair.
Or at least up to yout shoulders -
shoulders would be good.
And I want somebody
who's not just a taker.
You know, somebody who
gives as much as they get.
I want you to do stuff with me
without actually having to be asked.
You know, like, I want you to
really get off on being on my cock -
like, really get off.
Chain me up, or I want you on top.
I want you to get off
with me being in there -
like, right in there, deep.
And I want you to love it.
Tell me you love it and it's like,
I will fuck your brains out.
And I want you to know
that you're fucking me.
[ Click ]
SONG: # I am the one for you #
♪ I am your vitamin C ♪
♪ And you are mine too... ♪
[ Click ]
[ Click, Click, Click, Click, Click, Click ]
Hi.
Or going to your work?
Yeah.
You know,
sort of work their parents do.
OK.
Concert and everyone's going.
Can I?
Plus T-shirts.
Why am I buying Kirsten a ticket?
Well, her dad's gone bankrupt.
[ Chuckles ]
You'll send me bankrupt.
Come on, Mum. Please.
No, I'm sorry. It's too much money.
Mum, do you even care
what I've been going through?
Bonnie!
I have to put up with all this stuff
and I can't even take a friend
to a concert.
- It's too much money.
- Are you serious?
Yes.
- You're seriously saying no?
- That's right.
WOMAN ON ANSWERING MACHINE:
Hi. You've got through to 232.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
MAN ON ANSWERING MACHINE:
Hi, there. It's Dougie Miller.
I just wanted to see
if Chloe's available
for tonight or tomorrow night.
And send me a text
on the usual number.
It'd be great to see her.
[ Engaged Tone ]
[ Beep ]
Uh, Jack, here.
You've got my details.
I heard Chloe's back
from her break,
so if someone could give me a call,
I'm in town tonight, late-ish -
say, 10 o'clock.
Yeah, I'd like to book it.
[ Engaged Tone ]
[ Beep ]
It's Steve.
I've heard a rumour
that Chloe's back there,
so if that's the case,
I'd like to see her ASAP.
You've got my number. Thanks.
[ Engaged Tone ]
[ Beep ]
Are you OK?
Fine.
So, are we OK?
Sure.
See ya.
Have a good night.
I love you.
I love you too.
OK.
[ Click ]
[ Click, Click ]
[ Sighs ]
- What were you doing?
- I was just watching you.
No, you weren't.
[ Groans ] What were you doing?
I was just checking
you were still breathing.
Oh.
[ Groans ]
So, what's all this for?
- I thought you might like some proof.
- Of...?
Of how beautiful you are...
even when you're asleep.
Photographing someone
without asking them?
- It's sick, Nick.
- It's romantic.
It's creepy.
Well, actually, I was thinking
of selling them on eBay.
EBay? Oh!
Yeah, that's deeply hilarious.
You're very funny.
Where's delete?
- [ Camera Beeps ]
- Oh, come on. Leave me one.
Delete. Delete. Delete.
Gone...
...Mr Paparazzi.
Yeah, well, I'll be sure to use
the telephoto lens next time.
Next time, I'll make sure
to smash your camera.
I'm serious.
- I believe you.
- Mmm.
Go easy!
Oh!
[ Lauren Laughs ]
That is game, set and match.
Mwah!
Ah!
Since when have you been so fit?
Oh, I've been doing a lot of yoga.
Oh! You sure can twist and turn.
- The guys are gonna love you.
- Ha!
It's time to take the plunge, Lauren.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I should.
ASH: You'd think she could
have met us at the airport.
Hi, Mum.
LAUREN: Oh, my God!
- [ Gasps ]
- Were you expecting the kids back?
I must have got the wrong date.
Hi!
Oh, gosh!
I wasn't expecting you.
- We emailed.
- I don't read that. I'm far too busy.
What is going on in your world?
- Oh, it's so good to have you back.
- I'm gonna leave you to it.
- Yeah.
- I'll speak to you later in the week.
- Hello, Ash. Hello, Kate.
- Hi.
Come here.
Oh!
This is gorgeous. Thank you.
You too, Kate.
So?
How was it?
How was Hollywood?
Actually...
I really, really liked America.
Ash enrolled in a
digital animation course.
How does that work -
by correspondence?
What is it? Tell me.
There was this scholarship
I found out about.
And I only applied for it as a joke
but I got it.
So I'll be going back.
To stay with Dad.
You got a scholarship
in two minutes flat?
Where from, a drive-through?
No. I applied for it months ago.
I had no idea
that's what you were planning.
I didn't think I'd get it.
That's why I didn't tell you.
It's not just Ash.
I want to go back too. The school
was awesome - much better than here.
- Both of you?
- Sorry.
No. Katie, you are too young.
- Dad said yes, I could.
- Oh, f...
- It's alright with him and Carla.
- [ Sighs ]
[ Sobs ] I think I need a drink.
[ Sobs ]
[ Clattering ]
So, do you ever think about when
you might give it up - give it away?
- You mean like when I win the lottery?
- Yeah.
I've always seen myself in Italy.
You know, get a fleet
of really classy cruisers,
set up a charter operation
somewhere like Positano, Capri...
Oh! It sounds good!
Yeah.
Or just retire there
and do bugger-all.
[ Chuckles ] That sounds
more like your scene.
But do you ever think about it?
If someone offered me the
kind of money I'm making now,
I'd think about it, but until then...
Thank you.
What if someone was to, you
know, sweep you off your feet?
I can stand upright in a cyclone.
Oh, that sounds like a challenge.
Too many good men have died trying.
Besides, I couldn't have you
on my conscience.
So where are you, um...
Where are you off to now, then?
- We don't go there.
- We don't?
No.
I mean, this is just fun, isn't it?
Just two people having good fun.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
Mmm.
Besides which, one of us
is getting a very good bargain.
Oh, yeah? Who's that -
me or you?
That's very funny.
That's... that's very funny.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Phone Rings ]
- Ah. Achilles.
- Hmm? Oh.
Thanks.
Hi, Achilles.
Yeah, I'll be down in just a minute.
Mm-hm.
Thank you.
Chloe's completely booked
for this evening.
But if you'd like to...
You are so overbooked.
Look at this.
Tell me who you want to cancel
and I'll do it.
They're mostly regulars.
- Dougie! Ha!
- [ Dougie Chuckles ]
Hello, sweetheart.
Chloe!
It's good to have you back.
- BOTH: Mmm!
- I missed you.
Now, why don't you relax in th bar
and I will join you as soon as I can.
Can we afford a place like this?
Just shot up and take your shot.
You haven't paid for anything yet.
Maybe we just get pissed, eh?
Not getting cold feet, are we, Para?
No, no.
What do you think they're
gonna do - eat you alive?
Get me a beer and
a Bundy and coke.
[ Chuckles ]
Hello.
- Well, hi.
- Hi.
- Have we seen you guys before?
- Nah.
No, we're just down for the rodeo.
Yeah, Rosso's a champion
bull-rider in the States.
- And Para here is me press agent.
- PAPA: Yeah.
Now, I've always wondered,
after 'Brokeback Mountain'...
We all came out of the closet
after we saw that movie, didn't we?
TIPPI: Is that right?
You'd be hard-pressed to find
a straight cowboy these days.
- You know, that doesn't surprise me.
- Well, I'm gay.
He's crippled and gay.
I oughta get a grant.
[ Rosso Chuckles ]
So, um, what's it gonna take
to get you back on our side?
Well, maybe someone just like you.
Well, that can be arranged.
And if you've got a friend...
Well, if my mate's
gonna be converted back,
he might need two ladies.
And what about you?
Let's just get him organised first.
OK, I'll see what I can do.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Mwah!
You're back on the horse?
Hey, mate, they love ya.
TIPPI: Everyone's asking for you.
[ Laughs ]
I am wanted right now.
See you soon.
[ Phone Rings ]
Hold one moment, please.
[ Mouths ]
Peter.
Yes, I'm here.
I'll be there.
MAN:
...so we get their attention.
No, no, no. I appreciate that.
Tell the Minister to hold off
until the other side
have made their announcement.
Yes, I'll email it to him
later on tonight.
Yes.
No, no, no. Hold tight
and play their bluff.
OK. I'll talk to you then, Michael.
[ Sighs ]
You sound very busy.
Yes, as always.
[ Whispers ] Let's go.
I was gonna remind you
to turn that off.
Is something the matter?
No.
Of course not.
I'll let Heather know you're here.
I don't want my daughter
being raised by a neurotic cow
that thinks it's OK to steal a
husband after 20 years of marriage.
Slut.
Right.
I'm just gonna tell Kate
she can't go.
- Oh, she'll love that.
- Yeah, well...
I don't care.
Mmm!
Sorry, am I shitting you?
Ally's forcing a sale on the house.
- I thought it was yours.
- It is.
Can she do that?
Well, we lived together for more than
two years so she has de-facto rights.
Are you OK with that?
No.
She's got an open house
booked for tomorrow.
Make a sign on your bedroom door -
'Pregnant lesbian sex worker
sleeps here'.
I reckon that'd work.
I don't know, Lauren. I
don't think I want to live there.
It just gives me too much
to think about.
Oh!
Heather, I'm assuming full-on
sex with a paraplegic
is not your thing right now.
- I'm booked.
- Right. He's really hot.
- Paraplegic. Wish me luck.
- Come on.
Good luck.
Heather, um, you should probably
squeeze in a break tonight.
Pardon?
Maybe around 10 o'clock.
Are you feeling OK?
You usually want blood
from a stone.
I think he might want longer,
that's all.
Oh!
It's not about me. [ Chuckles ]
[ Continues Spraying ]
Let me know when he wants tea.
[ Laughs ]
Anything special you have in mind?
Oh, I don't know.
- Surprise me.
- [ Both Laugh ]
OK.
Well, not like... 'walk out and
leave me by myself' surprise me.
No, we know what you mean.
I've been thinking
about this for weeks.
On a big, wide bed
with two... beautiful women.
Thanks.
Hey, no need to thank us.
That's what we're here for.
[ Groans ]
- On the count of three.
- Yep.
- One... two, three, go.
- Aaagh!
OK.
Putty in your hands, girls.
Putty in your hands.
Oh! Nah. Nah.
OK.
Aargh! Ow!
- Yaagh!
- Aaagh!
- Oh!
- [ Laughs ]
- Aaagh!
- Oh!
My goodness!
That's a lovely tat.
- Thanks.
- You've got a huge flag on your bum.
[ Device Ticks ]
I'm, uh, being extra careful.
The sharks are circling.
Stop.
Give it to me.
Undress.
Yes, Mistress Heather.
Excuse me.
That girl there -
is there any chance
that I could, um...
I'm sorry. She's completely booked.
But I'm sure we can
find you someone.
Nah. No, it's just, uh...
Thanks.
OK.
You know, I was doing so well.
I'm sure you were.
It's this preselection - I mean, the
numbers are stacking up against me.
- If I don't...
- Shush!
- Oh!
- This is our time.
Yes, Mistress.
Mmm!
[ Sighs ]
Are you ready?
Yes, Mistress. I'm ready.
Luce?
It's me, Graham Ross.
Rosso.
Oh, my God.
- Rosso.
- Yeah.
[ Laughs ]
Hello! Hey, s-sit down.
What the hell are you doing here?
I was gonna ask you
the same question.
Yeah, well, it's a long story.
So, how have you been? How's
everyone? How's your dad, the farm?
- Are you married?
- Uh, well, uh...
No, not married and...
...there's no farm anymore.
Dad drank it away years ago.
So, what have you been doing?
I'm on the rodeo circuit -
been in the States four years.
[ Laughs ]
Wow. Small world, huh?
Yeah.
- Look, I'm sorry. I've gotta...
- No, no. No.
I just wanted to say hi.
But I don't know -
if you're here when I get back...
I'll be here.
OK. I'll see you then.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
[ Para Moans ]
I think he loves us.
I love you.
PARA: Oh! Oh!
[ Laughs ]
This is the best physio
I've ever had.
Ah! Ah!
[ Laughs ]
Oh... Oh!
[ Moans ]
Nat, I need half an hour
after this client.
You don't have it.
Reschedule my 10 o'clock
or give him to someone else.
He called at nine o'clock
this morning.
Please! I wouldn't ask
if it wasn't important.
Ah! I love this job.
Thanks. I owe you.
It's time for Peter to go now.
[ Gasps ]
Let me see.
Do you like what you see?
Yes. [ Sighs ]
Who are you?
Nobody.
Well, Mr Nobody...
[ Gasps ]
...you are very, very, beautiful.
Do you think so?
Oh, yes.
Absolutely.
[ Breathes Heavily ]
Perfect.
[ Grunts ]
[ Low Buzzing ]
- You like that, don't you?
- Yes, Mistress, I like that.
Oh...
It's good, isn't it?
Ooh, yeah. It's good. Oh!
- Tell me.
- I like it, Mistress.
- Tell me again.
- I like it, Mistress!
[ Breathes Heavily ]
[ Groans Climax ]
[ Slows Breathing ]
I'll leave you alone
to catch your breath.
[ Breathes Deeply ]
[ Pants ] There you go.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah, shoot.
You must have help.
You know, at home, getting
into bed. It must be really hard.
No, no, no.
These just come straight up.
I just roll out,
straight on the bed.
[ Laughs ]
If you weren't a paraplegic,
I would whack you.
LAUREN:
You could've saved our backs.
Look what I would've missed
out on. All that extra physio.
I'll see you in the bath.
You girls got a career in steer
wrestling if this ever goes bust.
Yeah, I'll keep that in mind.
How long have you been
in the chair?
Uh... four days
before my 20th birthday.
I was heading off
towards the States.
Gonna do the Texas circuit.
Is that why you've got the tattoo?
Yeah, I got it after the accident.
Souvenir you get when you're
never gonna get a souvenir.
Hi.
[ Clear Throat ]
This isn't a booking.
Um... unless you wanted it to be.
I just thought we'd have
a drink and a chat.
Yeah, great.
Whiskey?
[ Sighs ]
You're making me embarrassed.
I don't think I should
be dresses like this
with someone I went to school with.
I think you look fantastic.
[ Sighs ] To old times.
Hmm...
It was quite a scandal
when you ran away.
[ Sighs ] I was 14.
And you were never
gonna ask me out.
- Oh, is that why you left?
- [ Laughs ] No.
You were more interested
in Gayle Pierce anyway.
- Only because of her brother.
- What do you mean?
Well, if you had a brother,
I might've pretended
to go after you.
You're gay!
- I always thought everyone knew.
- [ Laughs ]
What are you doing here?
I'm shouting my mate
a double for his birthday.
[ Laughs ] I can't believe this.
[ Laughs ]
Well, at least there was
more chance of me being gay...
- Warren Pierce gay.
- Mmm.
That was before the brought.
No-one's gay in the bush anymore.
[ Laughs ]
You know that big hotel
in the Middle East?
On the point. Built like a big sail.
Burj Al Arab. Dubai.
Are you gonna tell me
that you've stayed there?
I had a client who stayed there
not long after they opened.
- And he flew you over, right?
- Yeah.
So, is it as good
as the photographs?
The hotel or my client?
[ Laughs ] No, it was good.
I'd never been to Dubai before.
It was great. We had a lot of fun.
Mmm. So the rich guys aren't
all that much hard work, are they?
Well, they know
how to buy their fun.
My next trip's to the camping
ground at Diamond Point.
Don't knock camping.
I quite like staying in tents.
Africa, ensuite bathrooms,
servants...
Hey, I was a Girl Guide.
I can rough it if I have to.
- Fortunately, I...
- BOTH: ...don't have to anymore.
[ Laughs ]
- You're OK to get up on your own?
- Yeah. Girl Guide, remember?
I can tie a knot in anything.
I think I'm ready for my tea now.
If you could let Nat know.
[ Breathes Heavily ]
Time goes by so quickly.
[ Sighs ]
Yes, it does.
There's never enough time.
[ Breathes Heavily ]
[ Door Opens ]
Shit.
Howdy. I was just
in the neighbourhood.
Mate of mine's opening
a new bar around here.
- Nice?
- Yeah, yeah, you know.
So, uh, who are we...
Who are we waiting on?
Mel.
Right. She with a regular?
Got someone new?
Oh, just wondering,
'cause, you know,
I just wanna know if we took
the booking for her or if she...
He's a long-term client.
[ Both Moan ]
Hey, Achilles, listen, mate.
Why don't you have
the rest of the night off?
I'll take over here.
I'm cool. I've got nothing
better to do.
No, seriously, why don't you,
uh... get a cab?
She expects me to wait, Nick.
Mate, go home.
You're the boss.
Shall I pour?
It's perfect.
The tea?
Here in this room. It's...
[ Sighs ]
There's a lovely smell.
I like it.
The way the room smells.
What does it remind you of?
- I'm sorry?
- The smell.
What does it remind you of?
A bathing cap my mother once had.
A brand-new doll.
A mat some kids
once rolled me up in.
We were playing a game.
I still remember it.
[ Laughs Softly ]
Of course you do.
Precious moment.
Yes.
And those moments, they...
...they never leave us.
[ internet Messenger
Service Beeps ]
I have the sound of you.
Slim, hips, peachy bum, long legs.
I like long legs.
Wrapped around my head.
I wanna fuck you long and hard
and slow, over and over.
Are you up for it?
Did you read he's going
to stand for preselection?
Now, there's someone I'd vote
for. He knows what he wants.
Does he actually...? You know.
Come?
Yep.
He's very responsive.
I guess there's just something
about... disappearing...
...into yourself.
I think it's about
forgetting yourself.
Your fear, your guilt...
...all your responsibilities.
That would feel great.
Whatever gets you through
the night.
[ Door Slams ]
Done.
Hey.
Oh, come on.
Don't look at me like that.
- Thought we could go out somewhere.
- This wasn't the plan.
So kill me. I'm spontaneous.
Where's Achilles?
I locked him in the boot.
Sort of thing you can do
when you're the boss.
- I just really wanna go home, Nick.
- Too easy, babe.
I mean my home, alone.
[ Mobile Phone Rings ]
- [ Sighs ]
- [ Clears Throat ]
Hello, Mel speaking.
Hi! How are you?
Are you?
Yeah, sure.
Sure, of course I could.
I'm... sure my driver
knows where that is.
OK, see you soon. 'Bye.
I need to go to
the marina in St Kilda.
You just take a booking?
Forget it. I'll get a cab.
- Whoa.
- No, you just stepped over the line.
- Nick, forget it, I'll get a cab.
- I'll take you. Hang on a second.
- I'll take you.
- No, I don't want you to take me.
I know that you won't take
me there, so just forget it.
[ Starts Car Engine ]
[ Tyres Screech ]
I had a blast from the past tonight.
- The other cowboy.
- Is that right?
Yeah. From when I was 14.
It brought back all these memories.
I can't even remember
when I was 14.
- I ran away from home.
- That must have been hard.
Not as hard as staying.
[ Keyboard Taps ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Computer Beeps ]
What are you doing?
- What's this?
- Nothing. It's nothing.
What have you been doing?
Bonnie.
What's nothing?
What have you been doing?
Get over there and don't move.
I mean it, Bonnie.
What is this?
[ Breathes Shakily ] Oh, my God.
...long legs wrapped around mt head.
- Who is this?
- I want to fuck you long and hard.
- He's a friend.
- What's his name?
He's a complete stranger on
the internet. Are you fucking crazy?
- Have you done this before?
- It's none of your business.
You are 14 years old, Bonnie, 14!
- So fucking what?
- [ Gasps ]
That's mine.
- I don't care.
- Give it back!
No! Not if this is
what you're doing with it.
- Mum, give it back.
- Does he know how old you are?
Old enough to have sex.
- No, you are not!
- And to stop having to be a virgin.
What do you mean,
"stop having to be a virgin"?
Everyone's having sex.
Why shouldn't I?
You do it all the time.
Do you have any idea
where all of this comes from?
Hmm?
This, this, this!
[ Shouts ] All of this, Bonnie!
Where do you think it comes from?
The house, the car,
your holidays, your school.
Where? From me, Bonnie.
It's not my fault.
I just wanted us to
have a nice life.
I'm sorry.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Birds Warble ]
[ Sighs ] Is this going
to be another lecture?
- Alright, you can go.
- [ Scoffs ]
You're joking, right?
But it'll be for a trial period.
[ Dryly ] A trial, right.
You may not like living there, I...
So, how long do I get
before you realise
you can't live without me?
- Three months.
- Six.
[ Sighs ] No.
Mum, that's not even
two terms of school.
Alright, six.
But I'm coming to visit
you after three.
Deal. And then we hit
Rodeo Drive, right?
You see, I think you've been
holding off dating because of the kids.
Subconsciously, you have.
Holding yourself back.
I reckon now you're on your own
you're gonna start meeting guys.
I'm telling you,
you need to get out there.
[ Sighs ] Actually,
that's the last thing I need.
Mmm. OK.
Mmm, I'm gonna be really frank.
You can't leave it too long.
Celibacy is insidious.
You get used to it and before
you know it you're stuck with it.
It's something you
used to do, past tense.
Wendy...
...I get all the sex I want.
I mean, with someone else.
I have sex...
...four or five nights a week.
Sometimes several times a night.
[ Inhales ] I fuck men for a living.
That's what I do.
I leave this house, go out,
I have beautiful lingerie and
men pay me to have sex with them.
So, that's it.
Any questions?
[ Sighs ]
Captioned by Grantman Brown