McKenna American Girl
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
I did it, Coach!
McKenna, we've talked
about this before.
Those back handsprings
leading into your dismount
are too advanced.
They're not consistent.
That could be risky for you.
You need to take it
one step at a time.
But it looks so awesome!
McKenna...
I know, I just wanna
impress the judges
at the qualifying meet!
I have to make
the regional competitive team.
For girls my age,
if you want to make it
to the Olympics...
Honey, this isn't
about the Olympics. Remember?
You have a qualifying meet
in three months.
That's just
enough time to perfect
what you already have.
(SIGHS)
You gotta be patient.
We're gonna get you
where you wanna go.
Do you trust me?
Yes.
Besides,
the judges are gonna be
blown away without
the back handspring.
(SIGHS)
(BOTH GIGGLE)
I saw your back
handspring dismount.
It was amazing!
That's the reason
you're the second-best
gymnast on this team.
Second-best?
Second to me, of course.
Just like it'll be in 2016,
Rio summer Olympics.
I'll be up on
the podium with my gold,
you next to me
with your silver.
(MIMICS PHONE RINGING)
Hello! Toulane.
It's reality calling.
I'm gonna be up
there wearing my gold!
(BOTH GIGGLING)
TOULANE: So what do you
think of the new girl?
Sierra?
WOMAN: Okay, Sierra,
let's work on that flip set.
MCKENNA: She seems nice.
In a totally annoying way.
I heard her saying
she gets straight A's.
No competition there.
You know who we so need
to worry about, though?
Megan Murphy from
Performance Plus Gymnasts.
Everyone thinks
she's all that.
Megan is pretty awesome.
But, whatever.
I'm not letting her or
anyone else scare me!
Yeah,
but if they're only taking
three gymnasts for
the competitive team,
we need to make sure
that they pick us!
They will.
What is it?
Are you sad that you've been
second-best to me
since we were three?
No.
(LAUGHS)
Coach Isabelle keeps saying
that I have to stick to
the boring, easy moves.
I feel like
I'm in baby gymnastics!
I can handle the hard moves.
Please,
you can handle anything!
You're a superstar.
We should get back
to work or my mom's
gonna be all over me
for messing around.
Okay.
Ready to work?
Ready to fly!
(BOTH MIMIC EXPLOSION)
(BOTH LAUGH)
Ready?
Let's go.
McKenna, McKenna, guess what?
I did a cherry drop today.
That's awesome, Maisey!
How about you, Mara?
I got nervous.
You'll do it next time.
GRANDMA: Let's go, sweetie.
Okay, let's go, Grandma.
Honey, you need to work
on your floor routine.
But I'm really trying.
It might help if
you didn't goof around
so much during practice.
I'm sorry.
Toulane, this is important.
If you don't make it
to the regional
competitive team,
you'll never have
a chance to become
an elite gymnast
like your sister.
I know. I'll try harder, Mom.
Okay.
(GLASS CLINKING)
MR. BROOKS: I've got
an announcement to make.
I was able to secure
a primo campsite
for this summer's
camping trip.
(ALL CHEERING)
Don't forget to tell Toulane
it's gonna be
the first weekend in June.
It wouldn't be
our annual camping trip
without her.
Got it.
Good.
Honey, how was
the coffee shop today?
Oh, it was great.
There was a line out
the door all morning.
Stop giving all your
chicken to the dog, Maisey.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
(WHINING)
MRS. BROOKS: Anyway,
you know the guitar player
I hired
for Music Mondays,
he didn't show up.
On his first day!
Honey, you could've hired me.
It's not too late.
I can call the rest
of the guys from the band
and we can get
a quick set together...
Oh, honey, you know
I love you, so much.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
But your grunge
college rock band
would probably just scare
my customers away.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, come on.
No one here can resist...
No, no, no,
he's gonna do it!
Cover your ears! Plug!
...the righteous sound
of I Hate Tuesday.
Dad, no, don't do it.
Dad, no, don't!
(SINGING) That was great
for a one day streak
But then came
the weakest day
of the week now
Ready?
(ALL VOCALIZING)
(DOG BARKING)
ALL: I hate Tuesdays
Dad, you're not a rock star,
you're a high
school principal!
(ALL LAUGHING)
A high school principal
who rocks!
You guys are so weird.
Yeah. Maisey, Mara,
why don't you go
play in your room?
Your dad and I want
to talk to McKenna.
Come on, let's go.
Just go play in your room...
No, Cooper!
Okay.
(BOTH SIGH)
McKenna,
your mother and I
got an e-mail
from your teacher,
Mr. Wu, today.
I can totally explain that.
I didn't mean to
feed that French fry
to the class guinea pig,
it just fell out of my hand.
No, no. Not about that.
About you falling
behind in your schoolwork.
Falling behind?
Mr. Wu has noticed
you're having difficulty
turning your assignments
in on time.
He suggested a tutor
from the middle school.
Four days a week
after school.
Four days a week!
No way!
Honey, Mr. Wu
thinks you need it.
And we think
gymnastics is taking up
too much of your time.
Well, there's a lot
going on right now.
I mean, first we
have that demonstration
where we show all
you guys our routines,
and then we have
the qualifying meet
for the regional team.
But I can do
better in school.
On my own.
I promise.
There's a science
quiz tomorrow,
and I'll study
really hard for it.
All right. We'll see
how the quiz goes.
But remember...
I know,
school comes first.
(SQUEAKS)
Okay, Polka Dot,
you can have a treat.
I wish I were a hamster.
You don't have parents
bugging you
about your grades.
You're so lucky. You get
to do your gymnastics
whenever you want.
MCKENNA: "The nuclear envelope
encloses the nucleus,
"separating the contents
from the cytoplasm. "
None of this
makes any sense to me.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
MCKENNA: It was awesome.
I know,
and it was so funny, too.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
So,
are you guys
nervous about the quiz?
Nervous? (SCOFFS)
I don't do nervous.
Yeah, but don't you think
the reading is
sometimes a little confusing?
Um...
You're forgetting,
Sierra gets straight A's.
Don't stress,
you'll be fine.
Oh, yeah,
I don't know why I was
freaking out anyways,
I'm sure it'll be easy.
MR. WU: Okay, everyone,
let's get started.
I hope you've all
studied very hard.
You've got 30 minutes.
Good luck.
MCKENNA: "Name
the differences between
plant and animal cells?
"True or false:
Every cell has a nucleus.
"What is a microscope?
A. A tiny piece of equipment,
(ECHOING) "B. Something used
to study small objects,
"C. A measuring tool...
"Specialized cells
do very specific...
"What part of
the cell controls..."
(CONTINUES
READING INDISTINCTLY)
McKenna,
can I see you for a moment?
MRS. BROOKS: I just
don't understand it. It's
so not like you to cheat!
I tried to do it on my own
but it was like...
I couldn't remember
anything I was reading.
(SIGHS) I don't know,
okay?
I'm sorry.
It's time to
meet that tutor.
Mr. Wu had to give you
a zero on the quiz.
He did?
MR. BROOKS: Yeah.
He thinks you might
have a problem with
reading comprehension.
He does?
Yeah. It happens a lot.
When I was
an elementary-school teacher,
I used to
see it all the time.
Mr. Wu says a lot
of fourth graders
deal with this.
There's even a name for it,
"fourth grade slump."
What's that?
Well, you know how to read.
Now it's all
about understanding
what you're reading.
That's where
you're getting stuck.
But I can't get
a tutor right now.
I have so much going on.
You mean gymnastics?
Well, yes, gymnastics.
Making the regional team
is the most important thing
to me in the whole world!
McKenna, listen up,
because here's the deal.
No tutor, no gymnastics.
Your school work
has to come first.
You're gonna start
with the tutor tomorrow.
Okay.
Thanks.
And we'll discuss
your punishment
for cheating later.
(SIGHS)
Great.
McKenna?
Hey. I'm Josie.
So you're my tutor?
Yep! Have a seat.
As you can see,
I've already done that.
I call him Lightning.
Cool. I like the color.
Thanks.
So, I guess
you've been having
some reading problems?
So my teacher says.
But I really
don't see how I could.
I mean,
I used to love to read...
Used to? But not anymore.
I don't know, it's boring.
And I'm really busy
with gymnastics.
Oh, yeah, that's right,
you're a gymnast.
Well, maybe you
can think of
studying with me
as gymnastics
for your brain.
Hi, did the book
I reserved come in?
Um...
LIBRARIAN: Yeah.
Great, thanks.
No problem.
(SIGHS)
Sorry, I dropped my pencil.
Actually,
I'm already gonna be
late for gymnastics.
So, can we start?
Yeah. I have
a flute lesson after this.
So let's make
the most of our time.
If that's okay
with your pencil.
Right.
Okay.
So, let's work on this today.
You said you had trouble
with a quiz, right?
I guess.
Okay, here you go.
Where were you?
What do you mean,
where was I?
It's Wednesday!
We always get smoothies
before practice
on Wednesdays.
Oh, right. Sorry,
I guess I spaced out.
So, are you psyched
for the demonstration
this weekend?
I can't wait to show you up
with my killer beam.
I don't know,
my mom keeps saying
I need more work
on my floor routine.
She says
I've been goofing off.
You have not!
And besides,
it's just a demonstration.
They're not even
gonna be judging us!
Is something wrong?
No, I'm just super thirsty.
MCKENNA: "...the dog would
have to go back to its owner.
"Julie's mother had
to insist even though
"Julie wanted to
keep the dog for herself.
"He was so sweet and playful
and he seemed to
really like her.
(ECHOING) "But she realized
that her mother was right.
"The dog didn't belong to her,
even though she found him.
"So she decided
to return the dog
to his owner.
(CONTINUES
READING INDISTINCTLY)
"Maybe she'd get
her own dog, someday."
You read aloud
really well.
So, how do you think
Julie feels at
the end of the story,
after she decides
to give her dog back?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
I've got another idea.
But these are books
my 5-year-old sisters read!
You really think
I'm such a loser
I need to read
kindergarten books?
You're not a loser, McKenna.
Sometimes we have to
go back to the basics,
and go back to
what feels easy.
Don't you ever do
that in gymnastics?
You sound just like my coach.
And I'm sorry,
but this is not gymnastics!
I don't think
this is gonna work.
I think I need to
get another tutor.
Okay, well,
that's your choice.
I'll tell Mr. Wu.
I'm sure you can find
another tutor who's
more your style.
Hi.
Hey.
Tell me
the theme of the story.
Go!
Um...
(MIMICS BUZZER)
Sorry, too slow.
Next question.
(SNORING)
What does the main
character learn? Go!
Uh...
(MIMICS BUZZER)
Sorry, too slow, again.
(SNORING)
Who are the main characters
in the story? Go!
(MIMICS BUZZER)
What is the setting
of the story? Go!
(SNORING)
(MIMICS BUZZER)
Too slow!
(SNORING)
Worst tutor ever.
There has to be someone else!
There's Josie.
But Josie makes me
feel like a baby...
McKenna, enough is enough.
You need a tutor.
And Josie is a great one.
Okay.
Good.
And good luck
on your gymnastics
demonstration.
Thanks.
Welcome, everyone.
The Shooting Star gymnasts
and I
are so excited to
show off for you
a little bit today!
In a little less than
three months, our girls
will be trying out
along with all
the other gymnastic clubs
in the area,
to make the regional
competitive team.
Now, these girls
have been working
really hard.
But today is just for fun,
so let's get on with it.
And first up is
Sierra Kuchinko!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
At least she
didn't fall this time.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Wow!
Good luck, McKenna.
Thanks, Coach Isabelle.
Remember,
stick to your routine.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
ISABELLE: And now,
McKenna Brooks on the beam.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
See that?
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(EXHALES)
(BONES CRACKING)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(CRIES OUT)
No!
No, McKenna!
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
Ow!
(GROANING)
McKenna...
(SOBBING)
I'm sorry, Coach.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
MRS. BROOKS: You're all right.
MR. BROOKS:
Let's get some ice.
MRS. BROOKS: Just try to
relax. Try to breathe.
Just breathe. That's a girl.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(LIGHTNING CRACKING)
MR. BROOKS: Come on over
to the couch, McKenna.
Let's get your foot up.
Here you go, honey.
Yeah.
How about some ice cream?
Cookies 'n Cream
can't help a broken ankle.
(SIGHS)
McKenna, Coach Isabelle
warned you not...
Mmm-mmm.
Honey, it's just eight
weeks in a cast. It's
not the end of the world.
It is the end of
the world for me!
Eight weeks means
my cast comes off
three weeks before
the qualifying meet!
You know what?
The doctor said
you can start exercises
that don't involve
that foot in two weeks.
Maybe it will all work out.
In the meantime,
you can spend more time
on your homework,
which is more important.
Right.
Whatever.
McKenna...
MRS. BROOKS: McKenna...
McKenna!
You guys are
probably glad this happened,
so I have nothing
to do but study.
You don't mean that.
McKenna!
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SOBBING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
McKenna!
I was sorry to hear
about your injury.
May I talk to you
for a second?
Sure.
Josie can meet you
tomorrow in the library
after school to start
your sessions again.
Yeah, okay. Thanks.
What was that all about?
Um...
I'm gonna leave class
a little early tomorrow.
To start physical therapy.
Physical therapy in a cast?
How's that gonna work?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
(SIGHS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
TOULANE: Where are you going?
Wow.
That's awesome.
I've never seen them
rehearse before.
I never should've quit dance.
I could totally
rock that move.
(GIGGLES)
Wow, you really
would be great at that.
Better not let your mom
see you goofing off. (LAUGHS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Right.
Hey,
you're lucky you don't have
to be in practice today.
Sierra is being
extra annoying.
She's like, "I'm gonna
have a slumber party
for the whole team!"
She's just trying
to make friends.
Why can't I say one
little thing about her
without you
jumping in to defend her?
I mean, if you like
her so much,
why don't you make her
your new best friend?
What are you talking about?
And what's your deal
with Sierra anyway?
I don't know,
it's just...
You must be hanging out
with somebody else
because I don't even know
where you are half the time.
I don't have to let
you know where I am
every five seconds, okay?
And I've got lots
of extra pressure
on me right now.
Like what?
You know,
with my foot and stuff.
Right. Whatever.
See you later.
(SIGHS)
Okay, there you go.
Triple espresso.
Hope you're planning
to be up all night.
Thanks.
Could you take this
up to Phillip, please?
Oh, there's my daughter.
MRS. BROOKS:
McKenna! Hey, baby!
(SIGHS) This is
the first time I have been
able to sit down
since this morning!
(EXAGGERATED) Mmm!
(SIGHS)
What? Is there
something here?
Here?
You would tell me, right?
Yeah.
Oh, I bet you would.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay...
Did I get it?
Yep.
Okay.
So, it's pizza night!
I was thinking of
bucking the system
and ordering from Antonio's.
What do you think?
Wherever is fine with me.
Wherever? Are you okay?
What's happening?
You're usually
filled with opinions
about where we order.
Sorry. I'm just stressing.
Tomorrow I start up
with Josie again.
And that's a bad thing?
I don't know!
I mean, Josie
treats me like a baby.
Oh, honey, I know
how hard this is for you.
I know.
You've always been
my strong-willed,
hard-charging little girl.
(KISSING) Mmm!
You were even born...
Say it with me.
...two weeks early.
Two weeks early.
Just ready to get out there
and take on the world.
Not anymore.
Now I can't seem to
do anything right.
And there's another thing.
There is? What?
Having a tutor, Mom,
it's embarrassing.
What's so funny?
(LAUGHS) No, no,
nothing, nothing.
It's just,
you know, honey,
you and I are a lot alike.
How?
Well, we both feel
like we should be
able to handle
everything on our own.
And sometimes we go too far,
and things sort of
get off balance.
You know how,
when you're on
the balance beam,
if you lean a little
too far to the right
or the left you fall off?
That's only the first thing
we have to learn.
Oh, okay, Little Miss Expert.
Well, that's the point.
It's the same in life.
You have to
have some balance.
Like, why do you think
I left the bank and
opened this coffee shop?
Um...
You like coffee?
Yes. And, I needed to get
some balance in my life.
I needed to be my own boss.
Yay, me!
And also, I needed to
be there for you guys
after school.
And I thought I could
do it all on my own,
be there for the twins,
take you to practice,
be home to make dinner.
It was overwhelming.
And your grandma came to me,
and offered to help.
And guess what?
What?
I was embarrassed.
Embarrassed to admit
I couldn't do it
all on my own.
But your grandmother
taught me something.
You know what that is?
What?
Nothing wrong with
needing a little help.
Thanks for meeting me again.
Look, I know that Mr. Wu
forced you to come here
and you don't
want to be here.
But, can we at least try
to make the best of it?
Um...
Okay.
Great. So, let's start
with science, probably.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
All righty then.
So, science...
I better go look
for another book!
McKenna...
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Oh, I just need to find
a book about oceans
for science class.
Whoa!
(ALARM RINGING)
Uh-oh.
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) Thank you.
Oh, well, guess we'll have
to try again Thursday.
Not if you spend
the whole time hiding again.
What?
Look, I get it that
you're embarrassed
to have a tutor,
but this is not gonna work
unless you give it a chance.
So, I hope you're
ready to do that
by Thursday.
McKenna, wait...
Toulane.
I really love how hard
you're working today,
but why don't you
take a break, now?
I can't.
My mom says my floor
routine looks messy.
I think I need to
keep working on it.
I mean, my sister made it
to the Olympic trials
in that event!
Yeah,
but then Tasha fell
and she broke her wrist
and couldn't compete.
You know there is
such a thing
as training too hard.
Besides, gymnastics
is supposed to be fun!
Tell that to my mom.
Um...
I just wanted to
tell you something.
I had a tutor too.
You did?
But you have straight A's.
Now I do, but I used to
be really bad at math.
So, I needed help.
But now, math is
a lot easier for me.
Please don't tell anyone
I have a tutor.
I mean,
I know you had one and all,
but I'm not ready for anyone
to know about mine.
I won't. I promise.
I understand.
Thanks, Sierra.
Look, you were right.
I was mad that
I had to be here
and embarrassed
to have a tutor.
But I get it.
You're just trying to help.
Geez, took you long enough
to figure that out.
I'm ready to try
things your way.
I really need your help.
Wow. This is like
a whole new McKenna.
Yep!
Cool, then
let's get started.
Okay.
Oh.
Should we read this one?
Actually, that's my book.
Oh. Are you into horses?
Kind of. I've actually
always wanted to ride,
but, you know...
People in wheelchairs
can ride horses, can't they?
Yeah, they can, but...
Quit changing the subject
and let's get back to work!
Okay, let's try it again.
(READING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(LAUGHING)
"'Well, surely
you must know,'
said the princess,
(ECHOING) "'that the queen
watches over me
with a magic looking glass."'
(GRUNTS)
I can't. I don't get it!
It's okay.
Don't be frustrated.
(SINGING)
(GASPS)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
The truth is,
you are really improving.
You're doing great.
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks.
(GIRLS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
You know, if you wanted
to do something
more challenging...
Okay.
(LAUGHING)
Sorry.
Okay, let's start
with this one.
You wanna try that?
We can move on to
something more challenging.
What was that noise?
I almost jumped
out of Lightning!
(GIGGLES)
You're awesome, Josie.
Thank you.
So, are you going to
introduce me to
your secret awesome friend?
Toulane?
What're you doing here?
Don't change the subject.
You're totally busted.
Physical therapy?
You lied to me!
Look, I'm sorry I lied.
But give me
a chance to explain...
Oh, I get it.
You've made a new
group of friends.
Sierra, and...
Whatever your new
friend's name is.
She's not my friend,
she's my tutor.
I mean,
she's my friend and my tutor.
And her name is Josie.
You have a tutor?
Why didn't you tell me?
I was embarrassed, okay?
I would never keep
a secret from you.
Not cool, McKenna.
I have to go
get ready for the
regional competition.
Have fun sitting
on the sidelines.
Only you would
want to walk the dog
while you're
still on crutches.
(BARKING)
Cooper! Cooper, Cooper!
(LAUGHING)
At least I'm
getting an arm workout!
Hey, way to look
on the bright side.
And look,
only two weeks from Thursday
until that cast comes off.
Is there any way
we can ask the doctor
if they can
move it up earlier?
Because, I'm nervous
I'm not going to
have enough time
to practice for
the qualifying meet.
We are gonna
worry about practicing
without the cast
when it's time to
practice without the cast.
Which is
two weeks from Thursday.
Fine. Two weeks
from Thursday,
but not one day later.
Oh, hey, listen...
Cooper, sit.
Um... We need to talk about
the family camping trip.
Your dad found out
he has a conference
that first week in June.
But he called
the park to reschedule,
and there is an opening,
but it's next weekend.
And we just think
with your cast...
Mom, I am not letting my cast
keep me from camping.
You're sure?
Absolutely.
Great. This time,
you and Toulane
can have your own tent.
You don't have to
share with the twins.
Um...
I think Toulane might
be busy that weekend.
Okay.
Just let us know.
Hey, can Josie come, too?
Yeah. That's a great idea.
Yeah, okay.
I'm so glad you guys
are becoming friends.
I guess we are.
She's pretty cool, Mom.
And she's like
the smartest person
I've ever met!
I'm going to see
her mom tomorrow night
at my Women in
Business meeting.
Maybe she and Josie's dad
will want to come along.
How does that sound?
Sounds great!
Yeah? Okay. Okay.
And you're sure you
and Toulane are okay?
(DOG BARKING)
Cooper! Cooper!
Yeah, I'm sure.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Toulane.
Toulane!
Can I talk to you?
Why? So you can
lie to me again?
Look, our family camping trip
got moved to next weekend.
And, even though
we're in a fight,
it wouldn't be
the same without you.
You're like
a member of our family.
You still want me to come?
Of course!
And Josie and her parents
are coming too.
And we can all hang out.
No, thanks.
I'm busy next weekend.
Fine. There wasn't
enough room in the tent
for you anyways.
MCKENNA: Geez,
this is hard.
It must be even
harder for Josie.
I feel bad for her.
How's she gonna
go hiking with us?
McKenna,
did you forget
that you might have
trouble hiking, too?
Oh, no! I totally
didn't think about that!
Well, luckily for you,
the world's coolest dad did.
I can't believe you
found this place, Dad.
Yep, and this path
is supposed to lead
to a pretty
amazing waterfall, too.
Told you I was
the world's coolest dad!
Don't push it.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Oh, wow.
So, what do you think?
I think I'm gonna
call mine Thunder.
And Thunder is gonna
beat Lightning
to the waterfall.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
You wanna race me?
You bet.
First one to get
to the waterfall
gets the first s'more?
You're on.
It's on.
(LAUGHING) Okay.
You're gonna lose.
All right.
You're going to lose.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
On your mark.
Get set. Go!
Whoo!
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Whoo-hoo!
(EXCLAIMS IN DELIGHT)
MCKENNA: Oh, no.
Eat my dust!
You forgot one thing,
thunder always
comes after lightning!
(JOSIE WHOOPING)
Can't beat the pro, McKenna.
(GRUNTS)
JOSIE: Whoo-hoo!
(SIGHS)
Uh-huh!
(LAUGHS)
Beat you, girl.
(EXHALES)
Wow!
You officially kicked butt.
Yeah, well,
I mean, I have had
a lot of practice.
But yeah,
yeah, I did kick butt!
(BOTH GIGGLE)
But, who cares
though, right?
Look at that.
(SIGHS)
Whoa.
(WHISPERS) Whoa.
Hey, Josie,
come check this out.
Oh.
Don't feel weird.
It's okay.
I can see from here.
It is pretty amazing, huh?
Yeah, it is.
I mean, when I see
something like that,
I don't feel as different
from everybody else.
That waterfall
is more powerful
than any of us.
Even the fastest,
strongest person
in the whole world.
MR. BROOKS: Don't worry,
girls, I'm almost there!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So, double or nothing?
It's on!
It is on!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Gonna beat you!
Oh, no, you aren't!
(LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
JOSIE: You're gonna
be sore tomorrow.
I'm just letting you know.
I'm already sore, yes.
Hi.
Hey.
MRS. BROOKS: You got
everything you need?
Um... Yeah.
Yeah.
Good. Okay.
McKenna, I don't know
what you two did
to your dad today,
but he's in our tent
making a sound like this...
(MIMICS SNORING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
All right.
Good night, girls.
Night, Mrs. Brooks.
Night, Mom.
(SOFTLY) Good night.
Okay, I can't believe
I ate five s'mores!
You know, the first one
was the best, though.
Nothing beats
the sweet taste of victory.
And since I beat you twice,
the victory was
twice as sweet.
(LAUGHING)
Okay, okay.
I'll stop.
Hey, I'm used to
smack talk.
Toulane and I do it
all the time.
When we were talking
to each other, I mean.
I think this is
the biggest fight
we've ever had.
Whatever. I'm tired
of obsessing about it!
Well, maybe you could
try and put yourself
in Toulane's shoes.
Like, you know,
today in the wheelchair.
You got to see what it
was like in my shoes.
Well, I know
her mom pushes her
a lot in gymnastics.
She watches her like
a hawk during practice.
That doesn't sound
very fun.
Yeah. But just because
her mom is hard on her
doesn't mean she has
to take it out on me.
Can we not talk
about Toulane anymore?
Yeah, sure.
I'm kinda tired anyway.
I think I'll
just close my eyes
and replay my
moment of victory.
Oh, wait,
my two moments of victory.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Okay! Okay!
No more pillow fights.
I'll be watching you.
Night, Josie.
Good night, McKenna.
MCKENNA: Sleep with
one eye open tonight.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
MCKENNA: "During her
short life only one thing
had troubled her,
"and that thing was
'the place' she was to be
taken to some day.
"The climate of India
was very bad for children,
"and as soon as possible
they were sent away from it,
(ECHOING) "generally to
England and to school."
"She had seen other
children go away..."
"She had seen
other children go away,
"and had heard their
fathers and mothers talk
"about the letters
they received from them.
"She had known
that she would be
obliged to go also,
"and though sometimes
her father's stories
"of the voyage
and the new country
"had attracted her,
she had been troubled
"by the thought that
he could not stay with her."
So, why do you think
she's being sent away?
Because it's not
healthy for her
to stay in India,
because of the weather there.
Right. So, why is it
such a big deal
for her to go away?
Because... Well,
first of all, because
she won't be with her dad!
So, what else do you
think might happen?
Well, I bet she'll
be nervous at first,
but then she'll end up
making new friends
and having
a new life in England!
(LAUGHING) You got it!
I got it!
I can't believe it! I got it!
I really understood it!
I know.
Thank you so much, Josie.
I don't know how
I could have ever
done it without you.
In gymnastics,
Toulane and I have
this victory handshake.
Here, let me show you.
Okay.
Ready? You go boom, back...
Back.
And then fist bump.
Fist bump.
(MIMICS EXPLOSION)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
That's really cool.
I like it.
We should do that.
Yeah, we should.
Uh... So, I've been wanting
to tell you something.
You know how
I've always wanted
to ride horses?
Well, I found a place
that lets me do that.
It's called Hearts & Horses
and it's
a special training center
for kids with disabilities.
That's awesome!
I know! I signed up
about a month ago.
Actually,
you kind of inspired me.
Really?
Yeah. I mean,
you're so fearless, you know.
And it's been
really cool so far!
So, the thing is,
my trainer thinks
that I'm ready to
move from a pony to
a horse this Thursday.
It's a pretty big deal,
and I'd love it
if you could come
for moral support.
Not that I'm super
nervous or anything.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I'd love to come.
Cool.
Wait, this Thursday?
That's when I'm
getting my cast off.
Oh, right, right...
Maybe you could move it
to the next day?
It would mean a lot to me
if you could be there.
Well, maybe...
No, I really can't.
With the regional
competition coming up,
I need all the practice
I can get.
Um... Yeah, I...
I get it.
Don't be upset.
Can't you get that this
is a big deal for me?
Once I get my cast off,
I can finally do
gymnastics again!
I'll finally be able to
get back to my real life.
Right. And I'm not
a part of your real life.
And I guess I'm
just your fake friend.
No, that's not what I said!
Can't you understand
how hard it's been for me,
being stuck in this library,
barely being able to move...
Believe me,
I understand
what that's like.
Josie,
I didn't mean it like that!
It's fine.
I have to go.
See you around, McKenna.
Josie, wait.
Won't I see you
tomorrow for tutoring?
No.
I think we're
done with tutoring.
You've really gotten
the hang of reading.
So, you don't
need me anymore.
I'll tell Mr. Wu, okay?
Your next math quiz
is next Tuesday. And...
(BELL RINGING)
Wait!
Before you all trample me
like a herd of rhinos!
(STUDENTS GIGGLING)
This is a list
of book titles.
You can choose any
one of these to read.
And next month on the 15th,
you're gonna
give an oral report,
demonstrating
your understanding
of the book's
content and themes.
See ya tomorrow.
The 15th?
That's the day after
the qualifying meet!
I know.
Looks like we're
gonna be crazy-busy!
There's no way
I can do it.
There's no possible way
I can do it!
It's gonna be okay.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Thanks.
Bye.
(WHISPERS) Bye.
(PLAYING SOFT MUSIC)
The truth is,
you are really improving.
You're doing great.
Thanks.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You got it!
I got it!
I don't know how I could have
ever done it without you.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Um...
Hey, Josie.
It's me, McKenna.
Ready for the big ride?
I'm really glad you came.
Hey,
that's what friends are for.
Real friends.
Right.
This place is pretty cool.
I know, it really is. I...
(WHINNYING)
Easy, Dusty.
Easy now.
COWBOY BOB: Hey, Josie.
Is that the horse
I'm going to be riding?
No. That's Dusty.
He's a new horse.
New horses like
Dusty get spooked
at the littlest things.
You'll be riding Snowflake.
Come here, Snowflake.
Come here, girl.
Come on.
She's much more experienced.
You're not going to fall.
I'll be right there with you
every step of the way.
MCKENNA: Listen, Josie.
Coach taught us this
cool breathing exercise
that might help you.
Take a deep breath,
and imagine you're
breathing in blue skies
and breathing out gray ones.
So, ready? Here...
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Blue skies in.
(EXHALES)
Gray skies out.
Thanks, McKenna.
I do feel a little better.
I think I'm ready.
It's okay.
You can do it.
Come on, Snowflake.
I knew you could do it.
(LAUGHING)
Whoo! Yeah!
Look at you!
Go, Josie and Snowflake!
You okay up there?
MCKENNA: Whoo-hoo!
Bring her home!
I'm gonna call her Snow.
(CHUCKLES)
(SNORTING)
(NEIGHING)
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, Dusty!
Whoa, whoa, girl!
(GRUNTING)
DUSTY'S RIDER:
That's it, boy.
Come on now.
COWBOY BOB: Whoa!
Easy, Snowflake.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come here, Snowflake!
Easy!
(GRUNTS)
(DUSTY NEIGHING)
(SNORTING)
Good girl. Easy, girl.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
COWBOY BOB:
Good eye, McKenna.
I'm sure glad
your friend was here.
Me too.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Hey, McKenna.
What are you doing here?
Josie invited me.
I hope
you're not mad.
I just thought that
you guys should talk.
Oh.
Uh... I'm gonna go help
Cowboy Bob groom Snowflake.
I'll be back.
Weren't you supposed to
get your cast off today?
Or was that another lie?
Look, I'm sorry
I lied about Josie.
I was embarrassed.
Okay? Having a tutor
made me feel like...
Like a loser.
Can't you understand that?
Maybe. But I don't
understand why
you'd come here
instead of
getting your cast off.
What about making
the regional team?
Don't you care about
gymnastics anymore?
We're supposed to
be in this together.
Of course I still
care about gymnastics.
Just...
Josie really...
Right. Josie.
First you invite her
on our camping trip,
and then you showed her
our secret handshake.
I'm sorry, okay?
I was excited that day.
I finally understood
what I was reading.
(SIGHS)
I'm sure that sounds dumb.
It's not that dumb.
Toulane,
I'm friends with Josie.
But that doesn't
mean she's going
to replace you.
We've been friends
since we were three.
You mean I've been
kicking your butt
since we were three.
So, friends again?
Friends again.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So, ladies.
With the regional qualifying
meet just three weeks away,
I expect you to make
the most out of practice.
That means no fooling around.
That means focus.
Very nice, Sierra!
Good job!
You've been working hard,
and it's really showing.
GIRL: Look who it is!
McKenna!
You got your cast off!
(LAUGHS) That's right.
Yes!
(ALL CHEERING)
Thank you. Thank you.
(GIGGLES)
Are you sure you wanna
do the dismount today?
Yeah.
Okay.
I just don't remember
it being so high up.
Well, it's the first time
you've been up
since the accident.
Of course you're gonna
be a little bit scared.
Just take it easy.
Come on.
I'm kinda freaking out.
Well, back off then.
Why don't we just go
work on the low beam?
No.
I only have a few more weeks.
I have to keep trying.
Okay.
Come on down, McKenna.
Come on.
Why can't I do it, Coach?
Well,
you've healed physically,
but I think the mental
healing is just gonna
take a little more time.
You can't keep
putting so much pressure
on yourself.
But, if I don't make
the regional competitive team,
everything I've worked for
since I was three
will be done for nothing.
Oh, McKenna, I love that
you have big dreams.
You really have to
take it one step at a time.
All you can do is your best.
The future will
take care of itself.
Why do adults always
say stuff like that?
(CHUCKLES) Because it's true.
Now go stretch and try
not to worry so much.
Okay?
So, are you totally psyched
to get your cast off?
I guess.
I just don't know how
I'm going to do all this.
Get ready for the meet
and finish my report
for Mr. Wu.
Either I'm going to
fail at the report,
or fall on my dismount again.
Or both!
It's too much for me
to handle on my own.
McKenna, it's okay,
calm down.
Who said anything about
doing it on your own?
You sound
just like my mom.
Hey, she's right.
You've got me,
Josie, your family.
Now,
I don't want to see any more
tears from you, young lady.
Okay, now you really
sound like my mom.
It's kinda creepy.
(BOTH LAUGH)
MCKENNA: "Despite
spraining her ankle,
"American gymnast
Kerri Strug managed to finish
"her second required vault
in the 1996 Atlanta Olympics.
"Her heroic move
clinched a gold medal
for the United States team."
I remember watching
Kerri Strug on TV.
It was amazing.
She must have been
so scared,
but she still managed
to land that vault.
(GRUNTS)
Come on.
You can do it.
(GRUNTS)
(READING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS LOUDLY)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Come in.
We knew you wouldn't
want to break for dinner.
But you do need
to carbo-load.
Thanks.
I never thought
I'd see you study
the night before
a big gymnastics meet.
Me neither. But I have
to finish this report.
And it was so cool
reading about other athletes,
it didn't even
feel like homework!
So, how are you feeling
about the meet tomorrow?
I still haven't
stuck my dismount
on the beam.
Coach Isabelle says that
I'm still holding back.
But every time I go up there,
I think I'm gonna fall.
I can't...
I can't attack it
like I did before.
I guess I'm scared.
Well, what's the worst
that could happen
at the meet?
I blow it and fall down.
And then I don't get to be
a competitive gymnast
like I've dreamed of
being my whole life.
I don't even know who I am
without gymnastics!
I do.
You are
my wonderful daughter.
Come here.
And my
wonderful granddaughter.
Yeah.
(GRANDMA CHUCKLING)
I have something for you.
(SOFTLY) Oh, my goodness.
It's beautiful.
Thanks, Grandma.
This is for you
to remember that
no matter what
happens tomorrow,
you're always
a star to us.
Always.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
Please welcome
the Keystone Kips!
Flippant Gymnastics!
Panther Gymnastics!
Fantastic Gymnastic!
Bring Your Clap!
Shooting Star Gymnastics!
And Performance Plus!
McKenna!
She sees us.
Hi, baby!
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
ANNOUNCER: Good afternoon
to everyone.
And welcome to
this year's
regional qualifying
gymnastics competition.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: Floor
routine competition
begins in 10 minutes.
All participating
gymnasts please report
to the judges' table.
Whoa. She's good.
Yeah, Megan Murphy
is pretty much
a shoo-in for
one of the three spots.
Good luck today.
Thanks. You too.
ANNOUNCER: All uneven bar
competition begins
in 10 minutes.
JOSIE: McKenna.
You came!
Of course I did.
I would not miss this.
How are you feeling?
You know how you said
that I was fearless?
I don't feel
that way right now.
I know you can do this.
You were brave
that day at the ranch,
and you'll be brave
out there today, too.
Come here.
Good luck, okay?
McKenna,
have you seen Toulane?
I can't find her anywhere.
Floor exercise
starts in five minutes
and she's up second.
Don't worry.
I'll find her.
Okay.
Toulane?
(SNIFFLING)
What's going on?
I threw up.
Oh, no! Is it nerves?
Or are you sick?
Yeah, I'm sick.
I'm sick of my mom
wanting me to be
as good as my sister
before her stupid injury!
I'm sick of the pressure!
I'm sick of all of it!
Sometimes I wish
I would break my wrist.
Or my ankle.
Then I'd have an excuse
not to do this anymore.
But what about going
to the Olympics together?
Don't you still want that?
Well, I know I got mad at
you for keeping a secret,
but I guess
I have a secret too.
What is it?
I don't want to
do this kind of
gymnastics anymore.
What? Why?
It's not fun
for me anymore.
My mom never
lets me forget that
all that matters is winning.
You're the only thing
keeping me here.
Remember when we watched
the rhythmic gymnasts
practice?
The way they just let go,
and feel the music.
(INDISTINCT CHEERING)
That's what I want to do.
Well,
how about you go out there
and try to talk to your mom?
I can't talk to her now!
Why not?
Because...
Because I just can't.
Look, I'm not sure
I want to go out there either.
I'm really scared
I'm going to fall.
But, I need to do this.
I guess we both do.
Together.
(SIGHS)
All right. Let's go.
Ready to work?
Ready to fly.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Oh! Are you all right?
Everything is fine.
Okay.
Then let's do it!
All right?
Next up is
Toulane Thomas from
Shooting Star Gymnastics!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoo! Go, Toulane!
Next up,
McKenna Brooks from
Shooting Star Gymnastics.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING WILDLY)
Next is
Sierra Kuchinko
on the uneven bars.
Whoo! Go, McKenna!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING WILDLY)
Whoo!
Go, Sierra!
Next up,
Megan Murphy
from Performance Plus.
ANNOUNCER: Next up,
Toulane Thomas from
Shooting Star Gymnastics.
(INAUDIBLE)
MALE ANNOUNCER: Score is 9.5.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
So far, so good, McKenna.
You've done great!
Yeah, but what if
I mess up on the beam?
Oh, you're not gonna
mess up on the beam.
Beam is your best event.
Go get 'em, okay?
FEMALE ANNOUNCER: Next up,
on the balance beam,
McKenna Brooks from
Shooting Star Gymnastics.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
This is it.
Knock 'em dead.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Good.
Go, McKenna!
(INHALES DEEPLY)
JOSIE: Blue skies in,
gray skies out. (EXHALES)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(EXHALES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Yes!
(WHOOPING)
We did it!
Whoo! Go, McKenna!
(INAUDIBLE)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
ANNOUNCER: The three
gymnasts to qualify
for the regional
competitive team are...
Toulane Thomas from
Shooting Star Gymnastics.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
BOTH: Yay!
Good for you!
Yeah!
Hey. Congrats.
Megan Murphy from
Performance Plus Gymnasts!
And taking
the final spot
on the regional
competitive team is...
McKenna Brooks of
Shooting Star Gymnastics!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING WILDLY)
Oh, McKenna!
Oh, my God, McKenna!
(LAUGHING)
Hey, Toulane. Wanna
come to the coffee shop?
Yeah, gimme five minutes.
You looked
incredible out there.
I'm very proud
of you, sweetie.
For someone who
just made the
regional competitive team,
you don't seem too excited.
I'm not.
What are you talking about?
This is what
you've wanted for years.
No, Mom. This is what
And you never
let me forget it.
Toulane, this is what
we both wanted for you.
Listen...
No.
I'm not Tasha.
I know that.
I never thought you were.
You really want to
give all this up?
Yes, I do.
If it's what
you want, Toulane.
Well?
I'm dropping off
the regional team.
My mom is telling
Coach Isabelle right now.
She's not thrilled,
but she gets it.
Sierra was first alternate,
so this means
she'll make it.
And she deserves it.
(INAUDIBLE)
And you can come
watch me kick butt
on the rhythmic
gymnastics team
any time you want.
Oh, I will.
(BOTH MIMIC EXPLOSION)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Let's go get
some lemon cake!
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
Hey, do you guys
wanna invite Sierra?
Sounds like she's in
the mood to celebrate too.
Sounds great.
(INAUDIBLE)
MCKENNA: Some people
think that athletes
only define success
by whether they win or lose.
But the most
successful athletes
know that winning or
losing isn't the only
thing that matters.
They are able
to balance sports
with all
the other important things
going on in their lives.
That's why balance
is an important theme
in this book.
Another lesson in
this book is that no one
achieves greatness
without help from others.
Everyone runs into trouble
and everyone gets scared.
But you can get
through any problem,
and turn even
the worst days
into the ones that make
your dreams come true.
As long as you
have the support
from your family
and your friends.
ALL: Shooting Stars!
MCKENNA: You've got to
believe in yourself
and know that
you can do anything.
But you also need to
believe in the people
who believe in you.
Because they're
the ones who will
always be there for you,
win or lose.
(BOTH WHOOPING)
(LAUGHING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING)
---the end---