( camera clicking )
STAND TALL,
ENEMY APPROACHING !
KRISSY TATE REQUESTING ENTRY
TO KING DAWG'S CASTLE, PLEASE.
IT'S GONNA COST YOU.
YOU HAVE TO KISS
ME FOR 5 SECONDS.
( boys )
ONE MISSISSIPPI, 2 MISSISSIPPI,
3 MISSISSIPPI,
4 MISSISSIPPI,
5 MISSISSIPPI.
ENTRY DENIED !
I HATE YOU,
DOUGLAS MENFORD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT !
HE SAID NO !
WHY DID YOU
DO THAT ?
HMM,
I'VE KISSED BETTER.
CAN I GET ONE OF THOSE
PLASTIC DIVIDER THINGS ?
SURE.
OH, OH !
BETWEEN
THE GOAL POST, BABY !
OH, YES !
OH, OH !
( moaning )
OH, HALLELUJAH !
OOH !
WHAT'RE YOU
DOING HERE ?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
ME BEING HERE ?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE I WORKED ?
DOUG.
UH, MR. LANGLEY,
HOW ARE YOU ? EXCUSE ME A MOMENT.
SIR, I'M SORRY.
THIS BROAD, I SLEEP WITH
HER ONCE, AND SHE THINKS SHE CAN FOLLOW ME TO WORK.
BUT I'LL TAKE CARE
OF IT. DON'T WORRY.
DOUG, THAT BROAD
IS MY WIFE,
AND YOU'RE FIRED.
STUPID TWIT !
THEY CAN ALL
KISS MY ASS, JOE.
EASY, DAWG.
NO, "EASY" THIS.
SCREW THEM.
SCREW R.P. LANGLEY.
YOU ALREADY SCREWED
HIS WIFE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS HIS WIFE.
I WISH I HAD KNOWN
WOULD HAVE MADE IT
MORE EXCITING.
( chuckling )
YOU KNOW WHAT ?
HE CAN LICK ME. CRACK TO SACK, OK ?
R.P. LANGLEY CAN LICK ME,
CRACK TO FUCKING SACK.
HEY, HEY, NOT IN
FRONT OF THE LADY.
SORRY, TOUGH WEEK.
THAT'S NO EXCUSE FOR
CURSING LIKE THAT.
IT'S IMPORTANT
FOR DECENT PEOPLE
TO CONTROL
THEIR LANGUAGE.
MOTHERFUCKING SON OF
A BITCH, YOU'RE HOT !
SO ARE YOU.
INCREDIBLE.
TAKE YOUR PANTIES OFF.
OH, NO, NOT YET.
COME ON.
NO.
COME ON,
I'M DEPRESSED, MMM.
SEX IS LIKE MEDICATION.
IT'LL HELP EASE THE PAIN, MMM.
WHY ARE YOU DEPRESSED ?
YOU'LL FIND ANOTHER JOB.
IT'S NOT REALLY
ABOUT MY JOB.
IT'S ABOUT
MY GRANDMOTHER, ACTUALLY.
AH.
SHE JUST DIED.
( groaning )
WHAT ?
W-WHAT'S WRONG ?
YOU'RE--YOU'RE USING
YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S DEATH
TO GET YOURSELF
A PIECE OF ASS.
THAT IS SO DEMENTED.
NO, WAIT, WAIT.
SEE, I'M SOMEONE WHO
CAN CHANNEL DEPRESSION THROUGH SEXUAL ENERGY.
BELIEVE ME, I'M
IN REAL MOURNING.
YOU'RE FUCKING SICK.
NO, AND I ONLY NEED
4 HOURS OF SLEEP.
IT'S A FUNERAL. HOW
AWAKE DO YOU HAVE TO BE ? WHERE'RE YOU GOING ?
(  Rollin' Tumblin' Remix
by R.L. Burnside playing )
♪ HEY, HEY ♪
I KNOW I'M NOT SCHEDULED
TO SPEAK HERE TODAY
ON BEHALF OF MY
BELOVED GRANDMOTHER, BUT I WOULD LIKE TO ADD...
♪ HEY, HEY ♪
SHE WAS A WOMAN OF
INCREDIBLE CHARACTER.
SHE WAS AN INCREDIBLE--
SHE WAS A GREAT WOMAN OF INCREDIBLE CHARACTER.
SHIT !
THE WOMAN WHO TAUGHT ME
THE VALUABLE LESSONS OF LIFE.
JUST DON'T MAKE THEM
LIKE HER ANYMORE.
( men chattering )
( man #1 )
YEAH, YEAH. OK.
( man #2 )
KEEP GOING, LOWER.
COME ON, MOVE
IT, COME ON.
OK. LET'S GO.
EXCUSE ME, UM, IS THIS
WHERE THE KATE MENFORD FUNERAL IS GOING TO BE ?
THIS IS WHERE
THE KATE MENFORD FUNERAL WAS.
NO, NO, NO. NO, NO.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE AT 9:30.
NO, NO, NO.
8:30. SORRY, PAL.
COME ON,
GET THESE, UH...
YOU GOT TO PUT THESE
ON THE TRUCK.
HURRY UP.
SORRY, GRAM.
I'M GONNA MISS YOU.
( car stereo playing )
( tires screeching )
( horn blaring )
( people chattering )
I MEAN, IF YOU
THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S A LOT LIKE SEX,
MISSIONARY STYLE, WITH THE LIGHTS TURNED OFF.
IT CAN ONLY LAST SO
LONG, YOU KNOW ?
( crunching )
IF YOU SCREW TOO MANY
TIMES ON THE TOP OF THE COFFEE TABLE,
FLIP THE THING OVER, AND TIE
YOUR PARTNER TO THE LEGS.
NOW, TRUST ME,
THAT'S HOT.
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
IT'S GREAT.
IT'S GOT TO BE ONE OF THOSE
BIG WOOD JOBS, YOU KNOW.
THE SQUARE KIND,
SOLID OAK.
WOW.
COFFEE TABLE.
TSK.
I'M SORRY. HOW--HOW
DO YOU KNOW MY GRANDMOTHER AGAIN ?
DOUG, I'M YOUR
COUSIN, DENISE.
COUSIN DENISE.
HI, HOW ARE YOU ?
FINE.
HOW'RE YOU DOING ?
HEY, YOU LOOK GREAT
SINCE YOU GOT THE BRACES OFF. YOU REALLY DO.
( chattering )
HMM.
WELL,
ONE DOOR CLOSES AND
ANOTHER ONE OPENS.
BYE, THEN.
HI, I'M ANNA LOCKHEART.
DOUG MENFORD,
HOW ARE YOU ?
( both )
NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU'RE NOT RELATED
TO ME, ARE YOU ?
OH, HARDLY, NO.
I'M YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S
ATTORNEY
AND THE EXECUTOR
OF HER ESTATE.
LOOK, I WANNA MAKE
THIS REALLY BRIEF,
'CAUSE I KNOW THIS
ISN'T THE TIME OR PLACE TO CONDUCT BUSINESS
AND, WELL, I IMAGINE
YOU MUST BE PRETTY...
I AM. I AM.
BUT MY STRATEGY IS TO LAY LOW
AND HANG OUT BY
THE FOOD TABLE,
BECAUSE, UH, USUALLY
WHEN YOU'RE EATING, PEOPLE DON'T BOTHER YOU.
USUALLY.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO--
NO, RELAX, I'M JUST
MESSING WITH YOU.
ACTUALLY, UH, THE TRUTH
IS EVENTUALLY EVERY GOOD-LOOKING WOMAN
IN THE PLACE WILL END
UP AT THE FOOD TABLE
BECAUSE WOMEN LIKE TO
EAT WHEN THEY'RE SAD.
REALLY ?
YEAH.
AND WHAT DO
MEN DO ?
WE LOOK FOR SAD WOMEN.
ARE YOU FREE ON
MONDAY AFTERNOON ?
YES.
HERE'S MY CARD.
BE AT THIS ADDRESS
AT 1:00.
WHY ?
WELL, LET ME PUT
IT THIS WAY.
YOUR GRANDMOTHER WAS WORTH
A LOT MORE THAN YOU THINK.
IN FACT, SHE WAS WORTH
MORE THAN ANYBODY THOUGHT.
AND OUT OF ALL HER
IMMEDIATE FAMILY,
DISTANT RELATIVES,
2ND AND 3RD COUSINS INCLUDED,
AND ALL MONEY-HUNGRY HOPEFULS
GATHERED HERE TODAY,
FOR SOME REASON,
YOURS IS THE ONLY NAME
THAT APPEARS ON THE WILL.
MR. MENFORD ?
UH--UH, HOW MUCH EXACTLY
IS SHE WORTH ?
1:00, MONDAY.
OK.
I'M HERE
ABOUT THE COFFEE TABLE. SOLID OAK.
OOH !
( laughing )
MMM,
ARE THOSE, UH--
OH, STRAWBERRIES.
( grunting )
♪ COME ON AND DO IT, DO IT ♪
♪ DO IT TILL
YOU'RE SATISFIED ♪
♪ WHATEVER IT IS ♪
♪ DO IT, DO IT
TILL YOU'RE SATISFIED ♪
♪ COME ON AND DO IT, DO IT ♪
♪ DO IT TILL
YOU'RE SATISFIED ♪
♪ WHATEVER IT IS ♪
KINKY !
THIS ISN'T EVEN IN
KINKY'S PARKING LOT.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO
DO IT DAWG STYLE.
♪ WHATEVER IT IS ♪
( Doug )
COME ON IN, GENTLEMEN.
♪ AS LONG AS IT PLEASES YOU ♪
HI.
♪ AS LONG AS YOU CAN ♪
IS THAT WHAT
I THINK IT IS ?
IT CERTAINLY IS.
WELL, SHARE
THE WEALTH, BABY !
MORE !
OH, MORE.
♪ WHATEVER IT IS ♪
( screaming )
OH !
( bell ringing )
( alarm clock buzzing )
( elevator bell dinging )
( people chattering )
YOU MUST BE
MR. MENFORD.
THAT'S RIGHT.
DOUGLAS MENFORD
IS HERE TO SEE YOU.
( Anna )
Thank you, Harris. Send him in.
GO RIGHT THROUGH
THAT DOOR.
GREAT, THANK YOU.
GOOD MORNING.
IT COULD BE.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN ?
DO YOU WANT ME TO DO
COMMUNITY SERVICE OR TAKE A PHYSICAL ?
HEY, YOU NAME THE
TIME AND THE PLACE, I'LL PEE IN THE CUP.
DID YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S
DEATH AFFECT YOU AT ALL, MR. MENFORD ?
LET'S CUT TO THE CHASE.
WHAT'RE WE TALKING
ABOUT HERE ? $20,000 ?
HER LINCOLN TOWN CAR, WHAT ?
MR. MENFORD,
WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT $1 MILLION.
WE ARE ?
YOU SURE YOU HAVE
THE RIGHT WILL ?
OH, YEAH.
HOLY SHIT !
WOW.
WHERE'D SHE GET
THAT KIND OF MONEY ?
YOU WEREN'T THE ONLY ONE
IN YOUR FAMILY TO DABBLE IN THE STOCK MARKET.
I DON'T DABBLE, OK.
I HELP PEOPLE WITH MONEY
DECIDE WHERE TO PUT IT.
OK ? AND AS LUCK
WOULD HAVE IT, MY CAREER
HAPPENS TO BE, UH,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF IN--
WHERE THE FUCK DID
SHE GET $1 MILLION ?
IT SEEMS THAT YOUR
GRANDMOTHER WAS SOME KIND OF FINANCIAL GENIUS.
GREAT. WHERE DO I SIGN ?
I'M AFRAID IT'S NOT QUITE
THAT EASY, MR. MENFORD.
"I, KATHRYN J. MENFORD,
"HEREBY DECLARE
MY GRANDSON,
"DOUGLAS LAWRENCE MENFORD,
"THE SOLE BENEFICIARY OF
ALL MY MONETARY SAVINGS,
"IF...
"AND ONLY IF...
HE SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETES
THE FOLLOWING MISSION."
MISSION ?
WHAT MISSION ?
LET ME TAKE A LOOK AT THAT THING.
MR. MENFORD, HOW MANY
SERIOUS GIRLFRIENDS HAVE YOU HAD ?
WHAT ?
GIRLFRIENDS ?
HOW MANY SERIOUS ?
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO
WITH MY GRANDMOTHER'S WILL ?
EVERYTHING,
ACTUALLY.
NONE, OK,
'CAUSE AFTER A WHILE,
THEY START HEARING WEDDING BELLS, SO--
UM, HOW MANY GIRLS
HAVE YOU, UM,
USED FOR SEX ?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
ONE-NIGHT STANDS, SAYING "I LOVE YOU"--
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN. I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
DO I HAVE TO ANSWER
THAT QUESTION ?
YES, YOU DO.
TSK.
LET ME THINK ABOUT IT, UM...
( sighing )
WELL, UM...
YEAH, OK, I--I THINK
WE GET THE MESSAGE. THANK YOU.
I'M ACTUALLY INTERESTED
TO FIND OUT NOW.
NO, NO, PLEASE STOP.
NOW, CAN YOU JUST
READ FROM HERE, THE 2ND PARAGRAPH,
I THINK YOU MAY GET
MORE OF THE GIST OF WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
"IN ORDER TO RECEIVE
YOUR $1 MILLION,
"YOU MUST TRACK DOWN
A SIGNIFICANT NUMBER OF THESE WOMEN
AND GET THEM TO SAY THE
WORDS 'I FORGIVE YOU.'"
( scoffing )
WHAT'S A SIGNIFICANT NUMBER ?
A NICE, ROUND DOZEN.
AND I SHALL SHADOW
YOU EVERY SECOND
OF EVERY DAY TO CHECK
THAT YOU DON'T CHEAT.
AND IF I EVEN GET
THE SLIGHTEST WHIFF OF ANY FRAUDULENCE,
THE WHOLE DEAL IS OFF,
AND HER ENTIRE ESTATE GOES TO THE LOCAL DOG SHELTER.
SO, ARE WE ON ?
I GET TO PICK
THE GIRLS.
DON'T BE
RIDICULOUS.
YOU'D MANIPULATE THE ROSTER OR
FIND SOME SILLY LITTLE GIRLS THAT WOULD COLLUDE WITH YOU.
YOUR GRANDMOTHER
LOVED YOU, MR. MENFORD,
BUT SHE THOUGHT YOU BEHAVED
LIKE AN ABSOLUTE JERK
WHEN IT CAME
TO WOMEN.
NOW, THEN. HOW WOULD
A MAN LIKE YOU RECORD HIS CONQUESTS, HUH ?
HAVE YOU GOT
A LITTLE BLACK BOOK ?
NO.
DO YOU MAKE NOTCHES
ON THE BEDPOST ?
NO.
THEN, UH, HOW ARE WE
GOING TO DO THIS ?
OH, THESE ARE
DISGUSTING !
RIGHT.
I AM GOING TO
SORT THESE OUT.
OH !
OK.
PLAY POKER, MR. MENFORD ?
NOT REALLY.
WELL, LET'S HOPE YOU
DRAW A LUCKY HAND.
PHEW !
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
RIGHT.
VERY GOOD.
NOT GOOD.
SOME OF THESE GIRLS
ARE GONNA BE HARD.
AND 12.
OK, 12 IT IS.
WHOO, BOY !
UGH !
( sighing )
WHAT ?
( grunting )
GOOD MORNING.
HELLO.
NEED ALL THESE BAGS ?
OF COURSE I DO.
WHAT THE HELL IS IN THIS ONE ?
KITCHEN APPLIANCES ?
( groaning )
NO, JUST A LITTLE
READING MATTER.
CAREFUL !
OH, MY GOD !
READING MATTER,
MY ASS !
ENCYCLOPAEDIA BRITANNICA.
OK.
NOW WHAT ?
THE DOOR.
THERE IT IS.
HA-HA.
MR. MENFORD, ONE THING:
I AM A NERVOUS PASSENGER.
UH-HUH.
PLEASE KEEP TO
THE SPEED LIMIT.
YEP.
( car engine starting )
(  Burn me down
by Evan Olson playing )
♪ BAD DAYS COME
AND BAD DAYS GO ♪
♪ THEN EVERYTHING'S
JUST FINE ♪
♪ AND LIFE MAY BE A TRAGEDY ♪
♪ BUT I AIN'T GONNA
LET IT BOTHER ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'D BE WASTIN' TIME ♪
♪ I TAKE IT FOR GRANTED
AND SMILE ♪
♪ THAT WAY I WON'T
LET IT BURN ME DOWN ♪
♪ EVERYBODY KNOWS
SOMEBODY ELSE ♪
♪ WHO KNOWS IT ALL ♪
( tires screeching )
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
WHY, INSIDE WITH
YOU, OF COURSE.
NO, NO, NO, I'M
NERVOUS ENOUGH AS IT IS. NO WAY. NO WAY.
HEY, LET'S JUST RECAP
HERE A LITTLE BIT, OK ?
YOUR JOB IS TO SECURE
12 "I FORGIVE YOUs."
MY JOB IS TO WITNESS THAT.
THEREFORE, I HAVE
TO BE PRESENT.
AH !
ALL RIGHT, GODDAMIT,
LET'S GET IT OVER WITH.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO START A RELATIONSHIP WITH TRUST.
LEAST YOU COULD GIVE ME
THE BENEFIT OF DOUBT.
RELATIONSHIP ?
BY YOUR ADMISSION, YOU
DON'T EVEN KNOW THE MEANING OF THE WORD.
VERY FUNNY.
( sighing )
WELL ?
I'M JUST REFLECTING
ON MY GRANDMOTHER'S KEEN SENSE OF HUMOR.
( sighing )
HEY, EASY, SHE
MIGHT HEAR YOU.
( door opening )
OH, MAN, NO WAY !
HI, MEGAN.
DOUG MENFORD ?
YEAH, IT'S ME.
UH, THIS IS ANNA.
HI.
HOLY SHIT !
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT THAT
ALMOST 6 YEARS AFTER RAPPING BACKSTAGE WITH THE BEASTIES,
YOU'D BE KNOCKING
ON MY DOOR ?
DO YOU REMEMBER
THE BEASTIE ACRONYM ?
UH...
BOYS ENTERING
ANARCHISTIC STATES
TOWARDS INTERNAL--
EXCELLENCE.
MAN, THIS IS SO WEIRD.
YEAH.
DO YOU MIND
IF WE COME IN ?
NO !
I MEAN, UH, NO,
PLEASE DO.
( laughing )
JEEZ.
EXCUSE THE MESS.
IT'S JUST ME AND MY FRIENDS.
( cats mewing )
WE DON'T GET
MANY VISITORS.
PLEASE,
PLEASE MAKE YOURSELF
COMFORTABLE. HAVE A SEAT.
SO, TELL ME ALREADY,
WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE ?
WELL, I--I--I
NEEDED TO SEE YOU.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
WHY ?
OH !
GET DOWN, "H" !
"H" ?
IS THAT SHORT
FOR SOMETHING ?
NO, IT'S HER NAME.
TO KEEP THINGS EASY,
I JUST ASSIGN THEM ALL LETTERS.
IT GETS TO BE KIND
OF A BITCH, THOUGH.
"B" SOMETIMES COMES
WHEN I CALL "P."
"M" ANSWERS TO "N."
UH-HUH.
SO, YOU WERE SAYING
YOU NEEDED TO SEE ME ?
UM...
( cat yowling )
CAN I HAVE A DRINK ?
MAN,
I AM SO RUDE !
ANNA ?
OH, NO, NOT
FOR ME, THANKS.
DOUG ?
JAGER AND COKE.
THE WOMAN'S INSANE,
HOW COULD YOU HAVE HAD SEX WITH HER ?
SHE WASN'T CRAZY WHEN
I HAD SEX WITH HER.
SHE DIDN'T HAVE
ANY CATS, EITHER.
NO. NO, YOU CAN HELP
OUT HERE, OK, IF YOU'RE GONNA SIT HERE IN THE ROOM,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
THROW IN A LITTLE--
OH, SURE, DO IT ALL
FOR YOU. WOULDN'T THAT RATHER DEFEAT-- HEY.
THANK YOU. THANK
YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
MEGAN,
UH-HUH.
UH, ANNA HERE IS ACTUALLY
MY A.A. COACH.
HMM ?
YEAH.
ACTUALLY, A--A SPECIAL
PROGRAM THAT I'M IN,
IT'S A NEW THING WHERE
YOU'RE ALLOWED TO HAVE, UH,
3 DRINKS,
AHEM,
A DAY,
FOR 3 WEEKS, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE WE LEAD SUCH...
HURTFUL LIVES, REALLY,
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, JUST
COMING AND GOING. WE LAY WASTE OUR TIME.
IT'S WHAT WE DO AND--
MR. MENFORD.
CATHARSIS.
DOUG.
LIKE--LIKE O-OLD
RELATIONSHIPS, FOR INSTANCE.
YOU KNOW, WE--WE-- SOMETIMES
WE SAY AND DO THINGS,
WE DON'T REALIZE
HOW IT AFFECTS PEOPLE, YOU KNOW.
AND, UH,
AND THAT'S THE THING.
FOR INSTANCE,
I--I--I HOPE I HAVEN'T
SAID THINGS IN THE PAST THAT MIGHT HAVE HURT YOU.
I LIKE THE THINGS
YOU SAID,
WHEN WE TALKED.
YES.
BUT, SEE, YOU'RE MAKING
IT EASY FOR ME,
AND I WANT IT TO BE HARD.
I WANT TO... I WANT
TO FEEL THE PAIN.
I WANT IT TO--
I WANT IT TO HURT. I WANT IT TO HAVE...
DEEPER MEANING, REALLY.
( gasping )
OH, NO.
OH, MY GOD !
( Megan gasping )
THIS HAS BEEN AROUND
FOR 3 GENERATIONS.
OH, REALLY ?
MY GRANDMOTHER HANDED
THIS DOWN TO MY MOTHER,
AND MY MOTHER PASSED
IT ON TO ME.
THIS IS A RILEY HEIRLOOM.
I'M SO SORRY.
OH, I...
I COULDN'T BE SORRIER
EVEN IF I WAS SORRIER.
YOU ARE VERY SORRY,
MR. MENFORD.
YES, I AM.
I'M EXTREMELY SORRY.
I'M--I'M TERRIBLY, HORRIBLY,
HORRIBLY SORRY ABOUT THIS.
AND HERE I WAS
MAKING AN APOLOGY,
AND IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE APOLOGY, I HAVE TO MAKE ANOTHER APOLOGY.
I'M SO APOLOGETIC RIGHT
NOW ABOUT HOW SORRY--
SHUT IT !
SHUT THE FUCK
UP ABOUT IT !
I FORGIVE YOU !
OK.
WELL, WE GOT TO GO.
SEE YOU LATER.
SORRY.
( crying )
OH, OH.
YOU CHEATED.
YES, AND ?
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
QUIT NOW AND FORGET ABOUT THE MILLION DOLLARS.
YOU CAN'T STAND
THAT I SCORED.
WHAT YOU DID BACK
THERE WAS DESPICABLE.
HEY, LOOK, YOU SAID NO
COLLUSION. YOU SAID NOTHING ABOUT CUTTING CORNERS.
CUTTING CORNERS IS CHEATING.
HEY, BUT IF THAT'S THE
ROAD YOU WANNA GO, JUST KISS THE MONEY GOODBYE.
YOU KNOW, AS LONG AS
WE'RE REDEFINING THE DEAL, LET'S GET SOMETHING STRAIGHT.
FROM NOW ON, YOU
STAY IN THE CAR.
OK, YOU DO NOT
COME INSIDE. YOU STAY IN THE CAR. PERIOD.
THE PIN-DROP 3000 RECEIVER.
WITHOUT A DOUBT, THIS
REPRESENTS THE CUTTING EDGE IN AUDIOPHILIC TECHNOLOGY.
THE BAND
FREQUENCIES ACTUALLY...
BEND THE WAVES
WITHIN THE COCHLEA,
CAUSING THE EAR
ITSELF TO BECOME A CACOPHONIC RESONATOR.
ADDITIONALLY, THE RECEIVER
HAS A BUILT-IN MICROPHONE
WITH A TRANSMITTING CAPACITY
OF 15,000 UBERHERTZ.
THE RATIO
OF CONDUCTION TO RECEPTION IS BEYOND COMPARE,
SOMEWHERE WITHIN
THE GRAPHOLOGIC PARADIGM OF BEING...
( bird cawing )
IN THE SAME ROOM.
FOR AN ADDITIONAL 3 DOLLARS,
I'LL THROW IN A FOUNTAIN PEN.
ON THE OTHER HAND--
COULD YOU JUST GO BACK
TO THE BIT ABOUT THE--
WE'LL TAKE THEM.
HMM.
( static )
CAN YOU SEE IT ?
NO, IT LOOKS GREAT.
OK, SO,
WE'RE GONNA BE ABLE
TO HEAR EACH OTHER
AND TALK TO EACH
OTHER IF WE NEED TO.
RIGHT. WHO'S NEXT ?
KIANA MORTENSON.
OOH, KIANA !
( dog barking )
PERFECT. OK, NOW LET'S
TEST THIS EQUIPMENT.
YOU JUMP OUT OF THE CAR,
WALK A LITTLE BIT AWAY,
AND I AM GOING TO SAY,
"TESTING, TESTING," OK ?
TESTING.
TESTING !
( drums beating )
DOES IT WORK, THEN ?
MR. MENFORD ?
OH, YES.
HEY !
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
ALL YOU NEED IS THAT
PLACE DOWN THE CARIBBEAN, AND YOU'LL BE ALL SET.
YOU REMEMBERED.
LONG TIME NO SEE.
HOW ABOUT SOME ICED TEA ?
I MISSED YOU.
FIGURED I'D TAKE A SHOT AND
SEE IF YOU'RE STILL AROUND.
PART OF ME THOUGHT
YOU WOULD BE IN SAINT CROIX BY NOW, BUT...
ARE YOU DISAPPOINTED ?
( moaning )
( Kiana screaming )
WA-WA-WAIT ! I WANT
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
( door creaking )
HOLY SHIT.
I DID IT MYSELF.
( bird cawing )
IT'S MY DREAM SPACE.
( grunting )
OH, OH.
( man singing Spanish )
( groaning )
( shrieking )
OH, NO.
I'LL GET IT, I'LL GET IT.
OH, NO. I HAVE IT.
GIVE IT TO ME.
HERE WE GO.
LET ME DO IT !
OK.
GOOD, GOOD.
( grunting )
HELP ME.
I AM.
OK, WAIT...
OK.
UP ! UP...
WHAT, WHAT'S WRONG ?
I WANT TO BE ON TOP.
OK.
Ok. All right, go, go.
GO THIS WAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WAIT, WAIT. ON THE
COUNT OF 3. 1, 2, 3.
DID YOU SAY "3" YET ?
YEAH, I DID.
OK, 3, ROLL.
I'M TRYING TO ROLL.
PULL MY BUTT !
OH, YEAH.
( both )
AH.
KIANA...
WHAT ?
SORRY, I--I--I...
OH, OW, OW.
SORRY FOR LEAVING
YOU IN THE THEATRE.
I SHOULD HAVE
GOTTEN THE POPCORN AND COME BACK.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
( groaning )
OH, MY GOD !
( moaning )
( screaming )
( grunting )
AH.
I FORGIVE YOU.
( sighing )
OH,
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
RIGHT.
( engine starting )
OH, SHIT !
( car horn honking )
( sighing )
VERY FUNNY.
SERVES YOU RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOIN' UP HERE ?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA DO THIS ONE WITH DECENCY.
TRUST ME, SHE'S
NOT MAD, OK ?
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT ?
BECAUSE SHE LOVES SEX
AS MUCH AS I DO, OK ?
SEX IS JUST AN
ACTIVITY TO YOU, ISN'T IT ?
NO.
SEX IS A BIG, GIANT PARTY.
YEAH, WELL, IT'S MORE
THAN THAT TO WOMEN. I CAN ASSURE YOU.
YOU HAVE SEX WITH
THE SAME WOMAN LONG ENOUGH,
SHE WANTS TO
HAVE YOUR BABY.
REVELATION ! DOUG MENFORD
IS TERRIFIED OF CHILDREN.
I'M NOT
FRIGHTENED OF CHILDREN,
I LOVE THEM,
I JUST DON'T WANT TO HAVE THEM.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE.
ONE'S A PHOBIA, THE OTHER ONE IS A CHOICE.
I THINK YOU'RE THE
MOST SEXIST, SHALLOW,
SELF-CENTERED MAN I'VE EVER
HAD THE MISFORTUNE TO MEET.
SHE WAS HORNY, I WAS THERE.
IT'S CALLED TIMING.
YOU MEAN SHE JUST
HAD SEX WITH YOU
WITHOUT GIVING IT
A SECOND THOUGHT ?
PRETTY MUCH.
I THINK THAT'S
SAD AND WEAK.
I THINK YOU HAVE,
A: A PROBLEM WITH
SEXUAL WOMEN, OR
B: A PROBLEM WITH SEX.
I HAVE A PROBLEM WITH YOU.
I DIDN'T SPEND
YEARS IN LAW SCHOOL
JUST SO I COULD
FOLLOW YOU AROUND,
DOCUMENTING YOUR SEXUALLY
DEVIANT BEHAVIOR.
HEY, TAKE THAT STUPID GRIN
OFF YOUR FACE AND DRIVE, OK.
LET'S GO, SHALL WE ?
( horse neighing )
( inaudible )
( beeping )
( cell phone ringing )
( inaudible )
HEY !
HEY, YOU GUYS.
( girls together )
WE FORGIVE YOU !
( laughing )
GOOD EVENING.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
I CAME TO CELEBRATE.
WELL, ISN'T THAT
A BIT PREMATURE ?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M OFF TO A GOOD START.
I'VE GOT 2 DAYS
TO GET 5 MORE. SO...
LET'S HAVE A DRINK.
I'M WORKING.
JUST ONE. TAKE A BREAK.
I THINK I'LL PASS.
SO, WHAT'S YOUR DEAL ?
I MEAN, THERE MUST BE
MORE TO ANNA LOCKHEART THAN BOOKS AND BUSINESS.
WHAT WOULD I FIND
LISTED UNDER HOBBIES ?
BETTER YET, WHAT WOULD
I FIND LISTED UNDER SKILLS ?
MAYBE YOU'LL
FIND WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR UNDER...
MARITAL STATUS.
YOU'RE MARRIED.
HAPPILY. HIS NAME'S COLE.
COLE.
WHERE'S THE RING ?
OH, GETTING RESET. ONE
OF THE PRONGS BROKE.
EXCUSE ME.
OH, REALLY ?
GENTLE REMINDER,
MR. MENFORD
I'M HERE BECAUSE
I MADE A PROMISE
TO YOUR GRANDMOTHER,
WHO WAS A SWEET AND LOVELY WOMAN.
AND THE WHOLE PURPOSE
OF THIS EXPEDITION WAS TO HUMBLE YOU, TO TAME YOUR EGO,
NOT TO BLOW IT OUT
OF ALL PROPORTION.
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT
TO MY GRANDMOTHER, SCREW THAT.
'CAUSE IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE LUCKY 7s NOW.
YOU'RE REALLY ENJOYING
THIS, AREN'T YOU ?
YES, I AM.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
GO AND ENJOY IT IN YOUR OWN ROOM ?
OK.
WELL, HERE'S TO 7 FOR 7.
( train horn blowing )
( car tires screeching )
( people chattering )
LISTEN, THIS LAYOUT
JUST ISN'T WORKING.
WOW !
HI, CHRISTINE.
EXCUSE ME, LADIES.
HONEY, THIS IS
DOUG MENFORD.
DOUG MENFORD,
THE EXPERIMENT.
DON'T WORRY, BROTHER,
IT'S ALL GOOD.
I'M SORRY, DOUG, DID
I MISS THE REASON FOR YOUR UNSOLICITED VISIT ?
WELL, I--I WANTED
TO APOLOGIZE--
( laughing )
OH, SHIT !
I'M GONNA KEEP THIS
BRIEF AND PAINFUL,
MUCH LIKE OUR
TIME TOGETHER.
YOUR APOLOGY
IS NOT ACCEPTED.
APPARENTLY, IT
AIN'T ALL GOOD.
NO, BUT I--I REALLY JUST
WANTED TO SAY ONE--
EXPERIMENT ?
I TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF HER BRIEF IDENTITY CRISIS, OK.
I WAS HER MR. WHITE.
OOH, BAD CHOICE
ON HER PART GETTING YOU.
I'M BARELY OUT OF THE
BLOCKS ON DAY 2, AND I GET SCREWED BY A POLITICIAN.
THANK YOU MAYOR HODGES.
HEY, DON'T BE PATHETIC.
GET BACK IN THERE.
AND DO WHAT ?
THROW DOWN WITH BILLY DEE ?
REPEAT WHATEVER I SAY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
I'LL BE YOUR
PROMPTER, JUST SAY WHAT I SAY, VERBATIM.
YOU'RE TRYIN'
TO TRICK ME ?
DO YOU HAVE
A BETTER IDEA ?
( Christine )
I JUST HATE THIS LAYOUT. WE CAN DO BETTER, THAT'S ALL.
NOW WHAT ?
I HAVE SOMETHING
THAT I NEEDED TO SAY.
I'M WAITING.
( sighing )
SO AM I.
WAITING.
For my entire life,
I've been a sexual slug.
WHAT ?
HUH ?
A sexual slug.
OH, OH, UM, WOW...
UH...
UM, AHEM.
Say it !
CHRISTINE, UH,
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I HAVE HAD, UH, SOME
SIGNIFICANT, UH...
UM...
BREAKTHROUGHS RECENTLY,
AND, UH, I'VE--I'VE, UM...
( man )
"AND, UM, AND, UM," TALK OR WALK !
SPIT IT OUT, DOUG.
$1 million, Douglas !
FOR MY ENTIRE LIFE,
I'VE SORT OF BEEN A, UM--
EXCUSE ME, I HAVE
A CAMPAIGN TO RUN HERE.
ALL MY LIFE, I HAVE
BEEN A SEXUAL SLUG.
HA, YEAH.
And a repugnant,
pompous dick.
AND A REPUGNANT,
POMPOUS GUY.
Dick.
DICK.
DICK ?
WHO ARE YOU
CALLIN' A DICK ?
NO, I WAS A DICK.
YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
OH, I'M LOVIN' THIS.
THIS IS FASCINATING.
UM, UH...
KEEP GOIN' !
UM, UM, LET'S GO.
I recently had an epiphany.
WAIT ! RECENTLY,
I HAD A-AN EPIPHANY.
EPIPHANY ? NOW,
THAT'S A GOOD ONE. COME ON, COME ON !
YEAH, I--I
DISRESPECTED YOU AND--
And I saw your skin color
as just another conquest.
I NEVER SAID THAT.
SAID WHAT ?
( sighing )
I SAW YOUR SKIN COLOR
AS JUST ANOTHER CONQUEST.
( grunting )
AND I WAS WRONG, AND
I BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS.
WOW,
THAT MUST HAVE
BEEN VERY DIFFICULT FOR YOU TO SAY.
LET HIM GO, DREW.
OH, IT'S OK, LET HIM GO.
( sighing )
OK, YOU GOT IT.
I FORGIVE YOU.
OH, THANKS.
GREAT, THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, MY MAN, YOU
BRING NEW MEANING TO THE WORD "WHITE LIE."
HA, HA !
VOTE FOR HODGES.
HOPE YOU KNOW
THAT I DON'T BELIEVE
ANY OF THE CRAP THAT
I SAID BACK THERE.
AH, IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF YOU BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
WHAT MATTERS IS THAT
CHRISTINE HODGES BELIEVED IT.
MMM-HMM.
I DID YOU A FAVOR BACK THERE.
THANKS.
HERE WE GO !
CUTTING AND SEPARATING.
I LIKE THINGS NEAT AND
IN THEIR PROPER PLACE.
THE PROPER PLACE FOR FOOD
IS IN YOUR STOMACH, OK ?
NOT MARCHING AROUND YOUR
PLATE, SINGLE FILE.
THERE'S SOMETHING TO BE SAID
FOR SELF-RESTRAINT, YOU KNOW.
SOMETIMES EVEN SELF-DENIAL.
REALLY ?
IS THAT WHAT YOUR
HUSBAND BELIEVES ? WHAT, ARE YOU BOTH MONKS ?
( slurping )
AH.
( Doug )
2 THINGS COME TO MIND RIGHT NOW.
ONE, EVERY MAN
HAS THAT CERTAIN
SEXUAL PARTNER WHO
STANDS ABOVE ALL THE REST.
FOR ME, IT WAS ANGEL.
( camera clicking )
AND 2,
I LOVE BREASTS.
( people chattering )
WH-WH-WHOA, WAIT !
All right, everybody,
take a break.
ANGEL HAS TO BE
WHO SHE IS. GIVE HER A MOMENT.
WHO ARE YOU AND
WHAT AGENCY SENT YOU ?
OH, NO. I'M--I'M
NOT FROM AN AGENCY.
IT'S ME, DOUG,
DOUG MENFORD.
THEY USED TO CALL ME DAWG.
OK, LOOK, DIG DAWG, DOUG.
SECURITY IS JUST
A SHOUT AWAY, SO DON'T MESS WITH ME.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
YOU--YOU AND I USED TO BE INVOLVED.
YOU KNOW, SEXUALLY ?
( all laughing )
WELL, YOU ACTUALLY TOLD
ME THAT I WAS ONE OF THE BEST YOU EVER HAD.
WAS I DRUNK ?
I DON'T THINK SO.
( eagle screeching )
I HOPE YOU FUCK AS
GOOD AS YOU SELL.
GOOD GOD !
OK, GUYS.
( people chattering )
Ok, everybody,
you know the drill. That's an Angel-5.
( man )
THAT'S GREAT.
OH, MAN.
OH, SOME PLACE YOU GOT HERE.
MMM-HMM.
WHO ARE THOSE GUYS ?
JUST FRIENDS.
( grunting )
NOW SHUT UP AND ENJOY.
( giggling )
MAGIC HANDS,
GONNA GET YOU GOING.
( moaning )
YOU LIKE THAT ?
OH, YEAH.
( Doug moaning )
OOH.
( groaning )
WHAT'S WRONG, BABY ?
( Doug )
Oh, nothing, it's great. It's great.
( sighing )
OK, ARE YOU SURE
NOTHIN'S WRONG ?
YEAH, YEAH, OH.
Yeah, oh, yeah.
OH, YEAH.
AH.
OK, LOOK, IS HE GONNA
COOPERATE OR NOT ?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Uh, yeah, oh, yeah.
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
OOH, YEAH.
YEAH.
( man )
2-minute warning, everybody. 2 minutes.
( sighing )
OH.
I, UH, THIS--THIS HAS NEVER
HAPPENED TO ME BEFORE.
SOME PEOPLE JUST CAN'T
PERFORM UNDER PRESSURE.
UH, BIGGIE DIG DAWG
DOUG, I FORGIVE YOU.
FUCK !
( bird cawing )
( sighing )
GO AHEAD, TAKE
YOUR BEST SHOT.
HEY, I NEVER HIT
A MAN WHEN HE'S DOWN.
COME ON, LET'S JUST DRIVE.
OOH, LOOK,
THERE'S A CHAPTER
HERE ON IMPOTENCE.
MMM...
HEY !
HEY, WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING ?
HEY !
( grunting )
( sighing )
( urinating )
( zipping )
( sighing )
AH !
FEELING BETTER ?
MUCH.
ME, TOO.
(  All Right Now
by Free playing )
♪ OH, OH, OH ♪
( tires screeching )
♪ THERE SHE STOOD
IN THE STREET ♪
♪ SMILING FROM
HER HEAD TO HER FEET ♪
♪ I SAID, HEY ♪
OK, TURN RIGHT.
RIGHT ?
YEAH.
YOU SURE ?
POSITIVE.
OK.
DO YOU EVER STOP EATING ?
NOPE.
PERFECTLY NORMAL
BODILY FUNCTION. OR DON'T YOU HAVE THOSE ?
LISTEN, IF YOU DON'T
FIND A BATHROOM, I MAY HAVE ONE RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
♪ LET'S MOVE BEFORE THEY
RAISE THE PARKING RATE ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT NOW ♪
HOW'S IT GOIN' ?
YOU EVER TRIED STANDING
UP ? IT'S EASIER. MORE NATURAL, TOO.
♪ ALL RIGHT NOW, BABY,
IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW ♪
YOU KNOW WHAT, LET'S FACE
IT. WE ARE INSANELY LOST.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
WELL, IF WE'RE NOT LOST,
HOW COME WE'VE PASSED
THAT SAME LITTLE PILE
OF STONES 80 TIMES ?
WE HAVEN'T.
LOOK, IT SAYS IN
THE MAP THAT WE--
OH,
DON'T TELL ME WE'RE
IN THE "MEN DON'T READ MAPS" PHASE.
NO, WE DON'T.
AND MEN ALSO DON'T
ASK FOR DIRECTIONS.
NO, WE DON'T. WE GIVE
DIRECTIONS TO WOMEN WHO ASK FOR THEM, OK ?
THAT'S PATHETIC.
LET ME EXPLAIN
SOMETHING TO YOU, OK, ALL RIGHT ?
A MAN IS A CLEAN, STRAIGHT
LINE. A WOMAN IS A WIGGLY CIRCLE, ALL RIGHT ?
WE HAVE A REAL
ONE-ON-ONE RELATIONSHIP
WITH REAL OBJECTS
IN THE REAL WORLD, ALL RIGHT ?
WE HAVE TOOLS, YOU HAVE
BOOKS. WE BUILD, YOU WATCH. CASE CLOSED !
( tire bursting )
MR. MENFORD.
YEAH.
CAN I ASK YOU
A WIGGLY QUESTION ?
SURE.
DOES A FLAT TIRE QUALIFY
AS A REAL OBJECT IN A REAL WORLD ?
AHEM.
( phone beeping )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
I'M CALLING A.A.A., OK ?
DON'T BE SO
RIDICULOUS. HANG UP.
WHAT ?
HANG UP.
YOU HAVE
A BETTER IDEA ?
AS A MATTER OF FACT, I DO.
I THINK THAT'S SUPPOSED TO...
AHEM.
( car doors closing )
ONWARDS.
GOOD NIGHT !
SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
YEAH ?
HAVE YOU
SEEN MY LUGGAGE ?
NO.
HEY, YOU'RE A
NATURAL MAN, GO NAKED !
HI.
MY NAME IS DOUG.
WHAT'S YOURS ?
LINDSAY ANNE WICKMAN.
WOW, COOL NAME.
THANK YOU.
YOU WANT SOME HELP ?
SURE.
MAY I COME OVER ?
OK.
YOU CAN HOLD THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE SPILLING THEM.
OH !
I DIDN'T REALIZE
THE TOP WAS ALL OPEN.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I JUST--
OK.
THAT'S MOST OF THEM.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST
GIVE THAT BACK TO YOU.
IT'S OK, I FORGIVE YOU.
THANKS.
SO WHOSE GARDEN IS THIS ?
Mine, but it used
to be my mommy's.
IS HER NAME EMMA ?
YES.
AND WHERE IS SHE ?
SHE DIED.
Where's your dad ?
I DON'T HAVE A DAD.
( Anna )
You ok ?
HOW OLD ARE YOU,
LINDSAY ?
8.
AND WHAT'S YOUR
BIRTHDAY ?
APRIL 13.
1992.
HOW DID YOU KNOW ?
WHO LIVES HERE
WITH YOU ?
MY GRANDMA.
( door opening )
( Mrs. Wickman )
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING ?
YOU ARE TRESPASSING.
LINDSAY, YOU GET
INSIDE, RIGHT NOW.
EXCUSE ME, I NEED TO,
UH, SPEAK WITH YOU.
WHO ARE YOU ?
MY NAME IS DOUG MENFORD.
I--I KNEW EMMA.
OH.
I'M SORRY, WE'RE BUSY.
( birds chirping )
( door closing )
WHAT HAPPENED
BACK THERE ?
I THINK THAT
LITTLE GIRL IS MINE.
I THINK IF SHE
WERE, HER MOTHER WOULD LET YOU KNOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO
COUNT THIS ONE.
COME ON, 2 MORE TO GO.
( engine starting )
( door opening )
( door slamming )
HELLO ?
( man on P.A. )
We don't open till 10:00.
UH, IS ERICA HERE ?
Erica ?
( laughing )
That's very funny.
Uh, Erica, you
got a visitor.
IS SHE HERE ?
DROP THE "A."
( Doug )
HUH ?
I SAID, DROP THE "A."
FROM WHAT ?
"ERICA."
( sighing )
ERIC KOYLE.
ERIC ?
WELCOME TO MY CLUB, DOUG.
I THINK I, UH,
NEED TO SIT DOWN.
YEAH, SURE.
HEY !
HEY, KILL THE LIGHTS,
LOU. YOU GOT THE POOR THING ALL SHAKY.
YOU WANT A BEER
OR SOMETHING ?
YOU KNOW,
NIGHT CLUB AND BAR
VOTED THIS PLACE
NUMBER ONE IN SACRAMENTO.
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THAT SHIT ?
GOD ! IT'S FUCKIN'
SURPRISING,
ESPECIALLY IN THIS
RIGHT-WING TOWN WE LIVE IN.
( laughing )
GOD, I CANNOT GET OVER
HOW GOOD YOU LOOK.
LIKE A MILLION BUCKS.
YOU KNOW, DOUG,
YOU ARE STILL A HOT PIECE OF ASS,
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
( dance music playing )
W-WHAT'S THE DEAL ?
DO YOU-- DO YOU-- NOW YOU LIKE WOMEN ?
YEAH, SOME ARE COOL.
AND--AND YOU ALSO LIKE MEN ?
I MEAN, I LIKED MEN
BEFORE. THERE'S REALLY NO REASON TO STOP NOW.
YEAH.
L-LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
OH, NO, NO, DON'T
TELL ME. DON'T TELL ME. LET ME GUESS.
YOU WANNA GO THROUGH
WITH IT, RIGHT ?
YEAH.
OK, LOOK, DOUG, I WAS SICK
OF BEING A FUCKING DOORMAT, FOR CHRIST'S SAKES !
I MEAN, YOU,
OF ALL PEOPLE, SHOULD KNOW THIS.
LET'S LEAVE ERICA
OUT OF THIS, RIGHT. THIS IS BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
I GOT AN IDEA.
WHAT ?
YOU WANNA SEE IT ?
SEE WHAT ?
MY BRAND-NEW DICK.
NOT REALLY. NO.
OH, COME ON. IT'S A REAL
CONVERSATION PIECE, DOUG.
NO, NO, NO.
COME ON, DOUG.
NO WAY.
I REALLY DROPPED A LOT
OF COIN ON THIS DICK. HEY, LOU ! SPOT ME, LOU !
DOUG.
( Doug exclaiming )
NO.
COME ON, DOUG.
LOOK AT MY FUCKIN' DICK.
OH, GOD. OK,
YOU HAPPY NOW ?
ISN'T IT A GOOD ONE ?
HOW THE HELL,
SHOULD I KNOW ?
ONLY BECAUSE I USED
YOUR DICK AS A MODEL.
OH, MY GOD.
( microphone buzzing )
REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
I SUCKED YOU OFF ?
YOU KNOW, THAT WAS MY
FIRST BLOWJOB EVER.
OH, GOD.
REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID TO ME
WHEN I ASKED YOU HOW IT WAS ?
LOOK--
YOU SAID, AND I QUOTE:
"Don't worry, you'll
get the hang of it."
ALL RIGHT. I'M A LITTLE
FUCKED UP NOW. I'M NOT REALLY SURE WHAT'S HAPPENING.
YEAH, WHICH IS ODD,
BECAUSE I'M DOING A LITTLE WONDERING MYSELF.
WHY ARE YOU HERE ?
I THINK YOU SHOULD
TELL HER THE TRUTH.
I STAND TO INHERIT
A LITTLE BIT OF MONEY, IF I CAN GET
SOME OF MY FORMER GIRLFRIENDS
TO, UH, FORGIVE ME.
OH, SO THIS IS
ABOUT THE MONEY ?
I SEE, IT'S LIKE
A LITTLE BIZ TRANSACTION, HUH ?
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
DOUG, LET'S LET THE NEGOTIATIONS BEGIN.
WELL, I DON'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT I CAN OFFER YOU RIGHT NOW.
OH, YES, YOU DO.
COME HERE.
CLOSER.
HEY !
ON YOUR KNEES.
OH, GOD.
AH !
I WANT--
I'M NOT GONNA BLOW YOU.
I WANT YOU TO SEE
WHAT IT'S LIKE FOR YOUR FIRST TIME, DOUG.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
EXACTLY HOW MUCH DOES THIS
INHERITANCE MEAN TO YOU ?
OH !
UH...
THIS IS NOT WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
IT'S LOOKING PRETTY BAD.
I'M--
WHAT IS THIS,
SOME KIND OF SICK JOKE OR SOMETHING ?
THAT'S, UH--
( clattering )
YOU SON OF A BITCH
MOTHERFUCKER.
UGH !
WOW ! YOU CAN
REALLY THROW A PUNCH.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
YOU ? FIGHT BACK !
I CAN'T.
SHE'S A GIRL.
SHE'S NOT A GIRL !
SHE'S A BOY.
I'M A MAN !
I CAN'T DO IT.
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T,
I CAN. HEY !
UGH !
RIGHT. YOU
FORGIVE HIM.
( groaning )
( laughing )
UNBELIEVABLE.
( grunting )
( sighing )
I FUCKING FORGIVE YOU, DOUG.
SEE ?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
SATURDAY NIGHT ?
( muzak playing )
( people muttering )
COLE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED IF I HADN'T COME
AND RESCUED YOU ?
LET'S NOT THINK
ABOUT THAT RIGHT NOW.
OK.
WHAT TIME DO
YOU HAVE ?
UM, VERY NEARLY
HALF PAST 8:00.
SO, ONE MORE TO GO.
AND THEN I CAN FINALLY
GET TO SPEND SOME
TIME WITH MY HUSBAND.
( thunder rumbling )
( knocking )
( sighing )
H-HEY !
H-H-HEY !
IF IT ISN'T
MR. BIG-MAN-ON-CAMPUS.
HEY, BILLY, RIGHT ?
WILLIE.
( laughing )
IT'S WILLIE.
LOOK AT-- COME ON IN HERE.
COME ON, IT'S
RAINING OUT THERE. GET YOUR ASS IN HERE.
AH, HA !
YEAH.
SO, UH...
YOUR SISTER AROUND ?
OH !
OH, OH-OH.
OH, THE BIG SHITTY CITY SUCKED
ALL THE SMALL-TOWN TALK OUT OF THE BOY, HUH ? HUH ?
( laughing )
YEAH.
YEAH, DARCY'S HERE.
SHE'S IN THE BACK.
CAN I TALK TO HER ?
SURE, WILL DO, OK.
( laughing )
( thunder rumbling )
( sighing )
( coughing )
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHO WE GOT HERE.
IT'S LITTLE
DOUGIE MENFORD.
( giggling )
WHAT A SURPRISE.
HOW ARE YOU
DOING, DARCE ?
COME OVER HERE NEXT
TO ME ON THE COUCH.
COMFY, HUH ?
I MEAN, YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU GOT YOUR ASS KICKED.
OH, YEAH, JUST
A LITTLE SCUFFLE.
YOU STILL LOOK GREAT.
THANKS.
HOW DO I LOOK ?
YOU LOOK, UH...
DIFFERENT.
( coughing )
YOU ALL RIGHT ?
OH,
YEAH, I GOTTA
CATCH MY BREATH.
( chuckling )
WHOO !
LONG TIME NO SEE,
HUH, DOUGIE.
YEAH.
WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN ?
YOU KNOW, JUST AROUND.
YEAH.
WELL, THE LEAST YOU
COULD'VE DONE WAS TOLD ME YOU WERE LEAVING.
WELL, I--I HAD
TO GET OUT. I--
YOU CAN'T GROW
IF YOU STAY IN YOUR HOMETOWN.
I STAYED, AND
I GREW PLENTY.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU
WERE GOING THROUGH,
YOU KNOW, ONE OF
YOUR LITTLE PHASES,
AND I LET YOU BE.
AND BY THE TIME THE NEWS
GOT BACK TO ME THAT YOU MOVED, I MEAN, THAT--
THAT WAS IT,
YOU WERE ALREADY A COLLEGE MAN.
I WAS TRYING
TO FIND MYSELF.
DID YOU ?
YEAH...
SO MUCH FOR
SOUL-SEARCHING, HUH ?
Y-YOU TOLD ME YOU
WERE GONNA MARRY ME.
L-LIKE AN IDIOT,
I BELIEVED YOU.
I MEAN,
IT WASN'T UNTIL LONG AFTER YOU MOVED AWAY
I FOUND OUT THAT
YOU'D BEEN USING ME ALL THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL.
DARCE.
YOU KNOW,
YOU KNOW WHAT THE
CRAZIEST THING IS ?
TO THIS DAY, I MEAN,
YOU ARE STILL THE ONLY PERSON I HAVE EVER LOVED.
LISTEN...
I WAS AN ASSHOLE, OK ?
BUT I CAN'T GO BACK
AND CHANGE THAT.
I wish I could,
but I can't.
YOU HURT ME.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN I THOUGHT
YOU BELIEVED IN ME, I BLOSSOMED.
AND ONE KISS FROM YOU,
I--I FELT I COULD FLY.
I TRIED. I MEAN, I--I ENTERED
A PERSONAL AD ONCE.
AND I ENDED UP GETTING
TO KNOW A REALLY NICE GUY OVER THE TELEPHONE.
HE CAME OVER.
HE TOOK ONE
LOOK AT ME.
HE DIDN'T EVEN
TAKE OFF HIS COAT.
AND THE SAD PART IS
I WAS ONLY HALF THE WEIGHT I AM NOW.
YOU KNOW, I CAN--
I CAN ALMOST UNDERSTAND WHAT HE DID.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, HE
WAS JUST BEING HONEST,
AND I WAS THE ONE WHO
STRETCHED THE TRUTH
WHEN I DESCRIBED
MYSELF OVER THE PHONE.
BUT YOU...
YOU HAD THE MOST
SOUGHT-AFTER PRIZE AT CASPER HIGH
WHO WANTED NO ONE
IN THAT SCHOOL BUT YOU.
I'M SORRY.
CAN YOU FORGIVE ME ?
HOW ABOUT A KISS...
JUST FOR OLD TIMES' SAKE ?
( grunting )
( gasping )
FORGIVE YOU ?
I FUCKIN' HATE YOU.
WILLIE, GET HIM
OUT OF HERE !
NOW WAIT A MINUTE--
NOW WAIT-- HEY,
NO. HEY, NO, NO.
WAIT. WAIT, 3 LITTLE WORDS.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
GET HIM OUT OF HERE, NOW !
( groaning )
STAY AWAY FROM MY SISTER !
YOU DON'T GET
IT, DO YOU ?
YOU RUINED
HER LIFE !
WILLIE, I--
HEY, BUDDY,
DO ME A FAVOR.
QUIT STOMPING ON
PEOPLE'S HEARTS.
THEY'RE NOT
ALL AS HARD AND AS EMPTY AS YOURS.
SO GET THE FUCK OFF
OF MY PROPERTY, BEFORE I CALL THE COPS !
( engine starting )
( tires screeching )
( glass shattering )
( Anna )
I THINK YOU'RE THE MOST SEXIST, SHALLOW,
SELF-CENTERED MAN I'VE EVER
HAD THE MISFORTUNE TO MEET.
( Darcy )
FORGIVE YOU ? I FUCKIN' HATE YOU.
( Doug )
MY NAME IS DOUG MENFORD. I--I KNEW EMMA.
( Mrs. Wickman )
OH.
I'M SORRY, WE'RE BUSY.
( sighing )
I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE BACK.
EMMA TOLD ME ABOUT
YOU BEFORE SHE DIED.
SHE TOLD ME HOW
SHE'D FALLEN SO MUCH IN LOVE WITH YOU,
ADORED YOU, WOULD
DO ANYTHING FOR YOU.
AND THEN, UH,
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT SHE WAS PREGNANT,
SHE TOOK ONE LONG
LOOK AT YOU.
AND SHE THOUGHT,
"THIS IS NOT THE KIND OF A MAN
THAT I WANT TO HAVE
RAISE MY CHILD."
( sobbing )
HELLO ?
ARE YOU OK ?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME.
AH...
WELL, IF I MIGHT
SAY SOMETHING,
I THINK THAT
DEEP DOWN INSIDE,
YOU NOW TRULY BELIEVE
THAT YOU ARE A DICK,
AND THAT MAKES
YOU FEEL HORRIBLE ABOUT YOURSELF.
THAT STUFF YOU HAD
ME SAY TO CHRISTINE IS ACTUALLY TRUE.
( sighing )
I KNOW THAT LITTLE
GIRL WAS MINE.
I WAS WITH HER MOTHER
THE WHOLE SUMMER OF '91.
SHE GOT PREGNANT.
SHE HAD OUR BABY
AND DECIDED NOT TO TELL ME ABOUT IT.
WHAT DOES THAT SAY ?
IT SAYS "LOSER."
"DEADBEAT."
I'M GOING TO STEP
OUTSIDE MY LEGAL CAPACITY FOR A MOMENT, OK ?
YOUR GRANDMOTHER TRUSTED
ME TO EXECUTE HER ESTATE,
SO I THINK SHE TRUSTS ME
TO MAKE A JUDGMENT CALL HERE.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR TEETH
KICKED IN ON THIS TRIP.
BUT I THINK
YOU'VE LEARNED THE SORT OF LESSON
YOUR GRANDMOTHER
WANTED YOU TO LEARN.
THE MILLION DOLLARS
IS YOURS.
REALLY ?
YEAH.
YOU'VE EARNED IT.
IN FACT, I THINK YOU DESERVE IT.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU.
IT'S MY PLEASURE.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR HUSBAND ?
I COULDN'T HELP
BUT NOTICE HE WAS MARKED DOWN TO $4.99
BACK AT THE DRUGSTORE.
I KEEP THAT PHOTO TO
SHIELD MYSELF FROM UNWANTED ADVANCES.
LIKE THIS ONE ?
YES.
( elevator bell dinging )
( door clicking )
HI.
THOSE ARE FOR YOU.
THANK YOU. UM...
TAKE A SEAT,
MR. MENFORD, PLEASE.
THAT'S A LITTLE
FORMAL, ISN'T IT ?
AHEM.
THERE IS NO MILLION DOLLARS.
WHAT ?
THERE'S NO INHERITANCE.
THERE NEVER WAS ONE.
DO YOU REMEMBER THIS ?
NO.
YOU BEFRIENDED ME FOR
AN ENTIRE SEMESTER,
AND MADE ME FALL
IN LOVE WITH YOU,
JUST SO YOU COULD
GET INTO SOME DICK-FEST ORGANIZATION.
MY FRIEND FOUND THIS
ON THE SCORE  DU JOUR
BULLETIN BOARD IN YOUR FRAT HOUSE.
OK, THAT WAS-- THAT
WAS A LONG TIME AGO. I'VE--I'VE CHANGED.
IT'S WAY TOO LATE
FOR YOU TO BE SORRY.
I WAS A FRESHMAN.
I HAD NO FRIENDS.
AND YOU CAME ALONG, AND
YOU TURNED ON YOUR CHARM
AND MADE ME FEEL
LIKE THE LUCKIEST GIRL ON CAMPUS.
LOOK. IT WAS A--
IT WAS A DIRTY TRICK, AND I'M TRULY, TRULY SORRY.
YOU RUINED MY 4
COLLEGE YEARS FOR ME,
AND I NEVER GOT OVER
THE HUMILIATION OF THAT.
I VOWED THAT ONE DAY
I WOULD FIND YOU
AND MAKE YOU FEEL AS BAD
AS YOU MADE ME FEEL.
WHAT ABOUT FRIDAY NIGHT ?
I MEAN, DOESN'T THAT MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU ?
OH, WELL...
I SHOULD THINK THAT
YOU, MORE THAN ANYONE,
KNOWS THE MEANING
OF THE WORDS "ONE-NIGHT STAND."
( sighing )
YOU PLANNED THIS ?
THAT'S SAD.
LET ME ASK YOU
SOMETHING. AHEM.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
FIND IT IN YOUR HEART TO FORGIVE ME ?
FOR WHAT YOU DID TO ME ?
NEVER.
WELL, FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I FORGIVE YOU.
( door closing )
( carousel music playing )
SO, DID YOU
LIKE YOUR HORSE ?
YEAH.
WAS HE FAST ?
UH-HUH.
GOOD.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
FOR SUPPER ?
PIZZA.
C-CAN YOU EXCUSE
ME FOR 2 SECS ?
HI.
I SEE YOU GOT HER.
OH, YEAH, MORE--
MORE LIKE SHE'S GOT ME, THANKS TO YOU.
OH !
HEY, LINDSAY. I'M ANNA.
ANNA THE LAWYER ?
YEAH !
MY DADDY TALKS ABOUT YOU.
REALLY ? WHAT
DOES HE SAY ?
HE SAYS THAT
YOU'RE SMART,
AND SMART WOMEN
ALWAYS WIN.
I DIDN'T SAY
THAT THEY WIN.
I SAID THAT THEY USUALLY
GET WHAT THEY WANT.
YEAH, BUT SOMETIMES WHEN
THEY GET WHAT THEY WANT,
THEY REALIZE
THEY DON'T ACTUALLY WANT IT ANYMORE.
WE SHOULD GET GOING.
YEAH, UM...
MAYBE SEE YOU AROUND.
MAYBE.
BYE, LINDSAY.
BYE, ANNA.
WHAT ?
IT'S OK.
OK.
( director chattering )
( director )
AND, READY ?
KEEP GOING.
IT'S OK, IT'S OK,
GET DOWN, GET DOWN.
AND ACTION.
♪ WASTIN' TIME ♪
♪ I TAKE IT FOR GRANTED
AND SMILE ♪
♪ THAT WAY I WON'T LET
IT BURN ME DOWN ♪
CAN I GET A COUPLE
OF THOSE, UH... I'M SORRY. CAN WE START THAT AGAIN ?
ATTITUDE.
( director )
A BETTER ATTACK, YES. READY ?
GIVE HER THE
CUE, DENIS.
( Denis Leary )
GET OUT OF THAT GODDAMN FRAME !
GET OUT OF
THERE. READY ?
♪ THEY'RE NEVER GONNA LET
YOU HAVE YOU TURN ♪
♪ YOU'D MIGHT AS WELL
TALK TO A WALL ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN
I STEP TO THE SIDE ♪
WHY DID YOU DO THAT ?
HMM,
I'VE KISSED BETTER.
OH, DAMN.
( man )
CUT, CUT.
( director )
ROLL TAPE.
♪ SOMETIMES IT'S BETTER
TO WALK AWAY ♪
( grunting )
( Denis grunting )
( director )
DIALOGUE ?
( Denis )
OH, OK, READY ?
( panting )
DIALOGUE,
YOU READY ?
( director )
DIALOGUE.
OK, OK, READY ?
GO !
I'M VERY COMMITTED, YES.
♪ JERKS MAY COME AND
JERKS MAKE GO ♪
♪ THEN EVERYTHING'S
JUST FINE ♪
♪ AND WHAT THEY KNOW AND
WHAT THEY SEE DON'T REALLY MEAN THAT MUCH TO ME ♪
♪ I JUST DON'T
HAVE THE TIME ♪
YEAH.
( director )
NO LAUGHING.
I KNOW,
I DROPPED MY KEYS.
♪ I TOOK AN EMOTIONAL DIVE ♪
♪ BUT I'M THROUGH
HANGIN' OUT WITH THE CLOWNS ♪
♪ I WON'T TURN AWAY,
NO, I WON'T LET 'EM BURN ME DOWN ♪
( Denis )
IS THAT PLANE BOTHERING US OR NOT ?
( plane engine humming )
♪ BURN ME DOWN ♪
♪ WON'T LET 'EM
BURN ME DOWN ♪
DON'T CUT.
IT'S GONNA BE GREAT
ONCE THE FUCKING THING GETS PAST.
♪ I WON'T LET 'EM
BURN ME DOWN ♪
YOU SHOULD TRY THEM.
FUCK.
THAT'S CUT.
Closed Captions provided by
SOFTITLER