Synced and corrected by Chitorafa
www.addic7ed.com
Bonnie: Ho, ho, howdy, everyone.
That sure was a fun Christmas.
Hello, villagers!
Whoo!
'Scuse me! Pardon me! Thank you!
Hey, there, baby reindeer.
Let's spread some Christmas cheer!
I am the goblin fairy.
I'll make you the most beautiful of all.
Pling! Hooray!
Excuse me, miss.
There's a bug in my son's ice cream,
and he has a bug allergy!
There you go, sweetheart. Enjoy.
Oh, no! My dinosaur has escaped!
I'll find you!
- Did you hear that, Rex?
- I am a bit concerned.
No!
For once, I'm finally going to
get played with as a dinosaur!
Oh.
Prepare yourself. Inhabit the part.
You must not play the dinosaur.
You must be the dinosaur.
But I am the dinosaur.
Exactly! Now, get out there and sparkle.
[Gasps]
There she is!
The terrifying... Kittysaurus!
Oh, no! She laid millions of eggs!
Bloop, bloop, bloop.
Rawr!
Mom: Bonnie, get ready
to leave, okay, sweetie?
Coming!
To be continued.
Whoo! That was fun!
The way Bonnie's mind works
is a mystery of science.
You make a fantastic little dinosaur.
- Well done, Kitty.
- I was completely convinced.
I didn't know you had it in you.
[Clears throat]
Oh, and, um, your portrayal
of the disgruntled lunch
counter patron was gripping.
Aw, don't worry, Trixie.
Next time, you'll be a dinosaur for sure.
Andy used to play with me
like a dinosaur all the time.
Yeah, me too.
It's not all it's cracked up to be.
- How would I know?
- Good point.
Mom: Honey, why don't you bring
some toys to share with Mason?
I'll get my spaceship.
Santa Woody, villager, daddy
reindeer, baby reindeer,
and the terrifying Kittysaurus.
[Sighs]
Greet the world with an open heart.
Ugh!
Remember to be polite, now.
"Please" and "thank you."
Dad: Hey! Go on upstairs, Bonnie.
Mason's easy to find.
Mason!
Mason?
[Video game noises]
Whoa! Oh, duck!
Whoa. That was close.
Um...
[Gasps] You've got to be kidding me.
He got an Optimum X for Christmas!
I never knew Mason liked video games.
Sadly, the controls are
beyond my limitations.
Limitations are the shackles
we bind to ourselves.
Mason!!
Oh. Hey, Bonnie.
Whoa! You have got to check this out.
[Grunts]
Come on!
Oh. Okay.
- Whoa!
- Buzz: Mayday! Mayday!
- Trixie: We're going in!
Aah!
Whoa!
Unh!
[Groans]
Everyone okay?
Rex: I guess we're not
getting played with after all.
Buzz: Well, who could blame her?
No one could resist an Optimum X.
Where is everybody?
Where's Socky and the little wrestlers
and the Eagle Force gang?
Looks like we got all afternoon
to find our old friends.
And maybe some new ones.
Wow. Mason really hit the
jackpot this Christmas.
Nobody's this good.
We're gonna meet some new toys!
I'm both excited and panic-stricken.
Trixie: "Battlesaurs,
the ultimate dinosaurs."
I love it.
- [Growls]
- Oh!
Hey!
[Growling]
Oh! [Chuckles]
Here, boy! Here, little guy.
Trixie!
Come on, gang. Let's stay together.
H-hey! Slow down, buddy!
- Where you going?
- Trixie!
Hey, Trixie!
[Panting]
[Snarls]
[Gasps]
You guys, this play date
just got very interesting.
A complete set, fresh out of the box.
- Where is everybody?
- Hello?
[Screeching]
Hey, motion-activated room sentry.
Impressive.
[All shouting, growling]
Whoa, look at 'em!
They're like dinosaurs plus
with the armor and the little red spears.
- [Snarling]
- Easy there, little doggie.
Speak swiftly, foolish outlanders,
or suffer my battle blade.
Ooh. [Clears throat]
We are savage warriors,
eager to slake our endless
thirst for conquest.
Huh? Huh?
Ooh, nice.
Everyone's so committed to their roles.
Who goes there?!
[Grunts]
Wah!
Go talk to him, sheriff.
Uh, well. Hi, there, sir.
My name is Woody.
And, uh... Nobody cares.
What fearsome dinosaurs are these?
- Oh.
Greetings. I am Reptillus Maximus.
And I am, um...
Oh, my name's Trixie. It's Trixie.
You're not like our females.
[Screeches]
Oh, you're quite a
unique specimen yourself.
[Chuckles]
[Horn blares]
[Squeaking]
[Chirps]
[Groans]
Now we know where they keep the fossils.
- [Chuckles]
- [Clears throat]
Strangers from the unforgiving outlands.
We have traveled far from
the distant Bonnie Tribe.
[Both chuckle]
Shh!
[Grumbles] Hmm.
Ugh!
Leave your offerings and be gone.
[Clears throat]
Are dinosaurs not welcome in
our great city, wise cleric?
[Grumbles]
Fine, fine. Have them made presentable.
I find their lack of armor disturbing.
[Chuckles] To the armory!
Well, I think I'm going to head back.
I'll go with you.
I've had enough "Shakespeare
In The Park" for one day.
Suit yourself. See you later.
[Both gasp]
[Chuckles evilly]
Welcome to Battlopolis.
[Laughs]
Oh, that's nice.
Excellent.
A notch here. A jog there.
- [Both chuckle]
- Now, go and be magnificent.
Ooh!
Ray-gon, indulge this dinosaur goddess
in your finest wear.
Hmm. I like where this is going.
Oh, look at you!
A ponderous monolithic
canvas to be adorned.
Keep talking.
The symmetry of a senatopsid
and such strong anterior protuberai.
- You are so discerning.
- Oh, yes.
I'm quite expert in the enhancitizing
and accoutremization of
Battlesaurs large and small.
[Gasps]
Ooh!
Okay. I'll take that.
- Oh, yes. Of course.
- And that.
- Azmacol warheads.
- Well, you never know.
- Gauntlets.
- Yeah, very nice!
- Dorsal sensory plates.
- For me?
Oh, most certainly.
Do you have the battle gogs in flame?
- Do you have to ask?
- Dish them on over, little fella.
Have I mentioned what a
fantastic time I'm having?
It is as plain as the horn on your face.
[Chuckles]
When do I get a turn?
Ha! I haven't forgotten you, brother.
It's perfect!
[Clears throat]
- [Chuckles]
- Ready for me?
- [Grumbles]
- Ohh.
Well? What do you think?
The Elders shall gaze upon this Battlesaur
with full and rapturous pride.
That's exactly what I thought you'd say.
Rex: Hey, Trixie.
Trixie! Ha!
Who's a fierce dinosaur now?
Rawr!
The ultimate dinosaurs.
[Chuckles] Come. Battlopolis awaits.
[Growls]
This set is incredible.
I could really get used to this.
Give us some muscle.
You're a bruiser, aren't you, lad?
Prehistoric buildings, dinosaur cars,
whatever that thing's meant to be.
What is it?
The Triassic Tower of the Dream Elders,
through which distant
beings convey cosmic wisdom
from another dimension.
Oh. At our house,
Bonnie just yells across
the room in a funny voice.
[Grumbles]
And here, the Volcano
Command base... my domain.
Everyone needs an apartment
shaped like their own head.
Battle well, brother.
With strength and honor. [Grunts]
Pricklepants is right.
You just need to be the Battlesaur.
Your Pricklypants is a wise prophet.
Battle is everything to us,
our survival, our legacy.
From a kingdom long ago...
♪ An enigma wrapped in mystery ♪
♪ We've battled every foe ♪
♪ Since before the dawn of history ♪
♪ History ♪
♪ Battlesaurs, Battlesaurs ♪
- [Guitar riff]
-♪ Battlesaurs ♪
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
[Chuckles] You even have a theme song?
[Sighs] You seem to have everything.
You are a puzzle, Trixie.
Well, technically, I'm
a posable action figure.
[Chuckles]
Now, tell me more of your world.
Oh. [Chuckles] It's nothing like this.
I'll bet you have the
most amazing play times.
Play times?
I do not understand.
Oh, you know, play.
When you give yourself over to a kid.
Giving is surrender.
A Battlesaur would never surrender.
Ooh.
So serious.
[Chuckles]
Trixie, you cause me to
question all that I know.
[Growls]
[Beeping]
Time for battle.
- Time for battle.
- [All shouting]
Oh, what's that?
The Great Dream Elder beckons
us to the Arena of Woe.
Okay.
[Cheers and applause] Reptillus Maximus!
Yay! Love you!
[Gasps]
Rawr.
[Cheers and applause]
[Chuckles]
Rawr!
Well, this seems festive.
[Squeaking]
[Clicking]
Let the battle begin.
[Horn blares]
Get on in there.
Socky! Pengo! Fauntleroy!
Oh, this will be good. I'll do a jab.
Then you pretend to attack me. Then...
You guys are so jumpy.
[Growls]
- Aaah!
- [Cheers and applause]
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Why are you doing this?
[Clicking]
Eek!
Oh, I got it!
It's doomsday.
[Growls]
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
Hey!
[Snarling]
- Trixie? - Trixie?
- What?
Trixie, the Battlesaurs are not playing.
They've never been played with.
They don't even know they're toys!
Incredible, isn't it?
[Chuckles evilly]
Kkkk!
[Growls]
[Gasps] No!
You got a crayon?
[Growls]
Aah!
Buzz... Buzz... Buzz
Lightyear to the rescue.
[Gasps]
Blast.
[Snarling]
Back off, you!
You bully!
Curse.
Release the Goliathon!
[Cheers and applause]
[Laughs]
[Shrieks]
Buzz: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Unh!
Ow!
Ohh!
[Slurps]
[Cheers and applause]
Cough up my friends, you... you!
[All gasp]
As I suspected.
She bears the mark of obedience.
Uh. What? This?
[Spectators murmur]
[Sighs] I thought I knew you.
I was thinking the same thing.
She is an enemy to the tribe.
Ray-gon, the supplicator.
The supplicator. [Muttering]
[Laughs]
Aah! Aah!
Rex, have you completely lost it?
I'm sorry!
I can't control myself! Ooh!
There is no escape,
Trixie of the Bonnie Tribe.
[Laughs]
[Gasps] Bonnie. Aah!
Run, Trixie! Get Bonnie!
[Snarling]
[Gasps]
Reptillus, stop her!
[Grunts]
Huh?
What?
[Grunts]
[Clicking]
[Chuckles]
[Chirping]
Hmm. Robot, obey.
[Gasps]
Ugh!
[Grunts]
- Rex!
I can't help it!
[Coughs]
Woody.
What?
Hey. Hey, that's Mason and Bonnie.
Oh, I get it.
You're glad Mason got the Optimum X.
He plays there while I rule here.
My Battlesaurs have no use for play.
They have everything they need,
content in their ignorance.
What's ignorance?
I don't know.
You've been a busy little tyrant,
and only two days since Christmas?
Christmas?
The joy that you give to others
is the joy that comes back to you.
Aw!
Bah!
You will all be cast into the pit.
- Pit? - Pit?
- Pit?
[Laughs evilly]
[Panting]
I've got to shut it down.
[Sighs]
Come on, buddy. Fight it off!
Rex, resist the supplicator.
Sorry. I'm sorry!
[Thudding]
Oh, boy.
[Grunting]
No!
- [Gasps]
- Aah!
[Growls]
Reptillus!
Your world is bigger than you know.
Let me show you who you really are.
But I am a Battlesaur!
You can be so much more!
And you know it.
[Laughs]
- Put down your...
- [Squeak]
Reptillus, it's your kid who
chooses what you're going to be.
It could be a dinosaur, baby reindeer,
or something you'd never even think of.
It's about being there for your kid.
It's... it's about...
Surrender.
- Huh?
- This bus is out of gas.
Dang it. The power's down.
Oh, hello.
Are you lost?
Come see my igloo.
We can wait inside with the
polar bears and the salamanders
until they find us.
Check the supplies.
We have hamburgers, pisketti,
pancakes, chocolate milk, gummy worms.
- Oh, what planet is he from?
- Neptune!
Or maybe Florida.
[Grunting]
[Laughter]
- Aah!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[Laughs]
Ah, hat!
Suit!
[Click]
Whoo-hoo!
We crash-landed on the party planet!
Aliens everywhere!
[Laughter]
Wait.
Where's my baby reindeer?
[Gasps] There she is.
[Whispering]
She says, "put on your dance pants!"
[Dance music playing]
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
Look, Buzz. I'm a boneless chicken!
How about a dance, Uncle Wormy?
Don't know how.
[Gasps] He's adorable.
Boop, boop, beep, bop.
Come on, Mecha Monster.
Let's fight some crime.
Pshew!
[Laughter in distance]
That was... glorious.
It was, wasn't it?
Dad: It's always so great
to have Bonnie around.
Let's have her back next week.
Mom: So, shall we say Tuesday around 3:30?
Bonnie!
Pshew!
Dinner, sweetie.
Bye, toys.
Whoo-hoo! [Smooching]
So, how was the play date?
Oh, you know. Typical crash landing.
Hostillizard people, hand-to-hand combat.
And I was a mindless, lumbering automoton.
- Well, that part adds up.
- What about you, Trixie?
Have you finally found
a role that suits you?
Goblin fairy, ghost clown...
- Hey, hey! Easy now!
- ... dancing queen...
a baby reindeer.
You name it.
I'm Bonnie's dinosaur.
And Bonnie's dinosaur
gets to be everything.
Be grateful for your gifts.
They are all around you.
All: Aw!
Synced and corrected by Chitorafa
www.addic7ed.com
[Snoring]
[Sighs]
Farewell, Trixie of the Bonnie Tribe.
My heart will burn bright
until the moment of your return...
Tuesday around 3:30.