Director: All right, let's
clear here.
Here we go.
Five, four, three, two...
Man: It's "America this
morning."
I'm Jay, this is my girl, candy.
And, of course, everybody knows
I'm an animal lover.
>> Yes, we know that, Jay.
That's because you're an animal.
>> Well, you're exactly right.
But, actually, I heard about
this town in Florida where
they're having a dog marathon.
>> You're kidding.
No, I'm not kidding.
>> All right, so that's 26.2
Miles of loud, dog barking and
dog fighting, and who exactly is
gonna clean up the poop
after this is all said and done?
Certainly not me. [ Laughs ]
But, listen, it's for charity,
though.
It's a good thing.
>> Oh, really?
What charity would that be,
the dumb ideas foundation?
Folks, my girl candy,
I mean, she's a cat-lover.
She's a hater, okay?
>> Oh, I'm a hater, am I?
Yes, you are.
>> All right, well, viewers,
we'd love to hear what you
think about this brilliant idea.
So, please, e-mail us, tweet us,
and we will weigh in this
subject at the end of the show.
Coming up next, we have a
brilliant wholistic doctor who
says that he has proof that a
rare mushroom can cure cancer.
We'll be right back.
Director: And we're clear.
>> Can someone please explain to
me why this is freezing?! Jay?
Yes?
>> After eight years of working
together, why would you refer to
me as a cat-person, when you
know I can't stand animals of
any kind?
It was for the segment, okay?
You gonna be okay?
Well, I just think it's a big
deal to falsely represent
someone. >> Here we go.
You know what?
In the future, would you please
just refrain from referring to
me as a dog-person or
a cat-person...
or even a goldfish-person,
because that's not who I am.
>> All right, whatever.
Are you gonna
get over it, though?
Yes, I'm fine.
Where's my coffee?!
Can somebody get her some
coffee, please?
Thank you. >> That's right there
oh, boy.
>> Director: All right, folks,
here we go.
We're back in five, four, three,
two...
>> It doesn't make any sense.
Welcome back to
"America this morning."
Our next guest...
>> We've confirmed for Thursday,
candy.
Now, Friday is the governor's
ball... we've not rsvped for
that, so are we a "go,"
what are we doing?
>> Okay, wait a minute,
it's this Friday? >> Yes.
We need to cancel.
I have other plans.
You want to cancel
the governor's ball.
Yes, we need to cancel.
Tell him I came down with
something.
>> Even though you were just
on the air looking perfectly
healthy?
Tell him it happened
after the show.
Got it. >> Also, one more thing.
Yes?
>> Yesterday, I saw some crumbs
on my desk.
I don't know if they were muffin
crumbs or something like that,
but are you trying to ruin my
career?
>> Candy, I didn't mean to bring
pastries around.
>> We have talked about this
several times.
I'm on a very strict diet for
the next 90 days.
>> I know that.
Which means that I can't be
around any sweets of any kind
because even the smell of sweets
is total mayhem for me.
And I don't want to be in
chat rooms and on social media
where people are talking about
how I've just become this big
fat cow, and they put a picture
of me in the tabloids next to
shamu!
>> Candy, it won't happen again.
That's a relief. Bounce.
Bye, thank you.
Muffin crumbs? Really?
Don't you think you're
overreacting just a bit, candy?
Louis, as a manager,
you of all people know how
vicious, sometimes, fans can be.
>> But that's your eighth
assistant this year.
>> Well, what is your point
about that?
>> I guess I have no point.
These just came in from that
f.A.N. Guy again.
That's the third time this
month.
[ Sighs ]
"Anyone can sing in the sun,
but not many people know how to
dance in the rain."
That's corny.
>> Aw, that's very sweet.
This guy always says the coolest
things.
Well, he just might be a
stalker.
Oh, relax.
I'm sure it's harmless.
I'm gonna put this with my
collection.
Oh, candy, the reporter from
woman now magazine is on set
ready for her interview.
>> Louis, really?
How many of these things
do I have to do in a week?
The book's not gonna sell
itself, candy.
Just give 'em 15 minutes,
at least.
Roger that. Gina, get out.
Ugh!
I need to get my head straight
before this interview. [ Sighs ]
You need to get a lot more
than that straight, candy.
You've won numerous awards
and honors for hosting one of.
America's favorite talk shows.
You have endorsement deals,
thousands of fans, and now a new
book.
Is there anything that
candy meyers can't do?
Um... You know, it's funny, I...
I don't think of myself as very
special.
I just... I'm blessed enough to
have the lord give me these
beautiful assignments, and I'm
crazy enough to say yes.
But one might wager, candy,
with your busy life and being a
woman of a certain age...
That maybe you've chosen to
sacrifice certain things,
like marriage and a family.
You know, I think it's
interesting, Nadia, that you
would equate a marriage and
family as happiness.
And I'm sure that there are
millions of women around the
world who would beg to differ.
Unfortunately, I don't have the
time to argue this point because
I have to re-shoot this promo.
But know I didn't mean to
offend you.
Oh, no, I know.
Thank you so much for your time.
Really, take care.
Good seeing you.
Thank you.
You want to tell me what's
wrong?
You haven't said a word since
the interview earlier.
I ever tell you I'm adopted?
>> No.
No, I would have remembered
something like that.
[ Sighs ]
I was eight years old
when my parents... the meyers...
told me.
Do you know what it was like to
be eight years old and find out
that your family doesn't really
belong to you?
>> I can't imagine that, no.
Well, I suddenly felt like,
I don't know, a hamster that you
bring home from the pet store.
You know, you're part of the
family, but you're not really
part of the family.
They love you, candy.
I mean, you and I both know
that.
>> Yes, I know that, Louis,
but that doesn't change how I
feel.
You know, and when that reporter
today stated so graciously that
I didn't have a family of my
own, I just started thinking,
you know, if I do end up having
children of my own, what am I
gonna tell them?
I don't know anything.
I don't know about their
grandparents, I don't know about
their ancestry, their history,
my medical background.
I know nothing.
>> Your grandparents are your
folks, Evelyn and errol meyers.
>> Yeah, Louis.
And when my imaginary kids turn
eight years old, I'll just tell
them that that was a lie, too.
Never mind.
I'll be back.
Louis: Three red onions, as
requested.
Candy: Oh, great! Perfect.
You need me to chop 'em up?
>> No, but can you shred that
gouda for me, please?
>> Why not?
You want me to milk the cow,
too, while I'm at it?
Let me wash my hands.
I figured you'd be done with
this already.
Yeah, well, my family shows
up for the first time ever
on time, and I'm nowhere near
done.
Yeah, I see.
Wow! What a treat!
Louis, it's so good to see you.
>> Hi, Gladys.
How are you? >> Excellent.
And yourself?
>> Blessed as ever.
Came to see if my eldest needed
any help?
No, thank you, mom. I've got it.
Mm-hmm. I see.
I guess you do... with Louis
here.
Isn't this your day off?
Don't you need a break from my
daughter's running you around
you around everywhere?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Correction, he's the one who's
always running me around...
book tours and interviews and
assignments.
>> I'm just dropping by to make
sure everything's okay. >> Mmm.
Checking in, huh? Off the clock?
Mom. >> For no money.
Mom!
>> Are you sweet on my candy,
Louis? >> Mom!
Stop! You're always reading into
stuff!
Louis and I have a perfectly
wonderful working relationship.
He is my business manager,
that is it.
>> Well, something's going on.
I mean, Robbie never checked in
on his day off.
That's because Robbie was an
idiot, which is why I fired him.
Don't say that. He's family.
Not my family. >> Come again?
Nothing.
>> Louis, since you're here,
why don't you stay for lunch and
join us?
Sure. >> No, no, no, mom!
I have something really
important I need to discuss.
It's a family issue.
>> That's okay, Mrs. meyers.
I got a few errands to run
anyway.
You need anything else?
>> No, this was awesome.
Thank you. Appreciate it.
All right. Good to see you.
You have a good day.
>> Take care.
Okay.
What? >> I think you hurt his
feelings. >> Oh, please!
Mom, he gets paid enough to get
over it.
Candace Ann meyers!
You're so bourgeois.
I wonder where I got it from.
[ Laughs ] Oh, my God!
All: Amen. >> Praise Jesus.
Pass the butter, please. >> Oh.
Here you are, daddy.
>> Thanks, candy girl.
More sweet tea, please.
>> Okay, coming right up.
Uh-uh. That's enough for her.
All right, well, does anybody
want anything while I'm up?
You want some hot sauce or I
have peppers in the fridge.
Or, John, you want anything?
>> No, I'm fantastic.
Why are you waitressing, candy?
Yeah, stop worrying about us
and just eat.
I just want to make sure
everybody's okay.
We're okay. Sit.
And where is all of this
nervous energy coming from, huh?
Wait. Are you seeing someone?
What's his name?
>> I'm not seeing anyone,
Charmaine. >> Oh.
Then when are you gonna start?
>> I don't know!
Do not snap at your sister,
she's just concerned about you,
as are we all. >> I am fine.
And when I start seeing the
right someone, you all will be
the first five people to know.
>> I think Louis is perfect
for you, honey.
I wish you would listen to me.
Mommy, I said the same thing!
>> He has love and adoring...
can we please... can we
please stop talking about my
love life? I have...
and he has a job!
>> I have something...
I have something that I want to
talk to you guys about anyway.
Hmm? >> What's on your mind,
baby girl? >> I...
I think it's time that I find...
Them.
Who's she looking for?
Mom...
I didn't mean to make you upset.
I'm not upset, Candace.
>> Clearly.
You have everything going for
you.
A great life, a fabulous career.
Money, fame.
Why now? >> I don't know.
I just feel like it's time.
>> At 35 years old?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize there was a
statute of limitations
for me to find my real...
we are your real family...
from day one!
Yeah, and then a miracle
happened.
We never treated you
differently when Charmaine was
born, and you know that.
>> I do know that, mom,
but I am different.
And I just... you know, I want
to know who I belong to.
>> You belong to me.
To us.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Please don't cry.
So we don't have the same
blood line.
Who cares?
You're still my big sister.
I will be, char, thank you.
>> And it's obvious to me
whoever your real parents are,
they don't care about you.
Charmaine! >> Mom, I'm sorry.
Look, they had enough time to
find her.
I mean, duh!
All they had to do was turn on
the TV, and there she was
in plain sight.
It's obvious they chose
to stay away.
You don't get it.
They could never love you
the way we do. >> Candace?
Coming, daddy.
Clearly, you gave this a lot
of thought before you told us.
Yes, sir. >> Yeah, well...
You're a grown woman.
Who am I to stop you?
Daddy...
None of this changes how I feel
about you and mom.
Uh-huh. I sure hope so.
Because I couldn't bear
to lose you.
You won't.
Well... We'll do anything we can
for you, candy yam.
Thank you, dad. You're the best.
[ Chuckles ] You, too.
Gina: Candy, did you get my
text that the signing was
scheduled to start
30 minutes ago?
I did. I ignored it.
Okay, not a problem.
Well, there's a huge crowd out
there, which is good, even if
you're late.
Do you need anything before you
start?
Yes, privacy... immediately.
Thank you. >> Got it.
Any calls?
>> No calls from the agency.
[ Sighs ]
I don't understand, Louis.
I mean, okay, there's no father
listed on my birth certificate,
but they found my mother three
weeks ago.
So why hasn't she contacted me?
>> Well, maybe she's scared,
candy. It's been over 30 years.
Well, I'm not waiting another
30 years.
I hired a private investigator.
Hopefully, he'll speed up the
results.
>> And I'm just now hearing
about this?
>> I'm sorry, I didn't realize
I needed to clear it with you,
Louis.
Well, as your manager, no,
but as your friend, I'd like to
be kept in the loop.
>> Hey, candy, they're really,
really asking very nicely that
we start the book signing
right now. >> Fine.
On with the show, right?
Here you are. >> Thank you!
You're welcome.
Evening, miss meyers.
>> Good evening.
Are you um, f.A.N.? >> No, no.
My brother Freddie is... was.
He had a heart attack and passed
away a couple days ago.
Oh, no, I'm...
I'm sorry to hear that.
His...
His cards and his flowers,
they always made my day.
>> Yeah, well, he would have...
He would have like that.
>> Please, give your family my
condolences. >> Well, you see...
That's just the thing.
You are my family.
Uh, just ask the...
Detective you sent.
What? >> Who are you?
I'm abner Thomas Nelson.
My brother was
Frederick Andrew Nelson. And...
He was your father, candy.
>> No, I'm...
I'm sorry, that...
That can't be.
Well, I'm sorry it had to
come to you like this.
Freddie was so looking forward
to meeting you.
Excuse me.
Um... [ Clears throat ]
Freddie's funeral is in a couple
of days out in Manning.
My number's there.
He would surely love it if...
If she could attend.
So you're not even gonna
consider it?
He's your biological father,
candy.
This is your last chance
to see him above ground.
All right.
You'll regret it if you don't.
I can't go.
Not by myself.
>> Who says you have to?
And as a friend, deal?
Well... This is it.
You ready?
Man: Yes. Brother Freddie...
Was a good man.
>> Woman: Yes, he was.
He... Oh, my!
[ Woman gasps ]
[ Whispering ] I think that's
Candace meyers.
>> [ People gasping ]
[ Shutter clicks ]
>> Brother Freddie...
Was a very hard-working man,
who served the lord
with joy in his heart.
He loved his family.
And didn't have an enemy in the
world.
Would help anyone in need
at any time.
And he continued to...
>> Woman: I just want to pay my
respects.
He was a friend of mine.
Move out of my way!
>> Abner: Oh, no!
Oh, my lord.
>> Woman: I can't believe this.
My sweet Freddie.
>> Somebody come get her.
[ Sighs ]
Man: Excuse... ex...
put that back!
Abner: Let her have I
let my brother have some peace
for once. >> Woman: What?!
Mm-mmm! Mm-mmm!
You just might get it.
You don't want to mess with me.
Crazy dingbat!
What kind of germ is that?!
Man: All right, all right!
Everybody, everybody, settle
down. Look, this is a home-going
service, not "tmz."
>> Abner, who's that crazy
woman? >> Your mother.
Man: Now...
Abner: Hey! [ Chuckles ]
Come on in. Ah.
Really good to...
To see you, miss meyers.
Oh, abner, please call me candy.
I think we can dispense with
the formalities.
Don't you?
>> Well, candy, let me introduce
you to some of your kinfolk.
This here is cousin jessie,
cousin Sam.
Cousin Jamie, and Melissa.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Oh, and come on in here.
I want you to meet a couple
of fine boys.
This is... Trevor and Andrew.
Candy, these...
These are your brothers.
I have brothers? >> Oh.
It's very nice to meet you.
>> Hi, Trevor.
Hi. >> You better give me a hug,
girl. Mmm!
[ Chuckles ]
Welcome to the family.
Thank you. >> [ Clears throat ]
Don't I get an introduction?
>> Um, this is Trevor and.
Andrew's mother... delores.
>> Ah, it's a pleasure meeting
you, Mrs. Nelson.
>> Well, don't forget...
I was married to Freddie.
And I was faithful for every bit
of 37 years. How old are you?
Abner: Careful, delores.
>> I'm 35, ma'am.
[ Scoffs ] >> Excuse me.
Hi, Mrs. Nelson.
I'm Louis... candy's manager.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Listen, we came a long way to be
here today.
I hear Southern women know how
to cook.
Quite frankly, we're starved.
Any chance we can get
a bite to eat?
Suzie mae?
Go to the kitchen and get
a hot plate for these people.
Hold up.
But bring me a cold glass
of ice water.
I'm gonna need it.
Thank you. >> Beautiful house.
Yes, it's nice. >> Mm-hmm.
And that's daddy after he got
his high school diploma eight
years ago.
He did regret having to drop
out, but he did have a family to
look after.
But that didn't stop him from
starting his own plumbing
business.
That's his store right there.
And his ice cream parlor.
>> And he had a delivery
service.
That's the one I'm in charge of
right there. >> Oh.
And she don't care nothing
about that.
Well, I was just trying to
show her that daddy was a
go-getter.
>> And I'm telling you she don't
care nothing about that.
>> Look, he wasn't no slouch.
Well, your mama made a
complete fool out of herself
today. >> Abner: That's enough,
delores. This child ain't come
here to be insulted by you.
>> She ain't no kin to me,
abner. >> Well, she's kin to me.
And I ain't gonna let you treat
her like some mangy dog done
wandered in off the street!
>> Mmm.
More like a mutt if you ask me.
>> Delores!
Mama, please!
>> This here is our family's
house.
And ain't nobody asked me how I
felt about her being here.
>> Okay, maybe I should go.
Blowing in here like she's
some big movie star.
Honey, we don't need your
favors, okay?
That wasn't my intention.
>> Mm-hmm.
You're probably on
the stuff, too.
Delores, stop it!
>> Delores: Mm-hmm.
Most big-time stars are.
>> That's not true.
Well, that wouldn't surprise
me none.
'Cause the apple don't fall far
from the tree.
What is she talking about?
>> Nothing.
She ain't talking about nothing.
>> Nothing?! You call one year
in the loony bin nothing?
And judging by that performance
she put on today, she needs to
go back in there.
Mama!
>> Okay, gentlemen, if you'll
excuse me, I'm gonna leave now.
Louis?
Thank you for your hospitality.
>> Delores: I can't say it was
a pleasure. >> Trevor: Candy!
Come on, baby.
Come on here to me.
Abner: God don't like ugly,
delores.
Mm-hmm.
Y'all done forgot I buried my
husband today.
>> Candy, you should friend me
so I can send you all the family
pictures.
Oh, you thought it was because
I wanted to brag to everybody
about you being my sister and
all, but I wasn't even thinking
that until just now.
And I'm sorry...
It's okay, Trevor, really.
>> don't worry about my mama.
You're always welcome in
Manning.
Thank you, Andrew.
>> Look after our sister, Louis.
Will do, man.
Thanks for having us.
I'll drive you all to the hotel.
Okay. Thank you, everyone.
Nice meeting you all.
Abner? >> Mmm?
How long have you all known
about me?
A few years now.
No one came to see me?
>> Yeah, Freddie's wishes.
He said it wasn't his call to
make.
Well, didn't he want to see me?
[ Chuckles ]
He saw you all the time.
Watched your show every morning.
And if you were somewhere close,
he'd go out to see you.
Of course, you know about the
notes and flowers and things.
>> Yeah, which I won't get
anymore. >> [ Sighs ]
He loved you, candy.
He just wasn't...
Wasn't sure you wanted
to hear it.
Why would he think that?
>> Because of what happened with
him and your mama years ago.
>> Right.
He was married to delores when
they had their affair.
Well, no, no, no, it's deeper
than that.
Much deeper.
>> Okay, so tell me.
My flight doesn't leave till
tomorrow morning.
Well, maybe you ought to talk
to your mama.
Her name is Mary Jordan.
We all call her Mary Jo.
You might as well, candy.
We're here.
Okay. Where does she live?
About an hour outside of town...
far away from everything
and everyone.
[ Sighs ]
[ Door alarm chiming ]
All right. Let's head on up.
[ Dog barking ]
[ Barking continues ]
Mary Jo, call off the dog!
You got company!
Easy, boy. We come in peace.
[ Continues barking ]
Be careful, abner.
>> Little mama's boy!
He can't get... [ Barking ]
Shoot! Mary Jo, I've had it!
Abner, it's okay. Let's go.
No, no.
I drove an hour to get out here.
You're gonna open up the door!
You're just a stubborn old mule!
Abner? Really...
If she doesn't want to see me,
I don't want to force her to.
All right, all right.
We'll head on back.
And I ain't scare of your dog,
neither!
This is precisely why I'm not
a dog-person.
Yeah.
[ Door alarm chiming ]
Oh.
[ Sighs ] Candy...
Uh, Freddie wanted you
to have this.
Thank you, abner,
for everything.
Well, I better be getting back.
Louis. Fine meeting you.
Likewise, abner.
Take care of yourself, man.
Now, don't you be a stranger.
We family now.
[ Sighs ] Open the box, dummy.
[ Sobs softly ]
She sounds like a real pill.
>> Yeah.
And then she accused me of being
on drugs.
What?! >> Me, yeah.
That's why you should have
come to us before going out
there on your own.
>> I had Louis with me.
That's not the same thing.
I'm your mother.
And I would have straightened
all this out.
Really? How, mom?
Well, first of all, I would
have popped that delores woman
in the mouth for talking to you
like that.
Mm-hmm.
>> And then that other woman,
the birth mother, Mary Jane.
>> Mary Jo.
Whatever, she couldn't even
open the door.
Well...
I'm glad you've gotten this out
of your system, and I hope that
you realize that you really do
have the best life.
You have the life that God
intended for you to have.
[ Knife clangs on board ]
So we're done with this, right?
Candace?
>> Mom, I have questions,
and Mary Jo is the only one
who can answer them.
Well, what if you don't like
what she says, what then?
Honey, you have all the answers.
Use wisdom,
and let it go.
Smells good.
>> Gonna taste good, too.
[ Laughs ]
So I can cover Cleveland and
Cincinnati on Tuesday, fly back
for work on Wednesday.
Wednesday afternoon, I'm at
heads in Chicago doing an
in-store visit, the sister
station, come back home
Thursday.
I'll stay local after the show,
do a couple press junkets with
radio, and then Friday
afternoon, I'm gonna head to.
D.C. for the breast cancer
auction, and I'll be there
Saturday to leave for new y...
What?
What's the problem?
Why are you looking at me like
that?
>> You hate doing interviews.
Now you're trying to do a
hundred in five days.
Well, Louis, you said that
the book isn't gonna sell
itself, so...
>> I just don't think it's a
good idea that you jam-pack your
schedule so tight, candy.
Well, fortunately, I don't
make decisions based on what
you think, Gina. I like this.
Let's... this is too bright.
Hold on a second.
Let me see something.
This is a size six.
I'm a size four.
Okay, you know, you've kind
of gained a little over the past
week. >> Okay, that's not true!
Candy. >> You know what?
It's all right.
I mean, it's not like a size six
is fatal.
I mean, there are lots of women
out there that wear a size
sixes...
you know what?
Well, that's great for them!
But I am a size four, and if you
don't know the difference
between a four and a six,
then perhaps you shouldn't be a
stylist.
>> Okay, I'll grab you a four.
All right, everyone,
I need a moment with candy.
Please!
Why did you do that?
>> 'Cause, apparently, you've
lost your mind.
>> You and I both know in this
business, a size six is a
fatality, okay?
I might as well just be one
"the biggest loser."
But you're overreacting, candy.
Really?!
Because I'm saying what it is I
want and how I want it?
>> Oh, I see.
You're angry about your
birth mother.
Things didn't go well with her,
so you're trying to take it out
on everyone else?
>> That's not true.
Listen, candy...
I know you're disappointed, but
you can't control how people
feel.
Thank you, Dr. Phil.
I spoke to abner again.
He said you haven't been
returning any of his calls.
>> You know what, Louis, if you
want to remain my manager,
then it's probably a good idea
for you not to bring up those
people or that place
to me again.
>> So you're threatening to fire
me, too?
Where are you going?
Where are you going?!
To get some air...
If that's okay, boss.
Francisca, Elijah!
We got two minutes.
You weren't tripping.
>> Well, I don't like animals.
You know that.
>> While you guys were gone,
of course, our last segment
where we had the spider monkey
from Argentina... >> right.
Cute little animals.
She's tripping.
Cute? Cute?
Hold on, how many cautionary
tales do we need about people
having their faced ripped off
by wild animals?
It's a wild animal.
>> The spider monkey is as big
as my hand.
>> Our last guest showed us how
to make some of our favorite
dishes with alternatives
in a more health way.
Now, okay, Jay...
I'm sorry, your last guest
was your next door neighbor.
No, really, seriously,
we have to start putting real
chefs on instead of people that
are your friends.
Our next guest has created a
new fitness craze that's taking
the nation by storm.
It combines soccer and samba.
What do you think about this,
Jay?
Um... I actually don't know what
samba is. >> [ Both laugh ]
Mm-hmm. Yeah, no.
I can...
I can just catch the red-eye
again on the way back.
That's fine.
No big deal.
Okay, well, I'll see you
Thursday. Looking forward to it.
You take care. Bye-bye.
Candy, I can get you an
energy drink to make it through
the day, if you want. >> Um...
Yeah, that would be great, Gina.
Thank you.
Oh, has... Has Louis called?
He should be here by now.
>> No, but I can get him on the
phone for you. >> Okay.
[ Knock on door ] >> Hey, candy.
Five-minute warning. Thank you.
Candy? Candy?!
[ Crunching ]
Hey, hey, hey! Slow down.
You're gonna have to eat some
real food today, you know.
No, I don't.
>> [ Mockingly ] "No, I don't."
I made a huge mistake today.
>> Which was?
I watched the news.
Apparently the whole world knows
that I fainted.
I can only imagine what the
Twitter thugs are saying.
>> Only that you o.D.Ed on some
diet pills, but that... sed to tl
you that.
Sorry.
>> Well, did they plug the book,
at least? >> No.
Oh, come on, candy.
It's gonna be okay.
Oh, no, char. I just...
I've never felt so lost.
And it has nothing to do with
you and mom and dad.
It's just...
I feel like I'm losing it.
You know, like I just feel
so out of place.
Will you pray for me?
Yeah.
Heavenly father,
we ask for your help to guide
Candace today,
for you to give her the insight
and direction on what
she should do.
We know that your desire for
her is for her to prosper and be
in health.
Touch her body, her mind,
her soul.
Restore to her your peace.
That surpasses all
understanding.
Thank you for it now,
and in Jesus'...
in Jesus' name, amen.
Is that soup homemade? >> Yeah.
Yeah, our cousin Campbell made
it.
You are such a bad liar.
You're supposed to make homemade
soup. I'm sick.
I forgot the chicken.
Hi. >> Hi.
How are you feeling?
>> I feel good.
A brownie?
From my favorite place?
How did you know?
>> Because I know you, candy...
better than you think.
I need to know what you want to
do about the rest of the book
tour.
Oh. You know, I'm so rude.
I didn't even offer you
anything to drink.
You want some lemonade
or ice tea or...
no, candy.
What do you want to do?
You're just like Charmaine.
She's checked on me like umpteen
times since this whole thing
happened, so...
Candy, what do you want to do?
I don't want to go, Louis.
What happens if we cancel
everything? >> Simple.
You lose a ton of money on book
sales, piss off a few dozen
venders, and disappoint a whole
lot of fans who want to see you.
Why are you acting like this?
>> Isn't this how you want me
to be... all business? >> No.
Then let's stop
playing games, candy.
I care about you.
I care about your health,
your wellbeing.
But you got unfinished business
in Manning.
And unless you get to the bottom
of it, you're gonna fall apart,
along with everything you've
built in your career.
Louis, I'm... Scared.
I know, but...
God is with you on this.
And so am I. Okay?
Okay. >> Good.
Maybe you should call your mom
or sister to go with you.
Well... I um...
Prefer to travel with friends.
Louis...
I can't do this without you.
Don't make me beg.
Okay.
[ Abner chuckles ]
>> Oh, thank you.
Mmm! >> Oh, my gosh!
Dinner was delicious. >> Mm-hmm.
And who made that amazing
pecan pie?
Right here. >> Y'all heard that?
She loves my pie. Mmm.
[ Chuckles ]
>> So think you're ready to see
miss Mary Jo tomorrow?
>> I don't know, Andrew,
but I hope so.
>> We're gonna give it a week
and see what happens.
>> And what about that dog?
Well, I have a steak
and a bb gun.
[ Abner chuckles ]
>> I'm gonna try the steak
first. >> Okay, okay.
We thought we'd never see you
again, candy.
And then we heard you fainted on
the news.
Yeah, everything's fine.
You know, it's just a lot
happened in a month.
I found out I have two brothers,
a sister-in-law, new nieces and
nephews.
And one amazing Uncle.
>> Mm-hmm.
Y'all want me to drive you
out there?
No, you don't have to do
that, abner.
We... we rented a car this time.
I remember the way, so...
All right. Well, let me know if
you need anything. >> Yes, sir.
Will do. >> Don't worry, abner.
I'm not afraid of Mary Jo.
>> You might have to use
that bb gun on her, too.
>> [ Laughter ]
Goodness.
Hello.
Do you remember me?
[ Dog barks in distance ]
Heel, granite.
Come on, boy. Come on.
Let's go. Good boy.
Sit down.
>> Mary Jo, please talk to me.
[ Starts engine ]
You weren't expecting her to
come easy, remember?
>> Did you see how
she looked at me?
Like I'm an intruder.
Well, she won't feel that way
too much longer,
'cause we're not giving up.
Come on.
Let's get something to eat.
Just a teaspoon.
And I mean a teaspoon...
Of white wine.
>> You're kidding.
Oh, I never would have guessed.
>> I know!
It's my secret weapon.
Now, if you tell anybody about
it, I will hunt you
and beat you senseless.
You understand? >> I do.
Okay, any questions? >> No.
[ Chuckles ]
Mary Jo?!
You in there?
Go away!
And stay off my property!
We need to talk.
>> I ain't interested.
Just go back to your fancy
hotel!
How do you know I'm staying
at a fancy hotel?
You got money, don't you?
Don't take a genius
to figure that out.
Mary Jo, I just want to talk
to you, and I'm not leaving
until we do.
>> Then you better get a
campfire going out there,
'cause I ain't opening the door!
You know what, abner is right!
You're just a stubborn mule!
>> No, no, no.
[ Sighs ] [ Knocks lightly ]
You hard of hearing, child?!
What are you afraid of?
I know you heard me.
I'm scared, too, Mary Jo,
but I'm here.
All right. This is the...
The best pecan pie I've ever had
in the whole wide world.
So I'm gonna come back tomorrow
and collect my dish.
Maybe some good food
will help you reconsider.
[ Sighs ]
We made some progress today.
At least she spoke.
Well, you'll...
You'll wear her down eventually.
Ugh. She's just so...
Bull-headed and stubborn.
>> Yeah, tell me about it.
What is that supposed to mean?
Well, candy, let's just say I
can see the family resemblance.
I am not stubborn, Louis.
I am meticulous.
I am tenacious.
>> Well, the rest of the world
calls that stubborn.
And you're too bossy.
All right, why don't you just
throw in "overbearing," while
you're at it?
>> And extremely sarcastic.
Well, I didn't realize I was
making everyone so miserable.
The pout. My personal favorite.
You know, can you please stop?
I do have feelings.
>> All right, all right, I'll
stop. >> Well, if I'm so awful,
then...
Why don't you just leave, quit?
Well... 'Cause I like you.
I like your heart.
I mean, when it's in the right
place.
>> Yeah, well, I bet you didn't
count on all this family drama.
>> I mean, what family doesn't
have drama? >> Really?
Okay, well, I'm all ears.
>> My parents divorced when I
was 12. My older sister died of
breast cancer.
My younger sister is in the
military.
Oldest brother is incarcerated.
My middle brother is happily
married in Florida, and then
there's me...
no wife, no kids, no rap sheet.
[ Chuckles ]
>> I didn't know any of that.
Louis, when did your older
sister die?
Last year.
Why didn't you tell me?
I mean, you didn't have to
grieve alone.
>> You were busy with your book,
so I didn't want to
distract you.
What was her name? >> Yvette.
Yvette. >> Yvette.
[ Bird cawing ]
She's gone.
Then we'll wait.
[ Sighs ] Hey.
At least she ate the pie. >> Oh.
I think. >> [ Chuckles ]
Well, somebody ate it.
It's so peaceful out here.
>> Yeah.
It's like the place that time
forgot, you know?
Not a strip mall or Starbucks in
sight.
No cameras or microphones.
You know, it's like there's no
expectations or demands.
I can just...
Be free.
Sorry. Just slipped out.
Don't be.
Since we're just sitting
here, let's go look around.
No. >> Come on.
Yeah! >> Really?
Oh, this girl's gonna get me
killed.
Come on! >> Wait, wait!
[ Gasps ] Oh!
Isn't this amazing?! >> A swing?
Yeah. >> I guess.
Uh, Louis?
Feel free to push me at any
time. >> Yes, boss.
[ Both chuckle ]
That's good? >> Yeah.
A little higher, please.
>> All right.
You asked for it. >> [ Laughs ]
This is so fun. >> Yeah.
You needed some of that. What?
It's true. [ Chuckles ]
You know, you're right.
I guess...
I don't really let myself
have this kind of fun, you know?
Not since I was a kid.
>> Miss those days, you know?
It's like when my father used to
take us camping when we were
little.
We really had some good times
together.
>> Where's your dad now?
He's... He's with yvette.
Sorry. >> That's okay, candy.
People die.
People we love very much.
That's why this is such a
blessing.
You know, you get a second
chance with Mary Jo.
And as long as she's alive,
there's hope.
We been out here a while.
You think she might be back?
I don't know. Let's go see.
Okay. >> [ Grunts ]
If I can get out. >> Um...
I'll race you.
>> Nah, I don't want to.
I don't want you to choke to
death, you know?
Choke on what? >> My dust!
Hold on, let me tie my shoe.
>> Oh, please.
Ready, set, go!
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Come on, come on. >> Aagh!
Candy! You okay?
Ugh. >> Is that...
[ Laughs ] Oh, it stinks.
Here, let me help you up.
>> Get off me, okay?
I don't need your help.
>> Okay, Mary Jo.
I'm not that woman.
>> You sure about that?
Wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, get off me! Get off me!
I'm sorry. >> Get off me!
I hate you.
>> Calm down, calm down.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said
that. >> [ Sobbing ]
Why did you say that about that
woman?
I'm sorry. >> [ Sobbing ]
Let it out.
I'm sorry, I'm...
I'm sorry I hit you.
That's okay. I'm a big boy.
I can take it.
I think she's back.
[ Sniffles ]
Louis, let's just go back.
Okay, I don't want to stand out
here all day begging her to open
the door.
And, plus, I stink really badly.
>> Yeah, you do.
That just might work to your
advantage.
Hold on one second.
>> Where are you going?
Come on, I just want to
get in the car.
Aagh! Come on, Louis, stop it!
Oh, quit whining.
>> What y'all doing?!
This is private property!
>> I'm sorry, ma'am.
Candy fell in some poop,
and, well, she stinks
really bad.
Mmm. This is good.
What is it? >> Rabbit stew.
Mmm, I like it. What's wrong?
I don't eat bunnies.
>> [ Chuckles ]
Well, you do now.
Here, I'll take it. What?
I'm hungry.
Thanks for dinner, Mary Jo.
Welcome.
>> Hey, listen, I need to make a
few calls.
I think I'm gonna wait
in the car.
I... I like your cookie jars.
Um...
I saw the greenhouse in the
back.
So what kind of vegetables do
you grow? Okay.
I'll just... Help you clean up.
I got it. I can take it.
No, no, I can...
>> would you please just let me.
Please! [ Dish shatters ]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for it to break.
Ow! Shoot!
Now look what you done
made me do.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's... this has to go in
the water. Put it in the water.
Okay, just...
Why did you come back,
after the funeral, I mean,
after everything?
I came back for me.
This is for me.
I mean, I have to get some
peroxide and put it on there.
It's pretty deep.
Here, put the pressure
like that. Here you go.
Okay, I know it hurts.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
How'd it go?
>> Can you drop me off here
tomorrow, alone? >> Sure.
Good.
[ Starts engine ]
Hello? Oh.
Hey, granite. [ Whistles ]
You remember me? Mary Jo?!
Mary Jo?
Seriously, you're gonna pull
this stunt again? Mary Jo!
I hadn't finished dressing yet!
Come help me with these crates
out back.
[ Slams door ]
>> Good morning to you, too.
You can start with them. >> Wow.
This is amazing.
You do all this yourself?
Uh-huh. 24 years.
Well, let's get loading.
I don't want to be late
on my runs.
So what is all this?
>> I sell fruits and vegetables
wholesale to the smaller
grocers, the little ones.
Jam, preserves, pickle peppers,
too.
Oh, so you're an entrepreneur.
Well, if that mean I own my
own business, yes, ma'am.
Well, let's get moving!
Come on, now!
Time is money!
[ Thunder rumbles ]
Lift from your knees,
not your back.
You want me to call triple-a
or something?
Triple-who? Nah.
Be fine.
Just the coolant leaking again.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
>> You know, I can drive if that
cut on your hand is hurting.
>> Oh, lord, I've lived through
more than this little scratch.
I'll be fine.
Well, you cut yourself pretty
deep.
You might want to have a doctor
look at it.
Nope. Had my fill of doctors.
You ain't never seen a woman
check her oil before?
Watch and learn. Yeah.
You see, this right here,
that's for your steering fluid.
Check it, you know, every six
months or so.
But your oil, you check that
every three weeks, and you keep
it full, 'cause it...
>> why'd you give me away?
You just gonna ask me out of
nowhere like that?
Yeah. Mary Jo, I need to know.
It wasn't meant for me to keep.
Wasn't meant for you to keep?!
I was your...
Child, your flesh and blood!
Okay, so explain to me what were
the mitigating circumstances
that warranted you surrendering
custody of me?
Oh, this your fancy way of
asking me if I gave you up for
no good reason?
>> Yeah, did you?
I don't want to talk about it.
Well, you know what?
That's just too bad, because
we're stuck out here in the
middle of nowhere, stuck in a
truck together.
So you're just gonna have to get
over it.
>> Your manners is terrible!
Said the pot to the kettle.
>> That's what's wrong with your
generation... disrespectful.
In my day, children was to be
seen, and not heard.
>> Well, you might want to take
a good look, Mary Jo, because
I'm not a child anymore.
You...
You don't know I been through.
You just a spoiled little rich
girl! >> Really?
And you are a nasty old broad.
>> You don't talk to me like
that, 'cause I'm your...
>> you're my what?!
My mother?
You're nothing but a stranger,
who happens to share my DNA.
Well...
I don't ride with no strangers!
Oh, okay. So, what?
You're just gonna leave me out
here in the middle of nowhere?
You know what, Mary Jo?
This getting-rid-of-me business
is getting kind of old! Bye!
[ Sobbing ] [ Starts engine ]
Bye!
Louis? Yeah, she left me here
in the middle of nowhere. Yeah.
You know what, I'm done!
I want to go home.
Hey.
You faced your fears, and you
came out here. I'm proud of you.
[ Ringtone chiming ]
Hey, abner. What?
No, she doesn't know.
Mary Jo had a stroke.
Where's her hospital?
Okay, we're on the way.
>> Woman, over p.A.:
Dr. florez, dial 118, please.
Dr. florez, please dial 118.
[ Curtain rod scraping ] >> Hmm.
[ Monitor beeping ]
I like what you've done
with the place.
It's the entrepreneur suite.
>> Mary Jo.
Beside, you're family,
this time.
Abner.
He knows people who work at the
hospital, so...
>> Well, that figures.
One busybody upper manager
is nosy.
Yeah, well...
We should probably be thankful
for him, because if it weren't
for him...
I wouldn't be here.
>> Well, why did you come?
You don't like me. >> True.
But that doesn't change
who you are.
Family. >> So now we kin again?
Yeah, but don't push it.
>> Yeah, we family all right.
You asked me a question,
and I think you deserve an
answer.
You was born in this hospital.
When they brought you to me,
girl...
You were something.
And you was beautiful.
And you was mine.
I was a 16-year-old dumb girl.
My big mama was dead.
And they brought me these papers
to sign, I thought it was so the
state could help me
take care of you...
welfare aid.
>> But it was the papers
that released custody of me.
I couldn't read the words right.
Freddie couldn't help.
Why? Why?
[ Curtain rod scrapes ]
>> Excuse me, miss meyers,
but visiting hours are over.
And miss Jordan here really
needs to get her rest.
>> Well, we just need five more
minutes. >> I'm sorry.
Doctor's orders.
>> Okay, well, I'm gonna stay in
town a few more days.
I'll see you when you get out.
Can I see your arm, miss Jordan?
Miss Jordan? Your arm?
I'm sorry.
[ Cell phone rings ]
[ Rings ]
Hey, mom. What's up?
What's up?
That's all you have to say to me
after two weeks?
Where are you, Candace?
I'm still in Manning. >> Why?
I mean, you all talked it out,
didn't you?
Why are you still there?
>> I don't know.
>> What do you mean
you don't know?
Your life is here in Atlanta
with your family.
Mary Jo's family, too, and...
She needs me.
Mom? >> Yes?
I love you.
And nothing is gonna change
that.
I just... I need to stay here a
little bit longer, and then I'll
come home, okay?
Okay.
>> All right, well, tell daddy
I love him, too.
And I'll talk to you both soon.
Bye.
What is that? >> Palak paneer.
Palak? >> It's Indian food.
I don't eat no Indian food! Mmm!
Well, you do now. >> [ Laughs ]
Oh!
Your daddy didn't like no funny
food, neither.
He was a strong meat and
potatoes man. Whoo.
You know, Mary Jo, why does
everybody keep talking about
Freddie like he's some sort of
hero?
He was a married man who cheated
on his wife...
no! >> Who seduced a young,
uneducated girl, and then he
left her when she was pregnant.
No, no, it wasn't nothing
like that.
All that stuff happened later
on.
I met Freddie when I was
14 years old and he was 16.
When I laid eyes on him,
I loved him.
And somehow I always knew that
that man was gonna be my
husband, and he knew, too.
Candace, it was Freddie who
wanted to wait until we
was old enough to get married.
But when the waiting got hard,
I started pushing him away.
And, well, that delores Jameson,
that little fast heifer,
she always had the hots
for my Freddie.
So she invited him to a party,
and since I'd been fighting him
so hard, he went along. And...
She got him pissy drunk
and seduced him.
And four months later,
they had a shotgun wedding
'cause they found out
she was pregnant.
And her daddy, Deacon Jameson,
wasn't having no bastards
in his family.
>> Okay, so then what?
So now he's married, and he
starts double dipping,
coming to see you and then...
>> no, no, he was not that kind
of man. No!
We stayed away from each other.
He came to the house 'cause the
found out that big mama was
dying.
And he knew I didn't have
nobody.
And so that's when... Oh!
Oh, it was the most beautiful
night of my life.
I finally had my Freddie.
And then when we found out we
was having you, we was so happy.
And we was gonna run away
together.
We had a plan and everything.
>> So what happened?
I mean, why didn't you guys just
leave?
We was gonna do it.
He drove up to the house with
all his stuff, and I hopped in,
ready to go.
And he just couldn't do it.
We sat in that car
for three hours, crying.
That man broke my heart
that day.
But that's what I'm trying to
tell you.
Your daddy was an honorable man.
Being the God-fearing man that
he was, he was ashamed that he
cheated on delores, and he
decided that he wanted to be
right by her and stay.
We knew we could never be
together, but we never stopped
loving each other.
See?
He gave me this...
And he put the same thing
on the back of his watch.
What does it mean?
"With every beat of my heart."
You were borne out of love.
So much love.
See, if you grab it just right,
you get that string right off.
Oh. Okay.
Can't I just snap 'em? >> Try.
Okay, I'll try. Hey, Mary Jo?
Hmm?
>> Did you always have trouble
reading? Like...
Where the letters get
confused sometimes?
No.
They get confused all the time.
You know, I think you have
dyslexia.
Now, what is that?
Make it plain now.
You know I don't speak no Greek.
>> No, it's just... okay, some
people, when they read,
they get confused.
No matter how many words they
know, the letters seem like
they're in the wrong place.
>> Exactly so.
That's exactly so. >> Mary Jo,
you're not dumb.
You're just undiagnosed.
Well, how you know
so much about it?
'Cause I have it, too.
And I found out it's hereditary.
From... Oh!
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
All right, it's my turn.
Where your friend?
Who? Louis?
Mm-hmm.
>> He went home last week.
Did you see him off?
>> Now, why would I do that?
He flies all the time. >> Mmm.
You love him?
What kind of question is that?
The kind of question you
ain't answered yet.
Do you love him? >> No.
Maybe. I don't know.
No. No, I don't.
Listen...
True love comes only once in a
lifetime, and I don't want to
see you lose your season.
[ Granite barking ]
[ No audio ]
[ Buzzing ]
Hey, candy.
It's... it's me again.
I'm just...
Just checking on you.
Yeah. Um...
Give me a call when you get a
chance.
Hope everything's all right.
All right, bye.
[ Chimes ]
From your knees, not your back.
>> Oh, my gosh!
Can you please stop nagging me,
Mary Jo.
You sound like my mother.
Now, I know for sure
it's time for you to go.
So, what?
You're sick of me already?
No. [ Spray bottle hissing ]
But it is time for you to start
living your own life.
And it ain't here selling
peach jam with me.
[ Chuckles ]
>> I like it here with you.
And I like that you like it.
You gotta stop hiding, Candace.
>> I'm not hiding!
I'm resting.
>> Yes, you're hiding,
just like I did when big mama.
It's just when I'm home,
you know, it's like everybody
wants something from me,
you know?
For the morning show and my
publisher and...
My business partners and...
I just... I just want to be
happy, okay?
I just want to be left alone.
Look at me.
You see what happens when
you're left alone?
You just become a cuckoo old
woman. Only friend in the world
is a dog.
Well, at least he's a cute dog.
Go home.
It's time.
[ Sighs ] Louis.
[ Sighs ]
Hey. I don't know where you are,
but it's me again.
Can you please call me when
you get this? Bye.
You're not gonna say hello?
>> Not when you're
five hours late. Where were you?
Out.
Out? Out doing what?
Why? >> So you were too busy to
return my phone call?
I was worried about you, Louis.
You didn't return any of my
calls when you were in Manning.
I was bonding
with my birth mother.
So, what, you just forgot
about me?
No, okay.
No, I didn't forget about you,
all right? That's not fair.
I called you, I saw the
pictures, and I called you over
to eat so we could, to...
>> to what, candy?
Huh, to what?
Never mind. Forget it.
Exactly.
Fine, I'll... I'll just go home.
Bye. Bye.
You know what, candy,
you are so stubborn,
and you're never gonna change.
That's why I quit.
I don't want to be your manager
anymore.
Fine, I don't want you to be...
well, everyone, this is the end
of my first week back to work,
and I just want to thank all
of you for your cards, your
letters, your e-mails, your
tweets to me and my family.
I really appreciate it.
And I also want to extend my
sincerest gratitude to the best
co-anchor in the world...
Mr. Jay grant.
You have worked with me for over
eight years, and you have never
said one negative word about me,
and I really appreciate that.
I love you, Jay.
Well, I love you, too, candy.
You know, I actually love your
book, too. >> Oh.
No, no, real talk.
George, is this it right here?
Good. "Having my chocolate cake"
and eating it, too,"
this was an incredible read.
I mean, it really, really was.
>> Oh.
Well done, candy.
>> Thank you, darling.
Well, everyone, that's our show
for today.
Now, you will be back next
week, right?
Oh, yeah, you're not getting
rid of me, Jay.
Oh, I hope not, 'cause
I can't work by myself.
I need my ace boon.
I need my ride or die chick.
You know what I'm saying?
I need my Michelle Obama.
I need my dwyane wade.
I need my Beyonce, all right?
Are you ready, b? >> Surfboard.
Right.
>> Okay, all right, listen,
Jay, say goodbye to the nice
people of America.
Goodbye to the nice people
of America.
See you later. >> Take care.
See you next week.
>> That was nice.
Director: And we're clear.
Great show, everybody.
Great week. That's a wrap.
That's a wrap. >> Thank you.
You're welcome.
[ Music playing ]
Woman: Who gives this woman
away to marry this man?
Me. And...
Her mothers.
>> And her beloved Uncle
on behalf of her deceased
father.
[ Chuckles ] [ Music continues ]
♪ [ Music continues ]