So you've decided
to make your own luck.
I can understand that.
I made Heineken
into a world class brand.
Me. On my own.
It's worth billions now.
I did that.
And not by sitting
on my ass either
waiting for the stupid
money fairy
to hit me on my stupid
damned head.
You know
that what you're doing
is completely stupid.
Unless, of course,
you pull it off,
in which case it can be
completely brilliant.
Yeah. I suppose
if I were in your shoes,
I would do
exactly the same.
Ah, there he is.
What are you doing?
Huh?
What are
you doing?
You can't bring
a kid to this.
He can wait
outside with Brakes.
This is fucked up.
Listen, it's
not fucked.
It's fine.
Cat, can you put
the kid down, please?
Just give him
to my little brother.
Right. Now,
is everyone ready?
Yes.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yeah!
Alright, let's do this.
Well, it's a pleasure
to finally meet you,
Mr. Iverson.
My name is Cor Van Hout.
This is Mr. Holleeder,
Mr. Boellard, and Mr. Meijer.
We're here today
in the hope
of asking you
for a loan.
- A loan?
- Yeah.
It's a business loan.
And what particular
sort of...?
Construction.
Yeah, we
were doing well.
Yeah, really well.
You've been running
a company employing
a hundred men?
Yeah, well, we were
all equal partners,
yeah, right down
the middle there.
Um, Mr. Boellard here
is a master carpenter.
Mr. Meijer has a...
If these numbers
are real,
you're in
fine shape.
Surely, if
you've been making
this kind of money,
you must
have investments
that you could stake
as collateral?
Uh, well, we had, uh,
you know, cars,
and we had boats
and we had
some race horses but...
Equities, bonds,
pension funds?
When the recession hit,
we cashed in.
The cars,
the boats,
the horses?
It's for paychecks, uh,
for guys living
from one Friday
to the next.
I think
you can understand
that their kids
can't live or eat off IOUs.
I think, maybe,
what you haven't heard,
Mr. Big Manager,
is that, uh,
there's a world
of hurt out there
right now...
Oh, believe me,
I know.
Well, we still got
a building.
Great.
What's the address?
Uh, it's Leidsegracht.
Six six three.
Hold on.
Leidsegracht?
The commune?
Commune?
It's a bunch of punks
that don't pay their rent.
It's hardly
a fucking commune.
Yes.
Squatters.
We're in the process
of evictions.
Government says
once they change
the locks,
they've got rights.
So that means lawyers.
I do see your problem.
But you're
welcome back
when you solve it.
Guys like him
don't lend money
to guys like us.
We'll get the punks
out of the building.
Yeah.
How are you
going to do that?
Yeah. I got
an idea.
Alright, listen.
You're going
to love this.
It's time to go, boys!
Hey, what's going on?
Time to go!
Open up!
Cat, get in through a window,
not the front door!
Open up!
Come on down!
You don't scare me!
You fucking stink!
Whoa!
I'll come back
for you.
Get the fuck out!
Coming!
Fucking coming!
- Oh, shit!
- Get out of here!
Shit.
Oh, shit!
Oh!
Get the fuck
out of here.
Oh, shit.
You going
to go?
Go and get
the fuck out of here!
- Get the fuck out!
- Go on!
Now you're in trouble!
Go! Go!
Everyone out!
Go, go, go!
Hey, this is
our building!
We own this place!
Fuckface!
Police! Police!
Everybody go!
You want
to do this?
No.
No, I think
I'll pass.
Pussy.
Hey!
Whoaaa!
Charge!
Get your fucking hands
off of me now.
I hope... well, fuck it.
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Fine. Thank you.
Bye.
What'd he say?
Well, he said
if we lived in Texas,
they'd throw us a parade.
But here,
well you know
how that is.
Yeah.
Anyway, good news.
Squatters aren't going
to press charges.
How kind
is that?
Whooptiedoo.
- Happy days.
- Cornelius Van Hout.
Yo.
Thank you.
- Only Van Hout.
- Huh?
Hey.
Bad news. You guys
resisted arrest.
Plus, not only do they
get to stay in the building,
we got to pay
for the shit we busted.
Yeah, including
the fish!
Fuck the fish.
Sonja?
Hey.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no.
Listen. I can explain.
I... Sonja,
please, will... Son...!
Sonja, what
are you doing?
You alright?
What's going on, Son?
What are you doing?
What are you doing
hiding in my kitchen?
Hey, who are you?
Who are you, huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know who you are.
I just worked it out.
Yeah, that's right.
You know what?
You are way
too good-looking
to be Karin's boy. Hm?
Oh, hey, Karin, hey.
Hey, how you doing?
I was just joking...
If you had any idea
what's been going
on with Sonja,
then you wouldn't do
as you do.
What do you mean
"going on"?
Sonja, please, wh...
what's going on?
I'm pregnant.
Ah. Ah.
What?
Ha.
Wow.
That's, uh...
Really?
That's unbelievable.
You're fucking pregnant?
Yeah.
I'll leave you two
to it then.
Bye!
See you, Karin!
Hey, come on, you!
Happy New Year!
Hey!
Hey, Ma!
Look at your hair
and your dress,
you look
like a model.
Thanks.
Hey, be careful!
Yeah, your sister's
knocked up.
Yeah, I know
It's great.
He doesn't greet
his old man...
or even have
a beer with him.
You know
I don't drink.
Especially Heineken.
Look at me
when you talk to me.
Heineken beer
and Heineken money
paid for this house
and for your upbringing.
You see that?
The man
is my friend.
But he fired you
and I don't think
he remembers your name.
You owe him respect.
- Okay, let's go.
-  Oh!
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bye, honey.
Happy New Year.
Bye, Mom.
Bye.
Take care of her.
Thank you.
Alright. Thank you.
Invite him round
next time, Pa.
We'll all
kiss his ring.
Well, that was festive.
Oh, come on.
Let's have some fun.
Let's go to Karin's.
Aw, come on, Sonja.
You know
what we got to do.
Hey? Come on.
I'll look
after him.
Come on.
It's tradition, alright?
Yeah, go.
You don't mind?
No!
No?
Alright,
I love you.
Love you, too.
Go!
Have fun!
Here's to making
this year count.
Alright, to getting
our old lives back.
Yeah, some fucking
New Year.
We've no money,
the company's bankrupt,
and no one's going
to give us a loan.
So how are we going
to get our old lives
back? Huh?
We could get jobs.
Yeah, that's the
alcohol talking.
Ha.
I'm not getting
a real job.
No, I'm not going
to bust my ass
every single day
to go
absolutely nowhere.
I think this year
I refuse to be miserable.
Actually, that's, uh...
that's why I want
to talk to you guys
about some business.
Cor, we just got out of jail.
I'm not talking
about that kind
of business.
I'm talking about
smart business.
So what type
of business
you planning?
I'm planning
something organized,
something big.
How big?
Big enough that we
never have to grovel
to another
asshole banker again.
Yeah, right, man.
We betting?
Or we talking
about a crime?
That's all crime is.
It's a wager.
Right?
Think about it.
You bet your liberty
against the payoff.
All I have to bet,
all I have left...
is my liberty.
And that's all
you guys have.
That's all you've
got left to bet.
So if you're going
to bet that,
I guess you're going
to have to bet it big.
How big?
Sixty million.
Shit.
Sixty?
Who are you
going to kidnap?
Kidnap?
Come on, man.
Shit.
Man, I thought
you were serious.
Idiot.
You're an idiot.
He's serious.
I'm serious.
He's been talking
about this since we
were fucking kids!
Grabbing anybody
is easy.
Collecting the ransom
and getting away with it
is impossible.
It's not.
It's not impossible.
Who do you
want to kidnap?
Got to be a local.
It's got
to be a guy.
I'm not messing
with women
or children, eh.
He's got to be
stinking fucking rich.
You're out
of your fucking mind.
It's like I said...
let's make
this year
count, huh?
Woo!
Happy fucking
New Year!
Hi, there.
Guys, look
what I've got. Huh?
Cat, this is
specially for you.
Oh.
Wow.
What is this?
Who do I
look like?
What do you think?
I don't know
if I love these
or hate these.
They're scary, eh?
I look like Willem.
No, you look
like a fucking pervert.
Where's Willem anyway?
I'm not wearing a wig.
We got to find
a place so we
can hide him
where no one's
going to look.
My workshed
would be perfect
but there's an office
full of bean counters
next door.
Guys, we can't just
dump him in the shed.
No. But we could
build a room
inside the shed.
That's good.
It's perfect.
I found
a boat we can steal.
It's fucking fast.
Was a boat
on the list?
No.
So why are we
talking about a boat?
I'm trying to think
outside the box.
Come on.
Yeah, well, don't.
Whoa.
Guns are on that list.
Right?
Okay.
Yes.
Now be careful
with that, please.
World War II?
Safety's a little
edgy on that!
Fuck, Spikes!
Man...
Shhh.
What?
Hear that?
Shit.
We're good?
Yeah.
Here I go.
What the fuck?
- It's okay.
- What was that?
Yeah, it was just
fucking Rambo
over here.
Listen, man.
Where have you been?
I've been thinking
about how we
grab Heiny.
We've been trying
to come up with
some ideas, too.
What you got?
If we're
going to do this,
we have to make sure
that the cops look
in the wrong direction.
That they have to believe
that whoever took Heiny
he's, like, some
big swinging dick,
like... Baader Meinhof?
Or Red Brigades?
Mafia?
And those fuckers
they don't mess
around. Yeah?
For a job like this,
they would have
military grade
weapons, radios.
They would have
a safehouse
to hold him.
They would have months
of preparation, months
of observation.
They would spend
at least a hundred grand.
Same old story, man?
Want to get rich?
You got to be
rich already.
Yeah.
If you want to do this
on a shoestring, fine.
But the cops are going
to look for a bunch
of local jerkoffs
and they're going
to nail us fucking flat.
Oh, fuck it.
Let's pay another visit
to the bank.
shoot
at the ground.
We know.
Okay, guys.
Let's go.
Now!
On the ground! Now!
Go, go, go!
Come on!
Go! Go!
Put your gun down!
Sorry!
Look out!
He's gone
to the next canal!
That's it!
Cat! Get ready
to cut the rope!
Go, go!
I'll cover you!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Shoot at the ground!
Get down!
Shit!
Get out of the way!
Look out!
Hoo!
Woo-hoo!
You sure it's clear?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Cor.
Wow.
Now who's big
swinging dicks?
Alright, it's time
to get down to business.
How was your day?
Yeah, it was fine.
It was good.
Somebody robbed
a bank.
Yeah, I know.
I heard that.
With machine guns,
like, Al Capone.
Wowww.
They shot
hundreds of bullets.
Hardly.
I don't think so.
It was all
over the radio.
And the TV.
Where have you been?
With Cat.
I was helping him
with his boat.
Where?
What do you
mean "where"?
At the, um, marina.
Up in Newlake.
Does he ever pay
you for stuff
like that?
Yeah. Yeah,
he does.
Mm.
Okay, okay.
Nice.
Amazing thing
about that robbery.
Mmm.
All that gunfire.
They didn't hit anyone.
Yeah?
Yeah, really.
Yeah, that's good.
Mm.
Thank you.
I've been waiting
for you, Obi-Wan.
That's good, right?
I'm going
to take that.
How much
do I owe you?
Hmm.
I'm going
to need a couple.
May I ask
you something?
You're not from
around here.
No, I'm just, uh,
passing through.
Here's my private
telephone number.
I can show
you around.
I weighed it.
Thirty five million
is all we can carry.
Maybe the wood blocks
that were heavier
than the money.
It'll all have to be
small denominations.
Yeah, and
different currencies.
I've carried
twice as much.
Oh, aren't you one?
I already picked
out my Ferrari.
A Ferrari?
Yeah!
You couldn't handle
a Ferrari.
You can
barely handle
a scooter.
Fuck you, man.
You want a Ferrari
because you got
a small dick.
Fuck you, man.
Ahhh!
I didn't hear anything.
Yeah, well.
I'm surprised.
Well.
Yeah.
We have to test
these as well.
Cat?
Oh.
Cat?!
Where is everything?
What happened
to the cells?
What's going on?
What...?
Where is everything?
I want you to think
of the Anne Frank house.
Oh, yeah.
Anne Frank!
Fucking brilliant.
You're a genius.
Come again.
You're a fucking genius.
Where's the door?
Ask and you
shall receive.
We did do
a door, right?
Ah, good job.
"Respond to our
ransom demand
"by the deadline
"by running
the code word 'Notice'
"in the newspaper
or you'll never see
Heineken or Doderer
ever again."
Okay.
Take it.
Can you fucking
stop that?
Okay, it's time.
Shit.
No, it's nothing.
You don't
know that.
Look, it's nothing.
It's just
a coincidence.
There's always an excuse
if you're looking for it.
If we're
going to do this,
we do it now.
Here we go.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.
Now remember,
if we need to speak,
then we only speak
in German.
Lovely evening.
We'll be in touch.
Alright.
Huh? Hands off.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Let me go!
Dumb shit!
Get into the fucking van!
What?
Alright, alright, alright.
Ahhh!
Ahhh.
Okay.
Ohhh!
Alright, okay, okay, okay.
Alright, let me have
all their clothes.
Come on.
That's nice.
I'll get the barrel.
Hey, can we talk now?
I told you to speak
in German!
Your man
didn't fight
like mine.
Shhh.
Enough!
Alright, listen.
Did anybody
leave their fingerprints
on this ransom note?
Huh? I'll ask again.
Did anybody touch this
with their bare hands?
I may have.
Oh, fuck.
Alright. Is there
anybody next door?
They should have
left by now.
Come with me.
Come on.
Let's start.
Willem, where do I start?
Here.
The copier is there.
Let's go,
let's go.
It's okay.
We got a new one.
You got his watch?
Alright.
Now remember,
once you're done
with that,
you make out
like it's any
other night.
Mm-hm.
We'll be
at the bar.
I'll be there.
It's our alibi.
Hey, kid.
You good?
Yeah?
You sure?
Alright, good.
Just don't think
about it
being a police
station, alright?
Ever think you'd deliver
an invoice for 35 million?
Are they really
going to pay
all that?
They have to.
Can't we just mail it?
Come on.
Take a breath.
- Breathe.
- Go.
It's not exactly
my favorite
neighborhood either.
Package is
delivered, boys.
You good?
We're heading home.
Cat, Cat, Cat.
Stay for one minute.
Come on,
stay for one.
Yeah, one drink,
one drink.
You alright?
Do it.
Ring the bell!
Ring it!
You guys do it up
right last night?
Well, you know me.
We made sure
we were seen
and we kept
it respectable.
Good.
You?
Oh, it was riveting.
I fell asleep
watching cartoons
with the kids.
Yeah.
Well?
How are they?
Heineken's fine.
Pissed off.
The driver
is not too good.
Now you
listen to me.
You are in
no danger here.
Anhh.
As long
as the money is paid,
you will be released.
Anhh.
Do you understand?
Hey, guys.
Check it out.
Do you have
a name?
No name.
Is it ransom
or money?
Are you the boss?
Okay, you're the boss.
So, I have
a few requests.
I'd like
a bathrobe, slippers,
a shaving kit,
comb, mirror,
um, reading glasses,
a decent
fucking chair...
and, um, what else?
Oh, yes, and if it's
not too much trouble,
a telephone.
You have
no name, huh?
You're part
of an organization?
You're Baader Meinhof?
Red Brigade?
IRA?
Symbionese Army?
- Hey, Cor.
- What?
Look at this.
What?
Oh, fuck.
You're going
to love it.
Oh, nice.
Mm-hm.
Nice, nice.
Says five guys involved.
How many have you?
This one says three.
Yeah, listen to this.
"An unknown number
of most certainly dangerous
and experienced criminals."
Let me see,
let me see.
It's perfect.
More about this
morning's top story...
Alfred Heineken,
the billionaire
of brewing,
was kidnapped by a group
of heavily armed
men yesterday...
I know
who did it.
...corporate in Amsterdam,
Police have
now confirmed
that they...
Who?
Bud.
Weiser.
Bud Weiser.
Yeah?
One way to beat
the competition, huh?
Funny guy, huh?
Police would not disclose
the size of the ransom
demanded
but it is assumed
to be significant.
What?
The ransom note.
What do you mean?
Did we leave it?
In the copier?
No, no.
...chased, until
he was threatened
by the kidnappers
with a machine gun.
Wait, did we...?
No, did we?
Oh, fuck.
Hey, uh...
George.
George, yeah.
Remember me?
Yeah.
How's it going?
Same old, same old.
So everything's alright?
I guess.
Do you mind
if we make
a quick copy?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Thank you
for that, too.
I assume you, uh,
sent a note about
the ransom.
Did they reply?
Well, they will.
In the meantime,
this music,
it's beautiful and laden
with tragic disillusion
but, uh, the same tape
over and over again,
all day long,
please, I know
I am your prisoner
but there's no need
to torture me,
my friend.
Some Johann Sebastian Bach
would be quite soothing.
Or, well...
Franz Fucking
Schubert, anything.
Silence, preferably.
Also, some books
would pass the time
and as much as I
adore ham sandwiches,
my friend,
Chinese food is
quite easy to get,
and it's cheap too,
and, uh, I know,
something like, um,
yeah, Bang Bang chicken.
With some
extra chili sauce,
how about that? Okay?
- Happy birthday.
- Cheers.
You'll be looking for
a regular paycheck now, hey.
Ah, finally.
I can serve
the cake now.
Hi, honey.
No more
fooling around, huh?
- My son Mark, he drives a tram.
-  Yeah, I know Mark.
Yeah, he's got
good hours.
Most importantly,
he's got a good pension.
Uh-huh.
You'd have to take
the training first.
Really? They train?
I could have
a word with him...
Yeah, could you?
Always the same stupid joke.
From my daughter
as well, now?
Wonderful.
What a kind and
thoughtful gift,
thank you.
Pa, it was a joke.
Cannot you at least
wait till they let
Mr. Heineken go, huh?
If they ever do
let him go.
Don't start
on this again.
If I get
those filthy bastards,
I will kill them.
We know.
Kill them!
Willem, please,
it's Pa's birthday.
Come on.
Cat?
How long do you reckon it'll
take Heineken's people
to pay the ransom?
Cat. How long
do you reckon it'll...?
No more questions.
Because I
don't have
the answers.
Aw, thanks.
Hey, and thanks
for the new music.
It's very whimsical,
very droll. Yeah.
Got books!
Good.
Alright.
Any luck
with the Bang Bang?
Huh?
No?
Some guys like
Bang Bang chili all the time.
But you like
sweet sour.
Ever since five years.
Sweet sour pork,
sweet sour prawn,
sweet sour beef.
You're a sweet sour guy.
So it's
Chinese, right?
Now me
is a chili guy.
Okay, okay.
You a goddamn
Bang Bang man.
Right.
See you tomorrow.
What can I
get for you?
Ah!
Wake up.
Fuck you, man.
Did they run
the notice?
Not yet.
Come on, man,
this was only supposed
to take five days.
What if he is sick?
We gotta kidnap
a fucking doctor?
Is he sick?
No.
Don't get
too personal.
Or he'll get
inside your head.
Look, leather jacket,
Popeye.
Cops?
Willem, even if
they are cops,
it doesn't mean anything.
You okay?
Fuck, I'm just
done waiting.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Alright?
Me, too.
What are you
trying to do?
Huh?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
If you tell
the Police where I am,
I could give you
half the ransom
and, uh,
a house
in Switzerland.
Lots of beautiful
Swiss girls,
blond, they're beautiful.
I'll...
I'll arrange it
as many as you like.
No?
You're not interested?
Are you gay
or something? Huh?
Any news
from the Police?
Oh.
It's been over
two weeks now.
The longer
they don't pay the money,
the more time they have
to figure out who did it.
You want to give up?
I do.
You what?
I do, yeah.
Let's let him go.
Knock down the cells,
burn everything.
Okay, we don't get
the money,
but you know
what we do get?
Our lives back.
Oh, come on.
Come on, look,
they're just
messing with us.
That's all that is.
Cat, where you going?
Uh... Really?
Cat...
Wait!
We failed!
It's my fucking shed.
I want him out of there.
Before it's too late.
Look, just listen!
Just listen.
Listen, listen, alright?
Look, it's all
just part of the game.
We're still
in control here.
You really want
to walk out...
on 35 million?
Huh?
What we got to do
is make the transaction.
Thirty-five million.
Someone has got
to relieve Brakes.
Alright.
I'm going home.
They didn't pay.
You've got to be
kidding me.
What do you mean
they didn't pay?
Last night
was the deadline.
We told them
that we would kill you
if they didn't pay.
And they didn't
fucking pay!
So time's up!
Okay.
There must be
some confusion.
It's confusion,
that's it.
Damn, I'm their boss!
Nobody else.
Must be out
of their fucking minds.
I'll fire them all!
Give me a pen
and paper.
and paper now!
And you're all fired!
You as well.
Don't worry,
you'll get
your blood money.
You know you will.
You have my word
of honor.
Okay? Okay?!
You fucking morons!
Yeah.
What's his problem?
What?
Now you
listen to me.
Can we also have your...
Ooh.
Can we also have
your word of honor
right now, in writing,
that when you're free,
you won't help the police
in any way?
My word of honor?
Yeah.
Yeah. That's the way
the game is played.
You've got
my word.
It's time to end
it now, okay?
Hello?
W... why is the door open?
Ab, is that you?
Boss?
Yeah.
Boss, are
you alright?
Yeah, I'm sort
of okay.
Tired of this crap.
Oh, God.
Um...
Are you okay?
Have they left you alone
or given you a rough time?
I don't know,
I... I... I...
How long have we
been in here now?
A month?
I don't know,
I've lost track.
I'm a little confused,
it feels longer.
Now, now,
I'll tell you now.
It comes to...
oh, almost
three weeks.
Yeah.
Why the hell
are you here?
You've got no money
to offer these jokers.
Well, if...
if your people
don't pay,
then, uh, then these
guys need to prove
that they're not
fooling around and...
well, it can't be
your head...
they'll send
to the police
in a box.
Don't worry, Ab.
We'll...
pay whatever
it takes.
If it's
a hundred million,
we'll pay.
I want to get out of this
as much as you guys.
But we have to let
them sweat it out
another week.
Let them believe
that their screw-up
killed Heineken.
You remind me again
why we grabbed
the driver.
Why?
What's your point?
A question
the police
are asking.
Is, uh... are these guys
the real deal?
Or are they just
a bunch of pussies?
And if the answer is
they're a bunch
of pussies,
they're going to string
this out forever.
So what are you
trying to say?
Well, we said
if they don't pay,
then there'll be blood.
You wrote that
in the letter.
This is business.
It's nothing personal.
And they didn't
fucking pay.
- I agree.
- Oh, really?
Yeah.
Yeah?
You agree?
Yeah.
With him?
Alright, good.
Big man,
alright then,
slice his fucking throat.
I'll do it.
Willem...
Hey. Hey. Hey.
You're acting
like a scared
little boy.
Hey, you
fucking do it!
A scared little boy.
Fuck!
I didn't sign up for this!
Cor, if he
does anything...
anything!
If he does
anything in there,
it's fucking
on you.
Do something!
Fuck.
Man!
Use your head!
Oh, fuck.
You alright?
Stop what you're doing.
What are you doing?
What are
you doing?
What are you doing?
Come here.
Come on.
Is he alright?
Yeah, no,
he's okay.
He's fine.
We all just need
to go home,
take a breather,
get drunk, get laid,
whatever you got to do.
But we
just got to stick
to the routine
and we'll see each other
in a few days.
Alright.
Let's go.
...in a case that has riveted
the nation and much of Europe,
the kidnapping
of billionaire
Alfred Heineken
has entered
its 19th day.
With no substantial leads
and no end in sight,
a massive manhunt involving
local and federal law
enforcement continues.
Oh, hey.
Where've you been?
You were supposed
to be at birth class.
What?
No, S...
Fuck.
No, no, no.
Sonja!
Listen, I'm sorry.
Listen, I'll make
it up to you!
Alright?
I'll make it up to you.
Sonja...
Have they paid?
Am I to be set free?
Did you give them
my message?
You know,
they have
one more chance.
If they screw it
up this time...
And they know
I've given you
my word
so they will pay, so...
how are you planning
to set us free?
I will put
the both of you in a car
and, uh,
leave it somewhere.
Call your people.
Oh, good.
Listen, if your people
don't pay soon,
then I can't answer
for my people.
I'll tell you what.
If you put us
in that car
right now, I'll, uh...
see to it that you get
what you want and...
I'll make sure
you're free to spend it.
That's a promise
and I have the power
to do that.
You know?
Of course.
You're a young man
and I must confess,
I do envy you.
There's no way
you could have
done this without...
no way you could have
done it without those
men in your life
that you trust
with your life.
Friends.
So congratulations,
well done, and uh...
soon you'll get
your money
and then you will be...
very, very rich.
But, um...
But what?
No, what I meant
to say, my friend,
is that, uh...
there are two ways
a man can be rich
in this world.
He can have
a lot of money
or he can have
a lot of friends.
But he cannot have both.
Cor?
Yeah?
Rub my back?
Please?
Yeah, yeah,
I will later.
Yes.
Listen, I...
I gotta go.
They put the notice we
requested in the newspaper.
Yeah?
They're ready
to pay.
Good.
What's this?
Proof of life photo?
Can I just comb
my hair a bit? No?
No.
He's looking
too relaxed.
Leave my damn
hair alone!
Please, please
don't hurt me.
Read.
Read aloud,
you idiot.
Uh...
"Eagle's instructions
for the Mouse.
"Paint a large
white X
"on the orange van
used for the kidnapping.
"Depart ten minutes
after this call.
"If anyone follows
it will be
"the end
of the hostages.
"Go to Utrecht
Central Station.
"The luggage locker
number nine,
"collect the assignment
and await instructions
from the Eagle.
"The next message
for the Mouse,
he will drive
to Hotel Totenhoff."
There it is.
"By the lamppost
outside the main entrance
you will find
a plastic jar filled
with further instructions."
Officer Hendricks
for Headquarters.
The next place
would be the gas
station in Jahr.
Alright. Last call.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Alright.
Yes, this is the Mouse.
"Eagle's instructions
for the Mouse.
"Drive to the covered lot
on Bizet Avenue.
"Transfer the money
to a yellow Volvo
with a bicycle.
"The key is
on the left
front wheel.
"Drive south
on motorway 311.
There will be
a radio in the car
for further instructions."
Spikes, one
kilometer ahead.
Driver, slow down.
You stop
at three orange cones
by the side of the road.
Listen up, Mouse...
drop the money
off the bridge
on your left.
Driver.
Leave now.
Let's go, let's go!
Come on!
I'll get rid
of the car.
Yeah, that's good.
We'll see you later.
Have a nice
bike ride back.
That's good.
Alright.
Freezing.
Yeah, it's cold.
But I don't care.
Police!
Open up!
Open the door!
Police!
Now!
Open the door!
You're a fucking idiot!
Hooray!
Did we do it?
Heiny.
We got to go get Heiny.
You know
I'm right.
No, no,
he's right,
he's right.
Wait, wait, wait.
Guys, okay.
We got
to finish the job.
Let's drive
to the shed
and we'll let Heineken go.
And I like it!
Let's do it!
Police say
the ransom was larger
than any paid
in modern times.
So far no arrests
have been made
and no suspects
have been identified.
An unidentified
police source
said that the kidnappers
were likely an established
organization,
well funded,
highly disciplined
and almost
certainly foreign.
Uhhh... no lunch,
no dinner, no lunch...
No! No breakfast,
no lunch again...
they, um...
They've done the deal.
That's why we, um...
someone big, we've...
Shit, something big!
Big!
Something big
must have happened.
Ab?
Hey, Ab,
have you saved
some water?
I've got four liters
of water here.
A man can last
about a month
on four...
four liters...
"Meticulous planning",
that's you, buddy.
Behind us.
Wait, what's going on?
What are you doing?
We're being followed.
Have a look.
It's the police.
Those are the cops
from the bar.
Yeah, I see them.
Shit!
This is the wrong way!
I'm going to try
and lose them.
Shit.
We almost got hit.
He turned off.
Turn left!
Shit.
What do we do?
What are we
going to do?
They don't know
where the money is.
So, Cor,
how long we got
before they do?
Come on.
Let's go!
Where?
To dig up the money
for Christ's sake!
All five of us?
In this car?
Yeah!
Yeah? And
then what?
Then what?
Well, I don't know!
What do you got?
What have you got?
Come on, think.
Alright,
I'm thinking...
Come on,
come on!
Alright, alright!
I think me and Willem
go and we get
the money.
The five of us
can't stay in this car
so Willem and I are
going to ditch
the car
and then we
dig up the money.
Then I think what,
we meet you guys
in four hours?
The boatyard.
Out at Newlake.
That's good,
that's good.
No, we can't be
worrying about Heineken.
There's no point
in worrying about
him now.
Fucking go! Go!
Where are you doing?
I'm coming with you.
Better get out
before I break
your fucking neck.
Just be careful.
Don't go home.
Promise me.
Okay.
Fuck you.
What's the time?
It's ten past.
They're not here.
They are not here.
They took
all our money.
Did you knock
on the door?
No, I didn't
fucking knock
on the door.
Why should I
knock on the door?
Where are their cars?
They're not here.
Hey.
Hey, come in.
Yeah, what's wrong
with him?
What's right with him?
Here.
Shit, that's way
too much.
Now come on,
you deserve it.
Here, come here.
I want to talk to you.
What's up?
I want you
to take this money
and I want you
to hide it in
the next 20 minutes.
Yeah, but I'll come
with you, right?
No.
What do you mean?
Listen, you'll be fine.
Look, I love you.
Which means I want
what's best for you.
Now you listen to what
I've got to say. Alright?
Okay, good.
You'll be fine.
You take this,
and you make life
work for you, alright?
Go on. Go on, get
the fuck out of here!
You'll find me, yeah?
Yeah, of course.
You promise?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Brakes is right.
About what?
Money's too heavy.
We had to leave
a sack in that drum.
You did what?
Oh, come on.
You didn't even notice.
Look at this, look!
You didn't even notice!
You left it
in the ground?
Seven fucking million?
Yeah, we'll get the rest
when we come back.
Come back?
I have a friend,
they live in Paris.
We're going...
We're going
to stay there
until everything's
calmed down.
Well, I can't.
What do you mean?
I can't stay
in fucking Paris.
Cor, I got a family.
I got kids.
What about
Mr. Heineken?
Mr. Heineken!
Answer me!
You let Heineken out now
they will grab you, man.
If we don't,
he'll fucking die.
Well, once we get
to Paris,
we can call
his people,
tip them off.
If they find him in Cat's shed,
then we can't ever go back.
Think about that?
Come on, think
about it!
Jesus, man.
You leave half
your brain
out in that whole
with the rest
of my money?
It's safe.
It's fucking safe!
It'll never be safe.
It's safe!
No!
Don't you get
it, Cor?
It'll never be safe.
Not here.
Not in Paris.
We're lucky
if we can hang
out in Timbuktu.
Take your fucking money,
take it! Take it!
We were worth
a lot more than that.
I'll see you
on the outside.
What about you?
Coming with us?
Yeah, I'll come.
Shit.
Halt!
Can you hear me, Ab?
Wherever you are.
Ah. Come on, John.
Sing with me,
get your mind
off all this rubbish.
Any song,
what is it?
Are you the police?
What the hell took you so long?
I'm alright.
Just my friend, Ab,
my chauffeur,
go and get him, please.
That's it,
go and get him!
Ab, it's over!
He's in there!
Ab, you okay?
It's over!
Are you okay, sir?
Jesus Christ,
it's over!
Oh, God!
Fuck.
Ah.
Oh, thank you, God.
Ab, you...
Oh.
Thank you, God.
Kidnapped billionaire,
Alfred Heineken,
has been rescued
in a police raid
earlier this evening.
Both Heineken
and his driver,
Ab Doderer,
were found in a shed
in the outskirts
of Amsterdam.
They were
apparently unharmed...
I don't know.
Maybe it was
the ransom note
we left in the copier.
Or all that Bang
Bang chicken
or maybe...
Listen, I'm not
saying he did, but...
maybe Brakes
could have
said something...
Wait, wait, wait.
What did you say?
I'm not saying
Brakes did,
I'm just saying...
Yeah, no, no,
I hear what
you're saying.
Maybe you all thought
he was fucking you,
did you think about that?
- -details of
the rescue...
Ah, fuck.
These are horse blankets.
So?
So what?
I'm allergic.
I stop breathing.
You promise?
I'm sick
of you complaining!
Alright, just calm down!
What the fuck?
Just fucking stop it!
Look, just stop it...!
Get out of my car!
Just take it easy!
Take it easy!
Hold it together!
Listen.
This fucking car...!
Look, just
hold it together!
You want your money?
Take your money.
Calm the fuck down.
We haven't got time
for this shit!
You, get in the car.
No way.
Not me!
I'm out of here!
Spikes, get
in the fucking car.
Let him go.
Spikes.
Fuck him.
Come on.
Can't even
pick up his bag.
Spikes.
Spikes!
Come on, Cor.
Look, Spikes!
You're not going
to make two fucking miles!
I'll make 10,000.
Come on, Cor.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
Let him
have the car.
You're not going
to make it without us.
Just get
in the car, alright?
You stay with that asshole,
he'll get you killed.
Come on, Spikes!
Look, Spikes!
Oh, fuck it.
Fuck!
Okay, bye.
This evening.
She's going to meet
us this evening.
Are you sure
she's cool?
Oh, she's cool.
Listen, I think
I'm going to call Sonja.
You leave
my sister
out of this.
Look, I won't
be long.
Wait.
No, I'm serious.
You put her
in this shit
and they're going
to know where
we are.
I've got to make
sure she's all right.
Alright, fine.
Well, you
make the call...
I'm out of here.
Seriously,
you're on your own.
Alright.
Come on.
Let's go.
What's this place
like, anyway?
It's, uh,
it's nice.
But it's safe.
That's all
that matters.
Forget about it.
Come back!
I'm coming.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm going
to make some coffee.
What's going on?
Front page.
Spikes turned
himself in.
"God told me
to burn the money."
Ha.
He's insane.
Or he's smart.
He's going to do
15 years at least.
Well, that's one way
to play it.
You think you could
play it like that?
No, God doesn't talk
to me that much.
Oh, yeah.
He looks
like an idiot.
Mr. Heineken, it's been
over two months
since you were released.
Looking back,
what was
your biggest fear?
My biggest fear was
for my driver, Ab Doderer.
Because he
suffered most...
and we both knew who
was really expendable.
Did they ever threaten
to kill you?
I honestly believe
that they believed
it was
a business deal,
nothing more.
Where do you think
Cor Van Hout
and Willem Holleeder
are now?
It doesn't matter.
As the great fighter
Joe Louis used to say,
"You can run
but you cannot hide."
We'll get them.
Thank you.
Hm.
I'm going
to have to phone Sonja.
You can't do that.
I told you,
you can't do that.
What about that one? Huh?
- That one's perfect.
-  What about it?
Well, you know, it's
got those tall windows
that you like.
I bet it's got a big
backyard for the kid.
If we're buying
fancy houses,
we might as well buy
one for Willem next door,
otherwise I'll never
see either of you.
Now he can buy
his own.
You're never even
going to try to live
in the real world,
are you?
Yeah, hello.
Karin, look, it's me.
Don't hang up.
Cor?
Now, listen to me.
I'm going to give
you a number
and I need you
to tell Sonja
to call me
as soon as she can.
from a phone box
some way over
from the house.
You understand?
Where are you?
Listen to me.
Listen to me, please.
Promise me,
look, it's for her.
- Hello?
- What did you do, Cor?
What the hell
did you do?
Don't start that now,
we haven't got
time for that.
Look, there's no time...
Cor, what the hell
did you do?
Cor, where are you?
Answer me, Cor.
Where...?
Cor?
Where are you?
Sonja?
Son... Sonja, are you there?
Sonja, Sonja!
I'm here.
I'm here, Cor.
Cor, Cor, this is...
they follow
me everywhere.
I know.
I just wanted
to hear your voice.
If I buy a loaf
of bread,
they check my money
in case it's...
I want to be
where you are.
Please.
Soon, Son, soon.
Listen,
after the baby,
I can come back, alright?
Soon.
That's a promise.
You promise?
I promise.
I promise,
Listen to me,
okay, Son, listen?
We're going to be
a real family.
You know?
We'll be
a real family
and I'm going to give you
everything you ever wanted.
And believe me.
Huh, you believe me?
I believe you.
But Cor, do you know
how big this thing is?
They've arrested everybody
you ever met in your life.
They bugged
all the phones.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean everyone?
Like Arthur
and my parents,
Your parents?
all your friends,
all of mine,
everybody's.
Cor, I've got to go.
I love you.
Okay?
Be safe.
No, don't hang up!
Don't hang up!
- Son, don't hang up!
-  I love you!
I, uh...
I think I messed up.
I think they have
this number...
since last night.
Just letting you know.
We better get
our stuff then.
Willem, wait.
Something feels wrong.
It seems too quiet.
You want to do this?
You know,
I think I'll sit
this one out.
In prison?
Look, we can get out
while we're still young.
They'll never find
the money.
You want to bet?
You know I do.
There are two ways a man
can be rich in this world.
He can have
a lot of money...
or he can have
a lot of friends.
But he cannot have both.