Something.
[SHUSHING]
[SCREAMS]
[GEORGE]: I know that's kind
of strange but,
my grandmother's always
been my best friend.
Seriously.
She's seen hard times.
Just after grandma had triplets,
they tell me my grandfather
axed himself
in the head while chopping wood.
They must think I was
born yesterday.
Uncle Lan calls it
the "axe-cident".
Pun intended.
Mom says he just uses humor
to hide his real feelings.
I don't know.
It must have been pretty
tough for them.
There's a lot of stories they
don't tell me, but
I can feel them.
They're in the dirt that I walk
on when I visit this place.
Anyway,
I'll never forget all the things
grandma tried to pass on to me.
Even the one she
didn't mean to.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Come on! Harder!
Harder, man!
[GRANDMA]: It's hard
being an outsider.
And you and me have come
from a long line
of outsiders.
People like to prey on
those who are weak.
[SIGHS]
But you have to remember
something.
It's not because we are weak.
It's because we are strong.
My grandma taught me that.
What's this?
A warning.
It means if anyone
who lacks courage
steps foot on her grave,
she'll reach out and
strike them dead.
But she was just
kidding, right?
See for yourself.
[BREATHING HARD]
- [SNAKE HISSES]
- Whoa!
Don't move!
If you move,
she'll strike.
You have to be brave.
You have to stand up.
Here.
Look her in the eye
and play.
What?
Do it!
[PLAYS VIOLIN]
She seems to approve.
If you can stand
up to a beast,
you can stand up to a bully.
- [JIM]: Oh!
- [WOMAN]: Wow!
- [WOMAN 1]: Mama!
- [WOMAN 2]: Mama!
- [LAUGHING]
- Wow!
[JIM]: Smells good!
What is it, mama?
[MUTTERING UNINTELLIGIBLY]
[GRANDMA]: Get out of my house!
Fuck!
What? What happened?
Mercy cut me.
Don't go in there!
[GRANDMA CONTINUES YELLING]
[DEMONICALLY] Get out!
Georgie?
Georgie!
I tried everything, Georgie.
I can't cure myself.
You'll be okay.
The doctors are coming.
They don't know... anything.
All I ever wanted
was a baby.
Georgie.
He's coming.
You got to get out of here.
- What?
- It's for your own good.
- Georgie.
- I'm not going anywhere!
I can protect you, grandma!
I love you.
I love you, too.
More than anything.
But... you can't save me.
George! You talked to her?
You need to come now.
- No!
- Come now! George!
He's coming! He's coming!
Did you hear what I said?
Grandma had a stroke?
Is she dead?
Mom said stroke. Stroke
doesn't mean dead.
Might as well be.
Ow, you moron!
Guys! Stop it!
She's not dead.
But she's in pretty bad shape.
The idiots at the
nursing home say
they won't take care
of her anymore.
Why?
There's been, um,
problems.
What kind of problems?
[SIGHS]
So she's going to live
with you now, huh?
I wish.
We're going to stay at grandma's
place for a while.
Mom says we'll take
care of her there.
What's wrong with your house?
She wants to die in hers, huh?
You haven't seen her
since she got sick.
I should have.
It's not your fault, George.
You care too much.
No.
You do.
That's why I watch over you.
- Georgie, look, you must--
- [MAN]: George!
Who are you talking to?
The girl next door.
- The girl next--
- Or God.
Maybe.
Well, either way. You're
supposed to be in class.
No, I don't. I'm home
for the week.
School policy, George.
You still have to go.
What? Are you going
to drag me in?
[GEORGE]: I'm nothing like my brother.
He hates going to grandma's.
But... he's kinda weird.
He's 15 and only cares
about his cooking and
being a chef one day but,
at least he has direction.
Maybe I'm the weird one.
Can't you just use ketchup
like a normal person?
I'm not a normal person.
I'm a super taster.
A what?
Dr Franklin said I have a third more
taste buds than most people.
I'm not sure your IQ points.
Guys! Oh, for god's sakes!
This blows.
Why are we stuck taking
care of grandma anyway?
- Uncle Lan was closer.
- He works.
And you don't?
What about aunt Jinny?
You got to get her out of
the nut house first.
It's a hospital!
I've got to get a
healthier family.
Why do you have to
be such a jerk?
Aren't you just a little sad?
I mean, it's the last time
you're gonna see grandma.
Oh, it doesn't look... so bad.
[COUGHS]
[BUDDY]: We should have
stayed in a hotel.
[GEORGE]: God.
Wa-Watch it!
Grandma's favorite lamp.
Oh, no. Not grandma's
favorite lamp.
[HOUSE CREAKS]
Yeah, see?
Now you get the haints angry.
That's just the house
settling down.
The house has been here
for 150 years.
Don't you think it's
already settled?
Don't try to freak me out!
I don't have to.
You know what happened here.
Grandma was sitting there.
Holding mom.
Grandpa Frank,
he was standing here,
holding an axe--
Bite me, George!
Everyone knows it
was an accident.
How can you cut yourself in half
by accident, you moron.
I'm sure it happens
all the time.
Maybe he like,
tripped.
And...
Who cares, anyways?
You do.
You think he's still here.
Can't you see him,
walking this room?
Rusty old axe in his hand?
[IMITATES AXE HITTING HEAD]
Tchuk!
- Tchuk!
- Just give it a rest, okay?
Tchuk!
What happens when he
runs out of head?
Who's he going to turn
his axe on then?
- Turn the light on.
- Tchuk!
- I'm warning you!
Tchuk!
You wouldn't hear him coming.
The last thing you'd
smell is his whisky
and his hot, stale breath
on your neck.
George!
- And then, tchuk!
- Stop!
- Tchuk!
Tchuk!
- [LAUGHING]
- What's going on?
What's going on? Hey!
Buddy, Basil. Come on!
[JIM] Basil, come on!
[BUDDY] I though you
were a ghost.
I ought to call the
cops on you, Jim.
The way you scared my boys.
Me?
Hell, Reb. You should have
seen him going at it.
This boy's gotten heavy too.
I think I threw my back out.
Buddy's cooking.
How's photography, Mr. Swann?
Selling any photos?
Uh, well some folks prefer
my wife's paintings, but
I do sell enough to afford
the occasional libation.
- Libation?
- He means getting plastered.
George!
Boy's got a mouth
and a vocabulary.
Speaking of which,
look what I got for you.
A little education.
Sweet!
Isn't that a little
scary for him?
Oh, hell no.
Just about a guy trying to
kill his entire family.
My daddy did it all the time.
Is there anything for me?
Damn, did I forget you?
Gift card to my cousin's
grocery.
You can bobby-flay yourself to death.
Thank you.
Anything um, left for me?
You...
Just my undying love and the
pleasure of my company.
I think your wife might have have
something to say about that.
[SIMULTANEOUSLY]
I wouldn't tell!
Well, I just figured you, you
know, would need some help
- getting the house ready.
- Oh, you don't have to do that.
- No, no.
- Oh.
Come on, your momma practically
raised me. I owe her big.
And it's a pretty decent
excuse for me to...
come visit.
[JIM] You'd better enjoy the
[INDISTINCT]
[REBECCA LAUGHING]
Mom's 15 again.
She should have married him.
She would have had
to move back here.
Yeah, so?
Mom loves Zona (???)
Not as much as she
hates this place.
[LOW RUMBLING SOUND]
Mom?
[RUMBLING SOUND CONTINUES]
[MOM] Hey, George. You ready?
Let's go get grandma.
[UNCLE LAN] Aw, shit!
Family reunion.
Hey, Uncle Lan.
Jesus, you boys got tall.
You got a little wide.
[SCOFFS] Yeah, and you started
a little early.
It's my day off, Bec.
In fact, I was just down
in Coopersville.
I got you guys a special
present, okay?
So you'll always have something
to remember your special trip
to see your grandma.
Here you go.
That was funny, alright? I'm
trying to lighten the mood.
You should try humor.
This is an advertisement
for dying young.
Welcome. Grandma's room's
right there, boys.
So I signed the discharge papers.
I thought that might help.
Help would be taking her
in yourself, Lan.
No, that would not be. That
would be... martyrdom.
What is this?
That's her room.
You told me she had
a private room.
She did.
At first.
Lanning! I sent you thousands
of dollars.
And it... got spent.
Medimucil tax.
Quality oatmeal, you
know. We had to get
a few roommates to
defray the costs.
How many?
I don't know. Four. Five.
[SOFTLY] Four or...
Six.
Six?
[SOFTLY] Get over here.
[LOUDLY] Let's go!
He said you'd come to get me.
- Keep her away from me.
- What?
Get me away.
- [OLD MAN] Jesus help me.
- What's going on?
This guy, he tried
to grab George.
What?
She's here, honey.
Geeze.
[UNCLE LAN] Sorry, George.
She's like this most
of the time.
Grandma?
You carry that thing
everywhere?
Just when I'm with
your grandma.
Why?
Ask her roommates.
Alright, so you got her drugs,
special pillow,
For god's sakes, don't give
her another pillow.
and then you've got these.
[BUDDY] Wait.
We have to change her diapers?
Yeah, she's pretty regular.
I-Is she ever lucid?
Yeah, for... a few minutes
of the day.
Mostly she's like an infant.
Gurgles.
Drools.
The most important thing
is you have to remember to give
her her shots when she's awake.
Chlorpromazine? Isn't that
for mental patients?
It helps keep her...
friendly.
You just got to dilute it
with uh, saline solution
and you'll be fine. Now
your brother said that
you had medical training,
correct?
In the army.
Great! That's good for me.
Wait, wait, wait. Um...
Do you think maybe you could stick
around for a couple of days
and make sure that we're
doing everything right?
Uh...
I'll pay you double what
you're making now.
[LAUGHS]
What do you...?
Take care.
[GRANDMA COUGHING]
Ugh! I'm going with Wendall.
You're not going anywhere.
What? You think just
because she's old,
we're going to dump
her in the street?
We're a family.
One day,
I'm going to be on that bed.
And you'll be taking
care of me.
- That's up to medicare.
- Ugh, Buddy.
Come here.
Come here!
Look, I know this is hard...
but we're in this
together, okay?
And we're going to face this
with love and dignity.
- Hold her down!
- I'm trying! I can't get a weight!
Sit on her feet then!
Just hold the arm.
Hold the arm!
Hold her arm down.
[YELLING AND MUTTERING
UNINTELLIGIBLY]
[SOBBING]
[GRANDMA SCREAMS OUT
UNINTELLIGIBLY]
What are you doing?
Didn't you see that?
Hmm...
No, it's in her handwriting.
Yes, of course I'm sure.
Alright, well, thank you.
Your aunt Jinny's been in isolation
for the last month.
They don't know how
she sent it.
Okay, well what does
it mean? Hastur's--
[SOFTLY] Don't say that.
Why? Who's Hastur?
Oh, come on! Come on!
No, it's just a stupid old name
that gets grandma all worked up.
I quit!
[SIGHS]
She doesn't like that
baby food crap.
She wants real food.
She will get what the
doctor ordered.
Look, mom. She doesn't
like it. Look.
Mama.
So, here's your baby back.
And there is the tekamaki.
It's sushi.
My dad fedexed me the
fish from New York.
It's a little undercooked,
son.
That's because it's sushi.
Why don't we go put
it on the grill?
See, Mercy? It's rosemary,
your favorite.
Let her smell it, Henriette.
Mercy? He just wanted
to see how you were.
- Wow!
- Yeah, I took that
- It's so good.
- a couple of years ago.
- Beautiful.
- I was like the uh,
the light there right?
It's gorgeous.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah?
Those yours?
Yeah, Charlotte and I started
our new catalog.
Look.
Wow.
- [REBECCA] Jesus.
- [JIM] Mm-hmm.
My darling wife painted
that one.
Isn't she awesome?
That's a death wolf.
[GEORGE] A death wolf?
Yeah, it's an old
hill-folk legend.
You haven't heard of it?
No, we don't believe
in that haint stuff.
Death wolf's not a
ghost, honey.
No, they say that she
walks the border
between this life
and the next,
hunting for lost souls.
If she catches you,
she will eat you
and shit you out in hell.
Nice.
My wife's the devil worshiper
in the family.
Really?
'Cause I'm gonna get five
grand for that painting.
George, could you get some
lemonade from the cellar?
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
You show your grandma this?
- What?
- Yes or no, boy. She seen it?
No!
Alright, come with me.
Please, you smell like whisky.
You ever drink alcohol,
George?
No.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
I was about your age
when I started drinking.
I'm not kidding.
You think I'm a class A
butthole, don't you?
[LAUGHS]
It's alright!
I don't hold it against
you, George.
It's most folks' opinion.
But you're the closest
thing I have to a son,
so I want you to listen
to me now, okay?
Hey!
You listen, alright?
Now, what did my sister tell
you about your grandmother?
Hmm? She say she's...
a good mama?
Made us lemon cake?
Put band aids on our
booboos, right?
Yeah.
Well, that's her story.
'Cause your mama ran off
when she joined the army
when she was 18.
Yeah, she never saw
how awful they got.
How awful what got?
Grandma's bad spells.
She had little ones when
we were young kids.
One minute, she'd
just be all...
kisses and whispers.
And then she'd turn on you
like a rattlesnake.
And your mama was
really strong.
Like you, you know. She
could handle her.
But when she left,
it was just me and Jinny. She
sat us down and she says,
"Ain't no more of my
kids leaving me.
Come hell or high water."
Jinny was fine with
it at first.
You know, she was the most
liked to grandma.
Things got complicated.
Let me show you something.
There's your aunt Jinny
with her boyfriend Terry Clay.
They were so in love.
It was beautiful.
Your grandma didn't like it.
She said, "There's
no way in hell
I'm letting you go, Jinny."
But Jinny stood up to her.
Said, "I'm moving out.
I'm getting married.
I love this man."
Wh-What'd grandma say?
"Enjoy your honeymoon."
Yeah, I didn't think
much about it.
'Til they went camping
near Holly River.
Jinny said they'd
be gone two days.
A week later, there were
injuries around them.
Papers called it
a bear attack.
What was left of Terry, you could
have fit in a shoe box.
And your aunt Jinny,
they found her hiding
up in the tree.
And she screamed.
She screamed all the way to the
goddamn nuthouse, George.
Now,
let me ask you something.
What kind of a bear
tears apart half the forest
and doesn't leave one
goddamn track?
I don't know.
You know, I never wanted to
stay in this shithole town,
but that old bitch--
No, uncle Lan, you can't
possibly think that
- grandma could have anything--
- Boy! Listen to me!
This is a warning.
Your aunt Jinny is just
like your grandma.
She sees things.
None of us are going
to rest easy
'til that old fucking bitch
is in the ground.
- You got it?
- Yeah, I got it.
Grandma, you ever hurt anyone?
How about some chocolate?
I know you're not supposed to
have any, but I snuck some.
Will you eat it for me?
Eat it for mom?
[SIGHS]
For Hastur?
Hastur.
[IMAGINARY LANGUAGE]
Beenum.
Mastur.
Enn siké.
Ha cis see.
Ah nini see.
Ah penni.
Ja koon ah!
Grandma?
Can't wait to get out
of this house.
Why?
Just creepy.
It's different, you know.
How it used to be.
Mom tell you what
happened today?
No. What happened?
I was feeding grandma
and
then she started
talking to me.
It was gibberish.
No, it-it sounded like
a real language.
Like,
middle eastern or-or something.
You think grandma's part Arab?
Maybe I should make couscous.
This isn't a joke!
She was herself, Buddy.
Maybe that Chlorpromazine
stuff is making her sick.
Are you a doctor?
- No...
- Then stay out of it.
You're just going to
make things worse.
- But, what if--
- No ifs.
I'm telling you, as
your brother,
leave it alone.
Oh, you're up.
Where'd you get that?
Right.
Our little secret.
You want your medicine?
No, grandma-grandma. I can't
throw it out.
I know. I don't like it either
but it's for your own good.
Stop!
No.
Grandma, stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop, grandma!
Grandma! Stop!
Stop.
- Stop.
- [GRANDMA CRYING]
Help me.
[REBECCA]: Come on, George.
You ready to go?
There you go, mama.
Babysitter's here.
[REBECCA]: It's about time.
Why do I have to go shopping?
My old clothe's just fine.
Yeah, I can smell
it from here.
We will be back in
a couple of hours.
Try not to burn
the place down.
Yes, mom.
Come on, let's just
have a look.
Uh, hey, mom. Can I
catch up with you?
There's something I want to
check out at the bookstore.
Alright, just, don't
be too long.
Okay.
So, what brings you
around here?
My grandma's been my best
friend my whole life.
Now...
people are telling me things.
So, why come to me?
I saw you at her house.
That's your job, isn't it?
Tell folks what to believe?
No one wants to believe bad things
about the people they love, son.
You think Abel wanted to believe
Cain was a murderer?
So, you're saying love's
a bad thing?
No.
I'm saying people do more evil
in the name of love
than anything else.
If God cannot stand against
the Abyss, how can we?
This was your grandma's bible.
You guys were friends?
Best friends.
She and your grandpa helped
me build this church.
She was the most...
christian woman I've ever met.
What happened?
She loved something too much:
children.
She wanted them more
than anything.
But the good lord decided
not to give her any.
[SCREAMING]
[CRYING]
Mercy!
A miscarriage. Just
like the others.
I'm sorry, Frank.
But she ain't ever
gonna be a mother.
[PRIEST]: Now, you have
to understand
this was a woman
who served God
every day of her life.
She could not fathom why
he had deserted her.
So in time,
she decided to look elsewhere.
Wh-what do you mean?
I don't hold these local
superstitions,
but there have been times when I've
looked out at those mountains
and I know there's
something up there
staring back.
Something old
and mean.
[PRIEST]: Folks say that
if God won't help,
what's up there will welcome
you with open arms.
Though, all I know is your
grandmother climbed
up into those rocks
- and when she came back down,
- Mercy!
nothing was the same.
Well, you sure fooled me.
We might even be
talking twins.
Now, it's a little early, so
I want to keep an eye on
you, but I don't see why
we can't celebrate.
Looks like we hit the jackpot.
Are you ready for
number three?
[SCREAMS]
[PRIEST]: She got
what she wanted,
but there was a price.
He became the town drunk.
Beat three of my congregation
half to death.
All I could do was tell him
to stay away.
Oh.
[SHUSHING]
The end was inevitable.
Frank?
We both wanted a baby.
[SCREAMS]
A month after your
grandpa died,
she found gold on her land.
Gold!
The next year, we
had a drought.
Her farm was the
only one spared.
Decade after decade, no matter
how bad things were,
your grandmother always
did very well.
And every time, she'd
get a little meaner,
she'd get a little nastier.
She was trading in the
good bits of herself
to get what she wanted.
Well, if you thought
she was so bad,
then why'd you keep her bible?
Love is blind.
Well, maybe I'm blind too.
She threw that bible at me
just after your grandpa had died.
Swore she'd never set foot
in my church again.
I've been praying 50 years
for her to come back
and claim it.
Maybe it's your turn to pray.
"It's your turn to pray."
Jesus Christ. See, this is
why we don't go to church.
Well, what was I
supposed to do?
You could have come to me!
You never talk about grandma.
He's right.
Alright, what do you
want to know?
Did she ever hurt you?
- Badly?
- Well, I'm still here, aren't I?
- That's not an answer.
- Are you a mother?
- No...
- Then how the hell would you
know what it's like raising
three kids alone,
no husband, no family, when
you've got 104 degrees fever
but you still got to change
three sets of diapers?
Think you'd be able to keep
your cool all the time?
Your grandma could be mean.
And she could be rough and I
hated her guts sometimes,
but she never backed
down from her duty.
But, uncle Lan said that--
Uncle Lan is a pinhead.
Do you know I carried him
and Jinny for 17 years
and all they could do was blame me
and grandma for their problems.
"Ooh, I've had such a hard life!"
Well, boo hoo. Grow up
and deal with it.
If there's one thing I
learned in the army,
it's you take responsibility
for yourself.
Then how come you ran away?
[REBECCA SCREAMS]
[GEORGE]: Lanning!
He killed her!
[REBECCA]: Killed?
It's not her blood.
[INDISTINCT]
[REBECCA]: Thanks.
You okay?
So now they're saying uncle
Lan died of an aneurism.
[SIGH] From all that drinking.
He hated her, right?
And he was drunk.
Put his hands around her throat
and started squeezing.
It sounds like you're trying to
convince yourself of something.
What do you know?
You're just a figment
of my imagination.
Is that all you think I am?
Tell me what to do then!
- Help me!
- She says you will fight,
George.
You have to finish it first.
What's happening to you?
[REBECCA]: She's going to need one
of us close now all the time.
So, we'll have to
sleep in shifts.
[GEORGE EXHALES HARD]
You mean it's a death watch.
- Can you just give us a minute?
- Yeah.
Hey, George.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
No.
I mean, I'm-I'm sorry.
She's been closer to you than
I ever was and
I'm gonna change that.
Will you help me change that?
Must have been where
the fight started.
Maybe we shouldn't open it.
What? You think it's gonna shoot out
bolts of lightning or something?
One.
Two.
Three!
What's it say?
Nothing.
- We're wasting our time.
- Charlotte's into all this stuff.
She's gotta know something.
Jim?
Charlotte?
We shouldn't be here.
No, it's fine.
Jim said come anytime.
George, they're not here.
We should go.
Here, see if you can find
anything in that.
What should I look for?
Books with raindrops.
No raindrops.
What about... tears?
Umm, tears...
Weeping, sobbing.
There is weeping.
Yeah. Weeping book.
During the witch hunts
of the middle ages,
anyone caught with a
magic related book
was routinely burned
at the stake.
Legend has it that necromancers
created a special type of book
that could avoid detection.
While the manuscripts and
pages appeared blank
text was actually written
in an ink that
only became visible upon contact
with solid human tears.
Hence the term weeping book.
An individual was required
to cry upon its pages
while praying for the thing
that one most wanted.
Words would then appear describing
a necromantic rite
needed to procure
what one desired.
[BARKS]
[BUDDY]: World hunger.
Darfour.
Julia Child.
- Julia Child?
- She died too young!
You're supposed to cry for something
you want, you dumbass.
What'd you think of?
There was a way to
cure grandma.
Well, look at it this way:
it'd make a really
great diary.
Buddy, wait!
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
We don't know what chopping
this thing up will do!
You'd rather keep it around?
You really think that's going
to solve anything?
No, but I sure feel a whole--
[BUDDY GROANS]
God.
Buddy!
Bud-- Mom!
We need to get to the
car, come on!
Come on!
Mom!
Here we go.
Come on, baby!
Mom, wait!
Stay with grandma!
- What?
- You know we can't leave her alone!
Mom, please! I'm
really scared.
Call Jim. Have him come over.
Call Jim!
Mom, let's go!
Jim. It's George.
Third message.
Just wondering when you're
going to be coming over.
Please call me.
[GRANDMA BREATHING]
Grandma?
[GRANDMA GASPS FOR AIR]
[SIGHS OF RELIEF]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Jim?
[GASPING]
[MUTTERING UNINTELLIGIBLY]
- [GRANDMA]: It's here.
- Grandma! There's-there's nothing.
What's here?
The death wolf.
Okay. Grandma-Grandma,
just stay-stay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Stay here.
[GRANDMA PANTING FRIGHTENEDLY]
[GRANDMA GROWLING DEMONICALLY]
[MUTTERING UNINTELLIGIBLY]
[DEMONIC GROWLING]
[DEMONIC NOISES]
[GRANDMA]: Hastur!
It's coming! It's coming!
- It's--
- [GRANDMA MOANS THEN CALMS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Mom?
It's your aunt Jinny.
She came to me, George.
Mercy's spirit. She told
me what it wants.
It's you.
- George, it's always been you.
- What?
She held it off as long as
she could but please,
you have to get away,
as far as possible.
You've got to get
out of the house.
I busted out of the hospital.
I had to hurt some people.
- Remember Dead Tree Hill?
- Jinny!
Just down the road
from grandma's.
Meet me there tonight.
If you see him,
- make the sign of the cross.
- Jinny?
Make the sound of the cross!
- Jinny!?
- Get away from me!
[PHONE HANGS UP]
[GRANDMA FALLS TO THE FLOOR]
Oh, no.
Come on. Get up.
Come on. Come on,
grandma, get up.
I can't lift you on
my own, grandma.
Come on!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
Grand-grandma, wake up.
Wake up! It was just
your medicine!
Please!
Wake up.
Grandma, it was just
your medicine.
Please wake up.
[SOBBING]
No.
9-1-1 emergency.
Yeah, thi--
This is George.
Mercy McCoy's grandson.
She's just...
Please hold.
[GRUNTS]
What is happening?
Help me!
I can't.
He's keeping me out.
What do I do?
Get the axe in the cellar.
Break down the doors.
[GROANS]
Hastur.
[GRANDMA CONTINUES MUTTERING
UNINTELLIGIBLY]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLS]
Jim!
Back up for a second. You
say she tried to cut you?
- No, she tried to eat me.
- Eat you?
Like-like the pictures
in the weeping book.
And then I-I grabbed
the verbena plant
and I burned her face with it.
And you fought her off
with a houseplant?
It was a demon, Jim.
And-and the death wolf
came after me and...
I ran and...
Y-you believe me, right?
- I don't know.
- [JIM]: Charlotte...
I used to think it was just
crap to tell tourists.
- But--
- But what? Kid's scared half to death.
He wouldn't have
imagined any of this
if you hadn't told him
those goddamn stories.
Don't blame me! What he's saying
is different from the stories.
What do you mean?
The death wolf isn't a demon.
It's meant to go after
wicked folk.
Why would it go after you?
Uncle Lanning.
What?
I switched out grandma's
drugs for saline.
She must have gotten some
of her strength back.
She killed him, Jim.
I helped her kill my uncle.
George...
You didn't help try
to kill anyone.
Then how else do
you explain it?
You said you left me
messages, right?
Well, there's nothing
on my cell.
Isn't it possible
that maybe...
I don't know, you...
- imagined or dreamed all this?
- No, it's true.
It's all real.
I called you.
- Call the police.
- And tell them what?
Think they're going to
believe this story?
They'll lock us up.
I don't care about the police.
I just want to see my mom.
[SIGHS]
Alright, you got it, my man.
Let's go see your mom.
What's the matter?
Jim?
Why couldn't you just
stay put, huh?
Why?
What?
Look, this is not
what you think.
You're like a son to me.
Do you know how much I tried
to turn her down?
Turn her down for what?
What the hell was she going to
give you, Jim? A new camera?
You're just a kid.
You don't know what it's like.
Look at me.
You don't know what it's
like to love someone.
And not be able to
be with them.
You have no idea.
She promised you my mom?
No.
Hastur did.
Hey! Don't!
Son, please!
Don't.
- Come on!
- George!
Shoot me!
- Stop!
- Shoot me, you asshole!
George!
[GUNSHOT]
[WOLF GROWLING]
Aunt Jinny!
Jinny!
Finally.
No, no, no.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
George?
- Mom?
- [INDISTINCT]
- George, where are you?
- Mom?
Where's aunt Jinny?
George?
Look, I can't find grandma
and the house is all
messed up and--
Oh, my god! [SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
You could just keep running.
It'd be suicide to go back.
You know that.
I have to try!
What if you fail?
Who's going to help them?
Mom?
Mom, wake up, please!
Please wake up!
Come on!
[RECITES RITUAL]
Hastur!
Grandma, please! There's got to
be something left of you.
Stop! Hastur did this to you!
This isn't you!
Forget Hastur!
You're my grandmother.
You're Mercy! [SOBS]
Mom.
That's what you want?
[GRANDMA]: You have
to be brave.
You have to stand up.
I love you, grandma.
Georgie?
I love you too, Georgie.
Grandma?
[GEORGE]: The deal grandma made
came from a strong
need for family.
The truth is, I would have never
been born if she hadn't done it.
So, in a strange way,
even the darkest things in
life can be a blessing.
But, no matter what
challenges we face,
we'll face them as a family,
just like grandma wanted.