[THUNDER]
[SHOVEL DIGGING]
JESUS CHRIST!
DISPATCH,
THIS IS ADAM DAVID 5.
REQUESTING
WANTS AND WARRANTS
ON A CORAL AND WHITE
FORD COUPE.
FLORIDA LICENSE PLATE
G-S-Q-7-4-K.
OVER.
ROGER, ADAM DAVID 5.
STAND BY.
[GRUNTING]
ADAM DAVID 5, NO WANTS
OR WARRANTS ON GSQ74K.
CAR'S REGISTERED
TO A VINCENT GOTTO.
ROGER, DISPATCH.
[THUNDER]
DON'T MOVE!
DROP THE SHOVEL!
I SAID DROP
THE FUCKIN' SHOVEL!
NOW TURN AROUND SLOWLY.
YOU DID A NICE JOB HERE.
THANK YOU, SIR.
IT'S A GOOD THING
YOU FOUND HIM WHEN YOU DID.
A COUPLE OF DAYS, THAT WATER TABLE
WOULD HAVE REALLY BLOATED HIM UP.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING HERE.
OH, CHRIST. ANOTHER ONE?
LISTEN, YOU GO BACK
AND GET FORENSICS, O.K.?
YES, SIR.
LET'S GET IT OUT.
EASY.
WHAT THE HELL--
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT THE HELL HAVE WE
GOT HERE, HUH?
O.K., TOMMY, ON 3.
1, 2, 3.
LOCAL WOOD SCULPTOR
AND CONVICTED SERIAL
KILLER VINCENT GOTTO
IS IN THE NEWS
ONCE MORE.
WITH HIS NEW EXECUTION
DATE LESS THAN A WEEK AWAY,
HIS ATTORNEY HAS FILED
FOR A COMMUTED SENTENCE
WITH THE STATE COURT
OF APPEALS,
AND HIS FUTURE IS
BEING DECIDED NOW
IN THIS VERY COURTHOUSE.
UH, YOUR HONOR, IF MS.
GARRICK HAS SOME NEW EVIDENCE
SHE WISHES TO SHARE
WITH THIS COURT,
THE PEOPLE WILL BE MORE
THAN HAPPY TO REVIEW IT.
DO YOU HAVE NEW EVIDENCE,
COUNSELOR?
WELL, NOT EXACTLY,
YOUR HONOR.
I'M AFRAID MY CLIENT IS
NOTORIOUSLY UNCOOPERATIVE,
BUT WHILE REVIEWING THE
ORIGINAL INVESTIGATOR'S NOTES,
I DISCOVERED
SEVERAL DISCREPANCIES.
I BELIEVE,
IF GIVEN ENOUGH TIME,
I CAN ACCOUNT FOR
MY CLIENT'S WHEREABOUTS
DURING AT LEAST TWO OF
THE ALLEGED HOMICIDES.
BUT YOUR CLIENT WAS NEVER CONVICTED
FOR EITHER OF THESE CRIMES, WAS HE?
UH, NO, YOUR HONOR,
HE WASN'T.
HE WASN'T EVEN CHARGED.
HE WAS CHARGED AND CONVICTED
OF ONLY ONE MURDER.
THE MURDER OF HIS OWN SON.
MS. GARRICK HAS THROWN UP
AN ELABORATE SMOKE SCREEN
AT THE PEOPLE'S EXPENSE.
YOUR HONOR, I OBJECT
TO MR. SILVERMAN'S
IMPLICATION AND ATTITUDE.
BUT HIS ARGUMENT
IS NOT WITHOUT MERIT.
AN ALIBI FOR A MURDER THAT YOUR
CLIENT WAS NEVER CHARGED WITH
IS NOT VALID GROUNDS
FOR AN APPEAL.
BUT JUDGE OLSON REFERRED TO THE
OTHER HOMICIDES DURING SENTENCING,
SO EVEN THOUGH MY CLIENT WAS
NEVER TRIED AS A SERIAL KILLER,
HE WAS CONVICTED
AND SENTENCED AS ONE.
OH, GOD.
ZOE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
ARE THEY ALL DEAD?
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, YOUNG LADY.
BACK TO BED.
ALL RIGHT. ARE YOU
ALL SETTLED IN NOW?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM?
NO.
YOU DON'T NEED
A DRINK OF WATER?
NO.
O.K. GOOD NIGHT,
SWEETHEART.
MMM.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NOTHING.
DID YOU HAVE ANOTHER ONE
OF THOSE BAD DREAMS?
ABOUT DADDY?
HIM AND HIS NEW GIRLFRIEND,
THEY WERE BOTH DEAD.
OH...
OH, SWEETHEART,
DADDY'S FINE.
DO YOU WANT TO CALL HIM
JUST TO BE SURE?
I'LL BET HE'S STILL UP. IT'S
NOT THAT LATE IN LOS ANGELES.
NO, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE LATER.
HEY, MAYBE WE CAN INVITE
HIM TO YOUR BIRTHDAY PARTY.
I THINK I WANT TO GO
TO SLEEP NOW, O.K.?
[SIGHS]
[SEVERAL TELEPHONES RINGING]
WELL, I SEE YOU FOUND
YOUR FRIEND, ALL RIGHT.
ANOTHER ONE OF YOUR JOKES?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU ASKED
FOR THIS STUFF.
WHAT?
PRISON IMPOUNDS
DROPPED IT OFF.
THEY HAD AN EVIDENCE REQUISITION
REQUEST WITH YOUR SIGNATURE.
OH, CHRIST.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT.
I ASKED FOR THIS STUFF
THREE MONTHS AGO.
THOUGHT IT MIGHT HELP
WITH THE APPEAL.
OH, WELL.
BETTER LATE
THAN NEVER.
WHEN'S THE DECISION?
TOMORROW.
AND IF THE JUDGE SAYS NO,
I'M ALL SET
TO ASK THE GOVERNOR
FOR A STAY OF EXECUTION.
NEVER HAPPEN.
NOT IN AN ELECTION YEAR.
"AND WHEN SHE REACHED
THE EDGE OF THE CLIFF,
"MATILDA LOOKED DOWN
AT THE BIG GREEN OCEAN.
"AND THEN SHE PULLED THE HAND
MIRROR OUT OF HER BACKPACK
"AND STARED
INTO ITS SHINY SURFACE.
"MATILDA'S REFLECTION
WAS STILL BEAUTIFUL,
"AND THE MIRROR'S FRAME AND
HANDLE WERE STILL MADE OF GOLD,
"ENCRUSTED WITH JEWELS.
"BUT MATILDA WAS NO LONGER
BLINDED BY THE BEAUTY.
"SHE DROPPED THE MIRROR INTO
THE OCEAN AND RAN HOME, HAPPY--
HAPPY TO BE
JUST PLAIN MATILDA."
SO...
WHO CAN TELL ME THE MORAL?
BETH?
THE MORAL?
[KIDS GIGGLING]
YOU WERE LISTENING,
WEREN'T YOU?
YEAH, SORT OF.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
ZOE, WOULD YOU CARE
TO GIVE BETH A HAND?
I THINK WHAT IT'S SAYING
IS THAT BAD THINGS
DON'T ALWAYS LOOK BAD.
SOMETIMES
THEY EVEN LOOK GOOD.
SO YOU THINK THE MIRROR
IS A BAD THING?
WELL,
WHEN MATILDA FINDS IT,
SHE THINKS IT'S GOING TO MAKE
HER BEAUTIFUL AND POPULAR,
BUT ALL IT REALLY DOES IS
MAKE HER STUCK UP AND MEAN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, BETH?
IS ZOE RIGHT?
UH, UM, YEAH, I GUESS.
WELL, THEN, WHEN THE TWO BEST
STUDENTS IN THE CLASS AGREE,
THEN IT MUST BE RIGHT.
O.K. NEXT WEEK WE'RE
GOING TO START DR. DOLITTLE.
GOOD. BETH LOVES
TO DO LITTLE.
[GIGGLING]
[GIGGLING STOPS]
WELL, IT'S A LONG SHOT,
BUT I FILED AN APPEAL TO HAVE
YOUR SENTENCE COMMUTED TO LIFE.
THE JUDGE IS TAKING A FEW
DAYS TO THINK ABOUT IT,
WHICH IS POSSIBLY
A GOOD SIGN.
AT LEAST SHE DIDN'T
DENY IT RIGHT AWAY.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT
SAVING YOUR LIFE.
WHY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHY?
LISTEN TO ME.
I KILLED MY SON.
EVEN IF I WERE FREE,
MY LIFE WOULD BE MEANINGLESS.
SO TELL ME...
WHY WOULD I WANT TO EXTEND
IT HERE IN THIS HELLHOLE, HUH?
BUT I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
COMMIT THOSE OTHER MURDERS,
AND THAT MEANS THE REAL
KILLER IS OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
THERE'S NO ONE OUT THERE.
WHAT?
THE OTHER CHILDREN?
I MURDERED THEM.
THEN WHY HAVE YOU KEPT
SILENT ALL THIS TIME?
HUH?
[GUARD]
OFF THE GLASS, GOTTO!
THAT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE,
BUT I'M NOT CONVINCED.
WHY DID YOU BURY HIM
WITH THE PUPPET?
PINOCCHIO?
IT WAS HIS FAVORITE.
I MADE IT FOR HIM MYSELF.
[GUARD]
OFF THE GLASS!
FOR HIS LAST BIRTHDAY.
THAT'S NOT EXACTLY THE ACTIONS
OF A DERANGED MURDERER.
WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW
ABOUT A DERANGED MURDERER?
WHO ARE YOU PROTECTING?
NO ONE.
IT WAS ME.
JUST LET ME DIE.
HMM?
PLEASE.
WAIT. MR. GOTTO.
[DOOR OPENS]
MR. GOTTO!
WHO REALLY KILLED
THOSE CHILDREN?
SOMEONE CLOSE TO YOU? IS THAT
WHY YOU'RE PROTECTING HIM?
MR. GOTTO!
STAY OUT OF IT!
LET ME DIE!
VISITING ROOM THREE!
ON THE DOUBLE!
JUST LET ME FUCKIN' DIE!
PLEASE...
STAY OUT OF IT!
JUST LET ME DIE!
PLEASE!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BELL RINGS]
PARTY AT MY HOUSE.
THIS FRIDAY AFTER SCHOOL.
IT'S GOING TO BE GREAT.
THANKS, ZOE-BLOWY.
I NEVER MISS A PARTY.
HA HA HA HA!
COME ON, BETH,
GIVE THEM BACK!
GIVE THEM BACK, BETH!
I MEAN IT!
WHAT? I'M NOT INVITED?
WHAT YOU GOING TO DO?
COME ON, BETH!
YOU CAN DO IT!
COME ON!
AAH! GET HER OFF!
GET HER OFF! GET HER OFF!
[PANTING]
OHH...
I TOLD YOU
SHE WAS CRAZY.
YEAH. COME ON.
YOU SHOWED HER, BETH.
HOW WAS SCHOOL TODAY?
NOTHING SPECIAL.
YOUR MOTHER TELLS ME
YOU HAD ANOTHER NIGHTMARE.
DON'T YOU THINK
WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT IT?
NO.
WHEN SOMEBODY HURTS US,
SOMEBODY WE'VE TRUSTED,
IT'S NATURAL, EVEN HEALTHY,
TO BE ANGRY WITH THEM.
IT'S PART OF
THE HEALING PROCESS.
BUT IT'S TIME
TO MOVE ON, ZOE.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN
TO FORGIVE HIM.
FORGIVE WHO?
WELL, YOU CAN BE SURE IT'S
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN AGAIN.
I HOPE NOT.
NO. I UNDERSTAND.
AGAIN, I'M REALLY SORRY.
ALL RIGHT. BYE.
ZOE.
THAT WAS A MRS. WAYNE.
SHE'S UNDERSTANDABLY UPSET,
CONSIDERING SHE JUST CAME
BACK FROM THE HOSPITAL,
WHERE HER DAUGHTER HAD
TWO STITCHES IN HER EAR.
SHE SAID YOU BIT HER.
SHE STARTED IT.
I DON'T CARE
WHO STARTED IT.
WE DON'T BITE PEOPLE
IN THIS HOUSE.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO.
OH, HI, WARREN.
GOOD TIMING.
REALLY?
YEAH. ZOE HAD ANOTHER
FIGHT AT SCHOOL TODAY.
WHAT? SHE CAN'T AFFORD
TO GET THROWN OUT AGAIN.
I KNOW THAT.
I--I CAN'T EXACTLY FOLLOW
HER TO CLASSES ALL DAY.
HERE. YOU TALK TO HER.
ZOE, IT'S DADDY.
[WARREN]
HELLO, ZOE.
ZOE?
HELLO?
WARREN, I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
O.K.
BYE.
YOU'RE GROUNDED,
YOUNG LADY.
NO TV AND NO PLAYING
AFTER SCHOOL FOR TWO WEEKS!
[DOOR SLAMS]
MMM...
YOU KNOW, HER BIRTHDAY
IS THIS FRIDAY.
OH, SHIT.
WELL, SHE'S GROUNDED
TILL THEN.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MAY I COME IN?
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
HOW ABOUT MRS. PIGGLE WIG,
HMM?
NAH. SHE'S MAD AT ME. I
FORGOT TO BRUSH OUT HER TAIL.
BUT...
WALTER SAYS HE WANTS
TO SLEEP WITH ME TONIGHT.
WHAT ELSE IS NEW?
WALTER ALWAYS WANTS
TO SLEEP WITH YOU.
WHY DOES SHE ALWAYS TAKE
EVERYONE ELSE'S SIDE?
SHE DOESN'T, HONEY.
SHE'S UNDER A LOT
OF STRESS RIGHT NOW,
SO WE HAVE TO TRY
AND HELP HER OUT
AS MUCH
AS WE POSSIBLY CAN.
I DO TRY, REALLY.
BUT EVERYTHING ALWAYS
TURNS OUT ALL WRONG.
YOUR ARGUMENT HAS BEEN
WELL-THOUGHT-OUT AND PRESENTED,
AND I HAVE GIVEN IT A GREAT
DEAL OF CONSIDERATION.
AND ALTHOUGH I BELIEVE
YOU MAY HAVE A VALID POINT
ABOUT THE CIRCUMSTANCES SURROUNDING
YOUR CLIENT'S SENTENCING,
THE FACT REMAINS THAT
IN THE EYES OF THE LAW,
A ONE-TIME MURDERER IS JUST AS
GUILTY AS A MULTIPLE MURDERER.
THEREFORE, I CAN FIND
NO JUSTIFICATION
IN OVERTURNING JUDGE OLSON'S
ORIGINAL SENTENCE.
MOTION DENIED.
JENNIFER! IS THIS
YOUR LAST HOPE?
WILL YOU APPEAL
THE COURT'S DECISION?
VINCENT GOTTO IS A VICTIM
OF PUBLIC OPINION
AND MEDIA HYPE.
A BROADCAST THE OTHER NIGHT
REFERRED TO HIM AS
A CONVICTED SERIAL KILLER,
WHEN IN FACT HE'S NOT.
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
WILL YOU BE A WITNESS
AT THE EXECUTION?
[DOOR CLANGS]
[PRIEST]
THE LORD IS MY SHEPHERD.
I SHALL NOT WANT.
HE MAKETH ME TO LIE DOWN
IN GREEN PASTURES.
HE LEADETH ME
BESIDE THE STILL WATERS.
HE RESTORETH MY SOUL.
HE LEADETH ME IN THE PATHS
OF RIGHTEOUSNESS
FOR HIS NAME'S SAKE.
THOU ANOINTEST
MY HEAD WITH OIL.
MY CUP RUNNETH OVER.
SURELY GOODNESS AND MERCY
SHALL FOLLOW ME
ALL THE DAYS OF MY LIFE,
AND I WILL DWELL
IN THE HOUSE OF THE LORD
FOREVER.
[BELL RINGS]
ARRRGH!
[GASPS]
CAN I HELP YOU?
I'M SOR--I'M SORRY. I--I
DIDN'T MEAN TO STARTLE YOU.
NO. IT'S O.K.
ARE YOU A MEMBER
OF THIS PARISH?
NO, NO.
ACTUALLY,
TECHNICALLY SPEAKING,
I'M NOT EVEN
A CATHOLIC ANYMORE.
I WAS DIVORCED
LAST YEAR.
THAT'S O.K.
THIS ISN'T
A CATHOLIC CHURCH.
IT'S EPISCOPALIAN.
IT'S, UH, SORT OF LIKE
CATHOLIC LIGHT.
HA HA HA HA!
COULD I, UM...
UH, BUY YOU
A CUP OF COFFEE?
SO I QUIT THE FIRM,
AND I TOOK A POSITION
AT THE PUBLIC
DEFENDER'S OFFICE.
IT'S A LOT LESS MONEY,
BUT THE SHORTER HOURS ALLOW
ME MORE TIME WITH ZOE.
SEEMS AS THOUGH YOU'VE
MANAGED TO MAKE THE BEST
OF A DIFFICULT SITUATION.
I WONDER.
WHY IS THAT?
ZOE'S BEEN
HAVING THESE...
HORRIBLE, VIOLENT
NIGHTMARES LATELY,
EVER SINCE
I BECAME A P.D.
HER THERAPIST THINKS SHE HAS
A LOT OF REPRESSED HOSTILITY.
OH, I...
YOU THINK YOUR JOB
IS TAKING ITS TOLL ON HER.
NOT JUST ON HER.
YOU KNOW, I DEAL WITH A LOT
OF BAD PEOPLE IN MY JOB.
I PUT A LOT OF THEM
ON THE STREET.
AND THE FIRST TIME
I HAD A CLIENT
THAT I THOUGHT
WAS ACTUALLY INNOCENT,
I COULDN'T SAVE HIM.
[DOOR CLOSES]
YOU DID EVERYTHING
YOU COULD, JENNY.
LET IT GO...
OR IT'LL
TEAR YOU UP INSIDE.
HOW COULD THE MAN
WHO MADE THIS
HAVE MURDERED
HIS ONLY CHILD?
EVIL COMES IN ALL
SHAPES AND SIZES.
MAYBE HE DID KILL
ALL THE OTHERS.
NO.
ALL THE OTHER CHILDREN WERE
BEATEN WITH A BLUNT OBJECT.
HIS SON WAS STRANGLED.
SO?
SO WHY
THE DIFFERENT M.O.?
MAYBE...THE OTHER
MURDERS WERE PLANNED,
BUT HIS SON WAS
SPUR OF THE MOMENT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MAYBE HIS SON FOUND
OUT WHAT HE WAS DOING,
AND HE HAD TO
GET RID OF HIM...
FAST.
NO.
GOTTO WAS DEFINITELY
PROTECTING SOMEONE.
BUT THE KILLINGS STOPPED
AFTER HE WAS ARRESTED, RIGHT?
SO HOW DO YOU
EXPLAIN THAT?
HAVE A GOOD WEEKEND,
JENNIFER.
GOOD NIGHT.
YOU, TOO.
OW!
OH, DAMN,
ANOTHER NAIL GONE.
[SPEED DIAL BEEPING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
GARRICK RESIDENCE.
SOPHIA, HI. IT'S ME.
HEY, DID WARREN
REMEMBER TO CALL ZOE?
YEAH, BUT, UH, SHE
WOULDN'T COME TO THE PHONE.
OH, MAN,
SHE'S RELENTLESS.
WONDER WHERE
SHE GETS IT FROM.
LISTEN, UM,
THE TOY STORE CALLED,
SAID THERE WAS
A MIX-UP IN SHIPPING
AND THEY WON'T HAVE
THE DOLL TILL MONDAY.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
DID YOU TELL THEM
I HAD TO HAVE IT TODAY?
OF COURSE.
THEY SAID
THEY WERE VERY SORRY,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
THAT THEY COULD DO.
OH, GREAT. O.K., UM...
WELL, I GUESS I'LL LOOK
FOR IT SOMEWHERE ELSE
WHEN I GO GET THE PIZZA
AND THE CAKE.
I DON'T KNOW.
BYE.
HI, YOU GUYS.
HEY, MOM.
SWEETHEART,
SORRY I'M LATE.
CAN I GET UNDER HERE?
WHAT'S IN THERE?
DON'T ASK.
HEY, I WAS JUST ABOUT TO SEND
OUT A SEARCH PARTY FOR YOU.
OH, THE CAKE WASN'T DONE
WHEN I GOT THERE,
AND I HAD TO GO ALL OVER
TOWN TO GET THAT DAMN DOLL.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT. WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
JUST--TIME-OUT. RELAX.
DAVID, I CAN'T. THE KIDS ARE
GOING TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
SOPHIA AND I
CAN HANDLE IT.
I GOT A TRUNKFUL
OF STUFF IN THE CAR...
I CAN GET IT.
I WILL GET IT.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AND
CHANGE CLOTHES AND RELAX,
AND I'LL CALL YOU WHEN
EVERYBODY GETS HERE?
THE DECORATIONS AREN'T--
I JUST WANT--
DAVID.
NO, NO, NO.
DAVID, COME ON.
YOU CAN'T.
BUT YOU--
NO BUTS.
GO ON.
TAKE A HIKE.
DON'T MESS UP.
THANKS. I OWE YOU.
THAT'S TRUE...
AND I'M GOING TO
COLLECT LATER.
[CHILDREN CHEERING]
[DAVID] READY? ONE MORE
TIME. ONE MORE TIME.
OHH!
O.K., WHO'S
GOING TO GET CANDY?
I AM!
WHO'S GOING TO GET CANDY?
ME, ME, ME, ME!
HEY!
OH, MOMMY, IT'S GREAT.
IT'S EVEN BETTER
THAN I HOPED.
IT IS? OH, GOOD.
[CHILD]
ME, ME, ME, ME!
I'M SORRY.
SHE SPOTTED IT BEFORE
I COULD GET IT WRAPPED.
WHERE'D YOU FIND
THAT THING?
IT LOOKS HAND-CARVED.
[SINGING
AND OVERLAPPING VOICES]
I'LL TALK TO YOU SOON.
COME ON, SWEETIE.
O.K., MOMMY.
BYE. SEE YOU
AT SCHOOL.
O.K.
BYE, YOU GUYS.
BYE!
YAHOO!
HAS ANYONE SEEN
PINOCCHIO?
HE'S MISSING?
HE WAS RIGHT HERE
A MINUTE AGO.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
HERE I AM.
JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
THE FIRE WAS OUT.
WOOD, YOU KNOW?
[EVERYONE LAUGHING]
HA HA HA HA!
HELP!
ZOE, YOU'LL HAVE TO
FORGIVE DAVID.
WOOD, YOU KNOW.
HA HA HA...
SOPHIA,
WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE THOSE?
I'LL DO THOSE TOMORROW.
OH, I DON'T MIND.
COME ON, IT'S LATE. I'LL
DO THEM IN THE MORNING.
YOU SURE?
YEAH.
YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW.
O.K. GOOD NIGHT.
HEY, YOU.
HOW YOU DOING?
O.K.
[GASP]
OH, HO HO HO HO.
HO HO.
GOOD ONE, KIDDO.
ZOE, YOU SCARED THE LIVING
DAYLIGHTS OUT OF ME.
COME ON, MOMMY. IT'S
JUST A LITTLE PUPPET.
OH, NO, NO. IT'S
NOT JUST ANY PUPPET.
THIS IS
PINOCCHIO.
PINOCCHIO
WASN'T SCARY.
HE WAS GOOD.
OH, YOU
THINK SO, HUH?
WASN'T HE?
YEAH,
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY HE COULD
BECOME A REAL LIVE BOY.
HE HAD TO BE GOOD.
WELL, THAT'S TRUE,
AND HE TRIED
TO BE GOOD.
HE TRIED
REALLY HARD,
BUT HE KEPT GIVING
IN TO TEMPTATION
AND DOING THESE
REALLY BAD, BAD THINGS.
AND THAT'S WHY
THE BLUE FAIRY
MADE HIS NOSE
GROW LONGER
EVERY TIME
HE TOLD A LIE.
THAT'S WHY SHE
GAVE HIM A CRICKET
TO ACT
AS HIS CONSCIENCE,
TO TRY TO
KEEP HIM FROM DOING
THESE REALLY
BAD, BAD THINGS.
BUT NOTHING
EVER WORKED.
AND NOW...
HE'S COMING
AFTER YOU!
[SCREAMING]
SO DID YOU HAVE
A GOOD TIME TONIGHT?
YEAH.
GOOD.
HEY, SOPHIA SAID DADDY
CALLED TO SAY HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
SWEETHEART, DADDY
LOVES YOU VERY MUCH.
HE WAS JUST UPSET.
IT'S THE FIRST BIRTHDAY
HE'S EVER MISSED.
PINOCCHIO SAYS HE WANTS
TO SLEEP WITH ME TONIGHT.
PINOCCHIO'S FINE
WHERE HE IS.
NOW, REMEMBER,
PINOCCHIO'S JUST VISITING
UNTIL YOU GET YOUR
REAL PRESENT, O.K.?
BESIDES, HE WOULDN'T WANT
TO SLEEP NEXT TO WALTER.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE HE GOT SWALLOWED
BY A WHALE, REMEMBER?
ARRRGH!
O.K. GOOD NIGHT,
MOMMY.
OH, I LOVE YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
GOOD NIGHT.
SO WHERE WERE WE?
OHH...
MMM...
AHH...
[THUNK]
THERE YOU GO.
I WISH YOU
WERE A REAL BOY.
THEN I WOULDN'T
BE ALL ALONE.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GASP]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH MY PINOCCHIO?
IN MY ROOM?
AND THEN DAVID MADE
PINOCCHIO TAP HIS OWN HEAD.
AT FIRST I THOUGHT
IT WAS KIND OF FUNNY,
BUT NOW I THINK HE MIGHT HAVE
HURT PINOCCHIO'S FEELINGS.
SOUNDS LIKE
A GREAT PARTY.
YEAH.
AND IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU AND
YOUR MOM REALLY LIKE DAVID.
YEAH.
YOU DO LIKE DAVID,
DON'T YOU?
YEAH, HE'S O.K.,
BUT...
BUT WHAT?
IF HE TAKES
MY MOM AWAY,
THEN I WON'T
HAVE ANYBODY.
HEY, MOM.
HI, SWEETHEART.
HOW WAS SCHOOL?
O.K.
CAN WE TALK?
WHAT'S UP?
WELL...
SOPHIA SAID THAT YOU SNEAKED
INTO HER ROOM THIS MORNING.
NOT ME.
PINOCCHIO.
HE WAS CURIOUS
ABOUT LADIES' BODIES.
AH, HE WAS, WAS HE?
YEAH.
I TRIED TO
EXPLAIN IT TO HIM,
AFTER HE HEARD YOU AND
DAVID IN YOUR ROOM.
DO YOU WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT?
NO.
WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
OH.
WELL...
I ORDERED THIS
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY.
IT'S A LITTLE LATE,
BUT...
BUT LOOK.
OH, YEAH.
IS IT THE WRONG ONE?
SWEETHEART...
YOU KNOW I HAVE TO TAKE PINOCCHIO
BACK TO THE OFFICE, RIGHT?
NO!
HE'S NOT OURS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S MINE.
LOOK, THIS IS WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN ASKING FOR.
PINOCCHIO'S
JUST VISITING.
NO.
FIST DADDY LEFT ME,
NOW YOU WANT TO MAKE
PINOCCHIO LEAVE, TOO?
YOU'D NEVER LEAVE ME,
WOULD YOU?
NO.
[RUSTLING]
OH, ALL RIGHT,
BUT JUST
FOR TONIGHT,
BUT DON'T TELL MOM.
GOOD NIGHT.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
[BELL RINGS]
O.K. TIME'S UP.
LET'S GO.
HEY, SOPHIA, HAVE YOU
SEEN PINOCCHIO?
ZOE TOOK HIM
TO SCHOOL.
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
DAMN.
SHE KNEW I WANTED TO TAKE
HIM BACK TO THE OFFICE TODAY.
OH...
MY GOD.
[SINGING]
COME ON, BETH,
GIVE HIM BACK.
GIVE HIM BACK!
COME ON,
GOOD ONE, BETH.
[THUNK]
HERE
SHE COMES.
♪ ZOEY-BLOWY ♪
♪ ZOEY-BLOWY ♪♪
PINOCCHIO, WHERE ARE YOU?
PINOCCHIO...
THERE YOU ARE.
PINOCCHIO.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
BETH, WAIT UP!
AAH!
OH, MY GOD!
HONEY, ARE YOU ALL
RIGHT? ARE YOU O.K.?
IS SHE ALL RIGHT?
I THINK SH--
I THINK
SHE'S O.K.
SHE MAY BE IN SHOCK.
OH, NO.
IT'S BETH.
SHE LOOKS O.K.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
SHE'S O.K. SHE'S FINE.
YOU'RE A FUNNY MAN,
BARRY.
OH, WELL, YOU SHOULD SEE ME
WITH A LAMPSHADE ON MY HEAD.
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, THANKS TO YOU, MY
DAUGHTER'S NOW COMPLETELY ATTACHED
TO THAT DAMN PUPPET.
WHAT PUPPET?
THE ONE YOU PUT
IN MY CAR ON FRIDAY.
PINOCCHIO?
[INTERCOM] JENNIFER,
THERE'S A DR. EDWARDS
ON LINE ONE FOR YOU.
A DOCTOR?
WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO THE GARDENER?
LANDSCAPER.
HELLO, DOCTOR. WHAT
CAN I DO FOR YOU?
ZOE JUST SHOWED UP HERE
AT MY OFFICE UNANNOUNCED.
WHAT?
THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT
AT HER SCHOOL.
SHE CLAIMS HER PUPPET
PUSHED ONE OF HER CLASSMATES
IN FRONT OF A BUS.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
I'M TAKING IT BACK TO
WORK TOMORROW ANYWAY.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
SHE SEEMS TO HAVE FORMED
A COMPULSIVE-DEPENDENT
ATTACHMENT TO IT.
SEPARATION AT THIS POINT MIGHT
BE TOO TRAUMATIC FOR HER.
ZOE, DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR NEW BETTY DOLL?
PINOCCHIO WAS JEALOUS.
AND WHAT ABOUT
THE GIRL AT SCHOOL?
SHE WAS PICKING ON ME.
PINOCCHIO WAS JUST
TRYING TO PROTECT ME.
DO YOU KNOW THAT SHE COULD
HAVE GOTTEN SERIOUSLY HURT?
PINOCCHIO DIDN'T MEAN
TO DO A BAD THING.
HE JUST DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN RIGHT AND WRONG.
HOW LONG'S
IT BEEN LIKE THIS?
EVER SINCE THE DIVORCE.
WE'VE BEEN DRIFTING
FURTHER AND FURTHER APART.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
COULD YOU QUIT YOUR JOB AND
STAY HOME WITH HER FULL-TIME?
DOES WARREN PAY ALIMONY?
MM-MMM.
JUST CHILD SUPPORT.
I WAS MAKING MORE MONEY THAN
HE WAS WHEN WE SEPARATED.
THAT WAS ONE
OF THE PROBLEMS.
WELL, YOU KNOW YOU COULD
ALWAYS MOVE IN WITH ME.
WHY NOT?
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT YOU AND ZOE.
I KNOW.
I LOVE THE OFFER.
BUT ZOE'S BEEN THROUGH
ENOUGH CHANGES FOR ONE YEAR.
HERE.
SPOON ME.
[SIREN]
LOOK,
THE BOTTOM LINE IS,
THE DECEASED WAS A
WELL-KNOWN PUSHER AND PIMP.
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I DON'T SEE ANY JURY
FEELING ANY SYMPATHY
TOWARD HIM.
OH, GEE...
WOW.
UM, MAYBE THEY'LL
HAVE A CHANGE OF HEART
WHEN THEY HEAR
HOW HE DIED.
SEE, YOUR CLIENT, HE--HE
HUNG HIM ON A MEAT HOOK,
AND THEN HE TORTURED HIM
TO DEATH WITH A BLOWTORCH.
YOU KNOW, HE EVEN RECORDED
IT SO HE COULD LISTEN TO IT
AND ENJOY IT AGAIN
AND AGAIN AND AGAIN.
IT'S GREAT.
HERE, TAKE A LISTEN.
AAH!
[CHUCKLING]
NO! PLEASE! GOD, NO!
OOH.
NO, PLEASE, GOD!
AAH!
THAT'S GOT TO HURT.
[CHUCKLING]
AAH!
[LAUGHING]
[RETCHING]
[WATER RUNNING]
HA HA...
AH, SO...
DO WE DEAL
OR DO YOU STILL
WANT TO GO TO COURT?
I NEVER HEARD
MY CLIENT'S VOICE.
EXCUSE ME?
ON YOUR TAPE.
WITHOUT HIS VOICE,
YOUR TAPE IS WORTHLESS.
I'LL HAVE THE JUDGE
RULE IT INFLAMMATORY.
THE JURY
WILL NEVER HEAR IT.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
GARRICK RESIDENCE.
SOPHIA, HI.
YEAH, IT'S ME.
LISTEN, I'M
GOING TO BE LATE,
SO DON'T HOLD
DINNER FOR ME.
I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT AT
THE I.N.S. THIS AFTERNOON.
REMEMBER?
TO RENEW MY WORK VISA.
OH, JEEZ,
I COMPLETELY FORGOT.
UM, LISTEN,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL CALL DAVID AND SEE
IF HE CAN BABYSIT.
O.K., THANKS.
KAMINSKY'S LANDSCAPING.
HEY. IT'S ME.
LISTEN, I NEED YOU
TO DO ME A BIG FAVOR.
SO AFTER YOU STOLE
HIS HEROIN,
YOU SOLD IT ON THE
STREET YOURSELF?
NO, MAN. I GAVE IT AWAY
TO THE POOR AND NEEDY,
JUST LIKE ROBIN HOOD.
BUT THE STUFF
WAS UNCUT.
THREE PEOPLE DIED
OF AN OVERDOSE.
HEY, THAT'S WHAT
THE BOX WANTED.
THE BOX?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW,
THE TELEVISION.
IT TOLD ME TO--
IT TOLD ME TO KILL HIM
AND HAND OUT HIS STUFF.
THE TELEVISION TOLD
YOU TO KILL THE PUSHER?
DAMN STRAIGHT.
I WOULDN'T HAVE
DONE IT OTHERWISE.
I LIKED THE GUY.
DO YOU MEAN YOU SAW A SHOW
ON VIGILANTES OR SOMETHING?
NO.
IT WASN'T NO DAMN SHOW.
THE BOX WASN'T EVEN ON.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M NOT CRAZY, LADY.
THE BOX DID TALK TO ME.
IT'S BEDTIME,
SWEETHEART.
GOOD NIGHT.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO COME TUCK YOU IN?
NO, THANKS.
[ZOE]
STOP PLAYING AROUND NOW.
WE HAVE TO GO TO BED.
I'M THE ONE WHO IS GETTING
INTO TROUBLE, O.K.?
ZOE...ARE YOU TALKING
TO SOMEONE IN THERE?
JUST PINOCCHIO.
OH...O.K.
ZOE, YOU SHOULDN'T
TELL PEOPLE I TALK TO YOU.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE THEY'LL
TAKE ME AWAY FROM YOU.
THEN I'LL NEVER
GET TO BE A REAL BOY
AND BE YOUR BROTHER.
YOU REALLY THINK WE'LL
BE A FAMILY SOMEDAY--
YOU, ME, AND MOM?
SURE. YOU KNOW
I'LL NEVER LEAVE YOU.
BUT WE CAN'T BE
TOO SURE ABOUT MOM...
NOT AS LONG AS
DAVID'S AROUND.
I KNOW.
I CAN MAKE DAVID GO AWAY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
PINOCCHIO.
REMEMBER, YOU CAN'T
BECOME A REAL BOY
IF YOU KEEP
DOING BAD THINGS.
GETTING RID OF DAVID
WOULD BE A GOOD THING,
THE SAME WAY PUNISHING THAT
BITCH AT SCHOOL WAS A GOOD THING.
[FOOTSTEPS]
PINOCCHIO.
WHERE ARE YOU?
[FOOTSTEPS]
ZOE!
[GASP]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
GETTING PINOCCHIO.
I THOUGHT
HE WAS IN YOUR ROOM.
NO. HE'S IN
THE BASEMENT.
WHOA. I'LL GET HIM.
YOU GO TO BED.
NO. THAT'S O.K.
I'LL GET HIM.
NO. IF YOUR MOTHER
COMES HOME, FINDS YOU UP,
SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
GO TO BED.
GO ON.
I'LL GET HIM.
O.K.
VERY FUNNY.
GET BACK TO BED, ZOE!
GOD--DAMN IT!
O.K., ZOE. HERE I COME.
YOU BETTER GET TO BED.
UNH!
[DOOR CREAKING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
EXCUSE ME, I NEED--
MOMMY!
ZOE!
ARE YOU O.K.?
[CRYING]
OH, MOMMY, IT'S DAVID!
WHAT HAPPENED?
LOOKS LIKE YOUR FRIEND
TOOK A NASTY TUMBLE
DOWN THE BASEMENT STEPS.
IS HE O.K.?
WE'VE NOTIFIED
HIS PARENTS.
IF YOUR DAUGHTER
HADN'T DIALED 911,
I DON'T THINK
HE WOULD HAVE MADE IT.
[SIREN]
O.K.
ALL RIGHT.
PINOCCHIO, DID YOU MAKE
DAVID FALL DOWN THOSE STAIRS?
ANSWER ME!
DID YOU MAKE DAVID
FALL DOWN THOSE STAIRS?
NO.
YOU'RE LYING,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU KNOW, MOM WOULD HAVE TO
SPEND A LOT MORE TIME WITH US
IF SOPHIA WASN'T AROUND.
ZOE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GETTING BUGS.
I FORGOT.
I HAD TO BRING ONE
FOR SCIENCE TODAY.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT WANT TO
STAY HOME FROM SCHOOL TODAY.
NO. I'M O.K.
YOU SURE? REALLY?
REALLY.
O.K.
MMM. HAVE A GOOD DAY.
[ENGINE STARTS]
ZOE.
I FOUND WALTER
IN THE TRASH.
DID YOU THROW HIM AWAY?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
[CRICKET CHIRPING]
A CONSCIENCE
FOR PINOCCHIO.
SO HE WON'T DO
ANY MORE BAD THINGS.
WELL...GOOD LUCK.
IN THE ORIGINAL
ITALIAN VERSION,
PINOCCHIO ACTUALLY
HAD A VERY BAD TEMPER,
AND HE SQUASHED THE CRICKET
DURING ONE OF HIS TANTRUMS.
COME ON.
DO YOU WANT TO TELL ME
ABOUT DAVID'S ACCIDENT?
YOUR MOTHER SAYS THAT HE
WAS VERY SERIOUSLY HURT.
YOU MUST HAVE SOME
FEELINGS ABOUT THAT.
[INTERCOM BEEPS]
DR. EDWARDS?
I'M WITH A PATIENT,
KELLY.
I KNOW, BUT YOU SAID YOU
WANTED TO PERSONALLY SPEAK
TO THE DELIVERY MAN
WHEN HE GOT HERE.
OH, RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
[BEEP]
EXCUSE ME, ZOE.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A MINUTE.
I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY.
NOW HE THINKS
I HURT DAVID.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DIDN'T?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW.
NO, I DON'T!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SLAMMED
THE DOOR IN HIS FACE.
ARE YOU SURE?
WHO ELSE COULD IT
HAVE BEEN?
WHO DO YOU THINK?
OH, NO.
IT WASN'T ME.
IT WAS YOU.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
SHUT UP.
DID YOU SEE ME?
SHUT UP!
IF YOU WEREN'T THERE, HOW
CAN YOU BE SO SURE IT WAS ME?
SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
YES, HI.
I'D LIKE TO CHECK ON THE
CONDITION OF ONE OF YOUR PATIENTS.
THE PATIENT'S NAME,
PLEASE?
DAVID KAMINSKY.
HE'S BEEN UPGRADED
TO STABLE.
OH, HE IS?
OH, THAT'S
WONDERFUL.
[BEEP]
OH, SHOOT. THAT'S
MY OTHER LINE.
HOLD ON--
ACTUALLY, WAIT.
JUST TELL ME,
WHAT TIME DO VISITING
HOURS START TOMORROW?
8 A.M.
GREAT. THANKS.
[BEEP]
HELLO?
[DR. EDWARDS]
MRS. GARRICK?
DR. EDWARDS, HI.
COULD YOU COME BY
MY OFFICE TOMORROW?
TOMORROW?
WELL , ACTUALLY I HAVE
A FULL CASELOAD,
AND I WAS GOING TO GO TO
THE HOSPITAL TO VISIT DAVID.
WELL, THIS
IS IMPORTANT.
WELL, IF THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG,
I'D LIKE
TO KNOW NOW.
WELL, I'D REALLY LIKE
TO DO THIS IN PERSON.
[SIGHS]
ALL RIGHT.
I SUPPOSE I CAN
REARRANGE A FEW THINGS
AND GO SEE DAVID
TOMORROW NIGHT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
STOP BY YOUR OFFICE
ON MY WAY TO WORK.
WILL YOU BE IN
THAT EARLY?
O.K. GOOD.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
GOOD NIGHT.
NOW YOU'VE DONE IT.
IF DAVID TELLS MOM
HE WAS PUSHED,
SHE'S GOING
TO HAVE ME PUT AWAY.
I COULD TALK TO HIM
FOR YOU.
ADMIT THAT
IT WAS ME, NOT YOU.
YOU'D DO THAT
FOR ME?
YOU'RE MY SISTER,
AREN'T YOU?
WE'RE FAMILY.
BUT HOW?
GIVE ME LIFE.
ME?
YOU HAVE
THE POWER, ZOE.
YOU ARE THE BLUE FAIRY.
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
CUT MY STRINGS.
YOU PROMISE TO BE GOOD?
I PROMISE.
I PROMISE!
[SNIP]
I'M FREE! FREE!
COME ON!
LET'S GO SEE DAVID.
[DOOR OPENS]
PINOCCHIO, WAIT FOR ME!
OVER HERE, ZOE!
THIS WAY!
PINOCCHIO?
PINOCCHIO, WHERE ARE YOU?
PINOCCHIO!
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[ALARM BEEPS]
[RING]
HELLO?
JENNIFER?
IT'S DAVID'S MOTHER.
MRS. KAMINSKY?
I'M GOING
TO BE THERE
AT VISITING HOURS
TOMORROW.
WHAT'S WRONG?
[SOBBING]
IT'S DAVID...HE'S GONE.
BUT I--I JUST CALLED
A FEW HOURS AGO.
THEY SAID
HE WAS STABILIZED.
IT WAS VERY SUDDEN.
THEY CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
HE'S GONE.
MY BABY.
[SOBBING]
OH, NO...
[JENNIFER SOBBING]
I OFTEN VIDEOTAPE
MY SESSIONS
TO DO A MORE THOROUGH
CASE STUDY LATER ON.
DURING YOUR
DAUGHTER'S LAST VISIT,
I WAS CALLED OUT OF THE
OFFICE FOR A FEW MINUTES.
[CLICK]
I HOPE
YOU'RE HAPPY.
NOW HE THINKS
I HURT DAVID.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
NO, I DON'T!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
SLAMMED THE DOOR IN HIS FACE.
WHO ELSE COULD IT
HAVE BEEN?
OH, NO.
IT WASN'T ME.
IT WAS YOU.
SHUT UP.
SHUT UP!
SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
I WANT YOUR PERMISSION
TO HAVE ZOE COMMITTED.
NO.
BUT SHE'S OBVIOUSLY DANGEROUS
TO HERSELF AS WELL AS OTHERS.
SPARE ME THE LECTURE,
DOCTOR.
I DEAL WITH DANGEROUS
PEOPLE EVERY DAY.
I KNOW WHAT EVIL
LOOKS LIKE.
I SEE IT IN THE EYES
OF MY CLIENTS,
AND I'M TELLING YOU,
I DON'T SEE IT
IN MY DAUGHTER!
NOBODY SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT EVIL,
BUT SHE'S A VERY
DISTURBED LITTLE GIRL.
SHE DIALED 911.
SHE SAVED DAVID'S LIFE,
FOR CHRIST'S SAKE!
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
HER COMMITTED,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
NOTIFY THE AUTHORITIES.
OF WHAT?
YOUR SUSPICIONS?
IF YOU BREACH ZOE'S
DOCTOR-PATIENT RELATIONSHIP
WITHOUT SOME VERY
STRONG, HARD EVIDENCE,
I WILL USE ALL
OF MY LEGAL RESOURCES
TO HAVE
YOUR LICENSE PULLED!
[DOOR SLAMS]
HI.
THERE'S SOME DINNER IN THE
OVEN IF YOU ARE HUNGRY.
HOW ARE YOU
HOLDING UP?
O.K.
WHERE'S ZOE?
WHAT?
ZOE. WHERE IS SHE?
ALREADY IN BED.
WHY?
IS SOMETHING
WRONG?
HOW DID THESE
GET MUDDY?
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S HOW THEY WERE
WHEN I FOUND THEM IN
ZOE'S ROOM THIS MORNING.
ZOE, WAKE UP.
WAKE UP.
HUH?
WHERE DID YOU GO
LAST NIGHT?
WHAT?
WHERE DID YOU GO
LAST NIGHT?
NOWHERE.
DON'T LIE TO ME.
YOUR SLIPPERS AND
JAMMIES ARE ALL MUDDY.
ALL RIGHT.
I WENT OUTSIDE.
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT?
WHY?
ZOE, WHY?
I WANTED TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL, O.K.?
TO SEE DAVID.
DID YOU?
NO. I COULDN'T FIND IT.
I GOT LOST,
SO I CAME HOME.
ARE YOU SURE?
ARE YOU SURE YOU DIDN'T
GO TO THE HOSPITAL?
NO. HONEST!
BUT I THINK PINOCCHIO DID.
THAT'S IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT I SHOULD HAVE
DONE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
DON'T YOU MOVE.
WAIT! WAIT!
BUT I--
DON'T PUSH ME, ZOE!
I HATE YOU!
I HATE YOU! I HATE YOU!
[DOOR CREAKS]
[KNIVES SCRAPING TOGETHER]
ZOE?
ZOE...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THIS, SWEETHEART?
HMM?
COME HERE.
I WAS PROTECTING YOU
FROM PINOCCHIO.
OH, SWEETHEART.
PINOCCHIO
CAN'T HURT ME.
HE CAN'T HURT
ANYBODY.
ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE
HIM BACK TO JAIL?
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU
MORE THAN ANYTHING
IN THE WHOLE
WIDE WORLD, DON'T YOU?
MM-HMM.
NO MATTER WHAT.
O.K.
OHH.
SOPHIA, ZOE'S NOT GOING
TO GO TO SCHOOL TODAY.
SO, IF YOU'D KEEP HER HOME
AND KEEP AN EYE ON HER?
IS SHE SICK?
MMM...I'M NOT SURE.
BUT I'M GOING
TO TALK TO BARRY
ABOUT WORKING OUT OF THE
HOUSE THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
OH, AND I'M GOING TO MAKE
ONE STOP AFTER WORK,
BUT I STILL
SHOULD BE HOME EARLY.
THANK YOU.
DO YOU BELIEVE
IN EVIL?
IT'S A JOB REQUIREMENT
IN MY BUSINESS.
RIGHT.
BUT DO YOU BELIEVE
IT CAN BE A...
YOU KNOW, A TANGIBLE,
NATURAL FORCE?
JENNIFER,
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
I THINK I KNOW WHO
GOTTO WAS PROTECTING.
HIS SON.
I THINK HE FOUND OUT
WHAT HIS SON WAS DOING,
AND HE STOPPED HIM THE
ONLY WAY HE KNEW HOW.
THAT'S WHY ALL THE MURDERS
STOPPED AFTER THAT NIGHT.
NOT BECAUSE
GOTTO WAS ARRESTED,
BUT BECAUSE THE REAL
KILLER WAS DEAD.
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
THAT A CHILD THAT YOUNG
IS CAPABLE
OF THAT MUCH EVIL?
THE SON OF SAM...
HE CLAIMED HIS NEIGHBOR'S
DOG TOLD HIM TO KILL.
AND THE GUY
IN THE TEXAS TOWER,
HE HEARD VOICES
IN HIS HEAD.
I MEAN, WE JUST ASSUME
THEY WERE INSANE,
BUT WHAT IF THEY REALLY
DID HEAR THOSE VOICES?
WHAT IF SOME KIND OF DEMON OR
EVIL FORCE WAS TALKING TO THEM,
MANIPULATING THEM,
MAKING THEM
INTO KILLERS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DO PERSONALLY
BELIEVE IN DEMONS.
BUT I'M NOT SO SURE THAT ONE
WOULD TAKE THE FORM OF A DOG.
WHY NOT?
WHY NOT A DOG...
OR A DISEMBODIED
VOICE...
OR A TELEVISION, OR...
A PUPPET?
[TURNS VACUUM OFF]
HOW ARE YOU DOING
TODAY, HONEY?
O.K.
CAN I HAVE
SOME JUICE?
SURE.
A LITTLE RESTLESS
TODAY?
I'M WORRIED
ABOUT PINOCCHIO.
I'M SURE YOUR MOM'S
TAKING GOOD CARE OF HIM.
NO. I'M WORRIED
HE MIGHT HURT HER.
THAT'S O.K.
HE'S GOT A CONSCIENCE
NOW, REMEMBER?
YOU FOUND IT
FOR HIM.
AAH!
ZOE?
ZOE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
AAH!
[THUNDER]
[VACUUM CLEANER ROARS]
OH, WHAT AM I DOING?
OH, MY GOD.
[CLATTERING]
[THUNDER]
ZOE...WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
ZOE, WAIT!
WAIT, PLEASE!
LET ME HELP YOU,
SWEETHEART! ZOE!
ZOE?
UNH!
[BARRY] EVIL COMES
IN ALL SHAPES AND SIZES.
[MICHAELS] DO YOU REALLY
BELIEVE A CHILD THAT YOUNG
IS CAPABLE
OF THAT MUCH EVIL?
[EDWARDS] SHE'S A VERY
DISTURBED LITTLE GIRL.
NO! JUST DON'T!
PLEASE!
IT'S O.K.!
I GOT THE POKER
AWAY FROM HIM,
BUT WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF
HERE BEFORE HE COMES BACK!
ZOE!
[FOOTSTEPS]
ZOE?
AAH!
DIE!
[SNARLING]
I'M GOING TO GET YOU!
STOP!
UNH!
LET ME IN!
OPEN THE DOOR!
LET ME IN,
YOU BITCH!
YOU HEAR ME?
AAH!
MOM, WHERE ARE YOU?
MOM! MOM!
ZOE, RUN!
GET OUT OF THE HOUSE!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[PINOCCHIO]
GOTCHA! AAH!
[CHILD LAUGHING]
[LAUGHTER]
[SNARLING]
AAH!
MOM, HELP ME!
[SOBBING]
ZOE...
[SNARLING]
AAH!
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
[SNARLING]
AAH!
HOW LONG WILL
SHE BE LIKE THIS?
HARD TO SAY.
WE'LL KEEP HER
CALM AND SEDATED
UNTIL SHE COMES AROUND.
SHE'S NOT DANGEROUS.
SHE KILLED YOUR NANNY
AND YOUR BOYFRIEND,
AND SHE ALMOST
KILLED YOU.
I KEEP TELLING YOU
IT WASN'T HER.
THE ROOM WAS DARK.
YOU WERE SUFFERING
FROM A SEVERE CONCUSSION.
I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
TELL ME SOMETHING...
DID YOU SEE THE PUPPET
MOVE BEFORE OR AFTER
YOU WERE HIT
IN THE HEAD?
I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
[SIGHS]
AND I'M GOING TO GET
MY DAUGHTER OUT OF HERE
NO MATTER
HOW LONG IT TAKES.
I HOPE NOT.
FOR YOUR SAKE...
[DOOR CLOSES]