( guitar music
playing )
( music stops )
( music resumes )
News anchor:
The situation on the ground
is ongoing
while the entire disputed area
remains closed
to news organizations.
As last night's
report of a series
of large explosions
awaits official
confirmation,
widespread fear of
a biological weapons launch
continues to spread
throughout the region.
( speaking Arabic )
Justine, what are you
seeing in the capital?
The Foreign Ministry
remains shuttered for
a second day
as evidence mounts
that the insurgents
may have used
at least some part
of their long-rumored
biological weapons
stockpile
in the course
of last night's incursion.
News anchor:
Have you been able
to get any word yet
on the government's
response?
- ( guitar music playing )
- Well, it's hard to find
any officials
here at all in
the capital, Mark.
But those who are willing
to speak off the record
confirm the regime's
plan for a massive
retaliation
in the next five
to seven days.
Well, while we are trying
to restore that image,
ITL News
has just obtained
amateur video footage
purporting to show
casualties
from last night's exchange
of missile fire.
A warning--
this footage contains images
that may be disturbing
to some viewers.
Obtained from a junior
military officer
fleeing the site
of last night's clashes,
it seems to belie
assurances from both sides
of the conflict
-  that no chemical
or biological weapons...
- Damn it.
...have been deployed.
Such images
are horrifying enough,
but there's an even more
horrific scenario
if the contagion spreads
beyond the region,
potentially
infecting tens...
if not hundreds
of thousands.
- They're saying--
- Look, I'm...
if you want,
I'm just gonna go
to the guitar shop.
The pickup
fried out, so...
They can't just
keep fighting, right?
Female reporter:
We are now going live
to a press conference
at the Centers
for Disease Control.
Man:
As of 8:00 a.m.
Eastern Standard Time,
the CDC has not measured
any airborne contaminants
beyond a 100-mile radius
of last night's advance
in the Middle East.
What this--
what this means
is the continental
United States has not
and will not be affected
by the reported use
of these pathogens.
Female reporter #2:
Steven, the situation
in the larger cities
near the epicenter
of the conflict
remains tense
as persistent rumors
of mass deaths
in scores of towns and villages
gain credibility.
At least three
regional governments
have begun issuing
gas masks...
Male reporter:
Rumors abound in the capital
as the prime minister
and his cabinet depart
the city...
( speaking Arabic )
Translator:
This is simply a precaution
in order for us
to maintain
government function...
Female reporter #3:
Meanwhile, a veritable
exodus of refugees
continues to stream
across regional borders,
desperately seeking safety
from a threat
that remains,
perhaps intentionally,
undefined.
Male reporter #2:
In Washington, the president
has issued a statement
urging calm
and affirming
that no known pathogen
poses any threat...
News anchor:
The trade winds
are spreading the pathogen
well beyond
the conflict's borders,
confirming
officials' worst fears
about the airborne virus.
Reports of mass casualties
as far north as Italy
and Portugal
are pending confirmation.
Female reporter #4:
What we're apparently
seeing here is a virus,
or a complex of viruses,
killing some almost
immediately,
while leaving others
fully mobile.
However, within hours,
nobody in the affected area
remains alive.
Stay tuned, please,
for further developments
on this breaking
news story.
- ( guitar music playing )
- Man: That pickup's all right.
But when I move around--
( strumming )
--it doesn't have that punch
and it's just fading out a lot.
- Clerk: Don't worry...
- Man: All right, so...
( strumming guitar )
Okay, cool. Thanks, man.
( faint rumbling,
screaming )
He says
it's gonna be,
like, an hour.
There's something...
- I am so hungry.
- Oh.
Woman:
I don't even know why
we're fighting this thing.
- Man: It was
the fucking dishes.
- Woman: Yes!
You guys have maids,
you know?
So it's not like
you see a dirty dish
and you're like,
"Hey, here's a dirty dish.
I've got to do something
about it.
I'm gonna wash
this dirty dish."
- You're-- ( laughs )
-  What are you-- I mean--
You're totally
fixated on this.
It's not the dish.
-  I'm not even talking
about the dish anymore.
- It's a metaphor.
- Yeah, it's a metaphor--
- I know what you're gonna say.
- No, you don't.
-  The dish is a metaphor
for my anxiety about
how different we are.
- ( laughing )
- What?
- You did know.
- Well, of course
I knew.
- So, fuck it.
- Just wash the dish.
- Just metaphor the metaphor.
- Just address my anxieties
with dishwashing liquid.
( chuckles )
We'd miss this
if we ever lost it.
We'd be like, "I wish
we could go back
to when the worst thing
we had to worry about
was the dishes."
Woman #2:
Hey.
Oh, my God. You guys,
congratulations!
Let me see.
Oh, my God.
That is
so adorable.
So what's going on
with this shit
in the news?
( sighs )
- Honestly,
I'm not watching it.
- Don't know, right?
- Nothing's changed.
- Woman: I am going to
go to the bathroom.
Oh.
Ahem.
( woman #2 giggling )
( car horns honking )
News anchor:
Although state and county
authorities
have been almost unanimous
in urging residents
to remain calm,
a spreading, seemingly
spontaneous exodus along
the Eastern Seaboard
has caused state highway
patrol officials
to shut down six
major northbound arteries,
piecing together--
( water running )
( distant siren
wailing )
( car horns honking )
Traffic's insane
out there.
Did you guys
eat my food?
I got you this.
( faint sirens
wailing )
( dishes clattering )
Anna, why have you
been so freaked out
lately?
So, what, I'm not
allowed to talk to any girl
I've ever slept with?
Are you gonna go crazy?
Is that it?
( dish clatters )
No, it's
the exact opposite.
I think you should talk
to all the people
you want to--
any girl
you've ever met,
whenever they call,
whenever they stop by,
whenever you
bump into them.
Yeah, I think
you should take
as many opportunities
as possible to talk
to them.
( mutters )
Jesus, Anna.
Because, God,
there is so much time,
isn't there?
There is so much time
between all the dishes
lying around,
the fucked-up amps,
the fried-out pickups,
your rich grandparents...
and your boring,
stupid ex-girlfriends
coming to the "Gates
of fucking India"?
You know?
Because
between all that,
there's so much
time for...
laying
in the bathtub...
and reading
the soap bottle...
( sniffles )
and looking out together,
up at the leaves...
and holding each other,
because we're both
so happy
that we're actually
scared.
( sniffles )
Because if it
really is all over--
Erik, if it was
just us,
and there really was
nothing left on Earth--
( Erik strumming softly )
What are you doing?
No, Anna, Anna,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's the song.
That--
that is the song.
Those are the lyrics
to our song.
That's it.
It's gonna be
beautiful.
( crying )
Male newscaster:
No one is willing
to confirm or deny
what we're seeing here.
It clearly isn't benign.
Even at this distance, David,
I've got to admit, I'm scared.
Male reporter:
We're getting unconfirmed
reports of rioting
at dozens of airports
as all domestic
and international flights
remain grounded.
Male newscaster #2:
Hundreds of thousands
of people are now running
through the streets here
seeking any kind of shelter.
Female reporter:
The president and his cabinet
have been evacuated
to an undisclosed
location
while assuring
local authorities...
Female newscaster:
...as yet another
American city reports
an almost unbelievable
casualty rate...
I, the Lord, have held
My peace a long time...
Male reporter #2:
Just in the last several
minutes, it's really--
oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Female reporter #2:
We are no longer
receiving reports
from the following cities
and municipalities--
Boston and the Boston
metropolitan area,
- Bridgeport and the...
- Male reporter #3:
Philadelphia...
- Male newscaster #3:
Baltimore...
- "Then the fifth angel
poured out his bowel
on the throne of the beast,
and His kingdom became
full of darkness
and they gnawed
their tongues because
of the pain..."
- Woman: Jesus Christ!
- Man: Oh, my God.
- Man #2: Oh, my God.
- "They shall become
refuse on the ground."
( buzzing )
( tone beeping )
( static hissing )
Announcer:
The following is a bulletin
from the Emergency
Management Agency.
If concentrations
in your area have exceeded
80 parts per billion,
you must
take immediate shelter
and remain where you are
for a minimum
of eight days.
State authorities
will continue to broadcast
hourly updates
as long as emergency networks
remain operational.
( birds chirping )
What does that even mean,
"parts per billion"?
Per billion what?
Per billion
of whatever else
was out there, I guess.
It's a beautiful day.
Not a cloud
in the sky.
( sighs )
We could read
something.
Sure.
( sniffs, exhales )
Remember this?
Oh, that.
That was a moment
of weakness.
Well, at least we're not
going to get divorced now.
It's so
clear out, baby.
The birds up there,
they're just flying
around.
It's too bad
we aren't birds.
I wonder what
they're feeling.
Like their favorite
TV show got canceled.
( laughs )
I could talk to you
for another 20 years.
( scoffs )
Aw, shut up.
I mean it.
I was just thinking it
the other day.
( sniffles )
I just realized that--
that you're my wife.
It took me practically
till just now
to really believe it.
( gas hissing )
( faint rattling )
We're going to have
to go to Children's.
- What?
- ( groans )
There are no more
canisters here.
( breathing heavily )
We're going to have to go
to Children's Hospital.
Okay.
( breath hissing )
- Woman: Oh, my God.
- Man: Don't look.
Woman: Oh, God.
That looks like...
that sweet nurse
in Cardiology.
Man:
Sarah. Her name was Sarah.
Sarah.
( sniffles )
( praying in Hebrew )
( yelling, wailing )
( monitor beeping )
Sarah?
Sarah. Sarah.
- Mr. Sachs, I--
- Wait a minute.
Look, I know
you're busy, but I
need a favor from you.
It's for my wife.
She's in there waiting
to see Dr. Henderson.
They took her
off life support.
They took her out of ICU.
We're just waiting, Sarah.
Well, we have
an emergency--
Well, this is
an emergency!
You understand?!
This is an
emergency, Sarah!
She's dying!
And the doctor's
just taken a three-hour
coffee break.
- Mr. Sachs--
- I'm sorry.
I know you're
a good person.
Esther and I really
think of you
as someone close to us,
like you're really family.
Please,
I'm begging you.
Just come with me.
Help me. Help me
get her to ICU.
Come on.
I'm not sure I'm going
to be able to do that.
We have an emergency--
Mr. Sachs?
- ( groans )
- Mr. Sachs!
Jacob! Get me
an oxygen unit.
Jacob, get me
an oxygen unit, now.
Yes, right.
( gasping )
Sarah:
Mr. Sachs? Lift your
head up for me.
( wheezing, coughing )
Try to breathe normally.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- I've gotta go.
- Wait, wait.
Listen to me.
It's a biological
attack.
- Isn't it?
- They don't know.
People can't breathe--
old people...
kids...
animals are okay.
We only have
about three hours--
( inhales deeply )
It has to do with
how much material
is in the air.
And winds and...
if it gets up to more
than 35 parts per billion,
you're going to need
one of these to survive, Sarah.
Now listen to me. Listen.
You got to get one.
Not a charcoal filter.
Pure oxygen.
You'll be able to last
eight days. Okay?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
- ( inhales deeply )
- Woman: Nurse!
I have to go!
( oxygen hissing )
"Connect me
to something.
Give me something,"
I said. You know?
"Give me something,
Counsel.
Give me something
that connects my client
eating baba ghanoush
at some
streetside cafe
somewhere in...
do we even know where
this was taken, Tracy?"
And then Tracy said...
And then I said,
"No, the prosecution
just gave us Exhibit 345,
defendants Hightower,
Esselen, and Sachs
and 'unidentified man.'
1979."
"So, please.
Help me out here,"
I said, looking
sort of baffled.
"Give me whatever
it is you're hanging
your case on
so that I can
defend my client.
But don't keep giving me
exhibit after exhibit,
so-called 'fact'
after so-called 'fact'
that doesn't add up
to A-- trade secrets,
B-- any of your employees
actually compromising
your trade secrets,
or C--
any material damages
done to your company's
overseas interests,
because if opposing
counsel doesn't
or can't,
or for whatever reason,
they won't...
Your Honor,
I respectfully request
that you
dismiss the case
against my client."
And the judge
dismissed it.
( footsteps approaching,
knock on door )
Woman:
You guys? We're...
we're evacuating
the building.
Reporter:
...the news,
then a proliferation
of rumors and hearsay,
and then almost street
by street...
Man on recording:
Hey, man. Leave a message
and I'll get back to you.
( beeps )
Hey, man. I'm leaving
a message, dude.
Did you--
if you're watching TV,
- there's a...
- ( people screaming )
anyway, turn on the TV.
It has something to do
with the war.
We're supposed to...
( sighs )
Reporter:
...conflicting reports
of trade winds...
So, um...
meet me
back at the house.
And...
please change
your outgoing message,
though, baby.
Seriously.
Reporter:
...but efforts
to keep citizens calm
and encourage them
to maintain their normal...
- ( phone buzzing )
- Man: I'm gonna take you
left, then right--
-  Ah!
- Man #2: Busted!
- ( buzzing )
- ...surprise myself!
Ah!
Take it back
right here.
And then I'm gonna
score again.
( both laughing )
Perfect defense.
Oh, yeah!
That's game, baby!
- No, no, no.
- That's game.
No.
( panting )
Okay, so here's
the deal.
If I sink this,
right here,
you let me
pay you back.
You don't owe me
anything, man.
You see,
that's exactly
the kind of talk
that won't be allowed
if I make this shot.
What happens
if you miss?
Uh...
You know, this is
really gonna determine
my inner morality.
If I miss,
then you never have
to hear about it again.
How's that?
Okay?
Borrowed your Jeep,
fucked up the transmission,
we're square.
But if I make it,
you accept the cash.
( sighs )
All right,
I'll trust your
subconscious.
You hear that,
Rick's subconscious?
You don't really
want him to make
this shot, do ya?
- ( chuckles )
- Make him miss.
You're just--
you're gonna stand
right there?
You never
said anything about
where I could stand.
- Okay. Okay.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
It doesn't really matter.
That doesn't bother me.
- 'Cause you know why?
- Why?
'Cause I got it
like that.
( laughing )
Man #2:
I give up.
( elevator bell dings )
Nice work
on the Sachs case.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
Home.
That's it?
That's it.
( sighs )
Whatever.
Let's not end this
on a bad note.
You're
a wonderful guy,
and who knows what
would have happened
if we had met before.
But it was never
a question.
There was
in my mind.
I'm sorry.
( sighs )
It's the end
of the world.
If it really is
the end of the world,
how funny, you know?
For once,
it really would be
when it feels that way.
- How romantic.
-  ( elevator bell dings )
- ( car engines start )
- ( car remote chirps )
Woman on phone:
Anyway, turn on the TV.
It has something to do
with the war.
Meet me
back at the house
and please change
your outgoing message,
though, baby.
- Come on, come on.
Let's go.
- Seriously.
I'm starting
to tighten up
a little bit.
Let's go.
What?
She told me
to turn on the TV.
- She wants me
to meet her at home.  - Now?
Yeah.
- So you're--?
- Sorry, man.
You know what, man?
You are so fuckin' whipped.
Hey, I canceled
a lot of shit for this
so we can
just hang out.
Yeah?
Like what?
Coffee at Saga?
Tarot card
reading?
- Yeah.
- I'll see you
on Thursday.
- You gotta be kiddin' me.
- I'll see you Thursday, man.
Yeah, fuck you,
motherfucker.
- Thursday.
- If you're lucky.
( distant siren wailing )
God damn it.
Erik:
Hey.
I finished the song.
I have an idea.
Why don't we
take a nap,
just forget
about everything?
-  ( distant siren wails )
- Listen to this.
"The souls
of all my dears
have flown
to the stars.
Thank God
there's no one left
for me to lose."
Hm.
You know what
your grandmother
said to me?
Mm.
She said...
that "the only
important language
spoken in the world
is spoken between
a man and a woman.
In bed."
( chuckles )
I don't know.
Maybe you want
to watch the news?
- Nuh-uh.
- Or write
some more poetry?
No.
You know what?
We should probably
get up and do the dishes.
No, I don't think so.
( giggling )
( faint ringing )
( Anna moans )
( ringing stops )
( couple
grunting softly )
And so, finally--
eight years later
or whatever--
at some
New Year's Eve party,
Grandpa finally
got up the courage
and he kissed her.
At least,
that's how my mom
used to tell it.
( engine stops )
They're gonna love you.
Seriously.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not
worried, baby.
( door closes )
( distant bird
cooing )
( knocking on door )
- Hello!
- Anna: Hi!
- Hi!
I'm so glad
to meet you.
I'm so happy
to meet you, too.
Yes! Goodness!
Ooh!
- ( Anna chuckles )
- Someone did very well.
This is a beautiful ring.
- Erik: That's right.
- Anna: He did very great.
How are you,
sweetheart?
Men are so
much like kids,
it's silly.
I mean, there's
the guitar
and there's
the garden
and there's basketball
and football--
it's a wonder
they have any time
at all
to devote themselves
to other responsibilities
for family.
But they do.
They do.
- Yeah.
- Bless 'em.
You know.
I'm gonna have to
sit down, I think.
- I just got a little pooped.
- Yeah, sure.
What you've gotta watch,
of course, is when you
breed something
more and more
specialized,
it can only survive
under very narrow
and specific conditions.
- ( groans )
- Erik: Here.
Thank you.
- Got something for you.
- No, Grandpa, I'm fine.
- No, no, no.
- I'm fine.
No, no, you can't
refuse me.
You just can't.
I'm not gonna take no
for an answer,
- so you might as well
just stop.
- Okay.
And I wanna tell you
something--
man to man, okay?
No matter how much
a woman may tell you
that she's happy
to support you,
that she's not interested
in material things,
she wants you
to be free--
sooner or later,
they all want the
good things in life.
- I know, I know.
But Anna isn't like that.
- Well, I'm sure she's not.
I'm not telling you
that she's shallow.
Probably is the most
natural, basic instinct
in a woman--
actually,
any human being--
make a home,
make a nest.
You know, I'm playing
a show at this thing.
It's called
"South by Southwest."
And you know
there's a lot of...
record company people,
and managers go.
That's wonderful.
- I can make a living
playing music.
- I'm sure you can.
And I'm sure you'll
figure it out.
Don't let anybody
pressure you, huh?
Just take
your time.
If there's anything
ever I can do
to help you,
you know I'm here.
So funny--
I was just thinking
this morning
that, God,
I have turned into
such a typical "girl."
( chuckles )
I never thought
it would happen to me,
but I--
oh, God--
I am completely
obsessed with him.
Beyond obsessed
with him.
I mean, even when
I'm angry or jealous
or, I don't know--
maybe that's the same thing--
but he leaves for an hour
and I can't stand it.
I don't know
what to do with myself.
I feel
kind of crazy and--
( sighs )
that can't be healthy.
Well, I'm not sure
it's healthy,
but it is
the way it is.
- Yeah.
- Anna: Yeah?
And I'll tell you
something else.
You'd be someplace--
at a party
or a friend's house
or something--
and he'll be over there
talking to somebody.
And you see his face.
And you think,
"He and I
are going to make
some beautiful babies."
- Cheers.
( cups clink )
You know what?
I don't think
I can take this.
No, no. I told you
I'm not taking no
for an answer.
- No, Grandpa, I can't.
- Oh, Erik, come on.
I got it, you need it.
- What's the difference?
- I always appreciate--
I am not
taking it back.
That's final.
( rips )
- I'm sorry.
- Idiot.
You're too good
for my dirty money?
You think there wouldn't
be such a thing as war
if it wasn't for me?
I got news for you, kid.
There are worse sinners
on this earth
- than your grandfather.
- No, no, no. I don't--
Wait till you have
a child!
a sick child!
Then you'll lecture me.
Attorney:
And if you have any trouble
at all remembering
or if you aren't sure
of your answer,
just say,
"I don't remember,"
or, "I don't have
any specific recollection."
Now, that last one
actually covers
quite a lot.
If, for instance,
you "sort of" think you
might remember something,
but it's possible
that you aren't
remembering it clearly,
it's never perjury
to say, "I don't have
any specific recollection."
They were developing
a pathogen.
I know, Mr. Sachs.
But the prosecution
won't be asking
about that tonight.
It wasn't even
my division.
I offered advice
to my clients
on pharmaceutical
lines.
Okay.
We have
about 15 minutes
until opening
statements.
They just offered me
so much money.
So much.
Millions.
Okay. Mr. Sachs,
look at me.
This trial is not
about how
certain governments
got a hold of
certain weapons
or formulas
for weapons
over 30
years ago.
This trial deals with
the very narrow issue
of whether or not
you violated your contract
with Sichel Systems
by revealing trade secrets,
and you didn't
do that.
You didn't
break the terms
of your contract.
You're innocent.
Have you had
a child?
- No.
- You can't
watch them die.
She lived
another 15 years
and she gave us
our grandson, Erik.
But the prosecution
doesn't need to know
that, do they?
I took it.
I took the money.
I knew
it was wrong,
but I took it.
My wife is living
in denial,
but I know
it's my fault.
I deserve
to be punished.
We really need
to leave, Mr. Sachs.
Esther:
Oh, my God.
Oh-- it's too far.
Sachs:
We'll get there,
we'll get there.
Hold on.
If we can find some more
canisters up there,
it's gonna get us
eight days of air,
and the poison
will be gone.
( Esther sighs )
To think
I was so scared
about having
that operation.
And Dr. Henderson
died--
Esther, if you're
going to go through
all the ironies
of the situation,
we're going to be talking
another 20 years.
You know that?
I won't say a word.
I don't ever want
to say anything.
What?
What did you say?
Excuse me?
You don't want
to say anything?
Huh?
You don't wanna
say anything...
about my pants?
Something
They're too high.
( chuckles )
Okay, here we go.
Sarah:
Have you been
looking for a job?
Man:
Yeah, I've been
looking for a job.
I print out another
175,000 resumes,
I change my profile
on another million
job sites.
- I mean, the thing is--
- I even call Human Resources.
I swear to God,
I feel like "Willy Loman."
I said...
( sighs )
"If anything comes up,
do me a favor.
Keep my number.
Give me a call."
I mean, you were
getting plenty of work
when you were putting her
through law school.
Yeah. People
used to hire writers.
You can get
any job you want.
Yeah.
One more job.
Pay some bills.
Buy some stuff,
get another job,
pay some more bills,
buy some more stuff--
Yeah, but it's that
or what?
Play basketball
with your buddies all day
and let Mia
buy your shirts?
You know what's
interesting to me,
is that why--
instead of printing
a bunch of resumes,
why we all don't
just stop
in the middle of
the street and say...
"What the hell
is going on here?
What is this
all about?"
I mean, why am I
here on this earth,
you know?
- Oh, Len--
- No, I mean it.
I mean it.
Why does the universe
expand for eternity?
Wh-why--
( stammers )
how much longer
am I gonna live?
Why am I the only
animal that knows
it's gonna die?
We all asked ourselves
those questions
when we were, like,
eight.
Yeah, but why
did we stop asking,
you know?
'Cause I never
got any answers.
( distant phone
ringing )
Is this
about the war?
( sighs )
This is about what
I'm supposed to be doing
with my life.
I just don't know
what I'm supposed
to tell Dad.
Oh, God, Sarah.
Tell him I'm happy.
I mean, you tell me--
X-ray vision--
am I horribly
depressed?
Len:
You know what I just
realized the other day?
We're at some party
at Mia's office
and we'd
just gotten in
some stupid fight
and we're outside
in the parking lot.
And I just
realized that...
she's my wife.
And I love her.
I mean,
I really love her.
She married me...
so I can't really be
that depressed, can I?
God.
I hope I meet someone
like you someday.
- Except with a job.
( chuckles )
( engine knocking )
( engine stops )
Come on.
( key rattling )
( engine sputters )
- ( rattling )
- Come on!
( distant siren whines )
( mutters )
Fuck.
Shit.
( car horns honking )
( honking continues )
( ringing )
( tires screeching,
sharp thump )
( faint ringing )
Mia?
Sarah, what the fuck
is going on?
Listen--
they're not telling
the whole story on the news.
Well, I haven't seen the news.
What's going on?
Just ignore
what everybody's saying.
You have to get back
to the house.
Get out your dehumidifiers
and ionizers--
anything you have
that filters air--
and seal yourself
into the basement.
( panting )
What-- what is it?
Is this the war?
Just listen.
Remember how we put
Mom's oxygen tanks
up in the attic?
Yeah.
I got rid of those
months ago, Sarah.
( sighs )
Damn.
Well, just stay down there
as long as you can.
Len:
I'm starting
to freak out here, Sarah.
What's going on?
How do you know all this?
Because I-- I met
someone who knows
about this,
- and I--
- Hey, Sarah?
Sarah, listen to me,
okay?
What the fuck?
Hold on a second.
I gotta give you
a call back, okay?
I'm gonna call you back.
- Len: Stay safe.
- ( handset clatters )
Recording:
Attention, please.
There has been
an emergency reported
in the building.
- ( Sarah moans )
- Leave the building
immediately
using marked stairways
and exits.
Do not use elevators.
Hey, buddy.
Do you know
where your mommy
and daddy are?
You okay?
Recording:
...using marked stairways
and exits.
Do not use elevators.
( sighs )
- ( groans )
- Attention, please.
Attention, please.
There has been
an emergency reported
in the building.
Leave the building
immediately
using marked stairways...
It hurts.
( sobs )
What hurts?
My tummy.
Where does it hurt?
Hmm?
It--
( gulps )
Okay, okay, buddy.
Okay.
-  ( distant siren wails )
- Uh...
we're gonna...
Man:
What the fuck
are you doing?
- Len: Hey--
- Get the fuck away
from my boy!
Hey, man, it's okay.
Your kid is not doing--
hey, whoa!
Hey, hey--
hey, listen!
Jesus Christ!
Hey, listen, man!
- Len: Listen!
- Fuck you--
- Daddy!
- Damn it! Listen!
( grunting )
Listen!
Jesus Christ, man!
Stop!
Listen to me.
Take care
of your son!
( distant police sirens
wailing )
( distant sirens
whining )
- ( music playing )
- ( laughter )
Hey, do you have
any Goldfish?
- Girl: Um...
- Anna: Yes, Goldfish.
Maybe up there.
Thanks.
Uh...?
( laughing )
Anna:
Wow.
Do you think
that they
stuffed everything up
like that for the party?
No, I think that is
just how they keep
their things.
- Erik: You know what's
weird about that?
- Anna: What?
- Oh, shh-- Oreos.
- ( Anna gasps )
- Look at this.
- Anna: Mmm.
- Mmm.
- Mmm, mmm.
( laughing )
- Yummy, yummy.
- ( laughing )
What's...
- what's weird?
- Huh?
- What's weird about it?
- What's weird, what's weird.
- You said--
- It was...
I don't know.
It's just weird--
ever since
we got engaged,
there's suddenly
like all these--
I don't know,
these waves that we--
No.
I know exactly
what you mean.
There's, like,
a right way
and a wrong way of
doing everything,
and we're, like--
You know why?
It's 'cause we're, like,
we are like,
the Anna and Erik tribe.
You know?
And I mean
there's something
terribly wrong
about putting the--
look, the cat food
next to the tea.
Yeah, but for
the Jprobably the way
Henry we stack things
and put things
together really neatly
seems completely insane
and constricting.
- Right?
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean it already
feels so wrong
to do it any other way
than the way we do it.
Right, but that
is how it begins,
you know?
That is why countries
invade each other--
'cause of that.
( giggling )
"You don't put
the tea in the
right place."
Yeah? Fuck you!
Fuck you, you're
the bad guys.
You have no idea
how to do it,
and we're better.
"You know what?
The green tea
goes on the top shelf
next to the cocoa,
fuckwad, or I'm
gonna kill you."
( laughing )
The beginning
of civilization.
I'm sorry.
I have got to
move this.
No, I mean,
it so doesn't
belong there.
There is something
immoral about it.
We'd be hypocrites
if we fail that.
Future generations
will thank us.
The products of
this apartment will
cry out for liberation.
It will be a beacon
of proper shelf
arrangement
- for the entire region.
- ( clattering )
( giggling )
Oh, my God.
So good.
Anna:
I can't find
the Goldfish.
( giggling )
He was up there.
God.
( music fades )
( faint screaming )
( car horns
honking )
( wind rustling )
( birds chirping )
( crows cawing )
I hear you.
( faint echo )
( wind rustling,
birds chirping )
( chirping continues )
( wings fluttering )
( rustling, crunching )
( birds chirping )
( footsteps approaching )
Hi.
- Was I talking
to myself?
- No.
I've been feeling
so weird these
past few days.
You know...
I see stuff.
Out of the corner
of my eye sometimes.
I don't even
tell my boyfriend--
my fiancé.
And these
past few days, I...
I mean literally,
last night,
for a second,
it was like there was
nobody left anywhere...
...except animals.
Running down the middle
of the street.
( sniffles )
God, and Erik was like,
"What?
What are you
staring at?"
You didn't say?
They say
schizophrenia starts
when you're, like,
19 to 25.
Rick:
You hear voices?
Well, I just heard
a bunch of crows
screaming
"War! War!"
( chuckles )
Well, they aren't
telling you
to jump off any
high buildings, right?
No.
Good.
My name
is Rick.
I'm Anna.
I've considered
the high
building option.
But life is so
absurdly short,
anyway.
Yeah, I've been
thinking that.
Makes you only want to do
the important things.
But what are
the important things?
I'm pregnant.
First time
I've told anybody.
- Woman: Greyhound.
- Erik: You got it.
Vodka
and grapefruit.
Erik:
Here you go.
Thank you.
You don't know
what a Greyhound is?
Hey, who got us
this job?
So, anyway,
all I'm saying
is marriage
is just
all of these
artificial
restrictions.
It's like going on
some radical diet
when you're
not even fat.
All I'm saying is,
yes,
agreed,
congratulations
Anna is hot.
She's incredibly hot.
And, granted, you're
probably not going to
meet anybody
who's that hot
and whatever cool
and interesting
and wonderful.
Mia:
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You're making
a scene.
Well, what is he
looking at, then?
Right now he's
looking at you.
Having dragged me across
the room and yelling at me
- in front of
all my coworkers--
- I'm not yelling at you.
Can I get a
vodka and tonic?
Brilliant, that's
exactly right.
- Yeah.
- Fucking more alcohol
because that's really
going to help.
Thank you.
See? He probably
thought he was marrying
the most magical,
beautiful girl
on earth.
It's up to you, man.
I'm just saying
you could be dealing
with that kind of shit
for the rest
of your life.
Or I could spend the rest
of my life saying,
"I met the one
true love of my life
when I was 22 years old
and I was too scared
- to ask her to marry me."
- If she is the one true
love of your life.
I mean, there are
billions of people.
( voices overlapping )
No, she's--
she's the one
true love of my life.
( chuckles softly )
Okay.
So you have the rest
of your life
to ask her
to marry you.
( mutters )
Fuck.
( exhales sharply )
It happens
every time.
I get dressed up
to come to a thing
like this,
and it's
a fucking disaster.
( sniffles )
( faint buoy bells
ringing )
Len,
none of these people
matter to me.
None of these people
mean anything to me
except you.
( sighs )
Let's get out
of here.
( both panting )
Len:
Ah, fuck.
( sighs sharply )
Oh, God
I need water.
Water.
( mutters )
Done.
What's this?
I got it
at the museum.
( bottle lid clanking )
It's a trilobite.
It's probably like
300 million years old.
And now they
just give them away
with a $50 membership.
( laughs )
There used to be
billions of 'em.
They must have had
a lot of sex.
They couldn't
help themselves.
( laughs )
They were in love.
Or it was
just instinct.
( laughs )
Same thing,
I guess.
I'd have babies
with you.
I mean, not right
away, but...
we should,
you know?
( sighs deeply )
( scoffs )
What?
I never said never.
I said, "Don't
marry me if you want
to have children."
- ( laughs )
- But you would?
I could.
Yeah, I would.
We should.
- Mia: Right?
- Len: Right.
Think of how beautiful
it would be.
"It"?
She. She.
Okay. We will.
You promise?
Not right away.
But someday.
Promise.
( key chain rattling )
( police siren wailing )
( key rattling )
Mia?!
( rapid thumping )
Mia:
There you go.
( both sigh )
- ( door bangs )
- ( sirens continue )
Len:
It's okay.
( car door closes,
faint tires screeching )
Come here.
So we need to--
I need you
to get everything
out of the kitchen
that you can, okay?
I need you to just get
everything that you can.
Okay?
I'm going to go upstairs
and get some blankets.
Okay?
Gonna bring it down
to the basement.
Okay? Yeah?
Sure.
Okay.
Announcer:
The following message
is transmitted
at the request
of the United States
government.
This is not a test.
All residents of the
United States
are strongly encouraged
to establish--
Len:
Gonna need
some more tape.
We've gotta seal
all the windows up here,
we've gotta
seal the door.
Mia:
Does creme soda
count as water?
What?
- ( cracking )
- ( Mia yelps )
- Len: Come on, sweetheart.
- I'll just get that, okay?
Let's get everything
downstairs.
It's all diet food.
It's all fucking...
low carb crap.
All of it.
It's okay,
sweetheart.
Hey, look--
I have a chocolate bar
in my pocket, okay?
With almonds,
okay?
Go back
downstairs.
Okay?
Go back
downstairs.
- Come on, sweetie.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Len:
I got it.
Do you need
this tape?
- Len: Nope.
- Okay.
Mia:
Did you call Sarah?
( sighs )
Mm-hmm.
You okay down there,
sweetheart?
( Sachs grunting )
( grunting )
Ooh.
Andy, it's...
it's time
to stop.
I thought
you didn't want
to talk anymore.
( groans )
Esther:
I just don't
want to sit here
watching you
kill yourself.
Sachs:
We'll get there.
You see?
If we can just
make it up there,
we're gonna find
some more canisters,
I know it.
Stop that, Esther.
Stop it, come on.
Take your hand--
( grunts )
- ( Esther moans )
- Sachs: --Take your
hand off the wheel.
( Esther grunts )
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
but look.
I've gotta--
we can't afford
the energy it takes
to fight like this.
( moans )
I wish-- I wish
you would put
more energy into
finding solutions.
There are no
solutions, honey.
The news broadcasts
have stopped,
and...
everybody
that we love is dead.
Listen to me.
Everyone I love
is not dead.
The only person
on earth that I love
is still alive.
Oh, you're such
a charmer.
You could
charm the knickers
off of any girl.
Well, there's no
girls left
but my girl.
( sniffles )
Okay.
Here we go.
( grunts )
( plane engines
whining )
Anna:
I can't stand how much
I miss you when I'm gone.
Erik:
I know.
Anna:
Oh-- so, I got
a new book
that I really
want to read to you.
Erik:
Okay.
Anna:
Wait, I don't know
which one to read to you.
Anna:
Wow, that song
is really good.
- Erik: Yeah, you know, I--
- Anna: Let me just
read you one.
What-- you don't
have to stop.
- ( laughs )
- I know, I know.
I mean,
I just, I just--
I just wanted to
show you something.
In the park.
I want your opinion
on something
that they're building
across the river.
Uh, what,
before we go home?
Yeah, yeah.
It's just been
bugging me. I pass it
every day on my run,
you know.
Right.
So do you want
to look at it?
Uh, sure.
You don't want
to hear this?
No, no.
Read it to me,
read it to me.
Ahem.
"At the red towers
of your native Sodom,
the square where
once you sang,
the spinning shed,
at the empty windows
set into the house,
where sons and daughters
blessed your marriage bed.
A single glance,
a sudden dart of pain
stitching her eyes
before she made a sound.
Her body flaked
into transparent salt.
Her swift legs
rooted to the ground."
Right?
That's--
that's incredible.
- You're so distracted.
- No, I'm not. I liked it.
No, you have no idea
what I just read to you.
Not no idea.
Come on.
Hey.
"Dilute."
( straining )
"Dilute. Dilute!"
Dilute. Okay.
Come on.
Let's go see your
weird-ass building.
( Anna laughs )
( ship horn blowing )
Erik:
Okay. Uh...
this looks right.
See that...
that big red building
with the arches?
It's that.
- Anna: Oh.
- Right next to it
with the...
The water tower,
just right under that,
there's like this cluster
of red buildings.
Anna:
That red garage-
looking thing?
- Erik: Yeah.
- I can't really see it.
- Anna: Is it next to the--
- Erik: Yeah.
What am I
looking at?
( shuddering )
Hey!
I have to give this
to you now.
Oh, my God.
What does that mean?
What does that...
is that a "yes"?
You have to say yes
if you're gonna--
( sobs )
- You still
need to say "yes."
- ( Anna laughs )
I love you.
I love you
so much.
- ( Anna laughing )
- Erik: Say yes.
You need to say yes.
Please.
Anna:
Look at you.
♪ You love me...
( giggles )
( grunts )
Esther:
Well, what do you
think of our news?
- What news?
- Our news.
Erik and Anna.
Oh, that's fine.
( grunts )
Oh, honey. You don't
dislike Anna, do you?
I think she's wonderful
and I just love her.
I'm just so happy
about this.
I like her fine.
( grunts )
You know I offered him
some money and he wouldn't
take it?
Oh, well, he's
getting married.
You know,
he's going to be
the big macho man now.
Head of the family.
He'll probably never
take money from us again.
Well, I bet if I
made it in real estate
or cattle ranching,
he'd take it.
- ( Esther chuckles )
- What are you laughing at?
Nothing--
well, yes, I am.
I'm thinking of you
standing in the middle
of a herd of cows.
Very funny.
( bangs jar )
- Honey, don't do that.
- ( smashes )
Oh!
Oh, shit.
God damn it.
- Did you cut yourself?
- No.
Just leave it.
I'll get it later.
Come on over here,
my darling man,
and talk to me.
What's the matter?
Tell me what's
really troubling you.
( sighs )
I took their money.
They wouldn't have
paid me so much
if they weren't
gonna use my knowledge.
Oh, no.
You weren't
working for them.
You were just working
at their laboratory.
They wanted
great scientists to work
at their laboratory.
It gives them
prestige.
I knew they were
working on pathogens.
They were just
picking my brain.
All I could
think about was Liza.
Listen.
That money...
gave Liza 15 more
years of life.
It gave her Erik.
What if they
use it, Esther?
What if they use it
and everybody dies?
Well, I think
you're going
completely crazy.
I really do,
you know.
You are not to blame
for everything
in this world,
no matter
how smart you are.
And I'll tell you
something else.
I'm taking a little
offense at this.
I didn't marry
a murderer.
I married
the kindest,
gentlest,
most loving man
in the world.
I don't think
you ever knew
just how much
I love you.
I swear, it--
- Esther?
- Ow--!
- What is it, honey?
- Ow!
- Come on, Esther.
Come on. Come.
- Oh. No.
- Come on, come with me.
- I'm fine. I just got excited.
Come on, come on.
Let me take you.
I'll take you upstairs.
Okay, come on.
- One, two, three.
- ( Esther grunts )
- Here we go.
- Oh...!
- ( panting )
- Come on.
Come on.
I'm okay,
really.
Len:
Well, whatever it is,
seven or eight days.
When we're done
with the water--
and there's
tangerine juice, too.
When we're done
with everything,
then we go up.
Even though the radio
said eight days.
Maybe we ought to
make it seven.
But what the fuck
do they know, you know?
Air could be clear
at six.
Clear enough, anyway,
for me to go up
and get supplies
and come back down here.
- Len: What?
- The last thing
they said was...
"200 million dead
in Europe."
So that's not
everybody.
Nothing's
gonna be left, Len.
We don't know that
until we see.
Len, nothing's left.
The radio stopped.
( sighs )
There's no more planes
or helicopters.
When's the last time
you heard anything
other than birds?
We'll stay down here
three more days.
- And then...
- ( Mia sobs )
- we'll drive
to the marina.
- No.
( sighs )
We'll get a boat.
We'll go out
on the lake.
- ( sighs )
- And we'll keep going
until we find someone.
- I don't--
- What?
I don't wanna...
wade through
a bunch of corpses
to go steal a boat
to go look at more corpses
lying on a bunch of docks.
( sobs )
Even--
( sniffles )
even if we did
make it, Len,
what are we
supposed to do?
Do you really want
to play "Adam and Eve"?
Build it all back up
so it all just gets
destroyed again?
Maybe people
will learn.
( Mia sniffling )
It's like that guy
who hit you for trying
to take care of his kid.
It's like that guy
I defended-- great guy,
good father,
always showing me
pictures of his grandson--
who helped invent the shit
that killed everyone.
People aren't
going to learn.
It's something
in us.
in the way
that we're made.
Then at least...
we'll have more time.
At least we'll go out
on the water together.
We'll find a boat
with a nice, big cabin.
Come on.
( sighs )
Len?
That guy, Jay,
from the law firm?
He fell in love
with me.
I never did
anything.
I never let him
touch me.
( sniffles )
But I...
you know, I--
I made him think,
I guess...
that he had
a shot at it.
- Why?
- It was just a way to--
Just a way
to pass the time?
--to feel better
about myself, I guess.
Why do you need
to feel better
about yourself?
Mia:
It wasn't about you.
( sobs )
It was
just my curse.
Len.
Why are they
gonna stay down here
like caged animals?
Or we're gonna go
upstairs tomorrow...
and lie down
on the grass.
Breathe in...
and die...
when and where
we choose.
We'll eat
the chocolate bar
before we do it, okay?
Mia:
Okay?
( playing softly )
( Anna giggling )
- Oh, my God.
- What? What?
Did you buy
this weird soap?
What?
Anna:
I seriously think
I've found my new religion.
( Erik chuckles )
Oh, yeah, that stuff.
Wait, have you
read this?
No. I mean,
the writing's
so tiny--
Wait a minute.
Listen to this.
"Einstein, 1939.
After Nazis
and Commies united,
proposes 'space bombs'
that destroys all
unless we finally
teach the moral ABCs
the real Rabbi Hillel
taught Jesus
to unite all in,
all one, God faith."
( sighs )
( latch clicks )
( oxygen hissing )
( hissing stops )
Did you find
a pay phone?
( coughs )
I got some noodles.
Just gotta add water.
And some drinks.
And there's
these things--
energy bars.
And napkins.
I couldn't find a pay phone.
I don't think they make them
anymore.
What is this doing
on a soap bottle?
And where
did you get this?
I mean, it was at
the health food store.
- It was cheap.
- "We're all one or none.
There is no god
but God.
Teach 'Love thy enemy.'
One Israel-Moses-
Buddha-Jesus-Mohammed.
- One! All one!"
- All one!
"Dilute! Dilute! Okay!"
( giggling )
How about
the switchboard?
The hospital
switchboard.
Or all of these
houses and apartments
around here.
They've all
got to have phones.
Esther...
he's gone.
- Erik's gone.
- ( Anna giggling )
Oh, look at this.
Read this.
"For on God's
spaceship, Earth"--
( together )
"With bomb and gun,
we're all one
or none.
All one, all one,
all one!
Exceptions eternally?
Absolutely none!"
"Absolutely none."
( laughs )
Oh, my God.
Why is the most
inspiring thing
that I've ever read
sitting
on a soap bottle?
"Dilute."
( together )
"Dilute! Dilute!"
"Dilute!
Okay."
( laughing )
- You don't know that.
- It's just the way it is.
Because he could be
with any of his friends.
That's just it,
honey.
You don't know it
for sure. You don't--
( sobbing )
No! No!
- Oh, oop!
- ( Anna giggling )
No...
( sobbing )
( laughing )
Esther:
Oh, God, no.
Shh...
( moaning )
( rustling )
( rapid footsteps
pattering )
( siren wails )
Man: Okay, people.
We're closing down
shop in two minutes.
You've got two minutes
to get your purchases
up to the counter.
Okay?
- That's it, man.
We gotta go.
- Cashier: Come on.
250. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
Um... fuck.
Man:
Hey. We're done, man.
Let's go.
I-I gave
all my money to--
here, just run this.
Yeah, okay, buddy.
That's it. We're outta here.
You're closing up shop.
Just-- just--
you're not selling
any more of these
anyway, right?
Don't be stupid, man.
We ain't giving them away,
either.
I understand that.
Just take this. Here.
That's all I got.
It's all I got.
Get the fuck
out of here.
out now.
( sirens wailing )
- Hey.
- Hey! Put down the kit!
It's the end of the world, okay?
Just let me walk out of here
with a chance.
- Put down the kit.
- ( gun hammer clicks )
What? The last thing
you wanna do on earth
is shoot me?
This is how this shit
started, anyway.
Right?
That's how it started
in the first--
( gunshot pops )
- Sachs: You ready?
- I'm fine.
Good. If you're fine,
the tests are gonna show it.
Anyway--
( groans )
we haven't
seen Dr. Henderson
for a long time.
- Come here.
- That's right.
And here I was,
trying to cheer you up.
Oh, yeah.
Sachs:
You remember when
we lived in Washington,
the Georgetown
apartment?
Esther:
Yes, I do.
We both got the flu
at the same time.
Yeah. And I
took care of you first.
I ran out
in the freezing cold,
went and got you
a nice, big bowl
of hot soup.
- Esther: It was so cold.
-  Yeah.
And I wrapped you up
all nice and cozy
in a blanket.
Remember?
Then I turned
the thermostat up
as high as it would go.
Esther:
Then it was my turn
to baby you.
- ( Sachs chuckles )
- Tucked you in real tight,
And I made you
some of those awful
poached eggs you like.
Mm-hmm.
It's been
a good life.
Yeah,
I think so.
Sachs:
A good life.
( silent )
Oh, I forgot
to tell you.
What?
The best thing
in the world.
( Anna, Erik
moaning )
( moaning continues )
I have something
to tell you.
( faintly )
What...?
The best thing
in the world.
We're going to have
a baby.
We don't
have to do this.
( sighs )
Whatever we said
last night,
we don't
have to do it.
Not today,
anyway.
Mmm, mmm.
I regret
every fucking diet
I ever went on.
( chuckles )
Mmm.
Come on.
Let's get out
of here.
Ahem.
( gasps )
If you have to,
if that's what
you have to do...
go, but I won't.
I--
I don't think we're
gonna run out of food.
I don't think
we're gonna run
out of water.
I think that if we
just stay down here
another couple of days--
- No.
- if we go up then,
we're gonna be fine.
- Mm-mm.
- Okay?
- No.
- Yeah.
Yes!
( sobs )
Yes.
Mia!
Don't leave me!
Don't leave me.
Stay with me.
I love you, baby,
I love you. I need you.
I need you, I need you.
I need you, I need you--
stay!
Please stay!
Please, I need you.
Please?
( sobbing )
( rustling )
( bird chirping )
Girl:
Mama, look
what I found.
( instrumental music
playing )
( guitar music