[Insects chirping]
[Frog croaking]
[Thunder]
[Buzzing]
[Ribbit]
- Welcome to wwe city.
Take the next exit
because it's just that good.
- I'm the miz,
and I'm awesome.
Who's awesome?
I'm awesome.
I am--uhh!
[Gasps]
[Thunder]
Kane, you're back.
I thought we'd never
see you again
after you lost
that last match.
- [Grunts]
- [Gasps]
Not that I agreed
with the decision.
- [Grunts]
- Not the face.
Not the face.
- Welcome to wwe city.
Take the next exit
because it's just that good.
- [Growls]
- Whoa!
Oof!
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about.
You keep on going, Kane.
You're lucky!
You got off easy this time.
[Indistinct rock music
playing]
Who's awesome?
I'm awesome.
Who's awesome--
- [Growling]
[Rustling]
[Growl]
- Who's in there?
Is that you, Kane?
Come on. Come on out
and get some.
- [Growling]
[Growling]
- Uhh!
[Grunting]
- [Growls]
- Uhh!
That all you got, yogi?
Uhh! Uhh!
[Sobbing] My--my face!
- [Growling]
- Welcome to wwe city.
Take the next exit
because it's just that good.
Good.
[Static]
- [Sobbing]
- [Growls]
- Really?
Ahh! No! No!
[Groans]
Unnecessary roughness.
- [Growls]
[Growl]
[Tires squeal]
- ♪ Ba ba, ba ba ba ba ♪
♪ ba ba ba ba
ba ba ba ba ba ♪
- ♪ are you pumped and ready? ♪
♪ hope your nerves
are steady ♪
♪ let's go make some history ♪
♪ solve ourselves a mystery ♪
♪ we won't stop until
the battle's done ♪
♪ the monster caught,
the case is won ♪
♪ I want to write you
so close ♪
- ♪ ba ba ba ba ba ba ♪
- ♪ champions and idols,
take down any rival ♪
♪ fightin' for survival ♪
♪ till they win the title ♪
♪ they don't stop
until the battle's done ♪
♪ the battle's won,
the rumble won ♪
♪ how could a fight
feel so good? ♪
[Engine revs]
[Glass shatters]
[Thunder]
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ ba ba ba
ba ba ba ba ba ♪
♪ ba ba ba ba
[Tires squeal]
Captioning made possible by
Warner bros. Animation
[glass shatters]
[Growling]
- Look out.
John cena is
the doctor of
thundernomics.
Ha ha ha.
He can't see me.
You can't see me at all.
Like, no one can touch
John cena.
- Sin Cara can.
Scooby dooby-doo!
- 1, 2, 3.
Sin Cara wins it.
- Way to go, Scooby-doo,
old buddy.
- Booyah.
Dooby-doo.
- Congratulations.
You just beat the game
on the hardest level ever--
double triple
beatdown extreme.
But can you complete
the victory dance?
- Oh, yeah.
- It's all yours, pal.
You earned it.
[Dance music playing]
[Tempo increases]
- Perfect score!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Hello there.
I'm Vince McMahon,
chairman and ceo of wwe.
- Mr. McMahon.
We're not worthy.
- Because you beat the game
on this level
and executed a perfect score
on the victory dance,
you win a special prize.
- We did?
- You've won an all-expense paid
trip to wwe city.
Come revel in a place
dedicated to everything wwe.
It'll be a week of fun
and excitement,
culminating in ringside seats
at wrestlemania.
Don't miss it.
- Report to training camp
in wwe city
as soon as possible
with this game disc
as proof of your win
to claim your prize.
- Like, wrestlemania.
Ha ha ha!
You gotta be kidding me.
Think of it.
- The fun.
- The fans.
- The food!
- We gotta go, old pal.
Like, we just gotta go.
We gotta go.
It's the ultimate slamtastic
life-affirming experience
of a lifetime.
It's wrestlemania.
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Uh, I don't know, guys.
It's not something
we're really into.
- And I have a lot
of reading to catch up on.
- Uh, no, thank you.
- Like, come on, guys.
Scoob and I never
ask for anything.
Like, I can't count
how many times
the two of us were bait
to catch some crazy
mask-wearing villain.
- Yeah.
- I got the photos
to prove it.
Take a good look, people.
Exhibit "a."
Like, here's the time
you guys made us dress
like giant tools
to catch the monstrous
mechanic.
Or as ducks to catch
the horrific huntsman.
Or when we had to be the cow
to catch the crazed cowgirl
from beyond the grave.
Scooby-doo almost got milked.
- It was so humiliating.
- And the piéce
De résistance,
the time we posed as
señor pepe Jose
and the dancing
hairless chihuahua don pero
to catch the ghastly
gordito of Guadalajara.
- Yeah, the hair didn't
even grow back in some places.
- Scooby was naked.
Look at him.
Just look at him!
- No, no. Ok.
We get it.
- You win, shaggy.
- [Spits, coughs]
Win? Wait, what?
- I was actually thinking
about taking a trip anyway
to try out my new allodium
q-36 digital slr camera
and optical stabilizer
zoom lens.
Maybe I can snap
some action-packed pictures.
- And this will give me
an opportunity
to explore the parallels
between the modern world of wwe
vs. Ancient warrior customs.
Besides, it beats another
weekend with grandpa dinkley
and his mysterious
odor problem.
- Scooby-doo almost
got milked.
- The hair didn't
even grow back
in some places.
- Ok, we'll go to wrestlemania.
- Whoo-hoo!
Wwe city, here we come.
- Oh, boy.
[Slurp]
Hee hee hee!
[Engine revs]
[Tires squeal]
[Insects chirping]
- Here comes the flying
huna caruna off the top ropes.
- [Gulps]
- Ha ha ha!
And it's countered
by Scooby's patented
corkscrew counter crunch.
- Um, exactly how
many more play-by-play
Scooby snack attacks
will we have to endure
before wwe city?
- Like, we brought
everything we had.
Scooby and I need
to keep our energy up
so we can cheer like crazy
at the main event.
- There's so many boxes
I can't even see the luggage.
- Luggage?
- You didn't pack
the luggage?
- Ruh-roh.
- Of all the food-induced,
insane things
you two have done,
this absolutely
takes the cake.
- Mmm. Cake.
- I mean it.
- Like, what's
the big deal?
We all wear the same
outfits every single day anyway.
- Well, you gotta admit it,
he does have a point.
- Hmph.
- Hey, look.
- Like, wwe city,
next exit.
- Hold the phone!
[All screaming]
- Looks like we're stuck.
- There's a car coming.
Maybe they can help.
- Well, now, this ain't
a good place for a breakdown.
- Can we help you kids out?
- John cena.
Whoa.
- Ok. Looks like you kids
ran into some trouble.
- This ain't safe, champ.
We gotta keep moving.
- Calm down, cookie.
- I'm just saying that it's
dangerous out here at night,
what with the bear trouble
and all.
That's why ruben,
my nephew here, and I
have been following
the superstars on their jogs.
- Hi.
- Well, these kids
aren't going anywhere
while their van is stuck.
This shouldn't take long.
- Uh, what's he gonna do,
lift the van out of the ditch?
[Record scratches]
[Cheers and applause]
- Scooby! Shaggy!
- [Grunting]
- Cool.
- I didn't know wwe superstars
were so hot.
Strong! I mean strong.
[Raccoon chitters]
- Grr!
[Growling and barking]
- Scooby, no!
Come back!
- Scooby! Scooby!
- Scoob, stop!
- [Barking]
Aah!
- Scooby-doo,
where are you?
[Panting]
- [Growling]
- Zoinks!
A mo--a mo--monster!
- Monster? Where?
Where?
- Oh, scoob!
Ha ha ha!
You had me worried, pal.
[Laughter]
- It's me.
- It's you.
[Gun clicks]
- Yikes!
[Raccoon chitters]
- What are you two doing
in my woods?
- Um, leaving.
- Cool down a bit, bayard.
The dog and the long haired
fella didn't mean to trespass.
They're just fans
come for the wwe.
- They all come for that.
And the more they come,
the hungrier they make
the beast.
- The beast?
- The beast called wwe city.
Every day it eats up
more and more of our land.
But not for long,
'cause there's a storm
a-coming,
and we're gonna watch it
blow you all out of here
like dead leaves.
Now, get off my property.
- Oh, don't let old bayard
spook you.
He's not what you call
a people person.
- Still, it's not right.
Can I make it up to you
by offering you some vip seats
at our live event tonight?
Would you be interested?
- Would we?
[Squealing]
[Rock music playing]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to wwe.
[Cheers and applause]
[All cheering]
- [Grunts]
- Uhh!
- Ahh!
- Like, pinch me,
I think I'm dreaming.
Ow!
I'm not dreaming.
- Boy, what an exciting
tag team match we have
here tonight.
The big show
and Alberto del Rio
are up against sin Cara
and John cena.
And cena wastes no time
delivering an elbow to big show.
- Whoo-hoo! Yes!
- Big show with a chop.
And del Rio blindsides cena.
That was a dirty move.
And I think the ref agrees.
Oh, my goodness,
sin Cara's up.
And he delivers high-flying
justice to del Rio.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Heh heh heh!
- And it looks like
the end for cena.
But somehow cena reverses.
He's got big show up.
Oh, no!
Look out!
[Cheers and applause]
That was my favorite table.
Del Rio's up.
But he walks right into
cena's sidewalk slam.
And the crowd goes wild.
But wait, big show's back.
With a picnic table?
Where did he get
a picnic table?
Oh, the humanity.
- I don't see anything
in the rules about
the use of furniture.
- It's a show, velma.
- It's sin Cara
to the rescue
with a tilt-a-whirl.
And it's a takedown
of the big show.
[Horn blows]
- Oh!
- Whoo-hoo!
- W!
- Best move ever.
- Cena gathers his...
- Well, I can't say I'm bored.
- And here it comes.
- You can't see me.
- Cena's vintage
5 knuckle shuffle.
- [Shrieks]
Let's go, cena!
Whoo! Whoo-hoo! Yay!
- With incredible strength,
cena takes big show
to the top ropes.
An avalanche.
Attitude adjustment.
Into the cover.
- 1, 2, 3!
- It's over!
[Bell dings]
Cena for the win.
- Yeah! Yeah, man!
- Amazing, dude!
- Tonight's tag team winners,
John cena and sin Cara.
- Oh, cena!
My gosh, you're wonderful.
- ♪ No chance,
that's what you got ♪
- Welcome, fans.
[Cheers and applause]
You should be excited
because I'm about to lay on you
something very heavy--
our very own wwe
championship belt.
[Audience gasps]
- Ahh.
- Yes, it's solid gold,
encrusted with priceless
gems and jewels,
but any wwe superstar
will tell you it's not
about the glitter.
The championship belt
represents honor, respect,
hard work, dedication,
the very soul of wwe.
[Cheers and applause]
As you know, ever since
Kane's wwe championship
match was overturned,
this championship belt
has been held vacant.
And so it shall remain
until a true champion
rises up
and proves themself worthy
this weekend in the main event
at wrestlemania.
[Cheers and applause]
- Did you know that
a golden ceremonial prize
was customary at ancient games
for thousands of years?
- No, velma.
Thank you.
- [Giggles]
Oh, it's a text
from John cena,
thanking me personally
for all the cheering.
That's a keeper.
- When did you give cena
your phone number?
- Oh, when I gave him
my email, my home address,
and my scarf size.
- Hey, why don't you
crazy kids join us at
the training camp tonight?
It's something to see.
- Wwe training camp?
[Both laugh]
- How'd you like sin Cara's
convertible?
- Like, it's a real
muscle machine.
[Rock music playing]
[Engine revs]
- Here we are, guys.
Wwe's rock yard,
where the pros train
for greatness.
- [Grunting] Ahh!
[All grunting]
- Uhh!
- Look!
- It's sergeant slaughter.
Like, zowie!
There's Jerry "the king" lawler.
- And Jimmy hart.
[Both gasp]
- Here at camp,
we even have our own
24-hour restaurant.
It's like home.
- More like paradise.
Ha ha ha!
- Is that
the championship belt?
- That's right, carved
into the Mountain.
A prize set in stone
and the dream of
every superstar.
[Camera shutter clicks]
- Mr. sin Cara, could we
stop for a second?
[Men grunting]
- Uhh!
Uhh!
- Sweet.
- Way to go, ruben.
That was a nice job.
- Yeah, nice move, Ruby.
- Yeah, funktastic, baby.
[Chomp]
- Like, wow, I didn't know
your nephew dude
was a superstar.
- That's what he'd
like to think.
I'd better get you all
settled into your cabins.
Up ahead on the left,
sin Cara.
[Starts engine]
[Wolf howls]
- I can't believe shaggy
and Scooby left all
our luggage behind.
Now all I have
are these two scarves.
Which do you think
John would like better?
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Be honest.
- The one on the right.
- My thoughts exactly.
- I don't understand,
Uncle cookie.
It's just not fair.
You know I'm good.
I know you know I'm good.
Why won't you help me
get into wwe?
- Somebody's got to put
some sense into you.
Do you think I built this brace
because it looks good?
All it takes is one accident
to put you out of contention.
- Maybe I'll be luckier.
- Maybe not.
You have to be practical.
You should keep going
to your computer classes.
Computers, that's
the ticket, Ruby.
- Poor ruben.
I feel sorry for him.
- It's understandable.
Ruben represents
the heroic male
aspiring to the stature
of decorated warrior.
His journey is relatable,
and therefore appealing
to a wide audience.
- Velma, has it ever
occurred to you
that maybe wwe isn't
something you can
scientifically explain?
- Don't be silly, Daphne.
Science and logic
explain everything.
[Rock music playing]
- Hey, like, the most
awesome thing about wwe?
You get all the food
you can eat.
- Yeah. All the food.
- Big day tomorrow.
Cookie said we get to see
some superstars training.
I want to grab
some wicked action shots.
Come on, lights out, you two.
- Okie doke, Fred.
Sweet dreams, scoob.
- You, too, raggy.
All the food.
Food.
[Snores]
Food, food, food, food,
food, food, food, food.
[Snores]
Food, food, food, food,
food, food, food, food.
[Snores]
Huh?
[Whirring]
[All growling]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
let's get ready
to Scooby-doo!
- You want to take me on?
Bring it.
[Bell dings]
- Ahh!
[Video game sounds]
- [Gulps]
Ahh!
[Slurps]
[Belches]
Uhh.
[Chomping]
- [Growling]
- Oh, yeah?
Prepare to become
a Scooby snack.
- [Growling]
- Scoob.
Scooby-doo.
- Hmm?
- Like, dude,
what are you doing
with that bear?
- Hmm?
- [Growls]
- Aah!
- Zoinks!
[Both screaming]
- [Growls]
- Really?
- Aah!
Uhh!
- [Growls]
[Both shouting]
- Ooh!
Aah!
- [Growls]
- Back off, ugly.
- Time to call your mama.
Aah! Ooh!
- Aah!
- Uhh!
Not funky.
- [Growls]
[Growling]
[All scream]
[Both gasp]
- [Groaning]
- Shaggy! Scooby!
Are you ok?
[Both stammering]
- Ghost...Ghost bear.
- Then it's true.
- What's true, cookie?
- The legend.
The monster has returned
from the grave.
Vicious, the ghost bear
has come to challenge us all.
- Oh.
- [Shudders]
- Well, gang, sounds like
we have another mystery
on our hands?
- [Growling]
[Bird cawing]
- Assault, battery,
property damage.
Ghost bear!
What the heck is going on?
And what are you kids doing
in wwe city anyway?
- We won a contest.
- Don't look at me, Richards.
You sent out that memo.
The victory dance contest.
- Oh, that's right.
That wasn't my idea.
Boys over in marketing
or game development.
One of those.
Who can keep things straight
with all these bear attacks
going on?
- There have been others?
- Indeed. Several.
All of them inside
our buildings.
The creature trashed
the kitchen
and totally obliterated
our video game studio.
And as quickly
as it appears,
it disappears.
- I'm telling you,
it's the ghost.
An evil from beyond
the grave.
- [Teeth chattering]
[Creaking]
- Let's try
to remain calm here.
We don't want to jump
to any crazy conclusions.
- Mr. McMahon.
- Like, in the flesh.
I can't believe I'm
actually face to face
with Vinnie Mac.
- The boss.
- The higher power.
- The Mac attack.
- The Mac daddy.
- Daddy Mac.
- Yes. Ahem. Thanks
for that trip down memory Lane.
Let me cut to the chase.
I've been doing a little
research on you kids.
You're some kind of
mystery solvers.
We could really use
your help here.
- Gee, Mr. McMahon,
we'd be glad to.
- My main concern is
the championship belt.
Not only is it worth
a fortune,
but wrestlemania wouldn't
be the same without it.
- Excuse me, sir,
but we don't need
these kids meddling
in security matters.
I promise the championship belt
is well guarded 24/7
with a state-of-the-art
electronic laser trip wire
alarm system.
There's no way the bear
could get to it
without tripping a beam
and setting off an alarm
that would bring in half
my security men within seconds.
- I understand, Richards,
but it couldn't hurt to have
these kids lend a hand.
- It's what we do.
- You mind if I help?
- Um--
- great idea, John.
- Awesome. Because
I think there's someone
you should talk to.
- Sin Cara?
- He knows the legend
of the bear better than anyone.
- Like, why is he hanging out
on the roof?
- Sin Cara has a flair
for drama.
- Ahh.
[Applause]
- But does he even talk?
- He doesn't have to.
Luckily, I speak
masked luchador.
I'll translate as best I can.
[Spanish music playing]
[Thunder]
The legend of the ghost bear
begins 100 years ago
when a monstrous bear was
part of a traveling show.
They named him vicious.
And for good reason.
The creature had a mean streak
a mile wide
and twice as ugly.
It'd never been beaten, ever.
Till it met...
Sin Cara Grande,
sin Cara's great great
great grandfather.
He challenged the bear
on this very spot
long before there was
ever a wwe city.
[Bear growling]
The battle between
man and bear was epic.
The bear was a horrible,
unstoppable beast.
But when the match was over,
it was the man
standing victorious.
[Bear growls]
[Growl]
The bear could not
contain its anger.
[People screaming]
He unleashed his rage
on the town.
Many lives would have been
lost that day
had it not been for
the brave luchador
sin Cara Grande.
[Bear growls]
[Bear groans]
While saving those
innocent townfolk,
he was injured.
Sin Cara Grande would
never wrestle again.
And the bear?
It escaped into the woods,
disappearing into a cave
north of town,
never to be seen again.
Until now.
Sin Cara believes
the spirit of the beast
has been stirred by
wrestlemania itself,
which is why the monster
has risen from the grave
to have its revenge.
- [Chattering]
- But fear not.
It is now sin Cara's
honor and duty
to continue his great great
great grandfather's legacy
and protect wwe city
at any cost.
- Wow.
- That's amazing, dude.
[Applause]
[Insects chirping]
- I have half a mind
to go out in the woods,
find that bear,
and rip its head off.
- [Gulps]
I don't know, triple h,
he's awfully tough.
- I think we should
stick together.
- What do you think, miz?
- Stick together.
[Groaning]
- I can't believe
you two are still hungry
after the meal we had.
- This is just
a late night snack.
Right, scoob?
- Right. Helps us sleep.
- Man, if you guys' muscles
were as big as your appetites,
you'd both be superstars.
- [Grunts]
- Like, fredster, don't you
want to join the pizzapalooza?
- Eh, no, thanks.
I thought I'd patrol
with the guards,
maybe get a picture
of the ghost bear.
I'll lock the door after me.
- Like, to keep the bear out?
[Shudders]
- To keep Scooby in.
- Good idea.
- Like, don't worry, Freddy,
the faster we eat--
- the faster we fall asleep.
[Both chomping]
[Door locks]
- [Snoring]
[Owl hooting]
- [Groaning and snoring]
[Birds cawing]
[Banging on door]
- Ahh!
[Teeth chattering]
Yah!
Like, is something wrong,
Ms. Richards?
- Indeed, there is.
The wwe championship belt
has been stolen.
And we know who did it.
Your dog.
- Uh, but that's ridiculous.
Scooby-doo's been in here
with me all night.
Isn't that right, old pal?
- That's right.
Oh?
- I saw that.
- Uh-uh, nothing
to see here.
Just me in bed.
- You, sir--uh, dog,
are a thief.
- But, Ms. Richards, Scooby
couldn't have taken the belt.
He's never stolen anything
in his whole life.
- Yeah, never.
- I have proof right here.
Last night's
security footage.
Take a look.
- Ooh. Uhh.
[Grunting]
[Beeping]
I--I--I did steal it.
- Say it ain't true,
Scooby-doo.
- [Whimpers]
- Hold on a second.
Is there something strange
about Scooby?
- You really want us
to answer that?
- Yep, this is the
championship belt all right.
I'd know it anywhere.
- Take it.
And we'll be taking
the thief with us as well.
- No! Don't let them
take me, raggy.
No!
- I won't, pal.
Hang on.
- Don't let them
take me, raggy.
I'm innocent.
- Jinkies! That's it.
Come on, we've got
to work fast
if we're going to
save Scooby.
- All right, kids.
What's going on here?
- Thanks for coming,
Mr. McMahon.
We've asked you all here
to show you
that our Scooby isn't a thief.
He's just a pawn.
Allow me.
Here's the security video
of Scooby as he was
taking the belt.
And here's the video file
of Scooby
doing his winning
victory dance
from the memory card
of shaggy's video game.
- Yeah, that's
a funkadactal move.
- Is there a point
to any of this?
- Watch as we slow down
the victory dance.
- It's the same movement.
- Scooby was programmed
with a post-hypnotic suggestion
to steal the championship belt.
- Like, that's why he's been
sleep walking since he got here.
- Ohh. Yeah.
- And just how did
the dog get this
post-hypnotic programming?
- My guess is from
the video game itself.
May I?
I'm connecting shaggy's
wwe video game file
to the tron screen.
[Beeping]
See, someone highlighted
every move with light flashes.
Flashes which
could have planted
a post-hypnotic suggestion
in Scooby's brain.
- Pbblt. Yeah, there's
a plant in my brain.
- Nice hacks, ruben.
- That's my nephew.
He's a computer genius.
- Listen, kids, as compelling
as this theory might be,
I'm still a guy that likes
to look at the facts.
- And the fact is,
he stole it.
And he's going to jail
for it.
[Both shudder]
Jail?
- And it was your video game,
so you're going with him--
as his accomplice.
- Accomplice? I'm no accomplice!
I'm not even sure
I know what that means!
- Miss Richards,
isn't there something we can do
to prevent that?
- No!
- Actually, yes there is.
- Whatever it is...
- We'll do it.
- Wwe city law states
that anyone accused of a crime
can compete in the ring
for a chance to win
their freedom.
[Both gasping]
- I have the power
to give you that chance.
But I have only
one competitor left
who is looking for a match.
[Kane's entrance music playing]
- Kane!
- I want another shot
at the title.
Looks like I'll have
to go through you two to get it.
I accept the challenge.
[Both whimpering]
- Like, you know, scoob,
I hear prison food
isn't that bad.
- No!
You want a chance to prove
your innocence in the ring.
They accept the challenge,
Mr. McMahon.
[Both gasping]
- Miss Richards, release
these two so they can prepare.
Unless they can prove
their innocence,
their match with Kane
will kick off wrestlemania
tomorrow night.
- [Gasps]
- [Grunting]
[Both gasping]
[Thud]
[Birds chirping]
[Bird squawking]
- Like, velma, are you crazy?!
- Yeah! We can't fight Kane.
- Look, guys,
pull yourselves together.
I need you to buy us
some time if we're going
to solve this mystery,
and clear Scooby's name.
- I don't know, velma,
we only have until tomorrow
before shaggy and Scooby
get slaughtered.
- Hello! Thanks, Fred.
- They're going to need
a whole lot longer than a day
to learn how to compete
in the ring.
- Could you help them, cookie?
- Please?
- Yeah, yeah, please,
please, please!
Oh-ho-ho, please, cookie!
- Eh, well, maybe I can
train 'em enough
so they might survive...
- Ooh!
- For a few minutes.
[Scooby and shaggy gulping]
- Aj, you want to help me here?
- Sure, cookie.
Hi, boys.
I heard you could use
some practice sessions.
Wouldn't want those
itty bitty whiskers to get bent.
- Like, Scooby-doo,
you know, this may not
be so bad after all.
Aahh!
- Never underestimate a diva.
- ♪ Let's light it up ♪
- ♪ light it up, light it up ♪
♪ let's light it up ♪
- ♪ let's light it up like
the night, like the diamonds
I see shining in your eyes ♪
- ♪ light it up, light it up ♪
- ♪ let's light it up ♪
♪ let's light up ♪
- ♪ light it up tonight ♪
- ♪ let's light it up like
the night, like the diamonds
I see shining in your eyes ♪
- ♪ in your eyes, in your eyes,
in your eyes, in your eyes ♪
♪ in your eyes, in your eyes ♪
- ♪ something about the night
is magic, I can't explain ♪
♪ every time the sun goes down,
I feel everything change ♪
♪ [indistinct]
Feel my temperate rage ♪
♪ every night,
a brand new page, yeah ♪
♪ let's light up ♪
- ♪ light it up, light it up ♪
- ♪ let's light it up ♪
♪ let's light it up ♪
[Crash]
- You ok, ruben?
- No, I'm not ok.
I don't understand
why my Uncle is willing to train
shaggy and Scooby and not me.
Just because he never won
a championship
doesn't mean I can't.
Sorry.
See, it's just because
all my life,
I've dreamed of being
a wwe superstar.
I've even come up
with my own name--
the bone bender.
I got an outfit I made out
of spandex and bones.
Real bones I ordered
off the Internet.
Want to see?
- Well, maybe later.
- Daphne?
- [Gasping]
- You got to hide us!
- Aj's like Kane, with lipstick!
- Hey, gang, we got maps
of the whole area.
- And I found the perfect place
to start looking for clues
about the ghost bear.
- Scooby, shaggy.
Where you boys hiding?
- Like, what are we waiting for?
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
[Insects chirping]
[Hooting]
- Like, wouldn't it be better
to clear our names
than to go, you know,
bear hunting?
- That's just it, shaggy.
I can't help thinking
that whoever framed Scooby
is somehow connected
to the ghost bear.
- Keep it down.
We don't want to attract bayard.
- You mean the hillbilly
with the thieving raccoon?
- [Snarls]
- Yeah. Their cave
is right on his property.
[Owl hooting]
- [Gasps]
- Can't say I didn't warn 'em.
- Zoinks!
Aroo?
- Run!
[All yelling]
- [Gasping and whimpering]
Run!
- [Gasping] Scoob!
- Aah!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-ah!
[All grunting]
Oh! Ooh, hoo, whoa-ho!
[All gasping and yelling]
- Aah!
- Huh?!
- [Grunting]
- Like, that was amazing!
- Cen-amazing!
- How'd you know where we were?
- Daphne texted me.
- Mmm.
- Naturally.
- What's going on?
- Hillbilly hospitality.
We should keep moving.
- Come on,
I'll explain on the way.
- This is it, guys.
Bear cave.
- Come on, follow me.
- Now, that's rich.
Those dummies
just walked into a trap
that's better
than any I could make.
[Water flowing]
[Bats screeching]
[Screeching]
[Both gulp]
- Bet you that was
the original bear.
- He doesn't look
so vicious now.
- How long do you think
he's been there?
- Who cares, as long
as he stays there.
- Yeah! [Gulping]
- [Grunting]
[Camera shutter clicks]
- Like, man,
what is this crazy place?
- My guess? The lair
of the ghost bear.
- Like, he has a lot of junk
for a ghost--or a bear.
- Not junk.
Clues!
- What are those?
- Books on hypnotism.
Hypnotic techniques
and subliminal hypnosis.
- Jackpot!
- Ohh!
- I think we just found
our first piece of evidence
to get you guys
off the hook with Kane.
- Evidence! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- We love evidence.
- Mwah!
- Hey, gang.
Check this out.
Schematics for emp.
- What's an emp?
- What's a schematic?
- An emp
is an electromagnetic pulse.
It's a device that can
destroy electronics
within its range.
[Camera shutter clicks]
- Urghh!
- Look what I found.
This calendar has the date
for wrestlemania circled in red.
R.I.P. Wwe.
[Camera shutter clicks]
Fred!
- Evidence photos, velma.
Can't have an investigation
without evidence photos.
- So someone thinks
they're going to knock
the lights out on wrestlemania?
Not on my watch!
- [Growling]
- [Grunting and groaning]
- John!
- Gh-gh-ghost bear!
- [Growling]
[Camera shutter clicking]
- Run!
[All yelling]
- [Growling]
- Yikes!
[All yelling]
- [Growling]
- [Gasping]
[Camera shutter clicks]
- [Growling]
[All yelling and gasping]
- Ohh!
- [Growling]
- Whoa!
- Ohhh!
- Ah-ah-aaah!
[All yelling and gasping]
[Both gasping]
[All yelling]
[All gasping]
- [Growling]
[All yelling]
- Huh?!
- [Growling]
[All yelling]
- [Snoring]
- We're right back
where we started!
[Bear growling]
- Jinkies!
And so's the ghost bear!
- [Growling]
- [Grunting]
[Indistinct yelling]
[All yelling]
- [Sighs]
Where are the boys?!
- [Snoring]
- We got to get the evidence!
- Don't worry, shaggy.
I still have the photos.
- Yeah!
- [Growling]
- No!
- Yoinks!
- Ahh!
- [Snoring]
- [Growling]
- Guys, hold on to something.
[All yelling]
- Aah--ohh?
[Growling]
- Ohh!
- [Growling]
- Ah. Huh?
- Boom!
- [Cheering]
[Camera shutter clicks]
- Epic!
- Ah, enough already!
[All groaning and coughing]
- Hey! Over there!
- Huh?
- [Grunting]
- Hey! What do you know?
- The caves are connected
directly to the storm drains
under wwe city.
- Giving that ghost bear
full access at any time.
- So you see, Richards,
that's how the ghost bear
gets in and out of so many
places so quickly.
- And we have reason
to believe that whoever's
behind these bear attacks,
has planted an emp device
right here in the stadium.
- He could shut down
the whole place
right in the middle
of wrestlemania.
- We shouldn't take any risks.
We'll have to cancel the show.
- We can't cancel wrestlemania!
That's like canceling Christmas.
Not to mention my career.
Besides, what could anyone gain
but shutting off the lights?
- Not only the lights,
but the TV cameras, too.
There'd be no show.
- People would panic
in the pitch black.
They'd get hurt!
[Whipping sounds]
- You're right, sin Cara.
It would tarnish
the entire legacy of wwe.
- Listen. I'll have my men
guard the stadium's
generators 24/7.
They'll check every square inch
of the building
right before the show.
No one's going to get away
with anything under my watch.
One way or another,
wrestlemania goes on.
- If the object of the emp
is to create chaos,
you can bet that ghost bear
is not going to be far away
when it happens.
- I think we all know
what we need to do.
- Run away?
- Nope. We've got to turn
wrestlemania into a trap.
- A big bear trap.
Whatever you plan, Fred,
count me in.
- Come on, then.
We don't have much time.
[Both groan]
[Thunder]
[Rock music playing]
[Kids giggling]
[Thunder]
- [Grunts]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
announcing a new match
for tonight's event.
Kane vs. Skinny man
and dead meat.
[Audience booing]
- Like, do you think
maybe the gang has
solved the mystery yet?
Because there's no mysteries
to where we're going.
- Yeah. To the hospital.
- No. The morgue!
- Come on, guys,
you got to have confidence.
You have to get up there
and give it your all!
If you don't hold back;
If you battle with
your heart and soul,
if you give everything
you've got,
then you'll not only
survive this, you could win!
[Both gasp]
[Both yelling and whimpering]
- Nice knowin' ya.
- Hey, uh...
Break a leg, you two.
- Ooh! If we're lucky.
[Rock music playing]
- Whoo-hoo!
- Let the games begin!
- Bring on the pain train!
- Whoo!
- This is going to be great!
- Yeah!
So awesome!
[Crowd cheering]
- Everybody in position?
- Check.
- Sin Cara's ready.
And so am I.
- Triple h?
[Thunder]
- Ready out here.
[Crowd cheering]
- ♪ No chance ♪
♪ that's what you got ♪
- Welcome to wrestlemania!
[Crowd cheering]
Allow me to show you
why we're all here--
bring it up.
The wwe championship belt.
[Crowd cheering]
The superstar who wins
tonight's main event
will be the new wwe champion.
- Jinkies! That's it. Fred,
I know where the electromagnetic
pulse device is.
- Tonight's first match
is a big one, folks.
We have the newcomers,
skinny man and dead meat.
[Audience booing]
- Ohh!
[Both groaning]
[Audience booing]
[Both whimpering]
- They'll be facing
the meanest competitor
in and out of the ring.
Back for revenge,
determined to destroy anyone
between him and the title.
I give you the big, red monster.
Kane!
[Cheers and applause]
[Both yelling and whimpering]
[Kane growls]
- This is a last man
standing match.
The superstar who's unable
to answer a ten count
after being knocked down
is declared the loser.
[Kane growling]
- Come on, scoob, we got--
we got to keep it together!
- Oh--oh--k!
[Whimpering]
- After Kane is finished
with skinny man and dead meat,
we'll be scraping them
off the mat with a spatula.
- [Growling]
- [Gulping]
[Bell rings]
- And there's the bell.
Kane explodes across the ring.
Oh! There goes any chance
for a fair match.
- [Grunting]
- Skinny man and dead meat--
slam into the big red monster.
Certainly that blow
can only increase Kane's fury.
- Ohh!
[All grunting and groaning]
- Miss Richards, you have
to open the safe and check
the championship belt!
- Are you crazy? Look,
I checked the entire stadium
for your electro-whatumacalit.
It's not here!
- It's right there.
- Impossible.
- If only I had a magnet
to prove it.
[Whipping sounds]
- Wow! Where did you get that?
- Luchadores--always
ready for anything.
- Ok. Miss Richards,
this magnet will prove
that your championship belt
isn't gold.
Because if it sticks...
Then it's made of iron
and it's a fake.
- Caught in the clenches
of Kane,
the newcomers are done for.
- Whoa!
- The bounce out of the ring
offers skinny man and dead meat
a chance for escape--
but look at this!
Kane has just taken
the match under the ring.
It's bedlam down below!
[Coughs]
[All yelling]
- Huh?!
- Ahh!
[Crowd cheering]
- Not again!
Somebody get me another desk
out here, please.
- Ha ha!
- [Gasping]
- Jinkies! The emp
is about to go off.
- We'll never get it
far enough away.
The arena power generator
is right below us.
I've got to warn everyone.
- I have an idea.
[Scooby and Kane grunting]
Hold this and let go when I say.
- Right...Ok.
- [Grunting]
Now!
- Eeh!
- [Gasps]
- That wasn't supposed
to happen.
[Belt beeping]
- Huh? Whoa!
[Crowd yelling]
- Huh? What's going on?
What happened?
- What happened to the TV?!
[All groaning]
- Oh, man, this is awful!
- Who turned out the lights?
[All yelling]
- [Growling]
- Ok, guys, it's here.
[All murmuring]
- The fans
are starting to panic.
- Plan b. Here we go.
- [Grunting]
[Groaning]
- Whoo-hoo! Nice throw!
- We can see!
- Let there be light!
- Funkadelic.
- Part of the show?
- That was just part
of the show! I was worried.
- I'm fine now.
- I'm ok!
- Scooby! You can do it.
You know all the right moves.
- I do?
- Yeah!
From the video game.
I trust the massive power
of your superstar-tastic
dance moves.
Just pretend you're playing
the video game.
- I can do this.
I can do this!
[Rock music playing]
- [Grunting and growling]
- That a boy, scoob!
- Huh?!
- [Grunts]
- Whoa!
- [Grunting]
- [Growling]
- [Groaning]
- Ghost bear sighted.
- Good. He's here.
Just like we thought he'd be.
- The lights are starting to go.
- Don't worry--Fred's on it.
- Triple h.
[Thunder]
- Ok, guys,
hit the generators.
[Electricity zapping]
- [Groaning]
- Huh? [Groaning]
- After a mysterious blackout,
we're somehow back on the air.
- Hey! Dead meat's not dead yet.
- Wow, look at that doggy move.
- Go, dead meat!
- [Growling]
- Freddy, go!
- Plan c.
- Hey, smokey!
Where's the fire?
Prepare to face the wrath
of the bone bender!
[Both grunting and growling]
- Is that a bear?!
- Like, zoinks!
- Is that ruben?
- [Grunts]
- Ruben, no!
[All gasping]
- Whoa-oh-oh!
Ohhh!
- I don't believe it, folks.
Kane has been flattened,
and a new competitor
has entered the ring.
But wait! Someone
has activated the cage.
Sin Cara and John cena
are leaping into the ring.
It's a cage match!
[Crowd cheering]
- [Growling]
- Like, we're all doomed!
- Don't worry, shaggy.
I'll protect you.
- [Growling]
- The mysterious new competitor
attacks the bear from behind,
creating a distraction
for cena to make a move.
But this powerful creature
turns the tables on them both.
Now sin Cara stands alone.
- [Growls]
- The fearless luchador attacks.
He glides around the bear
like lightning.
The bear
can't even touch sin Cara.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I haven't seen moves
like this in the ring before.
Sin Cara delivers
a stunning blow to the bear
while John cena
recovers on the mat.
He's going after the bear.
Cena is lifting the bear
over his head.
And the bear is down.
[All cheering]
- Yeah!
- Yay!
- Yes!
- What's that,
bear, what's that?
You can't see me!
- Ladies and gentlemen,
here it is.
Cena's vintage
five knuckle shuffle.
- [Growls]
[Crowd cheering]
- It's lights out
for this big, bad bear.
This match is over.
- Yay! Yay!
[All cheering]
Cena and sin Cara
going for a tandem pin.
- [Growling]
[Crowd cheering]
- Impossible!
- Huh? [Whimpers]
- [Growling]
- Ooh-hoo-hoo!
Scooby-doo, where are you?!
- This looks bad for skinny man.
But wait,
what is dead meat up to?
- [Chattering]
- [Growling]
- Dead meat has revived Kane.
The big, red monster has risen.
Never before have we seen
a stand-off like this.
It's monster vs. Monster
inside the cage at wrestlemania.
Who will survive
this supernatural match-up?
Who will be victorious
in this paranormal pandemonium?
Kane drives the bear back
with a stunning blow.
The bear hits the mat.
Kane pins down its leg.
A new competitor,
John cena and sin Cara
pile onto the powerful creature,
but they can
barely hold it down.
- [Grunting]
Scooby-doo, it's up to you!
- Only dead meat can tip
the balance now.
- [Growling]
- [Gulps]
- Can he do it?
Can dead meat save the day?
- Scooby doobie doo!
- Dead meat just delivered
a gut-wrenching belly bomb
and flattened the ring
and exploded the cage!
The dust is clearing now.
The bear is out cold.
Dead meat wins it!
[Cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- Dead meat!
- That bear is toast!
[Cheering and laughing]
- [Growling]
- [Gasping]
- You ok, velm?
- This...Is...Awesome!
Whoo-hoo!
[Laughing]
[Indistinct chatter]
- Now let's see
who this ghost bear really is.
[All gasping]
- Cookie?!
- Uncle cookie!
Why?
Wwe is your life.
- Wwe was his life,
but sadly, your Uncle cookie
never got the glory...
- And his injury
put him out of the spotlight.
- Permanently.
- He started to truly resent wwe
because he knew he could
never be the champion
he always dreamed of being.
- That resentment grew into
hatred over the years,
as he trained others to be
what he could not.
- That's when he developed
his plan for revenge.
- But that wouldn't be enough.
He needed a pawn to steal
the championship belt.
That's when he devised the idea
of hacking into a video game
and placing post-hypnotic
suggestions into it.
That game would become
part of a contest,
which cookie set up
with fake emails
he sent throughout wwe.
That's why he used
the bear to attack
your video game studio.
To cover his tracks.
- The contest assured
that only the most skilled pawn
would arrive at wwe city
to aid in the theft.
Cookie then used flashing
lights to activate Scooby's
post-hypnotic programming.
- When cookie identified
the belt in Scooby's bed
as the championship belt,
he was lying.
He'd already switched them.
With Scooby taking the blame,
cookie was free to carry out
his ultimate plan.
- Which was to turn out
the lights, and with
the help of the bear,
create so much
panic and injury...
[Bear growls]
That wrestlemania
would be completely ruined
and wwe would never recover.
- But thanks to Fred
here, we got the lights
back on pretty quick.
Good work!
- [Grunts]
Ah, um, thanks.
- And the real championship
belt, where is it now?
- Elementary,
my dear Mr. McMahon.
Cookie's wearing it.
- Sorry, cookie.
But the championship belt
isn't for cheaters,
it's for champions.
[Cheers and applause]
- Good call,
hiring these kids, sir.
I thought they might
come in handy.
- Just get cookie out of here!
- Yes, sir, will do,
sir, you bet.
- A championship belt
was the icing on
the cake, Mr. McMahon.
Cookie could live off its golden
jewels for the rest of his life.
- Boo!
- And I would have
gotten away with it, too,
if it weren't
for you meddling kids
and your giant, crazy dog!
[Audience booing]
- I guess after what
my Uncle's done,
you won't be wanting me
around anymore.
- Not so, Ruby.
- You're one of us now.
- You got the funk, son!
- That's right, ruben.
You've shown a superstar
spirit in the ring,
and at the computer.
You've earned a place with us
in whatever you want to do.
The choice is yours.
- Thanks, Mr. McMahon.
- Now that we have
the real championship belt,
it needs to be awarded
to true champions.
And after what I've seen
tonight, they're right here.
Skinny man and dead meat!
[Cheers and applause]
- [Grunts]
- [Both gasp]
[Audience gasping]
[Both whimpering]
- Really?
- Huh?
- Well done.
[Cheers and applause]
- Scooby-doo!
Scooby-doo! Scooby-doo!
Scooby-doo!
- Scooby doobie doo!
[Laughs]