RED SHOE DIARIES
WILD ORCHID III
The lord is my Shepard,
i shall not want.
He makes me to lie down in green pastures,
and leaves me beside the still waters.
He restores my soul.
He leads me in the paths of
righteousness for his namesake.
Yea though i walk through the valley
of the shadow of death
i will fear no evil, for you
are with me.
Your miracles will be performed in
the presence of my enemies,
you anoint my head with oil.
My cup runs over.
I'm sorry, Jack.
It's terrible.
All the day of my life, i was well
in the house of the lord.
I'm so sorry, Jake.
I'm really sorry about Alex.
We'll all miss her.
When you work up the courage
to talk about this,
you know where to find me.
Got it all cleaned up, Mr. Jack.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't take the cementery.
I don't undersatnd. She was so...
She was so much to live for.
Hi, we're not in right now.
Work, work, work.
Leave us a mesage.
Jake? It's Marlene.
So,could i take you out to dinner tonight?
And maybe just talk.
I just don't think you should be alone.
So, call me, all right?
Okay, bye.
Friday, July 12.
Too excited. Too much energy,
Took off from work early.
6 months and he's already a part
of my every breath,
my every thought. He's everything
i ever dreamed of.
A fairy tale Prince. If an hour
goes by without hearing his voice,
i'm lost. Adrift.
I've surrendered to his taste,
to his place, to his every wish.
He knows me inside out,
everything about me.
My troubles with my mother, the
abortion i had when i was 18,
my fear of the dark,
my fascination with fire.
No, Jack. There's people there.
No, Jake, the wedding.
- I don't care.
- No.
Yes.
No... okay... Maybe.
I've given him every memory of the past,
every dream of the future.
I've thrown all my card on
the table before him.
I'm an open book.
I want my mystery back.
Something. Anything.
One thought, one deed, one tiny
secret that's mine alone.
I don't understand.
Look at this, Paul.
When the sun rises,
it's gonna hit the buidings
and create shadows
for the people on the parks
down on the ground.
- It's gorgeus. - Who gives a shit
how the light hits down there?
- Nobody see it this way. Helicopter
pilots, maybe. - And angels.
Jesus Christ, Jake, not that
angel bullshit again.
No, look, just unclench.
Enjoy the sunset.
Think about how the angels are
gonna love this sunset. Look.
July 15th. Another 14-hour day.
We are both equally compulsive.
Equally dedicated to our work.
The difference is i change the look
of people's living rooms,
- the fabric of the couches.
- Bye, cutie!
Jake changes the skyline.
His buildings will affect the way
people live for yhe next 100 years.
Not much of a comparison when
you really think about it.
Do you know how lucky you are to
enjoy your work as much as you do?
And to be as good as you are.
And to be rewarded for it?
I envy that. I really do.
I've always had this thought
that maybe God put certain people
on this earth
to take care of us.
Doctors, poets, musicians.
People with vision.
People like you.
Come here.
Just stand right here.
- Take off your sweater.
- Why?
I wanna see the outline of your body
through your nightgown.
I love the way look.
I love the way you smell.
I love the way you taste.
I love the way you feel.
I love the way you smile.
I love the way you scratch me.
I love thew way you moan.
I love the way you come.
I love everything.
I love it.
- Don't say that.
- I love you.
O... T... A...
- L... Z... F?
- No, don't move.
August 8th.
Got my eyes checked today.
Try not to blink. You've got something
imbedded in your iris.
Looks like a little chunk of glass.
Have you felt any irritation?
No, please.
It'd be better for both of us
if you didn't move.
If this ruptured, it could cause you
serious trouble.
I read that 70 to 80% of all
the people in the world give up,
stop growing, stop dreaming,
and settle down the time
they are twenty-two,
become an eye-doctor and make
your mother happy,
nice and safe.
Don't move a muscle.
I could barely walk straight.
No perspective.
I should have called Jake, but
i sort of enjoy the adventure.
I hope you hit that son of a bitch back!
Amaizing. Every passing stranger
assumed I was a victim.
That I had been beaten by my man.
Don't let'em get away with it.
Get out.
You okay?
Crazy drivers.
- You get something in you eye?
- A piece of glass.?
It happens. Accidents.
You put in all this time and energy
planning for your future,
and bam! Acar runs you down
on the street
or bullet hits you by mistake.
- That sucks.
- Yeah,that sucks.
Nothing would piss me off more than that.
I think about it a lot.
- Goodbye dreams. Lights go out.
- That's all she wrote.
You just never know,
know what i mean.
I know what you mean.
It was just a piece of glass.
Take it easy.
Perfect teeth, perfect skin,
perfect chest, perfect hair,
I just fell into his arms.
The wind just sort of blew me his way.
Perfect.
August 12th. Got the bandages
taken off my eye today.
Just happened to end up on
the same corner.
A little childish, a little
narcissistic maybe.
the perfect contender in a battle
tha's already been won.
Someone so different from Jake,
there's no contest, no conflict,
no competition, no confusion.
THE PERFECT SECRET.
Lady's shoe outlet
- I know you, don't I?
- I don't think so.
- You looking for shoes?
- I'm always looking for shoes.
Come on in. Have a look.
I got something just for you.
Have a seet.
- Aren't you gonna ask me my size?
- Seven and a half B.
Yep. Seven and a half B.
Batia La Page.
- La Page.
- Who is she?
A woman in France.
- Did you buy there?
- Yes.
- How much?
- I don't remember.
Come on, how much?
- About two hundred dollars.
- Two hundred dollars?
These are American.
Kenneth Cole, my main man.
And they are much prettier.
Stand up, walk around, let me
see what they look like.
Beautiful.
They make you look like a Princess.
- You like them?
- Yes.
You know, I'm glad to see you
got that bandage off your eye.
- Can you see better?
- Obviously not well enough.
- I didn't recognize you in this store.
- I work two jobs.
I see.
- You know when the weather main broke the other day?
- It was funny.
It felt good, didn't it?
You like the way this feels?
Being close like this.
Answer me.
Yes.
There's no rational explanation for
the attraction between two people.
It just sort of happens,
like accidents.
It has to do with magic.
- Magic.
- Alchemy. Chemistry.
Electromagnetic vibratory
transmission forces.
The stuff that moved the blocks
for the pyramids.
Right now,
I could balance one of those blocks
on the front of my pants.
- Really?
- Yeah, have a look.
See what you see.
Ladies, I'll be right with you.
- Six double A, nine B. Am I right?
- Amazing.
So...
- Will this be cash or credit card?
- Credit card.
That is where i live.
Meet me tomorrow night.
Eight o'clock.
Thank you.
Step on a crack and break
your mother's back.
When I was a kid I dared myself
to do the most outrageous things.
I'd get right up to the edge,
and inevitably...
inevitably, i'd find an
excuse to tail out.
How many hours a day do you
spend in this thing?
Never enough. I lie back.
Close my eyes. I feel
nothing but warm darkness.
And I float up, up. Free.
You're one of those
Victorian mystery boxes.
You open one and there's another.
And you open that one and
there's another inside that.
Just when you think you've think
you've opened the last box,
there's another, always another.
- Jake?
- Yeah, baby, what?
Let's take tomorrow off.
Let's take a long ride
out to Santa Barbara,
stay in some seedy motel.
- Ican't.
- Why not?
I've got to duke it out with Paul
and the big boys over dinner.
- Do it another night.
- I can't baby.
Please.
I can't.
When the light's just
right like this,
it's as if the ship is
actually out on the sea,
somwhere in Mediterranean...
I can see the passengers,
men in their tuxedos and
the women in their gowns.
That on there is drunk.
You see, see the woman over
there in the feather boa?
- In the purple hat?
- Yeah, screaming at the captain.
- Yeah
- It's my mother.
- He just threw her off.
- As to be so lucky.
Come on, sweetheart, talk to me.
Stop me from going.
Filled with fire, burning with shame,
I kept telling myself over and over
that I'd never go through with it.
No way..
Are you going to a party, Mrs. Alex?
- A meeting.
- You look gorgeous.
- Of course you always look gourgeous.
- Thank you.
Are you okay?
My world was falling apart with each step,
but that didn't stop me.
I had to see Jake. I was sure that
he'd rush up to me,
hold me, stop me.
- 24 hours! If the shipment is not here...
- He didn't even see me.
- I will see your ass in court.
- Will you excuse us for a minute?
Be careful, Jake. This guy can
kill us, he will kill us.
If you show any weakness they'll
eat you for breakfast.
Trust me. Okay?.
Mitch, don't you dare fucking
stonewall me, okay?
I'm sick of your excuses
and I'm tired of you.
To know what you want and
to go after it and get it,
and to actually belive you deserve it,
my God, how envy Jake for that.
I told myself for the hundreth time: RUN!
I don't know what i'm doing here.
I told you I could move blocks
with my cock.
Your curiosity was piqued.
Now here you are.
Why don't you take off your clothes?
- I...
- What?
I just suddenly realize I don't know you.
I don't even know your name.
You're no stranger to me.
I know everything I need to know.
- You don't know anything about me.
- Sure I do.
I know you're beautiful.
You wear two hundreatd dollar shoes,
and you are with someone who
doesn't make you happy.
He does.
He makes me too happy, that's the problem.
Seriously.
Have you ever noticed how liars
start each sentence
with: "To tell the thruth"?
You keep saying "No, seriously".
It makes me think that you're
just fooling around.
Are You?
No.
Then, seriously, why don't you
take off your dress.
and walk over here in
your pretty new shoes?
Only a girl with a Gold Card would
leave her dress on the floor.
Unbuckle my belt.
This started with me on the my knees.
Now it's your turn.
Fuck you.
My panties, rip them off.
Do it.
He made love like he
worked on the street.
Tender as a jackhammer.
Jesus.
August 20th
I told my self over and over,
once could be rationalized as
a foolish mistake,
temporary insanity, an act of passion.
Twice was irreversible.
Who is it?
I like that.
The minute i saw him,
I understood what I wanted.
Something I've never had in my life.
Something I've always gladly
given up to others.
The greatest aphrosidiac of all:
control.
Hi, we'rw not in right now.
Work, work, work.
Leave us a message.
I haven't seen him in two weeks.
He's out of my life
like an alcoholic coming off the hooch.
One minute, one hour,
one day at the time.
And I'll never see him again.
This kind is more expensive, of course,
- but it's hundred percent silk.
- Excuse me just a moment.
I'm sorry to bother you, there's a
guy who says he's your brother.
I'm gonna send you two off
with Michelle.
She's gonna show you the other
colours and patterns.
Just give me fifteen minutes and we'll
finish everything off. Okay?.
- Right this way please.
- Thanks, Michelle.
- See what'd tell you?
- What a surprise.
I told her I was your brother.
I don't think she belived me.
How did you find me?
It wasn't hard.
I let my fingers do the walking.
I hate your suit.
Funny, I thought it
looked good on me.
He belonged to my father.
He wore it everyday of his life.
Said it brought him luck.
Why are you here?
I wanted you.
I want you all the time now.
I don't even know your name.
That's the way I want to keep it.
My name is Tom.
That's short for
Thomas K. Butler.
- I don't wanna hear it.
- Same name as my dad.
Please.
Everybody used to call me Junior.
After my dad died,
my mother started calling
me Tom for the first time.
I didn't even know who
she was talking to.
I had to drop out of school to
help support my brothers.
Gave up football scholarship
to the University of Illinois.
What the hell, right?
You gotta do what you gotta do.
I'm sorry you don't like my suit.
Pick out another one for me and
I'll go down and buy it.
You can pick up my underwear,
my shirts,
anything you want.
And I'll wear them.
You know why?
Because you're the one of
the only really nice things
that's ever happened to me.
When I'm with you I feel like
I just stepped out of the shower.
I feel clean.
Please, look at me.
What I'm saying is important.
If you don't come to me,
I'm gonna come to you.
I'll find out where you live,
I'll camp out on your doorstep.
Think your boyfriend will believe
that I'm your brother?
I'll see you around.
Now he has a name.
No place to run. No place to hide.
Trapped.
October 21st: my 26th birthday.
Now remember, keep a happy face.
- Shall I make a wish?
- Wish first. Concentrate.
I don't wanna kiss you,
I wanna make a toast to
lovely, gorgeous, stunning, radiant Alex,
whose perfect life I think
matches her perfect beauty
and Alex and I've been friends for...
How long? Tell the truth.
No, since... Wait.
Since we were seventeen.
Seventeen?
Please say you're seventeen.
Are you okay?
Yes. I might be coming down
with a flu or something.
That's what I told your brother when
you didn't show up for work today.
- My brother?
- He called. He was worried about you.
I said you hadn't been feeling well
and you were at home resting.
You didn't tell him where I live,
did you?
He asked for your telephone number.
He's your brother, for Christsake's,
I gave it to him.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Come on, please. Have a good time.
- I'm fine.
It's your birthday. We love you.
How does anyone know what
anyone else is feeling?
How can I turn to?
Who can I talk to?
I hate shrinks.
If I told my friends that my problem
was not one man, but two,
they'd kick me in the head.
Maybe I should run an ad in the paper:
"Woman out of control seeks clues
to own dark pain and passion.
from other women's experiences.
Willing to pay top dollar.
Send diaries to red shoes, P.O. BOx...
Whatever".
- Come back. Here it comes.
- Did it break? - Not yet.
He's a tough little bastard.
- A candy?
- Beautiful, isn't it?.
No, no. Unwrap that first.
- What's that?
- Atmosphere?
- You'll see.
- Come on over here. Come on.
- Where are we going?
Just come with me. Sit.
- What's this?
- I want to do this right
- Okay?
- Okay, go ahead.
Its...
A velvet box.
Marry me, Alex.
Is that a yes or a no?
I think I had too much to
drink this afternoon.
You wanna talk about it?
Jake, I know you think you
know everything about me,
but there's so much you don't know.
- Like what?
- Like...
When I was a kid I was so screwed up
I listened to myself breathe at night
because I thought if I didn't I
wouldn't wake up in the morning.
I used to bang my head against
the wall untill it hurt.
It was like I just
couldn't stop myself.
All kids feel like that
from time to time.
No. I'm talking dark.
So dark it scared the shit
out of my parents.
Who? Not your mother.
She took me to all types of
doctors 'cause she...
She thought it was my thyroid,
but it wasn't my thyroid, Jake.
And it just got worse and
she got really scared.
She got so scared because,
it's the only thing
she couldn't control.
I can remember writing this elaborate
will when I was eleven.
And then when I didn't die, I wrote
another one when I was fifteen.
- I was so fucked up.
- Those days are over, baby.
Fuck it! I can't even drive a car.
I'm the only person in Los Angeles
who can't drive a car.
Any idiot can drive a car, baby.
It takes a genius to get her
friends to drive her everywhere.
Stop. I don't want to.
That's the thing about life.
If you look at thing hard enough,
long enough, in the harsh
light of the day,
you'll eventually see the flaws.
That's why everything I make
I design with lots of shadows.
The shadows make things beautiful.
Special. Your shadows make
you beautiful, Alex,
I love you.
I want you to marry me.
It was like I was Standing
outside myself,
watching pieces of a puzzle
fall into place.
The whole picture of my life,
all the patterns that keep repeating.
All the same rotten mistakes.
Why when I have a good thing going,
do I always checkmate myself?
What's the matter with you, Rita?
Your boyfriend keeping you up nights?
You look like shit!
And one, and two, and three,
and four, and five, and six,
and seven, and eight.
All right, ladies,
that'll be all for today.
- So tell me. what's his name?
- Jake, mother. - Jake.
Exactly what kind of
an architect are you?
Hope not one of those conceptual
assholes spending his life therifing
the utopian environment.
- Jake designs skyscrapers.
- Design and build are different things.
He builds them to.
- I despise intimidating men.
- Jake's not intimidating.
Is that so? He bamboozled you,
otherwise you wouldn't defend him.
I don't know what she told you, but
her father was a real cocksucker.
You're not one of those passive
aggressive types, are you?
No, I'm just aggressive.
And intimidating.
Are you a good lover?
- Oh god.
- Are you attentive!
Patient? Unselfish?
Do you take your time?
Shut the door and
you'll find out.
Hey, wait a minute!
Fuck your mother.
She can piss on my head.
I don't care. It doesn't change
what I feel about you.
You've said enough about
my fucking mother. Fuck you.
Look at me.
What are you afraid of?
What?
Don't run away. what
are you afraid of?
Hi, we're not in right now.
Work, work,work.
Leave us a message.
I... If you're there, this is me.
what's going on?
Your office is closed and I...
I miss you.
Can't let him intimidate me.
Can't let him frighten me.
Got to tell him face to face.
If I can't do that, if I can't sit
in a room across from him,
and tell him that it,s over,
then I'n not worth shit.
Not worth a shit.
- I'm looking for Tom Butler.
- Yeah. What for?
- A letter.
- Right here.
- Sign right here for me.
- All right.
- Here you go. - All yours.
- Thanks a lot.
- Hey, nice boots.
- Thanks.
Where's the shoes?
Worn out.
It's all that running away
you've been doing.
I stopped by your office three
times this week.
Where were you?
I had flu.
And you're better now?
Is that what we are celebrating?
I'm getting married.
I won't be seeing you anymore.
Is this a game?
Are you playing with me?
I know you have my home number.
Please don't use it.
Ever.
- Say: "Please don't use it Tom."
- It's over between us.
It ain't over 'till it's over.
That's just the way it is.
I came here to see you.
To feel you.
To make love to you.
There's no way that I'm gonna
leave here until I do.
Not a chance.
It ain't over 'till it's over.
Make a move.
I'll move faster.
Touch me again and i'll scream.
Scream then. Get it over with.
Get it over with.
I'll have your clothes ripped off.
I'll be inside you before they
break down the door.
It ain't over 'till it's over.
I'll be like one of those dogs
you see in the park.
They'll have to turn a firehouse
on me to get me off you.
Please don't talk that way.
Why? Does it excite you?
- It make me sick.
- Puke then.
But please, don't leave me.
It's tragic, isn't it?
I thught that if you didn't know me,
you couldn't control me.
Now here I am again.
I'm an open book.
I want you to let me go, Tom.
Say my name again.
I love it when you say my name.
Things have a life and that life
comes to an end.
Sit down. I won't move
if you don't want me to.
I just want to feel you here.
No, not like that. Like this.
- can you feel how much I want ou?
- Yes.
Does it feel good?
Do you feel the way it feels?
Yes.
Do you thing that's something
with no life left in it?
Do you think I can
just walk out that door?
When I come I'm only gonna
wanna come again.
That's the way it is.
It ain't over 'till it's over.
I'm gonna kiss you goodbye tonight,
then I'm gonna kiss you hello again
next week.
Yes, yes, yes.
- Yes.
- It feels good, doesn't it?
From now on, Wednesdays are mine.
You're out of control.
Hey, you don't answer my phone calls!
If you don't come to the door at
least come to the windows.
I need to know what your plans are.
I need to know if you'll ever
come back to work.
Look, what happened to you is
horrible. Nobody can deny that.
But a lot of people put a lot of
money and a lot of faith in us,
and when they ask questions,
they deserve answers.
I'll cover you. Just
give me a date, a time.
A week, a month. Six months,
whatever. I just need to know.
Jake, don't be an asshole.
Damn!
Hey, where'd you come from?
What can I do for you?
I'm looking for something for
a friend. Very high, very sexy.
- Maybe red.
- Yeah. What size?
- Seven, seven and a half.
- Okay, I'll see what I got for you.
Everything but red.
Blue.
Pink.
And I heve green.
I had my heart set on red.
It's too bad.
It's a popular colour.
Hey, there. What's your name?
What do they call you?
Stella. Stella.
You know who said that? Stanley Kowalski,
"Street car named desire". Yap?
Tried out for the role in school,
they gave it to one kid with pimples.
That's too bad.
Red shoes with high heels?
I hear that.
Playoffs. Must be the end
of the half. I love basketball.
Thirteen triple E. Nine wide
in eleven and a half double E.
- Am I right? - Yes, right.
- Alright.
- What's up, man? Are you following me?
- Hey, the shoe salesman.
- How you doing?
- Alright. How you doing? A beer?
- I'd love one. - Reese, two beers.
- Okay, two beers.
- I'll pay for that.
- That's alright. Beer, man.
- Thank you.
- My one and only love.
Yes! NCAA action, you can't beat it.
Basketball, beer,
an occasional woman or two.
In a perfect world I'd be black,
6,9 feet and they'd call me Mike.
Some of the guys I played against
in the pick up games around here
are as good as the ones up there,
they took a wrong turn.
- Really?
- You know what I mean? - I do.
- How much money you got on you?
- How much I got on me?
Why, do you need some money?
I bet you a thousand dollars against
whatever you have in your pocket
that I can beat you in a game
of twenty one.
What?
I bet you a grand against whatever
you have in your pocket
that I can spot you ten points
and still kick your ass.
- What, are you kidding me?
- Don't I look like a ballplayer to you?
- No.
- Really?
Not everybody looks
like who they are.
I'd never have thought you were a
guy that sells ladies shoes.
It's a just a part-time job.
I know. When I was a kid, my
mother used to take me shopping,
the guys selling shoes were dignified
with greying hair at the temples,
drink Martinis at lunch,
who would have been gigolos in Miami
beach if they could go there.
That's my idea of shoe salesman.
But you really never know who
somebody is until you test them.
- You never know?
- You don't know.
A grand against whatever
you have in your pocket
says I am who I pretend to be and
I can kick your ass on the court.
What do you say, Michael?
You ready to be tested?
What have you got to lose.
I've called dozens of times,
left dozens of messages.
- I never got a chance...
- Marlene... - Hi.
- I'm just having a beer.
- I'm sorry.
We'll talk about it later.
My friend Ingrid, and this is
Ingrid's friend, Heidi
- and Heidi's friend, Heidi.
- Heidi again.
- And this is Jake and...
who's your friend? - Tom.
- Thomas K. Butler Jr.
- Hi. Tom. - Skol.
- Skol. - Ingrid and I were cheerleaders
together in high school.
Red, white, fight, fight.
Who fight? Red, white!
Fight, fight!
Fight!
She was the "Exchange student extraordinaire",
I was of course " Miss personality".
Now, Ingrid's best friend is Heidi
and Heidi's best friend is Heidi.
- Heidi one and Heidi two.
- Heidi iho.
Heidi one doesn't speak any English
but is just,
knocked out by America.
Aren't you, Heidi? - Yes.
Yes, amd American men.
She says yes to everything.
It's the only word she knows.
I think I've died and
I'm gone to heaven.
Let's bring them along, we play,
they can cheerlead, you and me.
Allright, make the take.
Ten zip. My ball. Twenty-one.
Jake, Jake he's our man.
If he can't do it, nobody can.
Hey, what about me?
Isn't anybody going to cheer for me?
Huddle up, huddle up!
Jake... Three!
I'm surprised at you, Tom.
From the way you talked,
I figured you'be a lot quicker.
Must be the beer, the latitude.
DoctorJack, my ass.
Get off the court,
get off the court now.
Just get off the court,
you're gonna get hurt.
Tom, Tom, he's our man.
Jake, you want some oxygen?
You did that when you were a kid?
Make belive you were an announcer
calling big game?
Time out! Time out!
Medical time out.
Chapagne break.
- Poor baby.
- You get a cold towel, not too bad.
Fuck! Jake, I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to fuck up your beautiful floor.
- No wait.
- Did you get a towel? Get a towel.
Just wipe it up with this.
Shit, you need a... I have a thing...
Contraceptive?
Hope and fear rolled into me.
Talk about paranoia.
- Talk about wishful thinking.
- Come on Michael. Let's go.
I'll be back
I'm gonna toss this guy off.
No basket, it's my ball
You drew blood, you lose, pal.
That was an intentional foul.
I'll let it slide this time,
but don't let it happen again.
You got that?
Oh! Excellent.
I might have underestimated your
athletic ability there, Jake,
but I could tell you lived in such
a place just by looking at you.
Just one look and you said I was
living in a renovated glue factory?
I could tell by your shoes. You could
tell almost everything from them.
Come on, Jake!
Chicks in worn heels,
cracked insteps and scuffs.
I can see their kitchen sinks,
cigarette butts,
plates piled high with mouldy food.
Now, chicks in two hundrd
dollar shoes from Paris.
I can tell, not a scuff
on the heels of toes.
I can take one look at 'em
and know everything I need.
What do you know?
I know what they're gonna smell like.
What they're gonna feel like
Is that right, Tom?
Is that why you sell shoes?
To pull up the shades to their souls?
Or you're gonna look at their feet?
Maybe to catch a glimpse
up their skirts.
I bet you keep a score card of how
many of them don't wear panties.
Tell me I'm right.
- Jake!
- This is crazy! Stop it!
- That's twice.
- Yeah?
Who the fuck cares?
Tell me what she smelled like.
- Tell you who smelled like?
- The chick in the 200$ shoes.
Was it like ivory snow?
Was it like fresh soap?
I ain't talking about a chick.
I'm talking about chicks in general.
And how many chicks
are chicks in general?
Four, eight, ten, twelve, twenty?
This is it! It's over!
What do you call them when they're
all clumped together?
Gaggle? Phalanx? Choir? Possyy?
Stop it, Jack. Someone's gonna
get hurt. I'm serious.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Tell me what she felt like.
Soft as a baby's butt?
Soft as a kidskin glove?
You're fucking nuts, man.
Am I? Tell me about these chicks.
You know what they smell like
and you know what that taste like.
Do you know what's inside their
heads? Anything about them?
Do you know what makes them laugh?
What makes them scream?
All I know is that
they all love shoes.
Every single one of'em.
And they go on buyin'em
until they die.
Guys, this is it. Hey, stop!
Fuck, man!
You fucking win!
Take your fucking goddamn money.
Here it is, take it.
Take the fucking money and
shove it up your fucking ass.
- Where is the bathroom?
- Straight ahead.
Don't quit now, Stanley.
We're just getting warmed up.
C'mon. I'll double your money
and I'll spot you five more points,
and I'll still take you.
That's your problem,
you give up too easy.
Just think, if you had that part
of Stanley Kowalski in high scool,
you could have been a star,
you could have been out of the shoe
business into the show business.
You could have chicks raining
down on you. Gaggles of them.
Litters of them. Covens. Choirs, Phalanxes.
You're a fucking shoe salesman,
you get down on your knees
and you look up their skirts,
that's all you do.
Get a real job, punk!
You mother fucker. Shit, shit, shit!
I miss her so much.
She would always tell me
that I was okay.
And that was pretty tough.
No.
I'm in love with a lady who
wears two hundred dollar shoes.
She was never a chick.
She was a always a lady.
Doctor, lawyer, Indian chief.
House in suburbs, Mercedes coupe.
And now she's probably married,
pregnant, starting to turn fat.
- Yes.
That's where I found her,
in that room.
Do you think that's all I'll
ever be, a shoe salesman?
Don't answer that.
Oh, Jake.
The fucking bastard. Fuck you!
- Come on out!
- Stop it!
What are you doing?
Don't! Don't!
I'm sorry. I just need to be alone.
I'm sorry.
- Can you girls go? Please?
- Yes, sure.
- I had a good time.
- Ingrid, did you see my bag?
Thank you girls. Come.
- My friend.
- What...?
- I have to get my friend.
- Where you going? No.
Okay, get your friend.
- I'm gonna stay. I think I'd just stay.
with him and you. - No.
I really think I should. You're do
something, I know you are.
NO Marlene. I'm fine.
- Don't fucking lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- Promise?
- Look. I'm fine. I'll call you.
- You'll call me?
- Sure, I'll call you.
- I'm fine. - I'll call you
in ten minutes. - Okay.
Would you please hurry up?
You gotta go outside.
- Heidi, come.
- Tom?
- No Tom, no more Tom.
- Good night.
Tom? Tom?
Tom, this is me and you, Tom.
Come on out, Tom.
It's just me and you, Tom.
One-on-one.
What's this about?
What do you want from me?
Put them on, bitch.
Where is she, motherfucker?
Where is she?
She's dead.
She killed herself.
This is Alex's stuff.
I loved your dauther.
I know you did.
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
Joey, can I get some quarters,
please?
Hi, I'd like to take out an ad
in your Personals column.
Women, do you keep a diary?
Have you been betrayed?
Have you betrayed another?
Man 35, wounded and alone,
recovering from loss of
once-in-a-lifetime love,
looking for reasons why.
Willing to pay top
dollar for your experiences.
Please send diaries to Red Shoes,
P.O.BOX7956-319,
Canoga Park, California 90309.
All submissions strictly confidential.
Thank you.
Edited by geoguyro.