(DISTANT DOGS BARKING)
(DOG HOWLING)
(HEART BEATING)
(WHIMPERING)
(CLICKING)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(GROWLING)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DISTANT DOG BARKING)
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
MAN: Well...
- we love the characters.
- But?
- It's a terrific story.
- And?
And the... (CHUCKLES)
- The dialogue is great.
- Paul.
I just wanna make sure
you give them your best.
(SCOFFS) Oh, my God.
Look, don't get me wrong.
We do think it has a lot of potential.
- Did you even read it?
- Of course I read it, Anna. Calm down.
I am calm, but this is the third time
you're telling me to rewrite my draft.
I mean, how am I even supposed
to meet the deadline, Paul?
Just take a look at the notes.
- I'm sure it's an easy fix for you.
- Yeah, that's what you said last time.
Why not let the studio decide
if they like it or not?
Because you only get one shot at this.
Listen, Anna.
This is me managing you.
I'm not trying to piss you off,
but it's not like one of your blogs
where people can look at photographs
when they get bored of the writing.
Well, that got your attention,
didn't it?
I just don't want you to be one
of those writers who screws up
before anybody's even read their script.
I've got you this chance, now use it.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
I've been experiencing sleep paralysis
since I was a little kid.
Like my mind is awake.
I can see and hear and feel,
but I can't move any part of my body.
It's terrifying.
(DISTANT DOG BARKING)
(OWL HOOTING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(KNOCKING)
PAUL: It's me.
I don't like flowers.
You should know that.
Yeah, well, it's the effort
that counts, though, doesn't it?
Do you have any idea what time it is?
PAUL: It's never too late
for an apology, is it?
I just wanted to say sorry
for this afternoon.
I think I was a bit rough on you.
I just don't want you to waste
your first opportunity, that's all.
No, thanks.
Really?
It's not like you to turn down
a glass of wine.
- I just had an Ambien.
- (PAUL CHUCKLES)
Still popping the pills, then?
- I thought you came for an apology.
- I did, but...
Well, then stop talking
and come to bed before I fall asleep.
PAUL:
Oh, I meant to tell you that I, um...
I managed to buy you
a little bit of extra time.
They agreed to, uh...
postpone the deadline on the script.
So I was thinking maybe we should
get out of the city for a few days.
You know, just relax.
Get some good sleep.
Forget about the draft.
You know,
take the heat off a little bit.
It'll be inspiring.
Remember I told you I have that
little hideaway out in Joshua Tree?
So around me is utter devastation
with dead bodies
floating down the street
and buildings collapsing.
And I have nothing better to do
but to go downstairs
and underwear shop with Prince
at what has turned into a Black Friday
sales event at Wal-Mart.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
Yeah, I started writing down
my dreams again.
A better dream memory is supposed
to help against nightmares.
Wow.
My therapist would make
a fortune out of you.
(BARKS)
(LAUGHS)
(DOG BARKS)
ANNA: Found some croutons in the cupboard.
I hope they're not expired.
(SIGHS)
- Man, this place is gorgeous.
- Yeah.
How come you've never
taken me here before?
Uh, it's been rented for the past
year and a half or so.
Do you think you're gonna be able
to relax while you're here?
ANNA: I don't know,
but I think that's up to you.
- ALEX: I'll do my best.
- Mmm.
(OWL HOOTS)
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
- (MOANS)
(WATER RUNNING)
(GARBAGE DISPOSAL GRINDS)
Ugh.
(SIGHS)
(RATTLING)
- (GARBAGE DISPOSAL GRINDS)
- Oh, fuck!
Oh, shit.
(GARBAGE DISPOSAL GRINDS)
Got you, you little fucker.
(DOOR SLIDES OPEN)
- PAUL: Come on, boy.
- (DOG BARKS)
Huh.
So I leave you for five minutes
and you've destroyed my kitchen.
I just, uh...
fixed the garbage disposal.
Yeah, you don't wanna touch that thing.
It's a fucking death trap.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
Listen, I, uh...
I got a call from the office.
You get reception?
Yeah, about a mile down there's a hillside.
You get a few bars up there.
Yeah, anyway, they called
and said they've had to put
an emergency meeting together
about one of my clients.
Apparently I'm the only guy who can...
who can talk to him, so...
Well, just tell them
you're already with a client.
Anna, I...
So we have to go?
When?
Kinda now.
Look, I'm really sorry. I wouldn't do this
if it wasn't an emergency,
but I've tried him and he's not
picking up. And there's no...
No, it's... it's fine. I understand.
Oh, come on, baby.
Come on. I'll make it up to you.
We can come back again
in a few days if you'd like.
Well, if that's the case,
why don't I just stay here?
Well, 'cause I'm taking the car.
And you'd be here by yourself.
Yeah, but it's fine. I mean,
didn't we just buy enough food for a week?
Well, yeah, but...
And maybe if I'm left alone,
I can get a little writing done.
I'm not a little girl, Paul.
All right.
I'll just do a little checklist of things
you need to know about the house
and I'll leave him for protection.
Protection from what?
- You never know.
- Oh.
- (CHUCKLES) No, he's good company.
- Sure, why not?
Well, it's just me and you now, Shadow.
And my laptop.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(OWL HOOTING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(SIGHS)
(TICKING CONTINUES)
(OWL HOOTING)
(SIGHS)
(CLOCK TICKING)
All right, fuck it.
Hey, buddy.
Ready to go for a hike? Yeah?
- All right, let's do this.
- (BARKS)
(BARKING)
- (SIGHS)
- (BARKING)
(SHADOW BARKING)
(SHADOW WHINES)
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
(ANNA GASPS)
(GROWLING)
(SHADOW BARKING)
Come on, Shadow.
Shadow, come on!
Shadow, come!
- Hey!
- Oh!
I'm sorry.
- What are you doing here?
- I was just out on a hike.
You're out on a hike, huh?
Look, are you some sort of park ranger?
No, I'm not a park ranger,
but this is my home. I live here.
I stay right over there.
(SHADOW WHINING)
Did you come from the glass house?
Yeah.
Is there something wrong?
No. No, there's nothing wrong at all.
I just used to, uh...
I worked for the owner.
- Paul.
- Mm-hmm.
What did you say your name was?
Anna. I guess we're neighbors, then.
Yeah.
Well, um... it's nice to meet you.
Let's go, Shadow. Come on.
Shadow, come on.
(OWL HOOTING)
(UNEVEN BREATHING)
(GASPING)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(ANNA WHIMPERING)
(DISTORTED LAUGHING)
(GASPING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES, ZAPS)
(PANTING)
(RUSTLING)
(ELECTRICITY HUMMING)
Oh, God.
(BARKING)
(COUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(GROANS)
(BARKING)
Oh, finally!
(DIALING)
This is Paul Wagner.
I can't get to the phone right now.
- Please leave a message...
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- (DIALING)
- (PHONE RINGING)
WOMAN: Ford and Willis Agency.
- How may I connect your call?
- Paul Wagner.
Mr. Wagner is in a meeting.
Would you like to leave a message?
No, Emily. It's Anna. This is an emergency.
Can you get him on the phone right now?
Hello, Ms. Parker. I'm afraid Mr. Wagner
cannot take your call right now.
No, Emily! You don't understand, okay.
It's an emergency!
I need you to get him
on the phone right now.
I'm just gonna keep calling back
until you get him on.
- One moment, please.
- Thank you.
(SIGHS) Anna.
Oh, thank God.
What's up?
The... the house isn't safe, Paul.
What do you mean the house isn't safe?
Has somebody broken in?
No, I... I don't know, all right?
Somebody's been there.
- PAUL: Did you call the police?
- No, I... I wanted to call you first.
When are you coming back?
I don't... I don't know yet.
We've got another meeting tomorrow which
could take a while. Is everything okay?
No, I'm not all right, Paul.
All right? I'm freaking freezing
and I'm standing on a mountain
in the middle of nowhere!
All right, just calm down.
Tell me exactly what happened.
I don't know, but the power went out
and this morning when I woke up,
there were... there were all these numbers
written all over the glass.
Are you sure it wasn't just a bad dream?
No, Paul, please!
You don't understand, all right?
This is different!
I can show you when you get here.
Look, Anna, it's gonna take me
all night to get there.
If you call the police,
they'll be there much faster.
No, I don't want the police. Do you get it?
This place freaks me the fuck out!
I wanna get out of here!
(SIGHS)
Okay. Okay, just calm down.
I'll tell them to push my schedule.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Just lock yourself in the house
and everything will be fine, all right?
Fine.
- Shit.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
(OWL HOOTING)
Oh, great.
(SHIVERING)
(PHONE BEEPING)
Shit!
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Oh.
- Good boy.
- (SHADOW WHINING)
Good boy. Yeah.
You're lucky you had the dog.
It was because of his persistent barking
last night that I even bothered to come over.
How's your head? You must
have a hell of a headache.
How did you get in here?
Well, that would be your keys.
- Give me those.
- Uh-uh.
- Give me my fucking keys.
- Easy!
Oh, what are you gonna do with that?
I swear to God, if you don't
give me my fucking keys,
I'm gonna beat the shit out of you!
Okay. All right.
Take your keys.
Nobody's threatening you.
Bullshit! You... you knocked me out
and you dragged me here to...
- To do what?
- I don't know.
I saw you running around last night.
You recognized me, you tripped over a rock,
you cracked your own head.
And the stuff on the wall,
you... you put it there, didn't you?
What the hell are you talking about?
Any idea what it means?
Come out here.
Take a look at this.
These are all the same.
3-0-2-12.
It's a date. March 2nd,
2012.
What?
Who did this?
- I thought you did.
- Why would I do this?
I don't know. I mean, you're the only one
out here. I just assumed.
- I gotta go.
- What does it mean?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do.
- Okay, wait, just... (SIGHS)
Look, you don't have to talk
about it, all right?
Will you just...
will you just stay
until it gets light out?
I don't feel safe here.
(EXHALES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Hi.
How you feeling?
What time is it?
3:00 in the afternoon.
You slept quite a while.
What happened to your head?
Did you see the numbers?
- What numbers?
- In the bedroom on the window.
No, I didn't see any numbers.
I saw the trash bags. I took them down.
Was it too bright in there for you?
This is ridiculous.
(PAUL SIGHS) Anna.
- It was all over the place.
- Listen.
There were no numbers on the windows.
There were just a couple of trash bags.
- I took them down, that's all.
- You don't believe me.
No, it's not that I don't believe you.
I don't know, maybe you had
another nightmare.
It wasn't a nightmare, Paul!
It was a date. March 2nd, 2012.
- It was all over!
- Look, stop! Anna, please.
This has gone too far now.
- Does that date mean anything to you?
- No, it doesn't.
You know what? Ask your housekeeper
or groundskeeper, whatever he was.
- He was here. He saw it.
- What, Jeremy?
- Yeah, I think that's what his name was.
- What was he doing here?
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
He helped me! He...
Okay, pack up your things, get ready
to leave. I'm gonna talk to Jeremy now.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Jeremy.
(COMPUTER CHIRPING)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLICKING)
I saw your little trick
with the graffiti.
You can't hide from me, Jeremy!
You try another stunt like that,
I'll have immigration
send you back to Canada.
Little wanker.
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(COMPUTER CHIRPING)
(COMPUTER KEYS CLICKING)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
PAUL: Hey, Anna, are you in there?
Uh, yeah.
- Are these bags ready to go now?
- Yeah, you can pack 'em.
Oh, listen, have you seen the key
to the boiler room?
- The what?
- The key for the boiler room.
I need to turn the furnace off
before we go.
Wait.
- I haven't seen them.
- Really?
They're not in your jeans or something?
Hold on a second. I'll be right there.
All right.
Oh, listen, would you mind
hurrying up a little bit?
I don't wanna get snagged up
in rush hour traffic.
Actually...
- Ah, here they are.
- Why don't we stay?
(ANNA GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING SHALLOWLY)
Paul?
Oh, hey. Morning.
So why did you sleep
on the couch last night?
Was I that bad in bed?
No, I, uh... I just couldn't sleep.
- Nightmares again?
- No, thank God.
- All right, I won't be long.
- Okay, I'm gonna go and get gas.
Okay.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Excuse me.
- More coffee?
- Uh, no, thanks.
I'm sorry, this might seem a bit random,
but do you know this woman?
She built a modern style glass
house out here,
about 10 miles north
of the old Gamma Ranch.
You may want to talk to Joe over there.
He knows everyone in town.
Thanks.
(CHATTER)
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you, but, um...
my name's Anna and I'm looking
for someone from around here.
The bartender said
that you might be able to help.
I'm staying at the glass house.
It's 10 miles north. You know it?
Yeah, I know that house. What about it?
I'm looking for the architect,
Vera Palm.
Does that ring any bells?
Let's talk outside.
I know her housekeeper.
- Jeremy?
- Yes. He...
- comes in for guidance now and then.
- What sort of guidance?
For $39 a session, you can find out.
I also offer a lot of original
healing stones and native artwork.
My shop is right over there.
I think this has been
a misunderstanding.
Are you sure?
Hey, Anna, you ready?
Look, I'm just trying to find
this woman.
Well, you can't. She's missing.
Since when?
- Last March.
- Wait, what happened?
JOE: Number's on the card.
Oh, it's freezing in here.
Why don't you take a little nap?
Then when you wake up,
I can grill up some of these, uh...
juicy local steaks I keep hearing about.
You know, I'm really glad
we decided to stay in the end.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Why did you lie to me?
What?
Don't, Paul. Why did you lie to me?
(SIGHS)
And there was me thinking we might
have a nice, quiet evening together.
- You know what happened on March 2nd.
- Who have you been talking to now?
Doesn't matter. What matters is you didn't
tell me the truth and I wanna know why.
(SCOFFS)
Okay, uh... the truth is
I didn't want to scare you.
It can be pretty intimidating out here
when you're by yourself.
I just didn't wanna fuel
your vivid imagination
with legends about
disappearing people in the desert.
Well, if it's just an urban legend,
then why not tell me?
Because that's what they are.
They're just...
(SIGHS)
Okay.
The designer of this house,
the architect of this house...
got lost in the desert.
She went for a hike and never came back.
Apparently it happens all the time.
People get lost, but she didn't come back.
- And you're saying you didn't know her.
- Well, how would I?
(SCOFFS) I don't believe you.
Anna.
I'm getting worried about you now, Anna.
It's... it's somewhere down here.
- Well, I guess you cleaned it out.
- The photograph? Yes, I did.
Because you didn't want me
to see her with you.
Of course I didn't want you
to see me with my ex.
I wouldn't want to see photographs of you
lying around with your ex either.
You're hiding something from me. And don't
just keep blaming it on my vivid imagination.
Oh, really, Anna? Because considering
your history of mental illness...
Nightmares are not
a mental illness, Paul!
Well...
judging by the amount
of medication you're tak...
I know what I've seen.
I made a terrible mistake.
What?
You're right about one thing.
I've been hiding something from you.
I couldn't just watch you pounding
these things down day after day.
They're placebos.
At least you've been having plenty
of vitamin C the last few days.
You switched out my pills?
Yeah.
That's why you've been having
such extreme reactions.
I'm sorry. I thought you could...
do without them.
I was wrong.
What are you doing?
Anna.
Don't touch me!
You know, maybe this writing gig's
just a bit too much pressure for you.
- I can't stay here tonight.
- Oh, God.
- I'm gonna stay in town.
- You serious?
- We'll talk tomorrow.
- Okay, well, listen.
Take these. Have a good night's sleep.
(GRUNTS)
(CAR BEEPS)
JOE: Who is it?
It's Anna. We met this afternoon.
I need to talk to you.
I'm closed.
You can come by again in the morning.
Are you sure?
These are all handcrafted
from various tribes.
Some from my own family, in fact.
(HITS DRUM)
Some I just picked up over the years.
Let me know if you're interested
in anything
and I'm sure we could work out
some kind of a discount.
Could we just start the session?
Yeah, of course.
Why don't you, um...
pick one of these stones.
- This one?
- Sure.
Good choice.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- Really?
- I don't have a free hand for the drums.
This will work just fine.
Just relax.
Why don't you, uh...
take off your top.
You gotta be kidding me.
Do you want me to help you or not?
(SIGHS)
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
Now lay down.
(RATTLING)
Now...
We'll search for the chakra
with the most negative energy.
(RATTLING)
Whoa.
What was that?
What just happened?
Do you ever, uh...
feel a growing pressure in your chest
when you... when you dream?
A feeling of numbness in your limbs
almost as if you were paralyzed?
How did you know that?
In the native culture, it's known that
spirits can possess the body when you sleep.
They can capture the soul
and take control of the flesh.
To do what?
It depends what you've done.
ANNA: But I haven't done anything.
No, I don't know what's happening
to me, all right? You have to help me.
Please.
The only... only way
to fight off this spirit
is to control your dream
and command it to leave.
We'll, uh... induce a wake-initiated
lucid dream and you'll become conscious.
When you reach that state, I need you
to perform some sort of physical activity
so that your muscles will echo
that movement in this realm.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Lay down.
Just listen...
and focus.
Listen and focus.
Let yourself sink deep into the bed.
Let your limbs go numb.
Okay.
Don't fight it.
That's it.
That's good.
You are awake... in your dream.
You're in a state of pure awareness,
but totally...
(WIND HOWLING)
...paralyzed.
That's good.
(WIND HOWLING)
(WHISPERING)
Stay in control.
Stay in control!
JOE: Anna!
Anna!
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING) Oh, my God.
Paul?
PAUL: Have a good rest?
'Cause I didn't.
Spent the night worried about you.
Feeling guilty about
swapping out your drugs.
But then I discovered this.
- (KEYBOARD CLICKING)
- Wednesday. Thursday.
Friday.
Sunday.
Where's Saturday, Anna?
I... I don't know.
That's weird because...
Saturday's the night
you were here by yourself.
Let me show you something.
I couldn't really care less
about the surveillance cameras.
Well, it's not as though anything
really happens around here, is it?
But then Shadow
found something out there.
And I thought to myself...
"What is Jeremy's body
doing buried in my backyard?"
Look...
I'm sure there is some...
perfectly rational explanation
for all of this.
And if there is...
you should tell me
before I call the police.
(PAUL SIGHS)
I'm gonna make the call.
You should stay here.
It can get pretty dangerous outside.
There's nowhere for you to go anyway.
(WIND BLOWING)
(BARKS)
- Come on.
- (BARKING)
(SHADOW BARKING)
(SHADOW WHIMPERING)
Come here.
All right, you stay here, Shadow.
All right? Stay.
So what now?
Eh? You're not gonna go anywhere.
Neither are you.
Well, why would I?
The police will be here in a minute.
Great, then you can tell them
what happened to Vera Palm.
What?
The blind woman who mysteriously
went missing out on the salt lake.
Who you keep pretending not to know
although her dog
is standing right over there.
Yeah, he dug this up
out on the salt lake.
So tell me, Paul. How did she go missing
if her guide dog was out there with her?
Vera was my wife.
She was a very talented, but, um...
unsuccessful architect.
This house was supposed
to change all of that.
For two years, the only thing she did
was work on this project.
Day in, day out.
She became obsessed with the place.
And by the time she laid
the foundations...
(SIGHS) ...we were living
completely separate lives.
We were like complete strangers.
She invited me out here to celebrate
when it was completed.
VERA ON PHONE:
Paul? Are you still there?
PAUL'S VOICE: But why would I?
VERA ON PHONE: I wanted you
to come out and celebrate.
PAUL'S VOICE:
This house had stolen my wife.
VERA ON PHONE:
I can't believe you're doing this.
Paul?
Paul, are you still there?
On the way home that night...
she fell asleep at the wheel
from sheer exhaustion.
When they found the car,
they said, um...
that she was lucky because...
the Joshua tree she hit
stopped her from going over the cliff.
But a branch came in
through the windscreen and, um...
blinded her.
Then what happened?
I became her scapegoat.
If I didn't already feel guilty,
she made me feel guilty.
She didn't miss a chance
to make me feel her pain.
I really tried,
but I just couldn't imagine...
being her caretaker
for the rest of my life.
So when she started to get better,
I got her the dog.
And she came to live out here
by herself.
My life was finally
becoming normal again.
And then something fantastic happened.
I met someone new.
Someone I could fall in love with again.
Then Vera called me
one day and said, uh...
said she wanted me to come out here
to discuss something.
It was the best time we'd had
for over a year.
Anyway, by the time
we got to the salt lake,
I realized what it was all about.
She said she wanted
to move back to Los Angeles,
have another go at our marriage.
It was the last thing I wanted to hear.
So I told her about us.
She was furious.
She said she would divorce me.
I would lose everything.
All my savings, the house.
She said she would ruin me
if I didn't stay with her.
Who wouldn't side with a blind woman
whose husband had cheated on her?
I couldn't let that happen.
You killed her.
We'd, um...
we'd walked quite a long way
into the salt lake.
And I just, um...
took the dog and kept on walking.
They never found her body.
This happened on March 2nd.
Yeah.
And Jeremy knew.
He saw me coming home without Vera.
Started asking some questions.
But an illegal immigrant
is easy to keep quiet.
You have to tell the police, Paul.
No, I'm not gonna let her ruin my life.
No, you don't understand. You have to,
all right? It's the only way she'll stop.
What are you talking about?
It was Vera that killed Jeremy
and she's gonna come after you next.
Have you gone completely nuts?
(SIGHS)
If you don't tell the police, I will.
Well, be my guest.
I can't wait to see the expression
on their faces
when a... a drug-abusing writer
with a history of mental illness
tells them that my ex-wife's ghost
is on some kind of revenge mission.
I'll let you do the talking.
PAUL'S VOICE: She said she would
ruin me if I didn't stay with her.
Who wouldn't side with a blind woman
whose husband had cheated on her?
Don't let her do this to us.
Don't let her separate us, Anna!
(GLASS BREAKING)
PAUL: Open the damn door!
- Shit.
- (GLASS BREAKING)
- (POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
- Stand down!
Officer, thank God you finally arrived.
(GASPS)
You need to drop that rock, sir.
- No, I know this looks a little weird.
- Drop that rock.
Officer! Please, you have to help me!
Don't listen to him!
I need you to drop the rock, sir.
Right now!
- There's just been a bit of a mis...
- Drop the rock!
Turn and face the window! Turn and face
the window! Hands behind your head.
(BARKING, GROWLING)
Tell your dog to back off!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GASPS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (OFFICER GRUNTING)
PAUL: Oh, fuck.
(PANTING)
- (CAR STALLING)
- Shit!
- Fuck!
- (CAR STARTS)
(SCREAMS)
(CRASHES)
(STEAM HISSING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(CRYING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(ANNA CRYING)
(PANTING)
(ANNA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ANNA GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(COUGHING)
(WIND HOWLING)
Ma'am? Are you all right?
Can you move?
Are you okay? Ma'am?
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)