Our solar system was formed over
4.6 billion years ago
in a galaxy called the milky way.
There are nine planets total
some experts would
argue eight
not counting Pluto,
a dwarf planet.
But I say nine
Mars is my favorite.
Ladies and gentlemen
I'd like you to meet
my good friend
former astronaut
Commander Perry Scott.
He led two Shuttle missions
and is now in charge
of rocket production
at Cape Canaveral.
Every planet is different,
I want to visit them all,
sail around the solar system.
Like Magellan
who circumnavigated
the globe.
When I grow up
I, Bradley Maguire
will circumnavigate
the solar system
and this model
will be my guide.
I want you
to see some others.
There's some great
ones back here.
Is anyone listening to me?
Hello?
It looks so,
real.
Stop!
Gee thanks!
A chocolate crater on Mars.
Unbelievable.
Hey what do you
think of my exhibit,
is it worth your vote?
It looks cool
but it doesn't do anything.
I want more chocolate.
Very precise rendition.
Enjoy your chocolate.
Bradley Maguire?
Aborting the mission, right?
Nobody cares.
Son,
with the exception of that
chocolate crater
this is one of the most detailed
accurate models of Mars
I've ever seen.
The Valles Marineris.
Impressive.
So you realize
what a waste of time it was.
What about that
one vote I saw you dump out?
What about him?
Some schmuck.
When I was a kid,
all I wanted was
to be an astronaut.
At that time sending
a man into space was
unthinkable.
But do you know
what my dad said to me?
the universe
is your playground.
Keep your chin up.
Up in the sky, look!
- It's a bird.
It's a plane. It's Superman.
We're here at the top of the hour
at Kennedy Space Center
with this breaking news.
We now join Katy Collins
broadcasting
live from Rocket Garden.
Last night at 8:51 pm
NASA lost communication
with the Horizon 1
the first manned spacecraft
en route to Mars.
The craft is scheduled to arrive
on the red planet in 2 weeks.
NASA experts are working
to reestablish communication
with the astronauts on board.
but so far
their efforts have proven
unsuccessful.
NASA made their first public
statement early this morning
around 6:00 am
acknowledging that the
crew members families
had been notified
late last night.
NASA did not go into great detail
as to what exactly happened.
But we have with us
Dr. Carl Spence,
NASA's emergency strategist
on the line inside NASA headquarters.
Dr. Spence when did you
last hear from the crew?
We lost communication
last night at precisely 8:51 pm.
Dr. Spence
what is the state of the crew?
The ship is currently
what we call transit float.
Whoa!
In other words.
Look what you have done.
I am so telling on you.
I, I didn't mean to.
We assume
the astronauts are continuing
on their plotted trajectory.
Which is exactly what the ship's
computers are programmed to do.
We have no reason to believe
the astronauts have deviated off course.
As such we will continue
to monitor their trajectory
and hope to reestablish
communication soon.
At this point,
all we can do, is wait.
The ship was burned to pieces.
Stop it!
You don't care!
What?
They're dead!
We're not dead!
We're out
that's how the game works.
Dodgeball!
Yeah that's it.
- Dodgeball!
I'm trying to tell you something.
- Whoa!
Stop it!
Yes. - Yeah.
- Stop it!
Oops!
Are you okay?
I think you killed him.
- Is he dead?
I should have dodged.
It's dodgeball.
If you don't move
there are consequences.
Dodged. Dodged.
Dodged.
Dodged. That's it!
Dodged!
Did we scramble his brain?
We better go see if he's okay.
He's lost it.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Hey can you guys help me?
You figured that out yourself?
Yes.
Well. - Wouldn't their
eggs destroy the spaceship?
I mean if they were
the size of school buses.
I was almost hit
by a school bus once.
Shut up!
That's what I thought,
but take a look.
At first I thought the ship
must have exploded, but
you see how
it's more like a streak
then just a round explosion.
Wouldn't NASA know about this?
They're like the smartest
people in the world.
How could they miss it?
Well NASA thinks
the astronauts are still on course.
Which is what the ship's computers
are programmed to do.
At least that is what NASA says.
But I think they dodged.
They knew they had
to get out there fast
to avoid the meteors
headed their way.
Blast off!
The rocks must have damaged
the spacecraft's antenna.
Which is why we can't
communicate with them.
NASA probably lost contact
with them before they dodged.
And I think they're looking
in the wrong place.
But they're out there.
We just need to find them.
Wait a second,
something is not right.
Neptune, Jupiter, switch.
Perfect!
Now that the planets
are in place, wind strength.
Hey, could you turn Mars slowly?
I need to make some estimates.
Mars is approximately
2,940,000 kilometers from earth.
They were only two weeks away.
And so from out of nowhere,
came the meteors.
They dodged,
sending them off course.
Traveling so fast
they'd be...keep turning.
Keep turning, keep turning.
There!
They'd be,
landing on Mars?
Just in the wrong place.
I've got an idea.
I know, I know.
- This is important!
I need to see
Commander Perry Scott!
I don't think you kids
are authorized to be here.
And besides,
where are your parents?
We came here on our bikes.
Alone. And you?
Please let us in.
Lives are at stake!
Security!
NASA's failed
attempts to locate and
reestablish communication
with the astronauts... .
Ah, over here, Security!
Spirits across the country are low.
Psst! Come on guys.
Kids!
- Come on!
Commander,
you should take a look at this.
I need to get through
to mission control.
Listen, kid.
No, you listen to me!
I need everybody
to listen to me!
Lives are at stake!
There are a bunch
of astronauts up there,
and I think they're in trouble.
I think I know how to find them.
Commander, I hope
you're out there.
I need you to get down here,
I have something to show you.
Congratulations, Bradley!
You did it.
Congratulations, to all of you.
I have something to show you.
Follow me.
Cool.
- Awesome. - Wow.
I can't believe it.
- Amazing.
I want to be
an astronaut some day.
Yeah Bradley,
can we go to space with you?
Of course.
The universe,
is your playground.
The End
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
E N J O Y   this   SRT   SUBTITLE   R e l e a s e
http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1731670
The Planeteer (2010) English for hearing-impaired.srt
AND: The Planeteer (2010) English.srt
FPS: 23.976
With special thanks to: "Emmanuel, Victor and Raymond"
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
We want more subtitles right NOW!
1) ALL DVD's to be subtitled.
2) ALL VIDEO GAMES to be subtitled.
3) ALL videos/DVD's used in lessons at school to be subtitled.
4) More pre-recorded & live subtitles on TV.
____           __            ___   __              ___        __               __
/     /   _   /    )  _   _ (_     /  _)        _  (_      _   /  _)        _   / _   _
(     /)  (-   /(_ /  (-  ( /  /     /(_)  () (/ _)   /   () /    /(_)  () (/ _)   (__)  /  () (/  /)
- Bringing you free subtitles       /                  Online  /  Since 1993    - /
-  |Africa| |Asia| |Australia| |Europe| |North America| |South America|   -  /
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+                          A big Thank You to EVERYBODY                            +
+        involved in making [closed capture] srt files and supporting us       +
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+