(Horns honking)
(Radio tuning)
[Radio] Laughter
is a sin around here.
You know why?
Because laughter
can mean happiness
And I want you
boys to always know
Happiness don't exist for you.
It exists for the
privileged, for the loved.
The world outside
don't care about you!
So laughing is just pretending.
And if they make believe
over here, uh-uh.
This here is a home
for the wayward,
For the orphaned,
for the discarded.
I am setting you up to succeed.
Because y'all too stupid
to know the truth.
And you'll thank me for this
when you get old enough, okay?
Believe me, you'll thank me
for telling you the truth.
(Horses whinny)
My hates have a tendency
to move around, you know?
I hate that I'm losing
this game of cards.
I hate you asking me questions.
Frank Stone?
I neither hate him
nor like him.
I'm a professional headmaster.
I'm objective.
I'm not a homosexual.
I'm a pedophile.
It's different, okay?
I teach them boys who they are.
So society wants to kill it.
These boys up here,
who do they got?
Ain't nobody, just
each other, just boys.
They gotta learn how
to love each other.
So I teach 'em how.
I don't mess with old men.
I'm married.
It's degenerate.
Outside the bounds.
He's on the other
side of the street.
I'm walking down
the street, right?
Right street.
He's across the street.
Always has been.
(Radio static)
Working for the mob.
Who does he think
he is, Al Capone?
(Suspenseful music)
(Screams)
(Screams louder)
[Wife] No, no!
(Screams) No, no!
[Frank] Knock it off.
(Crying)
I said knock it off.
(Panicked crying)
I got it open.
[Frank] Get the merchandise.
(Heavy breathing)
(Engine roars)
[Frank] Slow down.
You can get the
cops on a day off.
Listen to me, you
stupid jerk-off.
You're not my boss, so
don't talk to me like that.
If I want to get some action
off some brawd, I will, okay?
That's my business.
I thought you acted
inappropriately.
Were you tryin' to get
us popped for rape?
Next time, I'll
just fuckin' kill...
[Safecracker] Whoa!
[Frank] You should have
kept a better class of friend.
(Gunshot)
(TV plays)
[Radio] I see the
frustration of sin!
I feel the frustration of sin.
Let me tell you, if
you don't already know.
Sin is the apple that's
put in front of the horse.
It was the apple presented
to Eve in the garden of Eden.
And it's the apple
of my eye when I see
That nice little
rump on all of you.
It's mine to take!
I'm headmaster.
That's, like, God.
That's, like, the
final say, okay?
(Laughs)
I take, I give, my surrender.
But make no mistake!
It's still me and not you.
None of you have a
claim or say.
I am the last word.
Okay?
(Sirens wail)
(Horn honks)
(Phone rings)
[Man on phone] Hey Frank?
[Frank] Yeah.
[Man on phone] The boss
wants to see you tomorrow.
Understand?
(Children laughing)
[Vinny] Let's
not talk about it.
Hooked on that shit?
It's in their veins.
[Man in yellow] That's like
that energy drink, right?
It's their methedrine,
their methedrine.
The first energy drink ever.
Man, their first guy's
talking shit all the time.
Hey, Bud, are you in?
Hey, Frank, how're you doing?
Sit down, sit down.
What do you have for me?
A pretty nice haul.
Whoa!
Nice.
Real nice.
Clean job as always?
A couple of bumps
in the road,
But I paved them
over, as always.
[Tony] Yeah, I heard.
You know, you're one
coldhearted sonofabitch, Frank.
Took out his own guy.
You know, you remind me
of this bedtime story
That my father,
God bless his soul,
That he used to
read to me as a kid.
It was about an evil
bastard, just like Frank.
I'm tellin' ya.
Frank, did your
father ever used
To read you bedtime stories?
(Guys laugh)
I never knew my ol' man,
Tony.
Oh, I'm sorry,
Frank, I didn't know.
I didn't know, Frank.
Give him his money.
The money!
[Vinny] Okay, Frank,
here's your money.
Thanks, Tony.
[Vinny] Hey, Frank, I
got a question for you.
Now that you got all those
fazool's in your pocket,
Which one of your brawd's
you gonna take out?
(Laughing)
Maybe take a shower...
Take her to Paris, some
place more high end,
Romantic like Coney
Island for a hot date.
Did you need
anything else, Tony?
[Tony] No, that's it.
Thanks, Frank.
Good work, good work.
Have a nice day, fellas.
Yeah, take it easy, handsome.
What you guys
break his balls for?
He's a fern.
Alright, come on,
let's play cards.
Come on, come on, come on.
(Melancholy music)
(Whip snaps)
(Children laughing)
(Horses whinny)
Long, long time ago...
Long time ago!
You know, man figured out...
Animal skin, beneficial to 'em.
Good thing.
Now, like this here, keep
ya warm in the winter.
Dry in the summer.
My happy thing.
Animal skin.
Like this belt here, see?
It's leather, animal skin.
But there's many
different functions.
There's holding my
pants, you know?
Tie a woman down and shoot.
Be a good thing, too,
sometimes.
Depends on the girl.
Those women are hard to...
Hard to figure them out
sometimes, you know?
(Spits) It's romantic.
Hit 'em for the
punishment and...
You know, wrap it around
your hand like this
Or on your fist like this.
Bam!
No more problem.
That man go down.
It's going down!
Turn around, now.
Turn around!
Grab your ankles.
But you don't listen.
Now I'm gonna fix your
radio, I'll teach ya.
I'm using this belt as,
alright?
And this is a
romantic use for it.
(Leaves rustling)
Some place this was.
It's a good thing
they closed it.
It was horribly run.
Those poor boys, they use
them like punching bags.
That's what I heard.
It's a good thing we
didn't go there, huh?
(Menacing music)
Hey, you better hurry up.
Class starts in a few minutes.
What?
Oh, I thought you were in
my Creative Writing class.
Sorry.
Dominic was loaded, as usual.
He loved to drink,
which was a good thing
Because at this point,
he had to drink.
If he didn't start his
day by rolling out of bed
And crawling to the freezer
for a few shots of vodka,
His hands would shake and
he'd start to feel sick.
And he'd become as manic
as a mental patient.
But what are you gonna do?
Everybody's got their cross...
(Elevator bell dings)
Dominic was a drunk and
would always be a drunk,
But he was okay with that.
He was the heartbreakingly
tragic figure
He always wanted to be,
but with an abdominal sense
Of human that made
him borderline heroic
In his own mind.
Sure, he was destined
to crash and burn.
But it was going to be
epic, if not entertaining.
He had already come
close to cashing in once.
Couple of winters back,
he was found passed out
In his boxer shorts in
the boulevard during
A failed attempt to
get to a liquor store.
He spent the next five
weeks in the hospital.
Initially, the doctors didn't
give him much of a chance.
Dominic's liver was shot.
He was completely
yellow with jaundice.
His skin was yellow, the
whites of his eyes were yellow,
If he had been wearing
a top hat and a monocle,
He could have passed
for Mr. Peanut,
But somehow he survived.
Supposedly, the
liver is a highly
Regenerative organ,
or so they told him.
The doctors lectured
Dominic about how he
Was being given a second
chance to live and how he
Needed to make some serious
lifestyle changes...
Alright, thank you,
thank you, Bradford.
Anybody have any questions
for Bradford, class?
Yes, Ackley?
It didn't do anything for me.
Okay, okay...
[Ackley] I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
If that's what you
felt, that's okay.
Did't do, yeah, I'm sorry.
[Mr. Benson] Okay, no,
if that's how you felt...
Yeah, I just feel like
it just lacked emotion.
[Mr. Benson] Yes, Jackie?
I have something, Mr. Benson.
Okay, Jackie, go ahead.
[Jackie] Okay (Laughs).
Alright.
Alright, Jackie, go ahead.
Okay, okay, sorry, okay.
He never stayed long.
Never.
He liked Rosemary's company,
But always seemed
to be in a hurry,
Like if he had a duel
life or something.
But Rosemary didn't mind.
She was lonely.
And lonely women cry at night.
Rosemary got sick of it.
That's why she wore
her fancy bottle
Of perfume and best dress.
She wanted him to caress
her like a mink coat.
But it didn't happen this time.
Rosemary wept after he left.
She thought about
swallowing that whole
Bottle of pills,
but decided not to.
She didn't want any
man thinking
Someone killed
themselves for him.
Rosemary, instead, painted
a horizon on a canvas.
It seemed brighter
than her future.
You alright, Jackie?
[Jackie] Yeah, no, I
just get nervous sometimes.
Okay, what do you
call this story?
[Jackie] Oh, God.
I guess I would call it
"The Girl in Apartment 3J".
[Mr. Benson]
Alright, does anybody
Have any questions for Jackie?
Yes Ackley?
[Ackley] Yes, I was
wondering how long
We're gonna have
to hear about these
Desperate characters of yours.
The same characters from the
last story that you brought in.
I mean, when are
we going to hear
Something good for a
change, something...
What?
With more levels.
More, I want more.
I'm so sorry, Mr.
Herman Melville.
[Ackley] I wouldn't be
caught dead reading Melville.
Excuse me, Ackley?
Ackley, we could
do without that.
Well, the whole function of
this creative writing class
Is to learn and
experience and to grow.
[Ackley] I, yeah, I...
We do not need to
criticize to
The extent that you take it to.
- [Ackley] Oh...
- [Mr. Benson] Jackie?
What do you, what were
you feeling when you
Wrote this particular
passage to your story?
"The Lonely Girl
in Apartment 3F"
No, it was "The
Girl in Apartment 3J".
But I like that.
"The Lonely Girl
in Apartment 3F"
But, she's afraid
of being an old maid
And all her friends
are wondering...
Okay, Jackie,
thank you, thank you.
Does anybody else have
anything they'd like to read?
No?
I would like to read...
[Mr. Benson] Yes, Ackley?
I would like to read
my piece for the class.
[Mr. Benson] Can
you make it quick?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
So, this is an ongoing...
This is part of a trilogy.
You speak of one and...
[Mr. Benson] Okay,
alright, class dismissed!
(Sirens wailing)
[Radio] Frank!
Frank!
(Laughing) Frank!
You listening to me?
I know you hear me.
(Laughs)
(Engine revs)
(Horses whinny)
(Whip snaps)
(Children laugh)
There are certain
things in life.
things that are
Passed down in life, you know?
Like father and son.
In our case...
Headmaster to a...
Orphan.
Like the love of huntin'.
Yeah, killin'!
(Laughs) That was a good one.
That was a good one.
Fishin'?
Yeah, fishin' will work.
Yep, today, though, I'm
gonna do some new tradition.
From a long line of traditions
Between a headmaster
and orphan.
That's called sharing
a bottle of bourbon.
It's good.
Good for ya.
It's good, you know, I mean...
Take your mind off
of things that...
You know, get your mind off
of things that bother ya.
About yourself and stuff.
Purify your soul!
Got one.
What do you think
them priests be
Doing in church with
their wine?
Drunk.
Want a taste?
Here, here, have a taste.
I said to have a taste.
Here, go on.
There you go.
Not too strong, huh?
Too strong?
Whoa, hey, that's enough there.
Come on, give it back.
Give it back, it's mine.
It's mine, give it back!
It's a gift.
It's a gift to you, it's mine.
(Grumbles)
Take your pants off.
(Sirens wail)
Yes, may I help you?
I would like to take your
creative writing class.
Great.
Have a seat.
[Frank] Thanks.
Is there any
particular reason you'd
Like to join my
creative writing class?
No.
Well have you ever
written anything before?
No.
Nothing?
No poetry or news articles?
Okay, name?
Oscar.
Kissel.
Okay.
Oscar.
A lot of people have come
in here like yourself
That they have a lot to express
and they don't know how.
Creative writing will
help you with all of that.
I'm gonna give
you an assignment.
I want you to go home
and write about something
You know or like, but
make it fictitious.
If you like flying
on planes, write
A story about an airline pilot.
Or if you like walking
in the park on Sundays,
Write a story about
a softball player
That does well in
that park on Sundays.
Whatever it is,
do it thoroughly.
Get into details.
I want you to make
our class believe
In your character,
that it's real.
And then we'll feel for them
in their problems, okay?
Softball player?
(Typewriter clicking)
(Radio static)
[Radio] Goddammit, Frank!
Didn't that sweet ass you
got for a creative writing
Teacher tell you to write
about stuff you know?
Well, you know about the darker
things in life, don't ya?
So write about that!
Now get back on that
typewriter.
And write about that, you
mangy looking bastard.
Come on, I learned
you better than that!
Go.
(Intense music)
The night never knew a
shade darker than his soul.
That's what everybody used
to say about Frank Stone.
Like a clap of thunder, he
was brought into the world,
And like a flash of
lightning, he lived.
And that was pulling
off jewelry jobs.
It was his vice.
It gave him comfort, control.
And he would stop at
nothing to get it done.
Nothing.
He was as serious
as a heart attack.
(Horses whinny)
(Children laughing)
(Typewriter clicking)
But how can one live when
laughter can't sooth their soul
?
Frank knew he was dead
inside, born dead.
Didn't understand why.
Only certain things
made sense to him.
Like being found in a
dumpster on Christmas Eve,
With the umbilical cord
wrapped around his neck.
No.
That can't be good.
That was clear.
That's exactly what the
syndicate looks for, too.
Men with rage.
Frank was the most comfortable
in this kind of environment.
So was his boss,
Tough Tony Forte.
A local punk gangster
with a long arm,
Who always gave Frank work...
Whenever the need
would arise.
And fortunately for
Frank, that need
Came about on a regular basis.
He couldn't wait
to get that call.
It's the only time Frank
seemed to come alive.
That was just the way
things were in his world.
Hard, cold.
That was Frank Stone.
That's all I got so far.
Thank you, Oscar,
that was interesting.
Does anybody here have
any questions for Oscar?
Yes Ackley?
I'm sorry, but
that sounded like a
Gangster movie from the
1940's or something.
It was like just
so totally fake.
And, like, no one in real
life sounds like Frank Stone.
Except, since World
War II or something.
[Mr. Benson] Philip
Ackley, once again,
We are not here to judge.
We are here to
analyze and interpret.
Does anybody else have
any questions for Oscar?
Yes, Jackie.
Well, I thought it was good.
I really liked it.
It reminded me of one
of those crime novels.
You know what I'm
talking about?
Like they sell in
the bus depots.
You know, those things
that they're supposed to
Take your mind off the
journey you're about to go on.
I love those things.
I was once on this bus trip
from Virginia to New Mexico...
Yes, yeah, thank you.
Thank you, Jackie.
Does anybody else have
any questions for Oscar?
Okay, it not, well
class dismissed.
(Phone rings)
[Tony] Hey Frank?
Yeah?
[Tony] You can go ahead
with that operation.
[Frank] The Grobe brothers.
Vic and Ronnie, I presume.
[Vic] We're here.
Start talking.
I like your manners.
Sit down.
This job we're going to pull
is in the diamond district.
This place is an
upstairs distribution.
The way it works, you
guys got to "go-between".
He carries the diamonds
down in a little briefcase.
He doesn't take the
elevator, he uses the stairs.
It's bonafide, I
checked it out.
That's what will
make it happen.
How many stones
will he be carrying?
150k, minimum.
What's our cut?
It's a flat rate.
Twenty-five grand each.
Twenty-five?
What are you,
crazy or something?
We split it three ways
or we ain't interested.
Look, these
diamonds, they're rare.
No fence in New York is
gonna deal with them.
All you need to know is it's
gonna take time and money.
And that's the rate, 25k.
Nah.
Split it three ways or nothing.
Nothing it is.
You know, I was told you
guys were professionals.
I guess I was told wrong.
Sit.
Does that mean you're in?
Yeah.
[Frank] Alright, you
got any other questions?
[Ronnie] Yeah, I
got one question.
Me and my brother, we heard
a couple of things about you.
We need you to
clear it up for us.
You heard some
things like what?
[Vic] That whoever
works these jobs of yours,
They never get seen again.
Let me tell you
something, fellas.
People talk all the time, they
talk for a lot of reasons.
Envy, jealousy, greed.
All you need to
know is if you're
Square with me, I'll
be square with you.
I'll be in touch.
Hi!
How you doing?
You're new here.
I'm Jackie.
Well, actually, we met
the other day, kind of.
Yeah, what's yours again?
What?
Your name, dumb-dumb.
Oscar.
Oscar Kissell.
[Jackie] So what
are you hoping to be?
A mystery writer or something?
I don't know.
Oh my God, is that typed?
Do you...
You used the typewriter.
I didn't even know they
were around anymore.
I like typewriters.
I mean, I like things...
Hey, what's that?
Oh!
Gotcha.
Okay, class, everybody
take their seats.
We're gonna start.
[Voiceover] Monday,
late afternoon.
Diamond district.
And Frank Stone gets ready.
A large Romanian man
comes out of an office
With a briefcase full of bling.
But, today, that large Romanian
gonna be in for a surprise.
(Speaks Romanian)
You two midgets
think you can rob me?
Try it.
[Vic] Jesus Christ,
there's a fortune in here!
[Ronnie] Nice!
Grab the bag, let's
get out of here.
I think there's only
enough for me and my brother.
What?
[Vic] You heard me,
you dirty double...
[Frank] It's called
the double-cross.
Or the dirty double-cross.
Someone turning on
you is one of the
Unfortunate hazards
in this line of work.
Luckily for Frank, he's
always expecting it.
[Mr. Benson] Wow,
that's interesting.
It really is getting more
and more cohesive, Oscar.
Keep it up.
Hey, hey Oscar!
Hey!
Well, I was just wondering if
you wanted to get a coffee?
So, I just wanted to know what
Goes on in that head of yours.
What do you mean?
[Jackie] Well, how do you get
your stuff to sound so real?
I don't know, I just...
I feel like I'm in the same
world as your characters.
It's...
I don't know.
I just write whatever
comes into my head.
Wow, I mean, Frank
Stone is so cold.
He has a lot of
demons in his past.
They're going to stay there
until he gets rid of 'em.
He doesn't trust anyone.
That's how he survives.
[Jackie] Have you always
had this kind of imagination?
Did you read those recommended
Books the teacher
told us about?
I didn't read anything.
You're so serious!
But you're modest, too.
Can you pass me the sugar?
Boo!
Oh, sorry.
(Horn honks)
Thanks for giving me
a ride home, Oscar.
That was nice.
Well...
When did you start dressing
like a little tugboat captain?
You know, do you
like the open sea?
Hello?
Yeah, you...
You don't give that much.
You really don't
talk that much.
Oh.
Are you hungry?
Why don't you come
upstairs and let me
Make you a
fluffernutter sandwich.
Have you ever had one?
I can tell you haven't had one,
Cause your eyes didn't
light up when I said it.
You're missing out.
Do you want a beer?
No thanks.
I don't drink.
[Jackie] You don't drink?
Yeesh.
What are you, a boy
scout or something?
How about a glass of milk?
[Frank] That sounds good.
[Jackie] Here you go.
(Horses whinny)
What's the matter, Oscar?
I don't know.
Something strange
just happened.
[Jackie] What?
The horse on the glass
here reminded me of
Something that happened
to me when I was a kid.
You know I was raised
in an orphanage.
And one day, me and
all the other boys
We were all taken
on a field trip.
But when the bus got
there, the first thing
That I saw was this
beautiful Grey horse.
So I approached the
horse really slowly
And I was talking to him
softly, the way a kid would.
And all of a sudden,
the horse, he went nuts.
I mean, he went
totally haywire.
Started jumping up on
his hind legs, kicking.
He broke free from the chain
And he started to
scare the other horses.
Well, horses do weird
things like that sometimes.
Yeah, well the
headmaster, he got so angry
That he grabbed me and he
started to beat me publicly,
Right in front of
the other boys.
That headmaster
sounds like such a jerk!
And after that, all the
kids, they laughed at me.
They humiliated me, mocked me.
And I'll tell you
that headmaster...
After that, he never
missed an opportunity...
Let's change the subject,
talk about something else.
Hey, Oscar?
(Laughing)
Isn't it funny?
I'm leaving.
[Jackie] Oh, come on.
What's the matter with you?
Listen, you may think
everything is a joke.
But me, I take
everything seriously.
And I don't appreciate
you mocking me.
[Jackie] I wasn't
mocking you.
What's the matter with you?
I...
(Overlapping conversation)
[Vinny] Oh, look who it is!
It's Mr. Personality!
He came here to brighten up
everybody's day, now didn't ya?
I got a question
for you, scumbag.
How come you make everybody
sick at the very sight of you?
You got the
personality of a cobra
And I've had it up
to here with that.
Come on, Vinny, knock it off.
Sit down!
You have to excuse Vinny,
Frank.
Anyway, how are you
doing today, Frank?
Doing good, Tony.
Can I get you
anything to eat?
You don't have to be shy,
we have plenty of food.
More coming out.
No thanks, I'm not hungry.
No?
Give him his freakin' money,
let him get out of here.
[Frank] Thanks.
Oh, oh, Frankie, Frankie.
You know, not for nothing,
But we offer you
food all the time.
And never once, once, do you
everysit down and eat with us.
What's the matter?
My gesture of friendship
doesn't agree with you?
Look at me when I'm
talking to you, Frankie.
Now I want to know why you
think you're too good for us.
Look, it's not that, Tony.
It's just, you know,
I got some place
I got to be in a hurry.
Hurry?
Where you got to be, Frankie?
Somewhere.
[Tony] Frank.
The only place
you should ever be
In a hurry to get to is home.
Cause home is where
the family is.
Here, look, let me show this.
This is my family, alright?
This is my wife, my kids when
They were younger,
my grandkids.
And this, this is the
most cherished picture
I have of my father,
God rest his soul.
You know, I loved him more than
any son ever loved a father.
What about you, Frankie?
Do you have any
pictures of loved
Ones you'd like to show us?
No?
Why not?
You're always in such a
hurry, I would think that
You had hundreds, hundreds
of pictures to show us.
Now the next time that
I ask you to sit down
And eat with us, make
sure you have the time.
Alright, now get the
hell out of here.
Thanks, Tony.
What did you say?
What did you just mumble?
I said thanks, Tony.
[Tony] So, anyway,
about this weekend...
(Piano music)
[Voiceover] There's
nothing more frustrating
Than a man who just
can't express himself.
You know, tell you
how he feels.
That makes him no
different than a lamp.
Or a clay pigeon.
Yeah, clay pigeon, waiting
to get blown up into pieces.
Maybe that's why.
Maybe that's the root
behind Frank Stone's rage.
He just lives,
second to second.
Minute to minute.
Murder to murder.
Like an alcoholic.
Just one day at a time.
That's my boy.
* Bright eyes and
colors are blind again
* Haven't seen my love
in God knows when
* He went away, now
I'm all by myself
* All of this heart aching
is affecting my head
* Oh no
* I've been so alone, waiting
for you to get back home
* No more good mornings
or I love you
* Never thought my
nightmares would be so true
* All this seems
to fight for me
* But all I ever wanted
was for us to be alone
* I've been so alone,
yeah, waiting for you
* I waited for you
to come back home
* Yeah, I'm so alone,
I waited for you
* But now you're gone
(Applause)
[MC] Wasn't she great?
Chelsea, let's give
it up for Chelsea.
Great girl, nice act.
And now, next, he's your
favorite ventriloquist,
Mr. John Peasy.
Hey, folks, my name is John
Peasy, this is my friend Smokey.
Holy shit, they're all white!
Okay, we have a great
crowd of people here.
Yeah, they look good, this
look good, I like it, like it.
Yeah, we got a good crowd.
I'm the only black guy here.
Oh, it looks like my trial.
Looking good, looking good,
looking good, looking good!
I like this crowd, yeah, yeah.
If you like white people, yeah.
Hate them white men shit.
Oh yeah, now...
Hold up, where you
going, brother?
Sit the hell down, where
the hell you going?
I hate when a white guy gets
Up in the middle of
a show like that.
Sit the hell down, cracker ass.
Sit the hell down.
I'm in the middle of my
working here, cracker ass.
Don't sit there and
get up in the middle.
I'm working here.
Alright, don't pick
on the guy, huh?
He's a mean-looking guy.
What do you mean?
He looks like a killer.
Yeah, killer, I'll
kick his ass.
Homo, sit the hell down.
Don't pick on the guy.
I don't give a shit!
Look at him, I see you staring.
Let's have a
staring contest, go.
This is comedy, brother.
You don't just get up and
Walk out in the
middle of a nice show.
Alright, that's
enough, that's enough.
Why don't you say something to
The guy that would
make him feel good?
The way he looks,
attention k-mart shopper.
He's a loser, I can't stand
his white cracker ass.
That's right, folks, you
can laugh all you want.
I'll kick his ass right now.
Loser, loser, loser.
And you're white, cracker ass.
Hey!
This was just a joke, man,
I was only kiddin' ya!
No, no!
This week, Olivia's mailbox
wasn't empty as usual.
This week, it contained one
of those lovely pink slips
That indicated she had a
package at the front desk.
The clerk was so
excited for her.
Olivia, you have mail today!
Politely, she smiled
and took the package.
It was a five dollar
flat rate box.
Olivia was reminded
of how much her mother
Loved sending flat rate boxes.
Each week in college,
Olivia would receive
One of these packages, a
veritable treasure trove
Of candy, costume,
jewelry, school supplies,
Anything a college
girl could desire.
The package that
she was handed today
Was considerately different.
On the outside, it
looked like a standard
Five dollar flat rate box.
But the contents had
a macabre difference.
This package contained
her mother's ashes.
Wow.
You really have tapped into
something very personal.
Now, class, what we can
take from Mario's story
Is don't be afraid to
be deeply personal.
Oscar, please come on time!
Okay, Jackie, you had
something you wanted to read?
Uh, yeah.
Alright.
Rosemary thought
she was different.
She was always told that.
By her father, by her
mother, by her classmates.
She grew up thinking
bad about herself.
That's why she tried to
slit her wrists many times.
But she always managed to
find a way to get through it.
She thought she had met someone
who could relate to her.
Another tortured soul.
But this person was more
than a tortured soul.
He also felt the need
to be hateful and cruel.
He didn't want to
change himself
Or discover who he really was.
He didn't want to move
on from a dark past.
He wanted to relive
it every day.
He was pure nasty.
I hate him, I hate him.
[Mr. Benson] Wow, I...
Wow.
Jackie, I must say
you've really tapped into
Something very personal
to get this latest work.
Anybody have any questions?
Ackley?
I have to say, I thought...
[Mr. Benson] Oscar!
Oscar, please wait outside.
[Frank] Alright.
[Mr. Benson] Okay...
Wow, that was weird.
[Vinny] Alright, go to
Jimmy's on 10th street.
You know the way.
What the hell is that banana
head doing over there?
Pull over, pull over.
Stop.
What the hell is Frank Stone
doing in this neighborhood?
Wait up a second, I
want to talk to you.
Look, I'm sorry that I
spoke to you that way.
Alright, I made a mistake.
I thought you were
making fun of me.
What do you want, Oscar?
There's something
I gotta tell you.
Alright, my name isn't Oscar.
It's Frank Stone.
Your character?
And I work for Anthony Forte.
Tough Tony is real?
It's all for real, alright?
That's what I am, I'm a hood.
Why are you telling me this?
[Frank] I don't know.
I just feel like my
head's gonna
Explode if I don't tell you.
Just please, just
leave me alone.
Please, I'm sorry.
Please just stay
away from me.
What the hell
was that all about?
Wait here, I want to
go see what's going on.
Did I almost get
a smile out of you?
Almost.
Frank, how come
you never smile?
[Frank] Can I
ask you something?
You never once told me
anything about yourself.
Well you know
everything about me,
But I don't know
anything about you.
I'm just not that
open about myself.
My private self, that is.
[Frank] Yeah?
Is that why you
joke around so much?
To hide that private self?
No, that's not why.
You know, if you don't want
to talk about it, it's okay.
Well I married this really
Rich guy that I
didn't even love.
But I figured I'd
have everything.
But it wasn't really enough.
But then we had a
beautiful daughter.
Beautiful, beautiful daughter.
And my husband left me and...
He got full custody of her
and I can't even visit her.
So you see, all I want
to do is just call her.
Tell her I'm sorry
and that I love her.
But I can't.
[Frank] You listen to me.
I got to go right now.
[Jackie] Where are you going?
I got to go.
But when I get back,
you and me,
I'm going to take you
to see your daughter.
But she doesn't even know me.
She doesn't know
me at all anymore.
[Frankie] She
knows who you are.
And, believe me,
there's no Time
Like the present to
get reacquainted.
Everything's going to
be all right, Jackie.
You'll see.
I'll be back in a few hours.
[Tony] Hey, there he is!
Frankie!
Hey, Frank, have a seat.
How you doing, Frank?
How you doing, fellas?
Today is your
lucky day, Frank.
We got a call from
our boys out in Vegas
And they need someone
from back East
To run the security at
the casino and to oversee
All the used jewelry
business they got out there.
And I couldn't think of
anybody but you, Frank.
Me?
Yeah.
Well, for how long?
How long?
For as long as it takes, Frank.
You're going to be making
a cool 200 grand there.
200 thousand dollars?
[Tony] Yeah.
That's a lot of money, Tony.
[Tony] Yeah, you go
out there, you work hard,
You find one of those
show girls, you know...
Settle down with
her a little bit
And be happy for once in your
life, you miserable bastard!
You know, I mean 200 grand
make anybody happy, right?
When am I supposed to leave?
First flight tomorrow.
Hey, what's the matter?
You seem disinterested, Frank.
No, that's not it.
It's just that, you
know, I got a little
Something I gotta take
care of with someone.
You know, I'll definitely
make the flight, Tony.
Okay.
Is there anything else?
Yeah, just one
more little thing.
When you get out there, I
was just wondering if you're
Going to write anymore stories
about me and my operation.
Kill that rat bastard!
No, no, no, Vinny, Vinny,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Maybe we shouldn't do it here.
You know what?
Just take him down to the
warehouse and chop him up.
Come on, let's go
chop him up.
Pop the trunk.
Who's this?
Hey, fellas.
Can you tel me how to get
to the 59 street bridge?
Yeah, you keep
going straight.
If you hit the water, it
means you missed the bridge.
Hey, man, your humor
flows like molasses.
And if you keep going
straight and you hit water,
It means you missed the bridge.
[Police] Call for backup.
Tell him in Italian.
(Speaks Italian)
Hey, why don't
you keep smoking?
Or burn out.
[Police] Central B5
requesting an additional unit.
(Gun shot)
(Sirens wail)
(Police radio)
(Whistles)
Alright, call it in.
20 boy central,
requesting one addition.
[Radio] 5 boy 4 by on there?
[Intercom] Paging Dr. Bender.
Paging Dr. Bender, please.
Dr. Bender to the
mental ward, please.
[Detective] How
you doing, Frank?
Mind if we talk to
you for a minute?
I don't think he heard us.
Hey, Frank, can you hear us?
How you feeling, Frank?
Been in a coma for a few weeks.
I'm Detective Manteiga,
this Detective Maas.
We're from the
Organized Crime Unit.
We'd like to ask you
a couple of questions.
Would you mind explaining
to us how you ended up
In the trunk of
Vinny Gallino's car?
[Detective Maas]
Yeah, Vinny Gallino.
He works for Tony Forte.
Did you owe him and
his boss some money?
Come on, you know who
we're talking about.
Tony Forte, aka "Tough Tony".
Did you owe them money?
Come on, Frank.
Don't play dumb shit
with us, alright?
We're not rookies, we've
been around a long time.
You obviously must have done
something to piss them off.
What was it?
Did you get caught skimming
off the top, or what?
You mind telling
us what's so funny?
This guy's bananas.
[Intercom] Paging Dr.
Statement, Dr. Statement please.
So he's not crazy?
[Doctor] Well his head
has no structural damage.
But it's hard to
say at this point
Without doing any
further tests.
You think maybe you're
trying to put one over on us?
I don't think so.
Unbelievable.
The one guy we
find and he's nuts.
Anything he says is not
going to hold up in court.
You know that?
Yeah.
But I'm not buying it.
Thanks, Doc.
You know, I came into this
world full of piss and vinegar.
You know, I started making
my bones by running numbers
For Hunchback Charlie
and the 9th Avenue boys?
And I was still in Junior
High School when I did that.
I ran porn theater, strip
clubs, I had a stable,
20 girls working for me.
I started putting some
money out into the street,
Charging a vague that no
one could compete with.
I made a lot of money
for those fellas.
I made some serious scratch.
But then...
The babania, shooting
up four times a day.
Lost everything I had.
Wound up doing ten years
in jail for armed robbery.
Ten years.
When I got out, I was clean.
And I wanted to get back
into the business, you know?
So I had an uncle vouch for me.
And I went back into action.
And, now, it's taken
me 30 years, 30 years
To get my reputation
back and I'll be damned
If I let some muck like
Frank Stone bring me down.
Now I want that son of
a bitch taken care of.
I want him put on ice.
And I want that done, now.
Hate to be the
one who told you so,
Tony, but I told you so.
(Laughing)
[Intercom] Dr. Forest,
dial 118, please.
Dr. Forest, please dial 1-1-8.
(Machine beeping)
[Frank] No matter
where you roam.
(Laughs)
* They call it the blues
(Laughing)
I have to sit next
to you now.
I gotta sit next to you!
What's so funny, man?
What's so goddamn funny?
Come on, white boy,
share with me the joke.
See, last week this time,
I had a job, I had a car.
I had a woman.
A woman!
I had a woman, white boy.
I was making good
money, Arizona.
The place to be to work for
the right to make a living.
I used to play in the band,
a band like rock 'n' roll.
Stupid camisoles in the 80's,
that's where I met my girl.
Well, my ex girl.
She left me, white boy.
She left me for...
You're laughing!
She left me for a short order
cook and goddamn Mexican!
A goddamn Mexican!
[Frank] Dude, that's
just wrong, man.
My life sucks, white boy.
[Frank] What's
your name, brother?
John.
But you can call me Cricket.
Everybody calls me Cricket.
Cricket, cricket,
like a cricket.
That jumps around.
I jump around like a cricket.
[Frank] Oh, Cricket, baby.
[Cricket] I love you, white
boy, you're the best, man.
I have a tattoo.
[Frank] Yeah?
Tattoo of a cricket.
Look, look, look.
[Frank] Ah, look at that!
It's a cricket.
[Frank] Listen,
you know, brother?
I really appreciate you opening
up to me like this, brother.
I mean, really I do, you know?
I mean, from the heart.
The heart?
[Frank] You know
what I'm saying?
From the heart, brother.
(Hand buzzes)
[Cricket] Holy shit, man!
Oh, man!
Dammit!
Dadgummit!
(Continues yelling)
Alright, guys, finish
your drink and get out.
Wait a minute!
Wait, you throwing me
out of here for laughing?
Is that...
I mean, what is wrong
with this place?
Hey!
This place sucks!
Hit the door, pal.
I want you out of here, now.
[Frank] Alright,
alright, alright.
[Frank] No hard feelings.
Alright, I'm going, okay?
I'm going.
Hey, what's that on your nose?
(Yelling)
Crazy, man!
Goddammit!
[Frank] Hey, Cricket.
[Cricket] Goddamit!
Hi.
(Laughing)
Hello?
Hey, listen, I've
had a hell of a day.
I just broke out of a hospital.
What the hell you
laughing at, it's true!
These fuckin' guys
tried to kill me.
They did!
They took guns, they
were shooting at me,
They shot up the place,
they shot up my pillow.
Well, I needed something to
wear, so I borrowed these.
The guy next to me
was dying of TB,
I figured he didn't need 'em.
You're kind of a fun audience.
You, you, I love you.
Oh my God, you!
(Laughs)
I had eight dollars
stashed in my socks.
And I dug it out and
stuck it in my pocket
As I walked up Broadway
towards 137 street.
I saw Flockle standing in
front of the subway entrance.
"What's happening", I said.
Not much.
[Bystander] Yo,
what are you doing?
No!
Oh!
Keep throwing!
[Voiceover] Dear Jackie,
it's your friend, Frank.
I've been meaning to call
you for some time now,
But thought this note would do.
Something happened
that changed my life.
I'm still not sure
what exactly,
But all I know is
that I'm happy.
Truly happy for the first time.
And I want you to be happy.
So I suggest we see
your daughter together
As originally planned so you
can tell her that you love her.
Meet me at the coffee shop
tomorrow at three o'clock.
And we'll leave together.
I can't wait to look at
your inspiring presence
And your beautiful
face once again.
Thank you very, very much for
Taking the time
to understand me.
Your friend, always, Frank.
[Jackie] Frank?
How the hell did
you get in here?
That letter you wrote
me was so beautiful,
I cried like a baby.
[Vinny] Like a baby, huh?
Look at me.
I want to ask you one question.
One question.
If I don't like the answer,
we're gonna bash your face in.
Frank take you to
Coney Island, huh?
Did he do this to you, huh?
Did he do this to you?
I'm gonna ask you one question.
Where is Frank Stone?
I swear I don't know.
Answer him.
One more time,
where is Frank Stone?
[Jackie] I swear I
don't know!
[Vinny] Where is Frank Stone?
I swear I don't know.
I'd tell you if I did, I
swear, but I don't know.
Finish her off.
(Laughing)
Oh, if it isn't
Cocky and Snowwinkle?
What's up, Frank?
Paper time's over,
pajama boy.
Enough of the clown routine.
Catch any bad guys
lately, coppers?
Cut the bullshit,
Frank, alright?
We want you to testify
against Tough Tony.
I don't wanna, you know?
I'm having so much fun just
hanging out and being happy.
Why are you protecting
this piece of garbage?
He tried to have you killed.
So did my mother, but I don't
hold that against her, huh?
Yeah, well I can understand
why your mother hated you.
I know you five seconds
and I can't stand you.
Detective, you should really
Try a more refreshing
breath mint.
You think you're
crazy, huh, Frank?
Look at that.
But I'm the one who's
crazy around here.
I'm from east New York.
Brooklyn, kid.
We used to throw
people off rooftops.
Stick up gangsters.
Rob drug dealers, then
we'd sell it back to them.
So don't sit here and think
You're the only
one that's crazy.
Let me tell you something.
If I didn't have this badge,
I'd forget that I'm a cop.
[Detective Maas] I'd
really listen to that, Frank.
What are you gonna do?
You going to throw
me off a rooftop?
Then keep laughing.
Aren't you supposed to meet
that girl that you like?
Jackie, right?
[Detective Maas] I
got something for you.
You're gonna like this.
She's waiting for
you at this address.
Now that's funny.
[Frank] Is Jackie Mott here?
Oh no.
(Horse whinnies)
Where'd you take us?
I told you, this is the best
Rub and tub joint in
the city, bar none.
See, this is what
I'm talking about!
[Woman] Hello.
Follow me, please.
[Vinny] Sure, anywhere.
(Intense music)
(Tires screech)
(Horse whinnies)
Come on, I want
to win tonight.
(Gun shot)
(Tires screech)
(Horse whinnies)
(Urinating)
(Phone rings)
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
[Tony] Yes, it's me.
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
[Tony] I have a problem
that needs fixing.
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
[Tony] I found this
rat in my kitchen
And it needs to be
exterminated right away.
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
[Tony] I want you to
get the best exterminator
Money can buy,
that's what I want.
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
[Tony] He's the best?
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
[Tony] Alright,
set up a meeting.
[Man on phone]
(Speaks Italian)
Now I want to hire you cause
Word got around to me
that you're the best.
I know what people
call you by reputation.
What should I call you?
What do you call yourself?
Lucifer.
I'm gonna give you a chance
to live up to that name.
Because this isn't
business, this is personal.
I want you to cause
Frank Stone more pain
And suffering than
humanly possible.
I want you to cause him
more pain and suffering
Than you ever caused
anybody, ever.
Do we understand each other?
(Knock on door)
[Detective Maas]
Frank, open up.
We have a search warrant.
You think he's in there?
[Detective Maas]
Come on, Frank,
Or we're going to
bust down the door.
(Knocks on door)
Frank, open up.
(Radio static)
(Gun clicks)
(Grunts)
Well?
Did you get him?
I asked you a question.
Did you kill him?
Did you kill Frank Stone?
What's the matter with you?
[Girl] Bye, dad.
[Frank] You're Sarah, right?
My name is Frank.
I was a friend of your mom's.
She wanted me to
tell you something.
She wanted me to tell
you that she loved ya.
That she always loved you.
(Church bell dings)
How you doin', Tony?
Alright.
Alright, Frank.
You got me.
So just do what you got to do.
Alright, I just made
peace with my maker.
I don't care about dying.
Go ahead, do what
you got to do.
Do you really think a
one minute prayer is going
To straighten things out with
the big guy upstairs, Tony?
Yeah, I do.
He knows what I did
was out of necessity.
Necessity?
(Gun shot)
Frank!
[Frank] You feel it, Tony?
That's the feeling
of pain and agony
That you cause people
out of necessity.
I'm an avenging angel, Tony.
This time you hurt
the wrong person.
[Comedian] (Laughs)
Yeah, I feel better.
I used to be a bit
of a partier.
I used to drink too much.
A lot of people say to me
"Art, what's a wild
night of drinking to you?"
"You look like
you've had a few."
And I have.
A wild night of drinking
to me is when you
Drink too much and
eventually you pass out.
And when you wake
up, you're naked
In a police car with two cops.
But the weird part
is, you're driving.
That'll be a wild
night of drinking!
Not for you, man.
That's like a Tuesday
night for you.
(Laughing)
I did a lot of drugs, as well.
The reason I did
drugs was, I think,
The anti-drug slogans
when I was a kid were bad.
Like, remember "hugs
are better than drugs".
That didn't work for me.
My mother used to scream that
at me as I left the house.
"Remember, hugs are
better than drugs."
And I believed her.
I believed everything
my mother said
Until the first time
I got high at a party.
I leaned back and
I was like "Wow."
"This is way better than
when my mother hugs me."
"What else has she been
lying to me about?"
[Audience member] Oh my God!
Do I not have
great bone structure?
Am I not the best looking
boy in New Jersey?
Hugs are great, but
better than drugs?
Come on, let's not
lie to the kids.
Let me put it to you this way.
I never drove to Harlem at
4am to get somebody to hug me.
Hey, Carlos, here's 20 bucks,
just put your arms around me.
I grew up with a
domineering mother.
She would say stuff at the
Top of her lungs,
screaming at me.
Some bad, some good,
it was confusing.
I didn't know what to do.
She would say stuff
like "I hate you!"
"I never want to see you again."
"Are you hungry?"
"Get out of this house
and never come back."
"There are chicken goblets
in the refrigerator."
And since then, I
gained some weight.
I'm not gonna lie to you,
I've had some weight issues.
I try to lose weight.
Someone said "Oh, you
want to lose weight?"
"You should go swimming."
I've never been swimming
before in my life.
And that's because
it has never been
More than a half an
hour since I last ate.
You know what I'm
talking about?
(Clapping)
(Slow music)
[Mr. Benson] Any questions?
No?
Alright then, well
let's move on.
From nothingness came I,
and it is where I shall go.
Well, at least that is
what I used to think.
During those lonely days
and sleepless nights,
To pacify my soul, I
would say these words.
They made me, somehow,
understand my existence
Until I had to live
another day of coldness.
And I lived those
days and wept.
Like all men who
contemplate their agony.
Then, like a ray of sun
peaking through the clouds,
You came shining on to me.
With a radiance only the birds
of paradise could understand.
Bringing forth
wisdom and beauty,
Compassion and understanding.
Mercy.
Then, without warning,
you left this world.
But not without teaching me
who I am and what I should be.
And where I should go.
And it is that which I
am most grateful for.
That you taught me
to see the light.
Have a good night,
Tony, see you tomorrow.
Hey Tony?
I changed my mind.
I'm a person who
knew Frank Stone, okay?
When he was a
little, little boy.
Before he had a chance to
turn his rage on the world.
Okay?
Who are you?
And if you know, you'd be the
First person I
ever met that did.
Okay?
I got nothing else
to say to you.
Now many men don't mean this
when they say it, but I do.
If you don't leave here right
now, I'm going to kill you.
Okay?