MAN VOICE-OVER: Are you paying attention?
Good.
If you're not
listening carefully,
you will miss things,
important things.
I will not pause.
I will not repeat myself,
and you will not interrupt me.
You think that because
you are sitting where you are
and I am sitting where I am
that you are in control
of what is about to happen.
You're mistaken.
I am in control.
Because I know things
that you do not know.
Manchester Police Department,
please hold.
CONSTABLE THROUGH RADIO: Windows broken.
Home's been ransacked.
Send a detective down, will you?
MAN VOICE-OVER:
What I will need from you now
is a commitment.
You will listen closely,
and you will not
judge me until I am finished.
If you cannot commit to this,
then please leave the room.
MAN 2: Come in.
But if you choose to stay,
remember you chose to be here.
What happens
from this moment forwards
is not my responsibility.
It's yours.
Pay attention.
DETECTIVE: What's all this, then?
SERGEANT: Turing, Alan.
Professor at King's.
Seems there's been a burglary.
Oh? What of?
Well, that's just it.
Nothing missing, really.
What's he doing in Manchester?
Something with machines.
The project at the NPL.
I checked, but he won't
say what it's on.
Professor Turing?
Detective Nock,
Manchester Police.
Sergeant Staehl here tells me
you had a burglary last night.
Professor Turing?
Take a step back, and
don't breath heavily.
- Breathe?
- Undiluted cyanide.
It-it wouldn't take
more than a thimbleful
to kill you.
Ah.
Disappointing.
Pardon?
I-I had hoped for a bit more.
Sergeant Staehl, is it just me,
or do you get the sense
that we're being insulted?
Last night, you had a break-in.
Your neighbor, Mr. Springborn,
called to report the noise.
He said there was
quite a ruckus.
Only you say nothing was taken.
It's odd.
So how about you tell us
what happened, and we'll find
the chap who did this.
Gentlemen,
I-I don't believe
that you could find the chap
that did this
if, uh, he walked up to you
and spat in your face.
Uh, what I could us right now
is not a bobby,
but a really good cleaning lady.
So unless one of you
has a-an apron
in your car, I suggest
you file your reports
and leave me alone.
As you say, Professor Turing.
Best of luck with your cyanide.
STAEHL VOICE-OVER: I'll give you a quid
if you can name me
a more insufferable sod.
Seemed a bit forced,
though, didn't it?
Don't know what you mean.
Well, if you didn't want
a pair of bobbies
digging around in your
personal affairs,
that'd have been a stellar way
to make sure they don't.
Tell me you don't think
this is suspicious.
I don't think
A mysterious professor
who won't admit
he's had something stolen
from his house?
I think Alan Turing's
hiding something.
War declared!
800,000 children evacuated!
German bombs on their way!
Get your papers here!
Fresh off the press!
War declared!
800,000 children evacuated!
German bombs expected soon!
NEVILLE CHAMBERLAIN: This morning,
the British Ambassador in Berlin
handed the German government
a final note stating that
unless we heard from
them, by 11:00,
a state of war would
exist between us.
I have to tell you now
that no such undertaking
has been received.
And that, consequently,
this country is at
war with Germany.
KING GEORGE VI: For the second time
in the lives of most
of us, we are...
at war.
To find a peaceful way out...
Papers, please.
What are you doing here?
Oh, uh,
the lady told me to wait.
In my office?
She tell you to help
yourself to tea
while you were here?
Uh, no, she didn't.
She obviously didn't tell you
what a joke was, then,
either, I gather.
Was she supposed to?
Who are you?
Alan Turing.
Ah, Turing.
The mathematician.
Correct.
- However could I have guessed?
- Well, you didn't.
You just read it on
that piece of paper.
King's College, Cambridge.
Now, it says here you were
a bit of a prodigy
in the maths department.
I-I'm not sure I can
evaluate that, Mr...
- How old are you, Mr. Turing?
- Uh, 27.
And how old were you when you
became a Fellow at Cambridge?
- 24.
- And how old were you
when you published
this paper that has a title
I can barely understand?
- Uh, 23.
- And you don't think
that qualifies you
as a certified prodigy?
Well, Newton discovered
binomial theorem aged 22.
Einstein wrote four papers
that changed the world
by the age of 26.
As far as I can tell, I've...
I've barely made par.
My God, you're serious.
Would you prefer I made a joke?
Oh, I don't think you know
what those are.
Hardly seems fair that
that's a requirement
for employment here, Mr...
Commander Denniston, Royal Navy.
All right,
Mr. Turing, I'll bite.
Why do you wish to work
for His Majesty's government?
Oh, I don't, really.
Are you a bleeding pacifist?
I'm... agnostic about violence.
Well, you do realize
that 600 miles away from London
there's this nasty little chap
called Hitler
who wants to engulf Europe
in tyranny?
Politics isn't really
my area of expertise.
Really?
Well, I believe
you've just set the record
for the shortest job interview
in British military history.
Oh, uh...
Mother says I can be off-putting
sometimes on account
of being one of the best
mathematicians in the world.
In the world?
Oh, yes.
Do you know how many people
I've rejected for this program?
- No.
- Well, that's right,
because we're
a top-secret program.
But I'll tell you,
just because we're friends,
that only last week,
I rejected one of our
great nation's top linguists.
Knows German better
than Bertolt Brecht.
I don't speak German.
What?
I don't... speak German.
Well, how the hell
were you supposed to decrypt
German communications
if you don't...
I don't know, speak German?
Well, I'm really quite excellent
at crossword puzzles.
- Margaret!
- The German codes are a puzzle.
A game, just like
any other game.
- Margaret, where are you?
- I'm really very good at games.
Uh, puzzles.
And this is the most difficult
puzzle in the world.
Margaret!
For the love of God.
This is a joke, obviously.
I'm afraid I don't know
what those are,
Commander Denniston.
Have a pleasant trip
back to Cambridge, Professor.
Enigma.
You called for me?
That's what you're doing here.
The top-secret program
at Bletchley.
You're trying to break
the German Enigma machine.
What makes you think that?
It's the greatest
encryption device in history,
and the Germans use it
for all major communications.
If the Allies broke Enigma,
well,
this would turn
into a very short war, indeed.
Of course that's what
you're working on.
But you also haven't got
anywhere with it.
If you had, you wouldn't
be hiring cryptographers
out of university.
Y-You need me a lot
more than I need you.
I-I like solving
problems, Commander.
And Enigma is the most
difficult problem in the world.
No, Enigma isn't difficult;
It's impossible.
The Americans, the Russians,
the French,
the Germans,
everyone thinks Enigma
is unbreakable.
Good.
Let me try,
and we'll know for sure,
won't we?
DENNISTON: Welcome to Enigma.
The details of every
surprise attack,
every secret convoy
and every U-boat in
the bloody Atlantic
go into that thing.
And out comes gibberish.
It's beautiful.
DENNISTON: It's the crooked
hand of death itself.
Our Wrens intercept thousands
of radio messages a day,
and to the lovely young ladies
of the Women's Royal Navy,
they're nonsense.
It's only when you feed
them back into Enigma
that they make any sense.
But we have an Enigma machine.
Yes, Polish Intelligence
smuggled it out of Berlin.
So what's the problem?
Just put
the intercepted messages
back into the Enigma
and you'll...
Look, it's not
that simple, is it?
Just having an Enigma machine
doesn't help you to decode
the messages.
DENNISTON: Very good, Mr. Turing.
To decode a message, you need to
know the machine's settings.
Now, the Germans switch settings
every day promptly at midnight.
We usually intercept
our first message
around 6:00 a.m.,
which gives you exactly
18 hours every day
to crack the code
before it changes,
and you start again.
Five rotors.
Ten plugboard cables.
- That's... -One million...
- A thousand million...
No, no, it's, uh, I've got it.
- It's million, million.
- It's in the millions, obviously.
It's over 150 million million
million possible settings.
Very good.
159.
If you want to be
exact about it. 1-5-9
with 18 zeroes behind it.
Possibilities.
Every single day.
DENNISTON: Gentlemen, meet Hugh Alexander.
I personally selected him
- to run this unit.
- Didn't you...
Mr. Alexander won Britain's
national chess championship.
Twice.
DENNISTON: You're not the only one
who's good at games
around here, Turing.
Are-are we
to work together, then?
I prefer to have my own office.
You're a team,
and you will work as one.
I-I-I don't have time
to explain myself as I go along,
and I'm afraid these men
- would only slow me down.
play together, then I'm afraid
we can't let you play at all.
This is Stewart Menzies, MI6.
There are only five divisions
of military intelligence.
There is no MI6.
Exactly.
That's the spirit.
Mr. Turing, do you know
how many British servicemen
have died because of Enigma?
Uh, no, I don't.
Three... while we've been having
this conversation.
Oh, look, there's another.
I rather hope he
didn't have a family.
This war Commander Denniston's
been going on about,
we're not winning it.
Break the code, at least
we have a chance.
Shall we leave
the children alone
with their new toy?
Hm.
All right, gentlemen...
- Let's play.
TURING VOICE-OVER:
The game was quite a simple one.
Every single German message,
every surprise attack,
every bombing run,
every imminent U-boat assault...
They were all floating
through the air.
Radio signals that...
well, any schoolboy
with an AM kit
could intercept.
The trick was
that they were encrypted.
There were 159 million
million million possible.
Enigma settings.
All we had to do
was try each one.
But if we had ten men checking
one setting a minute
for 24 hours every day
and seven days every week,
how many days do you think
it would take to, uh,
to check each of the settings?
Well, it's not days, it's years.
Good morning.
It's 20 million years.
- To stop a coming attack,
- Thank you.
We would have to check
20 million years' worth
of settings in 20 minutes.
I'm famished.
Lunch?
ALEXANDER: Good Lord. What is it
about women with little hats?
The boys, we're going
to get some lunch.
Alan?
Yes?
I said we're going
to get some lunch.
Alan?
Yes?
- Can you hear me?
- Yes.
I said we're off to get some lu...
This is starting to get
a little bit repetitive.
- What is?
- I had asked
if you wanted to come
to lunch with us.
Um, no, you didn't.
You said you were going
to get some lunch.
Have I offended you in some way?
Why would you think that?
Would you like to come to lunch
with us?
- What time's lunchtime?
- Christ, Alan,
it's a bleeding sandwich.
- What is?
- Lunch.
Oh, I don't like sandwiches.
Never mind.
You know,
to pull off
this irascible genius routine,
one actually has to be
a genius, Alan.
And yet we're the ones
making progress here, aren't we?
Oh, you are?
Yes, we are.
We have decrypted a number
of German messages
by analyzing the frequency
of letter distribution.
Oh, even a broken clock
is right twice a day.
That-That's not progress;
That's just blind luck.
I'm designing a machine
that will allow us
to break every message
every day instantly.
Who's hungry?
Let's go.
I'm hungry.
What?
TURING: Peter asked who was hungry.
Can I have some soup, please?
Another break
in the circuit there.
What do you mean, "classified"?
No, I'm aware of the literal
meaning of the word classified.
What I'm asking is why would
a maths professor
have his military records
classified?
Yeah, well, I will come down.
WPC: Sorry, can I get you
to hold for a minute, please?
Pardon me, I'd like to see
some documents, if I may.
Service records of a Mr. Turing.
Alan.
Foreign Office sent me.
This is unacceptable.
If you wish to discuss
the complaint,
I suggest you make
a proper appointment.
Alexan... Complaint?
No, no, Hugh Alexander
has denied my requisition
for parts
and-and equipment that I need to
build the machine I've designed.
Your fellow code-breakers
are refusing to work with you,
and they filed
a formal complaint.
It's is inspired
by an old Polish code machine.
Only this one is
infinitely more advanced.
If you don't respond
to the complaint,
I shall have to take it up
with the Home Office.
Put those files by my desk.
Fine, my response is
they're all idiots.
Fire them and use the savings
to fund my machine.
I only need
about 100,000 pounds.
100,000...
Why are you building a machine?
You wouldn't understand.
I suggest you make
the effort to try.
Enigma is...
an extremely
well-designed machine.
Our problem is that we're only
using men to try to beat it.
No, what if only a machine
can defeat another machine?
Well, that's not very technical.
Hugh Alexander is in charge
of your unit; He said no,
and that is that.
I simply don't have time
for this.
Have you ever won a war, Turing?
I have.
Do you know how it's done?
Order, discipline,
chain of command.
You're not at university
any longer.
You are a very small cog
in a very large system.
And you will do as your
commanding officer instructs.
Yes.
Who-who is
your commanding officer?
Winston Churchill,
Number 10 Downing
Street, London, SW1.
You have a problem
with my decision,
you can take it up with him.
TURING VOICE-OVER: Mr. Menzies!
Mr. Menzies!
A-A-Are you going to London?
Possibly.
Would you deliver
a letter for me?
ALEXANDER VOICE-OVER: Look, I'm sorry,
but are you joking?
Churchill's put Alan in charge?
- This is a terrible idea.
- No, no, no, no, no.
So I can give these
men orders now?
I hate to say it, but yes.
Excellent. Keith and Charles,
you're both fired.
- Excuse me?
- What?
You're mediocre linguists,
and positively
poor code-breakers.
Alan, you can't just
fire Keith and Charles.
Well, he just said I could.
No, I did no such thing.
But Churchill did.
Go to hell.
Well, this is inhuman.
Even for you.
Popular at school, were you?
TURING VOICE-OVER:
The problem began, of course,
with the carrots.
Carrots are orange.
And peas are green.
They mustn't touch.
I got it.
TURING VOICE-OVER: Do you know why people
like violence?
It is because it feels... good.
Humans find violence
deeply satisfying.
But remove the-the satisfaction,
and the act becomes...
- Hollow.
STUDENT: Turing?
Come on.
Don't be such a kike about it.
STUDENT 2: Leave him to bloody rot.
TURING VOICE-OVER:
I didn't learn this on my own,
of course.
I had help.
Christopher helped.
Alan, are you all right?
It's not my fault.
The carrots got in
with the peas and...
I'm sorry.
I won't let them do it again.
They're getting worse.
They only beat me up because
I'm smarter than they are.
No, they beat you up
because you're different.
Mother says
I'm just an odd duck.
And she's right.
But you know, Alan,
sometimes it's the very people
who no one imagines anything of
who do the things
no one can imagine.
So, what do we do now?
We're short on staff.
TURING: Well, we, uh, we get
more staff then.
And how do you propose
to do that?
Um, Alan Turing to
see Stewart Menzies.
Very good, sir.
MENZIES VOICE-OVER: So who are they?
Oh, all sorts, really.
Teacher, an engineer,
a handful of students.
And you think they're
qualified for Bletchley
'cause they're good
at crossword puzzles?
Well, they say they're good,
and now we shall find out,
won't we?
VOICE-OVER: In order to aid your efforts,
there is, to the right of you,
a green scratch card book.
You are to make notes in that.
Gentlemen, you have six minutes
in which to complete the
puzzle, at which point,
I will...
Pardon, ma'am,
this room's restricted.
Oh, apologies for my tardiness.
The-the bus caught a flat tire.
Uh, may I continue, please?
Thank you. -You're not
allowed in here, ma'am.
Oh, but I'm only
a few minutes late.
The secretaries are
to head upstairs.
This room's for the candidates.
May I get on with
this now, please?
I-I am a candidate.
- For what position?
The letter didn't say precisely.
Yeah, so secretaries
are to head upstairs.
It did say
that it was top secret.
What is going on?
I-I solved
a-a crossword puzzle
in the newspaper,
and I-I got this letter saying
that I was a candidate for
some sort of mysterious job.
My name's Joan Clarke.
Miss, did you really solve
this puzzle yourself?
What makes you think I couldn't
solve the puzzle myself?
- I-I'm really very good at...
- Ma'am,
- I'll have to ask you to...
- Miss Clarke,
I-I find tardiness
under any circumstance,
um, unacceptable.
Take a seat so that
we may continue.
SOFTLY: Thank you.
TURING: Now, um,
as I was saying,
you-you have six minutes
to, uh, complete the task
in front of you.
Uh, gentlemen and lady, begin.
Six minutes.
Is that even possible?
No, it takes me eight.
This isn't about
crossword puzzles.
It's about how one, uh,
approaches solving an
impossible problem.
Do you tackle the whole thing
at once or divide it
into small... You've finished?
Yes.
Five minutes and 34 seconds.
You said to do it in under six.
MENZIES VOICE-OVER: Congratulations.
My warmest welcome to
His Majesty's service.
If you speak a word
of what I'm about to show you,
you will be executed
for high treason.
You will lie to your friends,
your family
and everyone you meet
about what it is you really do.
And what is it
that we're really doing?
We're going to break
an unbreakable Nazi code
and win the war.
Oh.
What's that you're reading?
It's about cryptography.
Like secret messages?
Not secret.
That's the brilliant part.
Messages that anyone can see,
but no one knows what they mean
unless you have the key.
How's that different
from talking?
- Talking?
- When people talk to each other,
they never say what they mean.
They say something else,
and you're expected to
just know what they mean.
Only I never do.
So, how's that different?
Alan, I have a funny feeling
you're going to be
very good at this.
Good night, Alan.
Good night.
WOMAN: Hold on,
Marion, I'm coming!
Coming round the lesser settings
and then route back through...
- Back to those ones...
Uh, careful, will you?
Um, it-it's not a toy.
ALEXANDER: Funny.
Looks like a toy.
Bloody great 100,000-pound one.
Your new minion's arrived.
Jack Good. We met...
Well, where's Miss Clarke?
Lovely, isn't he?
TURING: It's not just a-a usual
humdrum production mill factory.
I mean, well,
as-as I was saying,
it's a very important,
uh, radio factory.
I-It's not, actually.
Uh, well, um,
on the spectrum of,
uh... radio factories,
this-this one
is-is particularly...
Why are you not at Bletchley?
Thank you... so much for
your visit, Mr. Turing.
Was your trip pleasant? -Gather
your things and let's go.
I'm sorry, but I'm unable
to accept your offer.
We feel that such a position
would hardly be appropriate.
You earned a double first
in mathematics.
But sadly wasn't granted the
opportunity to become a Fellow.
You belong at Bletchley.
JOAN: I'm sorry,
but for someone in my position
to live... to...
to work in a radio factory
so far from home,
with all your men, um...
it-it would be...
indecorous.
What in the world
does that even mean?
We have a group of,
uh, young ladies
who tend to all of our
CLERICAL TASKS: Assistants, translators.
Uh, they live,
um, together in town.
W-W-Would that be a more,
uh, suitable environment?
Hm. So-so I would be working
amongst these women?
Yes.
Wonderful ladies. Uh, they
even organize social events
at St. Martin's Church
down the road.
Uh, really, the whole thing
is-is quite, uh...
uh, um... decorous.
Now, you won't have proper
security clearance,
of course, so, uh, we'll have
to improvise things a bit.
Why are you helping me?
Because there is only
one thing that matters
in this entire world right
now... do you understand?...
and that is breaking Enigma.
But-but, Mr. Turing...
why are you helping me?
Oh. Um...
sometimes it's the very people
who no one imagines anything of
who do the things that
no one can imagine.
Sir.
What's this? -Alan Turing's
classified military file.
- It's bloody empty.
- Exactly.
- It's an empty manila envelope.
- Yeah.
Well, you've cracked the case
wide open, then, haven't you?
Alan Turing's war records
aren't just classified,
they're nonexistent.
That means someone's
got rid of them.
Erased them. Burned them.
And that same person broke into
his house and stole nothing?
Guy Burgess and Donald Maclean.
What, the spies from the papers?
The Soviet spies.
But first they were
professors, weren't they?
Radicalized at Cambridge,
then they joined
the Communist Party,
then Foreign Office,
then leaked information
to Stalin during the war... now,
can you think of anyone else
we know who was at Cambridge,
then took up something murky and
top secret when war broke out?
You think this Alan Turing
might be a Soviet agent?
I think...
something very serious
is happening
right here under our noses.
Wouldn't you like to find out what it is?
Welcome, ladies.
If you'd like to follow me.
TURING VOICE-OVER: Some
people thought we were at war
with the Germans... incorrect.
We were at war with the clock.
Britain was literally
starving to death.
The Americans sent over
100,000 tons of food every week,
and, uh, every week
the Germans would send
our desperately needed bread
to the bottom of the ocean.
Our daily failure was announced
at the chimes of midnight.
And the sound would haunt
our unwelcome dreams.
Tick... tock... tick.
Damn it!
- What just happened?
- CAIRNCROSS: Midnight...
all the work we've done
today is useless.
Oh, but don't worry,
we've a few hours
before tomorrow's messages
start flooding in...
and we start all over again.
From scratch.
ALEXANDER: I'm so sick of this.
Four hours rewiring
his plugboard matrix.
Three hours yesterday
on his rotor positions!
- Don't go over there.
- Look, John, no.
If this job wasn't
already impossible before,
- it bloody well is now.
- Hugh, don't.
Damn you and your
useless machine.
My machine is how we are going to win.
Really?
This machine? Hmm?
Are you talking about
this bloody machine?!
- Hugh! Hugh! Hugh, don't!
- Hugh! Hugh! Stop!
ALEXANDER: You arrogant bastard.
You could help us.
You could make this go
faster, but you won't.
Get off.
He's right, Alan.
There are...
actual soldiers out there
trying to win an actual war.
My brother
protects food convoys
in the Navy.
My cousins fly RAF patrols.
All my friends,
they're all making a difference,
while we just...
while away our days
producing nothing.
Because of you.
PANTING: My machine...
will work.
Come on, Peter.
Okay.
WHISPERS: Joan?
SOFTLY: Oh.
- Uh, will you...
- Could you make
a bit more noise?
I'm not quite sure
- my landlady woke up.
- Oh, sorry.
Oh, uh, look.
I think that's the
best I can do.
No male visitors after dark.
So... what did you bring me?
There you go.
Here.
Some men try flowers, you know.
These are actual
decrypted Enigma messages
direct from Nazi.
High Command.
"0600 hours.
"Weather today is clear.
"Rain in the evening.
Heil Hitler."
Well, clearly,
that vital piece of information
is going to win us the war.
It's the relationship
between the encrypted
a-and decrypted messages
that interests me.
Can we find a clue here that
we can build into Christopher?
Who's Christopher?
Oh, he's, uh, he's my machine.
You named him?
Is that a bad name?
No.
No, never mind.
Are you trying to build
your universal machine?
I read your paper
- at university.
- Is it already being taught?
LAUGHS: No. No. No, I was precocious.
So... you-you theorized
a machine that
could solve any problem.
It didn't just do one thing,
it did everything.
It wasn't just programmable,
it was reprogrammable.
Mm.
Is that your idea
behind Christopher?
Well, human brains can compute
large sums very quickly...
even Hugh can do that... but I
want Christopher to be smarter.
To make a calculation
and then, uh...
to determine what to do next.
Like a person does.
Think of it.
Electrical brain.
A digital computer.
Digital computer.
Hmm.
- What's going on?
What's happening?
No. No, no. No, no, no!
Don't touch that!
- Stay back.
- That's my desk.
DENNISTON: Thank goodness.
I'd hate to think
we were searching
the wrong one. -What are
you doing? What's going on?
There is a spy in
Bletchley Park.
The Navy thinks that one of us
is a Soviet double agent, Alan.
Uh... why?
Our boys intercepted this
on its way to Moscow.
Look familiar?
It's a Beale cipher.
Encrypted with a phrase
from a book or a poem or...
You don't seriously think
I did this, do you?
Double agents are such bastards.
Isolated loners.
No attachments to
friends or family.
Arrogant.
Know anybody like that?
I... Hm, I know you
don't like me,
but that does not
make me a Soviet spy.
POLICEMAN: Nothing
out of the ordinary, sir.
Really.
Mm, all right.
The Home Office may be
protecting you now,
but sooner or later
you will make a mistake.
And I needn't bother firing you.
They will hang you for treason.
Hello.
I heard about what happened.
It's all the girls in
Hut 3 can talk about.
I have an idea
of what might cheer you up.
JOAN: So because no letter
can be encoded as itself,
there's already a handful
of settings that can be
rejected at the outset.
Is that your team?
- Y-Yes.
- Shall we say hello?
- No.
- Hello.
I-I told you not t-to do that.
- Alan.
- Uh, Hugh, h-hello.
- Didn't know you drank.
- He doesn't, really.
He just sort of sips
at the foam.
Well, I'll let you into a
little secret, Miss...?
Clarke.
- Miss Clarke.
- Please.
Foam's my favorite part, too.
Is it really?
Come and join us for a drink?
We'll be there in a moment.
Miss Clarke.
Well, he likes you.
- Yes.
- You... g-got him to like you.
Yes.
Why?
Because I'm a woman
in a man's job,
and I don't have the luxury
of being an ass.
Alan...
it doesn't matter
how smart you are,
Enigma is always smarter.
If you really want to
solve your puzzle,
then you're going to need
all the help
you can get,
and they are not going
to help you
if they do not like you.
- What are those?
- Apples.
- No.
- Oh, they really are.
Um, I... well, Miss Clarke,
Joan actually, um...
said that it would be...
nice if I was to, uh,
bring you all something.
So here we are. I... Thank you.
I like apples.
My best to Miss Clarke.
Uh, there are two people
in a wood,
and, um, they run into a bear.
The first person
gets down on his knees to pray.
The second person
starts lacing up his boots.
The first person
asks the second person,
"My dear friend,
what are you doing?
You-you-you
can't outrun a bear."
Uh, to which
the second person responds,
"I don't have to.
I only have to outrun you."
I'll be w-with Christopher,
if anyone needs me.
MAN VOICE-OVER: If we assume
that the square root of two
is a rational number,
then we can say
that the square root
of two is A over B...
where A and B
are whole numbers
and B is not zero.
Mr. Turing,
passing notes, are we?
No, sir.
Only Turing would pass notes
written in gibberish.
- All right, gentlemen,
do not forget your algebra
over the break.
Have a pleasant holiday,
and we'll resume
your irrationals
when you return.
Mm.
But Euler's Theorem
gives you that immediately.
Um...
Here. Look at this.
If you run the wires across
the plugboard matrix diagonally,
it will eliminate rotor
positions 500 times faster.
That's, uh...
actually not an entirely
terrible idea.
I think that was Alan
for "thank you."
Uh, th-that's my sandwich.
You don't like sandwiches.
You nervous?
What happens now?
It-it should work out the
day's Enigma settings.
How long?
CROWD VOICE-OVER: Sieg Heil!
Sieg Heil!
NEWSMAN: The German Army
has fanned out across Europe,
from Poland to Serbia,
Lithuania to Denmark,
Norway to France.
The Nazi flag now flies
from more than two dozen
national capitals.
Their campaign mounts in fury
as a free Europe crumbles.
MAN VOICE-OVER: Oh, it's still going.
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning, Margaret.
Gears keep spinning on and on.
Rotors on and on.
It's endless.
With no result in sight?
- No.
Ow.
Turing.
- Turing, - open the bloody door.
- Uh, no.
No.
Open the door or
we'll break it down.
I can't let you in! I-I...
I cannot let you interfere.
Go on, then.
Turn that thing off.
No. Don't, please. Please.
Please! Please!
No!
N-No. No!
Don't!
Well, then, it seems
that your great big
expensive machine doesn't work.
WHISPERS: It does.
Wonderful.
So you've broken Enigma, then?
It was just... s-still working.
This is my associate
from the Home Office.
You see, a hundred
thousand pounds
is rather a lot of money,
and he's here to see what
you have to show for it.
You... will never understand
the importance of what
I-I am creating here!
Have you decrypted
any German messages?
A single one?
Can you point to anything
at all that you've achieved?
Hmm. Your funding is up,
and our patience is expired.
It's with such great pleasure
that I am finally
able to say this.
Alan Turing, you're fired.
Please escort Mr. Turing
from the premises.
ALEXANDER: No.
DENNISTON: I beg your pardon?
If you fire Alan...
well, then you'll
have to fire me, too.
What on earth are you saying?
ALEXANDER: Trust me when
I tell you there is no one
who would rather say this
less than I do, but...
he's right.
Alan is right.
His machine can work,
and it's probably
the best chance that we've got.
God, it's beyond belief.
CAIRNCROSS: If you fire them...
you'll have to fire me, too.
PETER: And me.
ALEXANDER: We're the best
cryptographic minds in Britain.
Are you going to fire us all?
Commander, at least
give us some more time.
Six months, and if the
machine doesn't produce
any results that we need,
then we'll go back
to doing things the old way...
how about that?
One month.
And then, so help me
God, you're all gone.
Oh, leave him.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, and, Alan, your machine...
it better bloody work.
TURING: Hugh.
I swear...
I'm not a spy.
Oh, for God's sake, of course
you're not a bloody spy.
What?
Denniston gave me
the Beale cipher,
and guess what?
I cracked it.
"Ask, and it shall
be given to you;
Seek and ye shall find."
Matthew 7:7.
That was the key.
Far too simple
for the likes of you.
Pity Denniston disagrees.
- Come in.
Sir, I think I've got Turing.
I tailed him
to a pub last night,
where he met a bloke.
They exchanged an envelope.
So I follow this other fella,
pick him up,
give him a good shake.
He's a poofter. He confessed.
What?
The man admitted it.
Arnold Murray.
Hangs around that pub;
Men pay him for a go.
Turing's one of
the men that paid.
Only Mr. Murray here
then has the bright idea
of robbing Turing's house
after, with a friend.
That's what Turing's hiding.
Well, he's a poof, not a spy.
- No.
- What's the matter?
We can charge a
university professor
- with indecency.
- No, this is...
it's bloody rubbish.
Turing's up
to something important...
He's committed a crime
and he's broken the law.
And with a bloke. Jesus Christ,
- it's bloody disgusting.
- This isn't
the investigation
I was conducting.
Bring him in.
Wait.
L-Let me interrogate him.
Please. Give me
half an hour alone,
and then I swear,
I'll spend the next month
running errands on as many
rubbish cases as you like.
Fine. Now,
will someone get me a warrant
for the arrest of Alan Turing.
Alan?
Christopher's simply
not moving fast enough.
We should talk. -And even
with the diagonal board,
he's still not eliminating
settings as quickly
- as we need him to in order...
- I'm leaving.
But you've just walked in.
No.
No. Bletchley.
What?
It's my parents.
I'm 25, I'm unmarried,
I'm living alone,
and they want me home.
That's ridiculous.
That's my parents.
You... you can't leave...
I-I won't let you.
"I'll miss you.
" That's what a normal person
- might say in this situation.
- I-I don't care what is normal.
What am I supposed to do, Alan?
I-I will not...
give up my parents.
You... you have
an opportunity here
to make some actual use
of your life.
And end up like you?
No, thanks.
- I'm sorry you're lonely.
But Enigma will not save you.
Can you decipher that,
you fragile narcissist?
Or would you like me
to go and fetch
your precious Christopher
to help?
I'm sorry.
Mm...
I want you...
I want you to stay because I-I like you.
I like... talking to you.
I like talking to you,
too, Alan.
And what if you weren't alone?
What if you had a husband?
Do you have one in mind?
I do.
Hugh?
Hugh's terribly attractive,
I'll give you that,
but I don't really think
he's the marrying kind.
No, I-I wasn't thinking of Hugh.
Or Peter.
Peter's so quiet.
Oh, my God.
But this makes sense.
Did you just propose to me?
Well, it is
the logical thing to do.
This is ridiculous.
This is your parents.
I-I can't... believe
that this is happening.
Mm. Joan...
Is your middle name
Caroline or Catherine?
- Elizabeth.
- Um, Joan Elizabeth...
Clarke, um...
will you marry me?
WOMAN: It's beautiful.
Well, I know
it isn't ordinary, but...
whoever loved ordinary?
- ALEXANDER: She had it in both hands...
and she looked up at me
with her doe eyes and said,
"Am I supposed
to put that in my mouth?"
And I said, "Yes.
You know, the French way."
So she pops it in,
clamps her lips around it,
and starts humming
the bloody Marseillaise.
Come have a dance.
ALEXANDER: No, no,
no, you can dance
with your fiance
anytime you like.
Right now, this moment...
- My turn.
What's the matter?
Wh-What if...
Wh-What if I don't
fancy being...
with Joan I-in that way?
Because you're a homosexual?
I suspected.
Well, should-should I tell her
that I've had...
affairs with men?
You know, in my...
admittedly limited experience,
women... tend to be a bit touchy
about accidentally
marrying homosexuals.
Perhaps not spreading
this information about might be
in your best interest.
TURING: I care for her, I truly do.
I...
I-I... I just don't know
if I can, um... pretend.
You can't tell anyone, Alan.
It's illegal.
And Denniston is looking
for any excuse he can
to put you away.
I know.
This has to stay a secret.
JOAN: Come on, it's your turn.
Ah. Okay.
Cup of tea?
No, thank you.
Mr. Turing, can I
tell you a secret?
I'm quite good with those.
I'm here to help you.
Oh, clearly.
Can machines think?
Oh, so you've read some
of my published works?
What makes you say that?
Well, because I'm sitting
in a police station,
accused of entreating
a young man to touch my penis
and you just asked me
if machines can think.
Well, can they?
Could machines ever think
as human beings do?
Most people say not.
You're not most people.
Well, the problem is you're...
asking a stupid question.
I am?
Of course machines...
can't think as people do.
A machine is different...
from a person.
Hence, they think differently.
The interesting question is,
just because something, uh,
thinks differently from you,
does that mean
it's not thinking?
Well, we allow for humans
to have such divergences
from one another.
You like strawberries,
I hate ice-skating,
you... cry at sad films,
I... am allergic to pollen.
What is the point
of-of different tastes,
different... preferences
if not to say that
our brains work differently,
that we think differently?
And if we can say that
about one another,
then why can't we say
the same thing for brains...
built of copper and wire, steel?
And that's... this
big paper you wrote?
What's it called?
"The Imitation Game."
Right, that's... that's
what it's about?
Would you like to play?
Play?
It's a game.
A test of sorts.
For determining
whether something is a...
a machine or a human being.
How do I play?
Well, there's a judge
and a subject, and...
the judge asks questions,
and, depending
on the subject's answers,
determines who
he is talking with...
what he is talking with,
and, um...
All you have to do
is ask me a question.
What did you do during the war?
I worked in a radio factory.
What did you really do
during the war?
Are you paying attention?
Damn it!
CAIRNCROSS:
We're soon out of time. A month.
PETER: So that's it, then, is it?
Oh, the trouble is, it doesn't
matter how much we improve it.
The machine's never
gonna be able to process
159 million million million
possibilities in time.
It's just bloody hopeless.
It's searching. It's just...
It... doesn't know
what it's searching for.
If we knew what the messages
were going to say...
were going to say,
we wouldn't have
to decrypt them at all.
Who's Alan's friend?
Hugh. He's a bit
of a cad, actually.
So my type, then?
- Well, I'll introduce you.
- No.
He'll come over.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I smiled at him 15 minutes ago
and haven't looked back since.
Who's that with Joan?
Hmm?
TURING: Uh, Helen. Works with her.
She's really pretty.
She wants me to come over.
What? H-How on earth
can you know that?
She smiled at me a while back
and she hasn't
looked again since.
And got him.
Now, why is this,
that when I was single
I found it very boring,
but now that I'm engaged,
I just find it dreadfully fun.
Bingo. She's in.
Alan, introduce us.
What?
Wh-Why me?
Because there's nothing
like a friend's engagement
to make a woman want to do
something she'll later regret
with the fiance's
better looking chum.
Let's go.
Half a crown says Alan
bollixes this up entirely.
- No bet.
- Alan Turing has a theory.
- JOAN: He has many.
He believes that the regulations
against men and women working
side by side are sound
because such proximity will
necessarily lead to romance.
What? No, I don't.
I... However...
I disagree.
- You do?
- Yeah.
I think that if I were working
beside a woman all day long,
I could appreciate her
abilities and intellect
without taking her to bed.
I'm sorry, have we met?
I don't recall.
But let's assume we haven't.
Helen Stewart. Hugh Alexander.
So who do you agree with,
- Alan or myself?
- Well, Alan, of course.
I-I'm very flattered, really,
but I-I don't think...
- ALEXANDER: Rubbish.
-HELEN: Well, I work beside a man
every day, and I can't help
but have developed
a bit of a crush on him.
Well, who is this man?
So I can kick his arse.
Well, there's no need
to worry... it's been chaste.
We've never even met.
He's a German.
- Now I really want to kill him.
How-how do you mean
you work alongside a German?
Well, each of us
intercepts messages
from a specific
German radio tower.
So we have a counterpart
on the other side
who's tip-tapping out
the messages.
Everyone types
a touch differently,
so you get to know the rhythm
of your counterpart.
It's strangely intimate.
I feel as if I know him so well.
It's a pity he has a girlfriend,
but that's why I disagree
with you, Mr. Alexander.
Because I'm in love
with a coworker of sorts,
and we've never even met.
Well, allow me to buy
you another pint,
and I'll tell you
why you're wrong.
Let's.
Excellent.
Thanks.
ALEXANDER: Um, pints.
Have you got any sloe gin?
In case you were wondering,
that's what flirting looks like.
TURING LOUDLY: Helen...
Really, no cigarettes?
Alan... Yes, Alan?
Wh-Why do you think
your German counterpart has a girlfriend?
It's just
- a stupid joke; Don't worry.
- No, no, no, no. Tell me.
Well, each of his messages
begins with the same
five letters:
C-I-L-L-Y.
So I suspect that Cilly
must be the name
- of his amore.
- But that's impossible.
The Germans are instructed
to use five random letters
at the start of every message.
HELEN: Well, this bloke doesn't.
Love will make a man do
strange things, I suppose.
In this case, love just lost
Germany the whole bloody war.
Oh!
Go, Peter.
Sorry.
JOAN: Alan!
Alan!
GUARDS: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey! -Alan!
- I just want...
Hugh Alexander. John Cairncross.
Peter bloody Hilton.
Alan?
What-wha...?
PANTING: What...
what if... what if Christopher
doesn't have to search
through all of the settings?
What if he only has
to search through
ones that produce words
we already know will be
in the message? -Repeated
words; Predictable words.
Exactly.
JOAN: Look, look, like this one.
"0600 hours. Weather
today is clear.
Rain in the evening.
Heil Hitler."
Well, that's it.
Exactly.
They send a weather report
every day at 6:00 a.m.
So that's-that's three
words we know will be
in every 6:00 a.m. message...
"weather," obviously,
- a-and...
- Heil bloody Hitler.
Heil bloody Hitler.
Here's the 6:00 message from this morning.
TURING: Hugh, the, uh,
the right-hand letter wheel,
set them to...
I know, I know.
"Weather" and "Hitler."
Peter, John, run voltages
through those letters,
- through the back scramblers.
- PETER: So we'll use the loops?
- TURING: Yes. Joan, what was
- the last 6: 00 a.m. message?
- L...
- H... - TURING: H...
- W... TURING: W...
- JOAN: A... - A... - Q.
- Q.
Done.
QUIETLY: Come on.
Come on. Come on, Christopher.
Oh, my God.
Wh-What happened?
- Did it work?
- Alan?
ALEXANDER: Alan!
Alan!
I need a new message.
The latest intercept.
SOFTLY: Thank you.
- O... T...
- JOAN: Ready? - Yes.
- M... - M... - Y...
- Y...
- M... S...
- A... I... - A... I... - C...
- C...
- T... - T... - R...
- R...
- I... - I... - S... O...
- S... O...
- A...
- Y... R... I...
- Y... R...
- TURING: I.
"KMS Jaguar is auf punkt...
"is directed to 53 degrees
24 minutes north
and auf punkt one...
degree west."
TURING&ALEXANDER QUIETLY: Heil Hitler.
Turns out that's the only German
you need to know
to, uh, break Enigma.
Yes!
Oh!
- JOAN: M...
- TURING: M...
- A... - A... - Y...
- Y...
- I... - I... - T...
- T...
- R... - R... - O...
- O... T...
- T... A... - A... - H...
- H...
- Q... - Q... - TURING: U...
- U...
- R.
ALEXANDER: My God, you did it.
You just defeated Nazism
with a crossword puzzle.
There are five people
in the world who know
the position of every
ship in the Atlantic.
They're all
- in this room.
- Oh, good God.
Oh, I don't think
even He has the power
- that we do right now.
- JOAN: No.
There's going to be an attack
on a British passenger convoy.
Right there.
God, you're right.
All those U-boats are only
- 20, 30 minutes away.
- JOAN: Civilians.
Hundreds of them.
We can save their lives.
ALEXANDER: I'll phone
Denniston's office so that
- he can alert the Admiralty.
- Do you think
there's enough time
to save them?
There should be,
if we can get...
Commander Denniston's office,
please. It's urgent.
No.
What the hell are you doing?
You-you can't call Denniston.
You-you can't tell him
about the attack.
- What are you talking about?
- CAIRNCROSS: We can have
air support over that
convoy in ten minutes.
Let the U-boats...
- sink the convoy.
- Look, it's been
a big day... maybe you're...
- We don't have time...
- No!
JOAN: Oh! Hugh! Hugh!
That's enough!
- That's enough!
- CAIRNCROSS: Stop, Hugh!
John, the attack is in minutes.
Yes, no, I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
You know why people
like violence, Hugh?
It's because it feels good.
TURING: Sometimes we can't do
what feels good.
We have to do what is logical.
What's logical?
Hardest time to lie to somebody
is when they're expecting
to be lied to.
Oh, God.
What?
If someone's waiting for a lie,
you can't just,
uh, give them one.
Damn it, Alan's right.
What?
TURING: What would
the Germans think if we destroy
their U-boats?
Nothing. They'll be dead.
No.
No, you can't be right.
TURING: So our convoy
suddenly veers off course...
a squadron of our air bombers
miraculously descends on the
coordinates of the U-boats...
what will the Germans think?
The Germans will know
that we have broken Enigma.
JOAN: They'll stop all
radio communications by midday,
and they'll have changed
the design of Enigma
- by the weekend.
- ALEXANDER: Yes.
Two years' work.
Everything that we've done here
will all be for nothing.
CAIRNCROSS: There are 500
civilians in that convoy.
Women... children.
We're about to let them die.
TURING: Our job I-is
not to save one
passenger convoy, it is to win
- the war.
- Our job was to crack Enigma.
We've done that.
Now for the hard part.
- Keeping it a secret.
- PETER: Carlisle.
What?
The convoy you're about to...
it's, uh...
The HMS Carlisle
is one of the ships.
We can't act
on every piece of intelligence.
So fine, we won't.
Just this one.
Peter, what's
the matter with you?
My-my brother's...
well, he's on the Carlisle.
A gunnery ensign.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Who the hell
do you think you are?
This... this is my brother.
He's my big brother,
all right, and you have
a few minutes
to call off his murder.
We can't.
CAIRNCROSS: He's right.
Alan.
Joan.
Hugh.
John.
CRYING: Please, I...
The-the Germans, they
won't get suspicious
just because we stop one attack.
No one will know.
I'm asking you...
as your friend.
Please.
I'm so sorry.
You're not God, Alan...
you don't get to decide
who lives and who dies.
Yes, we do.
Why?
Because no one else can.
Why are you telling me this?
We need your help to keep
this a secret from...
Admiralty, Army, RAF.
Uh, no one can know
we broke Enigma.
Not even Denniston.
Who's in the process
of having you fired.
You can take care of that.
While we develop a system
to help you determine
how much intelligence
to act on...
which a-attacks to stop,
which to let through.
Statistical analysis.
The minimal number of actions
it would take for us
to win the war...
but the maximum number
we can take
before the Germans
get suspicious.
And you're going to trust
all this to statistics?
- To maths?
- Correct.
And then MI6 can come up
with the lies
that we tell everybody else.
You'll need a believable
alternative source for all
the pieces of information you use.
A false story
so that we can explain
how we got our information
that has nothing to do
with Enigma.
And then you can leak those
stories to the, uh, the Germans.
And then to our own military.
Maintain a conspiracy of lies
at the highest levels
of government.
Sounds right up my alley.
Alan, I so rarely
have cause to say this,
but you are exactly the man
I always hoped you would be.
TURING VOICE-OVER:
They code-named it "Ultra."
It became the largest store
of military intelligence
in, uh...
the history of the world.
It was like having a tap
on Himmler's intercom.
♪ I-E-O... ♪
VOICE-OVER: Secrecy
became the primary concern,
and for some reason, they...
they trusted me.
Peter... do you have the, uh,
the-the 630 decryp...
TURING VOICE-OVER: It's a Beale cipher
encrypted with a phrase
from a book or...
ALEXANDER VOICE-OVER: "Ask,
and it will be given to you;".
Seek and you will find."
Matthew 7:7.
That was the key.
Peter will come
around eventually.
Jack.
Could you give Alan and
me a moment, please?
The Soviets and us,
we're on the same side.
What I'm doing
will help Britain.
I-I have to tell Denniston.
No, you don't.
Because if you tell
him my secret...
I'll tell him yours.
Do you know what they
do to homosexuals?
You'll never be able
to work again,
never be able to teach.
Your precious machine...
I doubt you'll
ever see him again.
TURING: Hello. Can I... can I, um,
speak to Stewart Menzies,
please? It's urgent.
FEMALE OPERATOR: One moment, please.
Hello. Menzies.
TURING VOICE-OVER: Some
advice about keeping secrets.
It's a lot easier if you don't
know them in the first place.
Were they steaming my letters,
tapping my telephone?
Trailing my nervous walks?
You know, I... I
never did find out.
Joan?
What's...
Uh... where's Joan?
Military prison.
What have you done?
Decoded Enigma intercepts.
I found a pile of them
- in the bedside table.
- No, no. I-I gave those to her
over a year ago when
I was trying to figure out
- a link between...
- I'm sure you did.
Denniston's been looking
for a Soviet spy.
He's been looking inside Hut 8.
I know who the spy is.
It's not Joan. It's...
it's Cairncross.
I-I found the Beale
cipher, the Bible.
God, I wish you'd been a spy.
You'd be so much better
at this than he is.
You knew it was him?
Of course I bloody knew.
I knew before
he came to Bletchley.
Why do you think
I had him placed here?
But we have an Enigma machine.
DENNISTON: Yeah, Polish Intelligence...
TURING VOICE-OVER: You-you placed
a... a Soviet agent
at Bletchley Park?
It's really quite useful
to be able
to leak whatever
we want to Stalin.
MENZIES VOICE-OVER:
Churchill's too damn paranoid.
He won't share a shred
of intelligence
with the Soviets.
Not even information that will
help them against the Germans.
SIGHS: There's...
so much secrecy.
Cairncross has no idea
we know, of course.
He's really not
the brightest bulb.
Which is why I need your help.
I want to know
what to leak to John,
what to feed to the Soviets,
as well as the British.
SOFTLY: I... I'm not a spy.
I'm... I'm just a mathematician.
I know a lot of spies, Alan.
You've got more secrets
than the best of them.
You... you have to promise me
that you will release Joan.
Yes, Joan's at the market.
She's gonna be back
in an hour. I lied.
I better hold on to these.
If anybody finds out about them,
prison will be
the least of her worries.
Oh, Alan...
we're gonna have such a
wonderful war together.
TURING VOICE-OVER:
I need you to leave Bletchley.
What? -It's Menzies.
I don't trust him.
- TURING: It's not safe here.
- Do you think it's any safer
- anywhere else?
- You need to get away.
You need to get
very far away from me.
Alan, what's happened?
We can't be engaged anymore.
You... your parents
need to take you back
and find you
a husband elsewhere.
What's wrong with you?
I have something,
uh, uh, to tell you.
I'm...
I'm a homosexual.
All right.
No, no. M-Men, Joan...
uh, not women.
- So what?
- Well, I-I just told you.
So what?
I had my suspicions;
I always did.
But we're not like other people.
We love each other
in our own way,
and we can have the life
together that we want.
You-you... you won't be
the perfect husband.
Well, I can promise you,
I have no intention of
being the perfect wife.
I'll not be... fixing
your lamb all day
while you come home
from the office.
I'll work.
You'll work.
And we'll have
each other's company.
We'll have each other's minds.
a better marriage than most.
Because I care for you.
And you care for me.
And we understand one another
more than...
more than anyone else ever has.
I don't.
- What?
- Care for you.
I never did.
I-I just needed you
to break Enigma.
I've done that now,
so... so you can go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I've spent entirely
too much of my life
worried about what
you think of me,
or what my parents think of me,
or the boys in Hut 8
or the girls in Hut 3.
And do you know what?
I'm done.
This is the most important
work I will ever do,
and no one is going to stop me.
Least of all, you.
You know what, they were right.
Peter, Hugh, John.
You really are a monster.
The war dragged on
for two more...
solitary years...
and every day we performed
our blood-soaked calculus.
Every day we decided
who lived and who died.
Every day we...
helped the Allies to victories,
and nobody knew.
- Stalingrad.
The Ardenne.
The invasion of Normandy.
All victories that
would not have been possible
without the intelligence
that we supplied.
And people...
talk about the war as
this epic battle between, um...
civilizations... freedom
versus tyranny,
democracy versus Nazism,
armies of millions
bleeding into the ground,
fleets of ships
weighing down the oceans,
planes dropping bombs
from the sky
until they obliterated
the sun itself...
The war wasn't like that for us.
For us, it was just...
half a dozen
crossword enthusiasts
in a tiny village
in the South of England.
WINSTON CHURCHILL: This is...
your victory.
- Victory...
of the cause of freedom
in every land.
PRESIDENT TRUMAN: This is
a solemn but glorious hour.
I wish that
Franklin D. Roosevelt
had lived to see this day.
TURING: Was I God?
No. Because... God
didn't win the war.
We did.
ALEXANDER: So, what happens now?
Is it... back to university
for us, I suppose?
Yes, pretty much.
But you've one thing left to do
before your service
to your government
- in concluded.
- What's that?
Burn everything.
- Burn? Why?
- You were told when you started
this was a top-secret program...
did you think we were joking?
- But the war is over.
- TURING: This war is.
But there'll be others.
And we know how to break a code
that everybody else believes
is unbreakable.
MENZIES: Precisely.
Tear it down. Light it up.
Sweep away the ashes.
None of you have
ever met before.
None of you have ever even heard
the word Enigma.
Have a safe trip home.
MENZIES: Behave. With a bit
of luck, you'll never have
to see me or one another again
for the rest of your lives.
That's unbelievable.
SIGHS: Now, Detective,
you get to judge.
So, tell me... what am I?
Mm, am I... a machine?
Am I a person?
Am I a war hero?
Am I a criminal?
I can't judge you.
Well, then...
you're no help to me at all.
VOICE-OVER: Come in.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Turing. Sit down.
Something the matter?
You and Christopher Morcom
are quite close.
I wouldn't say that.
Well, your mathematics teacher
says the two of you
are positively inseparable.
We're the best students
in the class.
He caught you passing notes
the other day.
Cryptography, to pass the time.
The class is too simple.
You and your friend solve maths
problems during maths class
because the maths class
is too dull?
He's not my friend.
Well, I'm told
he's your only friend.
Who said that?
Something's come up
concerning Morcom.
Why am I here?
Christopher is dead.
I don't understand.
His mother sent word
this morning.
The family were
on holiday, you see.
I don't understand.
Well, he had
bovine tuberculosis,
as I'm sure he told you.
So this won't come
as a shock, but...
still, all the same, I'm sorry.
You're mistaken.
Did he not tell you?
Well, he's been sick
for a long time.
He knew this was coming soon.
But he had a stiff
upper lip about it.
Good lad.
- Are you all right, Turing?
- Yes. Of course.
Like I said,
I didn't know him very well.
Ah. I see.
Very well.
May I leave, Headmaster?
Congratulations, sir.
Sorry.
I would have come.
I would have testified.
And what would you have said,
that I, uh...
I wasn't a homosexual.
Alan... this is serious.
They could send you to jail.
Damn it.
Your hands. You're twitching.
No-no, I'm not.
- Alan.
- Uh...
It's the medication.
The medication?
Uh, well, the judge
gave me, um, a choice...
uh, ei-either
two years in prison
or... ho-hormonal therapy.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Chemical castration.
Um, to, uh, to cure me
of my, um...
CHUCKLES: Homosexual predilections.
Well, of course I chose that.
I mean, I... couldn't...
work in prison, and, uh...
All right.
Now, I-I'm going to
speak to your doctors.
I'm going to speak to your lawyers.
I'm... I'm fine.
Please let me help you. -No,
I, uh, don't need your help,
thank you.
Alan, you do not have
to do this alone.
I'm not alone.
Never have been.
Christopher's become so smart.
If-if I don't continue
my treatment,
then they'll, um...
they'll take him away from me.
You...
CRYING: You-you can't let
them do that. You can't.
You... you can't let
them leave me alone.
SOBBING: I don't...
I don't want to be alone.
- I don't want to be alone.
- All ri... all right, all right.
All right.
It's all right.
Come and sit down.
- It's all right.
Oh, well, that's a...
that's a much nicer ring
- than the one I-I made you.
Yes. His name's Jock.
He's an Army man, if
you can believe it.
- We work together.
Why don't we do
a crossword puzzle.
It'll only take us five minutes.
Or, in your case, six.
There.
Uh...
Uh, p... perhaps later.
Yes, of course.
You-you got what
you wanted, didn't you?
Work, a husband.
Normal life.
No one normal could
have done that.
Do you know, this morning...
I was on a train
that went through a city
that wouldn't exist
if it wasn't for you.
I bought a ticket from a man
who would likely be dead
if it wasn't for you.
I read up on my work...
a whole field of
scientific inquiry
that only exists because of you.
Now, if you wish you
could have been normal...
I can promise you I do not.
The world is an
infinitely better place
precisely because you weren't.
Do you... do you
really think that?
I think... that sometimes
it is the people
who no one imagines anything of
who do the things that
no one can imagine.