Translation and adaptation: Undergrow & Kprice
Subtitles-us Team / www.subtitrari-noi. ro
RESCUE MISSION
June 6, 1944
? in an effort to? NFR? nge for? They German
occupying Fran? a,
US and allied troops
storm the beaches of Normandy
? n the largest sea invasion?
in history: Day Z.
Autumn 1944
P? R? S northern France? Her
? nc? the? expects? release,
It is controlled by the German Army?
and the Waffen SS.
? n time? it? s the villages
under the deal? ie Nazi?,
some officers? SS officers commit
r crimes warfare dire
? against civilians and the soldiers? OF THE alia and.
? in- and head down!
Hurry!
You? Returned.
- I missed you.
Lewis!
What's the situation? Take?
Almost went with all? Ii, sir.
Have r? C mas? Few tanks, us?'re Doctors,
mai avem maxim 20 de minute. 20 00: 05: 42.479-> 00:
05: 44.735 We do not have 20 minutes available? Ie.
How is my daughter, Nancy?
- Dreams? it? n below.
Withdraw and V? to trees!
Shit! Scans? trees.
P? Zea!
? MPU? c? it!
Lewis? MPU? C? It!
Withdrawal!
S? go.
Lewis!
Up? Up!
You have the worry? the wings!
Lewis!
S? go!
Ave and 10 minutes!
Jones? Mpachetat
and ready to go, sir.
Tell s? leave.
Yes, sir.
We and prepare yourself? I?
- Almost.
Shit!
is that? Captain Becket!
E r? Nit seriously!
Where's Nancy?
- E? N truck? To.
Stop and V?!
Stop and truck!
Nancy!
I need you now.
They told me to? m? climb? n truck? stand.
- Come on, s? It lu? M on next? Tor.
S? go!
? Supports and it down!
- Stay Nemi? Cat, Beckett.
Stay Nemi? Cat, damn it!
- ? Supports and it down!
They gave him morphine? c? mpul battle?
To and people here should
s? either go? i already.
There we?? m.
- Forget? them, come s?? We begin!
You should? I leave? m now!
You should? oppressed? ngerarea, c? Captain,
otherwise you will die.
L? To? And it s? v? operate.
If? I do not leave? m now
we die to? ii.
Quick, Nancy, m? There? S.
Come on!
Penicillin??
- Yes, prepare yourself?'re Not.
Le? In?, s? I us? c? m.
- Maxwell.
Maxwell.
- Yes Yes.
Get us out of here.
Po and operate it? In a
transport means?
? n any case.
C? T long do we have?
- About 10 minutes, sir.
Ave and 5 minutes.
It? S good?
- Yes, sir.
I was r? Nit.
- Not what I meant.
What you got there?
At ease, dolls Tiul.
My sister has he f? Cut.
It is my talisman, b? I suspect.
Yes, there are many like? Be here.
That is yours?
Your talisman?
It's just a lighter?
What's your name? Your?
- Lewis, sir.
What's surname t? U?
- James.
Okay, soldier James Lewis.
? You know how? Nemi stay? as the position? IE?
Yes, sir.
- Good. Stay here and be careful nazi? S.
Sir?
- Yes.
What? do if? v? d one?
- No it to? I s? between? n? within.
How's his pressure?
- Is good?
Forceps.
Las? It.
Do not shoot and not shoot? I! It's a hospital,
is a hospital!
It is a team? Medical?!
Good good! We teach? M we teach? M!
Go and see what's going on out there?
Hurry!
Continue?!
We? N the midst of a medical procedure.
You can and s? v? consider and with all? ii,
the prisoners of the Third Reich.
Preda? I?, v immediately.
Doctor. Immediately.
Doctor! Please!
If? not? close my wound this man,
He will die.
Want to? c mean? no?
I say that? I want to? forms and lines? te,
that s? I can finish what I do.
Bring them on to? I.
V? Please! You should? finish? m.
How you name? Your?
Lieutenant valued
Vera Cornish.
Vera... You have a minute.
Nancy.
A s? be good.
- Not good.
We are prisoners of r warfare,
n a s? we r? NEASC?
They? MPU? How the doctor.
Lini? Te!
Lini? Thou? NSU and!
Do not shoot? I!
? This is an ongoing transport
r prisoner of warfare Americans.
A transport vehicle
r prisoners of warfare.?
We are Americans.
Yes? Then tell me which is the best?
team? Baseball in America?
Probably? you say New York
but I was? say that? e Brooklyn.
Brooklyn?
There is no m? An op car SECTION.
I wanted to? Boston say,
but I think? m? you kill?
? nc? I can do it.
Jesus! I hit us?
- No. It sl? Bit of work? Ie.
Sorry r? U for that.
I thought? is a truck with weapons.
I? S OK?, I needed a haircut.
He? S lucky.
Nearly c? I never miss?
Where are we?
What is your unit?
Just me and Fisher.
C? When we landed, we Desp? R? It
Our unit?
S hope? use radio
that s? lu? m leg? tour with her.
L sabotaged.
- Shit! Really?
Nearly c? I hit.
- You want to? c mean? I almost c? I f? cut it.
What? No no.
- I was not and got on to? I?
No. Two of them fled.
Z? U? A, b? IE? I.
Vera, sit? N truck.
What you and to me? Nwhich here?
- Probably m? NCAR Naso? nem? EASC?
Liverwurst!
It's a great name.
Jesus!
Resist?, buddy!
Apas? her!
Fish!
Sta? I? Ntina and the p? M? Nt!
I resist?! Apas? hard on it!
Vera!
Have packages sulfur there?
- A s? I'm looking for!
Go and fetch him.
Go and get it!
Cover and-m?!
Come on!
I resist?! Resist?, buddy!
I resist?! Resist?, right?
My mother is...
- T? I worry? N leg? Tour? with her,
a s? be good, m? You hear?
A s? be well.
Vera, where packages sulfur?
Maxwell.
Take one.
I help you.
A s? tert sons? r.
I resist?! A s? We deal? m?? knew two guys,
then s? We Care? by you. Good?
Stay awake!
Anderson!
I want to? go? n heads toward the trees.
? itself struggles? s? shoot? n her right side?
You got it?
- Yes, sir.
M? name? Griggs, sir.
- Griggs. I want to? are you going? n the st? ng?
C? When you? We see? bend
c? v? approaching and the middle one was? attack? m.
Lewis, c? Nd? I slowly fire
? you started, did you? n? understand?
Yes, sir.
- You got it?
- ? All right?
Fish! Fish, resist? buddy!
Is there? You with us?
Shit!
Go, go!
Come on!
M? teach!
God!
No? Try and s? v? I? that? s,? nc?
? I'm r? u. A s? Me take the dolls while, sir.
What kind of escape is this?
- One not very successful? It?
Lewis!
M? s happy? you are and well, sir.
Who said that? I'm fine?
- M? excuse? i.
You succeeded? S it? you collect?
Yes, sir.
Where to AFL? M?
? try? m s? It d? m out.
One of them chose? surrender.
Are you going? Tri?
- Yes, sir.
May Maxwell tr? IE? Te?
- Yes. Perch purchasing truck.
Who the hell is she? Lie?
Sturmf? Hrer Otto Dittrich.
It is our prisoner.
- Jesus! Bring Maxwell!
You were lucky?
Nothing useful, with
Except? he h? r? ii.
Griggs was right.
They destroyed the radio.
Was awakened c? Captain.
- Yes?
We started here
and evacuation withdrew p? n? here.
Shall I? Nd? N direction? Take this for...
an hour? and a quarter an hour? and half? ity.
That puts us,
cam through this area.
Shit!
- Cam that's what it?
C? Captain!
For what? To?
- As and support when c? Nd go and, sir.
I work with limited resources.
and myself.
There were too many.
Here.
You should? be here.
? In the best case,
we walk 50 kilometers.
? I? N the r your case?
- It would be far at? T.
It can not? go? at? t much.
He seems? believe? c? can.
- Because? not resulting effect of the medicines.
Then as well,
s? hit the road.
Ladies? Nt? I.
C? Pitanii May? Nt? I.
Nancy.
Cuno? Team a fetus? Dutch?
with names stand.
Not? S Dutch, right?
No.
? I know that? I have no right
s? I? I ask this.
I have m? Nc? Rhymes? Behind ear
And I can not reach it.
M?? wondering...
Never mind?, forget? this is why.
I do not want? I feel and st? njenit?
At this ear?
- Yes.
Mul? Thank you.
You saved me.
What are you doing?
Nothing. Dittrich had an m? Nc? Rhymes.
There? S stand his name.
His name is "Nazi".
La p? M? Nt! Hide and-you?!
If? SCO and a cuv? nt, it? s dead!
Hell, no!
Put it down!
Pune and dolls that down!
Down with it!
No, put it down!
Pune and dolls that down!
Shut your mouth?!
Put it down!
It? S? Surrounded by Americans!
If? not put dolls as below...
Shut your mouth?!
Put it down!
It? S? Surrounded by Americans.
Shut your mouth?!
Pune and dolls that down!
Where are the rest?
There can be one, right?
Ba is one.
Trust and c? is a deserter?
One to admit? c? nc? l v? d.
I'm fine.
I'm fine dn? Lt...
It was? Nt? Mplat something?
No.
You do what you ui? I?
Who is it? You?
Good? day!
Talk and English?
It? S American??
- Yes.
Please!
We need help t? U.
- Can not help.
I have a c? Pitan r? Nit with me.
Not M? look? you.
We can not leave.
Tell friend t? U s?
- and let the gun out?
Seems a place at? T lines? Tit here.
I grew up on the farm?
No? I knew? it? s the? it?
Yes...
My family always wake
c? nd c? nta coco? ul.
Claia this straw
? I remember?'re the house?
i miss?? p? Parents? I t? i?
? I miss my mother.
and tat? t it? u?
He...
He left that? When I was 8 years old.
Have you not you? Seen since?
I do not want? May it you? D.
Mother and my sister have not deserved
s? are? nt? mple that.
C?? I are? I?
Six with all? Ii.
- Americans?
Like you?
Yes.
Have a telephone or radio?
- Telephone no. It only? N hour?
You po? I go there
should? bring medicines.
E occupied by the Germans.
I am... as they say... all Street? Days.
Nor should they? be and here.
- We m? Nwhich and water?
No hotel here.
? n? understand the risk.
Really?
Who tr? IE?'re Here?
- None.
Who is the lady?
So? My take.
Where is it?
Is dead?
Maxwell, po? I s? the? tep? i?, out please.
? I'm r? u so? Your take.
But who would believe it?
Neajut? NDU on us,
and Aju and the nazi? s.
Do not talk about it? I take now.
And I lost it I? ul.
A dead? In a hospital,
? n Africa.
For this I's? Revving
Nurses Service.
Whatever I do... m?? ask
if? he would have me? ndru me.
What he thinks about me now.
So? My take was a woman
very cautious?
You may be told to? go and.
I do not believe you.
I do not believe you!
T and dishonor it? Take.
I?? s always wanted? see?
New York.
and myself.
It? S good?
We leave? s? sleep? n barn
And I d? m? nwhich.
It was c? T s p Needle? and is blow his brains today.
I ordered was that soldier? you? MPU? te.
? I know that, sir.
Not p? C rut?? tii.
I wanted? give the goal position? Our take?,
then s? We wake up with nem? ii us.
C? S ass nd t? U to b? Cut,
should? water and the tr? Slack.
I wrong? It, sir.
Then? N tran? Ee, I...
- Do not talk about tran? Ee,
there was a completely different? GRE? eal?
My friend had just been? MPU? As,
really? n fa? mine.
That's your excuse?
C? boyfriend t? u just been? MPU? how?
People? Take me were like us?'re Brothers and.
- You think? no? I know this?
Stay here and? Are you telling me this?
No? You know any c? T damn soldier.
It? S been hard on him.
It's just a little? Ti.
T and can afford to? or a little? it here.
If you mind? I stay here?
You lost a friend today?
? I'm r? u.
We? MPU? As a pu? S German today.
I looked.
Fix? The eye.
Then I? MPU? Cat.
This... should? m? do?
s? m? feel good.
No? That... I'm...? make a good soldier.
That's why we're here, right?
S? murder? m r guys? i.
A? E.
C? T time it? S here?
- C? S Teva? For? M? Ni.
It is not how I imagined.
E r? T ndul your already?
- Yes, sir.
Did you succeed? S it? sleep?
- Pu? In.
Get it slightly... c? Pitan. Good?
- S? I take slightly?
M??? ur you.
R warfare? Re...
Instead you?
s?? r? on?'re some things.
C? Captain? Itself struggles?
just s? you? in?? n?? life, dolls Tiul.
C? T bad? e, Lieutenant?
I v? Seen and worse, sir.
Is Infected?, needs medication.
- Lewis or should I? go.
? S and s? read and their labels?
- F? Us a list?
I can not? I do.
You should? m? go? n?, s time? v? d what
and s? I take the right ones.
Bruno a s? m? go?
A s? son? okay?
What talk? I?
About wound c? Captain.
A s?? I try? g? SESC and a phone.
We could use sugar.
It helps to clean the area?? the infection take.
He needs medication true? Installments.
You should? I go now.
You brought the truck? In
that s? I help you.
I was? N truck.
As and gone?
I got out of the truck? At,
that s? m? Aju and there? s
save life? C? Captain.
P and no po... and s? por and that.
It would take as a brake? Uzoaic??
and fits?'re good.
It? S prepare tit?
One moment.
P? Remains on? Me them.
He dies c? Captain?
Who is?
Mrs.?
Mr.
Bruno Travert?
- Yes.
Talk and German?
English?
- Yes. Can I? v? help?
and your? Talk and English?
Yes. Pu? In.
We us? I check? Ri.
There should? long.
It seems... that? we have a problem? here.
Apparently? the recordings of our
They are incomplete.
? we have just noted Mr. Travert
to this address.
Who you are and you?
Is it? My take.
Excluding Wedding rings??
It had been a sell.
For m? Nwhich.
How did? called? i?
Margot.
The letter V? please.
M-A-R-G-A-T.
You have the kids?
No.
May tr? IE?'re Someone else here?
A s? need? s? take a look.
Nothing, ma'am?
You should? We do it
every house?
I leave? M once? T.
At? T for c? T no...
hide and someone.
Like a Jew.
C? T long you are and c? S? Tori? I?
For 15 years.
15 years?
? Means? c? a and was t? n? r?
- Yes.
He r? Mas a room?
Come and here.
Who sleeps here?
None.
Fra... My brother,
c? nd coming? n Vizit?
And he believes about it? Your take?
O? NDR? Ge? Te.
I am convinced? a? a is.
What do we have here?
Someone has an attraction? Ie sweets.
Hiding And so? Your, Lord?
VRE and one?
Safe.
V? please.
A and v? Saw someone on your property,
not you? known
or was? in the past?
No.
A s? need? s? We look? m
the remaining property?? ii.
Dn?
Mr Travert.
V? Please s? We would? t? s barn.
Not a good idea?, nazistule.
Where the hell have ap? Rut?
Fourth.
Okay? Intitle, dolls Tiul.
C? Captain. Bruno a s? m? go?? n hour?
Watch?, lieutenant.
- A s? I, sir.
Nancy, we need something else?
Good.
Vera.
See if? they and some cold beer you.
One could do the top priority.
? You know that? we can not take with us.
and neither can it not? it here.
? I know.
I? C?
Mi? C?!
- V? Well, yes and let me go.
Shut your mouth?!
- No one was? say nothing, nim? odd.
V? Well, yes and let me go.
- Shut your mouth?!
I will not say anything...
Here.
I will say nothing, nim? Odd.
- ? Ngenuncheaz?
? ngenuncheaz?!
V? please you? beg!
I have a mother?
V? Please have a mother?!
Her name is Nadia.
- Nim? Odd does not care? your mother.
V? please you? Please...
- Shut your mouth?!
I am her only son.
V? Please, I'm the only son
my mother.
Lewis, put them c? Lu?
No. Please, please!
No no no.
I beg you!
Shut your mouth?
No! No!
? I'm r? u, pu? Tiul.
Kill her? Him.
I want to? v? d.
That's an order.
You sense and ever? guilty?
For?
For the people and kill.
No.
? n t place your nth? do that.
I've asked have you do it.
- We do not have too many bandages.
Mr.
It's my body and if you I want to? am
What I p?? I, find out.
If? not? MPU? c I
m?? MPU? c? them.
That we? N common.
Not M? I feel guilty about that.
No reason was? m? I feel guilty.
You have? I leave? m.
- What is it?
Wine nem? Ii.
Nem? They have reached the firm?
- Vera where it is?
No? I know.
There have? Returned? Nc?
Ready. Go? Back? I see
if? and g? it? s Vera and Bruno.
Do not attract attention of thee
And do not get to and you? low, okay?
Yes, sir.
Lieutenant!
down! Down!
I f? Cut everything to me and asked.
? You know what I do mincino? team?
Or tr? D? Tors?
V? please.
I? S tried? v? help.
S? m? aju? i?
Americans are there.
Where obersturmf? Hrer my site?
No? I know.
- Exactly. No? You know.
S? move forward.
E Lewis.
You should? I leave? m.
We heard? MPU? C? Ture.
Where Vera?
On her killed? T it?
- No.
No, not her.
Bruno.
- And Vera where he is?
Is it enough? N?, hour sir.
M?? come back.
- It's not her. Ran away.
Contact your? Our unit?
Last place? N who would lead the firm's?
Lieutenant, go ahead!
If? You go there and attract nem? ii
to us, to kill us? ii.
S? go.
Lewis.
Insurance? C yourself? have failed? s it? run?
Are Chance s? be? n?? life.
- Yes, sir.
R? m? nem f? r? fuel.
Please have? the nearest tell us?
stay? ie power. Over.
Continue? to drive Charlie.
Charlie. Over.
Recep? mentioned.
Rekon three over.
Red Fox 1. Over.
Red Fox Red Fox 1. 1.
Are Yankee 3. Over.
Red Fox 1 are Yankee 3.
M? hear?
Tell us position? Your take.
Over.
We? Behind enemy lines
and separating and for our unity?
We need alia coordinates? ILOR.
We prepare tim departure.
Over.
C? Nd go? I?
Done.
16:00.
Over.
We come there.
Red Fox 1 where looking for you
c? nd get there?
Kprice not pri? EPE what he says? The
I'm having a beer, Bill.
Done.
Front Desk mentioned.
- Front Desk mentioned, over and disconnected.
What the hell? Nt? MPL? there?
Wine nem? Ii!
God...
Cover?
- And ears, soldier.
Where's Nancy?
Dementia hell!
If? do this,
a s? being sp? nzurat.
? nc? No.
We are here.
Nem? I'm here.
Location? Nt? E lnire here somewhere,
a radius? 16 km.
Talk and park? We could leave here.
Good? morning? a, friends.
Nancy.
Mr C? Pitan, you look surprised? m? see.
O? Cigarette??
No?
? I'm r? u, but it's a visit?
courtesy.
V? mas offer? and cas?,
but should? do and something new
if? deign and.
Mr C? Pitan Beckett, please.
I do not need lame.
Nancy.
? I'm r? u Vera.
What do you? mean?
What i'm?? r? U?
Dittrich! Dittrich! What i'm?? r? U?
Get yourself Damn!
Killed? T her Vera.
- Do not say that!
You're from where?? tii.
- It is my fault.
Why do you say that?
I gave you? N bar? c? When I? n tran? ee.
Should they? be here.
Mr C? Pitan Beckett
if? You were not r? nit...
No? I know what was? Nt? Mplat there, dolls Tiul.
- I did not f? Cut job.
I did not f? Cut job.
We are? Nt? MPL? everyone less? Tiul.
Agree?
No soldier should not? be? mpov? rat
with such a wine?
How the hell? I not r? u
if? you staring at me?
Bring my son.
Bring it immediately!
Good.
Right, and I get it.
I want to? - l V? D.
You should? - l V? D.
Rest? You up.
M? go to? get it.
Tell him that?..
Where are we?
? I'm r? u.
Vera should? m? treat...
Vera is not here, sir.
This man needs medication.
We are prisoners of r warfare and ave and
Bound take s? We give and medical aid.
? I? m Elegant say? car?
Where Dittrich?
What? means? this?
Have Six c? R? S game.
Yes. Have Six c? R? S game.
fucker Six c? r? s game.
You Six c? r? s game.
Motherfucker!
You Six c? r? s game!
You Six c? r? i!
fucker Six c? r? i!
- What? nt? MPL? here?
- Fucker Six c? R? I!
Oberf? Hrer.
Yes.
Bring and it? ncoace.
Forget? Yourself to those around t? U.
I'm a soldier and.
They left her home?
And they come? into a? should? str? in?
one reason.
S? fight.
And however and dictate Fuhrer
is there? st? m on the site...
and s? the? expectations? m.
? In this village continued struggle?
Ace? S people...
Ace? S soldiers and...
Merit? s? see? s? nge.
Â therefore...
Which of you offer? volunteer
s? fight?
Patric.
I do not struggled elsewhere.
But you?
Soldier Lewis.
Want to? wolf and for? your country?
Wait, dammit s? either!
Damn!
If? Want to? we fight? m,
I fight!
I'm fighting!
Get? from there, Nancy!
- Enough! I'm fighting!
Get out? from there, Nancy!
? begins!
Tic? Losul hell!
It? S anger?
You have an r? Zbuni t? N? R??
Then fight?
Come on, Lewis.
Come on Lewis!
Let c? po? i!
Come dolls Tiul.
A? A.
Up? Up!
Come up? Yourself there!
? keep guard up, Lewis.
Up? guard.
? keep guard up, Lewis!
? keep guard up!
Fight and!
Come and!
Love?'re It!
Lewis covered? Yourself.
? learn?? s? Wolfs!
Lewis, sit down!
Lewis cover? Up!
Las? It? Alone.
Have you? Seen?
? I definitely am a man m? rinimos.
If? r? m? nem here
to kill us? ii.
It's pretty slightly s? escape? m
in the? like this improvised?
Yes? And then what?
No? I know.
It? S good?
M? jaw pain.
A s? kill us, right?
- No.
I heard you talking.
- I am pl? Ngeam mln themselves? At? T.
M?? ask? re a s? last p? n?
it? s tell them? c mother? I disappear? rut.
A s? pl? ng?
You have no idea how much it was? pl? ng?
E sensitive?
I heard that someone? pl? ng? like her.
It confused?
A? Expectations that much.
? I'm r? u.
It does not matter?
A s?
- And review the mother, Nancy.
Have you slept at all?
They sent only a guard with me
and Lieutenant c? When I was at the lake yesterday.
? I told my son, soldier?
Mr!?
He was a good child.
A b boy n? Dejde.
It was? Nrolat.
He was 17.
It would be? Nrolat and earlier
if? could.
and always wanted
s? like me.
So? I told him that? This one s? it send?
direct? n grave? nt.
Nearly c-hit it.
It was wrong? It in December? T? N? Iruirea things.
M?? I wonder if?? knew that? a s? die?
If? And I was afraid?
I'm sure? It was a good soldier, sir.
? You know what? s makes the soldier? be good?
S?? s you...? press the tr? Slack.
Humanity's.
Sometimes you have to? ap? s? m on tr? Slack.
But a good soldier doesn? S wishes? S you? pull?
This is a big pig? Rie.
What we do...
A s? you b? ntuie c? nd get home?
Mr.
Forget? all this, Lewis.
Go home?...
and happy? life?? yourself.
Do not be sad.
Yes, sir.
Lewis.
S?
- And luck.
I really needed a lighter?
Yes, p? I...
It's an amulet? lucky?
It? S prepare tit?
Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
It? S tert? R? Lieutenant! Damn!
You got nothing. It? S tert? R?
Probably? not least? Tiul.
- Damn s? either!
Get? From here, dolls Tiul.
- No. No, I do not abandon!
It's your only? Ans? Get out? from here.
Get out? That's an order.
Get out?!
No.
It? S rite? The air.
Vino? Ncoace, Nancy.
Vino? Ncoace.
Who was it?
Maxwell.
Lewis is a good soldier.
N it? S take him?
C?? s do you have?
C?? s soldiers and and died?
Five or more? I?
mouth and I? C?!
It? S okay.
Nothing.
? knees!
Hurry!
Bring it!
I? c? yourself.
I? c? yourself again?
Faster
Americanu!
Stop hiding!
Lewis Soldier!
It's your last?? ans?
Ie the American?, and sight!
Lewis Soldier!
This is the result of your actions.
Friends t? U will not be considered and
r prisoners of warfare.
Ve and be judge and to his works.
And the verdict? A...
Sentences? A is s? be and execute and.
Las? S them up? leave.
? MPU? c?
- m? me if? must, but? You do not no r? u them.
Not right, damn!
? You know that? that's not fair!
Last? Ans?!
Fire!
Raise and V?, sir.
- Save? Women Lewis.
Not V? abandon, sir.
- It's a direct order, soldier.
Not V? abandonment, sir!
Where is Maxwell?
Maxwell does not come.
You should? I leave? m!
Soldat.
V Third Reich? I order?
s? v? teach and immediately.
How and is there? N back?
It's good.
He looked and!
Viewing and that?
Yes, they are.
Fi and more alert, sir.
Bravo, Lewis!
Bravo!
You should? I leave? m, sir!
? nc? Two? minutes.
I told them that? S the? Expectations? M
p? n? 16:00.
Nem and!
- Comes a machine in? with nem And, sir!
You visibility?
- That?'m Trying, sir.
Shoot as soon as po? I.
Translation and adaptation: Undergrow & Kprice
Subtitles-us Team / www.subtitrari-noi. ro
Wait!
They are Americans.