>> OBSESSIONS SOMETIMES GRAB
HOLD OF A MAN.
HE MAY THINK, FOR EXAMPLE, DAYS
AND NIGHTS OF NOTHING ELSE BUT
THE MOON.
I HAVE SUCH A MOON.
DAYS AND NIGHTS, I'M HELD IN THE
GRIP OF A MEMORY.
IT CONSUMES ME.
AN IDEA FOR A STORY...
>> WHY, THIS COUNTRY IS A
SHINING CITY ON A HILL.
THE STRONG -- THE STRONG, THEY
TELL US, WILL INHERIT THE LAND.
AND I ASK YOU NOW, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
FOR THE GOOD OF ALL OF US, FOR
THE LOVE OF THIS GREAT NATION,
FOR THE FAMILY OF AMERICA, FOR
THE LOVE OF GOD, PLEASE MAKE
THIS NATION REMEMBER HOW FUTURES
ARE BUILT.
THANK YOU AND GOD BLESS YOU.
>> LAST CALL FOR HARLEM...
FORDHAM, WOODLAWN, WAKEFIELD,
MT. VERNON, FLEETWOOD,
ROSSVILLE, WHITE PLAINS,
VALHALLA, MT. PLEASANT,
CONCORD, PLEASANTVILLE,
MT. KISCO...
>> WE'RE LATE.
>> ...BEDFORD HILLS.
>> YOU'RE LATE.
>> APOLOGIES.
>> PLEASE, CAN'T WE DRIVE?
>> WE ALREADY FOUGHT ABOUT THIS.
>> YOU'RE TOO OLD FOR TRAINS.
>> I LIKE TRAINS.
>> I'LL BUY YOU ONE.
PETER. PETER!
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
>> DID YOU KNOW THAT, IN KOREA,
JILTED LOVERS COMMIT SUICIDE BY
SEALING THEMSELVES IN A ROOM
FILLED WITH LILIES?
APPARENTLY, THE PERFUME IS
TOXIC.
I WONDER HOW MANY YOU'D NEED TO
KILL EVERYONE ON THIS TRAIN.
>> HE LIKED TRAINS BECAUSE, ON
THEM, COUPLES RARELY FEEL THE
NEED TO SPEAK.
HE MIGHT NOT HAVE TO HEAR THE
REASONS WHY HER SHOW GOT
CANCELED OR DEFEND HIMSELF FOR
NOT CASTING HER IN HIS NEXT
FILM.
HE WOULDN'T HAVE TO ENDURE THE
ENDLESS QUESTIONS ABOUT HER
BROTHER'S ILLNESS.
WHAT COULD HER DOCTOR FRIEND
TELL HER THAT SHE DIDN'T
ALREADY SUSPECT?
HE MIGHT NOT HAVE TO DISCUSS HER
SON'S ARTISTIC ANARCHY OR GOSSIP
ABOUT THE CARETAKER'S DAUGHTER
AND HER MARRIAGE OF NECESSITY.
HE'D MEET ALL OF THEM, SOON
ENOUGH.
THEY WERE OFF TO HER COUNTRY
HOUSE TO CELEBRATE HER BROTHER'S
BIRTHDAY.
IT WAS MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND,
1984.
>> I FEEL LIKE MERYL IN
"SILKWOOD."
>> WHERE IS SHE?
>> OH, GOD.
BRACE YOURSELF.
>> WHERE IS SHE?
NO ONE HERE.
OH, OH.
OH, MY GOD!
I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU.
OH!
>> OH! OH!
STOP. STOP.
JOHAN, PETER. PETER, JOHAN.
>> OKAY, JOHAN.
>> HI.
>> MASS TRANSIT.
THE WITCH'S TIT MUST HAVE FROZE
OVER.
>> IT'S HELL.
>> WHAT?
>> HELL MUST -- N-NEVER MIND.
>> WHAT? AND?
>> AND EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
CATS AND DOGS.
HERE. SMELL THESE.
>> OH.
>> BREATHE DEEP.
>> MM.
OH, THE HELL FROZE OVER.
>> THINKS HE OWNS THE PLACE.
WHERE'S THE WAGON?
>> I HAD THINGS TO DO.
>> WHY IS THERE A GUN IN THE
CAR?
>> IT'S A RIFLE.
I TAGGED A BULL ON THE WAY IN.
YOU KNOW, IT SHOOTS DARTS.
>> JOHAN!
>> WHAT? SORRY.
THAT'S HOW WE MEDICATE NOW THESE
DAYS.
>> GENTLE.
>> LIKE FOOT ROT, BLACKLEG,
CANCER EYE, FOOT AND MOUTH,
LUMPY JAW, WARTS, WOOD TONGUE...
IT'S WHAT'S FOR DINNER.
>> DON'T THINK ABOUT IT.
>> SORRY.
>> JOHAN!
THIS IS VERY EXPENSIVE LUGGAGE.
>> PAIN IN THE NECK.
GET IT?
>> I PAY HIM.
>> WELL, HARDLY.
>> AFTER YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MARY PUTS UP
WITH HIM.
OHH, IT STINKS IN HERE.
>> SORRY.
>> IMAGINE YOU'RE ATTACKING THE
AUDIENCE.
>> I'M ATTACKING THE AUDIENCE,
BUT WITHOUT EMOTION?
>> JUST LIKE YOU'RE READING IT.
>> THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
>> COME ON.
>> "ALL EXPERIENCE HATH SHOWN
THAT MANKIND ARE MORE DISPOSED
TO SUFFER..."
>> THAT'S GREAT. THAT'S BETTER.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-HMM. ONE MORE TIME.
>> HERB IS GONNA HATE THIS.
>> NO, HE'S NOT.
COME ON, JUST READ.
JUST...
>> WHY COULDN'T YOU GET HIM A
TIE OR A GOLDFISH, LIKE ANY
NORMAL PERSON?
>> I'M NOT A NORMAL PERSON.
>> YOUR MOM IS GONNA HATE IT.
>> OF COURSE SHE'S GONNA HATE
IT -- SHE'S NOT IN IT.
>> IS SHE REALLY BRINGING PETER
THIS TIME?
NO IDEA.
>> I LOVE HIS MOVIES.
>> JUST READ THE LINES.
>> I COULD GET DISCOVERED.
>> HE'S BLIND.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
>> HE COULD PUT ME IN A MOVIE.
>> AND DEAF.
>> I COULD BE A STAR.
>> GOOD LUCK.
I GOT TO GO.
>> WHAT?
YOU WON'T COME BACK IN TIME.
>> MY DAD DOESN'T EVEN KNOW I'M
HERE.&-I GOT TO GO.
HEY!
>> DON'T BE LATE.
>> I WON'T.
>> PROMISE.
>> YOU'RE LATE.
>> OH, HELLO, MARY!
>> OH!
>> HERE.
>> OH, BEAUTIFUL!
>> PETER.
>> MARY, PETER. PETER, MARY.
>> OH, WE HAVE HEARD SO MUCH
ABOUT YOU.
>> HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> YOUR HUSBAND IS AN IMBECILE.
>> HE'S A STUPID, STUPID JERK.
>> WHEN GRANDMA FARTS, WE HIT
THE DOG.
YOU GOT IT?
>> YEAH.
>> DID THE WIG WORK AT ALL?
>> NOT A SOUL.
>> WONDERFUL.
>> OH, SORRY.
>> HOW DO I LOOK?
>> WELL, FAIR TO MIDDLING.
NOT BAD, HUH?
>> NO.
>> YEAH. PUT ME IN A MOVIE.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
>> JUST PUT ME IN A MOVIE, YOU
KNOW?
>> UH-HUH.
>> SHUT UP, JOHAN.
>> THERE IS A BEAR IN THE WOODS.
FOR SOME PEOPLE, THE BEAR IS
EASY TO SEE.
OTHERS DON'T SEE IT AT ALL.
SOME PEOPLE SAY THE BEAR IS
TAME.
OTHERS SAY IT'S VICIOUS AND
DANGEROUS.
SINCE NO ONE CAN REALLY BE SURE
WHO'S RIGHT, ISN'T IT SMART TO
BE AS STRONG AS THE BEAR...
IF THERE IS A BEAR?
>> 96.3.
102.
101.
100.5.
>> MOVE.
>> 99.8.
99.5.
HUH.
>> Very much...retrovirus.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> THANK YOU. OKAY.
>> Take care.
>> I WILL.
>> Bye.
>> OH, MARY, I LOVE THE
PLANTINGS.
THEY'RE GORGEOUS.
>> THANKS.
>> HERB BEHAVE HIMSELF?
>> YOU KNOW YOUR BROTHER.
>> IT'S LOCKED.
>> WELL, IT CAN'T BE.
>> IT'S NEVER LOCKED.
>> KNOCK.
>> HELLO?
OH, I JUST HEARD SOMETHING.
>> IT'S NOT OPENING.
>> WELL, IT'S PROBABLY STUCK.
>> USE YOUR SHOULDER.
>> YOU.
>> STEP ASIDE. STEP ASIDE.
STEP ASIDE.
>> EVERYTHING IS A PRODUCTION.
>> OW!
>> OHH. HERB.
>> HERB!
>> OHH!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HONEY. WHERE'S LOUIS?
>> I'LL -- I'LL GET HIM.
LOUIS!
>> OHO!
>> PETER?
>> YES.
>> HOW WONDERFUL TO MEET YOU!
>> YOU, TOO.
>> WELCOME.
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> OHH!
>> OHHH.
>> SORRY AGAIN.
>> JOHAN!
>> SORRY. OH.
>> OH, HERB. COME ON.
LET'S GO SIT DOWN.
>> COME ON.
HE'S GETTING BLOOD EVERYWHERE.
>> OHH! IMPOSSIBLE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> HE HID AND SOUGHT.
>> OW!
>> COME SIT DOWN.
>> ONCE MY BROTHER, NOW MY SON.
>> WHAT DID WE SAY ABOUT ACTING
YOUR AGE?
>> THAT IT'S POINTLESS.
>> COME. HAVE A SEAT.
>> HERE, TILT YOUR HEAD BACK.
>> I CAN'T STAND THE TASTE OF
BLOOD.
>> KEEP PRESSURE ON IT.
>> IT'S LIKE I'M EATING
SOMEBODY.
>> DOES HE NEED THE HOSPITAL?
>> HE'LL BE FINE.
>> OH, THANK GOD.
>> STEAKS.
>> WONDERFUL.
>> PETER, DOCTOR.
DOCTOR, PETER.
>> OH, LOUIS. NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> YOU, TOO.
>> EXCUSE ME. SIT TIGHT.
>> LIKE A LION WITH FRESH KILL.
OH, ALEX.
SORRY.
>> HI.
AWW.
STEPHEN.
OH, WHOA, YOU LOOK LOST.
>> SHE -- SHE HAS ME IN A
RELATIVE PIN.
>> WELL, THAT -- THAT SOUNDS
PAINFUL.
>> HELLO.
>> OH, STEPHEN, PETER.
PETER, STEPHEN.
>> HI.
>> ALEX, PETER. PETER, ALEX.
OH, THERE'S THAT...
>> KEEP STILL.
>> ...BEAUTIFUL BABY OF YOURS.
>> AH!
>> PIECE OF SUNSHINE.
AWW. I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
EXPECTING ANOTHER ONE.
>> WE ARE?
>> OH, STEPHEN IS
SINGLE-HANDEDLY SAVING
MOTHER NATURE ONE BIRD AT A
TIME.
HE'S TAKEN OVER THE ENTIRE
WATERFRONT -- EVEN GOT THE
COUNTY RESTRICTING OUR LAND USE.
THE NEIGHBORS LOVE US.
>> MY GOD, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MNH.
>> KEEP STILL.
>> I'M STARVING.
WHERE'S MY SON?
>> STOP.
>> HE'S UP IN HIS ROOM.
>> HE'S GETTING HIS MOVIE READY.
>> MOVIE?
>> INSTALLATION THING.
WHATEVER.
>> TONIGHT?
>> YOU WERE WARNED.
>> SUPPER IS ALMOST READY.
>> FOR FUCK'S SAKE!
>> I NEED TO WASH.
>> OH, YOU GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
JOHAN.
>> WHAT?
>> SORT OUT THE LUGGAGE.
>> NO, THANK YOU.
>> THAT WASN'T SO BAD, WAS IT?
>> OH!
SORRY.
>> OF COURSE, THE MORE MONEY
THEY THROW AT YOU, THE LESS
INTERESTING IT ALL IS.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A LOVE
STORY, BUT WHERE'S THE HAPPY
ENDING?
>> I LOVE IT.
GOT IT?
>> I DON'T GET IT.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> IGNORE HIM.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M POURING A GLASS OF WINE.
>> CAN HE DRINK?
>> IT'S FINE.&->> WELL, WHAT ABOUT HIS
MEDICINE?
>> WHAT -- WHAT MEDICINE?
>> HE CAN HAVE SOME WINE.
>> NOT LIKE I HAVE TO ASK FOR
PERMISSION.
>> I THOUGHT --
>> DON'T. DON'T THINK.
>> SO, STEPHEN, WHAT EXACTLY IS
IT THAT YOU DO?
>> NOTHING.
>> DAD.
>> I'M AN ORNITHOLOGIST.
I'VE BEEN TRACKING A FAMILY OF
EAGLES WHO MIGRATED TO THE
SOUTH SIDE OF THE PROPERTY
TWO YEARS AGO.
>> THAT'S NOT ALL THAT HE WAS
TRACKING.
>> MOM.
>> THE MALE ABANDONED, LEAVING
THE FEMALE AND HER EGG, SO I'VE
HAD TO BE A LITTLE MORE
INVOLVED.
>> IS ANYONE COLD?
>> IT'S A LITTLE TOUCH AND GO,
ACTUALLY.
>> ABE WOULD NEVER ABANDON.
>> ABE?
>> THAT'S WHAT HE CALLS HIM --
OLD ABE.
>> HOW MUCH ARE THEY PAYING YOU?
>> DAD.
>> WHAT?&-NOTHING, ZERO, ZILCH.
>> I BUILT A PERIMETER FENCE,
DEVELOPED A MANUAL HYDRATION
SYSTEM, FOOD REGIMEN.
>> LIKE A PRISON.
>> TECHNICALLY, I WORK FOR
THE DEPARTMENT OF ENVIRONMENTAL
CONSERVATION.
>> HE'S A FORENSIC...WILDLIFE
PATHOLOGIST.
>> WHAT?
>> SORRY.
>> COME ON.
REALLY -- REALLY, I'M AN --
I'M AN AVICULTURIST.
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
>> OH, MARY!
>> MANNERS, PLEASE!
OHH!
>> THEY LOOK DELICIOUS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IT'S PERFECT.
THERE'S NO STRESS IN THE MEAT.
YOU CAN ALWAYS TASTE, AND YOU
CAN FEEL IF THE ANIMAL HAD A
STRESSFUL END.
>> PLEASE STOP TALKING.
>> NO, WELL, IT GOES TASTELESS.
IT GOES BLAND, BUT THIS IS
PERFECT.
>> ALEX, DOES YOUR FATHER LISTEN
TO ANYONE?
>> NO.
>> A MAN WALKED INTO HIS HOUSE
WITH A SHEEP UNDER HIS ARM.
HE SAYS TO HIS WIFE, "I JUST
WANT YOU TO SEE THE PIG THAT
I'VE BEEN FUCKING WHILE YOU'VE
BEEN AWAY."
AND SHE SAYS, "THAT'S NOT A PIG,
DARLING -- THAT'S A SHEEP."
AND HE SAYS, "I WASN'T TALKING
TO YOU!"
>> YOU GOT IT?
SHE WASN'T A SHEEP.
>> EAGLES, BRISKET, AND SHEEP.
OH, MY.
>> WELCOME HOME, BABY.
>> IF MUSIC BE THE FOOD OF
LOVE, PLAY ON.
GIVE ME EXCESS OF IT, THAT,
SURFEITING, THE APPETITE MAY
SICKEN, AND SO DIE.
>> NEWTON'S THIRD LAW OF
MOTION -- TO EVERY ACTION,
THERE IS AN EQUAL AND OPPOSITE
REACTION.
>> EVA?
>> YOU SAID COME AND GET YOU
WHEN IT'S READY.
>> HAVE YOU SEEN EVA?
>> NO.
>> IS MOM HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE ARE THEY?
>> FEEDING.
>> IT'S CALLED "THERMAL
CONVECTION."
EAGLES GENERALLY SOAR ON THERMAL
CONVECTION CURRENTS, WHICH MEANS
THAT WE COULD GENERALLY PREDICT
THEIR FLIGHT PATHS.
>> LOOK AT ME, FLAPPING MY
WINGS.
>> UH, BUT R-RECENTLY, THERMAL
CURRENTS HAVE BEEN EXPANDING.
IT'S -- IT'S LIKE AN OVEN, AND
WE'RE JUST -- WE'RE JUST FRYING
OURSELVES.
>> WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
>> SO PREDICTING FLIGHT PATHS
HAS BECOME NEAR IMPOSSIBLE.
HE COULD BE LOST IN
NONDIRECTIONAL WINDS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BUT, UH, PERSONALLY, I-I
THINK IT'S TOXICOSIS.
>> ENGLISH.
>> MERCURY, LEAD POISON,
PESTICIDES.
>> GREEN GIANTS.
>> BUCK SHOT, POACHING --
THE LIST GOES ON AND ON.
>> MEANWHILE, THE WHOLE PLACE IS
IN QUARANTINE.
>> WELL, EAGLES ARE
BIOINDICATORS.
WE NEED TO PROTECT THEM...
>> NERD.
>> ...LIKE CANARIES IN A GOLD
MINE.
>> GROW A BEARD.
>> READ A BOOK.
>> HE WON'T LET ME FIX THE DOCK,
MAINTAIN THE RIDING TRAILS --
NOTHING.
>> I REPAIRED THE DOCK.
>> I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE ON THAT
DOCK.
>> SWEETIE.
>> HEY.
>> COME HERE.
OH!
MM.
YOU HUNGRY?
>> UH, I ATE ALREADY.
WHAT'S GOING ON, CRAZY?
>> NOT MUCH.
YOU?
>> COME ON.
WE BETTER GET READY.
>> OHH.
>> WANT THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> NOTHING. HE'S FINE.
>> FINE -- FUCKED UP,
INSECURE...
>> DAD.
>> HE'S FINE.
>> YOU ALWAYS SAY THAT WHEN
NOTHING IS.
WHAT WAS IT?
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> BOREDOM.
YOU GET COOPED UP IN THE COUNTRY
LONG ENOUGH, YOU START DOING
THINGS TO MAKE LIFE INTERESTING.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ME.
I GOT MARRIED AND HAD A KID.
THE SHOW IS GONNA BE READY IN
30 MINUTES.
GOBBLE GOBBLE.
OHH, MY FOOT IS ASLEEP.
>> TEA?
>> YES.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> GIVE ME A KISS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M SHAVING.
WE DID THIS ONCE IN OMAN.
WE HAD NO SOAP.
WE USED MASHED POTATOES.
YOU'RE MAKING ME NERVOUS.
EVA WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HERE
AT 7:30.
BEEN CALLING, BUT IT'S BUSY --
PROBABLY HER PARENTS.
>> YEAH, THEY'RE TYRANTS.
♪ WHEN I WAS YOUNG,
SEEMED THAT LIFE
WAS SO WONDERFUL, A MIRACLE ♪
♪ OH, IT WAS BEAUTIFUL,
MAGICAL ♪
>> STOP IT.
>> I KNOW.
I HAVE A
HORRIBLE VOICE.
OW!
MM, LIKE RATS FROM A SINKING
SHIP.
>> WHERE'S YOUR SWEATERS?
>> HAVE YOU SEEN ANY OF PETER'S
FILMS?
>> YES.
COME ON. SWEATER.
>> CLOSET. THEY HANG.
>> IS HE TALENTED?
>> NO.
>> HE'S QUIET.
HE LOOKS. HE LISTENS.
I THINK HE'S TALENTED.
>> WELL, YOU'RE WRONG.
ASK ANYONE.
>> I'M RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE SICK.
>> WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES THAT
MAKE?
>> ARM.
>> I'M SORRY.
WELL, I DIDN'T MEAN TO...
WHOOPS.
>> THAT'S MY NIGHTGOWN.
>> IT'S FOR ERIC'S SHOW.
>> YOU ARE WEARING MY TROUSSEAU
NIGHTGOWN.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> ERIC'S MUSE.
LIVES DOWNSTREAM.
DOESN'T DO ANYTHING, BUT SHE'S
SWEET.
I HAVE TO PEE.
>> SHE'S WEARING MY NIGHTGOWN.
HE GAVE HER MY NIGHTGOWN.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> HE'S A FRAUD.
>> NO.
>> PICK ANY MAGAZINE.
>> IT'LL TELL YOU.
ANY OF THEM, ANY MONTH.
>> OH!
>> EVA?
WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
>> THIS IS MARY'S NIGHTGOWN?!
>> OH!
>> HI, HERB.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M PERFECT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
>> HEY.
>> YOU SAID YOU BOUGHT THIS.
>> I DIDN'T.
>> I LOVE THIS ROOM.
>> I SAID I BROUGHT IT.
>> YOU'VE BEEN TO SO MANY
PLACES.
>> AND LOOK AT ME...
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN ANYWHERE.
>> ...LANDLOCKED.
>> WE'RE LATE.
>> I WALKED RIGHT INTO DINNER.
SO EMBARRASSING -- YOU HAVE NO
IDEA.
AND PETER'S HERE!
YOU SAID HE WASN'T COMING.
>> NO, I SAID I DIDN'T KNOW.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN MORE
EMBARRASSED IN ALL MY LIFE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I FELL.
THERE USED TO BE A TRAIL.
>> WE GOT TO GO.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THE
SHOW'S ABOUT TO BEGIN.
>> IT'S SO HUMILIATING.
>> I THINK YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
>> MEET YOU THERE.
>> YOU'LL GET LOST.
>> IT'S EASY FROM HERE.
>> SHE'S LIKE A DEER.
I THINK I'M GOING TO ASK HER TO
MARRY ME.
SOMEONE SHOULD.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE A GOOD GRAPE ON
THE VINE TOO LONG.
>> I'VE GOT IT COVERED.
>> OH?
>> YEAH, I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
>> HAS SHE?
>> WATCH YOUR STEP.
ALL WE NEED NOW ARE A FEW
GERMAN SHEPHERDS AND A MACHINE
GUN.
JOHAN, TURN IT OFF.
>> "ALL EXPERIENCE HATH SHOWN
THAT MANKIND ARE MORE DISPOSED
TO SUFFER..."
>> SUFFER.
>> "...THAN TO RIGHT THEMSELVES
BY ABOLISHING THE FORMS TO WHICH
THEY ARE ACCUSTOMED."
>> WHAT IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
>> IT'S THE DECLARATION OF
INDEPENDENCE.
>> AH.
>> "BUT WHEN A LONG TRAIN OF
ABUSES AND USURPATIONS EVINCES A
DESIGN TO REDUCE THEM UNDER
ABSOLUTE DESPOTISM, IT IS THEIR
RIGHT, IT IS THEIR DUTY,
TO THROW OFF..."
>> THROW OFF.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A BUMPY
RIDE.
>> SHUT UP!
LET FACTS BE SUBMITTED
TO A CANDID WORLD.
[ SOUSA'S "THE STARS AND STRIPES
FOREVER" PLAYS
]
>> HERE.
JOHAN, PASS THIS TO LOUIS.
>> STOP TALKING!
>> LOUIS.
>> MM.
>> BLANKET.
>> "HE HAS FORBIDDEN..."
>> FORBIDDEN.
>> "HE HAS RESOLVED...
HE HAS ENDEAVORED TO
PREVENT..."
>> PREVENT.
"HE HAS OBSTRUCTED THE
ADMINISTRATION OF JUSTICE."
>> JUSTICE!
>> "HE HAS KEPT AMONG US, IN
TIMES OF PEACE, STANDING
ARMIES."
>> "HE HAS PLUNDERED OUR SEAS.
HE HAS RAVAGED OUR COASTS,
BURNED OUR TOWNS..."
>> WHAT AM I SITTING ON?
>> "...AND DESTROYED THE LIVES
OF OUR PEOPLE!
HE IS TRANSPORTING LARGE ARMIES
OF DEATH...
DESOLATION...
TYRANNY!"
>> TYRANNY!
>> "...SCARCELY PARALLELED IN
THE MOST BARBAROUS AGES, AND
TOTALLY UNWORTHY THE HEAD OF
A CIVILIZED NATION."
>> "AND THE UNHAPPY MOON LIGHTS
HER LAMP IN VAIN..."
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> "A PRINCE, WHOSE CHARACTER
IS MARKED BY EVERY ACT WHICH
DEFINES A TYRANT..."
>> COOL.
>> "...IS UNFIT..."
>> THIS IS HORRIBLE.
>> "...TO BE THE RULER OF A FREE
PEOPLE."
>> THIS IS SICK.
>> IT'S REALLY DANGEROUS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WILL YOU STOP TALKING?
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
JUST STOP IT. STOP IT!
THE STAGE IS ALL YOURS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT WAS THAT?
>> DISTURBING.
>> YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
>> WHAT? DISTURBING.
>> ALL RIGHT, SHOW'S OVER.
ART HAS SPOKEN.
PETER, EVA. EVA, PETER.
>> WONDERFUL.
>> WAS IT?
>> SOMEBODY FIND HIM.
>> COME BACK AND HAVE SOME CAKE.
>> I GOT TO GO.
>> NO, COME ON.
>> HERB, COME ON.
>> YOU COULD HAVE KEPT YOUR
MOUTH SHUT.
>> WE'RE NOT LAB RATS.
>> WHAT A MESS.
ERIC IS SUCH A MESS.
I CAN'T STOP THINKING -- CAN I
TAKE SOMETHING FOR THAT?
>> NO.
>> USELESS.
YOU COMING?
>> IN A BIT.
>> WHAT'S FOR LUNCH?
>> THE USUAL -- CHEESE, FRUIT,
BEANS.
>> CAVIAR.
>> DREAMS.
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN THE WORLD?
>> NOTHING WORTH REPEATING.
>> LOUIS...HOW'S THE TIME?
>> STOPPED.
>> BORING, BORING, AND MORE
BORING.
IT'S ALL SO BEAUTIFULLY BORING,
AND THEN THERE'S THAT.
>> WHERE'S ERIC?
>> JOHAN, WHY DO YOU HAVE TO DO
THAT?
>> DO WHAT?
>> APPEAR.
>> HAVE YOU SEEN ALEX?
>> NOT FOR A WHILE.
>> WE WERE GONNA CHECK THE NEST.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
>> THERE'S NO FIRING OF GUNS ON
THE PROPERTY.
>> TALK TO JOHAN.
>> I'M TALKING TO YOU.
OHH, BROTHER.
OKAY, IF YOU SEE ALEX, TELL HER
I WAITED.
>> YOU LOOK RIDICULOUS --
YOU KNOW THAT?
>> I DO?
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
>> THINK ABOUT WHAT?
>> HE'S NOT LIKE YOU.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> HE'LL EAT YOU ALIVE.
>> YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE.
>> WELL, YOU'LL SEE.
>> CHARGE!
LIGHT BRIGADE.
LITTLE HORSES.
GO.
>> LET ME SEE THAT.
>> WAIT.
HEY, CAREFUL -- IT'S LOADED!
OH, THAT IS NOT OKAY!
>> THERE -- SOMETHING HAPPENED.
>> YEAH, YOU BLEW MY EARS OUT.
>> IF YOU SEE ERIC, I'M AT THE
BLIND.
THAT IS NOT OKAY.
>> NO FIRING GUNS ON THE
PROPERTY!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
WHO ARE THOSE CHILDREN?
>> HEY, KIDS, BE CAREFUL.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE FIRING GUNS!
>> KIDS, GET AWAY FROM THAT
CART!
>> DON'T WORRY -- THESE FILLIES
ARE UNDER FULL DISCIPLINED
CONTROL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HERB, STOP!
>> STOP THAT CART!
>> WHOA!
>> HERB!
>> OH, GOD.
OH, HERB!
OH!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HERB!
OH, IT'S NOT FUNNY!
>> IT MUST BE THE WATER --
MAKES US ALL MAD AS A BOX OF
FROGS.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> YOU NEED TO MOVE.
>> YOU COULD'VE KILLED THIS MAN!
>> OH, STOP IT, MARY.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
>> THEY JUST SHOWED UP.
>> LET'S GET YOU INSIDE.
>> I'D LIKE TO STAY.
>> NO.
>> VETOED.
>> WHERE DID THEY COME FROM?
>> WHO CARES?
>> DEMONS.
>> PETER.
PETER, PETER, PETER.
>> HOW'S THE FISHING?
>> FINE, I GUESS.
THERE'S RODS UP THERE IN THE
SHED.
>> I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO LEARN
HOW TO FISH.
>> IT'S DULL...LIKE EVERYTHING
ELSE AROUND HERE -- REALLY,
REALLY DULL.
>> SHE'S SPYING ON US.
>> IS SHE?
WHY IS THAT?
>> I DON'T THINK SHE TRUSTS US.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHEN YOU'RE WITH SOMEONE LONG
ENOUGH, YOU BEGIN TO HEAR THEIR
THOUGHTS LIKE YOUR VERY OWN.
>> WE'RE JUST SITTING HERE.
>> TALKING.
>> AND WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
>> OH, EVERYTHING.
>> FOR EXAMPLE?
>> WE COULD SAY THINGS.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> I COULD SAY HOW ATTRACTIVE
YOU ARE.
YOU COULD SAY HOW FAMOUS I AM.
>> HER IMAGINATION IS VAST.
BORING, BORING.
>> I SHOULD GET HER INSIDE.
>> DID I MAKE YOU UNCOMFORTABLE?
>> NO.
SHE DOES.
>> GROSS.
>> IF YOU DON'T PUT YOUR DICK
DOWN, DARLING, YOU'LL RUN INTO
SOMETHING.
IT'S TEMPTING -- I KNOW.
YOU JUST WANT TO CRAWL INSIDE
THAT YOUNG VAGINA AND HIDE FROM
THE WORLD, BUT YOU'LL BE
DISAPPOINTED.
SHE HAS NO EXPERIENCE,
NO ENDURANCE, NO TRAINING,
NO MUSCLE.
YOU'LL HATE IT.
>> MM.
>> YOU WILL.
>> MM-HMM.
>> STOP.
>> NO, COME ON.
>> I SAID STOP IT. STOP IT.
STO--
>> EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
>> DIDN'T SEE YOU.
>> IT HAPPENS.
YOU OKAY?
>> I'M FINE. THANK YOU.
THIS BOTHER YOU?
>> NOPE. HOW'S HERB?
>> WET.
>> HE'S THE ONLY ONE AROUND HERE
WHO EVER ENJOYS HIMSELF.
CAN I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
I'M LEAVING.
>> OH?
>> I'M GETTING OLD.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> ANYWHERE.
>> THEN, BY ALL MEANS...
>> DO ME A FAVOR AND MAKE SURE
ERIC GETS THIS.
>> WE'RE LEAVING TODAY!
I JUST HAVE TO TALK TO LOUIS!
ARE YOU DEAF?!
>> YOU'RE SCARING THE FISH.
>> EVA, WOULD YOU GO DOWN AND
HELP PETER?
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH
THAT ROD OF HIS.
YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
>> OF COURSE NOT.
>> I DIDN'T THINK SO.
>> SEE YOU, LOUIS.
>> BON VOYAGE.
>> YOU TAKE A MAN FROM THE CITY,
PUT HIM IN THE COUNTRY --
SUDDENLY, HE'S NOT SO ATTRACTIVE
ANYMORE.
>> YOU'RE PLAYING WITH FIRE.
>> I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
HELP HIM CATCH SOMETHING!
IT WOULD BE LOVELY IF THE DAY
WEREN'T A COMPLETE WASTE!
LITTLE TWIT.
HERB -- HOW IS HE?
I'VE KNOWN YOU FOR CENTURIES.
WE ARE INCAPABLE OF LYING TO ONE
ANOTHER.
>> DOESN'T MEAN THAT WE STOP
TRYING.
>> I NEED THE TRUTH.
>> IT IS A BURNOUT.
HIS IMMUNE SYSTEM IS CRASHING.
IT FITS THE PATTERN.
IT IS NOT GOOD.
BUT HE -- HE DOESN'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT, NOT UNTIL AFTER
THE WEEKEND.
>> HOW MUCH TIME DO I HAVE?
>> HE HAS A YEAR...
A FEW MONTHS...
MONTH.
NO ONE KNOWS.
>> LESS THAN A --
OH. OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
[ INTRO TO SUPERTRAMP'S
"THE LOGICAL SONG" PLAYS
]
>> ♪WHEN I WAS YOUNG, IT SEEMED
THAT LIFE WAS SO WONDERFUL,
A MIRACLE♪
♪ OH, IT WAS BEAUTIFUL,
MAGICAL♪
♪ AND ALL THE BIRDS IN THE
TREES, WELL, THEY'D BE SINGING
SO HAPPILY♪
♪ OH, JOYFULLY,
OH, PLAYFULLY WATCHING ME♪
>> WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
>> BE PATIENT.
>> NOT MY STRONG SUIT.
>> IF YOU COULD HAVE ANYTHING IN
THE WORLD, WHAT WOULD IT BE?
>> SLEEP.
>> WEIRDO.
>> ALL RIGHT. A RIDE.
>> I'M SERIOUS.
I WOULD HAVE A RIDE TO THE
STATION.
>> SO CALL A CAB.
>> NOT SO SIMPLE.
>> IT ISTHAT SIMPLE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> WHAT ABOUT ME?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I WANT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
>> WHAT'S KEEPING YOU?
>> NO MONEY AND A SICK AUNT.
SEE? SIMPLE.
>> YOU SEEM PRETTY SURE OF
YOURSELF.
I'M NOT.
I GUESS I'M, UH --
I DON'T KNOW -- DISTRACTED.
I LACK DISCIPLINE. I'M LAZY.
I DON'T -- I WORRY.
>> MAYBE OTHERS -- MAYBE
ELIZABETH KNOWS WHAT TO DO WITH
ME BETTER THAN I KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH MYSELF.
I THINK TOO MUCH.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T CALL A CAB --
NOT SO SIMPLE.
>> YOU'RE LONELY.
>> I'M GONNA DO SOMETHING.
STOP ME IF YOU WANT.
>> THANK YOU.
IF YOU FIND YOUR WAY OUT, TAKE
ME WITH YOU.
>> DEAL.
>> PROMISE?
>> I PROMISE.
>> PIECE OF ADVICE --
DON'T HATCH.
OHH!
AAH!
>> DAMN IT.
>> ERIC! DAMN IT!
DON'T FIRE WITHOUT ME!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
ERIC.
>> OH, NO.
OH. OH, FUCK.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> ARE YOU HURT?
>> OHH. IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
IT ATTACKED ME.
>> ATTACKED YOU?
>> F--
>> OH, DAMN IT.
DAMN IT!
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THEY'RE SHOOTING GUNS.
>> I HEARD ONE.
>> OH, MAN.
THEY'RE NOT ALLOWED.
>> WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE?
>> I'M GONNA CALL THE POLICE.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> I WANTED A BABY.
>> YOU HAVE A BABY.
>> I WAS IN -- UM, WENT TO THE
FOREST, AND -- AND -- AND I
HEARD SOMETHING, AND I WAS --
>> JUST GET TO THE POINT.
>> SO, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SAY
THIS, SO -- WELL, OTHER THAN TO
JUST SAY IT.
>> SO SAY IT.
>> WELL, THE -- THE -- THE
BIRD IS DEAD.
>> WHAT BIRD?
>> HE KILLED A BIRD.
>> IT WAS STEPHEN'S BIRD.
>> WHAT?!
>> YES.
WELL, ERIC SHOT STEPHEN'S BIRD.
>> OH, NO!
>> STEPHEN.
>> HI, SWEETHEART.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> HE WAS RIGHT HERE.
CAN YOU TAKE HER?
STEPHEN!
OH. NO.
>> STEPHEN!
I'M SORRY.
>> I THOUGHT WE'D HAVE A NICE,
BIG SALAD.
OF COURSE, THERE ARE OTHER
THINGS.
>> LIKE A CHICKEN.
>> LIKE A HALF-WIT.
>> PICK UP YOUR STONES AND
THROW!
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> SOMETHING I SAID?
>> GO AWAY.
>> WHY?
>> JUST GO.
>> WHAT'S THE CHARGE?
>> LEAVE THE TABLE.
>> IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
>> GO TO YOUR ROOM.
>> IT WAS AN ACCIDENT, AND I
HAVE THE RIGHT TO A FAIR TRIAL.
HERB -- JUDGE.
>> ONLY IF I CAN WEAR THE WIG.
>> DEAL.
>> HERB, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> THIS IS A DEMOCRACY -- WEIRD
THINGS HAPPEN.
>> JOHAN, COUNCIL FOR THE
DEFENSE.
>> ERIC, STOP THIS!
>> PLEASE RISE.
COURT IS NOW IN SESSION!
>> CHIEF JUSTICE ABE PRESIDING.
WE WILL START WITH OPENING
STATEMENTS.
>> YOU'RE ALL INSANE.
>> SUCCINCT.
>> THE DEFENDANT IS CHARGED WITH
UNLAWFUL DISCHARGE OF A WEAPON
AND FIRST-DEGREE MURDER OF OUR
NATIONAL BIRD, THE SYMBOL OF
FREEDOM AND JUSTICE.
THIS CARRIES A FEDERAL OFFENSE
PUNISHABLE BY 2,000 YEARS OF
BANISHMENT  AND
SURRENDER OF ALL COURTLY RICHES
TO THE MOTHERLAND...
SIEG HEIL!
>> LOUIS, STOP THIS!
>> ...INCLUDING ALL SERFDOMS...
>> NOT MY FARM.
>> ...FLOCKS, HAREMS...
>> MOTION TO DISMISS!
>> OVERRULED.
>> THERE IS REASONABLE DOUBT
THAT MY CLIENT ACTED IN
SELF-DEFENSE!
>> STRIKE THAT FROM THE RECORD.
>> OBJECTION!
>> HERB, PLEASE, STOP THIS!
>> WE'RE IN COURT!
>> STOP!
>> HERB.
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH NOW.
>> SO WHAT?
I'M GUILTY?
AND IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
>> ERIC, LET'S GO OUTSIDE.
>> SO I'M BANISHED?
>> YES, YOU LITTLE SHIT!
NOW GET OUT!
>> WAIT.
>> GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE, NOW!
>> I HAVEN'T RULED YET.
AAH!
>> HERB!
>> OH!
>> HERB.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> HERB! HERB!
>> OH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
>> A SEIZURE.
>> HERB?
>> HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> HERB.
>> GET HER TO A CHAIR.
>> JUDGE?
>> BAILIFF.
>> GO EASY.
>> I'M TRYING.
>> HE'S YOUR SON.
TRY HARDER.
NO MORE BEATING AROUND THE BUSH.
LOUIS TOLD ME.
>> HE TOLD YOU NOTHING.
>> HE TOLD ME EVERYTHING.
>> THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
NO ONE CAN KNOW EVERYTHING.
>> OHH, WHAT IS IT WITH YOU?
>> I BEAT BUSHES.
>> SHADES?
>> OPEN.
I LIKE TO WATCH STARS --
SIMPLE...AND BEAUTIFUL...
JUST LIKE YOU.
>> GO TO SLEEP.
>> YOU'RE A STAR.
>> I USED TO BE.
>> ONCE A STAR, ALWAYS A STAR.
>> SAVE YOUR SERMONS.
GET SOME REST.
>> REPEAT AFTER ME -- "I LOVE
YOU, AND I'M WITH YOU."
"I LOVE YOU, AND I'M WITH YOU."
>> I...
I LOVE YOU, AND I'M WITH YOU.
>> THAT'S ALL I EVER WANT TO
HEAR.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> I CAN'T SLEEP WITH YOU DOING
THAT.
>> SORRY.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> GOOD NIGHT.
>> YOU SHOULDN'T BE IN HERE.
I'M GOING FOR A SWIM.
I BROUGHT YOU A TOWEL.
>> IT'S TOO LATE.
>> OH, YOU'LL LOVE IT.
IT'S LIKE FLOATING IN SPACE.
WE'LL LEAVE TOMORROW.
I LOOK...
YOU REALLY WOULD LOVE IT.
OH, MY GOD.
STEPHEN!
OPEN THE DOOR!
GET YOUR CAMERA.
THERE -- THE SCRAPING.
>> IT'S CALLED THE EGG TOOTH.
>> THE WHAT?
>> IT'S A -- WELL, IT'S A TOOTH
GROWN JUST FOR BREAKING THE
SHELL.
>> THIS THING IS ON, RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH. YUP, YUP.
IT'S BLINKING.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS ALL LOST.
>> DAD CAN BE USEFUL SOMETIMES.
>> WELL...IT'S GONNA BE A WHILE
BEFORE HE BREAKS THROUGH.
>> OR HER.
OR HER, YEAH.
>> GET OUT HERE!
>> YOU WANT THIS ONE...
OR THIS ONE?
>> VIRUS.
GOD!
>> NO FIRING GUNS ON THE
PROPERTY, YOU ASSHOLE!
>> WOW.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> THAT WAS A SHOT.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO?!
>> WHAT?
>> YOU SHOT STEPHEN!
>> WELL, NO. NO, I DIDN'T.
>> YOU FUCKING SHOT MY HUSBAND!
>> NO, I DIDN'T.
>> HE FINALLY DOES SOMETHING
WORTHWHILE, AND YOU SHOOT HIM?
>> IS ANYONE HURT?
>> WELL, DEFINE "HURT."
>> ERIC?
ERIC!
>> MARY.
>> OH, MY GOD! OH, GOD!
>> OKAY, ON THE COUNT OF 3.
1...
3!
>> OH, NO.
LET'S JUST DRAG HIM.
>> THERE'S A 2.
MOM, YOU'RE POINTING THE GUN AT
MY HEAD.&->> OH, I'M SO SORRY.
>> ELIZABETH, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> HELP ME.
WE NEED TO GET INSIDE.
>> OH.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HE'S BLEEDING.
>> HE'LL BE OKAY.
HELP STEPHEN, PLEASE.
>> STEPHEN?
>> YES. GO, GO.
>> OKAY.
>> OHH!
>> DAD!
>> WELL, HIS BODY WASN'T
STRAIGHT.
COME ON.
>> OH, FOR CHRIST'S SAKE!
>> OH!
>> PUSH! ALEX!
>> I'M TRYING.
>> MARY.
>> OH, CAREFUL.
>> OHH!
>> OH, IT LOOKS SO PAINFUL.
>> HE'S REALLY GONE.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> THERE YOU ARE.
>> YOU HEAR HIM BREATHING.
>> OH.
>> HE'S REALLY GONE.
>> ANYONE WANT ANY TEA?
>> YEAH. THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
AND LOTS OF ICE.
>> HEY! STOP IT!
>> HE HAS TO WAKE UP.
>> STOP IT.
>> HE HAS -- NO, HE HAS --
HAS TO WAKE UP.
>> IDIOT.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> JOHAN!
WHAT DID YOU USE?
>> THAT'S A BULL'S LOAD.
6 cc OF ROMPUN -- SHOULD BE 4,
SO I USE THAT NEXT TIME.
>> DO YOU HAVE, UH, ALCOHOL OR
PEROXIDE?
>> UH, UH, IN THE BACK BATHROOM.
>> KEEP HIS HEAD ELEVATED.
>> OKAY. SORRY.
>> OH, MY GOD!
ALEX, THE EGG!
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> IT'S BREAKING!
OH, MY HEAVENS.
I CAN SEE SOMETHING.
OH, IT'S -- IT'S -- OH, MY!
AN EYE!
I CAN -- I CAN SEE
AN EYELID.
WELL, IT'S AS UGLY AS A MUD
FENCE.
OH, ALEX, YOU HAVE TO SEE THIS.
IT IS AMAZING!
HOW DO I KNOW THIS IS ON?
>> THE LIGHT BLINKS.
>> OH, YOU LOOK EXHAUSTED.
MAYBE YOU'D LIKE A LITTLE WATER?
>> NO WATER.
>> NO WATER?
>> NO.
>> NO WATER.
THERE -- THERE -- THERE'S
SOMETHING IN THE FRIDGE.
IT'S -- IT'S -- IT'S MARKED.
>> HE GOT YOU GOOD.
YOU'RE GONNA WAKE UP A RACCOON.
HER PARENTS CALLED.
SHE NEVER WENT HOME.
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
THEY'RE CALLING THE POLICE.
OW!
>> YOU COULD HAVE KILLED
SOMEONE.
>> IT WAS SALT.
>> OW!
>> NOT FUNNY.
>> IT WAS ROCK SALT.
>> STOP IT.
>> "SO FULL OF ARTLESS
JEALOUSY."
>> STOP IT! STOP IT! STOP IT!
>> ERIC!
>> YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
>> CALM DOWN.
IT'S OKAY.
HE'S LEAVING TOMORROW.
I'M TAKING HIM AWAY, AND THEN
SHE'LL COME BACK, TAIL BETWEEN
LEGS -- YOU'LL SEE.
>> YOU'LL BOTH...LAUGH ABOUT IT
WITH YOUR GRANDCHILDREN.
>> I'D, UH, LIKE TO BORROW YOUR
TRUCK.
>> THE KEYS ARE IN IT.
JUST PRETEND YOU'RE WATER --
DOWNHILL TO TOWN.
STATION'S ON THE RIGHT.
THERE'S A TRAIN EVERY HOUR ON
THE HALF-HOUR.
LEAVE KEYS UNDER THE MAT.
&-
>> TODAY, THUS, REPRESENTS A
MOMENT OF HOPE.
BUT I BELIEVE THERE'S SOMETHING
DEEPER, SOMETHING THAT INVOLVES
BERLIN'S WHOLE LOOK AND FEEL
AND WAY OF LIFE -- NOT MERE
SENTIMENT -- SOMETHING,
INSTEAD, THAT HAS SEEN THE
DIFFICULTIES OF LIFE IN BERLIN,
BUT CHOSE TO ACCEPT THEM, THAT
REFUSES TO RELEASE HUMAN
ENERGIES OR ASPIRATIONS,
SOMETHING THAT SPEAKS WITH A
POWERFUL VOICE OF AFFIRMATION,
THAT SAYS "YES" TO THIS CITY,
"YES" TO THE FUTURE, "YES" TO
FREEDOM.
IN A WORD, I WOULD SUBMIT THAT
WHAT KEEPS YOU IN BERLIN IS
LOVE...
...LOVE BOTH PROFOUND AND
ABIDING.
AS I LOOKED OUT A MOMENT AGO
FROM THE REICHSTAG, THAT
EMBODIMENT OF GERMAN UNITY,
I NOTICED WORDS CRUDELY
SPRAY-PAINTED UPON THE WALL --
QUOTE -- "THIS WALL WILL FALL.
BELIEFS BECOME REALITY."
>> OOH! THAT WIND.
WATCH YOUR STEP -- IT'S
SLIPPERY.
>> THERE YOU ARE!
HELLO, PETER.
>> HOW WAS THE DRIVE?
>> IT WAS FINE. THANKS.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> HOPE YOU'RE NOT TOO HUNGRY.
WE'RE RUNNING NEAR EMPTY.
>> SHE MAKES THE BEST SOUP.
>> IT'S ALMOST DONE.
>> WHEN DOES ERIC GET IN?
>> HE'S BEEN HERE A FEW DAYS.
>> AHH, THAT WAS THE LONGEST
DRIVE I'VE EVER HAD IN MY ENTIRE
LIFE.
LAST TIME I'M DOING THAT WITH
THOSE TWO.
I HAD TO WAIT IN THE CAR JUST
NOW TO REMEMBER WHAT SILENCE
FELT LIKE.
"MAN DELIGHTS NOT ME."
>> "NOR WOMAN NEITHER."
>> NOR WOMAN. YES, YES.
MM. ANYWAY...
WHERE ARE THEY?
>> UM, THEY'RE IN THE KITCHEN, I
THINK.
>> OH. HERB IN HIS ROOM?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I'LL MAKE MY ROUNDS.
>> HE'S A MIRACLE, ISN'T HE?
>> WHO ISN'T?
>> AND I OPEN THE FLYER FROM THE
PERFORMANCE ART NEXT WAVE
WHATEVER, AND THERE WAS YOU --
FULL PAGE.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BRAVO.
>> APPARENTLY, IT'S THE TALK
OF THE TOWN, LITERALLY.
THE NEW YORKER
JUST
PUBLISHED A PIECE --
"THE HOPE OF MEDIA VILLAGE."
VERY COOL.
THEY CALLED ME A VETERAN
ACTRESS, WHICH MEANS I'M --
I DON'T KNOW.
>> FOOD FOR WORMS.
>> OH, YOU NEVER PASS UP AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR AN ENTRANCE, DO
YOU?
>> MISSED A CALLING, I'M SURE.
>> AMONG OTHER THINGS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HELLO, STEPHEN.
>> GOOD EVENING.
>> HI, DADDY.
>> HI, SWEETHEART.
HEY, PETER.
>> PETER, ABE. ABE, PETER.
>> FOUND HIM IN THE CLOSET.
>> HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> HE'S MINE.
>> HI, DOCTOR.
>> CAPTAIN.
>> A DOZEN TIMES, HE'S TRIED TO
ESCAPE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD LET HIM.
>> JUST CLOSE THE CAGE.
>> I DIDN'T OPEN IT.
>> SURE, YOU DIDN'T.
HE ALMOST FLEW OUT THE BACK
DOOR, WHICH YOU ALSO LEFT OPEN.
>> I CAN'T EVEN GET OUT OF THIS
DAMN CHAIR -- HOW CAN I OPEN A
CAGE?
>> HE'S NOT READY YET.
>> SO YOU SAY, BUT LOOK AT THE
KID -- HE WANTS OUT.
>> SOON.
>> WELL, NOW.
>> I'M SORRY.
EXCUSE ME.
>> HE SAID HE HAD TO SEE THE
LAKE.
HE'S HAD A HORRIBLE TIME.
HE NEEDED TO COME BACK.
>> HERB, DO WE HAVE TO?
ABE IS SO MUCH HAPPIER EATING IN
HIS CAGE.
>> WELL, I INSIST.
>> WELL, OF COURSE YOU DO.
>> MMM.
>> IS PETER OKAY?
>> EVERYTHING'S FINE.
>> I'LL LEAVE HIM A BOWL IN THE
KITCHEN.
>> I LIKE YOUR UNIFORM.
IT'S MI-- IT'S MISSING A FEW
PATCHES.
>> DID YOU SEE THE NEW TRUCK OUT
THERE?
SO PROUD OF MY BOY.
>> THANKS, POP.
>> DON'T CALL ME THAT.
>> YES, DAD.
>> I'M NOT YOUR DAD.
>> NOTHING CHANGES.
>> WILL YOU BE TAKING ABE TO
LIVE WITH YOU?
>> YEAH, THE RESERVATION HAS AN
EDUCATION CENTER, SO I'LL TAKE
HIM THERE UNTIL HE'S READY TO BE
RELEASED.
>> WHEN YOU DON'T NEED HIM
ANYMORE.
>> IS THAT CORIANDER?
>> CUMIN.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
IT'S LOVELY.
>> NOT ENOUGH SALT.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> PARSLEY.
>> OH, I LOVE PARSLEY.
>> CAN YOU PASS ME SOME BREAD,
PLEASE?
OH, THANK YOU.
>> YOU NEED TO SEND ME THE
RECIPE.
>> I WILL.
>> I SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
IT'S SO COLD, ISN'T IT?
MY FACE IS LIKE AN ICICLE.
>> COME INSIDE.
>> NO, THANK YOU.
R-REALLY, I'M FINE.
>> PLEASE.
YOU LOOK FREEZING.
>> JUST FOR A MINUTE...
AND THEN I HAVE TO GO.
ISN'T IT FUNNY?
THEY ALL COME BACK WHEN IT'S
TIME TO GO.
EVEN PETER -- HE'S HERE.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER FOR
HIM.
HE JUST DISAPPEARED.
I COULDN'T FIND HIM.
I COULDN'T FIND ANYONE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
MY FAMILY LEFT, TOO.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
>> YES.
>> SOMEONE'S BUYING UP THE WHOLE
LAKE.
THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
WINNER TAKES ALL.
I STILL REMEMBER THAT NIGHT.
"THE MOST BARBAROUS AGES..."
IT'S NOT TRUE, IS IT?
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE FAMOUS?
>> I'M NOT.
>> YOU ARE...
AND IT MAKES ME HAPPY.
THAT BIRD -- INCREDIBLE, ISN'T
SHE?
SO BEAUTIFUL.
I WISH I COULD HOLD HER.
IT WAS A DISASTER.
I CAN'T STAY.
I JUST...
WANTED TO TELL YOU...
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
AND THAT I MISS YOU.
>> EVA?!
EVA!
>> FOR THE CITY, IT'S A VERY
NICE PLACE -- LARGE DINING ROOM,
STUDY, DECENT KITCHEN, PLENTY OF
ROOM FOR THREE OR FOUR
COMFORTABLY.
IT'LL BE GOOD FOR HERB.
>> MOMMY, I HAVE TO TINKLE.
>> WHY DOESN'T DADDY TAKE YOU?
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY,
TINKLE TOES?
HOW MUCH DO I LOVE YOU?
>> PAST THE STARS.
>> AWW!
>> AWW.
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S WONDERFUL
IT WORKED OUT -- SUCH A RELIEF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW...HARD IT'S
BEEN SORTING EVERYTHING --
ALL THE PAPERWORK.
WE'VE KILLED A FOREST.
THE NEW OWNERS SEEM LIKE NICE
PEOPLE.
YOU'LL GET ALONG JUST FINE.
DEVELOPERS -- APPARENTLY,
THERE'S A BOOM COMING.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, THEN, THERE'S HOPE.
>> I'LL TAKE THE BOWLS.
>> I'M AFRAID THERE'S -- THERE'S
NOT MUCH IN THE WAY OF DESSERT.
>> PAST THE STARS.
>> I HAVE KEPT OUT ENOUGH --
ENOUGH TEA AND COFFEE TO GET US
THROUGH TO SUNDAY.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> JUST A HUNTER.
I'LL TELL THEM TO SHOO.
>> I'LL BE BACK.
EXCUSE ME.
>> SOMETHING I SAID?
WE SHOULD HAVE EATEN OUTSIDE.
>> I LOVE YOU...
AND I'M WITH YOU.
>> I'M SUPPOSED TO SAY THAT TO
YOU.
I THINK I'LL...GO SEE WHAT'S
GOING ON.
ERIC.
>> NO. NO!
>> JOHAN!
> NO! NO!
NO! NO!
>> "HE CLASPS THE CRAG
WITH CROOKED HANDS..."
>> NO!
>> "...CLOSE TO THE SUN
IN LONELY LANDS..."
>> "...RING'D WITH
THE AZURE WORLD, HE STANDS.
THE WRINKLED SEA
BENEATH HIM CRAWLS;
HE WATCHES..."
>> NO!
>> "...FROM
HIS MOUNTAIN WALLS..."
>> "...AND LIKE A THUNDERBOLT
HE FALLS."
LET'S OPEN THE WINDOW...
AND GET SOME BREEZE THROUGH
HERE.
IT'S COOL.