[buzzing]
NARRATOR: She lied about
the baby to save
the senator's career.
It didn't.
Now, decades later, in the
midst of a comeback, he's
poised to be the next president
of the United
States, and she's
lost everything.
I asked her if she would
tell her son.
She just looked at me.
[ringing]
-Hello?
Who is this?
[honking]
-15 minutes I've been waiting.
-The place was a madhouse.
It took longer than I thought.
-Well, then call or text.
You just left me standing on
the street like an idiot.
Now, we're gonna have
to make this quick.
We can't leave her
any options.
-She does have a say
in this, you know.
-No, she doesn't.
She obviously can't care
for herself anymore.
Some stranger?
-Elliot, that's how
it's done, OK?
You can't just leave her
alone out in the
middle of bumfuck Egypt.
Just let me do the talking,
all right?
-Do I have a choice?
[classical musical playing]
-Hello?
Mom?
[knock]
-Mom?
-What are you doing here?
-Nice to see you too.
-That bad, huh?
-You lost a lot of weight.
-I know.
It's my coffee and
cancer diet.
I'm gonna write a book.
-We thought you were
in remission.
-Someone called and told me that
you checked yourself out
of the hospital last night.
-Yeah.
-What happened?
-Oh, Laura, give it
a rest, will you?
-No, I'm not gonna
give it a rest.
What's going on?
-OK, relax.
-Would one of you go make
me a cup of tea?
-Sure.
-You want milk?
-Just honey, thanks.
-Look, she knows just
how to piss me off.
-Hello.
Sorry, didn't mean
to startle you.
I'm Ted Kingsley.
I called you last night.
-Laura.
-And you must be Elliot?
It's nice to meet you.
Your mom has told me a
lot about you both.
-Who are you again?
-I'm the groundskeeper.
-What happened to Hector?
-He left.
I think he and your mom
had a disagreement.
-OK, well, do you have a number
we can reach you at?
I'm sure we'll have some
questions for you.
-I, um, I live here.
-You live here?
-I have a room down the hall.
I've been here about
six months.
-Six months?
-I was going to cook dinner.
-What in the hell's
going on here?
-What are you talking about?
-You were in a hospital, you
look like shit and you live
with some strange guy--
-You met Ted.
He's a dear.
-Why does he live here?
-Because he's probably
trying to take
advantage of you for starters.
-Don't be ridiculous.
-Well, what happened
to Hector?
-We had a parting of the ways.
-Why does the groundskeeper
have to move in?
-Oh, Laura, I don't have it
in me to fight with you.
Not now, OK?
-Ma, I just want to know
what's going on
here, that's all.
-What's going on here is that
you and your brother haven't
even seen me in a year
and a half so my
life is a little different.
That's my business.
-So are you sleeping with
this Ted character?
-I wish.
-Your brother was telling
me that your
father hated this place.
I can't imagine that.
-My father didn't
hate this place.
He hated my mother.
-Well, that must have made
for some hilarious dinner
conversation.
-This is great.
-Ted cooks all organic.
-Well, it's from your
greenhouses.
-You cook every night?
-Not every night but most.
-Why?
-Well, I cook for myself
every night anyways.
Plus, it's no fun cooking
for just you, you know?
-So you're the groundskeeper
and the cook?
-He's a better cook than
groundskeeper.
Ted's also a very
talented writer.
-Have you published anything?
-I had a novel out last year.
-I sent it to you for
your birthday.
-The one about the woman who
comes home from the war?
TED (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
-I read that.
-You're the one.
-No, I loved it.
I thought she should
have murdered the
grandmother in the end.
-She did in a previous draft.
-That book was kind
of a big deal.
I remember seeing it on
some bestseller list.
ELLIOT (OFFSCREEN): So you're
working on your next one?
-Yeah, I figured a change of
scenery would give me a fresh
perspective.
-Ted, do you administer
meds to my mother?
-Excuse me?
-Laura.
-I'm not a home health
attendant, if that's what
you're asking.
LAURA (OFFSCREEN): What is
your role here then?
-There is nothing inappropriate
about Ted's
presence here.
Now that's enough.
-Ted, would you mind letting
my family have a private
discussion?
-I'll be in the kitchen.
-Why don't you just jump in
his lap, for Christ sake.
(MOCKINGLY) I think that book
was quite a big deal.
-Stop it.
Now, what is it that you want?
LILLY (OFFSCREEN): Everything
is taken care of.
The home health agency comes
on Monday, and they'll make
sure I get everything I need.
-Ma, can you at least
think about it?
-I'm sorry, but I don't
think any of us
want to live together.
-You're not mixing your meds
with alcohol, I hope.
-If you remember, I quit
drinking two years ago.
-Well, sometimes that stuff
is hard to kick.
-Not when you're dying.
-Look, I don't want to fight.
I just want you to know
that you're welcome to
come live with me.
-Tempting.
I do appreciate the
offer though.
Thank you.
[groans]
-What is it?
-I'm fine.
I'm just a little tired.
I think I'll turn in.
-Do you need some help?
-I wouldn't mind.
-What?
-Weren't you just in college?
-I wish I was still
in college.
-Growing us doesn't
agree with you?
-That's something we don't
have a choice over.
-You have more choices
than you think.
Don't forget that.
-Elliot, she's playing
you like a fiddle.
I told you we can't give
her any option.
-I don't think we can
take her anywhere.
I mean look at her.
She--
-So why did you call my kids?
-You don't want them here?
-No, I don't want them
to see me like this.
That's why I didn't call them.
-Well, what about all those
talks about second chances?
This is an opportunity.
-I will not be manipulated.
-Lilly, you know I think the
world of you, but I'm afraid
to leave the house in case
something happens to you.
This is not my job.
You need help here.
-So you're leaving?
-I think it's best.
I mean now that your
kids are here--
-Don't leave me alone
with them.
-Lilly, they don't
want me here.
-I want you here.
Just until they leave.
Can you promise me that?
-What on earth are you doing?
-Smoking pot.
It's amazing.
-Honestly, I don't even
know where to begin.
-It's not that deep.
-No, of course not.
-Ted, could I have a
word with my kids?
-No problem.
LAURA (OFFSCREEN):
This is crazy.
You know that, right?
-You know what's crazy, Laura?
LAURA (OFFSCREEN):
What's that?
-That we don't have a
relationship, you
and I. Any of us.
And that's my fault, and
I apologize for that.
I brought a lot of bullshit into
this house, but the fact
remains, I'm lonely.
So what if Ted lives here.
He's a nice guy.
And you should be happy
someone's cooking your mother
dinner every night.
-Then why don't you
come with me?
With Jeff gone, there's
more room.
-Oh honey, you still
don't get it.
This is the end of the road.
-What does that mean?
-I'm gonna make some tea.
-Chamomile would be lovely.
-Sure.
-She's not doing well.
-So I'm gathering.
-I'm sorry.
-I just--
how did it get to this?
-Are you scared?
-I was.
-Not anymore?
-I remember when
you were a kid.
We signed you up for
swimming lessons.
Then when we got there, you
saw that some of the other
kids could swim better
than you.
That was it.
You were done.
If you couldn't win, you
didn't want to play.
-Any other fun little childhood
stories you want to
-That's my fear for you, that
you never try anything out of
your comfort zone.
-I do plenty outside
of my comfort zone.
-Good, but next time an
opportunity comes up, throw
yourself into it.
See what happens, OK?
-Sure, but can I tell
you something?
I remember you forcing me to
take swimming lessons so I
wouldn't be in your way.
That's how I remember it.
-That's not true.
-No?
Does this ring a bell?
"You're taking swimming lessons
so I can get you out
of my hair for an afternoon."
That's what you said.
-That's pretty shitty.
I'm sorry.
-You didn't give a shit about
anything but your fucking
flowers, and now you want to act
like mother of the year?
I don't buy it.
-Sometimes it takes something
big to make you see how you
screwed things up.
I can't change that,
but I am sorry.
-Hello, Dr. Klein,
this is Laura
Garcia, Lilly's daughter.
I've been sort of broadsided by
my mother's condition, and
I was hoping to get a clearer
picture of what's going on.
I know It's not business hours,
but if you get this
message, I would greatly
appreciate a call back.
-Is she asleep?
-Yeah.
-This is definitely in the
running to be one of the
longest days ever.
-Elliot, what am I gonna do?
-Let's go for a swim.
-Hello.
-Hey.
Listen, um, I wanted to
apologize to you for how I
acted earlier.
-Thank you.
I appreciate that.
If this is weird, I can--
I'm just--
I'm really tired.
I was gonna go to
sleep anyway.
Good night, guys.
-You have a pretty
sweet deal here.
-I do.
It's been amazing living
in this house.
-I have no doubt.
What are you gonna do when--
-I'll figure something out.
How are you doing
with all this?
-Good as I can, I guess.
TED (OFFSCREEN): Your mom
is a good person.
-Yeah, well, she wasn't always
a pot-smoking cancer victim.
-She told me she was
a bad mother.
How bad?
-Just stupid stuff, you know?
I used to do this every
night growing up.
-I thought you grew
up in Manhattan.
-I moved to Manhattan
when I was 17.
My dad lived there.
Mom always loved it here.
-I can see why.
-Is there any booze
in the house?
-Why did your dad hate
your mother?
-Um, he wanted to bang every
woman he could get his hands
on, and when my mom did,
she was a whore.
-Wow.
-She didn't get mad.
She got even.
-Do you like what you
do in New York?
-No.
My sister and I run a chain
of laundromats.
It's the family business.
-I know.
Lilly told me.
-She did?
-She told me all
about you guys.
-Oh yeah?
Like what?
-Like you have had a series
of failed relationships.
-She said that?
-It isn't true?
-I think I've had great
relationships.
-You're very handsome.
-Thanks.
-I mean it.
-What are you doing?
-Sorry.
Uh, it's been a while.
-No, it's cool.
It's just--
I should probably
get some sleep.
Good night.
-Night.
[sighs]
-I think this may have been
a poor choice on my part.
-Wow, I can't believe you
just said that out loud.
-No, I don't mean that.
I just mean with my mom in
the other room dying.
It just seems like an iffy
decision at best.
-Honestly, I think she wanted
this to happen.
-Oh man.
-You OK?
-Yeah.
-Your mom told me about
Senator Adams.
-I don't want to talk
about that.
-Did you know him?
-I don't know anything
about it.
-I didn't mean to pry.
-Who's the guy in the photo?
-That's Eric.
-OK.
-He's not here.
-But that leads me to that
lovely pine cone art piece
over there.
Thoughts?
Excuses?
-Your mom made that.
-You lie.
-Nope.
Open it.
She was pissed.
-She loves her orchids.
-You travel with your own bow?
-No, I found it in
your garage.
I think it's your dad's.
A few months ago, I couldn't
even hit the target.
Come on.
Give it a try.
OK, right there.
Here you go.
This is an arrow.
OK.
So you straighten your arm.
Make sure your feet are apart.
Then you pull this back.
Is this how they teach archery
where you're from?
-Pay attention.
OK.
Draw it back.
Yeah, a little further.
OK, now focus on the bullseye.
And let it go.
-Well, that was fun.
-Ma?
Ma?
-[screams]
Is something wrong?
-No, nothing's wrong.
-What the fuck is
wrong with you?
-Hey.
-Morning.
-What are you doing?
-I'm making my famous
cranberry pancakes.
-Sounds good.
Can I help?
-No.
Sit back.
Be prepared to get
your mind blown.
-I can do that.
-Should we have eggs too?
-Yeah, I don't care.
-In that case, there's fresh
parsley in the greenhouse.
I'll be right back.
-Well, it sure looks like
you're on vacation.
-What does that mean?
-You sleep with him?
-Why would you ask that?
-You did.
That is so fucked up.
I can't even look at you.
-At least you're not judging.
-Oh no, I am judging.
-Yeah, what's new.
-Nothing, apparently.
Look, what is this need
for you to have
a man at all times?
It's sad.
-Elliot, I wish I knew
you could cook.
I would have put you to
work a long time ago.
-I've cooked for you more
than a few times.
-You have?
Well, I'm sure it was amazing.
-I'll be happy to make
dinner if you want.
-That would be lovely.
I was thinking that maybe
we could go on a
little outing today.
-Obviously.
I'm the one suggesting it.
-What did you have in mind?
-Oh, just sit on the ground,
get a little fresh air.
Ted, I hope you can join us.
TED (OFFSCREEN): That
sounds like fun.
Thank you.
Terrific.
-That's it, honey, hit
every bump you can.
-I'm not doing it on purpose.
You know that.
-I know.
It just feels like it.
Jesus Christ.
-There you go.
Now, that's more like the
mother I grew up with.
-Ow.
I never get sick of this.
-Ma.
-What?
I'm already dying.
-Nice.
-Honestly, it helps
with the pain.
-No, thank you.
Have you ever smoked
pot before?
-She was baked for about
seven years.
-Yeah, and then I grew up.
-Growing up ain't all it's
cracked up to be.
-Apparently.
[muttering]
-[chuckles]
-Whoa.
What was in that shit?
I'm ready to grow into a ball.
-Did you buy this house
or build it?
-Oh, Jesus.
-God.
-What?
-We bought this property with
another house on it.
It was somewhat of a historical
landmark in town,
and we had it torn down.
It was before they had city
ordinances protecting landmarks.
-Oh my god.
-I know.
I was so pompous.
I grew up with nothing,
and I valued nothing.
And my husband, he just wanted
to spend money to show what a
success he was.
That's just one of those
things that if I
could just do over.
Laura, do you still sing?
-No, no, not really.
TED (OFFSCREEN): You sing?
-Used to.
ELLIOT (OFFSCREEN):
She was good.
Remember that play in college?
-That was a highlight for me.
-Really?
-Of course.
-You never said anything.
-I didn't?
I should have.
Hey, could you boys
do me a favor.
Could you go find
me some rocks?
-Excuse me?
-I'm making something,
and I need some small
rocks, pretty ones.
-How big is small?
-No bigger than my nail.
And I need three to nine.
-Three to nine?
Why not nine?
-I'm not quite sure what
I'm doing with them.
I'm stoned.
-All right.
-Come up here.
So what happened?
-Are you OK?
-What do you mean?
-Ever since breakfast,
you've been on edge.
-My sister knows we
slept together.
-So?
-So she thought it was
in poor taste.
-Fuck her.
Do you think it was
in poor taste?
-Kind of.
-Really?
-Ted, you honestly don't think
it was kind of low?
-No, I don't.
And I wasn't joking
last night.
I think your mom would
applaud this.
-There's no this.
There's last night.
-And this morning.
But we don't have
to do it again.
See?
Problem solved.
What are we looking for?
-Pine cones?
-You have no idea
what happened?
So how can you just assume
I'm to blame?
-I never said that.
-Then what did you say?
-We all have a part in
everything that happens to us.
Own that, and then call Jeffrey
up and apologize for
what you brought to the table.
That'd really freak him out.
-Yeah, I bet it would
-There's no shame in saying
that you were wrong.
-Why am I wrong?
What about him?
-You're both wrong.
Why are you so hung
up on being right.
-Yeah, I just--
I feel like I can't
talk to you.
I feel like this is the first
time we've ever spoken.
-But we're not talking.
You're just spouting out all of
this New Age mumbo jumbo.
-Well, I've become a little
clearer on a few
things these days.
-No, you've replaced booze with
pot, and now you think
you're Hare Krishna.
-Laura, you have what
I never had.
Don't be too quick
to let that go.
If I had known it would have all
come down to this, I would
have had the whole
place paved.
-No, you wouldn't have.
-That's what you think.
-Hey.
-What are these?
-Pine cones.
-I asked for rocks.
I thought you said pine cones.
-What am I supposed
to do with these?
Make sure you handle the
funeral arrangements.
Stupid.
ELLIOT (OFFSCREEN): So what do
you want for the funeral?
-Nothing, really.
I want to be cremated, and then
maybe scatter my ashes in
the back garden.
I don't think a big service
is necessary.
I doubt anybody would
come anyway.
-Don't say that.
-It's true.
Ted's my only friend, and
he doesn't even know it.
-No, he likes you.
-It doesn't matter.
You can't sweat the
small stuff.
Words to live by.
-The good news is, you're
not dead yet.
-I'm gonna get some produce
from the greenhouse.
-No, but could you
do me a favor?
Get me an orchid from the
small greenhouse.
I want to put it by my bed.
-Sure.
Any color in particular?
-Something beautiful.
-Elliot, you're cooking.
Why don't you go pick out
what produce you want.
Your brother seems
a little lost.
-Yeah, we're all
-Well, that's your fault.
-This has been a crazy couple
days, you know?
-Yeah?
-And I don't think last
night was a bad thing.
-OK.
-I just a message from
Ma's doctor.
-Yeah?
-It's really bad.
I think that we need to get her
back to New York and see
if anything can be done.
-Where have you been
the last few days?
We can't make her do it.
-Can we at least agree to try?
-Sure.
Good.
-Elliot, you've outdone
yourself.
-Uh-huh.
-For real.
LILLY (OFFSCREEN): Your dad
could cook, you know.
He had all of these recipes
from Puerto Rico.
It's a shame he stopped.
-Well, Elliot sure didn't
get it from you.
-No, he didn't.
-I want to get back
to this afternoon.
I want to hear you sing.
-I don't think so.
-Honey, that would
be wonderful.
-Mom, I don't want to.
-I may never get the
chance again.
-Oh, come on.
-OK.
Let me see.
(SINGING) Like a flower in the
sun, like a peaceful Saturday.
Like a moon shining bright, you
can take my breath away.
I'll sing your love found within
your arms, wanting so
much to know who you are.
So show me and tell me.
Open up your soul.
I'll make it easy to
give it all my
love, your entire heart.
All I am is all that you are.
[clapping]
-Mom?
What's wrong?
-That made my night.
Thank you.
You should sing.
That's all I'm going to say.
-I second that.
-Yeah, I'll get cracking on that
as soon as I get back to
the city.
-That is a very non-committal
response.
-I think that's what they
call a brush off.
-I think you're right.
-You'll take care of this
place, won't you?
-What do you mean?
-This is yours.
-What about Laura?
-She'll get the beach house.
She loves it there.
This place was always
more you.
-Do you play an instrument?
-Piano, some.
-I took piano lessons
for three years.
I sucked.
-I'm sure you weren't
that bad.
-I'm not being self-deprecating.
God never intended for
me to be a pianist.
-And what did God intend
for you then?
-I should have been a drummer.
My mom wouldn't let me.
-Well, you can still
play drums.
You're not even 30 years old.
Just take lessons.
-You get back to singing, and
I'll take drum lessons.
How's that?
-Ted, chances are, you and I
are never going to see each
other again, so I wouldn't
wait on me for anything.
-OK, this is amazing.
-It is.
-So Mom, Elliot and I were
talking, and maybe you can
come home with me and see
some specialists.
One last ditch effort,
you know?
-I thought we already
talked about this.
-I just want to make sure we
look into every possibility.
-And you think I haven't?
-I'm just saying that--
-What do you know?
You haven't been here.
I've done chemo, yoga, Tai Chi
and every other useless thing
that's out there.
Don't you dare insinuate that
I haven't looked into every
way out of this.
-I'm just worried about
being there for you.
We have a business to run.
We should be home.
-Then go.
-Elliot, do you want
to help out here?
-Ma, Laura wants you to
do what she wants,
not what you want.
So think about that.
How's that?
-What was that all about?
-Hey.
-I don't know why you would
say something like that.
-Maybe the same reason
you would--
-All I asked for was support.
Is it that hard?
-She doesn't want to go.
Do you want to drag your home?
I mean what is it
that you want?
-Elliot, there comes a time
when you have to do the
responsible thing, not what you
feel like but what makes
more sense as an adult.
-This again.
I'm not your little
brother anymore.
-There's 10 years between us.
You'll always be my
little brother.
-I'm not a child.
-Well, when you start making
adult decisions, then you
won't get treated like one.
-Well, how's this for
an adult decision.
-Oh, it's that easy, is it?
-It is that easy.
Dad never wanted me there
to begin with.
He wanted you to run it.
-Elliot, that's not--
-You got what you
wanted, Laura.
You got the whole thing
to yourself.
-I never wanted that.
-Well, you got it, and I don't
care if you run the whole
fucking thing into the ground.
And that's how easy this is.
You start fucking some stoner,
and all of a sudden you're
this free spirit?
-What are you two
arguing about?
-Elliot here just quit
the business.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
-Good for you.
What are you gonna do.
-I don't know.
-Whatever it is, I hope
it's something fun.
-Me too, Ma.
-Oh, Laura, you should
be happy for him.
He hated that job.
-But that was daddy's dream.
-It wasn't Elliot's dream,
or yours for that matter.
-So, what?
We just throw it all way?
Do you know how much money
you could get for it?
Sell it.
Go on an adventure.
Don't waste another second
of your life on
someone else's dream.
-That's easy to say when
you've never had one.
-I've got news for you, Laura.
Laundry wasn't your
father's dream.
And look where it got him,
a heart attack at 55.
Oh honey, you can't take
any of it with you.
It's all just things.
And in the end, we all leave
just the same way we came in,
naked and alone.
-Who's feeding you all
this bullshit?
-Honey, I lost the
love of my life.
You don't have to.
-You should have told daddy
that while he was alive.
-I didn't mean your father.
-Mom?
-Yeah, I--
I think I'll just
get back to bed.
You mind giving me a push?
-Yeah?
-Are you OK?
-Ted, would you mind taking
her to her room?
I'm gonna go get her
a pain pill.
-Sure.
-Thanks.
-OK.
Maybe you should think about
going home with Laura.
-And maybe you should start
figuring out what's next.
-Maybe I should.
-Did you get what you needed?
-You need anything--
-Thanks.
-Mom, why didn't you call us?
-I thought it was too late.
-How are you doing?
-I'm good.
-What are you looking at?
-No one ever pays attention
to this side of the house.
-It's a driveway.
-It's a garden.
-I guess it is.
I'm gonna clear the table.
-I'll give you a hand.
-We're not done, you and me.
-OK.
-Why would you pick this
night of all night
to pull this shit.
-Elliott--
-You--
And when you can't,
you freak out.
-Well, someone has to at least
try and take control.
-Of a situation you can't
possibly control.
I have news for you.
Ma is gonna die any day, and
there's nothing any of us can
do about it.
In the meantime, you'll just
fuck Ted and make pancakes?
-Fuck you, Laura.
-I know.
I'm the asshole.
But who do you think takes
care of all the
details around here?
-You, Laura, out of guilt.
You don't give a
shit about Ma.
You just want to rush in and
save the day so everyone will
what a good daughter you are.
-Oh, really?
-Really.
And all of this talk about
responsibility, where have you
been this past year
and a half?
-Same place as you, Elliot, or
am I at fault because I didn't
pack your bags and
drive you here?
That's why you're a child,
Elliot, because you wait for
everyone else to take
care of you.
Have you even thought about
the fact that we
have to plan a funeral?
No, why would you when you know
someone else is going to
do it for you.
And why can't you be alone?
You're the neediest
person I ever met.
So don't tell me that you're
not a child, Elliot.
That's exactly what you are.
-You got all the answers,
don't you?
-I got a few.
Your husband left you.
Why is that?
Think about it.
-Hey.
Look, this is none of
my business, but
think about your mom.
-You're right, Ted.
This is none of your business.
-Just-- she can hear you guys.
-Why are you still here?
-Don't turn this on me.
-No, what normal person
stays in a house
while someone is dying?
Out of respect for our family,
you should have left the
minute that we came here.
-Your mom asked me to stay so
she wouldn't have to be alone
with you two.
And I completely get it.
You both have made this whole
thing about you every chance
you've got.
Now, I didn't know your mom back
then, but right now, she
is in there dying.
And you, Laura, argue nonstop
with everyone in this house.
It's insane.
-And you got it all together,
is that it?
Keeping a framed photo
of your ex-boyfriend
who fucked you over?
Spare us the lecture.
-You don't know anything
about that.
-I know.
You're so complex.
I could never figure you out.
-Your sister was right.
You are a fucking child.
What do you want, Elliot?
-I'm sorry for what I said.
It was stupid.
-It was.
-Yeah, well I'm sorry.
LAURA (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
did I wake you?
Sorry.
Look, I just wanted to, um, to
say to you that I've been
thinking a lot about us.
And, um, I want to apologize
for all the
stupid shit that I did.
I just--
I know I can be a bitch,
and I never
wanted to be that person.
You deserve more than
that, so I'm sorry.
No, I'm not drunk.
-What are you doing?
-I was kind of hoping
that maybe I could
stay with you tonight.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
-Elliot, this is getting
kind of weird.
-I think it was weird
before I got here.
You don't have to do anything.
I just want to--
stay with you.
-Ow, ow.
I'm gonna call 911.
No?
Mom, I think that--
OK.
Can I get you anything?
I don't know what I'm
supposed to do.
-When you sang tonight,
I saw you.
-Oh yeah?
-You're so beautiful.
-Why are you living here?
-I guess I checked
out for a while.
It's been nice.
-What happened?
-What do you mean?
-With Eric.
I don't know.
You live in a house
with a dying woman
who's twice your age.
What is that about?
And you don't have
to talk about it.
But isn't it hard being around
someone who's dying?
-That's nothing.
I rented a room from a woman
who had her legs
blown off in Iraq.
She had to walk on her hands.
-Like the woman in your book?
Is that with this is?
Is it?
I don't know what
to do with that.
-With what?
Honesty?
-You're just using us.
-That is not how I look at it.
-How do you look at it?
-Elliot, your mom was so
lonely when I met her.
-You just want to know how the
great Ralph Adams lost his
political career.
-At first, but I told
her months ago.
She's cool with it.
-So you're not a
groundskeeper?
-I try.
Look, what is the difference
between right now and
half an hour ago?
-You lied your way
into this house.
And just because you think
my mom is cool
doesn't make it OK.
-That's a bit dramatic.
-Is it?
-Elliot, when I got here, your
mom was desperate for
attention, and she has so
many great stories.
And your whole family
is so fucked up.
I mean the book wrote itself.
-Who's Eric?
-My boyfriend.
Five years now.
It's open.
He knows everything.
-Am I in your book?
That went in too.
-No.
-What am I then?
-I haven't figured
that out yet.
-Honesty, huh?
-Ma?
[knocking]
-I can't find Ma.
-I know where she is.
I'll go in this one.
Ma?
-[gasps].
Elliot?
She's so cold.
-How long have you been here?
Are you OK?
Elliot?
-Hey.
Our mother left this for you.
-Thank you.
-I know this hasn't been easy.
She considered you a friend,
so thank you for that.
-Well done, grasshopper.
Your sister just gave me this.
-What does it say?
-Break up with Eric.
-Did you?
-No.
Hey, are we cool?
-I haven't figured
that out yet.
Fair enough.
-We should get going.
-Let me get my bag.
-Jeff?
-I came as soon as I heard.
-How did you know?
-Elliot called me
this morning.
What's up, scrub?
-Not much.
-Let's get you home.
Drive safe.
-I will.
-Is it weird for me to
go to the funeral?
-I don't think anything's
weird anymore.
-Hey, uh, do you want
to ride with me?
-No, I'll drive.
-OK.
NARRATOR: That last night, as
Elliott sat at her bedside,
Lilly told him the truth.
And he wasn't shocked.
He'd always heard the
rumors growing up.
Fear kept her from
telling him.
Fear stopped him from asking,
but it's in those moments when
we pushed through the fear we
find new opportunities, even
when we think it's too late.