[ SCREAMING ]
NO!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ LIGHTNING STRIKES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ FOOTSTEPS PATTERING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY CONTINUES ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
[ DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE ]
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
[ MUNCHING ]
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
[ MUNCHING CONTINUES ]
[ GROWLS, MUNCHING ]
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
EMMA?
[ GROWLING ]
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ BIRD CALLING ]
KATE.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ BIRD CALLING ]
[ SIGHS ] I LOVE THAT COLOR!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
WHAT IS IT?
[ SIGHS ] I LOVE THAT COLOR!
[ SIGHS ] IT'S ORANKA.
WHAT IS IT?
A FANCY NAME FOR ORANGY GOLD.
[ SIGHS ] IT'S ORANKA.
OH.
A FANCY NAME FOR ORANGY GOLD.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
OH.
DO YOU GUYS WANT RED OR
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
WHITE?
DO YOU GUYS WANT RED OR
UM, WHITE, PLEASE.
WHITE?
SAME FOR ME.
UM, WHITE, PLEASE.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
SAME FOR ME.
SO, HOW ARE EMMA AND DANNY
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
DOING?
SO, HOW ARE EMMA AND DANNY
ARE THEY STILL TOGETHER?
DOING?
WHO KNOWS?
ARE THEY STILL TOGETHER?
THEY'RE ON AGAIN, OFF AGAIN.
WHO KNOWS?
EMMA SAYS SHE THINKS DANNY'S
THEY'RE ON AGAIN, OFF AGAIN.
BEEN SEEING SOMEONE BEHIND HER
EMMA SAYS SHE THINKS DANNY'S
BACK.
BEEN SEEING SOMEONE BEHIND HER
OH, REALLY?
BACK.
MM-HMM.
OH, REALLY?
DOES SHE KNOW WHO?
MM-HMM.
MM, SHE SAYS SHE DOES.
DOES SHE KNOW WHO?
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
MM, SHE SAYS SHE DOES.
HMM.
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ BIRD CALLING ]
[ CRIES, BREATHES HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CALLING CONTINUES ]
[ GRUNTS, BREATHES HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CALLING CONTINUES ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
[ POUND ON DOOR ]
[ RATTLES ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
KATE?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HELP ME.
KATE?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HELP ME.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I-I CAN'T REMEMBER.
HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
I-I CAN'T REMEMBER.
EMMA ATTACKED ME.
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
WHERE IS SHE?
EMMA ATTACKED ME.
IT'S OKAY.
WHERE IS SHE?
WE'RE SAFE FOR NOW.
IT'S OKAY.
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
WE'RE SAFE FOR NOW.
I CAME WITH LUCY.
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
GOD, LUCY...
I CAME WITH LUCY.
WHERE IS SHE?!
GOD, LUCY...
SHE RAN INTO THE GARAGE.
WHERE IS SHE?!
YOU HAVE TO GO AND HELP HER.
SHE RAN INTO THE GARAGE.
I THINK SHE'S LOSING THE BABY.
YOU HAVE TO GO AND HELP HER.
GOD, I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
I THINK SHE'S LOSING THE BABY.
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
GOD, I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
OKAY, LOOK, JUST STAY HERE.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
LUCY?
NO, PLEASE!
OH, GOD, LUCY!
KARA.
IT HURTS SO MUCH.
CAN YOU WALK?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YOU SHOULD REST A WHILE TILL
WE FIGURE OUT WHAT WE DO NEXT.
WHERE IS DANNY?
MAYBE HE COULD HELP US OUT OF
HERE.
[ SIGHS ]
HE WENT AFTER TOM.
THEY GOT SEPARATED WHEN A COUPLE
OF THOSE THINGS CAME AFTER US.
[ GASPS ]
I DON'T WANT MY BABY TO DIE!
WE WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
[ GASPS ]
[ CRYING ]
[ WATER RUNNING ]
[ BIRD CALLING ]
[ GASPS ] OH, GOD!
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
I NEED TO GET TO A HOSPITAL.
THE NEAREST ONE'S 25 MILES
FROM HERE.
MAYBE DANNY OR TOM GOT HELP.
WE CAN'T WAIT FOR THEM.
WELL, HOW ARE WE GONNA GET
HELP?
WE CAN'T EVEN CALL OUT OF HERE
WITH THE GRID DOWN.
I DON'T KNOW!
SOMEONE PLEASE THINK OF
SOMETHING!
UH, EMMA'S CAR'S IN THE SHOP.
IT'S ONLY 10 MINUTES' WALK FROM
HERE.
WITH THOSE PSYCHOS OUT THERE?
WE SHOULD FIND SOMETHING TO
ARM OURSELVES WITH.
NOT FUNNY!
I'M UP FOR THAT.
I'M NOT HAVING MY CHILD HERE
WHERE THOSE FREAKS CAN EAT HIM
FOR DINNER.
WHAT ABOUT EMMA?
I GUESS WE SHOULD LEAVE HER
HERE FOR NOW.
SHE'LL BE OKAY.
[ SIGHS ] COME ON, LET'S GO.
[ BIRD CALLING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ CALLING CONTINUES ]
I'M SO SORRY, EMMA.
I'M GONNA FIND YOU SOME HELP.
I PROMISE I'LL COME BACK FOR
YOU.
[ CALLING CONTINUES ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ GASPS ]
HELP...
ME.
PLEASE.
HELP ME.
WE CAN'T STOP.
WE HAVE TO KEEP GOING.
WELL, WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE HIM
HERE.
THOSE MAN-EATING FREAKS COULD
GET HIM.
WE SHOULD AT LEAST HELP HIM
INSIDE.
HELP ME, PLEASE.
[ GRUNTS ]
NO! [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTING ]
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT FOR?!
WE CAN'T TRUST ANYONE.
THESE THINGS, PEOPLE, WHATEVER
THEY ARE ARE SMARTER THAN THEY
LOOK.
WE HAVE TO PROTECT OURSELVES AT
ALL COSTS.
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
DANNY!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WHERE'S EMMA?
WHERE IS SHE?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
S-SHE'S OKAY.
WHERE IS SHE?
IS SHE...
S-SHE'S OKAY.
SHE'S FINE.
IS SHE...
WE NEED TO GET HER SOME HELP,
SHE'S FINE.
BUT FIRST, WE NEED TO GET LUCY
WE NEED TO GET HER SOME HELP,
TO A HOSPITAL.
BUT FIRST, WE NEED TO GET LUCY
FUCK.
TO A HOSPITAL.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
FUCK.
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
DANNY, GET IN!
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
DANNY, GET IN!
GO, GO! WHAT THE...
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WE'RE GONNA GO!
GO, GO! WHAT THE...
I'M GOING!
WE'RE GONNA GO!
AGH!
I'M GOING!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
AGH!
OKAY!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, GO AWAY!
OKAY!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, GO AWAY!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
CALM DOWN, PLEASE.
EVERYONE, CALM DOWN.
[ MURMURING CONTINUES ]
WHEN'S THE DAMN GRID GONNA BE
BACK ONLINE?
I CAN'T SPEAK TO MY PATIENTS
AFTER HOURS OR USE THE INTERNET
FOR...
PERSONAL USE.
PERV.
AND MY WIFE WOULD ALSO LIKE
TO KNOW...
SORRY, I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
WHEN THE GRID WILL BE BACK UP AS
WE HAVE SOME IMPORTANT CALLS TO
MAKE TO THE CITY.
AND SOME PURCHASES. [ SIGHS ]
I UNDERSTAND YOUR
FRUSTRATION.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE ENGINEERS
WON'T BE OUT TILL MONDAY.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, I...
I GUESS WE CAN WAIT UNTIL THEN.
UH, T-THAT'S NOT ACCEPTABLE.
THE LAST GUY I SENT UP THERE
DISAPPEARED -- LEFT AND QUIT
WITHOUT NOTICE.
THEY CAN'T SEND SOMEONE
SOONER?
I MEAN, I'D DO IT MYSELF, BUT
THEN, WELL, I'D HAVE TO CHARGE
YOU.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SAM, YOU KNOW WE HAVE TROUBLE
GETTING DELIVERIES FROM THE BIG
TOWNS THIS FAR OUT.
HAVING AN ENGINEER SENT FROM THE
CITY MEANS THEY'D HAVE TO PAY
MORE FOR DISTANCE, WHICH THEY
WILL NOT DO.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET A
WASHING MACHINE SENT FROM THE
CITY, AND THERE IS A FOUR-WEEK
WAIT LIST.
WE ALL KNOW ABOUT YOUR NEW
APPLIANCES, RACHEL, YOUR NEW
CAR, ET CETERA.
WE'RE NOT HERE TO TALK ABOUT
YOUR FANCY WAYS.
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO
MEAN?
IT MEANS SHE'S CALLING YOU A
B--
ANYONE HAVE ANYTHING BESIDES
THE GRID BEING DOWN?
I WOULD LIKE SOMEONE TO COME
OUT AND TEST THE WATER.
ARE YOU HAVING WATER
PROBLEMS, MS. SULLIVAN?
PERHAPS YOU NEED TO MAKE AN
APPOINTMENT AT MY PRACTICE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
MY HAIR HAS STARTED TO FALL
OUT.
UH, I HAVEN'T USED ANY NEW
PRODUCTS.
YEAH, FOR ABOUT 80 YEARS.
LOOK, THERE'S SOMETHING IN
THE WATER, I TELL YOU.
I'VE BEEN FEELING SICK FOR THE
PAST FEW DAYS.
[ SIGHS ]
I WILL GET SOMEONE OUT THERE
TO LOOK INTO THAT FOR YOU,
MARTHA.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HOW LONG UNTIL WE GET THERE?
UH, WE SHOULD BE THERE IN
ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
[ SIGHS ]
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC CONTINUES ]
ONCE WE GET LUCY TO THE
HOSPITAL, WE NEED TO GET HELP
FOR EMMA.
HOW BAD IS SHE?
SHE'LL BE FINE.
I KNOW SHE WILL.
FINE? FINE?
SHE DAMN NEAR RIPPED MY ENTIRE
ARM OFF.
YOU OKAY?
ONLY NOW THAT YOU RESCUED US.
WHAT HAPPENED TO TOM?
I DON'T KNOW.
KARA AND I LOST HIM BACK AT THE
HIGH SCHOOL.
I WENT BACK TO CHECK FOR HIM TO
SEE IF MAYBE HE FOUND SOMEWHERE
TO HIDE OR...
HE FOUND SOME HELP MAYBE.
BUT I COULDN'T FIND HIM.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
THANKFULLY, THE KIDS ARE OUT
FOR THE SUMMER.
OTHERWISE, GOD KNOWS WHAT
WOULD'VE HAPPENED TO THEM.
COME ON, KIDS.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
MY SON HAS BEEN SICK ALL DAY.
DR. TRAVERS SENT HIM HOME WITH
BABY ASPIRIN, BUT I'M SURE IT'S
SOMETHING MORE.
MAYBE MARTHA'S RIGHT.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING IN THE
WATER.
WELL, IF MY PROFESSIONAL
OPINION DOESN'T SUIT YOU,
MRS. CROSS -- OH, I'M SORRY.
IT'S MS., ISN'T IT?
JERK.
THE WATER DOESN'T EXPLAIN HOW
MY DOG ENDED UP WITH ITS GUTS
RIPPED OUT.
[ GASPS ]
IT HAD WHAT?!
YOU LET HIM ROAM AROUND WITH
THOSE COYOTES AGAIN?
IT WASN'T THE COYOTES.
I HEARD SOMETHING MOVING OUT
IN MY YARD LAST NIGHT, AND IT
WAS A LITTLE BIG TO BE A COYOTE.
THOSE CRITTERS WOULD'VE
DRAGGED ITS CARCASS OFF INTO THE
WOODS.
HAS ANYONE EVER THOUGHT IT
MIGHT BE THOSE KIDS THAT HANG
OUT AT NIGHT AT THE SCHOOL?
I'M SURE THEY'RE NOT UP TO ANY
GOOD.
WE SPOKE ABOUT THAT LAST
MONTH, RACHEL.
WELL, THERE SHOULD BE
STRICTER CURFEWS AND STRONGER
PUNISHMENTS IN PLACE.
ANOTHER ONE?
YOU ALREADY GOT US BANNED FROM
THE PARK AFTER 7:00.
SORRY, JACOB.
I KNOW YOU GOT STUCK WITH HER AS
YOUR WARD, BUT IT IS KIDS LIKE
HER WHO ARE BRINGING THIS TOWN
DOWN.
[ CHOPPING ]
[ CLATTERS ]
[ BLENDER WHIRRING ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ ENGINE CUTS OUT ]
DAMN IT!
WHAT'S WRONG?
THE ENGINE FINALLY GAVE OUT.
[ SIGHS ]
ARE YOU KIDDING?
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT THIS
CAR DECIDED TO BREAK DOWN IN A
SECLUDED AREA WHERE THERE'S
ZOMBIES RUNNING AROUND?
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING. I...
I JUST FEEL A LITTLE NAUSEOUS.
THAT'S ALL.
[ VOMITING ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ SIGHS ]
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I'M OKAY.
JUST A LITTLE UPSET TUMMY.
I HEAR YOU.
[ SIGHS ]
THIS WHOLE ORDEAL IS HARD TO
SWALLOW.
OH!
WELL?
LOOKS LIKE IT'S HAD IT.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
NOW I'M GONNA HAVE MY BABY IN A
DITCH.
COME ON, LET'S AT LEAST SEE
HOW FAR WE CAN GET ON FOOT.
[ SIGHS ]
DAMN IT. [ SIGHS ]
STILL NOTHING?
NO.
UM, HEY, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET MOVING 'CAUSE IT'S GONNA BE
DARK SOON, AND I DON'T WANT TO
STAND AROUND HERE UNTIL THOSE
THINGS COME BACK HERE AND FIND
US.
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
JOSH?
JOSH, HONEY?
JOSH, ARE YOU READY FOR BED YET?
[ JINGLES ]
JOSH?
JOSH, ARE YOU OKAY?
[ JINGLES ]
JOSH?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME CALLING?
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ JINGLES, CLATTERS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
THANKS FOR COMING BACK FOR
US.
WELL, I WASN'T GONNA LEAVE
YOU BEHIND.
REALLY?
I WAS WORRIED YOU MAY HAVE GONE
BACK FOR EMMA.
WELL, I MEAN, I-I DID, BUT
I'M REALLY GLAD THAT YOU'RE
OKAY, TOO.
SO, DO YOU THINK WE CAN PICK
UP WHERE WE LEFT OFF?
UM, N-NOW MIGHT NOT BE THE
BEST TIME FOR THIS.
WELL, WHEN IS A GOOD TIME?
DANNY, I NEED TO KNOW.
KATE...
ZOMBIES.
OKAY?
NO PHONE, NO CAR, ZOMBIES!
FETUS! UH [SIGHS]
HELLO?!
SO, WHAT DID YOU DECIDE ON AS
A NAME?
JEFFERSON.
AFTER YOUR FATHER.
WELL [SIGHS] I FIGURE IF THIS
KID'S GONNA BE ASSOCIATED WITH A
FATHER, IT MIGHT AS WELL BE MY
OWN.
WALT HASN'T TRIED TO GET IN
CONTACT, HAS HE?
NO. THANK GOD.
[ SIGHS ]
THIS BABY'S THE BEST THING
THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
I'M NOT GONNA LET THAT LUSH NEAR
HIM.
LOOK, I REALLY NEED TO REST.
DANNY, WE NEED TO STOP FOR A
WHILE.
LUCY SHOULDN'T BE WALKING THIS
MUCH.
[ SIGHS ]
I COULD DO WITH A REST, TOO.
I'M STARTING TO FEEL A LITTLE
FAINT.
SERIOUSLY?
OKAY, OVER THERE LOOKS GOOD.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
NO.
DANNY, LOOK AT THEM!
THEY NEED A REST!
[ SIGHS ]
LOOK, WE DON'T KNOW IF THERE ARE
10 OR 50 OF THOSE THINGS OUT
THERE, AND YOU WANT US TO STOP?!
LOOK, HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO
PROTECT OURSELVES WITH STUMPY
AND PREGO OVER THERE TAKING A
NAP?!
IF WE HAVE ANY CHANCE OF
GETTING OUT OF HERE, ALL OF US
TOGETHER, WE NEED A REST.
[ SIGHS ]
FINE.
DANNY AND I WILL KEEP WATCH,
BUT WE REALLY NEED TO GET GOING
WHEN YOU TWO CAN WALK AGAIN.
JUST MAKE SURE SOMETHING
DOESN'T TRY AND EAT US WHILE WE
SLEEP.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ CICADAS CHIRPING ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
HELEN?!
HELEN, IS MY DINNER READY,
WOMAN?!
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
MMM.
[ SIGHS ]
[ CHANTING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ CHANTING CONTINUES ]
[ BIRD SQUAWKING ]
[ SQUAWKING CONTINUES ]
[ CHANTING CONTINUES ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
UM...
SORRY.
DID YOU FALL ASLEEP, TOO?
MM-HMM.
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
DID WE SLEEP THROUGH THE
NIGHT?
MM.
I BELIEVE WE MADE IT OUT THE
OTHER SIDE.
MM.
HOPEFULLY, IT WAS JUST THOSE
PEOPLE AFFECTED OUR SIDE OF THE
TOWN.
WHERE'S KATE?
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
KATE?
KATE, COME ON, WE SHOULD GET
GOING.
KATE?
OKAY.
[ GRUNTS ]
WE SHOULD PROBABLY TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO GET GOING.
I THINK THE CONTRACTIONS HAVE
STOPPED.
MAYBE THIS BABY FINALLY CAUGHT
ON THAT COMING OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE CARNIVAL AIN'T THE BEST
OPTION.
CARNIVAL.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD CALL HIM
"BOZO."
[ SNIFFS ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
KATE!
COME ON, REMEMBER, LADY WITH A
BABY HERE!
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
YOU KNOW, WE PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T STICK AROUND AND SEE
IF ANY OF THOSE THINGS ARE
PLAYING HIDE-AND-SEEK WITH US.
HOW COULD SHE JUST WANDER OFF
LIKE THAT?
[ SIGHS ]
I THINK WE WOKE THE LITTLE
MONSTER.
YOU KNOW, WE SHOULD GO.
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
WHERE THE HELL IS SHE?
KATE, PLEASE, WE HAVE TO GET
GOING!
[ SIGHS ]
YOU KNOW, SHE PROBABLY
FLAGGED DOWN A CAR AND GOT THE
HELL OUT OF HERE.
I MEAN...
TOWN'S GOT TO BE CRAWLING WITH
ARMY OR CDC BY NOW.
I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
I MADE PANCAKES.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU KNOW, I DON'T APPRECIATE YOU
BEHAVING THE WAY YOU DID AT THE
MEETING.
PEOPLE LOOK UP TO ME.
AND HAVING YOU ACTING UP DOES
NOT INSTILL THEIR CONFIDENCE IN
ME.
WILL YOU PUT THAT DAMN BOOK
DOWN?
NOW, I THINK IT'S TIME YOU GET A
JOB, SOMETHING TO GET YOU OUT OF
THE HOUSE.
IF YOU DON'T WANT ME HERE, I
CAN LEAVE.
[ SIGHS ]
I'M THE ONLY FAMILY YOU HAVE,
GIRL.
I FEED YOU. I HOUSE YOU.
WHAT THANKS DO I GET?
WHY DID YOU TAKE ME IN IF YOU
DIDN'T WANT ME?
IF I'D HAVE KNOWN WHAT A
DISAPPOINTMENT YOU'D BE...
I WOULDN'T HAVE.
PLEASE STOP.
YOU'RE NOT MY DAUGHTER.
AND DON'T THINK YOU EVER WILL
BE.
YOU KNOW...
MAYBE IT WOULD BE BETTER FOR
EVERYONE IF I WAS DEAD, TOO.
SOME STAPH INFECTION?
THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHAT IS THIS?
INFECTION?
VIRUS, RABIES?
DAD!
DAD?!
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON WITH
HER?
[ SIGHS ]
I'M HUNGRY, DAD!
SHUT UP.
I'M HUNGRY!
SHUT UP!
JUST SHUT UP!
I'M HUNGRY!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
SHH! SHH! SHH! SHH! SHH! SHH!
WE NEED TO MOVE FASTER.
I'M TRYING.
THIS BABY'S KILLING ME.
THE PAIN'S GETTING WORSE.
KEEP BREATHING.
I'M SURE IF WE KEEP HEADING THAT
WAY, WE'LL MAKE IT BACK TO TOWN.
BACK THERE?
I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK TO THOSE
FREAKS.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK WE'RE ANY
SAFER OUT HERE.
I-IT'S KATE!
KATE, WE'RE OVER HERE!
KATE, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?!
KATE, COME ON!
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE THIS BABY
HERE!
WHAT IS SHE DOING?
SHE LOOKS REALLY SPRIGHTLY
FOR SOMEBODY WHO NEVER WAKES UP
BEFORE 10:00.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT?
DANNY, SHE DOESN'T LOOK
RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD, SHE'S ONE OF THEM!
RUN!
[ GASPS ] OH!
RUN! COME ON!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
DANNY, WAIT!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SIGHS ]
YOU KIDS NEED TO GET OUT OF
THESE WOODS BEFORE YOU GET
YOURSELF DEAD!
YOU NEED TO CROSS ALL 20, THAT
SOMETHING DON'T EAT UP THAT
PRETTY FACE.
THANK YOU?
I'VE NEVER SEEN NOTHING THIS
DARN CRAZY SINCE THEM ALIENS
CAME AND TOOK ME IN THEIR SHIP
AND DID THAT RECTAL PROBE THING
UP MY --
[ GROWLING ]
LUCY, RUN!
[ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMING CONTINUES ]
[ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
I HATE YOU.
I HATE YOU SO...
SO MUCH.
HATE YOU.
WHY?
WHY DID YOU GO?
I SHOULD BE THERE, TOO.
[ PILLS RATTLE ]
[ TAPS ]
WHAT THE HELL?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
ARE ANY OF THOSE THINGS OUT
THERE?
DID YOU SEE ANY OF THOSE
FREAKS?!
>>   YOU'RTHE FREAK.
[ SIGHS ]
SERIOUSLY, IS THERE ANYTHING OUT
THERE?
NO, AND LIKE I CARE.
IF YOU SAW WHAT I SAW, YOU
WOULDN'T BE SAYING THAT.
WHATEVER.
HEY, YOU CAN'T GO OUT THERE.
SERIOUSLY, WHAT IS WRONG WITH
YOU?!
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO TELL YOU.
WE'RE NOT SAFE HERE.
WHY?
BECAUSE THOSE FREAKS OUT
THERE DID THIS TO ME.
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY, I'M GONNA LEAVE NOW.
OW, GET OFF OF ME!
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST TRYING TO SAVE YOUR
LIFE.
THIS IS NOT A JOKE.
[ SIGHS ]
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
HEY, CAN WE START OVER?
I'M TOM.
JESSICA.
GREAT, NOW WE'RE ACQUAINTED.
CAN WE HIDE OUT SOMEWHERE TILL
THIS BLOWS OVER?
I'M NOT STAYING HERE WITH
YOU.
STILL HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT IF YOU
REALLY ARE A FREAK YET.
OH, ZOMBIES?
COME HERE.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
FRESH MEAT FOR YOU.
COME...
[ BREATHING HEAVILY
CONTINUES ]
...ON.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY
CONTINUES ]
JESSICA?
RUN!
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLS ]
YEAH.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
COME ON.
THAT IS HOW YOU DO THAT!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AGH!
[ SHOUTING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OH, P-PLEASE, PLEASE HELP ME!
[ SHOUTING ]
OH!
OH, P-PLEASE, PLEASE HELP ME!
PLEASE, MY SON AND I WERE
OH!
SEPARATED...
PLEASE, MY SON AND I WERE
SHH! SHH! SHH!
SEPARATED...
...WHEN THAT MAN ATTACKED US!
SHH! SHH! SHH!
YEAH, YEAH, OKAY. SHH!
...WHEN THAT MAN ATTACKED US!
O-OH.
YEAH, YEAH, OKAY. SHH!
YOU HAVE TO FIND HIM!
O-OH.
[ SCOFFS ]
YOU HAVE TO FIND HIM!
NO, I HAVE TO FIND MY FRIENDS,
[ SCOFFS ]
OKAY?
NO, I HAVE TO FIND MY FRIENDS,
[ GROANS ]
OKAY?
HE'S ONLY 10.
[ GROANS ]
I-IT'S HIS BIRTHDAY.
HE'S ONLY 10.
OH, HIS BIRTHDAY?
I-IT'S HIS BIRTHDAY.
I-I PROMISED HIM A CAMPING
OH, HIS BIRTHDAY?
TRIP.
I-I PROMISED HIM A CAMPING
UH-HUH.
TRIP.
A-AND I WANTED TO DO
UH-HUH.
SOMETHING SPECIAL FOR HIM...
A-AND I WANTED TO DO
OH.
SOMETHING SPECIAL FOR HIM...
...BECAUSE HIS MOTHER DIED...
OH.
[ SCOFFS ]
...BECAUSE HIS MOTHER DIED...
...A MONTH AGO.
[ SCOFFS ]
MOM DIED, TOO, HUH?
...A MONTH AGO.
[ MOANS ]
MOM DIED, TOO, HUH?
OKAY. [ SIGHS ]
[ MOANS ]
I'M GONNA GO. GOOD LUCK.
HONEY, DO YOU THINK WE COULD
REPLACE THE CARPET IN THAT BACK
BEDROOM?
I NOTICED THEY HAD THE PERFECT
SHADE OF LEMON AT A STORE IN THE
CITY.
WE COULD HAVE IT SENT SPECIAL
DELIVERY -- NONE OF THIS WAITING
FOUR WEEKS.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW WE CAN AFFORD
IT.
MICHAEL?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
SHALL I GO AHEAD AND ORDER IT
THEN?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ HEART BEATING LOUDLY ]
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
MM, I'LL CALL THEM ON MONDAY.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
[ COUGHS ]
[ VOMITING ]
[ SIGHS ]
HOW LONG HAVE WE BEEN WALKING?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE COULD BE WALKING IN CIRCLES.
YOU TOLD ME THAT WE WERE
GOING BACK INTO TOWN.
I'M SORRY!
WE WERE HEADING THAT WAY...
BEFORE KATE.
GOD, KATE...
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
FIRST EMMA, THEN KATE!
[ SIGHS ]
PLEASE...
KARA.
PLEASE GET US OUT OF HERE.
OKAY.
HOW COULDN'T I HAVE SEEN THIS
EARLIER?
IT'S SO SIMPLE.
IT'S JUST A VIRUS.
IT'S JUST A SIMPLE, LITTLE
VIRUS.
AND IT'S MINE.
I DISCOVERED IT.
LEAH, IT'S A VIRUS.
I'VE WORKED IT OUT.
IT'S A VIRUS THAT AFFECTS BOTH
THE ADRENAL GLANDS AND THE
THYROID.
IT'S A MUTATION I'VE NEVER SEEN
BEFORE.
THE EFFECT MAKES PEOPLE HUNGRY
FOR...
BLOOD AND FLESH, AND...
IT MAKES THEM RAVENOUS LIKE AN
ANIMAL, OH, BUT -- BUT YOU KNOW
THAT, SWEETHEART.
I HAVE TO CALL THIS INTO THE
CDC.
IT'S A MEDICAL DISCOVERY.
I'LL BE PUBLISHED IN EVERY
MEDICAL JOURNAL.
[ SIGHS ]
I'LL DO MORE TESTS, AND I WILL
PROVE THIS CONTAGION.
THE MEDICAL BOARD'S GONNA HAVE
TO LET ME BACK IN NOW.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT ARE THOSE?
GOD KNOWS.
ARE THOSE -- ARE THOSE BONES?
WE SHOULD JUST KEEP MOVING.
THIS ISN'T WHERE THAT WEIRDO
LIVES, IS IT?
IT CAN'T BE.
HE LIVES WAY OFF FROM TOWN.
[ SIGHS ]
AND HE ISN'T A WEIRDO.
REALLY?
DOESN'T HE DO VOODOO OR STUFF?
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT SOME WITCH
DOCTOR DELIVERING MY BABY.
I WANT A REAL DOCTOR.
WE'LL GET YOU A REAL DOCTOR.
I DON'T WANT HIM, LIKE,
STICKING PINS IN A DOLL THAT
LOOKS LIKE ME.
THERE ARE ZOMBIES RUNNING
AROUND, AND YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
SOME DOLL?
JUST SAYING.
[ SIGHS ] COME ON.
HEY, ISN'T THAT A CABIN OVER
THERE?
UH, MAYBE THEY HAVE A BED FOR
YOU OR SOMEWHERE SAFE FOR US.
IT'S HIS, ISN'T IT?
[ SIGHS ] LUCY, COME ON.
[ SIGHS ]
I TOLD YOU.
HE'S GONNA SACRIFICE ME OR
SOMETHING.
THAT'S WHAT THESE WACKOS DO.
THEY OFFER YOU UP TO SOME EVIL
SPIRIT.
THEY ONLY DO THAT WITH
VIRGINS, AND YOU ARE HARDLY ONE
OF THOSE.
HAHA.
WE SHOULDN'T BE BREAKING INTO
SOMEONE'S HOUSE.
HELLO? IS ANYONE HERE?
SHH!
DON'T LURE HIM OUT HERE!
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'VE SEEN PEOPLE TORN LIMB
FROM LIMB, AND YOU'RE MORE
SCARED ABOUT AN OLD MAN IN A
SHACK?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M FEELING MUCH BETTER, OKAY?
WE CAN HEAD BACK TO TOWN.
LOOK, IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
ANYONE'S HERE.
MAYBE HE GOT OUT OF TOWN
ALREADY.
YEAH, OR MAYBE HE PUT A CURSE
ON THE TOWN, AND HE'S JUST
WAITING FOR SOMEONE TO WANDER
INTO HIS SHACK SO HE CAN PERFORM
SOME SICK, RITUALISTIC KILLING.
LUCY.
[ TAPS ]
BEHIND HERE!
[ CLATTERS ]
WHO'S THERE?!
JASON?
NO, PLEASE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?!
WE JUST NEEDED SOMEWHERE TO
REST!
SNOOPING MORE LIKE.
MY FRIEND REALLY NEEDS TO GET
TO A HOSPITAL, AND IT'S NOT SAFE
FOR US OUT THERE.
THAT'S NOT MY CONCERN.
YOU SHOULD LEAVE.
COME ON, KARA, LET'S GO.
YOU PEOPLE NEVER HELP.
MY PEOPLE?
I'M SORRY ABOUT HER.
SHE'S ABOUT TO HAVE A BABY.
WE REALLY NEED A CAR TO GET US
TO THE CITY.
AND WHY SHOULD I HELP YOU?
ALL OF YOU IN THAT TOWN ARE JUST
A BUNCH OF IGNORANT, RACIST
HICKS.
I'M SORRY FOR ANYTHING ANYONE
MAY HAVE EVER SAID ABOUT YOU,
BUT IF YOU SEND US BACK OUT
THERE, WE WON'T SURVIVE.
I TOLD YOU, THIS FREAK'S NOT
GONNA HELP US.
COME ON.
GET OUT.
PLEASE!
I SAID GET OUT!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ WINDOW RATTLES ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ GRUNTS, SHOUTS ]
NO, NO, NO! [ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
[ SHOUTING ]
DO YOU THINK IT'S GONE?
JESSICA?
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT WERE YOU DOING HERE,
ANYWAY?
WANTED TO BE ALONE.
WAS THAT BOX WHY YOU WERE
HERE?
IT'S A LONG STORY.
[ SIGHS ]
WELL, I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE, AM
I?
WAIT, JESSICA.
ARE YOU THE MAYOR'S NIECE?
UNFORTUNATELY.
WELL, THEN HE'S GONNA BE
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
HE'LL...
HE'LL SEND SOMEONE TO FIND YOU,
RIGHT?
DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH.
IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
HE'LL CALL THE POLICE, AND WE'LL
GET OUT OF HERE SAFE AND SOUND.
LISTEN, THE CHANCES OF HIM
CARING ENOUGH ABOUT ME TO
ACTUALLY WORRY ABOUT ME...
ARE ABOUT AS SLIM AS US PLAYING
STRIP POKER WITH THAT THING
OUTSIDE.
WHY?
HE'D RATHER I DIDN'T EXIST.
AND RIGHT NOW, THAT SEEMS LIKE A
PRETTY GOOD OPTION.
DON'T SAY THAT.
[ SIGHS ]
WE'RE GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
WHAT'S THE POINT?
EVEN IF WE DO, I ONLY HAVE THAT
TO GO BACK TO.
NO, YOU'VE GOT CHOICES.
YOU CAN --
LIKE WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW. YOU CAN...
GO TO THE CITY, FIND SOMETHING
THERE.
NOT EASY, IS IT?
I NEVER EXPECTED TO SPEND THE
REST OF MY LIFE IN THIS SMALL
TOWN.
SO, WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE
THEN?
[ SIGHS ]
I GUESS I DIDN'T HAVE THE
BALLS.
LET'S MAKE A DEAL.
WE'LL GET OUT OF HERE.
WE'LL GO TO THE CITY.
THERE WILL BE POLICE WITH GUNS
AND PHONES THAT WORK.
[ SIGHS ]
[ RATTLING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
GOOD TO SEE EVERYONE SO
[ ALL MURMURING ]
PLACID TODAY.
GOOD TO SEE EVERYONE SO
PERHAPS THINGS ARE FINALLY
PLACID TODAY.
GETTING BETTER.
PERHAPS THINGS ARE FINALLY
BUT THEY'RE NOT.
GETTING BETTER.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
BUT THEY'RE NOT.
OKAY, OKAY, I CAN'T HEAR OVER
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
ALL OF YOU.
OKAY, OKAY, I CAN'T HEAR OVER
MAYOR.
ALL OF YOU.
ABIGAIL, LET'S GO WITH YOU.
MAYOR.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WRONG
ABIGAIL, LET'S GO WITH YOU.
WITH HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WRONG
MY SON REALLY NEEDS HELP.
WITH HIM.
I HAD TO LOCK HIM IN HIS BEDROOM
MY SON REALLY NEEDS HELP.
TODAY.
I HAD TO LOCK HIM IN HIS BEDROOM
HE DID THIS.
TODAY.
YOU REALLY SHOULD SHOW THAT
HE DID THIS.
CHILD SOME DISCIPLINE.
YOU REALLY SHOULD SHOW THAT
DISCIPLINE?
CHILD SOME DISCIPLINE.
[ SCOFFS ]
DISCIPLINE?
YOU TRY TELLING A 9-YEAR-OLD TO
[ SCOFFS ]
GO TO SLEEP WHEN HE'S JUST
YOU TRY TELLING A 9-YEAR-OLD TO
EATEN...
GO TO SLEEP WHEN HE'S JUST
THAT'S WHY WE SENT OUR
EATEN...
CHILDREN OFF TO BOARDING SCHOOL.
THAT'S WHY WE SENT OUR
YOU WILL NEVER BE ABLE TO FULLY
CHILDREN OFF TO BOARDING SCHOOL.
CONTROL THEM IF THEY HAVEN'T
YOU WILL NEVER BE ABLE TO FULLY
ALREADY BEEN CONTROLLED.
CONTROL THEM IF THEY HAVEN'T
HEY, DID YOU GIVE BIRTH TO
ALREADY BEEN CONTROLLED.
KIDS OR TO ROBOTS?
HEY, DID YOU GIVE BIRTH TO
I'M VERY SORRY, ABIGAIL.
KIDS OR TO ROBOTS?
PERHAPS WHEN DR. TRAVERS GETS
I'M VERY SORRY, ABIGAIL.
HERE, YOU CAN SPEAK WITH HIM.
PERHAPS WHEN DR. TRAVERS GETS
ANYONE ELSE?
HERE, YOU CAN SPEAK WITH HIM.
COLE?
ANYONE ELSE?
I'VE BEEN HAVING A BIT OF AN
COLE?
UPSET STOMACH.
I'VE BEEN HAVING A BIT OF AN
I THINK THE MEAT MUST BE OFF.
UPSET STOMACH.
I HAD SOME LAST NIGHT FOR
I THINK THE MEAT MUST BE OFF.
SUPPER, AND I'VE SPENT THIS
I HAD SOME LAST NIGHT FOR
MORNING ON THE CRAPPER.
SUPPER, AND I'VE SPENT THIS
DELIGHTFUL.
MORNING ON THE CRAPPER.
I TOLD YOU IT'S THE WATER.
DELIGHTFUL.
HAS ANYONE BEEN OUT TO TEST IT
I TOLD YOU IT'S THE WATER.
YET?
HAS ANYONE BEEN OUT TO TEST IT
I'M RIGHT ON THAT, MARTHA.
YET?
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'M RIGHT ON THAT, MARTHA.
MICHAEL?
DON'T YOU WORRY.
ANYTHING NEW WITH YOU AND
MICHAEL?
RACHEL?
ANYTHING NEW WITH YOU AND
WELL, THERE IS STILL THE
RACHEL?
INCONVENIENCE OF THE INTERNET
WELL, THERE IS STILL THE
BEING DOWN AND THE PHONES.
INCONVENIENCE OF THE INTERNET
OH, AND MICHAEL'S BEEN SICK.
BEING DOWN AND THE PHONES.
WELL, THERE'S OBVIOUSLY SOME
OH, AND MICHAEL'S BEEN SICK.
SORT OF STOMACH BUG GOING
WELL, THERE'S OBVIOUSLY SOME
AROUND.
SORT OF STOMACH BUG GOING
WE SHOULD ASK THE DOCTOR WHEN HE
AROUND.
GETS HERE.
WE SHOULD ASK THE DOCTOR WHEN HE
EVERYONE TALKING ABOUT ME
GETS HERE.
AGAIN?
EVERYONE TALKING ABOUT ME
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
AGAIN?
MICHAEL HAS BEEN IN THE
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
BATHROOM.
MICHAEL HAS BEEN IN THE
YOU SHOULD BE CHECKING ON
BATHROOM.
THIS!
YOU SHOULD BE CHECKING ON
MAKING A MESS!
LET'S JUST GO INSIDE THIS
BUILDING.
IT LOOKS OKAY.
I'M SURE IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE SAFE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
JUST BREATHE.
[ MACHINE WHIRRING ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
HOW MUCH FURTHER?
WE'LL GET YOU ON THAT TABLE
OVER THERE.
[ CRYING ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
WAIT HERE FOR A MINUTE.
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE IT'S SAFE.
NO! DON'T LEAVE ME!
OKAY, OKAY, I'M STAYING.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
SHH! SHH!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DIE.
[ SNIFFLES ]
YOU HAVE TO DELIVER MY BABY.
WHAT?!
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU SAID YOURSELF THIS BABY'S
ONLY SEVEN MONTHS.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
THIS BABY'S COMING WHETHER YOU
HELP ME OR NOT!
[ CRIES ] HELP!
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
IT HURTS SO MUCH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ BABY SUCKING ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
[ THUD ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
[ CRYING ]
I WAS SICK ALL NIGHT.
MY NOSE WOULDN'T STOP BLEEDING.
RIGHT. OKAY.
ANY OTHER SYMPTOMS?
HUNGRY ALL THE TIME.
HMM.
INTERESTING.
HONEY, NO ONE NEEDS TO KNOW
ABOUT YOUR PROBLEMS.
I'M THE SAME.
I CAN'T STOMACH ANYTHING BUT RAW
MEAT, AND I'VE BEEN PISSING
BLOOD.
CHARMING.
I'M ALMOST BALD IN PLACES.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS WHAT
THIS COULD BE?
IS IT THE WATER, CROP SPRAYING,
MAD COW DISEASE?
SHOULD WE GET SOMEONE OUT HERE
TO TAKE A LOOK?
WELL, THEY WERE SPRAYING FOR
BUGS OVER IN LIGHTFORD.
MAYBE SOME OF THAT WASHED UP
OVER HERE.
IT COULD BE.
MAD COW DISEASE?
DOESN'T THAT AFFECT YOUR BRAIN?
OH, MY GOD.
MY LITTLE BOY HAS BRAIN DISEASE?
NOT AT ALL.
IT SEEMS...
I-IT SEEMS TO BE SOME SORT OF
VIRUS THAT AFFECTS CERTAIN PARTS
OF THE BODY.
VIRUS?
VIRUS? WHAT TYPE OF VIRUS?
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
PLEASE, PLEASE CALM DOWN.
NOW, DR. TRAVERS, WHAT KIND OF
VIRUS?
LIKE THE FLU?
I'M NOT 100% SURE.
I NEED TO FIND OUT WHERE THE
SOURCE OF THIS CONTAGION CAME
FROM.
CONTAGION?
ARE YOU SAYING MY SON COULD DIE?
I'M NOT SAYING ANYTHING,
ABIGAIL, TILL I KNOW WHERE THIS
VIRUS CAME FROM.
BUT I BELIEVE IT CAN PASS FROM
PERSON TO PERSON, PERHAPS
THROUGH CONTACT.
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW JUST YET.
SHOULD WE BE WORRIED?
DO WE NEED TO GO TO THE CITY FOR
HELP?
I NEED TO TAKE SOME MORE
TESTS.
I NEED TO TAKE SOME BLOOD FROM
EACH OF YOU.
IF IT MEANS I CAN PERM MY
HAIR AGAIN, YOU CAN HAVE ALL THE
BLOOD YOU NEED.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE BACK IN AN
HOUR, AND I'LL TAKE YOUR BLOOD.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE EVERYTHING WILL BE
FINE.
HEY, DOC?
NO SMOKING HERE.
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE SHOULD KNOW
IT'S BAD FOR YOUR HEALTH.
HEY, HOW ARE WE REALLY DOING?
LIKE I SAID, THERE'S NO NEED
ALERTING ANYONE IN THE CITY JUST
YET.
I'M SURE IT'S JUST A FLU STRAIN.
IF THAT'S YOUR MEDICAL
OPINION, WE'LL WAIT ON YOU.
JESSICA?
SHH.
I THINK IT'S GONE.
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHAT IT --
THAT -- IS.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOME STRUNG-OUT
JUNKIE TO ME.
WHAT KIND OF JUNKIE DO YOU
KNOW THAT EATS OTHER HUMAN
BEINGS?
WE NEED TO FIND A WAY OUT OF
HERE.
[ SNIFFS ]
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
OH.
DEATH.
PERHAPS WE SHOULD WAIT TILL
BACKUP ARRIVES.
WHAT ARE YOU, THE FBI?
WE'RE NEVER GONNA GET OUT OF
HERE IF WE DON'T GET OUT OF THIS
ROOM.
YOU CAN STAY IF YOU WANT.
I'M GOOD.
[ GASPS ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ SPITTING ]
[ COUGHS ]
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
DO YOU HAVE THE VIRUS, TOO?
OH, NO. NO, NO, NO.
YOU DO, DON'T YOU?
YOU KNOW, I HAVE ALWAYS
WANTED TO ASK YOU OUT FOR A
DRINK.
REALLY? WHY?
YOU HAVE A SPARK.
AND I SEE HOW MUCH OF A GOOD
MOTHER YOU ARE.
YOU AND ME, WE SHOULD GET
TOGETHER.
I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED IF YOU
NOTICED ME.
ESPECIALLY SINCE WE'RE BOTH
SINGLE PARENTS, I THINK WE HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS WHEN
EVERYTHING BLOWS OVER, OKAY?
OKAY.
IT'S DAMN HOT IN HERE.
WHAT IS THAT?
I FOUND ONE OF THOSE ON THE
TREE BY MY HOUSE.
THIS WAS ON MY PORCH.
THAT LOOKS LIKE ONE OF THOSE
VOODOO THINGS THEY HAVE OUT IN
MORLAND'S WOOD.
THAT OLD FREAK KNOWS BETTER
THAN TO COME INTO TOWN.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT HE CAME
UP TO OUR HOMES, PROBABLY
WATCHED US WHILE WE SLEPT?
I'M SURE IT'S JUST KIDS
STIRRING UP TROUBLE.
YOU KNOW, NOW THAT I THINK
ABOUT IT, I'M PRETTY SURE IT WAS
HIM THAT I SAW IN MY BACKYARD.
HE MURDERED MY CRAVEN, HIM
AND HIS VOODOO MAGIC.
NOW, LET'S NOT JUMP TO
CONCLUSIONS.
I'M SURE MICHAEL IS RIGHT.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST THE YOUTH
PLAYING PRANKS.
DON'T THOSE FREAKS HAVE
ZOMBIES AND STUFF?
I KNOW IT WAS HIM.
HE PUT A CURSE ON MY CRAVEN.
[ SCOFFS ]
WHAT?
ZOMBIES?
THERE ARE NO ZOMBIES.
IT'S JUST A VIRUS.
WAIT, ZOMBIES?
BUT THEY EAT PEOPLE, DON'T THEY?
DO YOU THINK HE DID SOMETHING
TO MY LITTLE BOY?
PERHAPS IT ISN'T A VIRUS.
IT'S -- I THINK THEY PUT A
VOODOO CURSE ON US.
ZOMBIES, CURSES?
NOW WE REALLY ARE SPECULATING.
ANYBODY MESSES WITH MY FAMILY
IS SURE GONNA REGRET IT.
HE PROBABLY POISONED THE
WATER.
I THINK MARTHA MIGHT BE RIGHT.
I VOTE WE PAY THAT
WITCH DOCTOR A VISIT, GET HIM TO
ANSWER FOR WHAT HE DID.
I'M FOR THAT.
YEAH!
YEAH.
COME ON.
FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING ON.
NOW, EVERYONE CALM DOWN.
DR. TRAVERS, WILL YOU PLEASE
TALK SOME SENSE INTO THESE
PEOPLE?
THEY ARE ON SOME KIND OF A
VIGILANTE MISSION TO OLD MAN
EFRAN'S CABIN.
THE WITCH DOCTOR?
HE CURSED MY SON.
COME ON.
LET'S GO GET SOME ANSWERS.
WELL, I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHERE THIS VIRUS STARTED.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT?
PERHAPS THIS WOULD BE A GOOD
PLACE TO START.
GOD KNOWS WHAT SORT OF DEAD OR
DISEASED ANIMALS HE HAS UP IN
THAT PLACE.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE, THIS IS
GONNA BE PURELY AN
INVESTIGATION.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE USING
PHYSICAL FORCE.
NOPE.
JUST A FRIENDLY LITTLE CHAT.
WE'LL ASK HIM ABOUT THOSE
ZOMBIES AND STUFF, SEE IF HE'S
HEARD ANYTHING ON THE GRAPEVINE.
OKAY, SAM, I'LL MEET YOU AT THE
ENTRANCE TO WOODLAND TRAIL IN
30 MINUTES.
DOC TRAVERS, ARE YOU COMING WITH
US?
LISTEN, GET THE INFORMATION
YOU NEED, AND THAT'S ALL.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING REPORTED
BACK TO THE CITY NEGATIVE.
BELIEVE ME, I'LL GET
EVERYTHING I NEED, IF HE REALLY
DOES HAVE ANSWERS TO ALL OF
THIS.
[ SIGHS ]
COME ON. LET'S GET THESE THINGS.
WAIT.
KARA?
TOM?
IS THAT YOU?
ARE YOU AFFLICTED?
SERIOUSLY, TOM?
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE THE TIME TO
ASK ME IF I'M AFFLICTED WHILE
I'M GNAWING ON YOUR LEG?
[ CHUCKLES ]
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE ALIVE.
WE THOUGHT WE LOST YOU.
WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
UM, EMMA'S SAFE, BUT LUCY AND
KATE ARE GONE.
AND I CAN ONLY PRAY DANNY'S OUT
THERE SOMEWHERE ALIVE.
WHO ARE YOU?
NOBODY.
JESSICA. HER NAME'S JESSICA.
OKAY, JESSICA, DO YOU KNOW IF
THERE'S A WAY OUT OF THIS PLACE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE GONE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
CAN WE NOT TALK ABOUT THIS
RIGHT NOW AND JUST FIND A WAY
OUT OF HERE?
I THINK THERE'S A WAY OUT.
NEAR THE BOILER ROOM, THERE'S A
SERVICE ENTRANCE THAT GOES OUT
BACK.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE OPEN.
YOU THINK IT'S USABLE?
I THINK SO.
I THINK TOM'S RIGHT.
YOU WOULD.
WHAT?
I SAID WE SHOULD.
WE SHOULD FIND A WAY OUT OF
HERE.
WILL YOU TWO STOP BICKERING?
THERE'S PEOPLE DYING OUT THERE.
NOW, I WOULD LIKE TO GET OUT OF
HERE BEFORE YOU TWO RIP EACH
OTHER'S THROATS OUT BEFORE THEY
DO.
WHAT'S TAKING HIM SO LONG?
HE'LL BE HERE.
YOU OKAY, DOC?
LOOK A LITTLE PALE.
YEAH, I'M JUST, UM...
I AM ANXIOUS TO FIGURE THIS ALL
OUT AND GET EVERYONE BACK TO
HEALTH AGAIN.
WELL, I HOPE NOBODY HAS ANY
PROBLEM WITH ME APPLYING A
LITTLE PRESSURE TO THIS OLD
CRAZY IF HE SHOULD BE
UNCOOPERATIVE, IF YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN.
YEAH, WE GOT YOU, COLE.
LET'S JUST FIRST FIND OUT IF
HE'S THE CAUSE OF ALL THIS
TROUBLE.
UH, SO, LOOKS LIKE IT'S JUST,
UM, WHAT, US ON THIS WITCH HUNT.
I THOUGHT MICHAEL WAS JOINING
US.
[ SCOFFS ]
WITH HIS NAGGING WIFE?
OH, GOD, SHE PROBABLY HAS HIM
CARTING SOME RIDICULOUS PIECE OF
FURNITURE FROM ONE FLOOR TO
ANOTHER.
YOU KNOW, IF I WAS HIM, I'D HAVE
CLUBBED HER ALREADY AND BURIED
HER IN THE BACKYARD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SHALL WE?
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
CAN YOU TAKE OUT THE TRASH
BEFORE IT STARTS TO SMELL LIKE
LAST NIGHT'S DINNER IN HERE?
WHICH, I BELIEVE, BY THE WAY,
WAS ONE OF THE BEST COQ AU VIN
I HAVE EVER MADE.
ALSO, YOU REALLY NEED TO LOOK
INTO THAT PROMOTION YOUR BOSS
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE THE LAST TO
APPLY.
RIGHT.
I'M GONNA GO UP AND TAKE A REST
NOW.
BE A DEAR AND BRING MY TEA UP IN
30 MINUTES.
[ SIGHS ]
IS IT 30 MINUTES ALREADY?
JUST -- JUST LEAVE IT ON THE
SIDE TABLE.
MM. NOT NOW, MICHAEL.
IT ISN'T EVEN SATURDAY.
BESIDES, YOU HAVEN'T TAKEN A
SHOWER YET.
[ YAWNS ]
JUST LEAVE ME BE.
I'LL BE DOWN SOON.
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
MICHAEL.
I SAID NO.
M--
[ GASPS LIGHTLY ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SNARLS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
HOW CAN ANYONE LIVE OUT IN
THIS?
I DON'T THINK IT'S A QUESTION
OF CHOICE, DOC.
WE DON'T LIKE HIS KIND COMING
NEAR OUR TOWN.
YEAH. RIGHT.
HOW FAR DOES HE LIVE, ANYWAY?
ABOUT 3 MILES PAST THE
OPENING WE JUST CAME THROUGH.
NOT FAR ENOUGH, IF YOU ASK
ME.
SO, IS IT TRUE WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT HIM?
WHAT, CRAZY OLD FOOL?
VOODOO-LOVING FREAK, MORE
LIKE.
WHAT, SO HE KILLS CHICKENS
AND DANCES AROUND, THAT SORT OF
THING?
DOC, YOU START GETTING THE
HEEBIE-JEEBIES, YOU LET US KNOW.
IT'LL JUST MEAN THERE'S SOME
DARK, EVIL MAGIC BEING WORKED ON
YOU.
HEY, YOU KNOW THAT'S
NONSENSE, RIGHT?
SHOULDN'T WE HAVE COME ARMED?
WE FIGHT LIKE REAL MEN, USE
OUR FISTS.
AND LIKE SAM SAID, IT'S JUST
SOME OLD GUY IN A HUT.
BOO!
JESUS!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
SORRY, DOC. COULDN'T RESIST.
CAN WE JUST GET GOING?
YOU ARE LOOKING A LITTLE
SICKLY, DOC.
YOU SURE YOU WANT TO COME WITH
US?
IF HE'S TO BLAME, HE HAS A
CURE.
I'M NOT GONNA LET THAT SLIP
THROUGH MY FINGERS.
OKEYDOKEY.
[ LAUGHS ]
DAMN.
THERE'S NO WAY OUT.
AAH!
AAH! GET OFF!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
GO! GET OUT OF HERE!
GO!
I'M NOT LEAVING YOU!
I'LL BE FINE!
GO!
I'LL SEE YOU!
[ SIGHS ]
SHOULD BE ANOTHER 10-MINUTE WALK
FROM HERE.
FINE, IF THE DOC HERE WOULD
KEEP UP.
YOU THINK HE'S GOT THE VIRUS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M STARTING TO THINK I MIGHT
HAVE A TOUCH OF IT MYSELF.
I MEAN, I PUT IT DOWN TO THE
THRILL OF SHOWING THIS CRAZY
WHAT FOR, BUT I'M STARTING TO
THINK IT'S GETTING A LITTLE
WORSE.
DON'T WORRY. WE'LL HANDLE IT.
JUST LIKE WE DID IN '84.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
ARE WE THERE YET?
ALMOST.
WELL, IF NO ONE OBJECTS, I'M
OFF FOR A CALL OF NATURE.
WHERE'S COLE?
OH, I SEE.
BET HE THOUGHT HE COULD GET A
JUMP ON THE OLD MAN BEFORE WE
GOT THERE.
OKAY.
TWO CAN PLAY AT THAT GAME.
COME ON.
[ COUGHING ]
GOOD. GOOD.
JUST CHEW IT SLOW.
TAKE IT EASY.
CHEW IT SLOW, SON.
WHAT THE HELL?
I BELIEVE YOU OWE US SOME
ANSWERS.
GET OUT OF MY HOUSE!
THIS ISN'T EXACTLY A HOUSE.
WHERE'S COLE?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHO THAT IS.
WE JUST WANT SOME ANSWERS AS
TO WHAT IS GOING ON.
I MEAN, WHY IS EVERYONE GETTING
SICK?
CAN'T YOU SEE I'M TRYING TO
TAKE CARE OF MY GRANDSON?
I TOLD YOU WE DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
RIGHT.
WE KNOW ALL ABOUT YOU
EXPERIMENTING WITH THE DARK
ARTS.
TREAT YOUR OWN GRANDSON LIKE
A GUINEA PIG.
I TOLD YOU, WE DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
LEAVE US ALONE.
Y'ALL DO ENOUGH WITHOUT COMING
OUT HERE SPREADING LIES.
WHAT IS THIS, IF YOU DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT?
I CAN KEEP WHATEVER I WANT IN
MY OWN HOME.
IT'S NOT LIKE COLE NOT TO BE
HERE.
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH HIM?
I SAID, WHERE IS HE?
[ CLICK ]
COLE.
OKAY, NOW, DOCTOR TO DOCTOR,
I KNOW THIS ISN'T SOME ZOMBIE
SUMMONING UP, AS EVERYONE PUTS
IT.
PLEASE LEAVE US ALONE.
I JUST WANT MY GRANDSON TO GET
WELL SO WE CAN LEAVE THIS PLACE,
AND YOU WON'T HAVE TO SEE US
AGAIN.
IS THIS MAKING HIM BETTER?
[ COUGHS ]
YOU'VE GOT IT, TOO.
I HAVE NOTHING.
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE IF I START
TAKING THIS, I'M GONNA FEEL A
WHOLE LOT BETTER.
IT DOESN'T WORK LIKE THAT.
WE'RE GONNA BE BACK, AND
WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT HOW YOU DID
THIS.
EVEN IF WE HAVE TO TEAR THIS
PLACE APART.
[ PANTING ]
SAM! COLE!
HOW THE HELL DO I GET OUT OF
THIS PLACE?!
UNH!
[ WHIMPERING ]
SORRY.
FOR WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
SORRY FOR THE WAY I TREATED YOU
BACK THERE.
SORRY, SAD, AND CONFUSED.
EVERY TIME I THINK WE'RE CLOSE
TO GETTING OUT OF HERE, SOMEONE
I CARE ABOUT DIES.
I HAVE NO ONE LEFT TO FEEL
SAD ABOUT.
HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
YOU LED US HERE.
FUNNY.
I MEAN, HOW DID YOU GET TO THIS
TOWN?
I'VE BEEN HERE FOR FOUR
YEARS.
I GUESS YOU JUST NEVER NOTICED.
WOW. SORRY.
YOU CAN STOP SAYING "SORRY,"
YOU KNOW.
SORRY.
OKAY, UM, WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
I'M THE FAMOUS WARD OF THE
MAYOR.
OH, I HEARD HE TOOK IN A
NIECE.
I DIDN'T FIGURE IT WAS YOU,
THOUGH.
TO BE HONEST, YOU DON'T SEEM ANY
RELATION TO THAT STUFFY OLD
FART.
THAT'S A COMPLIMENT.
I'M GLAD YOU TOOK IT THAT
WAY.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER JUST WANTED TO
GET OUT OF THIS PLACE?
AND I DON'T MEAN NOW THAT OUR
FRIENDS ARE BEING CHEWED UP BY
ZOMBIES.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
EVERY DAY.
AND WHEN I CAN GET OUT OF HERE,
I WILL, WITHOUT LOOKING BACK,
BUT I CAN'T TOUCH MY TRUST UNTIL
MY BIRTHDAY.
WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
TOMORROW.
[ SCOFFS ]
WELL, THEN WE BETTER MAKE DAMN
SURE THAT WE GET YOU OUT OF
THESE WOODS SO YOU CAN GO
CELEBRATE WITH A BEER AND I CAN
GO BACK TO MY SISTER.
SOUNDS GOOD.
WHERE IS YOUR SISTER?
SHE'S AT HOME.
SHE'S NOT WELL.
IS SHE, UH...
NO, NO.
I-I JUST NEED TO GET SOME HELP,
AND THEN SHE'LL BE UP AGAIN IN
NO TIME.
[ SIGHS ]
I'M OUT OF THE WOODS.
GO BACK INTO THE WOODS.
JUST MORE AND MORE WOODS.
ONLY IT'S JUST...
DR. TRAVERS?
[ SIGHS ]
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW NICE IT IS
TO FIND SOMEBODY WHO'S OUT HERE,
YOU KNOW, ALIVE.
DANNY.
YOU FEELING OKAY?
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE, UH,
IF YOU'RE IN ANY WAY AFFLICTED
OR NOT FEELING SO HOT, I CAN GO
BACK THE WAY I CAME.
THAT'D BE FINE.
NO.
YEAH.
YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU'RE KIND OF
LOOKING LIKE YOU WANT TO RIP MY
FACE OFF RIGHT NOW.
I'D LIKE TO KEEP IT FOR LATER.
SO YOU CHILL.
YOU HANDLE IT.
YOU HANG OUT.
I'M GONNA GO.
STAY THERE, DR. TRAVERS.
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
COME ON!
DANNY, DUCK!
[ GRUNTS ]
DUCK!
THANK GOD.
I THOUGHT WE'D LOST YOU.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
THERE YOU GO.
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
GLAD YOU'RE ALIVE, THOUGH.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
OH.
I-I GOT LOST.
SO, SO LOST.
UH, FIGHT WITH A ZOMBIE, THOUGH.
YOU MISSED IT.
I'M PRETTY CONFIDENT I WON.
IT WAS GOOD. MESSED HIM UP.
SOUNDS FUN.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
YEAH.
SO, WHERE'S LUCY?
DID SHE FIND HELP?
I NEVER MET HER.
I HEARD SOMETHING ABOUT...
A GIRL CALLED LUCY AND...A BABY
EATING ITS WAY OUT OF HER WOMB
AND THEN A LOT OF BLOOD.
RIGHT.
OKAY, UM, TOM.
DID WE FIND TOM?
THEY'RE BOTH DEAD.
GEEZ.
I'M SORRY.
LOOK, CAN WE NOT TALK ABOUT
THIS RIGHT NOW AND JUST FIND A
WAY OUT OF HERE?
RIGHT. YEAH. OKAY.
UH, WHICH WAY?
I THINK THERE'S A ROAD OVER
THERE.
WE MIGHT BE OKAY NOW THAT
THERE'S THREE OF US.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO DO
ANY RUNNING, I'M AFRAID.
WHAT'S THAT?
PROBABLY NOTHING.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET OUT OF THESE DAMN
WOODS.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU NEED?
WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE AS
FAST AS WE CAN.
DAMN ROTTEN PEOPLE, FORCING
ME OUT OF MY OWN HOME.
GRANDFATHER, IT'S THOSE
THINGS OUT THERE.
IT'S NOT THE PEOPLE.
THEM AND THEIR BACKWARDS
WAYS.
I HOPE THEY GET EVERYTHING THEY
GOT COMING TO THEM.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN PUTTING YOUR
CURSES ON THEM, HAVE YOU?
I THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T BELIEVE
IN WHAT I DO.
YOUR MOTHER CERTAINLY DOESN'T
APPROVE.
RIGHT NOW, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I BELIEVE IN.
ALL I KNOW IS I ATE UP THAT
MAN'S GERMAN SHEPHERD, AND IT
TASTED GOOD.
AND THAT AIN'T RIGHT.
I NEVER MEANT FOR YOU TO GET
HURT.
DID YOU DO THIS?
IT'S LIKE YOU SAID BEFORE.
IT'S ALL JUST NONSENSE.
I NEED MY TOTEM FROM THE OLD
TREE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING BACK OUT
THERE.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
LOOK, LET'S JUST GET TO THE
TRUCK AND GET ON THE ROAD.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I NEED IT. IT PROTECTS US.
LOCK THE DOOR BEHIND ME.
I'LL BE BACK IN 20 MINUTES.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, IF I NEVER SET FOOT
IN THESE WOODS AGAIN, I WILL BE
A HAPPY MAN.
LOOK, WE NEED TO HURRY.
GOD KNOWS IF EMMA'S STILL SAFE.
LOOK...
KARA, THE ME AND KATE THING --
JUST LEAVE IT.
WE SHOULD BE BACK AT THE ROAD
BY NOW.
I'LL GO AHEAD AND SEE HOW FAR WE
ARE.
YOU CAN'T GO OFF ON YOUR OWN.
WELL, WE'RE GETTING NOWHERE
FAST WITH DANNY HERE GOING AS
SLOW AS A LEGLESS TURTLE.
UH...[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE FUNNY.
YOU'RE VERY FUNNY.
MAYBE SHE'S RIGHT.
WE'VE BEEN WALKING FOR AN HOUR
NOW AND STILL NO ROAD.
MAYBE IF SHE GOES ON AHEAD, WE'D
BE CLOSE TO FINDING A WAY OUT OF
HERE.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
JUST BE SAFE.
AND BE QUICK.
OKAY, HOW DO WE KNOW IF SHE'S
COMING BACK?
WE DON'T.
WHICH IS WHY I KNOW WHERE WE
NEED TO GO.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
I SAW THESE AT THE
WITCH DOCTOR'S CABIN WHEN I WAS
THERE WITH LUCY.
HE MUST KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THE VOODOO MAN?
DON'T YOU START.
WHAT? WHAT DID I SAY?
NEVER MIND.
LOOK, WE NEED TO GET SOME
ANSWERS, AND WE NEED TO GET SOME
HELP FOR EMMA.
OKAY, AND TEEN ANGST, ANGRY
JESSICA, WE'RE JUST GONNA --
WE'RE GONNA LEAVE HER OUT HERE?
I'M SORRY, DANNY.
I NEED TO GET SOME HELP FOR
EMMA.
AND I'M NOT WAITING AROUND HERE
FOR THOSE ZOMBIES TO COME AND
ATTACK US.
BESIDES, IF YOU WERE HER AND
YOU FLAGGED DOWN A CAR, WOULD
YOU COME BACK?
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
BUT IF HE TRIES TO EAT MY
BRAINS, THAT IS ON YOU, OKAY?
I'M NOT GONNA BE NICE!
[ SIGHS ]
STOP! STOP!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH AN ORDEAL.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
WHERE TO?
I'M NOT SURE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET ANYWHERE
QUICK IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE GOING.
I HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M GOING TO THE CITY.
YES.
YES WHAT?
I WANT TO GO TO THE CITY.
OKAY, THEN.
DO YOU HAVE A CELLPHONE?
I NEED TO GET SOME HELP FOR MY
FRIEND.
I DO, BUT IT'S NOT GONNA DO
YOU ANY GOOD.
I HAVEN'T HAD ANY SIGNAL FOR
ABOUT 5 MILES NOW.
ARE YOU OKAY?
ANYTHING I CAN DO?
NO, I'M...YEAH.
I NEED TO GET SOME HELP FOR MY
FRIENDS.
I-I'M SURE THEY'RE OKAY.
I GUESS WE CAN MAKE A CALL WHEN
WE GET CLOSER TO THE CITY.
SO WHAT BRINGS YOU OUT HERE?
[ ZIPPING ]
GREAT, JASON.
WE CAN GET GOING.
PLEASE, WE NEED YOUR HELP.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO LEAVE
ME ALONE.
KARA, THIS GUY IS A KOOK.
HOW IS HE GONNA HELP US?
WE NEED TO GET BACK ON THE ROAD.
I KNOW DR. TRAVERS WAS HERE,
AND HE TOOK THIS.
WHAT IS IT?
KARA?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
JASON?
THIS IS YOUR GRANDFATHER?
JASON, YOU KNOW THIS GIRL?
THEY WERE JUST LEAVING.
PLEASE, JASON, WE NEED TO
KNOW WHAT THIS IS.
IT'S NOTHING.
LOOK, EITHER YOU HAVE ANSWERS
OR YOU DON'T HAVE ANSWERS.
JUST TELL US, AND WE'LL BE ON
OUR WAY.
PLEASE.
WE HAVE TO HELP THEM.
WE CAN'T LET THEM JUST GO OUT
THERE WITH THOSE THINGS RUNNING
AROUND.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
THOSE THINGS THAT YOU PROBABLY
MADE.
WHAT, DO YOU GOT A MAGIC WAND IN
THE BACK?
JUST WAVE IT AROUND A LITTLE
BIT.
POOF.
SCREW THE WHOLE TOWN?
DANNY, NOT HELPING.
LIKE I SAID, NO.
LOOK, KARA IS A GOOD PERSON.
SHE'S NOT LIKE THOSE PEOPLE IN
TOWN.
PLEASE.
WE CAN TRUST HER.
THIS IS ON YOU.
I KNOW.
SHE'S BEEN GOOD TO ME, AND IT'S
ABOUT TIME THAT WE PUT THIS HATE
BEHIND US.
BESIDES, THEN WE CAN LEAVE TOWN
AND NEVER LOOK BACK.
THE BLOOD IN THAT VIAL
CONTAINS AN ANTIDOTE.
I CAN'T GUARANTEE THAT IT'LL
WORK FOR YOU.
BUT IT HEALED MY GRANDSON.
WHAT DO I DO WITH IT?
YOU MIX IT WITH FOOD AND
INGEST IT.
IN 48 HOURS, IT'LL TAKE FULL
EFFECT.
OKAY. OKAY, GOOD. GOOD.
WHERE'S THE REST OF IT?
THAT'S IT!
THAT'S ALL I HAVE.
BUT YOU COULD MAKE MORE.
YOU GOT WHAT YOU WANT!
NOW LEAVE US!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING MY SISTER.
KARA, WE'RE GONNA NEED MORE
OF THAT STUFF.
WHAT IF YOU NEED IT?
WHAT IF I NEED IT?
WELL, THEN LET'S PRAY THAT WE
DON'T.
THEY CAN AT LEAST GIVE US A
RIDE IN THE TRUCK.
CAN WE?
LOOK, THEY'D BE A LOT SAFER IF
THEY DROVE WITH US.
I'VE DONE MORE THAN ENOUGH
FOR THEM.
NOW TELL THEM TO LEAVE THIS
HOUSE, OR I'M GONNA PUT SOME
REAL BLACK MAGIC ON THEM.
OH. OOH.
I'M SORRY. I...
I HOPE YOU MAKE IT TO YOUR
SISTER IN TIME.
KEEP SAFE.
YOU TOO.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
THAT'S IT?
IT'S -- THERE'S NO WAY TO APPEAL
THAT OR ANYTHING?
JUST COURT ADJOURNED.
PFF!
WOW.
[ SNIFFLES ]
THESE BEADS ARE STUPID.
THANK YOU.
LIKE I TOLD THEM, THERE'S NO
GUARANTEE THAT I'LL WORK.
DON'T THANK ME JUST YET.
[ PIANO PLAYING SLOWLY ]
[ PIANO PLAYING QUICKLY ]
[ SIGHS ]
PLEASE, PLEASE GET BETTER.
AND YEAH.
AWESOME.
[ CHUCKLES ]
All: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
HAPPY MY BIRTHDAY!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
I'M A REALLY LUCKY GIRL TO
HAVE SUCH A WONDERFUL BOYFRIEND
LIKE DANNY AND TO SPEND HIS
SPECIAL DAY WITH HIM, AND I'M
REALLY LOOKING FORWARD TO
EATING.
OKAY, FINE. I'M ON IT.
LUCY!
SORRY.
WELL, HERE WE HAVE SOME
LOVELY FOOD.
WHAT?
OKAY, I'M REALLY HAPPY TO BE
HERE, CHILLING BY THE LAKE FOR
DANNY'S BIRTHD-- [ GASPS ]
LUCY!
SORRY.
All: ♪ ...TO YOU
NOW, HERE WE GO. READY?
MAKE A WISH.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
MAKE IT A GOOD ONE.
WHOO!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DANNY.
I HOPE YOU HAVE A GREAT DAY.
AND I HOPE YOU GET LAID 'CAUSE
IT'S PROBABLY BEEN A WHILE,
RIGHT?
UM, AND ALSO I REALLY HOPE YOU
GET A NEW CAR, 'CAUSE YOURS IS A
PIECE OF CRAP.
WHAT THE HELL?!
SORRY!
UGH!
GET IT!
I'LL GET IT.
YOU WILL NOT GET IT!
DANNY!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
[ DOG BARKING ]
ripped by HD4FUN.COM