- Art Subs -
Subtitles
- othelo -
Would you still love me
if I couldn't pay for dinner?
Possibly.
Yeah...
What do we do?
I'm thinking.
We can have a big row.
And throw some shit,
they might kick us out.
Been done, I don't want
to draw too much attention.
- What are you doing?
- I'm taking my shoes off.
I'm going to leave first...
and then when the time is right,
like when the maître d'
is not looking,
you meet me down the street.
Excuse me, sir.
Hey, run!
Run, run, run!
Oh, fucker!
- Baby, are you okay?
- I'm dying.
- Do we lose him?
- I don't know.
Really, I don't think
he even chase us.
- Hey.
- What?
Hey-hey-hey, look-look-look.
Look at them.
- This is pretty good, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
- Hey.
- What?
There is only one heart
in this body.
Have mercy on me.
Shut up.
Hey!
Ms. Ludlow, are you ready?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Can I... does it kind of hurt?
- No, it's fine.
This is all your stuff?
Let me...
Are you sure?
- Nice meeting you.
- Yeah, have a great day.
- Ça Va la vie d'El?
- Ça Va.
Where's Philip?
He's asleep.
He's exhausted.
- What should I do?
- Just put it somewhere.
I closed
your wireless account.
Thanks.
What do you want to do
with all your stuff in the city?
You've got some clothes here
in the closet,
and I have some more stuff
in the attic if you want.
I'm sure that will do fine.
Just like old times.
Hey, daddy.
So what happens now?
I'm guessing you give
a speech of some sort?
What do you want to do, El?
Something else.
I'm open to ideas.
You could take some classes.
Can we talk about it later?
What about Conor?
- Auntie El.
- Hi!
- Missed you.
- I missed you.
- What did you guys do today?
- Chasing butterflies.
- I "catched" one.
- You did?
Let's give her some time
to get settled in, okay, baby?
- Bye, honey.
- Bye.
- Do you need anything?
- No, thank you.
I'm riding to town in a bit.
Wanna join? Get out?
Yeah, you yell up at me
when you're going?
That's brutal, man.
Maybe she wants you
to go after her.
No, she doesn't.
Maybe wait a couple of days
and go after her?
Stu, don't.
Well, I guess...
- When someone flirts with extinction...
- Shut the fuck up.
Okay, I'm sorry,
I don't know what to say.
- What am I supposed to say?
- You don't have to say anything.
Just shut up, drink,
and talk about the weather.
Hey, the dude at table 2
said he's gonna kick your ass
if he doesn't get
his chicken satay soon.
- Tell him he can suck my balls.
- You should tell him that yourself.
Table 2?
I'll deal with it.
- Hey, we're out of beer.
- How can we be out of beer?
We've got two boxes
back there, go and...
You don't throw shit in my place, man.
What's your problem?
- Where's our fucking food, man?
- Listen, don't threaten my chef.
- Calm down.
- Don't tell me to calm down.
If you threaten my chef again I will
drop kick you out of the fucking door.
- Are you kidding me?
- Come on...
Stu!
Hey, Conor...
- Get the fuck out!
- Fuck you!
Fuck you, man.
What a nice comeback, very nice.
Get out of here you too.
Get out.
Did you get
your stupid sunglasses too?
Fuckhead.
You have reached a number
that is no longer in service.
Please check the number and try
your call again. Thank you.
- Hello?
- Mary?
- Yes?
- It's Conor.
Is El there?
Hello?
Hey.
I thought I could...
I thought I could
stay here for a little bit.
Hi, Ralph.
You know where
the guest bedroom is?
Yep.
There's towels in that closet
in the hallway,
not much in the fridge.
Got some Cheerios.
That's fine, I mean, I can go
get some stuff, that's easy.
Well, I've gotta head
to the restaurant.
- Okay.
- Good night.
Good night.
Wow, hey. Hey, El!
- Hey.
- Hey, Stu.
- How are you?
- You remember of my dad?
Hey.
- How are you?
- Good, thanks.
- You are the chef.
- Yeah, I'm the chef.
Alright...
- How is the restaurant?
- Good.
Yeah, it's going good.
It's going really well.
- El, you have to register.
- We have to head off.
Alright, I gotta get this back
to the restaurant.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
Hey, if you ever wanna get
coffee or something...
you know,
shoot me a text or call me.
- Okay.
- Good seeing you.
So Lilian is expecting you.
- She and I were colleagues at NYU.
- I know, you told me.
You have...
- Pencils and notebooks and all that?
- Yes, dad.
I have class and...
I have patients.
So I guess I'll...
- See you at your house later at night.
- Okay.
- El...
- Yeah?
- Have a good first day.
- I will.
- How's the weather down there?
- Balmy.
- Do you have an appointment?
- I'm Eleanor Rigby.
That must be tough.
I'm here to talk my way
into your Identity Theory class.
Oh, you're Julian's kid.
I need some caffeine,
are you walking the walk with me?
Okay.
So is Julian
into the Beatles or something?
- Sort of.
- What you mean, "sort of"?
He met my mom
on the street,
during one of the
Beatles hoaxed reunions.
There was a rumor
they were gonna play a show here
before Lennon died, just like the one
they did in the rooftop in London.
My parents stood next
to each other,
waiting for the band
that never showed.
Nostalgies.
That and my dad's surname
is Rigby.
- You must detest the Beatles.
- No, not really.
You want something?
Double espresso,
three Splendas, please.
So why do you wanna be
in my class?
Your course sound interesting.
And, look...
You are a colleague of my dad, so...
Well, you gotta do better
than that.
- You want me to make something up?
- Well, most people do.
You're just taking classes
just to take classes, right?
- Something like that.
- Well, let me save you some time.
All the perpetual students
that hedge fund wives
in your generation
of too many choices
they usually go
to Tim Gunn's class
listen to him talk
about Project Runway.
Or you can take
the Art History class
on the advent
of color photography
just for a good
cocktail party conversation.
"My generation
of too many choices"?
Democracy has its drawbacks.
- Double espresso, three Splendas.
- Thank you.
You're teaching classes
just to teach classes, right?
Something like that.
I'm having a month.
I'm sorry.
Your father didn't give me much warning
or tell me much about you.
And I'm really not one
for nepotism.
I just got the call asking
if I could squeeze you into a class.
So I don't really know
who you are.
It's okay.
Neither do I.
- You want to help me?
- Are you making honeys?
With summer vegetables and...
and some basil.
You remember when you
first had them, in Le Baron?
No?
You were 4.
And you were so fat.
My mother and I would cook
a big plate of them
and leave that
on the kitchen table.
And you would eat one and the other...
until the plate was completely empty.
You went to nursery school
that fall.
And all these women gave me
was weird looks and...
they were wondering
what I was feeding you with.
- I was a butterball.
- I felt completely stupid.
Like I had no idea what I was doing,
the way those women looked at me.
- Did you?
- Did I what?
Did you know
what you were doing?
I think I didn't realise
I wouldn't be able to retrieve
all the opportunities
that there were then.
You're not the only one
who has done stupid things to herself.
My darling.
I have no clue where she's gone.
She turns off her cell phone
and like that she's vanished.
Does that make sense to you?
- No, Conor.
- Come on, knock it off.
No, no, I'm like, you know...
How'd you call that? I plead the fifth.
I tried to be helpful, I pretended,
but it didn't workout.
It's not gonna be of help.
Look, I realise that I've been
a little off-balance lately,
but I think with hindsight
I'm learning to deal with it better.
- A couple of weeks counts as hindsight?
- Fucking A, Stu.
I've got nothing for you.
Come on, come on...
I'm just asking a simple question.
You don't have to candy cover it
like you're gonna hurt my feelings...
but did you see
this coming?
Look,
with the exception of my dog,
I haven't slept next to the same person
for more than 2 or 3 days in a row,
so I don't know
what I'm gonna say
that is gonna be relevant
to your situation.
I opened a restaurant
for you, asshole.
No, you opened
a restaurant for you, asshole.
And according to the Village Voice
it's a bar with uninspired food.
Whatever, look... I'm simply asking
for my best friend's opinion.
Even if it is
an uninformed piece of crap.
Okay.
"We are young
Heartache to heartache
we stand
No promises,
no demands
Love is a battlefield"
- Pat Benatar.
- You're a fucking idiot.
I feel like I walk
on eggshells around you.
You know, I...
I tried to talk to you
about this for months...
- I'm not talking about that.
- This is what I'm talking about, man.
I don't know how to be
your friend anymore.
You're no fucking picnic.
Look, I saw her
the other day.
You what?
- Saw her.
- Where?
- Astor Place.
- Did you talk to her?
- No.
- You didn't talk to her?
She was far away, walking away,
going to class or something.
Class?
- Yeah, she had book bag with her.
- What school?
NYU or Cooper Union or...
I don't know,
it's not hard to find out.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I just did.
- What are you guys talking about?
- You.
Okay?
I'm not here to approve...
or disapprove,
just so you know.
Your mother always gave me crap
for never stepping up to the plate.
Okay, what?
She sad I never stepped up.
I'm sorry, what does that
have to do with anything?
Well, you are
a bit like me.
No, I'm fucking not.
I stepped up.
Okay.
- So what else?
- Nothing.
Nothing, we don't have
to keep talking.
Yeah, but you are the one
who came into the room.
Yeah, to turn down
your stupid music.
Everyday I do one thing
that makes me happy.
Right? One thing,
and that is either...
listen to my stupid music
or read this stupid paper.
And that is the best way
I found to deal with myself.
So just go...
back to the guestroom
and count the fucking raindrops.
Count
the fucking raindrops?
I was never very good
at this kind of thing.
Okay...
It isn't your job to...
investigate the expansive memory
that is called "the past"
and judge what is right
and what isn't.
Seriously, what the fuck
are you talking about.
You shouldn't be interested
in regretting things.
I'm not.
Let's do this.
"Intuitive answer
to this question.
At bottom,
the sense of Self corresponds
to that experience
of ownership...
and impenetrability
of one's thoughts,
of one's
internal dialogues,
affective states...
that many but not all of us
have from infancy."
Can I borrow
a piece of paper and a pen?
Please.
Thanks, and a pen?
I'll give it back.
"... solitude that Descartes
had in mind
when he redefined the concepts
of subject and subjectivity."
_
"The faculty of knowing lies
within the subject...
in his head,
and the subject...
has such a status by dint
of being enclosed within himself..."
Hi again.
Would you mind passing this
to the girl with the red hair?
C'mon, please.
Thanks a lot,
don't forget your pen.
Right here, thank you.
"... strange behaviour
is signaled by tapping
one's forehead
with one's forefinger?"
Boy, I'm learning something.
"'Why the Mind is in the Head'
is the title of one of the lectures
delivered
at a 1951 symposium."
Hey.
"One of the most authoritative voices
in this chorus is Ken Gergen's,
who asks the question:
'can we compellingly re-inscribe
what it is to be a person
in a way that moves us away
from the individualist premise...
and toward the relational?'"
Hey!
- Hey, Rigby.
- What the fuck are you doing?
I barely got a chance to respond
before you went AWOL.
- What did I ask you, Conor?
- Just give me a second of talk.
- What the fuck did I ask you?
- Just give me goddamn a second.
I've given you plenty of seconds!
Do me a favor, leave me the fuck alone.
Fine, you do what you gotta do.
You can just keep fucking...
Conor!
Oh, shit.
- Conor?
- You know this guy?
He's my husband.
Well, that was exciting.
Yeah, it was awesome.
So, you're back to school?
I'm taking some classes.
I almost didn't recognize you.
What do you mean?
It's just your hair.
It's really pretty.
Where are you living, El?
None of your business.
Was that what you so desperately
needed to talk to me about?
No.
What is it then?
I was gonna say
something good.
Something that would've...
solved all our problems
and made everything all better,
but, you know what?
I forgot what it was.
- That is too bad.
- Ain't it?
- I'm gonna go.
- No...
All I want...
Is a chance to talk it out.
And after that
you can disappear.
Wherever it is
you disappear to.
Ready, sir?
Damn.
Yeah, I was born ready.
Nice and easy.
Watch your step.
I'll see you around.
All right, watch your head
coming up.
- Got him?
- I got him.
Take it easy.
- Put your arm here for me.
- Okay.
Can I keep stalking you?
Are you awake?
Auntie El, are you awake?
No, Philip.
Your eyes are open.
Apparently.
Why do you have
your shoes on in bed?
Morning, sunshine.
I was making french toast.
- All right, I'll be right down.
Okay.
Came in late last night.
What's with the feast?
We have a special guest star.
Outside.
Well, it's been hard.
There is a barrier...
Good morning.
- No fucking way.
- El.
You sandbagged me.
He chose
the Psychology Department.
Good for him.
Well, I just thought he'd be
a bit more qualified...
to deal with your circumstance.
What's my circumstance?
He was my grandson.
I lost him too.
None of us know
how to help you.
Well, neither do I.
So glad they delegated
the speech to you.
He's not a stranger...
that some hospital referred you to,
he's a colleague of mine.
I don't think one session
a week would hurt.
Why can't you talk to me
once a week, dad?
Why outsource it?
I'm not outsourcing it,
and I don't really think
you wanna talk
to me about it.
I don't need to talk
to another therapist.
Eleanor...
Please, stop reminding me
that something is wrong.
That's not my intention.
Then please let me stop
thinking about it.
Tragedy is a foreign country.
We don't know how to talk
to the natives.
What are you talking about?
You know, there's this
really cool thing called chairs.
Yeah, I've heard about those.
It's actually
not too shabby down here.
You're okay?
- Sure.
- Liar.
Sure.
- When is your next class?
- It's yours.
You like hamburgers?
I used to be a vegan...
Mostly 'cause my husband
was a vegan.
Not that I don't agree with most
of the tenets of vegan ideology, but...
He was one of those
reformed socialists
who seemed sexy before
the 60's started to fade.
Does he teach?
He won tenure at University
of Oregon, I got it here.
He was soft, I stayed hard.
That was it.
- You've kids?
- A son.
I'm not sure why
people have kids.
First there's the 9 months
of agony...
your body hurts, it's hot, it's cold,
you crave pickles and...
there's no words to describe
whatever fuck the labor is.
Then this little stranger
comes out,
sucking every bit of
life you have left in you,
and as soon as you are ready
to jump out of the window...
all of a sudden he smiles.
Jesus Christ, this is good.
And whatever you do,
however you do it...
however you imagine your child's life,
what kind of parenting you did,
29 years later he is
in some shrink office,
accusing you
of some stupid thing
that you said or did
that for the life of you
you can't remember
saying or doing.
Tell me that, at your age, you're not
taking classes out of boredom.
I don't know
what the hell I'm doing.
What was before this?
Life in general.
Any kids?
- Boy or girl.
- Boy.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Who was that man that chased you
out of my classroom the other day?
He went soft, I stayed hard,
that was that.
- Well, it's been real, everybody.
- No, it hasn't.
Hey! Goddamn it.
Slow night?
A couple of people came in
to use the bathroom.
How are we doing?
Well, aside from being
an endangered species?
- Not so good.
- Can you translate that for me, please?
Friday night. This is the only night
we're making any money.
I have missing bills
and we can't cover the overhead.
- I see.
- Yeah.
You got a plan B?
Burger King?
Seriously? Come on,
I wanna show you something.
- This is the spreadsheet...
- No, I can't.
You got protection?
- Viagra?
- Please, be quiet.
- You want me...
- Shut your mouth.
- My what?
- Shut up.
Dude, I'm being serious,
shut up. I believe.
- In what?
- Higher power, can you hear it?
Not right now.
- Later.
- Bye.
- You guys have fun.
- You know, I got a plan B.
- Do you?
You know, you can
get out of here.
I was thinking about getting
my real estate license.
What?
Why would you
do something like that?
'Cause it seems more impressive
than pouring drinks.
Does it? What happened
to your life in the arts?
That will probably faze it into a...
Sunday afternoon hobby kind of thing.
You?
Plus, I think it's kind of indecent
to have things so worked out
that they wind up exactly
like you thought they would.
Are you gonna be okay?
Probably.
We're living a world
full of probablys.
Well, I'm a decent listener...
if you ever want to talk
about whatever.
Talking about
whatever is overrated,
I prefer to see the things stew
inside of me and then have a violent...
Why did you do that for?
Just seemed like the next
interesting thing to do.
- I'm kind of married.
- I don't mind.
I cannot do.
- There's nobody looking.
- You know, in another life...
We shouldn't do this.
When was the last time
that you got laid properly?
Fuck, I can already taste
the regret.
Stop thinking,
because it's unhealthy for you.
- Alexis...
- Yes.
- Tomorrow is gonna be awkward.
- Probably.
I'm sorry.
- I wasn't expecting you.
- No, no, no.
I wasn't
expecting me either.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Is she here?
No.
Is she living here?
- Do you want to come in for a second?
- Will that be all right?
Yeah, come in.
Can I ask
how she's doing?
I don't know,
to be completely honest.
As good as she can be.
Do I seem like
a different person to you?
Do you feel
like a different person?
I kind of.
You look the same to me.
You know I didn’t like you
when Eleanor first brought
you out here for dinner.
However long ago it was...
- How long ago was it?
- Seven years.
- Seven years!
- Yeah.
You sat there in the exact same spot
seven years ago.
With a glass of water because you were
afraid of having a drink in front of me.
This obnoxiously
perfect kid
who walked off with my
daughter's attention.
- You grew on me, though.
- Oh, well.
It's true.
Look I...
I don’t want to interfere
with her life...
or whatever she has to do,
but I can't just chalk this
up to destiny.
I walked on
with my life because...
moving forward
was the only way to go.
I guess people grieve
differently.
I'd wish to be some appropriate,
articulate thing to say, but...
I just wanted
the mundane daily bullshit back.
I think Eleanor wanted
something else.
And I think that...
there was nothing appropriate
about any of this.
Hey!
Guess what.
- What?
- I got asked on a date.
- I feel fat.
- Katy, shut up.
You are not fat.
That's gorgeous.
Goddammit!
Excuse me?
Hey, come in here.
What was that?
This keeps breaking off.
Okay, but we don't
say that, lovie.
- Why?
- 'Cause it's not a nice thing to say.
Are you sure
that you're okay to watch him?
Mom and dad
should be back pretty soon.
He's here.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm positive!
- Let's...
- Change, right?
So what do you wanna do?
What do you wanna do?
Can I get electrocuted
by lightening bugs?
No, they're harmless.
This song is horrible.
- It's not good.
- No, it's not.
I think that bad music
turns you on.
Seriously.
Wow, car, car!
Do this thing!
I don't want them to see
your thang-thangs.
Okay, we're good.
- Help me.
- What?
You know what you're doing?
You're stupid!
- Here you go, shall I do it?
- Yeah.
Okay, this is kinda
counter-intuitive.
I think I'm instinctually wired
not to be able to do this.
Yeah...
3, 2, 1. Just like that.
- You look good!
- Very impressed.
Do we have
to listen to this?
- Hey!
- You want it? You want it?
- Pop?
- What? No.
- Country?
- No!
- Can I have some?
- You got.
Baby...
As comfortable as this is,
I'm losing circulation
in my legs.
- What are you trying to say?
- That you're fat.
And I love
every pound of you.
Come here.
- Have you seen my shirt, El?
- I put it at the back seats.
- Where are you going?
- On here.
You coming?
Yeah!
- Where are we?
- Someplace good.
All the things
you said to me
I was so obsessed
You were always talking,
talking
God I did my best
Heaven is cold
Without any soul
Amazing.
I was so in love with you
It's hard to believe
It went that badly?
I could have given him
a normal kiss of good night
instead of jamming my tongue
down his throat.
- So he's cool?
- I'm so fucked...
- You had a little drink tonight?
- Yeah.
What's that?
Philip gave it to me
so I wouldn't be afraid of the dark.
Still having trouble
with that?
Yeah, I guess so.
Come on.
Were you okay with him?
Yeah.
Oh, I don't mean...
That's not what I was...
- I just...
- I'm okay.
- Is it okay to be okay?
- Yeah, be okay all you want.
Are you really okay?
I can pretend.
All of a sudden
I kind of miss him.
Who?
Conor.
He came by the house
the other day.
He talked with mom...
and she told me
not to tell you.
- I'm sorry, Katie.
- What for?
I feel like I just dropped in
on you guys
and I sucked all the air
out of the room.
You were
kind of a selfish bitch.
Hey!
You don't have to be
so honest.
- I was really mad at you.
- I know.
- I'm still really mad at you.
And you pulled the floorboards out
from under Conor.
He threw Cody's stuff
into the closet.
And then 10 minutes later
he ordered Chinese.
I tried for six months.
We were million of miles away
in the same room and...
I started to think thoughts
I'd never thought I'd have.
How have you and mom
made it this far?
I'm not sure.
Endurance?
Everyone starts out
thinking this is forever.
Then things get hard.
At some point or another.
And then other things don't pan out
the way you thought they would.
I suppose the trick is
not running for the hills
even when you think
it's the most rational thing to do.
I don't know.
- I hate this room.
- I've seen worse.
- Where?
- Huh?
Where have you seen worse?
- NYU, Yale...
- Yale is butt-ugly.
New Haven's butt-ugly.
Did you attend any
of those fine institutions?
NYU. And then I grew up
at Yale, my dad was there.
Of course,
you were a faculty brat.
You and my son would get along
like cupcakes.
Not that I'm trying
to set you up or anything.
He lives in Washington State.
He's been pretending to write
a novel there for the last 4 years.
Learned anything
interesting in NYU?
- I abandoned in dissertation.
- Bold!
- What department?
- Anthropology.
Sociolinguistic?
I was writing an ethnography
on the social world
of performance artists of Paris.
Musicians, dancers,
actors, etc.
Why?
I don't know, my mom is
a musician and she's french, so...
I mean,
why did you abandon it?
Don't tell me something
stupid like love.
You're very talkative.
- I'm more fond of listening to you.
- You'll get over that.
I got pregnant.
Oh, that.
Come on, wake up.
Wake up.
Mais, qu'est-ce
que t'as foutu?
What?
I went into your room
to check about you
and you were gone
and the car was gone.
- Yeah, I went for a drive.
- Well, don't ever do it again.
Why were you
checking on me?
I've always checked on you.
You're feeling
a bit dramatic today?
No, why?
I played
second violin on this.
Boston Symphony,
Zach Proman.
I haven't forgotten.
No, I was
just reminding myself.
What?
I never wanted
to be a mother.
Not much you can do
about that now...
Yeah, it's too late.
I was too young
when I had you.
- I was the baby.
- Why are you telling me this?
I'm telling you this because
I don't want to lie to you.
I don't want you to take
our relationship too personally.
I don't.
- No.
- Give me my wine!
Why didn't you tell me Conor came
by the house the other day?
Run for your life, El.
What is that supposed
to mean?
Well, this is all too realistic,
run away for a while.
You're sure
you're not projecting?
Yes, I'm sure
I'm not projecting.
You liked
your semester in Paris,
so why don't you go back there
and finish your dissertation?
You could write in cafes...
read Le Monde, Elisa Hawke.
Eat bread.
Make eyes with strangers.
Yeah, I could.
So why are you still here?
I don't know.
- I don't get it man.
- Let's hope you get it.
Well, your...
Well, your dad is like
a culinary maverick,
he's like the Mick Jagger
of the restaurant game.
All you gotta do is make one
phone call and that saves our asses,
but instead...
you want us to drown like 90%
of the other restaurants in the city.
- I don't get it.
- Stu...
What did he do?
- What you mean?
- Your dad, what did he do?
At least take a page out
of his book, what did he do?
- He married my mom.
- What's that mean?
It means he married my mom.
She gave him all the money
that our family left her
and he opened
the restaurant,
it was a big success,
then he dropped her like a bad habit.
So, you know what?
Why don't you go and find yourself
some lonely loaded ol'lady
and then we can take it
from there.
I'd rather fail
catastrophically than...
give him the satisfaction of thinking
he handed me my life in a platter.
That is the stupidest thing
in the history of stupid things.
Why is that stupid?
You know what is stupid?
You think I'm gonna call my dad
and he's gonna go like:
"Hey, son. Why don't you come
and bring your friends?"
- "They can work here too".
- Yeah.
It’s not like a fucking
slumber party.
- I was not... It's a job!
- Stu...
- As decent a cook you are...
- I'm a chef.
All right, chef.
You don't exactly cut it
in those kitchens.
Oh, relax, you don't wanna
have this conversation.
You know, let's talk about it.
When was the last time
you joined in the care?
- Seriously.
- Really wanna have this conversation?
When was the last time you cooked
and egg and you didn't plunge the yolk?
In all kind of kitchens
in that world you would be a busboy.
- You fuckhead, fucking failure.
- No, I'm telling you.
Stupid fucking...
Like that?
You'll hit me
with a fucking kale?
That all you got?
Come on.
Oh, God. Jesus.
Okay, yeah.
This is what you want?
Is that a joke?
No, I think they're
really going at it.
We're not quite open yet.
I was third in my class...
at the New York Academy
of Culinary Arts, you fuckhead.
I know that, asshole.
I'm a chef.
Hey...
I love
our little set up here.
I do.
It's just the lease has gotten
prohibitively expensive
and unless you want
to camp out in the kitchen...
Yes, I would.
I'll bring the sleeping bags.
It's just time to let go.
- Time to grow up.
- Hey, I'm growing up.
- I am.
- Fine.
When do we call it quits?
End of next week.
Can we have one last banger
before we close up shop?
Yeah.
- Can we abuse some heavy narcotics?
- Whatever tickles your thing.
Good.
I'm sorry.
- Blow me.
- Okay.
Yeah, it's amazing.
- Doing well?
- Okay...
Good.
Sorry, it was not a...
Holy shatner.
Nice to see you too, Stuart.
Well, this was nice.
Like old times,
reconnecting and all.
- I'm gonna go to the kitchen.
- Yeah.
I will join you.
Shirley Temple?
Please.
What do I owe you?
Your money is no good here,
you know that.
Okay.
- Business is good?
- It's great.
We're closing.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
Yeah, me too.
- So what's next?
- I don't know.
I thought I might...
develop some interest
in things
that people actually take
an interest in.
You're gonna work
with your dad?
Before you I had
no idea who I was.
Then when we were
together...
I thought I had it all
figured out.
Now I'm just back
to wondering again.
When you figure it out
tell me how, okay?
Okay.
- Let's get out of here.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Right now?
Yeah, that's the idea.
Okay.
Don't forget to fill it up
before you drop it off.
You got it.
- That...
- What are you doing?
You wanna listen to that?
Yeah, suck it up, Ludlow.
Is it gonna rain?
Fuck me!
Of course we get the car
with the retarded wipers.
We could just wait it out.
What are we doing here?
You tell me.
You're the one who said
that we needed to talk,
you stalked me,
you went to my parents house...
What are we doing here?
Just recently,
like an hour ago,
you walked
into my bar and...
you suggested we drive aimlessly
into the perfect fucking storm here.
This is funny.
Yeah.
Yeah,
that's fucking hilarious.
For a while there
I thought we'd actually
pieced together
a pretty decent life.
I have to move everything
out of the apartment next week.
You want me to keep
anything for you?
Where will you move to?
I don't know.
I could stay with my dad
for a little while.
- 'Til I get things figured out.
- How is he?
I'm pretty certain he's losing his mind.
Fernanda left him.
He's getting all talkative...
Waxing philosophical.
Same shit he pulls every time
he's between significant others.
I think it's probably
more than that.
Yes, maybe.
- At least you guys are talking.
- Yeah.
What did tell your parents
about us?
What would I say?
That we're fabulous.
I feel like we're living
some dreadful disaster cliché.
We are.
You're sopping wet.
You noticed! Thank you!
- Wait.
- No, no, no.
No, wait.
Just a second, wait.
Shit.
I slept with someone else.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
What do you mean
it doesn't matter?
- Get off me.
- Don't...
- El, come on.
- Get off.
What do you mean
it doesn't matter?
Get over yourself, Conor.
- You don't care?
- No.
That's bullshit,
I know you care.
El, you're supposed to say:
"What the fuck
were you thinking, Conor?"
You're supposed to say:
"Your selfish piece of shit."
No.
We're past that.
And you just said it
for me.
Come on,
let's go back to the city.
I'm gonna get out of here.
- Ma'am?
- Yes.
Hi.
What a jerk.
And you look like ass.
Thank you.
Where were you last night?
Do you want
to take a load off?
I come here on breaks.
All the librarians advocate
is a whole nap philosophy.
Nap philosophy?
Yes.
One nap to start the day like...
help with productivity and stuff.
If you wanna read this...
What?
I was hoping
you could read my mind.
Wouldn't that be nice?
You know I did something
stupid this weekend?
Yeah, you're queen
of doing something stupid.
What are you thinking?
Deep end.
Take a train to the city.
Save the world.
When did you become
an idealist?
Couple of seconds ago.
I have a date with the dentist
this weekend.
It's okay, I can be
your third wheel.
- Let's get drinks?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'll have a drink.
- Should we get...
- A shot.
- Three shots?
- Tequila.
A round of tequila!
I feel old!
- What?
- I feel...
I feel old!
Me too!
Cheers.
What's your name?
I'm good, thanks!
Wait.
Oh my God.
Wait. No, wait!
What?
What is it?
Yeah.
Did I hurt you?
No.
What is it?
You're a stranger.
So are you.
You ever had that moment
when you...
know you're doing something
stupid but you do it anyway?
Yeah, everyday.
- What? Come on.
- No.
- Come on.
- Stay there.
- I'm gonna go.
- No, don't go.
- Don't.
- Jesus.
Just stay for a minute.
Really?
Sorry.
Where to?
Make a loop
around the city.
Got a destination?
Eventually.
Hey, Phoebe.
- Hey, how are you?
- Good.
- Your hair got long.
- Not really.
He's in his spot.
That's good.
You could make this place
your own if you want.
- And do what you like with it.
- Seriously, like...
I'm done.
Used to be pretty cool
once upon a time.
Some of the same faces
still show up.
Except more wrinkled.
Some are less, though.
Stones went last week
after playing the Garden, but...
mostly, people are
just fading away.
I've been doing this
way too long.
I think you've done
pretty good.
Yeah, well... Complacency
scares the shit out of me.
Yeah?
And how is this: I forfeited
the loan the bank gave me,
I'm losing
the lease of my bar,
Eleanor's gone...
with the fucking wind.
I'm 33 years old,
and my life is
a fucking boat-wreck.
I'm on my sixties,
I lost a grandson
this year,
but I'm basically
forbidden to talk about,
my third wife
just walked out of me,
and I come here
every afternoon
to this restaurant named
after your mother.
- It's time to shoot the crow.
- Where you're gonna go?
You’re gonna fly off
to Never Never Land?
Become a Buddhist?
What are you doing here,
anyway?
I was just
in the neighborhood.
"Just in the neighborhood."
What is it?
Do you ever wonder why
we fall in love with a specific person?
Not really.
I think to myself:
"Something’s wrong here, but I can’t
quite put my finger on what it is."
There's always one
that haunts us.
So give her time.
It's the right thing to do
given the circumstances.
- Circumstances suck.
- Yeah.
I really forbid you
from talking about him?
What the fuck
are you gonna say to me?
Ever since he...
Ever since what happened
happened,
any thought or memory of him
has been something
just to run my mind as far
as fuck away from as I can get...
And that...
A shooting star
only lasts a second.
But...
Aren't you glad that you
at least have seen it?
That's nice.
It's a little Hallmark,
but it's nice.
I mean, it is nice.
You have
a delicate soul, dad.
Nobody's ever said
that to me before.
You know you are
in imminent danger of sappiness?
We can't have that, can we?
- Are you hungry?
- Yes.
- I'll fix you something up.
- Okay.
All the lonely people...
Where do they all come from?
This is the Beatles' song
you were named after.
Three Splendas?
Full service.
Want me to come down there
or you wanna join me in here?
I think I'm gonna leave
your class.
You're breaking up with me.
So this is what
heartbreak feels like.
You never had
your heart broken?
Only read about it
in books.
- Liar.
- Sure.
You don't have to tell me this,
you could have just not shown up.
I just gotta get out
of here.
Here?
The Tri-State Area.
You know they say
that if you...
walk away from things
then you will just...
keep walking away and...
start a whole history
of walkaways.
Did this sound as lame
as I thought it did?
No.
Good, 'cause I don't have
a fucking clue
of how life should
be lived.
Well, could you refer me
to someone who does, please?
Yeah.
I had a dog, Miles.
Got him from a pound.
He did pretty well and lived
every day like he won the lottery.
Where's Miles
when we need him?
Somewhere in Pennsylvania.
Took him on a road trip,
trying to be all travels with Charlie.
As soon as we hit
the open countryside,
he started jumping up and down
like he picked up a scent
or found something
he'd always been looking for.
We let him out...
He hightails it,
chasing the sun in nowhere.
He ran away?
I imagine he's happy
wherever he wind up.
Hooked up
with some Amish people.
- Lives on a diary farm.
- It's possible.
I have a colleague at NYU.
It's from my days I've worked
with your dad there.
Teaches Anthropology
at American University in Paris,
does some work
at the Musée du quai Branly.
I make a phone call...
send him that dissertation
you started on...
Want half a bagel?
- No, I'm good, I'm good.
- You're getting enough to eat?
You're starting
to sound maternal.
That would be a first.
When's the last time
you got to talk to your son?
Some holiday too long ago.
Is it sad
that I don't remember?
Probably.
I should call him,
shouldn't I?
Yes.
Now you sound maternal.
Hello?
With your kiss
my life begins
And like the leaf clings
to the tree
Baby, please, cling to me
We are creatures
of the wind
Wild is the wind
You touch me
I hear the sound
of mandolins
And you kiss me
With your kiss
my life begins
Love me, love me
Say you do
Let me fly away with you
Hey.
Do I seem like
a different person to you?
You look the same to me.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For disappearing.
We'll never get
to where we were.
Where was that?
Someplace good.
Yeah.
Tell me what are
you thinking.
I forgot
what he looked like.
Sometimes I'll get a glimpse
of his eyes or...
the way he'd smile at me
from his crib.
But then it will vanish.
I can't picture his face.
I can't picture
his face anymore.
He was pale.
He frowned a lot.
He had your eyes,
he had your nose,
he had your lips
he had your cheeks.
El, he was all you.
He was the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
I wasn't prepared
for what this feels like.
I know, neither was I.
I love you.
I know.
- How's it coming?
- It's coming.
There was a great cafe,
called "Le Cafe",
at the Rue Tiquetonne,
then a lot of artsy fartsys
to go too,
your mother and I used to go there
when we visited her parents.
We met Jean-Marie Le Clézio
there once.
- Before he won his Nobel.
- Cool.
And you should get...
some of those
big french macarons,
at Ladurée...
in Saint Germain.
Call me when you do...
and I will live
vicariously through you.
I will, thanks.
I lost you
in the ocean once.
What?
I lost you
in the ocean once.
We had rented a house,
in the Ditch Plains Beach,
on Montauk.
We only could afford
Montauk.
You were about 2.
Your mother was pregnant
with Katy.
And I took you down,
swimming, one afternoon.
And a lot of people
down there...
I...
I waited out...
holding you.
Thinking at one point:
"This might not be the best idea."
But you were game.
Or I imagined
that you were game
because you never ever
seemed scared.
About anything.
The Atlantic is moody,
and a big set of waves
knocked in.
We made it
under the first one.
You were clinging
to my neck.
But we got caught
in front of the second...
and I came up without you.
And I have never felt
anything like that.
The throes of stupid
couple seconds...
treading the white water.
And then miraculously I...
felt you at my feet.
I never told your mother.
I never told anyone.
It was the worst
and best moment of my life.
Can I...
- Is this ready?
- Yes.
- I'll be downstairs in a bit.
- Okay.
What you got?
Chardonnay.
It's good, huh?
You know I am
full of shit, right?
Depends on the day.
But you know
that I love you, huh?
Say goodbye
to auntie El, okay?
Okay.
Goodbye, chickadee.
You make sure
that they behave, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, kiss.
What time is it in France?
- It is past your bedtime.
- Why?
Don't be a stranger.
I won't.
I don't wanna go to bed.
There's still light out.
You don't have to go
to bed, sweetie.
Be good, okay?
I'll be back.
When is auntie El
coming back?
She'll be back next summer.
Hey, guys.
Gonna go take a stroll
before the rush, okay?
Okay.
Aren't you worried
about these 15 people
as to how we can deal
with them?
You know how we do this?
We could use the back room.
If every dream
Are ways to be
A way to you
If every clock
Turns back to me
Turn back to you
Still
No fate awaits
Still, without you
Still, no fate awaits me
If every road
Comes back to me
Come back to you
If every road
Comes back to you
Come back to me