♪ Every morning
when the sun comes up ♪
♪ Gonna chase
those blues away ♪
♪ Every morning
when the sun comes up ♪
♪ We're gonna
find the strength to say ♪
♪ Whoa, this is gonna
be my day ♪
Okay, if you're
gonna force me.
(Laughs)
No one's forcing you.
You can stop anytime.
So, Robert,
your latest book's
on top of the bestseller
list, huh?
Yeah, it's
creeping up there.
My agent's really
been pushing it.
Little Sully here could
care less about bestsellers.
Oh, maybe she doesn't read your books,
but the rest of us do.
And I thank you.
Seriously, those books
have helped Julia and I
manage our money.
You should be proud.
To Robert, America's
next financial guru.
To Robert. Pretty soon,
you're gonna have
your own TV show,
syndicated radio program.
No chance of that.
Nothing's gonna pull me
away from my family.
Hey, where did Sarah
run off to?
I haven't seen her since
we sang happy birthday.
I can't
keep track of her.
She's always
running around.
She's probably digging
in her garden.
Well, that's what you get for marrying a girl off the farm.
It's working out pretty
well for me so far.
Hey! Let's take
the boat out!
What is she doing?
I think she wants
to take the boat out.
The dock is rotten.
We're hoping to have it
fixed by next week.
Honey,
get off the dock!
You can hardly wait for
that baby brother, huh?
I'm more excited about
the baby than she is.
That's 'cause
you don't have to carry
the little monster around
for the next nine months.
Captain Robert Benson!
You! Boat! Now!
(Sigh) Looks like I'm
gonna have to run down there
and pull her off
that dock myself.
Captain Robert Benson!
I am getting
in this boat!
(Creaking)
(no audible dialogue)
Woman:
Sarah, Sarah!
Sarah, breathe!
Sarah! Sarah?
Sarah? Sarah?
Please.
Please, Sarah.
Please? Please, God.
Please?
Breathe!
Sarah.
- Oh, God.
- (Coughs)
Okay!
- (Siren)
- Oh, thank God.
(Crying)
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(Beeps)
My word, the recluse!
Robert, what cave
did you crawl out of?
Hello, Debbie.
How's New York?
It's not as healthy
as Storm Lake.
Everything okay?
Well, I'm gonna be late
on the pages.
It'll take me
a couple more days.
Also, I want to cut
the fourth chapter.
I read it last night.
I think it's unnecessary.
I'll pass it along
to the publisher.
Very excited about
the book, Robert.
I think I can help a lot
of people with this one.
Ever the crusader.
Is everything okay
otherwise?
Meaning?
Meaning I am your
oldest friend, Robert.
Clean and sober, Deb.
I'll have the new draft
in a couple of days.
Love you.
(Sighs)
You're gonna love it.
You can't even tell it's organic.
We loved the cookies
you made last week.
Oh, thanks. Maybe
I'll make 'em next week.
He doesn't believe
they're sugarless.
Well, technically,
he's right.
I mean, I use honey,
but it's my own honey.
So there's no refined sugars
in there, I promise.
- Awesome. Thank you.
- Thanks, guys.
Okay. I'm gonna
start packing up.
Thanks, Charlie.
I think we did
really well this week.
Yeah. All the gluten-free
stuff went fast.
Either this town's
getting hip,
or it actually
tastes good.
Or maybe both.
Mm-mm.
This town is not hip.
Mommy!
Hi.
Are you done yet?
Almost. Why?
You know why.
My party.
Party?
Is it your birthday?
Come on!
Do you wanna see one
of your presents now?
Can I?
A bike!
My own bike!
With tassels
and everything.
I thought we said we'd
wait another year.
I know, but all
of her friends have bikes,
and I couldn't resist.
But we've talked
about this.
You know exactly what happens
to her blood sugar level.
Robert, it's her birthday.
Daddy,
isn't it the coolest?
It's the coolest.
Those training wheels
aren't coming off
till you graduate
college, though.
Dad, I'll be an old lady.
Hi, Mr. Benson.
Hey, Charlie.
How'd our local farmers do today?
I don't know about these other hicks,
but we killed it.
Yeah. We almost sold out
of all the pies,
and I sold all my honey.
That's amazing.
Do you need any help?
No, I've got Charlie. It's okay.
You can take her back.
Get her ready
for the party.
I'm sorry
about the bike.
I really
couldn't help it.
And we have to
trust her at some point.
(Sighs)
You're right.
Kids have bikes.
All right, Sully,
let's get ready for your party.
And don't worry.
I got her a helmet,
knee pads.
I also got her
a suit of armor.
Ha ha ha. Very funny.
Bye.
- Bye.
(Squealing)
Guys, slow down!
No running!
The more they run around,
the better they sleep.
I'm gonna be the one
that needs the sleep.
Well, you can't
stop them anyway,
so live
and let live, I say.
Yeah, tell that
to Robert.
I'm telling you, Julia,
he babies that girl
way more than I do.
He checks her blood sugar
like every five minutes
and doesn't even
trust the test.
Well, he's just scared,
that's all.
Yeah, but I don't know.
Something's different.
Jerry said
he stopped drinking.
Yeah. No, yeah, he did.
I don't know
what he did,
but he hasn't had a drink
in like six months.
Good for him.
Yeah. I think
it's the day, too.
You know, he remembers
the accident
and still
can't forgive himself.
That was five years ago.
Believe me,
I've moved on.
But, you know,
he's just not there yet.
Hey, how's
the baby search going?
Robert:
Sarah!
I'd get out here.
Someone's about to open
their presents without you.
We'll be there
in a minute.
Actually,
the agency called,
and they have a new birth mother they want us to meet.
Robert's hated
them all, right?
Yeah. I mean,
I haven't been too crazy
about
any of them either,
but apparently
this woman
is really just jumping at the chance to meet us, so...
Well, maybe she's the one.
I hope so. I really
think another baby
will bring
the old Robert back.
I remember that guy.
He used to dance around this
kitchen to corny old music.
Yeah.
Seems like
a million years ago.
Well, we pulled
that off, another year.
All those kids.
She never stopped
running around.
No wonder she passed out
like a log.
A happy log.
You seem distracted.
Oh, it's this deadline.
I have to get the book
to the publisher
by the end of the month.
So it's just
the book then?
Okay, Sarah,
you know it's the day.
It always
has this effect on me.
Yeah, but maybe every year gets a little easier.
That's just it.
I think it's actually
getting worse.
I can still picture the accident like it was yesterday.
You shouldn't--
I knew the dock was rotten.
Robert, stop beating
yourself up.
You know what happens.
I'm trying.
I believe you.
It's not just you
I'm thinking about.
Don't you think I know?
It's Sully.
I can't stop
worrying about her.
The diabetes.
Did she eat too much cake
when I wasn't looking?
Is she too active?
It's driving me insane.
Well, hopefully,
you'll like this birth mother tomorrow.
I think having a second
baby around here
will really restore
the balance.
I know.
And we've tried
everything.
You know
I can't have children.
You're right.
I think it's the day,
this book.
It's just
all too much stress.
Well, you know,
I know an old-fashioned remedy for stress.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Old family secret?
Oh, yeah, it's been
in the family for years.
I'm all yours, doctor.
- Hello, there.
- Helen, hi. Welcome.
Don't mind me.
I was just watering.
This is Bridgette.
Hello.
I thought houses like this
only existed in the movies.
Oh, thanks. Yeah, we're
really proud of it.
Come on in.
Is Robert here?
Yeah, we're expecting
both of you.
Can I get you anything?
Coffee for me.
My husband should
be down in a second.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
You sure I can't
get you anything?
Yeah.
I just had a shake and some fries before I got here.
Your daughter?
Yeah. Sully.
She's our world.
- She's beautiful.
- Oh, thanks.
You like children?
Oh, yes.
One day, I want to have
a really big family.
I mean, when I'm ready.
Of course.
Hello, everyone.
Robert,
this is Bridgette.
Bridgette...
Bridgette Gibson.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Oh! Oh, look what I did!
It's quite all right.
No, no. I'll go get a broom.
I'm so stupid.
I don't want you
to cut yourself. It's fine.
I'm so sorry, sir.
No, please,
call me Robert.
Please sit down.
So, tell us
about yourself.
Um, right now I live
in Idaho Falls.
I was going to college,
but I ended up dropping out
because I couldn't afford it.
I was going to take out
one of those student loans,
but I really hate
being in debt.
Sounds like you read one
of my husband's books.
People who read his books
are afraid of being in debt.
That's not true.
My books preach fiscal responsibility,
that's all.
I did read one of
your books, Mr. Benson.
"Debt: Not Just
a Four-Letter Word?"
Yes, of course.
I'm actually
a really big fan.
- See? What'd I tell you?
- Very smart.
I'm just trying
to save up my money
so that I can get out of my current living situation.
What is your current
living situation?
I'm in a shelter.
It's okay, though.
Just okay?
I mean, the food
isn't that great
and I don't sleep that well.
I do worry about this
little guy, though.
How so?
I mean, it would
probably be better
if I could rest
a little more, you know.
So you say it's a boy?
Yeah, a boy.
How far along are you?
Six months.
Is it hard?
Well, you know, in the beginning,
there's morning sickness and...
I know why you
wanted to meet me.
And any parent
adopting a child would.
I'm the same.
When I got a call
from the agency
saying they had
found a couple,
I just wanted to be sure.
I love my baby,
and if I could afford
to live in a house like this
and give him a life
like you two could...
I know in my heart
what I'm doing is right.
So the agency will contact you both if it's a fit
and if Bridgette agrees.
Fingers crossed,
but it looks positive.
Daddy,
look what I can do.
Where's your helmet?
I'm so sorry.
I'm really over-protective
when it comes to kids.
No, don't be sorry,
Ms. Gibson. Sully--
I don't like it on my head.
Here, let me.
Let's keep that
head of yours safe
so you grow up smart
like your mom and dad.
Is she gonna be okay
in that shelter?
It really is
the best place for her.
I'm ahead of my wife
on this one.
What if she were
to stay with us?
People do that,
right?
Well, yes,
it's done all the time,
but you should take time
and think about it.
What do you think
about that, Bridgette?
I wasn't paying attention.
Well, if we were to decide
to go through with it,
would you be comfortable
living here with us?
We'd make it very
comfortable for you.
I wouldn't want
to bother you guys.
Well, why don't
you think about it?
So? Are you gonna
say anything?
About what?
You know about what.
I like her.
I liked her a lot.
It's just
a big decision.
Sarah, it's just we don't even
know if she's gonna like us.
Robert,
you're just scared.
Besides, what's
not to like about us?
Well, if she's read one of my books,
she can't be that bad.
I think we're
gonna be very happy.
Hi. Welcome to our home.
No more heavy
lifting for you.
Give me those.
Oh, I'm okay.
Aw, you better
listen to him.
He's not gonna
let you out of his sight
for the next three months.
And finally,
this is your room.
Hope you like it.
The bathroom's in there,
and extra towels,
I think, are in here.
- It's nice. It's so big.
- Thanks.
Robert and I added it on when we
thought we were having a second child.
I guess maybe I never
stopped believing
that this would be
a baby's room again.
Well, now it will be.
Thank you.
I can't tell you how much this
means to me and my family.
- Hey, you.
- Hey, Mommy.
Hey, you remember Sully?
Of course. How's
the bike riding going?
Okay. My dad wouldn't
take off my training wheels.
My daddy wouldn't
either,
but I'm sure
he'll come around.
Yeah, don't be so sure.
Is that a baby in there?
Yeah, it's
your baby brother.
Do you wanna feel?
Okay, maybe next time.
I don't feel him
kicking now anyways.
All right, well,
let's check your pump and get you some breakfast.
Okay.
Can I get you anything?
I could go for
a giant bowl of ice cream.
Sorry.
We don't keep a lot of sugary things in the house.
Because of her.
She's diabetic.
But I'm sure I can
find you something.
Oh, actually, I'm good.
Yeah. Just to warn you,
I'm one of those
organic food people.
What can I say?
Ooh.
Oh, you okay?
Yeah. I think
I need to rest.
Oh, okay.
- Hello?
- We're in the guest room.
Charlie helps me at the farm stand.
You'll love him.
Bridgette. Thank God
you're finally here.
Maybe the boss lady
will relax a little.
Yeah, don't count on it.
Did you see how many orders
of pumpkin bread we got?
Work, work, work.
If I didn't love her
so much, I'd kill her.
Okay, we're gonna
leave you alone.
Great meeting you.
You'll be seeing too much of me around here.
And you'll be seeing
way too much of me.
I like her.
All right, we're
suffocating you now.
Okay, bye.
Oh, Robert..
What a mess.
Was thinking
of having Sully
help me out at
the farm stand today.
Get her out of your hair
and let you write in peace.
That would be great.
I could use
the peace and quiet.
Oh, hi. Good morning.
Good morning.
I don't usually
sleep in this late.
Oh, you can sleep
as late as you want.
I'm sure you're really
tired from yesterday.
I was out like a light.
That bed is so comfortable.
And it's so peaceful here.
So what can we get you?
Oh, don't bother.
I don't really
eat breakfast.
Nothing? I can't
make you some eggs?
Hot cereal? Anything?
Some coffee, but
I'm not really hungry.
You have to eat
for the baby as well.
You better
listen to her.
She's bossier
than her mother.
Okay, you win.
What should I have?
Cereal. I bet cereal's
good for babies.
Okay, cereal it is.
Don't indulge her.
You'll never hear the end of it.
She'll give you more advice
than a pediatrician.
So Sully and I are
gonna go into town today.
I have a farm stand there.
Do you wanna go
into town with us?
You should come!
You could work
at the stand like me.
Ladies,
let the girl rest.
How about this?
We'll come into town later for lunch.
That's a good idea.
Meanwhile,
you can get settled.
Yeah, I think
that'd be better.
Plus, I saw you guys
have a dock out there?
I'd love to go
down there and read.
The dock is off-limits.
It's too dangerous.
All right. Well,
we should get going.
Charlie likes to have
help setting up.
Let's get
your coloring books.
Okay.
Stay close
to your mother.
Don't forget
your emergency snack.
Okay. Bye, Bridgette.
Bye, Sully.
Hey, thanks for the advice.
So what did
the publisher say?
They're fine with cutting
that chapter, Robert,
but they're hoping for
a late fall release.
I know. I'm working
as fast as I can, Deb.
That's not why I called you, Robert,
and you know it.
The answer is no.
Robert, we sell twice
as many of your books
if you do a book tour.
I make enough, okay?
And I've said it a billion times.
No more book tours.
Those days are over.
Why do you hate
your readers?
I love my readers.
I just don't have the stamina
to go on the road again,
especially after last time.
Oh, come on, Robert.
You're not fooling me.
No one partied as hard
as you did on the road.
Is that what that was?
Partying?
I believe they have
a clinical name for it.
If you recall,
I blacked out last time.
Fine, so lay off
the booze.
But you still
have groupies,
and they
want to see you.
Debbie.
Fine, I'm done. I will
wait for the pages.
They want a corrected
proof in a month.
Don't remind me.
Bye, Deb.
Bye. Love you.
(Knock on door)
Come in.
I'm so sorry
to bother you.
I was going to sit out
on the patio in the sun,
and I was wondering if you
have any sunblock in the house.
Sunblock? Yeah.
Oh, I did it. I'm
totally bothering you.
No, no, no. It's just
when I come in here,
I go to a different place,
that's all.
The life
of a writer. Wow.
It must get hard,
Robert.
Hard?
It is sometimes.
Alone all the time.
Sunblock. Follow me.
Well, I know she keeps
bug spray in here,
so I'm assuming
we'll find sunblock.
Honestly, I could get rid
of half this stuff
and I don't think
anyone would notice.
Well, I found a box
of Christmas lights.
Perfect. Oh, if you need
gardening gloves,
there's a whole bag
over here.
Oh, there's more stuff in here than my last apartment.
If you see bug spray,
it should be close by.
Oh, here's bug spray.
Okay, it should be
right by the bug spray.
I don't see it.
- Ah, sunscreen.
- Awesome.
SPF-30.
Is that enough?
Yeah, it'll do.
Well, if you need
anything else,
batteries, lighter fluid,
it should all be in here.
I'll keep that in mind.
- Coffee.
- Oh, you're a lifesaver.
Gosh, we had a pretty
good crowd this morning.
Yeah, best little farm
stand in Storm Lake.
Hey, Robert's bringing Bridgette into town for lunch.
So what's she like?
She's quiet. You know,
I think she's getting used to us.
And you just leave her alone
in the house with Robert?
She's six months
pregnant.
Some men like that.
How would you know?
Look, gay people live in the
same world as everyone else.
She's not his type.
Oh, you're right.
Men hate gorgeous women.
No wonder
she got knocked up.
Charlie! I feel sorry
for her, poor girl.
Look, you're doing
a beautiful thing.
And knowing Robert,
he's probably hiding in his attic
too afraid
to even talk to her.
(Laughs)
We should get going if you wanna do lunch in town.
I keep falling asleep.
Well, we don't
have to go.
I could make you
some lunch here.
Yeah, I think
that might be better.
I just don't know
if I'm feeling up to it.
I'll just text Sarah
and let her know.
She won't be disappointed,
will she?
Sarah? No. She never
stops working,
and that's the way
she likes it.
(Cell phone vibrates)
No--
I am. What do you think
I'm doing?
I know, but these
things take time.
Would you stop
freaking out?
Bridgette? Hi.
Hi. Charlie.
Sarah and Robert's friend?
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
I was on the phone
and my mind was
a million miles away.
Don't stress about it.
I'm completely forgettable.
You getting
your morning fix?
Yeah, I don't operate
without my coffee.
Same. So how's life cooped up
in the Benson mansion?
I love it.
Robert is so nice.
Listen, you should
really be careful.
Robert has a really
violent temper,
and the police in this town have
a 24-hour surveillance on him.
For what?
(Laughs)
I'm totally kidding.
He's like the nicest man
in the world.
Maybe a little reserved,
but everyone
has their demons, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Can I feel?
- Oh.
- I'm sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
It's totally fine.
It makes me uncomfortable.
Yeah, of course it would.
I mean, strangers coming up
to you feeling your belly?
It's weird.
- Miss, large latte?
- Yeah.
Charlie, leave
my customers alone.
Don't get on her bad side.
She'll spit in your coffee.
Well,
it was nice seeing you.
Yeah.
I'm sure
I'll see you around.
Can't be avoided.
So, Bridgette, you've
been here for a few days.
What do you think
of our little town?
It's like
a little dream town.
Everyone is so friendly.
I feel like
I could live here.
We like it.
I had coffee
at the little café in town,
and then
I went into some shops.
It's tourist season
right now.
People come here
for the lake.
Robert hates them,
but I kind of like it
when the town picks up.
I don't hate them.
I just don't like the big motors on the lake.
It's too loud.
Robert's trying to regulate
the size of the motor
you can have on the lake.
It's a political thing,
and if you're not on Robert's side,
you're an idiot.
Well, they are idiots.
I'm trying to help them
save their town.
See, I think I prefer
peace and quiet, too.
I had this boyfriend once
who had a really big
loud boat,
and every weekend, we'd go
up to this lake by us,
and he'd make me sit
on the front in a bikini
just to show me off.
I knew how to pick 'em.
So you ran
into Charlie today?
Yes, I did.
He's the best.
He's been working for me for about four years.
I used to sell organic
fruits and vegetables
out of the back
of my truck,
and Charlie was the one
that got me thinking bigger.
Sarah's about to open two new stands in nearby towns.
If this continues,
I may be able to retire.
(All laugh)
What would you do
if you could retire?
Exactly
what I'm doing now.
I'd write and make sure
this little girl
has everything
she needs.
Don't forget about
my new baby brother.
You're right.
Sarah can work,
and I'll stay at home with the two kids.
That sounds perfect.
Can I say something?
When I first got here,
I guess
I was a little scared,
'cause this is really
a big decision.
But you guys are so nice
and you really do have
the perfect life.
I know my baby couldn't be
in a happier place.
I can't tell you how happy
you've made us.
And you're gonna have a perfect life, too,
one day, I promise.
I hope it's in
a town like this
with a family like yours.
You bet.
Okay, right there?
Right there?
Yes. Okay. I'm gonna
hold you to start.
Okay, I'm gonna
let go in 1, 2, 3.
Okay, don't get
too close to the road!
Sully!
- (Car horn honks)
- Aah!
Dwayne?
So a girl's gotta
be more careful, huh?
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know.
I'm just checking up on my two favorite babes.
It's a nice house.
Yeah, well,
you can't be here.
I told you to wait
for me at the cabin.
Hey there, little girl.
What's your name, hmm?
Dwayne, cut it out.
You have to go.
Okay, okay.
Now.
I'll see you soon.
Go.
It was nice meeting you.
Do you know that man?
Sort of.
He scared me.
I know, but he's gone now.
Men like that,
you gotta be careful, Sully.
Most of them
just want to use you.
Did you see?
I rode my bike without
the training wheels.
I did, yeah.
But listen, if your daddy caught you,
he would not be happy.
So how about
we just make this
our little secret
for a while, okay?
But I want to show him.
I know,
but if he finds out you took the training wheels off,
he might
take your bike away.
- He will?
- Mm-hmm.
So don't tell anybody
about the training wheels
or the man that
was just here, okay?
Okay, but you can't
tell anyone either.
Cross my heart.
Coffee break
in 10 minutes?
Yeah. Can we
make it five?
Hey, how's Bridgette
working out?
She's really great.
She and Sully are
practically best friends.
What does Robert think?
Um, I don't know.
He's been kind of a
little shut down lately.
What do you mean?
It's like he's afraid
or something.
Afraid of what?
Oh, everything.
Life, having fun, Sully.
He worries about her so much,
I don't know what to do.
Well, maybe he should
see a therapist.
Oh, you know Robert.
He thinks therapists are for sick people.
Typical.
I really thought bringing
Bridgette into the house
and adopting this baby
would sort of pull him
out of it you, you know?
But it's almost like
it's made it worse.
Even I've noticed that Robert's been a little off lately.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I think
he's just stressed.
Yeah, once we have
the baby,
I feel like we'll all
find some peace.
- Is that how it works?
- Yeah, all right.
Go get your coffee,
smart-ass.
- Hello.
- (Gasp)
You startled me.
I was daydreaming.
I do that a lot.
Wishing
you were on the lake?
Gosh, no.
Oh, sit.
The truth is,
I'm actually afraid to get on the water.
Afraid?
Some years ago,
Sarah had an accident.
Accident?
The dock broke.
She hit her head
and fell in the water.
She was
six months pregnant.
We lost the child.
You must have been
so tortured.
The worst part is,
I blame her.
I know
it was an accident.
If she just hadn't acted
so foolishly...
Yeah.
I just can't seem
to get past that.
Sometimes I think I may never
love her the way I used to.
It's funny. I've never
told anyone that before.
Well, maybe
you feel safe around me.
(Chuckles) Maybe.
Robert, are you happy?
Happy?
I'm not really sure.
Sometimes I am, I guess.
What about you?
Are you happy?
I think soon
I'll be very happy.
You really are
a strange girl.
(Chuckles)
Hey, Charlie.
Good morning.
Coffee for me,
decaf for Sarah.
You got it.
How's work today?
Charlie?
Your coffees?
Oh.
You haven't turned the page
in five minutes.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Okay.
I was in
the pantry today
and I found an unopened
box of chocolates.
It was probably a gift
or something.
Come on, Sarah.
If Sully
were to find that,
you know exactly
what would happen.
Robert, what is going on?
You know the dangers
of diabetic ketoacidosis.
And Sully knows not to eat
candy unless we say it's okay.
You have to trust her.
She's six.
I cannot take this
anymore, Robert,
with all this worrying.
Ever since you got back
from your last book tour,
you've been completely
shut down.
It is suffocating.
I've noticed it,
Sully's noticed it.
Even Charlie said something
to me about it.
What is going on?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Bridgette?
Sully!
Were you spying on me?
What's that?
This? It's nothing.
Why do you wear that?
Look, I have
to tell you something,
but it needs to be
our little secret.
Okay.
So some women,
when they get pregnant,
they have big bellies
and some don't.
I have a small belly.
Then why do you have
that pretend one?
Because if I didn't,
your parents might not believe that I have a baby,
and I do have a baby.
- I can tell them.
- No! No, no, no.
It's gotta be
just between us, okay?
Just like
your training wheels.
You don't want your dad to take your bike away, right?
No.
So that's why
you can't say anything
or something really bad
is going to happen.
Pinkie promise?
Pinkie promise.
Hey, I have an idea.
(Cell phone vibrates)
Oh, I just got a text
from Bridgette.
(Door opens)
Sarah asked me to take Sully to the farm stand.
She did?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. We'll see you
at dinner?
Yep. We'll see you
at dinner.
(Knock on door)
Bridgette?
"To Joni.
Don't stop daring."
It's Joni.
I didn't hear
what you said.
Joni Mathers?
I was at the reading.
Not here.
It'll be
our little secret.
Bridgette.
Sully!
Sarah?
Robert?
What are you doing here?
Sully! Where's Sully?
She's with Bridgette
at the park.
She said
you said it was okay.
I'll be at the park,
okay?
Is everything okay?
And where were you,
Mr. Benson?
Here in my house.
Sheriff, why aren't we
out there looking for her?
You were in the house.
What made you go out looking for your daughter,
Mr. Benson?
No reason. I'm just
very protective of her.
It's not unusual, officer.
He gets very worried.
Because of her
medical condition.
Yes.
Sheriff, have you issued
some sort of alert?
Are you putting up
a roadblock?
Are you organizing
any sort of search party?
We have people working on this,
I can assure you.
I just want to get
a clearer picture
of this woman
Bridgette Gibson.
That may not even be
her real name.
I'm sorry. Do you
know something?
Well, no.
What is there to know?
She's taken our child.
She's pregnant and we're
adopting her baby.
We actually know
very little about her.
She seems very nice.
I'm sure this is just
a misunderstanding.
We're wasting time, okay?
Our child has been taken from us.
She's out there.
She's sick
and she's scared.
Is there any reason
at all
for you to think of
for Ms. Gibson
to want
to take your child?
No. She seems
to like us very much.
We like her. No.
Mr. Benson?
Huh?
Any reason she might
want to take Sully?
No, I can't think of any.
Look, I'm tired of
sitting around here.
I'm gonna go look
for her myself.
Chief, we got a picture
from the agency.
Okay, great. Let's
get that out there.
Pass it along
to the state.
This a current
picture?
No, that's not her.
That's the wrong photograph.
That isn't Bridgette Gibson.
We double-checked.
That's Bridgette Gibson.
Is there any possibility
that the woman
that's been living here
is not Bridgette Gibson?
We should be long gone.
This is perfect.
Everyone's gonna think we're
halfway out of the state by now.
Why are we still
in the area?
I mean, we should be
on our way
to Kansas City
or something right now.
Just stop worrying, okay?
I'd feel a lot safer
in a bigger city.
It's okay.
No one is gonna be
looking for us
on this side
of the lake,
so we stick to the plan.
What are you gonna say
to her when she wakes up?
Leave it to me, yeah?
(Sigh)
Hey.
Mm-hmm?
How rich are they, huh?
We will be getting
crazy money.
(Laughs)
Then we're
out of here, right?
Yeah, just the way
we planned it.
Hey, you don't think they're
looking for us, right?
They don't even know
you exist.
Oh, I can't wait
to change.
I don't know.
I kind of liked you with a big belly.
Please.
Just saying.
Don't start.
This is ridiculous.
Robert, please don't.
Sarah, come on.
One drink.
I'm going crazy.
We can't just sit here.
There's nothing
we can do.
Well, what are you doing?
I'm making a flyer.
I couldn't think of anything else.
I don't know.
I'm gonna put them
everywhere tomorrow.
I let you down.
I let everybody down.
Robert, please don't be
so hard on yourself.
It's not helpful.
You don't understand,
Sarah. I know her.
What?
I think I know her.
Bridgette.
I was on a book tour,
the last one.
When we lost the baby,
I went crazy
and I said yes
to every book tour.
I think it was a way for me
to get rid of the memory.
And I drank.
I drank every night
out on the road
because I hated myself.
I hated everything.
The accident...
It was like I was trying
to kill myself.
And I hated you
for falling that day.
Robert...
I slept with her.
You slept
with Bridgette?
I was drunk.
I was wrong.
I don't know
what made me do it.
This morning,
I went into her room.
I knew something
wasn't right.
I found my book.
Inside I'd written a note
to some girl named Joni.
And all of a sudden,
it came flooding back.
I don't understand.
The picture the sheriff
showed us
is probably
the real Bridgette.
The girl who's been living with us is named Joni.
What does she want with us?
Why did she steal Sully?
I don't know. Revenge?
How could you do this?
I don't have an answer.
I was lost.
Why didn't you
just talk to me?
Don't I matter?
Sarah, I did something
that I can never take back,
and it consumes me
every day.
I know you hate me,
but I hate myself more.
If you think I hate you for cheating on me,
you underestimate me.
I hate you
for endangering our child.
My baby is out there without her
medicine with a crazy woman
because of you!
You did this!
How could you do this
to our family?
Hey, baby,
how you feeling?
Your hair.
You look different.
Do you like it?
I changed it.
Girls do that
all the time.
Where am I?
We're at
my friend's house.
We had so much fun
last night.
Do you remember?
Where's mommy and daddy?
They had an emergency,
so they asked me
to watch you.
What kind of emergency?
Their friend is sick
and he's in
the hospital,
so they're gonna be gone
for a few days.
Shouldn't we go home
and wait for them?
No.
I thought that you and I could play house here.
Me and you, all day.
Doesn't that sound fun?
My tummy hurts.
Yeah?
Okay, I'm gonna go get you
something for your tummy.
You just stay here, okay?
- Okay.
I messed up.
Why? What's going on?
I should have grabbed
her medicine
for her pump
before I left the house.
Hold on. I can go
get some medicine.
No, that's not
going to work.
It's prescription,
dummy.
Well, what's she got?
She's some kind
of diabetic.
Oh, hell,
my brother had that.
Yeah, it's low blood sugar.
We used to give him
a couple candy bars
and he'd be good to go.
She doesn't look
too good.
Well, seeing as how
you can't go into town,
I guess I'll have to
go get us some candy, then.
Thank you.
In the meantime, you
call that daddy of hers
and tell him his
little girl is sick
and needs his help, yeah?
Oh, and tell him to get his
some money, too, huh?
So you saw this girl Bridgette get out of a truck.
What kind of truck?
Just a regular
pickup truck.
What make?
I don't know.
Older. Not too old.
It was green and white.
You get
a license plate number?
No. It happened
really fast.
All right, tell me
about the guy.
Um, he was scruffy.
You know, had
a five o'clock shadow.
He was wearing jeans.
Maybe cowboy boots.
He was kind of handsome
in that redneck
kind of way.
He was young,
about her age.
She definitely knew him.
Why didn't you tell
the Bensons
you saw Bridgette
with a strange man?
Robert, Mr. Benson,
would freak out.
He's a bundle of nerves.
You afraid of him?
Mr. Benson? No.
Has he ever been
violent around you?
No. Look, you're barking
up the wrong tree.
Mr. Benson might be
a little cold,
but he'd never
hurt Sully.
Well, from what
I'm learning,
he's got
an interesting past.
I just hope she's okay.
We'll find her.
- (Cell phone rings)
- Hello?
Sarah, listen, I'm headed
toward the lake cabin.
- What?
- I'm following a guy who I think may have Sully.
- Charlie, I cant--
- Hello?
Really?
(Crunch)
Looking for something?
Are you that stupid?
Babe, this only makes
the decision easier.
Hey, let's just get
the hell outta town.
No. We're sticking
with my plan.
Hey, Charlie.
Sully better be alive.
Oh, she's alive.
Shut up, Dwayne.
Police are already
looking for you.
They know all about your
criminal friend here.
You've got a really
big mouth, Charlie.
What are you gonna do,
lock me up with Sully?
I can't afford that.
What are you gonna do?
I ain't gonna do nothing.
Well, Charles, you were
right about two things.
She's insane
and I'm a criminal.
No. No, please don't.
(Gunshot)
♪ Simple words ♪
♪ Understand ♪
♪ I brace my mind ♪
♪ Crossed the line ♪
♪ I'm falling through ♪
We did some checking up
with your adoption agency
to see if we
can locate anyone
who might know
Ms. Gibson.
Yes. I told you.
Ellen Macy.
She's the one that did
the background check.
Unfortunately, we're not gonna get much out of Ms.
Macy now.
She's dead.
She's dead?
She was found
in her apartment.
Police are still
investigating.
Do you recognize
this man, Mrs. Benson?
Uh, no. Should I?
He was spotted
with Ms. Joni Mathers
by a friend of yours,
Charlie Holmes.
His name
is Dwayne Tisdale.
He's wanted in Texas
in connection with
two murders down there.
What does that have to do
with Bridgette-- Joni?
Not sure yet.
Do you know where your
husband is, Mrs. Benson?
He's out
looking for her.
We had a fight.
Well, in light of what you
told me about him and Joni,
is it possible that
they're together right now?
Hey, are you sure
this is a good idea?
You want your money,
don't you?
What if we just call
the dad and--
It has to be this way.
Yeah, but they're
looking for you.
You feeling better,
sweetie?
I don't feel good.
I know. I know.
Well, I'm gonna go
rent us a boat
so we can get out
on the lake, okay?
I think I need
my medicine.
And we're gonna get some
for you real soon.
But you need to eat
some candy first.
It's gonna help you
feel so much better.
Dwayne, the candy.
All right,
just a few bites.
And then maybe you can try and
sleep while I go rent us a boat.
Dwayne will be here
the whole time.
My daddy won't let me
go on boats.
Well, just because your dad is scared of the water
doesn't mean your dad and I can't go for boat rides.
And when you're older,
maybe I'll even
let you drive.
But right now I need you to rest, okay, sweetie?
Hey! Hey!
What now, Dwayne?
Hold up.
Come here. Come here.
What was that all about
back there, huh?
- What? Boat rides?
- What?
We're not keeping
the kid.
Obviously. I was just trying
to make her feel good.
You're a paranoid
son of a bitch.
Hey, don't walk away from me when I'm talking to you!
Come here!
You better not be
messing around with me.
I'm in this for the money and nothing else.
Yeah, I'm gonna get you
your money and my money.
You stay here with the girl
and you try and stay out
of sight this time, okay?
Okay.
Sorry, I'm closing.
Please.
I'll only be an hour.
Okay. Paddle board
or canoe? What kind?
I saw that you guys
had outboards out there.
Oh, you know
how to run 'em?
How much is it?
50. Going fishing?
Here's 50.
(Tapping)
Hello, Sarah.
Bridgette, What have you
done with Sully?
- Please!
- She's okay.
She's okay.
My God,
you're not pregnant.
No, I never was.
Don't worry about Sully.
She's fine. She's safe.
Bridgette, please,
please tell me where she is.
You're never gonna
see her again.
I'm her new mom now.
Robert and I are going
to take her away.
Robert's with you?
Mm-hmm.
He'll be here soon.
Do you know how crazy
this sounds?
Don't call me crazy.
Bridgette, wait!
Please.
Shut up!
You are pathetic.
The second I met you,
I knew I didn't like you.
Your stupid fruit stand
and your organic
vegetables.
Bridgette, please!
My name's Joni,
by the way.
You need to know
something, Sarah.
Robert doesn't love you.
He told me so.
He blames you
for the accident.
And he loves me.
But why take Sully?
What does she have to do with any of this?
(Laughs)
That night...
That night when he was
making love to me,
I got pregnant
with his child.
I carried him around for three months,
and I lost him.
And then right when I was feeling like a dirty little slut,
I turn on the TV
and I see your face
and his face
and his daughter's face,
and I didn't like that
very much.
I hate you for
stealing him away from me.
Bridgette, please.
You're sick, okay?
Let me help you.
Give me the gun.
(Laughs)
I already told you
my name's Joni.
This is perfect.
Sarah is so upset
about losing her baby,
people are gonna think
it's a suicide.
Just like Charlie.
(Engine starts)
Sarah?
Hello? Sarah?
Robert.
Bridgette!
No, you can call me
Joni now.
Where's Sarah?
You don't have to worry
about Sarah anymore.
It's fine.
I have Sully.
Sarah?
No, no.
Don't you get it?
You're free.
We're free to be happy.
- What did you do to her?
- I took care of her.
Where is she?
Robert, you're acting
very strange.
Don't you get it?
We have everything, okay?
We can start
our lives together.
This is what
we always wanted.
What are you
talking about?
You know what?
I'm calling the police.
You weren't happy.
You told me you weren't happy.
I don't
understand you, okay?
Don't do that!
We don't have much time to get away.
We have to get away.
Hello, yes, can I speak
to Sheriff Watson, please?
Put the phone down!
Oh!
Oh, God.
Please don't make me
shoot you again.
- Oh, you're sick.
- No, I'm not.
Okay, Joni, put
the gun down, all right?
Let's just talk about this.
You told me
you didn't love her.
Tell me where Sully is,
and we'll forget this ever happened.
I thought this is what you wanted.
I don't understand.
Just put it down,
all right?
- Aah!
- Oh!
Robert!
No! I didn't mean to!
I didn't mean to.
(Crying)
We gotta go.
Where is she?
Hey, you got the money?
Where is Sully?
She's in the bathroom.
She's not feeling too good.
Oh, damn it.
I forgot her medicine.
We have to clear out.
Where's your gun?
It's on the table.
Hey, you got the money?
(Knock on door)
Sully, baby girl!
Hey, what happened?
I don't feel good.
I know. I know, baby.
Listen, baby,
your daddy is dead,
but you and I
are gonna be fine.
We have to go.
You screwed up,
didn't you, huh?
You ain't got no money.
Hey, I told you what was gonna
happen if you messed with me!
Now I'm taking the girl.
Let her go!
Yeah? Or what? Huh?
We weren't getting money
out of this anyway.
It was about him
the whole time.
It was about
the husband.
Imagine a guy like that with a crazy whore like you.
I'm warning you.
What are you
gonna do, huh?
What, are you
gonna shoot her?
Are you gonna
shoot me? Huh?
I said to let her go.
Yeah, I'll let her go,
as soon as I get
my half a million.
- Aah!
- Oh!
I want my mom!
You shot me!
Your mommy
is already dead.
I'm your new mom now.
(Groans)
(coughs)
Sarah.
Sarah? Sarah?
(Coughs)
Jesus! Sarah!
Sarah.
Sarah, breathe!
Oh, you're okay.
Robert, Robert,
she has our baby.
I know. I know.
Charlie tried to tell me
about the cabin.
Across the lake?
- Yeah.
- Yes?
Robert, you're hurt.
It's my fault.
I blamed you
for everything.
I was wrong.
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna go get her.
How?
Well, she won't
drive back into town.
The only other way out of Storm
Lake is across Mackinaw Bridge.
Robert, you can't.
Where are you taking me?
Somewhere safe, sweetie,
where no one can get us.
I don't wanna go with you!
You're mean!
Don't say that!
I am not mean!
I am the only nice one!
Everyone else
wants to hurt us.
Hands up!
Hands up.
Where's the girl?
The crazy bitch
just took off
about 15 minutes ago.
Where were they headed?
I don't know.
Call for an ambulance.
She shot me and she's
probably gonna kill that kid!
Dwayne Tisdale,
you are under arrest.
She shot me!
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used--
Daddy.
They're all the same.
Why do they
have to hurt me?
No! You're gonna hurt him!
We don't need him!
No! You're
gonna kill him!
Let go! I'm your
new mother now!
You're not my mom!
- (Shouts)
- (heavy thud)
Sully!
Daddy!
(Groans)
Sully?
It's okay.
You're okay, all right?
I have your insulin
in the boat, all right?
It's all over.
Mommy's waiting for us.
(Gunshot)
You can't take her,
Robert.
Joni, please,
she's dying.
I need to give her
her medicine.
You don't think
I'm a good mother.
You think I'm nothing.
You used me, Robert.
You are never gonna
use me again.
I'm taking her from you.
- Daddy...
- It's okay.
Robert! I'm gonna
shoot you both!
Daddy?
Robert!
- Listen to me.
- I'm scared.
I'm scared, too,
but I need you to do something,
all right? (Whispers)
Last chance, Robert!
Okay?
I trust you, okay?
Okay.
That's a smart choice.
We could have
had everything.
We could have had
a happy life together.
But you're a selfish coward
and a liar just like
the rest of them!
Come on, let's get
out of here.
Come here.
Baby, come on.
Robert!
(Gunshots)
(gunshot)
It's okay.
♪ (Vocalizing) ♪
She sure loves that bike.
I told her she could ride
into town tomorrow.
Look at you.
Not a care in the world.
She can't be a baby forever.
At some point, you
just have to trust her.
That is very wise.
Some good parenting.
How'd I get so lucky?
Luck had nothing
to do with it.
Well, whatever it was...
I love this song.
♪ (Music playing) ♪
Come here, you.
♪ We're gonna
shake, shake ♪
♪ Sh-sh-sh-shake it ♪
♪ We'll be shaking
all night long ♪
♪ We're gonna jump,
jump, j-j-j-jump ♪
♪ Yes, we'll be jumpin'
all night long ♪
♪ We're gonna bounce
bounce, b-b-b-bounce ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll be bouncin'
all night long ♪
♪ We're gonna bounce,
jump, shake ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll be here
all night ♪
♪ We're gonna fly, fly
fl-fl-fl-fly ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll be flyin'
all night long ♪
♪ We're gonna jitter,
jitter, j-j-j-jitter ♪
♪ Yeah we'll be jittering
all night long ♪
♪ We're gonna
boogie, boogie ♪
♪ b-b-b-boogie ♪
♪ We'll be boogie-ing
all night long ♪
♪ We're gonna
boogie, jitter, shake ♪
♪ Yeah we'll be here
all night ♪
♪ We'll be here
♪ Here all night ♪
♪ Here in the morning ♪
♪ Feeling all right ♪
♪ 24, 48 hours a day ♪
♪ (vocalizing) ♪