Looks like another
hit and run.
Tire tracks match car
belonging to suspect
known as one...
Miss Henderson.
Lucas! Breakfast!
A nine-year-old Metro girl
has a new lease on life
thanks to surgery at the
hospital for sick children.
You're gonna take him
to school, right?
What? No. Well, I told
you I've got a meeting.
Oh, great.
I thought we agreed you wouldn't
bring the laptop to the counter.
No, no, no, no!
No.
Let's go. That wasn't
finished uploading.
You're gonna be late for school.
Come on. Let's go.
Young grammarians.
To conjugate,
or not to conjugate.
That is not
the question.
Conjugating a verb
is just very simply,
uh, uh, uh,
creating a logical for, uh,
uh, presentation
for as many forms
like, I walk.
Hey!
You walk, he walks.
There are six tenses...
For the English... verb
what are you
listening to?
I said, what are
you listening to?
Is that chopin?
I've been taking
cello lessons.
I love classical.
What are you
filming?
Nothing. Just some
b-roll for my movie.
Oh.
Looks like a hit and run.
Probably miss Henderson.
I gotta go.
Don't you live
over there?
Ladies and gentlemen,
you are about to witness
history in the making!
And introducing the best
skater on the planet,
Jake Simons!
How long have you been
making these movie, Lucas?
A while.
What do you like about
filming funerals?
Do you show these movies
to your parents?
Not really.
Why not?
I don't think
they'd like 'em.
What kind of movies
do you like to watch?
The good kind.
"Evil dead,"
"army of darkness"...
"Psycho."
Time up?
I'll let you know
when we're done.
So, what about Jake?
What kind of movies
did he like to watch?
How about I tell you
when we're done?
Right about now.
Hey, wipe your feet!
Lucas, open the door.
Mom, I'm changing.
You left mud all
over the floor!
I'll clean
it up later.
Did you eat? There's
dinner on the table.
Mom, I'll grab
something in a bit.
Good morning,
sleepy head.
Fell asleep at
your desk again?
Come on. Oh.
Hey, hop up.
You dad's taking you to school,
so let's go. Don't be late.
See? What do you
think that is?
I don't know. It's amazing what you
kids can do with your apps these days.
That's cute.
Hey, gotta go.
What? Hold on.
Let's roll.
You know, It's not
such a good idea for you
to spend so much time
staring at a computer.
Your mom told me you fell asleep
at your desk last night.
That's not a good thing.
You're not getting your rest,
you're not getting
your school work done.
It's not a good thing.
Yeah, dad, but this video.
I mean, what do
you think that is?
I don't know.
You ever thought about
doing something different?
I mean, like-like, I ran into
coach Caldwell at the buy rite.
He told me he thinks they're gonna
have a really good team this year.
Said he'd love to have you
come and try out for the team.
Yeah, dad,
that's not gonna happen.
Not gonna happen,
huh? Okay.
You just gotta realize there's more to life
than making these weird videos of yours.
Yeah. Like skateboarding.
The forecast,
showers heavy at times
with occasional thunderstorms
today and a high of 89 degrees.
Partial clearing tonight
with a low of 74.
More showers developing
tomorrow and not as warm
with a high of 77.
With the winds out of the west
at 22 Miles per hour currently.
Fourteen people arrested...
There are more indications
that the president
of the united
states will not...
In Washington today
there is more likelihood
that the budget will result
in additions to welfare.
And the European union
is in trouble.
There are more things
today...
Death.
What's it like?
We'll explore that next with
local author Chris Brighton,
who has firsthand experience.
He's also written a new book,
"living the now."
Chris,
you were dead
for nearly nine minutes.
Yeah, so I hear.
During those long nine
minutes, what'd you see?
Well, you know, Paula,
I'm asked this question a lot,
and quite frankly,
I didn't see anything.
No white light?
Not even the familiar face
of a deceased loved one?
Look, you know,
everyone wants to know
If I experienced something
amazing or even supernatural
in my dying, and quite
frankly the answer is yes.
I did.
Yeah.
But it wasn't
until I woke up.
That's why in my new book,
"living the now,"
I discuss the importance
of making the best of this...
Was it quiet?
Did you get a sense
that you wanted to stay,
you know, dead?
Well, Paula,
If there's no afterlife,
why would anyone
make that choice?
So you don't
remember anything.
The grim reaper is
a great tour guide,
but he doesn't let you
take pictures along the way.
Ha! You're
funny, Chris.
Yeah, funny.
We'll be right back
after the break.
Um, can I be excused?
I have homework to do.
Sure.
Hey, Bob.
Hey, man. You killed
it out there today!
Hmm, yeah, I loved
your book, by the way.
Oh, so you read it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Most of it.
Uh-huh.
Look, I'm sorry we didn't get
to talk about it more but,
but you know how it is,
you know, the suits upstairs,
the ratings
and all that.
I just thought
we had a deal.
No dead talk,
just the book this time.
Yeah, I know.
Hmm. We'll catch you
on the flip side though.
Look, I don't know
If there's a heaven or not,
but that's just my experience,
but what I realized is that
everyone experiences death
in one way or another.
But that's not what
life is all about.
A 49-year-old unidentified
man was observed last night...
Hello?
Police are not
releasing any information.
You're drinking coffee?
Speaking.
A government bill to
crack down on laboratories...
What?
Sure!
Okay. Yeah.
No, We'll-We'll be here.
All right, all right.
We'll see you then.
That was
the local news.
What?
The news. They want to interview
our son about his ghost video.
Wait, what-what video?
Why-why would they...
Why would they want to interview Lucas?
Lucas, what did you do?
Nothing, mom. It was
the video I showed you.
Well, we're
gonna be on TV.
Isn't that
exciting?
Hmm.
All right, good pass.
Nice interception.
Come on, spread it out.
All right, let's see who's gonna
start this week. Good shot!
Nice! Nice shot.
So, where shall
we start?
Hmm? The mall?
They usually have
pretty good deals there.
We need to get you
a new suit.
And I can certainly use
a new dress.
We're gonna be
on TV, Lucas!
Aren't you the
least bit excited?
Cute!
Lucas, what do you
think about this one?
Mom, I'm sure It's
just as good as
all the other dresses
you've tried on.
Why are you asking me?
I like it.
Bach's "toccata and fugue")
Who are we
hiding from?
You shouldn't scare
people like that.
We have to
watch out.
That security guard
is pure evil.
Thanks for
the warning.
Can we go?
All right.
This is exciting.
I've never been
in a movie before.
You ready?
Yeah. Uh,
on one condition.
For every question
that you ask me,
I get to
ask you one.
It's fine. I can
just edit you out.
Okay.
Chris, take one.
Please state your name for the record.
Yes, sir.
Christopher
p. Brighton
the first,
capital "c."
Ah, go ahead.
Are you married?
Not anymore. You?
Does it hurt to die?
Uh, about as much as
falling out of a window.
How long have you been
doing these videos?
Since I was eight.
Where do you think
you go when you die?
I don't know If
you go anywhere.
So why did you
stop playing sports
and start hanging
around in cemeteries?
I don't play, I document.
And that was two questions.
My turn.
All right.
What do you think
that thing was
that I filmed?
Uh, a ghost?
Look. I don't
believe in ghosts.
Then, what do you
think it was?
I don't know. It's a
good question though.
And there's nothing wrong with
asking questions, you know?
It just, sometimes you might not get
the answer that you're looking for.
Why do you think
you came back?
I don't know. I asked
myself that many times.
People who believe in ghosts
think that they come back
because they have some kind
of unfinished business.
Do you have
unfinished business?
Maybe.
Look, what I'm saying is
that sometimes things happen
That'll make you...
Question your beliefs.
Like that thing
that you captured,
I don't know
what it is, but
it certainly
makes you think.
Well, great.
This must be
the interview my amazing
parents scheduled for me.
Ah. You know what?
I've done a ton of these interviews.
Just have fun with it.
Maybe you should do
the interview like this.
See? Works every time.
Hey, maybe you
can come and
play basketball
with us.
You know, film one of
our games or something.
Shoot some hoops.
I'll think about it.
All right.
Oh, he's always
been an artistic child.
Creativity. You're either
born with a desire to create or
you're not.
Hmm.
Actually, um,
I did that piece over there.
It showed for a few weeks
at a gallery in soho.
Oh. That's interesting.
Thank you.
Oh, well,
look who's home.
Excuse me.
Oh. Where've you been?
Wait!
We've been waiting for an hour, Lucas.
Where have you been?
Uh, no, there's no time to change now.
You just gotta go.
And Lucas, Lucas. They want us
watching from the sidelines, okay?
I think they want
more of a one-on-one.
Okay, go! Go.
Oh, and Lucas.
Break a leg!
Excuse me.
Hi.
You must be Lucas.
Catherine goodwin.
Have a seat.
Uh...
Okay.
And we're rolling.
Lucas.
Why don't we begin
with you telling us
a little bit
about yourself.
Hmm.
Oh. Hi.
H-how did he do?
How was he?
Uh, fine, fine.
He did just fine.
- Wonderful.
- Um...
Listen.
If you're thinking of doing
more of these interviews,
may I give you a bit of advice?
Of course.
Okay. Um...
You might want
to consider
taking your son
to an optometrist.
They can do wonders
these days.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Thank you. Bye.
Excuse me.
You just show up
to these funerals uninvited
to make these
videos of yours?
What do you
call yourself?
A funeral
crasher?
Sometimes you
just have to steal a shot.
Lucas, that was a totally
awesome video, dude.
You should seriously consider
joining the Sci-Fi club.
We do a lot of paranoia stuff like this.
Hey, Lucas.
Hey. Do I have
a ghost on my shoulder?
Not anymore.
He goes
to funerals.
What a weirdo.
He has
cross eyes.
You think you're
a big shot now?
You know what I think?
I think your video was a fake.
Yeah, phony!
Get your
eyes checked.
Lucas Simons
is becoming
quite a local celebrity.
His latest video, which is
being called "anyone's ghost?"
Has surpassed three
million hits on YouTube.
Hello?
Friday the 12th it is.
2:00?
Local paranormal
filmmaker
Lucas Simons
is here to answer
the big question we've
all asked ourselves.
Oh, thank you.
Is there life
after death?
I really don't
have any answers.
You the man! You the man.
Right, here, right here.
Low! You missed it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Lucas! Lucas!
Your movie so touched me!
Just one question! Lucas!
Did your video change...
Lucas! Lucas! Big fan!
Be in my contacts!
Please can I have
your autograph?
Can you bring my kids back?
People want answers!
Lucas! Lucas!
There she is! There she is!
Mrs. Parker! Mrs. Parker!
Are you in on this?
How do you feel about the video?
Mrs. Parker,
what happened that day?
Mrs. Parker!
Leave the dead alone!
That's right!
They're people too!
What do you
think it was?
I have my theories.
Care to share?
Not really.
Aren't you supposed to be
the expert on everything?
Well... If you're
a religious person
you could say It's
her husband's soul.
I'm not religious.
Are your parents?
Not anymore.
What do they think
of the video?
It's the best thing that's
ever happened to them.
What makes
you say that?
My mom just
loves all the attention
and my dad's convinced
we're all gonna be rich.
Well...
Maybe they're just
excited for you.
Nice of them
to care now.
Look at his eye.
He looks like
a zombie.
Zombie squirrel?
That would make
the best movie ever.
"Attack of the zombie squirrels!
Now in theaters."
"Zombie squirrels from Mars."
Yeah.
You're kind of
famous now.
Yeah. It's weird.
Do you think
it was a ghost?
I don't know. Maybe.
Well, be careful of
that zombie squirrel.
It might come back
to life and bite you!
Man to man defense!
Who's on him? Good shot.
Pass it back.
Find your man.
Find your man. Come on,
pass it around, pass it around.
Nice! Nice!
Stay with it!
Yeah!
Good job, guys!
That was an excellent practice.
Put it in there.
Next week we're gonna
work on fundamentals.
Oh, come on!
All right, "team" on three.
One, two, three!
Team!
That's better.
Get out of here. Hey.
You know, I'm not
a famous director or anything,
but I think in order to
capture some really good shots,
I think you need to take
the lens cap off of the camera.
Funny.
How's my favorite
celebrity?
It's kind of
weird being famous.
This one lady
tried to pay me
to bring back
her dead turtle.
Hoo-hoo. How's your
parents doing?
What about them?
Well, you never really
talk about 'em that much.
Surely all of
this media attention
is having some
effect on them too.
Who cares how they're
dealing with it?
Okay. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
I never wanted this
kind of attention.
Let's just
leave it at that.
All right.
Fair enough.
I don't play.
Come on,
take a shot.
Well, you're never gonna know
unless you give it a try.
Oh, boy.
All right.
Told you,
I suck.
Yeah, that wasn't great.
Look, first of all,
I want you to
do this. Okay?
And second of all,
take that jacket off.
Too tight for
you anyways.
Here you go.
Whew.
Boy.
Well, Rome wasn't
built in day.
One more.
That was pretty good.
You know, I like how you get better
and better when you're doing things.
That's something you should,
you know, take to heart.
First you were one out of fifty,
and then one out of ten.
That's pretty good.
Oh.
I gotta go.
All right. Hey.
I expect you to play
next Saturday.
Maybe.
Oh. The phone has been
ringing off the hook.
Okay, so I have scheduled
a few more interviews
for next week,
I hope that's okay.
Do I even have a choice?
What?
Look, son. I know this
is a lot to take on.
But this, this is
a good thing for us.
We-we could
use the money.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
So, Lucas,
your previous works suggest
a profound fascination
with the afterlife.
Have you ever considered
exploring a lighter genre?
Well, Leslie...
May I call
you Leslie?
So, Lucas, where do you
get your inspiration from?
What?
I can't hear you!
You know,
death, It's,
It's no more
a mystery than life.
Why are we here
other than
a hot pastrami sandwich,
Beethoven's fifth?
It's-It's all
suffering and misery.
Don't ask me
a question like that!
I'm not biting!
You can't make me
dance to your tune!
I'm not a monkey!
Why are we so worried about
learning about death
when we haven't even
figured out life?
What made...
What?
So, why funerals?
Why the cemetery?
Haven't you heard?
People are just
dying to get in there.
Anybody in there?
Yeah.
Yes!
Ahh.
Way to go!
You're getting better!
One out of seven that time.
I guess I don't
totally suck.
Get on defense.
Hey, you are quite
the performer, you know that?
I've been checking out your
interviews. They are hilarious.
I didn't know
you were into acting.
I was trying to
have fun with it.
Yeah?
Make it bearable.
Well, fame comes
and goes pretty quick.
Maybe your 15 minutes
are almost up.
I hope so.
I cannot believe he
said that!
Oh!
What's going on? Lucas?
Come here, honey.
Come on. Sit down.
We have a surprise
for you.
We're going to
New York City.
Why?
Huh?
Wait. There's
one more thing.
Hold on.
Ta-da!
What is that?
It's for New York!
You're gonna be on "good morning
usa" and you need a new costume.
Mom, I don't wanna
go to New York.
Son, you've just
been booked on national TV.
I thought we were done
with all these interviews.
I'm not going to New York.
I don't wanna go!
Whoa, Whoa. Excuse me, sir,
but we already told them
that we would be there, so you
are going, and that is final.
Good morning, usa.
I'm Julian Peters.
And I'm
Carson Dale.
Our first
guest today is
child viral sensation
Lucas Simons.
He has the viral world
at storm about
his new video called
"anyone's ghost?"
So here he is,
Lucas Simons.
Lucas, let's get
right into it.
How did you
fake the video?
I mean,
it looks so real.
You must be the youngest p.T.
Barnum the world has ever seen.
Lucas, tell us how in the
world you, at 11 years old,
have been able to fool
scholars and scientists
the world at large into thinking
this is anything but a giant hoax.
It's not a hoax.
Okay, well,
Lucas, your video
has now surpassed
ten million hits.
So If the video
is real,
what do you think it was
that you captured?
Lucas, you with us?
Lucas?
There he goes, off to
create his next masterpiece.
And we can't wait to see that one too.
We'll be right back.
You stop right there,
young man!
What do you think
you're doing?
Don't you dare
ruin this for us!
Maybe It's time
that we give Lucas
a little break from
these interviews.
Come on, son,
it'll be all right.
- You're pushing him.
- Oh, me?
You're the one who jumped
at the first opportunity.
Oh, yeah,
this was my idea.
You're the one telling
him that we need money!
Money? Have you seen our bills?
His funeral isn't even paid for!
Are you seriously
bringing that up right now?
Who's all this for? I
mean, It's not for Lucas.
Okay, this is about me?
Well, have you seen the interviews?
You-you eat up the attention.
Well, what do you expect me to do?
Just go back to the way things were?
Look, this isn't
what he needs!
Maybe he needs a father who'll
sit down and talk to him!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You're mother of the year.
Look, you don't have
a monopoly on grief!
Nobody's talking
about that!
You're not
the only one!
I just can't handle this, Roger.
I can't. I'm done.
Okay? I'm done!
Bitch.
I've never heard them
fight like that before.
You think they're
gonna split up?
Well, parents
fight sometimes.
Doesn't always mean
they're gonna get a divorce.
I hate them.
Come on.
You don't hate them.
Brussels sprouts you hate,
your parents not so much.
I can understand that
you're angry with them.
I mean, they certainly aren't gonna
win any parent of the year awards.
Win? They wouldn't
even be nominated.
Look, Lucas, It's not
always easy being a parent.
You know? Sometimes you just
do the best that you can.
How would you know? You've
never even been a parent.
Look. It's okay to be mad.
But the important thing
you need to learn how to do
is to forgive.
Sometimes that's
the only thing you can do.
And If you can't do that,
It's hard to move on.
Lucas?
Son, we've been worried.
Your father's out
looking for you right now.
Come here.
Do you remember
that time you
fell into the lake
trying to feed the ducks?
I almost had
a heart attack.
And then
Jake got all mad
because he jumped
in for no reason.
Yeah.
I think he thought
you were gonna drown.
It's not that deep.
I miss him
too, mom.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
And I love you
so much.
Hi, you've reached Claudia.
And Drake.
Sorry we can't
get to the phone right now,
but please leave us a message
and We'll call you right back.
Have a nice day!
Oh! It's Halloween!
I forgot it was
Halloween!
Just a minute. Have I
got something for you.
Just a minute!
Wait right here.
Ah, here!
Look what we have here!
Ah.
Let's see If we can
feed the skeleton.
Can we?
There it goes.
Oh, he'll be full now!
Oh, um, I'm...
Looking for
Susan Parker.
It's Sam now.
Who are you?
Mrs. Parker?
What brings you here?
Making another movie?
I... I really just came
here to say I'm sorry.
Oh.
So you're sorry now,
are you?
What you filmed,
what you captured
was extraordinary.
I believe it was real.
But it belonged to me,
and you, you ruined it.
I didn't... What were you doing
filming my husband's funeral anyway?
I was just... I know you like
filming other people's funerals.
So I guess you just like
other people's pains.
Is that it?
What you did...
Turned my grief
into a, a joke.
I know you're just a child so I
guess that you're just too young
to understand
this kind of pain.
Look,
Mrs. Parker.
Just because I'm a kid doesn't
mean I don't understand pain.
I lost my older
brother, okay?
He was my
best friend.
Out family used to be happy,
but when he died,
everything changed.
I miss him every day.
And sometimes... I wish
I would have died, and not him.
I didn't mean to turn
his funeral into a joke.
It sucks! So many people
have said so many bad things
about you,
and I am sorry.
That's the only reason
why I wanted to come here.
Lucas?
Martin's in
a better place now.
That's what
I've come to believe.
What I've accepted.
I'm starting to move
on with my life now.
So...
Maybe It's time
that you did the same.
I'm sorry about
your brother, man.
I know what It's like
to lose someone you love.
I just...
Don't know how.
Well, what
do you mean?
I miss him
every day.
I just don't know
how to move on.
It's tough.
You're never gonna stop missing
the ones that you love.
You're always gonna wish you
can go back and change things.
But at some point,
you pick up the pieces
and you just start
living again.
What'd your family
used to do for fun?
Dad used to take us
to the amusement park.
One time, mom threw up
on the tilt-a-whirl.
Jake never
let her forget that.
I like go-carts.
I'm right
behind you!
Aah! What? What?
Well, you know what?
You cheated.
No way. I beat
you by a mile.
Hmm.
Hey, Lucas, with all your
new found fame and fortune,
you must be beating the
ladies off with a stick.
No!
Well, there is
this one girl.
I knew it! Name!
Kimberly, but
she's just a friend.
Mm-hmm!
She's actually
kind of cool.
We both like a lot
of the same things.
I was thinking about asking her
to the dance, but I don't know.
What? Go for it.
How?
Just call her up.
I'm not a big phone person.
Plus, she lives just next door.
That makes it easy. Just go
up to her and ask her out.
Okay, look,
here's what you do.
Throw some rocks at her window,
and then when she opens it
you throw in a paper airplane
with a note that Says,
"will you go to
the dance with me?"
No. And that's
vandalism.
All right.
Well, think
of something.
You're
creative.
Just make it
your own.
Chris! She said yes!
Way to go!
Wait. Do you even
know how to dance?
Huh?
Come on.
All right. Let's see
your moves, kid.
Okay, stop. You look
like you're in pain.
Is that the robot?
Yeah.
What's-what's wrong
with his arm?
It was broken?
It's the dance.
Why is the robot on the dance
floor with a broken arm?
He should be at a robot
shop being repaired.
Look. Okay.
You're too stiff.
You gotta loosen up
a little bit, okay?
Get some soul into it.
Yeah, move your body.
Just have fun with it.
You got to feel the
music all through you.
Okay, now look.
This is you.
It's like you're driving
a stagecoach or something.
No, you gotta feel the music.
Okay? You can't be shy.
At the dance
you gotta...
Foom!
See that?
That's really good!
All right, come on.
Keep it going.
Okay, you know, I think I
know what our problem is.
Our music choice. What kind of
music do you usually listen to?
Classical.
Classical?
You can't dance
to classical.
I don't plan
on dancing.
Wait, wait, wait.
I think I got an idea.
Dad?
What?
Can you help me
with this tie?
Yeah. Sure.
All right.
Big night for
my little man, huh?
Measure it off
right where you want it.
Should come down to just
the top of your belt buckle.
Now, under, around.
This is a half windsor.
And through.
There you go.
Symmetrical knot.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I like your outfit.
It's different.
It's cool.
Thanks.
It's very "nosferatu."
Those guys
are jerks.
It's okay.
Wanna dance?
Sure.
This music sucks!
Yeah, principal worley's
a horrible d.J.
Hold on. I got it.
Pff!
Hmm.
Honey,
this is terrible.
I know.
Whoa.
The spice cap
fell off.
I can tell.
Oh, my gosh!
I wonder how
the dance is going.
Oh. I can't believe
Lucas went to a dance.
With a date!
You know, I think he's
getting better. Hmm?
Yeah. The other day I was watching
a basketball game. Mm-hmm.
He walks in the room and he makes
a comment about the point guard.
No! Believe me, I was
as shocked as you.
Hmm.
We got a great kid.
Yeah.
I love that version
of Beethoven.
It's a very modern take.
Maybe you could learn
to play it on your cello.
Yeah, I was...
Kind of thinking about
giving up the cello.
I suck.
Vell, you know
what zey say.
Transylvania vas not
built in a day!
Chris! You'll
never believe it.
Beethoven's fifth
was a total hit.
Chris?
Chris!
Nurse, what do
we have here?
Male, mid-forties.
Ultra panic state.
Stay calm.
We have a heart attack.
Dr. albanson, 204.
He's right there.
Chris!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Oh, don't worry.
Everything's fine.
I-I'm gonna be okay.
I found you on the floor.
I thought you were gonna die.
Yeah, well,
thanks to you, I didn't.
What's wrong with you?
Well, the way the doctors
explained it to me is that,
um, I have a weak heart.
They said It's the reason
I almost died before.
I guess I've just been
living on borrowed time.
Why didn't you
tell me before?
Well, that's not something
I wanted to focus on.
Hey, did you call your parents
and let 'em know where you are?
Okay, good.
So how was the dance?
But, you're gonna
be okay, right?
Yeah. Well, thanks to you
I got a third chance.
So about
the dance, what happened?
Well...
Is-is everything okay?
Hi.
You're Chris?
Mmm.
Uh, well, Lucas has,
he's told us a little about you.
Oh. It's nice
to meet you folks.
I'm sorry it couldn't be
under better circumstances.
Oh, no, It's...
Lucas, honey, we should probably go.
I'm sure Chris is tired.
But, I wanna
stay with Chris.
No, no. You should go
with your parents, buddy.
I'll be all right.
Mmm.
I love you.
Good night, son.
We're here to see
Chris Brighton.
Hmm.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mr. Brighton was never admitted.
It looks like he was
released to hospice care.
What's that?
Oh, honey,
it just means
he went to a different
kind of hospital.
Come on.
Lucas.
Sweetheart.
No matter what happens
to your friend Chris...
You're not alone, okay?
Buddy, I'm here.
Your dad's here.
We're a family and we're
gonna stay that way,
I promise you that.
He's dying,
isn't he?
No flip book
today, Lucas?
Nope.
Just me.
Anything
on your mind?
I'm mad at
my friend Chris.
He's a liar.
Why do you say
he's a liar?
He always talks about living
when he's actually dying.
So you think he should focus
on the fact that he's dying?
I guess you have a point.
Go right
there, okay?
Hey! Lucas!
Long time no see.
How've you been, buddy?
I've been good.
I'm glad you came by.
Lucas, I have some things
I wanted to tell you.
I haven't been
totally honest with you.
Well, what do you mean?
I never told you
about my son.
You have a kid?
Well, he's not
a kid anymore.
He's in college now.
And I haven't seen
him in a long time.
Why not?
Well, I sort
of blew it
when he was
a child.
I got married
pretty young.
I wasn't ready
to be a father.
My ex-wife,
she moved away.
And eventually we
just lost contact.
Don't you try
to talk to him?
Oh, yeah,
I've tried.
I don't think he's ever
gonna forgive me.
And quite frankly I don't,
I don't blame him.
Well, you shouldn't
give up.
And sometimes...
Maybe you just have to
forgive yourself.
Right.
So what
have you been up to?
I've been thinking.
About what?
I'd like to...
Reinvent myself.
Oh, really?
As a director?
And I need your help.
Okay.
Do you have
a crew this time?
All right,
tell me more.
A great man
once told me,
life is all about
living the now.
At least, that's what
I think he was saying.
Whoo!
Life is made up of a series
of magical moments.
Some we understand
and others we don't.
Bad things happen, and
that's just a part of it all.
The important thing is not
to dwell on those bad things,
and move on.
Just keep living and...
Focus on...
Life.
You did so good.
I have to say bye to Chris.
Okay.
Hey.
I really loved
the movie.
Thanks. It-It's
just a rough cut.
Yeah.
Yeah, well,
I think It's great.
Oh, and by the way, I thought
you might like to know
that my son called
me the other day.
How'd that go?
Well, Rome wasn't
built in a day.
Lucas, you-you got
a real talent, man.
Don't ever stop
seeking the truth, okay?
'Cause nobody
has all the answers.
We're just trying to
do the best we can.
Everyone deals with death
in their own way.
And letting go...
Is the hard part.
I know
your brother Jake
meant the
world to you.
You're never gonna
stop missing him.
And that memory is gonna
always be a part of you.
And that's okay.
Because it just
means that Jake
will always be
a part of you.
But you can't
stop living
when bad things
happen.
Because...
Every experience
is precious.
And every experience,
it ultimately ends.
And that's life.
That's life, buddy.
I...
I don't want
you to die.
You got your whole
life ahead of you.
Your whole life.
I'm just glad that
I got to be a part of it.
Thank you.