♪
♪ we're gonna have
a happy christmas ♪
♪ we're gonna have a--
we're gonna have a ♪
♪ get up get up
♪ it's the holiday season
♪ right up
♪ now it's christmas time
Jason, stephanie.
Inside voice
and walking feet, please.
Yes, miss bell.
[man]
looking for someone?
James!
So happy you made it.
Of course, I made it.
Next time,
Use that app I showed you.
And you'll see
If I'm not with you.
I'm always on my way.
So, how was the big
holiday pageant?
Uh, terrific.
If you ignore the fact
that two of the shepherds
Were picking their noses,
And mary twisted her ankle
on the dreidel.
Oh, a judeo-christian mishap.
I'm so happy we're spending
Christmas together.
So, you ready for tonight?
The ballantine capital
holiday party
Is the social event
of the season.
At least to the ballantines.
I'm still debating
on what to wear.
Well, I'm sure
whatever you wear,
You will look beautiful.
And my mother will
scrutinize your dress
And find it distasteful.
Oh, sounds like fun.
It will be, as long
as we're together.
Come on, I'll show you
my classroom.
Oh.
♪ frosty has his top hat
♪ rudolph his red nose
Good job today,
merry christmas.
Bye everyone,
Miss bell?
Oh, mrs. Lo,
wasn't bobby just darling?
I can't find him.
I've looked everywhere.
Oh, I'm sure he's here.
Okay, why don't you
check the cubby room,
And I'll look
in the classroom.
Okay.
I'm sure he's hiding
under one of the desks.
Oh, yeah.
[man]
come on, get in the car.
Honey, you know what?
I think I left
my scarf by the manger.
Will you run and get it?
Scarf retrieval. Can do.
Thank you, sweetie.
I'll go check on bobby.
Stop!
Miss bell?
Miss bell, that's my dad.
He is? You are?
Uh-huh.
Oh. Oh, uh...
Well, unfortunately,
The faculty was
informed that your
Visitation rights
have been suspended.
It's christmas.
Bobby, say goodbye
to your dad
And then go find your mom.
Okay. I love you, dad.
Bye, bobby.
Bye.
Do you have a phone?
Yeah.
You're lucky I'm in
the holiday mood, mr. Lo.
You see, if I call this
in to the police,
You would be
in big trouble.
But if you did,
They'll probably
give you a break.
Merry christmas!
[james]
was he under the desk?
Yep, I know my bobby.
So you ready
to face my parents?
Uh, I think
I can handle it.
♪ [piano plays carol]
Before my mother gets
the chance to berate you,
I have to say,
you look amazing.
Mm, flattery will
get you everywhere.
[chuckles]
Honey...
Why is everything
so quiet?
This is a party,
isn't it?
Shh, don't tell them.
They might actually smile.
Oh, got it.
Uh-oh, incoming ballantines
at ten o'clock.
Now, remember,
my parents are old money.
Old establishment.
Aloof.
Upper crust.
And arrogant.
This is gonna be fun-- hi!
Hi, dad.
James.
Mom.
Darling.
I'd like you to meet...
Tory bell.
Hi.
Told you.
Well, I'm glad you
could join us, tara.
It's-- it's tory.
Happy holidays.
Well, not half as happy
as yours is going to be.
The south of France
sounds so exciting.
Oh, never been?
[phone vibrates]
Sorry.
Um...
Will you just excuse me
for a moment?
Dad, I know you have
your reservations,
But I really have
feelings for tory.
How much do you know
about this girl?
I know I care about her,
I know I want to be with her,
And I know, for me,
that's enough.
[man]
guess who?
Sorry, drawing a blank.
I'm hurt, tornado.
Spending six years
on the inside
Kept your memory
very fresh for me.
I didn't know they
allowed calls this late.
[man chuckles]
Read the morning papers,
bell. I'm out.
And I'm coming for you.
All of you.
Fresh glass?
I have to go.
Go where?
I have to leave.
Ah, I get it, you're--
No, I-- I have to leave.
New york. Right now.
No, w--
I can't get
into it right now.
It's just-- it's too much.
But I love you.
I'm about to give my toast.
Where should we all stand?
Unfortunately, I have to go.
But I'm sure it'll
be a great toast.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You sure?
I'm sure.
I have to go
help my parents with--
Stuff.
Tory?
James, please.
Tory, I just need to know
That you're okay,
that we're okay.
We're totally okay.
Look, I promise, I will
explain everything to you
At new year's.
New year's?
What about--
I will so
make this up to you.
It will be a whole different
kind of celebration.
Something like...
[whispers]
You can do that?
Willing to try.
Okay, I'm completely baffled,
But my new year's
countdown starts now.
[giggles]
New year's.
You are a mysterious woman,
tory bell.
Ma'am.
Thank you.
Tenth and first
for a quick stop.
Then trenton, new jersey.
And hurry, please.
Baby!
Daddy!
Sweetheart!
Mommy!
Oh! Did you flip
your daddy again?
Yeah.
Ma, clothes.
Oh, being such a prude.
Look, she's so cute.
Look at you, you look like
a real new yorker now.
I can... Hardly...
I'm gonna get you something
for your shoulder.
She took you down
pretty hard.
That's my girl.
What were you
thinking, dad?
That move has never
worked on me.
You home for the holidays?
Uh, kind of,
for the holidays.
You're not spending it
with that new guy?
I googled him.
I gotta know
What my little girl
is up to.
Guys, guys, guys, look.
I'm so happy
to see you, but...
I'm actually not just
here for the holidays.
I got a call.
Marty's motorcycles?
I put your name
in the christmas raffle.
I got a call from manucci.
He's still got 20 years
on his sentence.
He's out.
And he's coming for us.
For me.
He threatened you?
I was always afraid of this.
You took him out when
you were just a teenager.
That drove him crazy.
Well then, we gotta
take him down again.
Put him away for good.
I'll get cousin bones
to put a tail
On manucci's sister.
I wanna know where
big donna's heading.
Nobody threatens the bells.
Nobody.
Welcome home, tornado.
Let's get to work.
[gale]
our tail said big donna
should be here.
Yep, big donna's
definitely here.
You and me, we'll suit up
so donna and her bodyguards
Don't pick us out.
Mom? What's up?
You never could get
your hair right yourself.
[chuckles]
[tory coughs]
Still gorgeous.
That does not look like me.
Used to.
Can't believe I got
my baby girl back.
You sure you're
up for this?
Yeah, I'm cool.
Ma?
Yeah, hon?
What if someone sees me
in these pants?
[gale chuckles]
Let's go catch a bad guy.
[tory]
you sure I look okay?
[gale]
I think you look gorgeous.
Wow.
[tory]
he's your tail?
Just cause you two broke up
Doesn't mean we fired him.
Hey, come here.
Be careful out there.
I love sounding official.
What?
Electric blue pumps
look good on you.
Very funny,
but I have work to do.
You tweaking
on seeing me again?
I'm not tweaking,
I just...
I wanna get this done, and
I don't want any distractions.
I'm a distraction now?
Say, I used to be
your partner.
I have a new boyfriend now.
And a new life.
I heard. In fact,
most of trenton has heard.
Investment banker.
Pretty fancy.
Okay, as much as I'm
enjoying this small talk,
This is what
we're going to do.
As soon as we see big donna,
[through radio]
you guys take
the bodyguards out.
I'll get close enough
to drop
The tracking device,
then we're out.
Dad, tory. You copy?
Sweetie, code names,
remember?
Right.
Tornado to banshee one.
Any sighting of the target?
No target present.
Black hawk?
No visual.
Ho ho ho!
I've got her.
She's definitely covered.
[gale]
did she spy you?
No, she's looking at shoes.
Hideous shoes, but shoes.
[hawk]
and the bodyguards?
Too close.
We can't move yet.
She's at the salon.
There's no way they'll
let the bodyguards
Into the treatment rooms.
Now's the time
to take them out.
[tory giggles]
I just need someone
to touch up my gels.
Sure, let me see
what I can do.
Whenever you
have an opening.
Move, now.
It's true what they say.
The right undergarment
makes a woman
Feel like a woman.
You coming?
She'll be in there a while.
Ain't that the truth?
All right, I'm going
to hit the head.
All right.
[groans]
One down, he'll
be out for a while.
Ho ho ho.
Want a closer look?
Come on, don't be shy.
[groans]
Two down and out.
[men grunt]
A... Puppy?
[fight over radio]
Come on, mike.
Come on.
[kid]
thank you, santa.
Is... Is he okay?
Yeah, he slipped. Yeah.
Three down.
It's all you, tory.
Tory "wild woman" bell?
I can't believe you're back!
Hi!
Hi, hey,
We're gonna have
to catch up later.
Tony? Mario?
Cover's blown.
She's running.
[tory]
excuse me.
Pardon me.
What's wrong, manhattan?
Jersey too rough
for you now?
Out for a day
of beauty, donna?
Girl's gotta look her best.
Now back off me, bell.
All of you.
I know my rights.
You can't
hassle me like this.
I'm a classy lady
in these parts.
[gale chuckles]
You're right, donna.
I'm sorry.
We just get ahead
of ourselves sometimes.
That's more like it.
It's like you
never left, tor.
Oh, cousin bones is texting.
According to bones, she's
heading east onto ashmore.
Oh, no, you're not
going anywhere.
Mikey muscles,
how's it hanging?
Lizzie the legs.
Shaved, moisturized,
and ready for action.
Liz, I would love to catch up,
but this really is--
First of all, you never
told me you were coming back.
What the front-door
is that all about, huh?
I missed you, girl.
I--
second, I thought
You got out of
the family business.
That's why you left.
She thought she did too,
But we pulled her back in.
Well, I'm glad.
Liz, I got a great
teaching job there.
So, what, you went
to manhattan, that's it?
It's only through
the holland tunnel.
I guess it's also
kind of a different world.
It is to some people.
Liz, I am so sorry
I didn't call.
I-- I meant to,
it's just that I--
You got all caught up
in your new guy.
Been there, done that.
But you can't forget
your girlfriends.
I know.
So...
How does it all work, tory?
I mean, big banker
and a bounty hunter?
Yeah, how does that work?
It works fine.
I'm not a bounty hunter
anymore.
This is just
kind of a one-off.
Oh. Okay, well...
I hope this whole visit
isn't just a one-off.
It'd be nice to hang out
with you again.
For sure.
Later, mikey-boy.
Over and out, legs.
[man]
smile!
I get why you don't
wanna hang out with me.
Since I'm your
smokin' hot ex-boyfriend.
Ha-ha, very funny.
Thank you.
Tory, there's a lot of people
On this side of the bridge
who still care about you.
You might wanna
think about that
While you're so busy
planning your new life.
Worked like a charm.
[locater beeps]
Good.
What do you think?
If he's in there, that service
door is his access point.
No fugitive ever wants
to be too far away
From his vehicle.
Gale, watch
the front entrance.
I'm gonna take
the east exit.
The two of you
stay together.
Could be a trap.
Go.
[mike strains]
Really?
Okay.
That works too.
They're here.
Leopold?
That girl is mine.
You got it, boss.
You hungry?
[voice]
tory?
Tory?
I know you're here,
I used that app I showed you--
Mike, 12 o'clock!
All right.
Did the bear just explode?
Who's this guy?
This?
Uh...
Dad, james.
James, dad.
All right, here we go.
How is he?
Delicious and fine.
It was just a bump.
Thanks for
the house call, liz.
It's nice having a nurse
in your contacts, isn't it?
Yeah.
Liz, I'm-- I'm sorry
I let so much time
pass between us.
You were always
a really good friend.
I still am.
You should give me
a test drive sometime.
You got it.
So, aside from
mr. Delicious,
What's so great
in manhattan?
Uh, well, in manhattan,
I-- I can be...Tory.
You know, in trenton,
everyone sees me as tornado.
It's like this role
I fell into that never ends.
I thought you loved
being a bounty hunter.
No, I do. I did.
But, no, I like the...
Other parts of me.
You know, when I met james,
That's all he saw.
Just the other parts of me,
and it felt great.
The guys here, they just--
Just sees me as
one of the guys.
One guy didn't.
Yeah, well, I guess
I wanted an option other than
Mikey muscles.
I understand.
All right,
house call's over.
I gotta get back to work.
All right.
Thanks again.
Okay, I just need
To make a few
little adjustments.
What's she doing
with redneck santa?
I just want the place
to look nice.
Honey, I worked for hours
getting it just right.
Okay. Okay, this stuff
cannot be in the house.
What're you
so worried about?
He doesn't know about the...
Family business.
You didn't tell him
we're bounty hunters?
It, uh, never came up.
I know, I know,
I know, it's just,
James is not just
another boyfriend.
He's from a whole
different world.
Mom, you know,
you googled him.
Tornado renee bell.
You can't hide yourself.
She's not hiding herself.
She's hiding us.
I'm not hiding you.
I love you guys.
I do, it's just, well,
This would be a bit
of a shock for james.
I just need
to ease him into it.
Please.
Please help me.
Just play along.
Okay, honey, okay.
How?
Just act... Normal.
Can do.
We got your back, tor.
Consider it done.
What do you mean by normal?
Well, let's start with
putting the girls away.
Well, I'll try, but
the girls aren't exactly shy.
Okay, ma, normal people
don't say things like that.
Got it.
Okay, uh...
Daddy?
Do you have any...
Sleeves?
[gasps]
Ain't doing it.
Do it.
Done.
Use mine.
Anything else, sweetie?
[james moans]
Act fancy.
Act fancy!
Cracker?
Cheese?
Footrub?
Um...
Sweetie?
Oh, thank god.
Ah, I thought I was...
Did that cheese
come out of a can?
Honey, I am so glad
you're feeling better.
You really
hit your head hard.
Ow, I did?
Yeah.
Mom. Dad.
Cousin bones.
This is my boyfriend.
James ballantine.
Charmed.
Enchante.
Oh, nice to meet you all.
Oh, very festive tree.
And crossbow.
I know, right?
That was a wedding gift.
My dear.
Aw, don't mind if I do.
Libation?
You know, I think james
should rest some more.
No no no,
really, I'm fine.
So, I've never been
in this part of new jersey.
It's very--
[electricity sizzles]
Oh!
Is that a weapon?
Nah, it's just a stun-gun.
For a little peace of mind,
you know what they say.
Criminals always come to the
nice side of town to steal.
Right, of course.
[police radio chatter]
Not to worry, that's
just my police scanner.
Computer game
that I play nonstop.
That's why it's always on.
Oh, you're a gamer?
At work, I have excel tetra.
[bones]
no way, which version?
Five.
[women chuckle]
Wow, that's impressive.
See, we're all
getting along so well.
Yes we are, mrs. Bell,
And I am so happy about that
Because I actually came here
To speak to mr. Bell.
Me?
Yes.
I know you don't
know much about me.
And that I haven't been
dating tory for very long.
So your mind must be
filled with questions.
Who is this man?
What does he stand for?
Where is he from?
Well, here are
some answers.
My name is james oswald
ballantine the third.
Fancy.
Mom.
I come from the upper
east side of manhattan.
And I stand for
Whatever makes tory happy.
Oh my.
I know you feel protective.
Protective? You
obviously haven't
Seen my girl
choke someone out.
Up. Choke someone up.
With emotion.
Tory's got a lot of heart.
A crazy amount.
Oh, I know.
And that's why
the real reason
I came here today,
mr. Bell, was
To ask your permission
To propose to your daughter.
[mom gasps]
What'd I miss?
Tory's getting married!
Some ring you got her.
Well, she's worth it.
Well, I didn't unscrew
the good stuff for nothing.
Let's celebrate!
I say we take this party
to boccino's.
Honey, you were
banned from there.
Oh yeah.
Boccino's sounds good.
But don't we have
work to do?
Serious work?
Tory, you gotta
celebrate tonight.
This is everything
you've ever wanted.
But... I don't have
clothes for boccino's.
Of course she does.
But... I need, um,
Boccino's
is kind of a dive.
Oh, your favorite bar
is suddenly a dive.
A dive bar, really?
Good, 'cause I can't tell you
How sick I am of cristal.
[they laugh]
I know, I know,
You and me both, right?
What is that?
Ma, help me get dressed.
Okay.
So you like the ring?
Hello, jersey.
I know, right?
I picked out
all your faves.
So many choices.
And so little time.
Help with your hair?
Oh, not tonight, ma.
I know it's
not quite your style.
Me, I'd say it
needs more gold.
But it's nice.
Thanks, ma.
For trying so hard
with james.
You got what
you wanted, tory.
A new life. Manhattan.
You're always gonna be
my little girl.
And I'm gonna miss you.
But I'm so happy for you.
Thanks, ma.
Tory, if you wanna go back
to new york with james,
We get it.
Between us and mike,
we can handle manucci.
No, I put manucci away
the first time.
He's back because of me.
And I'm gonna put him away
the second time too.
Like it or not,
You're a bell.
Okay...
[loud music plays]
Oh my god!
Tory, that's like
the taj mahal in rock.
Uh, james, this
is nurse stonebrook.
But I've known her my entirely
life as lizzie the legs.
You can use elizabeth
if it feels better to you.
Uh, no way, I much prefer
"lizzie the legs."
Oh my god, he's so cute.
I could just...
Mikey muscles,
what brings you by?
I just missed
the big moment.
I couldn't miss
the celebration.
Mike.
Yeah, tory.
Don't take it personally.
Exes are like that.
And by exes,
I just meant...
I'm gonna stop now.
Do you need to use
the bathroom?
No.
Yes, you do.
You dated him?
Young and dumb.
Well, how long
did you guys go out?
Oh, I wouldn't even
call it going out.
It was over
before it began.
He used to work for my dad,
And... You know.
Right, right.
Tory, what kind of business
is your dad in?
I mean, when you mentioned that
your father was a businessman,
I kind of pictured--
james.
I want to explain
it all to you.
And I will, but it's
a little complicated,
And I just wanna
do it at the right time.
Honey, can we please just
Celebrate tonight?
Yes.
Hi.
Sorry about that, tory.
I figured you told him
about mike.
I was going to,
but this thing came up.
Plus, mike and I are
done. It's over.
If you say so.
Come on,
there's a coat girl.
Oh, no no. It's fine.
I think I'll keep it on.
Come on, tory,
you gotta move.
Come on, bell, dance.
You look gorge!
Now you're talking!
How long have
you known tory?
Since junior high.
You?
Ten months.
Dude doesn't waste any time.
Well, when it's meant to be,
it's meant to be.
What're you drinking?
Uh, well, uh,
I think champagne
is appropriate.
Can I get a champagne
for my friend, and a--
Shot and a beer chaser,
mike?
How'd you guess?
Actually,
forget the champagne.
I'll have what he's having.
A shot and a beer.
Chaser.
Oh, looks like your ex
and your man are getting along.
Oh shoot.
Help me.
So, what do you do?
Uh, well, we...
Look for companies
that are in trouble,
And we acquire them.
Sounds like we're
in the same business,
Except we find people
in trouble, and we--
Okay, stop being such guys
And get your butts
on the dance floor.
Ah, I'm waiting on a shot.
And a beer chaser.
Fine, I'll go easy on you
'cause it's your
first night tonight.
Muscles, don't
make me play hard.
You win, legs.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Pookie, hi!
Hi.
Woo.
Nice work today.
You too.
Okay, should we talk?
About what?
Well--
three years later,
You're engaged.
Now you wanna talk?
You know when
I wanted to talk?
Before you ditched me
and left town.
I know I didn't
handle it well.
But mike, it wasn't
anything you did.
It was me.
Wow.
That's what it feels like
to hear that.
What?
It's not you, it's me.
I use that line
a few times myself.
Have a nice night.
Hey.
I haven't danced
in quite a while.
Oh, you're pretty good.
No, tor, I'm inspired.
Aw.
[women laugh]
hey, tory!
You up for a shot
and a beer chaser?
It's pretty good!
Sure!
Come on,
future mrs. Delicious.
Let's toast.
You snagged a good one.
I know. James is amazing.
It's kind of hard
to celebrate with mike here.
Oh, come on, you can't expect
mikey to be happy tonight.
He's been hung up
on you for years.
He'll get over it.
Years?
He hasn't had a girlfriend
since you left.
A guy who looks like that,
you do the math.
But he'll get over you.
If you let him.
Ooh! Party.
I know you think
I didn't care about you.
Don't tell me
what I think.
And I know you don't
understand--
don't tell me
What I don't understand.
Okay, mike,
let's not make this
Any more difficult
than it already is.
Difficult? For you
or the guy you left behind?
Tory.
What you don't understand is
I love you.
Loved.
Past tense, right?
Past, present.
Future.
I'm engaged.
♪ [house music]
You've been
holding out on me.
You are an incredible
dancer.
Come on!
I wanna see some more moves.
What're you doing
with those?
Oh, just reminiscing.
Our shore lives
are really crazy.
But fun.
Do you remember that
christmas in key west?
Do I remember it? That was
the best christmas ever.
We nabbed tommy franklin.
Dewey beach.
When hawk and gale
collared cole harper.
Wasn't that the first time
you used a stun gun?
Yep.
Do you think I can
be a normal wife?
With a normal family?
I think you can be anything
you wanna be, tor.
We all do.
Mike called. He got a tip.
Manucci'll be at
the cliff street lot tonight.
Where they sell
christmas trees?
Yep.
Let's roll.
Come on,
let's stake it out.
Maybe someday, honey.
Where is everyone?
They went out.
Out? Where?
To the christmas tree lot.
In case auntie
got sick of hers.
Oh, well, shouldn't
we have gone with them?
I mean, shouldn't we help
pick out the tree?
I'd prefer to stay here
in case the phone rings.
Oh. You're the desk guy.
Exactly. Besides,
Mike is with them, and he can
help them with the tree.
Mike is with them?
Yeah, he's a pretty
strong guy.
[clears throat]
You know, I'm a...
Desk guy, too.
And, uh, sometimes
I get really sick of it.
Tell me about it.
Don't you ever wish
you could just say,
"screw the rules"
and follow your passion?
You have no idea.
Let's go.
Let's go chop down a tree.
Yes!
Come on!
♪ o christmas tree
o christmas tree ♪
♪ much pleasure doth
thou bring thee ♪
♪ for every year
the christmas tree ♪
♪ shines through all
so brightly ♪
♪ o christmas tree
o christmas tree ♪
♪ much pleasure doth--
Tory! Hey!
James!
Honey, what are
you doing here?
Yeah, what are you
doing here, sweetheart?
James and I aren't
desk guys.
Have you lost your mind?
A little, I'm sorry.
We both wanted to help
pick out the tree.
Shh!
Huh?
I mean, I... Honey,
I-- I wanted to surprise you
With what will be our
first christmas tree
To hang my crystal angel on.
Oh, well, a family
Should pick out
their tree together.
Where do we start?
Shh!
Daddy, where do we start?
Well, gale's gonna
wait by the car.
To make sure that
it keeps running.
Yeah, and-- and...
Tory and mike,
uh, why don't you
Check around that trailer.
See if you'll find anyone.
Bones and james.
Take the far, far, far
east end of the lot.
Far.
Great trees there.
Wow, so you take your
tree-shopping seriously.
I do.
Deadly serious.
Now go.
Be careful.
It's a tree lot
in trenton, tory.
Not the black forest--
shh!
I love you.
Mike, if anything
goes wrong,
I've gotta
watch out for james.
Will you help me?
Really?
You're really
asking if I'll help
Protect your fiancee?
Sure.
Just your partner.
Manucci's here, for sure.
Okay, you get him.
I'll look for manucci.
[chuckles]
Now, I'm almost sad
to see this end, bell.
Almost.
Goodbye.
What was that?
Sound like a .38!
Yeah, right.
Get off of me,
you little spider monkey!
Come on!
Are you kidding me?
[men grunt]
[tory shouts]
I got this,
boss, I got this.
I didn't manhattan socialites
could fight like this.
I'm not a manhattan
socialite.
Yet.
Let's go, let's go!
Tory?
James, get down!
Why are you holding a gun?
Because I'm--
A bounty hunter-- get down!
A what? A what?
No, tory!
James! J--
Daddy, daddy, are you okay?
Go with mike!
I can't believe
I got james into this.
It's not your fault.
He's the one that poked his
head out from behind the tree.
Mike.
Seriously, who hears gunshots
and pokes their head out?
Mike!
[car horn blares]
Seriously, don't
most people hit the deck?
Look, he's not
one of us, okay?
Okay, I didn't mean
anything by it.
[car horn blares]
"hey, bad guy with a gun,
I'm over here, shoot me."
Pssh, pssh! "ouch!"
[james grunts]
[car horn blares]
Damn it!
[manucci chuckles]
This is my fault.
He shouldn't even be here.
Listen to me.
We're gonna get him
back for you, okay?
You're gonna get married,
and it's all gonna be good.
Okay?
Thanks.
They're not gonna hurt him.
It's you they want.
Wow, thanks.
I didn't mean it like that.
No no no, really.
Thanks, you're right.
I'm good now.
Manucci's gonna lay down low
like the rat that he is.
But with a hostage,
he's gonna need a solid base.
If the tracking device is
still in big donna's pocket,
I can try to reactivate it.
Good thinking.
Hey guys!
Ooh, look who snagged
end-of-the-shift donuts!
Any takers?
Everyone okay?
Manucci got james.
Oh snap.
Can you imagine how much
that boy must be freaking out?
I mean, that dude's scary.
I'm shutting up now.
I don't know
what to do, dad.
If james gets hurt--
The tory I know knows
exactly what to do.
She knows how
to catch a criminal.
And probably
save her fiancee too.
You got him once, tory.
You can do it again.
Come on, bells, think.
Oh my.
What is it, tory?
White rhinestone heels.
Facial wax.
Extensions, spray tan.
Prom?
White glittery gazebo.
Oh my god.
A jersey wedding.
Big donna's
getting married.
It's probably gonna
be a big wedding.
'cause big donna's...
Big.
What we have
to figure out is--
Where. That's where we'll
get manucci and james.
Well, I know the location.
It's at the warehouse.
I saw the gazebo there.
Nobody moves a gazebo
once it's built.
But when is the wedding?
When did she get
a spray-tan?
Uh, two days ago?
A spray-tan goes
streaky in...
72 hours.
It's tomorrow.
Bones, see if you can find
plans on the warehouse.
[phone vibrates]
I need points of entry.
Passageways.
Underground, everything.
Okay.
What is it, tory?
Our invitation.
I need a donut.
You look beautiful, donna.
That makes two of us.
Huh?
Means a lot that you
came back to jersey for this.
I wanted at least one family
member at my wedding,
And everyone else is--
Dead.
[both]
or in prison.
Look, I wouldn't have
missed this for anything.
I mean, it's not every day
You see your
little sister get married.
No, it's not.
You know, but I know
this isn't exactly how
You pictured your wedding day
But I can't risk
being seen--
I know, being seen in public.
I know.
Do you think we would've been
happier if we'd gone straight?
No.
No way.
Absolutely not.
[both laugh]
Now remember.
This is my day, okay?
No funny stuff.
No guns. No business.
You think I'm dumb enough
to mess with a girl's wedding?
Even I'm afraid of that.
[people chatter]
Is the perimeter secure?
East end secure.
South secure.
Bones, any building plans?
Working on it.
Work faster.
You're sexy
when you're bossy.
Good to see you.
Great to see you!
So glad you could make it.
Oh. It is my honor,
my friend.
It is my honor, huh?
Look at you, who let you in?
Two beautiful women.
What has he got
that I don't got?
Huh? Share the wealth.
Good to see you,
good to see you.
They're here.
Good, glad they
could make it.
Try the shrimp.
Definitely.
Where is the shrimp?
How am I supposed
to rescue him
If I don't know
where he is?
Wait a sec.
You're gonna call him?
I'm gonna track
where he was.
Obviously manucci
took his phone.
But if we can find it,
James'll be nearby.
[phone beeps]
This does it for you?
Mm-hmm!
He's close. Blackhawk,
you see where james is?
Great.
They're at
the west corner.
I can't tell which room.
Hold up! Hold up!
Check out the crowd.
What is it?
Ho ho ho,
and a merry christmas
To the bell family!
[hawk]
all of these guys have
Outstanding
bounties on them!
Oh my.
Yeah, I'm a happy guy.
Yeah.
[dad]
bobby lace. $20,000!
Sticks crismarek? $30,000?
Oh, if we play
our cards right,
This is going
to be a very bountiful
Christmas for the bells.
Okay, fine,
but stay focused here.
James first.
Manucci second.
Then you guys can have your
Holiday shopping spree.
Roger that. Banshee one.
I'll see you
at the east exit.
Not if I see you first.
♪ [organ plays]
Should've been in here.
They had him here.
There's gotta be another
concealed space close by.
You actually thought
I'd be dumb enough
To let him keep his phone?
I'm insulted.
[gunshots]
[crowd shouts]
Are you freaking
kidding me?
Pardon me.
It's just a small caliber.
Sorry about that, huh?
Oh boy.
I told him no funny stuff
at my wedding.
My brother's a dead man.
He's headed that way!
Find james, I got this!
Aah!
What's your name?
Sorry, exit's closed.
Stick around.
It's almost cake time.
How's the shrimp? Yummy?
[manucci groans]
Aah!
It's been fun!
[manucci moans]
freeze!
It's over, manucci.
Yeah, bell.
It finally is over.
[manucci whistles]
[manucci laughs]
Let him go.
Let's make a deal, bell.
I mean, after all,
prince charming over here,
He's not the one
who caught me.
And sent me away
for six years.
What are you proposing?
I let him go.
And you, well...
You come with me.
Tory, or whoever
you actually are,
Don't.
[manucci laughs]
Yeah.
Yeah, that's
a good bell, huh?
Chin up.
It's going to be okay.
Just try and stay calm.
Please, "calm"
is my middle name.
Or "sort of calm."
Three fingers, duck.
What?
[tory groans]
Tory? Baby?
Tory, you okay?
Okay, james, stay right here.
No no no.
Don't move. Don't move!
No, tory!
Open the door!
Do it!
[manucci screams]
She's good.
She's really good.
She's a bell.
Watch your head.
Escaped convict with
a new attempted murder charge.
He's not gonna see the light
of day for a long time.
You're amazing, tory.
But you probably
already know that.
I do.
But you can tell me anyway.
I could tell you.
I could stand here
and tell you all day
That every time I see you
or talk to you,
It's as exciting as
the first time I saw you.
How I love
watching you fight.
But I also love watching you
Walk and talk and just be.
But there's another guy
who wants to do that.
A great guy.
Who can give you
a good life.
The new life
you wanted so much.
Lizzy keeps telling me
how you've changed.
She's right.
There is something
different about you now.
I'm even more handsome?
What changed, tory, is you.
You left and I realized
you needed more than just
Mike muscles,
although he was fine.
In your eyes.
So I took some
courses at college.
I'm pre-law now.
Get out!
Word of honor.
Losing you changed me.
So maybe the next
Beautiful, smart,
motivated butt-kicker
That walks into my life
will have a reason.
To stay.
Your guy's waiting.
[police radio chatter]
My hero.
You okay?
Uh-huh.
So, crazy, but I thought
You meeting my family
was the big hurdle.
I should've never
lied to you.
No, you shouldn't have.
Because I can't help
but wonder
What else wasn't true, tory?
Your name is tory, right?
I'm sorry.
If I was just
honest with you,
I know none of this
would've happened.
You wouldn't have
been knocked out.
Well, that's actually
happened before
On the slopes of chamonix.
You would've
never been zapped.
That was a first.
Kidnapped?
Ditto.
But it was
kind of a rush.
I just wish you'd given me
a chance to love the real you.
Because...
The woman I met in new york
And the woman I met here...
They're both pretty amazing.
So now that
all three of us have met,
Can we try again?
A big part of me
Wants to say yes.
But these last few days,
I've learned
An even bigger part
of me realized
I'm still a bounty-hunting,
Criminal-collaring,
Occasional
animal-print-wearing
Jersey girl.
[sighs]
Well, I'm gonna miss you,
jersey girl.
Bell? What the--
Welcome back to jersey.
[gale]
okay, attention,
attention.
I just want to say,
Welcome home to my girl.
We love you,
and we missed you,
And we are so happy
That you are home,
I can't tell you.
And because you and mikey
work so well together,
I was thinking,
me and my banshee
Could take some time off
And go on that honeymoon
we've been talking about.
What're you saying?
Follow me.
What're you doing?
Aww.
Crazy man.
Wait for it, wait for it.
Ah.
[gale gasps]
Oh!
Whoa!
You--
Daddy, you are so romantic.
Oh, it's the best
christmas present
I ever got.
I'd love to ride
with my guy.
Ho ho ho!
Ooh! Fancy.
Look at you two.
Must be working
some kind of magic.
I know a trick or two.
I wanted to drop off
my famous--
Cookies?! Liz's
christmas cookies?
Hot, sweet, and straight
from the oven.
Whoa, save some.
Yeah, right.
So, what's this I hear about
You staying in jersey?
There's nowhere
I'd rather be.
Aww, merry christmas,
you guys!
♪ snow is falling
♪ on the ground
♪ wind is blowin'
♪ and all around
♪ but ever since you
♪ came to town
♪ it's christmas
♪ every day
♪ you're the gift that
♪ keeps giving
♪ you're the song that
♪ keeps me singing
♪ 'cause when I have you
♪ next to me
♪ it's christmas
♪ every day
[santa]
ho ho ho!
Merry christmas!
♪ when I jump jump jump
♪ jump jump jump jump
♪ I do a fist pump
♪ pump pump pump pump pump
♪ when I jump jump jump
♪ jump jump jump jump
♪ I fist pump
makes me jump ♪
♪ so I don't look
like a chump ♪
♪ in the sleigh
way up high ♪
♪ deliverin' presents
christmastime ♪
♪ it's cold
temp drops below zero ♪
♪ polar bear club
got my speedo ♪
♪ me and phelps
nice and slow ♪
♪ with my jingle bells
all ready to go ♪
♪ make it snow
make it pour ♪
♪ let me pump my fist
some more ♪
♪ santa play it,
make it blow ♪
♪ milk and cookies
pump and go ♪
♪ going crazy
cut me loose ♪
♪ presents here
for me and you ♪
♪ catch my breath
and pump to the beat ♪
♪ with santa claus
next to me ♪
♪ I do a fist pump pump
♪ pump pump pump pump
♪ and I jump jump jump
♪ jump jump jump jump
♪ I do a fist pump pump
♪ pump pump pump pump
♪ and I jump jump jump
♪ jump jump jump jump
That's a wrap for
christmas bounty.
[applause]