[ music playing ]
[ waves crashing ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ gasps ]
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
[ gasps ]
[ waterfall rushing ]
[ panting ]
[ stereo playing rock-'n'-roll ]
Excuse me.
Have you seen this woman?
No.
How 'bout this man here?
Hey, if I were you,
I'd take
those photographs,
and I'd leave.
All right.
[ music playing in Spanish ]
[ woman gasping ]
Wait! Wait!
Wait, wait!
[ gasps ]
Please wait.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
No, stop! Stop! No!
[ yells ]
MAN: No, no, no! Todd!
Todd! Todd! Todd!
She's good.
Shit, we gotta go.
Come on! Come on.
Come on! Move!
Come on! Come on!
Erin!
I think we have--
Erin, stop!
Come on!
Wait! What the hell
is going on here?
Wait. Another one?
Yeah, yeah.
What do you mean another one?
Who are you people?
They're bad. We have to go.
Where am I?
Follow us. Come on!
[ sparks crackle ]
[ screams ]
There you go.
Jeez.
What'd she fall, three feet?
Bitch has been pretzeled.
Think she'll live?
No.
[ shallow breathing ]
[ panting ]
Okay, sweetheart, listen to me.
We'll get you out of here.
It's gonna be on a boat.
It's gonna be very choppy.
I'm not sure if you'll be able
to take the pain.
Give me a blink if you want me
to stop the pain.
Give me a blink, sweetheart.
[ neck cracks ]
All right.
Let's get her out of here
while she's still warm.
[ gasps ]
Shh, shh. Shh.
[ sobbing ]
What the hell was that?
Every few days,
they take someone new.
Where do they take them?
We don't know, but if you want
to survive out here,
you have to talk to Quentin.
And this Quentin,
he knows why we're here?
You can ask him yourself.
Let's go.
Come on.
[ beeping ]
What you got for me?
Got a call
from Nikolai in Kiev.
Nothing bad.
He said he's very pleased,
and he has some other business
he'd like to send our way.
That is excellent news.
Also our friend from the east
is coming tomorrow.
Mao? Okay.
Well, then I guess let's make
sure that there's a room prepared.
Mao's not coming alone.
Okay. Well, then I guess
we'll have to make sure that
there are more rooms prepared.
Hey, Chloe.
Where's Erin?
She's gone.
What?
No, no, no, no! Hey!
Chloe, where's Erin?!
Hi.
I love you.
What the hell happened?
They came out of nowhere,
and we got separated.
You're not supposed to separate!
Interesting.
One gets taken.
Another one shows up.
What's your name?
Billie,
Billie Kope.
I'm Quentin.
You can have that hut there.
It was Erin's.
There are some rules you'll
have to hear
before you settle in.
Mr. Quentin!
Thank you so much
for the hospitality,
but I never said I was staying.
You don't have to.
We don't
hold hostages here.
Who were those people
that came after us?
I've got some ideas.
Join us for dinner.
So, Ms. Kope...
what's your story?
Tell us how you got here.
You first.
Heh. They've all heard my story.
You'll find that a lot of the
circumstances are the same.
Yeah, I won a sweepstakes.
[ chuckles ]
Visit paradise. Heh.
The last thing I remember, I was
at a bar in Guatemala.
I was supposed to meet with this
crazy witch doctor dude.
He was gonna get me these
German expats on how to make ayahuasca.
What's ayahuasca?
That's hippie shit.
You got a closed mind, Todd.
No, it's not.
I never got to try it.
[ sighs ]
I was in a bar
drinking some tequila.
Next thing you know, right here,
paradise.
It was about a week ago.
I been here about five days.
I was doing a presentation
in Caracas,
and my head felt weird.
My stomach was hurting.
I thought I had food poisoning,
went to the doctor,
checked on my vital. It was good,
so I went back to the hotel.
Then I passed out.
Then, boom, I am here.
I felt like someone hit me
over the head
with a baseball bat.
I don't remember anything else.
Your turn, Ms. Kope.
Tell us your story.
Have you seen this man?
Do you know him?
No,
but I know someone who does.
Come on.
Look, I don't have anything.
I have no money, nothing, okay?
[ chuckles ]
Catch!
[ blade scrapes ]
[ laughs ]
[ groans ]
[ bone cracks ]
[ yells ]
[ gasps ]
I guess just like you guys,
I went out to a bar,
I came home...
and the next thing I remember,
I woke up here.
Why don't we all, uh...
have a moment of silence
for Erin?
Walsh, look alive.
We got incoming.
Jesus Christ, what happened?
Occupational hazard.
You killed her?!
She did it to herself.
Yeah, right.
Cut the bullshit.
What happened?
I don't know. Why?
Is there a problem?
Rich, I need you to go over
the stuff for Mao's visit.
Mao's coming? When?
Tomorrow, so be ready.
Walsh, what do you think?
She's still warm.
Gotta get her on the table
and look inside.
If she's not past
her expiration date, then we're good.
Xander, you were there.
What happened?
It's like the Sarge said.
Cut the bullshit.
What happened?
Look, I was
running after her.
I took the shot.
I missed.
She took off.
She fell,
broke her neck.
All right, get her inside.
Hurry.
[ birds warbling,
insects chirping ]
Hey, Billie.
Billie.
Hey, listen.
I know you're, like, freaked out
and stuff, right?
I got your back, baby.
I'll protect you.
I swear to God
I'm so good at that.
I'm good, thank you.
[ sighs ]
Billie.
You know
what sounds good?
Like, a bike ride...
and a nice cup of coffee.
If you need, like, a shoulder
to lean on,
I'm really good for that, too.
Th-Thank you.
And then cuddling naked.
[ sighs ]
Jean, how long
have you been here?
10 days.
And how'd you get here?
I went to San José,
Costa Rica,
for my wisdom tooth
to be removed.
I was visiting
friends in Cancún,
and they didn't want
to go out one night,
so I went out by myself.
Do you remember
where you were before?
Were you in prison?
Yeah, I was,
was in a Mexican prison.
It was just an ounce.
Pulled me over at a checkpoint.
They, uh,
searched my car.
It wasn't hidden very well,
and the rest is history.
Somebody must have slipped
something in my drink,
'cause I started
seeing spots.
They, uh, took me
to this prison doctor,
and he runs, you know,
test after test on me.
I took a cab back home.
I went back to my cell
to sleep, and...
I went back to my hotel...
And I woke up here.
So you go to sleep in
a Mexican prison
and then wake up here?
Yeah.
Is there anywhere I can get a
full view of this island?
Yeah, it's through this way.
You know,
both Berto and Todd
saw the doctor
before they came here.
Yeah, but, uh, Todd was
from Venezuela,
and, uh,
Berto was in Mexico.
So what? Still could be some
connection here.
Even Jean had
been to a dentist.
Had you been to a doctor
before you came here?
Actually, I did.
I got blood work done
in Guatemala City,
malaria test.
Did you have malaria?
No, I'm actually perfectly healthy.
Okay, so all of you have been
to a doctor
and had some kind of
blood work done.
What about you?
No.
How did you know
Berto was in prison?
Lucky guess.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Have you been in prison?
No...
you can't ask.
[ announcements
playing in Spanish ]
You must understand
that in this part of the world
people go missing from
the penal system all the time.
Some escape.
Others buy their way out.
But for your sister,
I'm afraid it may be
something different.
For instance,
someone like yourself,
young woman, attractive,
someone like that,
sometimes...
get sold.
Sold?
Sold to who?
Wait. I need to know
who buys prisoners.
Lower your voice.
I need to know
who bought my sister.
Please.
Okay. I'll do
what I can to help.
And, please,
for your safety,
don't go around asking about
these people,
or you may find yourself
vanishing, too.
Hey, look. There.
Another island.
We need to get there.
Oh, no, Billie, Billie,
like, that--
that island
is five miles off.
That's five miles of
ocean currents.
You get knocked off course,
you're gonna be 20 miles out
before you know what happened.
So what do you suggest,
staying here
and waiting to die?
I'm just saying,
if it was that easy,
don't you think we would have
already swam there?
How can you say
something can't be done
until you actually try it?
So you gonna swim there?
I didn't say that.
Come on.
Good.
There's plenty of wood
for us here.
So we're building a boat?
No, a raft, just enough
to keep us afloat,
and then we'll paddle the rest
of the way.
[ whispering ]
Don't move too fast.
There's someone there.
Little birdies left the nest.
What do you want?
Same thing you do,
to get the hell off this island.
How long you been here?
44 days.
Two months?
How did you
survive out here alone?
What I'm trained to do.
What's your background?
S.A.S.,
British special forces.
I was on exercise
on Honduras,
support and training.
Done a tour in Afghanistan.
Injured twice in the surge.
Survival specialist.
How did you get here?
No idea.
Last thing I remember,
I was traveling along
in a transport van.
We got hit.
There was this massive blast.
Then I just heard Miskito
or maybe Spanish.
Anyway, fell unconscious.
Woke up here.
Do you know
why we're here?
Mm-mm.
But together
we could find out.
No way.
What if he's one of them,
you know, waiting for us
to lead him back to our camp?
Oh, shush, pretty boy.
I know
where your camp is.
I've been there nights.
I could have
strangled every single one of yez,
but I didn't.
The only person
I wanna kill is them.
You have
my word on that.
There's another island
a few miles away,
and I'm gonna try
and get there,
and any of you who want to get
the hell off this island
can come with me.
You're gonna go with her, Nick,
take a nice swim in the open ocean?
We're not swimming.
We're building a raft.
You're building a raft?
Don't you think
I tried everything
to get off this island?
I built a raft.
Plan was to go
to the next island,
that island you're talking about.
If there was no one there,
we'd resupply and
move to the next one.
Oh, we did it.
Except I didn't
factor in a few things.
This island is a seamount.
That means that
once you pass the reef
it drops down 3,000 feet.
Blue water.
There are two things
you have to watch out for.
After the reef,
there are currents
that are like the jet stream.
You'll get tossed about.
The raft'll get broken apart to
a million different pieces.
And then the sharks.
You've got mako
and oceanic whitetips.
They call them
wolves of the sea.
We were
two miles offshore
on that nice
little raft we built.
And that's when we
ran aground on the reef.
I'm the only one that
made it out.
So don't tell me about trying to
get off this island, Ms. Kope.
The wolves,
they'll come after you
and show no mercy.
God bless you.
Who's coming with us?
I'm coming.
Now, we're gonna need driftwood.
Look on the coastline.
Jugs, plastic bottles,
whatever shit
people throw away,
that's what
we're gonna use.
So what is it you do again?
I'm a hairdresser.
NICK: If anyone
wants to take a break,
someone should probably
get on top of there.
Yeah, Stitch, you're
gonna need a break.
Shut up, man,
Just keep going.
We're almost there.
Nearly there.
Come on. Keep it together.
[ screams ]
Todd?
Oh! There's
a lot of blood!
Oh, my God!
Sharks! Sharks!
Hello?
Anyone here?
Is there someone there?
Hello? Hello?
Necesito teléfono,
por favor.
Sí. No.
Let me check this door.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Can we use your phone to make a call?
Oh, hi.
¡Vayanse aquí!
Llamada la policia.
Llamada
la policia.
Por favor.
Hey! Hey! Come here.
We need your help!
Wait!
Hello? Hi. Sorry.
Hi. Can you please help us?
Hello? Damn it.
What, they don't like Americans
or something?
Nobody likes Americans.
It's not that.
It's something else.
Oh, shit.
4-3-1.
Huh.
Gave up on you a long time ago.
I thought you were dead.
Yeah.
If you and your pussies get rid
of your stun guns,
then we'll find out
who's dead.
[ chuckles ]
[ coughs ]
You need to learn some manners.
All yours.
Okay, when you're finished,
bag 'em, and tag 'em.
[ groaning ]
[ spits ]
Let's go.
[ winces ]
[ seabirds calling ]
[ groaning ]
No. No.
Damn it.
[ groans ]
Why the hell
didn't they kill us?
I don't know.
Doesn't make sense.
[ coughs ]
Rich.
Yeah?
Girl Sarge brought in
was too far gone.
Shit.
We need a replacement,
preferably one that's
not frickin' dead.
Sarge, the dead girl
you brought us was obviously garbage.
I need you to go back out there
and find somebody else,
preferably in one piece.
We've already
been out there once
to dump those idiots
on the island.
Then go back out again now.
Understood.
The people on that island,
their blood work is perfect.
They've been handpicked.
See, that's what we're
selling here is perfection.
That's a little hard to do
when you beat the shit out of 'em!
I mean it.
Not a scratch!
Okay, guys, let's fall out.
Xander, if Sarge and I
have a falling out,
are you prepared to take over
the operation?
What are you asking me?
Not asking anything yet,
but I think you know what I mean.
What did he want?
He wanted to know what happened
to the girl.
I said it was my fault,
I missed the shot.
He told me not
to mess up again.
What did you say to that?
Well, I told him
maybe if he thinks he could do
a better job,
he should come along with us
and take one out himself.
You two go on. Not you.
So you wanna take over, eh?
No.
Did he ask you to kill me?
I don't believe you.
Let's go.
[ grunts ]
There's only room
for one leader here.
[ brush rustling ]
[ blade slashes ]
[ steady whine ]
[ whimpering ]
What's that?
Think it's an ear.
Yeah, I can see that.
Oh, my God.
[ sobs ]
Oh, God.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God.
She's going into shock.
Okay, we gotta
get back to camp.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
If you take things
into your own hands again,
that will be
your ear on that machete,
and it won't be no accident.
You understand?
What happened?
They cut her ear off!
What do we do?
Put her here.
Put her here!
Jean, get some firewood!
I've got to cauterize this.
Make a fire quick.
Hey!
Where's Todd?
He didn't make it.
You happy now, Billie?
They trusted you.
All right,
we gotta keep her warm.
Okay.
[ brush rustles ]
[ wings flap ]
[ frogs croaking ]
Okay, tonight we're gonna swim
back to the island.
Why?
I mean,
there must be
some method to their
madness. I mean,
why would they just bring us
back here
to hunt us down again?
A sociological experiment?
Some sick human hunting game
for rich people?
I don't know.
I have a sister...
Rina.
We've always been different.
She took after our mother,
liked girlie things, shopping.
Not me.
I was Daddy's girl.
Hold that jab.
He was a judo champion
back in the Soviet Union
and an officer in the Army.
Jab, right cross.
Follow with that right cross.
He started training me
as early as I can remember.
That's it. Go deep.
That's it.
Okay, don't be afraid.
That's okay.
Don't be afraid.
That's it.
I got you.
You're okay.
That's it.
[ coughing ]
Good, good, good.
You were choking me.
Yes, but I need you
not to be afraid of it.
How does your mom
feel about all that?
She didn't feel anything.
She was already dead.
I'm sorry.
What happened to her?
It was a robbery.
It went bad.
That's why it was
so important for our father
that his daughters learn
how to fight.
Faster! Faster! Faster!
That's what I'm looking for.
Ah, that's it.
That's it.
Relax.
Breathe.
Okay.
That's it.
Hold it. Hold it.
Now push yourself up.
Lift yourself.
No thinking.
No mind.
No thinking!
Lift. Lift.
Lift. Lift. Do it.
That's it.
Again. Down.
Concentrate. You can do this!
Come on. Work.
Work. Hold it.
Hold it there.
Push! Push it up.
Push it up!
[ groaning ]
Push.
That's it.
One more time, last time.
Come on.
You can do this.
Go down.
Go down slowly.
That's it.
Breathe.
If you can't carry your body weight,
you can't do advanced technique.
Work it. That's it.
There you go.
Okay, push from internal. Go.
Don't look down.
Push! Push! Push!
[ groans ]
Good job.
Breathe! Breathe!
Push up,
all the way up.
Good job.
[ groans ]
Jab, right cross.
Here.
Okay,
now this time--
Come on! Grab my weight!
Put your chin into my shoulder!
There you go.
Push it down.
Bring my wrist down.
That's it.
Now pull out.
Put it up. Hold it.
Hold it there.
Very good.
Nice job.
Well, Rina rebelled
after our mother was killed.
She moved to New York
and got deep into heroin.
Dad cut her off,
but she just blamed him
for not being there for our mother.
I got so angry with her.
I told her I wished
she would just disappear,
and she did.
She was arrested in Juarez
six years ago
for possession
of heroin and cocaine.
I guess you could say
she has a bit of a problem.
She has a good heart, though.
And if this whole thing
is not connected, then I've got
the worst luck in the world.
Well, you met me.
That's kind of lucky.
Heh.
[ chuckles ]
Hey...
Ahem!
Guys, come on.
We need to get to shelter
before it gets dark.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Quentin, what's the nature
of this call?
Is it an emergency?
You tell me.
I got one of the kids
with a missing ear.
Who was it?
Chloe.
Well, they're bringing
somebody else in, right?
Yeah. They got the--
They got another match,
all right?
Listen, we need to go over
a few things, Rich.
Look, it'll have to wait, okay?
We've got a little bit
of a full plate
over here
with this Mao thing.
No, it's not gonna wait.
I'm done.
You got it?
I want out of here.
What are you talking about?
I'm not gonna keep up
the charade anymore.
I'm finished.
I'm tired of wiping my ass
with banana leaves.
You got it?
It was supposed to last a month,
not a permanent thing!
I want out!
I'm done!
Quentin, what is this?
You trying to renegotiate?
Renegotiate?
Are you crazy?
No, I want off the island.
It's as simple as that.
And you'll get off
the island as promised,
and you'll be rich
as promised, all right?
Just give me
a little bit more time.
How much?
Until this business
with Mao
is taken care of.
[ sighs ]
No, you're better off
with me over there with you.
That can't happen right now.
You get me off this island,
either your way or I'll do it
my way,
and you know I can.
They don't know about
this place.
It's got
fresh running water.
As long as you don't mind
the bats, it's all good.
Those markings
on the wall, Stitch...
are they for the days
you've been here?
'Cause there's more than 44.
Uh-uh.
That's how many people
have since showed up
since I been here.
So many of them.
Any of them could be her.
Hey, guys, I made up a couple
of hammocks over there.
It's better than sleeping
on the rocks, that's for sure.
Oh, thank you.
[ thunder crashing ]
That's Mao?
I've only ever spoken
to the assistant.
[ thunder crashes ]
Ms. Mao, it is so nice
to finally meet you in person.
I'm Rich Napier.
I do hope your journey
was--was pleasant.
It's Mao.
Of course.
And this
must be Violet. Hi.
Mao, Violet is
in the best of hands.
Our fine doctor,
Dr. Walsh,
is a hepatobiliary specialist.
In fact,
he's pioneered several
breakthroughs in the field.
He is without a doubt the
best surgeon money can buy.
Nice to meet you.
You have kids?
Somewhere, daughter.
What's her name?
Ruby. Why?
Pretty name.
Hey, sweetie.
I'm gonna make you
feel better.
I promise, okay?
Now you and Violet
will want for nothing
while you're here.
We have a lovely suite
for you upstairs,
and we have places set for
your men in the outer compound.
They stay with me.
Of course.
Baby, last time, okay?
Promise.
You heard that man promise.
And that one looks like
your ferret.
[ laughs ]
Ah, there's my smile.
It's like the sunshine!
Swear it gets hotter
when you smile.
You go spread that sunshine around
this place, okay?
I'll come find you
in a little bit.
[ pats ]
I love you.
[ thunder crashing ]
I'll look forward to seeing
the facilities.
Please, follow me.
Yeah.
Proper medical data encryption
and Latin America
don't necessarily go hand in hand.
When someone comes in
for a blood test or dental work,
it all goes into a database.
My Estonian boys have the code
to sift through that data.
If we find somebody
with good statistics,
like a certain
blood-type, right,
no diseases, perfect health,
we target and track them.
Track 'em?
Yeah, it's easy
these days.
I mean,
you have cellphones.
You have
credit card statements,
uh, social networking,
laptops.
As soon as we find them,
my boys bag 'em.
They bring them here
to our private island,
and after a few weeks of
fruits, vegetables,
and pure island drinking water,
their bodies are clean.
Then we wait for clients
like yourself to call us,
and we have our whole stable
of donors just waiting.
When the client shows up, within hours,
we can harvest the donor.
Hmm.
I'd like to see Violet's donor.
Eh, we don't generally do that.
It's not a request.
No, I understand,
but we've had
a couple of clients
change their mind
after seeing the donor.
I hate to use this word,
but it humanizes them.
I promise you, Mao,
Violet is in good hands.
We will take
excellent care of her.
I, uh--
I wouldn't swim in there.
There's a lot
of snakes in there.
The leeches, too,
they're--
Breakfast is ready.
I'll just--
I'll wait over here.
[ men yelling ]
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! What's going on?
There's a problem with
the specimen.
What?
Donor's unacceptable.
She has no chi.
I'm sorry, but no chi
is not a viable medical condition.
With all due respect,
Mao,
this donor was handpicked
and primed as a perfect match
for your daughter.
I mean, we've gone
through great lengths
to make sure that she's the
perfect specimen for this procedure.
Look into that woman's eyes.
Do you see
the thousand-mile stare?
Hmm?
She's broken.
She has accepted her demise.
She has no fight!
Right now, her body is being
flooded with fear hormones,
adrenaline, and bile.
It's poisoning
her entire system!
She is weak!
I need someone strong.
Very well.
Dr. Walsh,
Mao is paying premium.
She gets what she asks for.
Thank you.
If this girl
doesn't have enough chi,
she doesn't have
enough chi.
We'll find her
a suitable replacement.
But we need to operate now.
Every hour we waste risks
that little girl's life.
I want one of those.
I want her.
Sure. Uh, that can be arranged.
Dr. Walsh, change of plans.
MJ?
Thank you, gentlemen.
Out.
Won't let you down.
Walsh, prep the girl
from yesterday.
Screw Mao. She's not
gonna know the difference.
What about that girl
on the island?
I-I'll have them kill her.
She wasn't brought here
for her blood work anyway.
She was asking around
about me,
specifically me.
I just had her put here
so I could find out
who she's working with
and what she knows.
I thought it would be
a good idea
to put her with
a sympathetic ear,
but Quentin has apparently
dropped the ball on that.
I'm not sure
what to do with her.
I think you should do what
you feel's right.
That's my girl.
[ monitor beeping ]
Hey.
[ groaning ]
[ blade slices ]
All right.
We'll have to be quick about this.
NICK:
Too heavy, Stitch.
BILLIE:
Am I hurting you?
No. Am I hurting you?
No.
What the hell
is going on here?
Put her down!
Put her down now!
Is that you, Nick?
[ laughing ]
You're with them!
No, but you are.
All along,
you were with them!
Oh, come on. Stop it!
We see right through you.
Back up!
Just stay away!
You see nothing.
It's gonna be tough
going up against them.
Good luck.
[ laughs ]
I'm outta here.
Sayonara!
[ laughs ]
[ groans ]
Okay, guys, this is
do or die for us.
We have to take that boat,
no matter who we meet,
no matter what
we encounter, okay?
We will.
Okay, let's go.
Shh.
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Don't move.
BILLIE:
You guys can have the boat.
Go wherever you want.
You're free now.
But first,
you're dropping me off.
NICK:
Are you crazy?
I'm not going anywhere
without finding out
what's going on here.
So there's no way we
could change your mind?
Not on this.
Seriously?
You have that low
of an opinion of me?
What about you, Stitch?
What am I supposed
to say, eh?
We made it this far,
didn't we?
[ laughs ]
Be rude not to, really.
Thank you.
What's
our operational status?
Surgery on Song Mao
is under way now.
And the, uh, mission
to the island?
No report yet.
I'll be in me quarters
if you need me.
[ overlapping chatter
in Spanish ]
Well, hello there,
little lady.
[ gasps ]
You want a job working on
a private island?
We've got complications.
What?
She's had the Kasha procedure,
hasn't she?
Well, it's resulted in
biliary atresia.
RICH:
Speak English.
Her bile duct
isn't functioning.
I don't know if
the new liver'll help.
And I don't care
what you have to do, Walsh.
You get back in there right now,
and you save her.
Yeah, I will,
but we've gotta be prepared to--
Walsh, fix it!
You want to
come up here and do it?!
[ gasps ]
I came...
Doesn't look like the dock's
guarded, you know.
Yeah, well, there might be
some people around the house.
What are we waiting for?
Hey, guys, wait!
Stop! Stop.
Look, uh,
I've got
an admission to make.
I'm not in the S.A.S.
I mean,
I went for special ops.
Just that, well, I got washed out
of their training program.
I mean, I'm military.
Heh. Well,
did the basic training.
It's just that I'm not
like those guys out there.
They're trained killers.
You weren't taken into a
battlefield hospital?
No.
Oh, I mean,
I was hospitalized,
but not
from the front line.
I got food poisoning.
I work
in the mess hall.
What about Afghanistan,
the two times wounded?
Didn't you say that?
But you've been
in combat before, right?
Before today, no.
Heh. Great.
I knew something was up
when you said how long you
were on the island.
A Special Ops soldier
on an island for 44 days?
Two months?
Doing what? Nothing?
Sorry.
[ sighs ]
Look, Stitch,
you can stay here with the boat
if you want to, okay?
Nick, you're coming
with me, right?
We'll come back for you, okay?
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Just wait.
[ sighs ]
Look, if it
wasn't for you guys,
we'd still be stuck
on that island, right?
I owe you guys my life.
I'm coming, all right?
I'm coming.
[ exhales ]
On the count of three.
Okay.
1, 2, 3.
Just give me a minute.
[ grunts ]
[ neck cracks ]
[ flies buzzing ]
Clear.
[ coughs ]
[ gasping ]
Oh, my God.
It's Jean.
Holy shit.
They're organ thieves.
They're harvesting us
for this, our organs.
An organ farm.
Where's Sarge?
ANNOUNCER:
20,000 Polish fans
are packed into Wembley.
It's an electric atmosphere.
[ radio continues indistinctly ]
Well back.
He's falling in.
[ continues indistinctly ]
That was an excellent move
by Wayne to get it down.
It takes you there.
There's a chance
to break out here.
Taking it across here.
Hits the bar! No!
Ah, into the side netting.
Reporting for England there.
Look at the space.
In the clear.
Once again, Poland looking
to counterattack here.
Oh, it's been left beautifully.
Lewandowski into the area,
and he's pulled his shot wide.
He can barely believe it.
[ continues indistinctly ]
England stretched at the back.
Townsend on the charge.
Smalling is offside here.
Here's the ball back.
Way to go.
And it's Townsend.
Hits the bar!
[ continues indistinctly ]
Ball straight to the keeper.
Ah, England highly
under pressure.
And with Townsend
rattling the crossbar.
Sturridge on the follow.
[ continues indistinctly ]
Oh, Sturridge!
It goes wide!
They fall back.
What an unbelievable miss.
Sturridge right to left,
goes right instead,
drives down the middle.
Ball in under pressure here.
Ah, it's left of beam.
It's Wayne Rooney!
England takes the lead!
And Wembley breathes
a sigh of relief.
Beautiful ball in for Wayne.
[ continues indistinctly ]
[ door clicks ]
[ gasps ]
[ sobs ]
[ footsteps clattering ]
[ door opens ]
[ monitor whining ]
[ crying ]
Shh.
Whoa! Whoa!
Don't shoot!
We can work this out!
Just hold on!
Wait! One moment!
[ Rich yelling ]
[ gunshot ]
Stop! No! Stop!
RICH:
Wait, okay? Hold on!
We can settle this now.
Hold on!
Stop.
[ gasps ]
Mao, it is this woman's fault
right here.
Our first two donors
died because of her.
Your daughter would still be alive
right now if it weren't for her!
Lies!
You stole my sister.
You are the cause of this.
You're pathetic.
Hold on.
Allow me
to eliminate her for you.
No!
[ yelling ]
[ gunfire ]
Just what England
needed at the moment.
Fucking stuck.
Oh, my God.
You've been shot.
[ gunfire continues ]
Go, go, go!
STITCH:
Go on. Let's get out of here!
[ gunfire continues nearby ]
Okay, clear!
[ blows ]
Oh, shit.
[ groaning ]
Ah, shit.
[ gasping ]
[ gunfire continues nearby ]
Kat!
You're dead!
You betrayed me!
[ clicks ]
[ gunfire echoing ]
Oi!
Ah, shit. I'm out.
Billie, you take Nick
and your sister.
Get 'em out of here.
You sure?
Yeah, just go.
[ yelling ]
[ gasps ]
[ coughs ]
[ Nick panting ]
Billie, what are you doing here?
How did you even find me?
What do you mean?
I never stopped looking for you.
I've been searching all over
the world for you for five years.
Well, you should have stayed away.
I'm no good.
You know Dad always said that.
Katerina, Dad's gone.
It's just you and me now.
And I don't care what he said.
You know he didn't mean it.
He loved you very much.
He was just too proud
to admit it.
Billie, I've done
some bad things.
I don't care.
It was all in your past.
You can start a new life now.
You can do
whatever you want.
That's why I'm here.
And I'm sorry for how things
ended between us.
I really, really am.
I know. I know.
I just want my sister back.
Please.
Let's just keep moving.
Come on.
Okay.
Come on. Let's go.
No, no.
Please.
No, I-I can't go much further.
I'm sorry.
Stay here with Nick,
and keep it quiet.
I gotta go find Stitch.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
I-I'll take care of him.
I'll be right back.
[ helmet clatters ]
Okay.
I'll be right back.
BILLIE:
Stitch?
Oh, shit.
[ gasping ]
[ moans ]
Oh, Stitch.
Hey. Hey, Billie.
Hold still.
I'm gonna get you help.
Don't worry.
H-He got me.
[ gasps ]
I'm bleeding out.
No, no, no, no, no.
Billie...
I was a real soldier,
wasn't I, Billie?
Yeah, you were.
You were great.
Go.
[ calming breaths ]
[ yells ]
Again. Go!
[ slow motion ]
Get up.
[ heart beating ]
Get up! Get up!
[ normal speed ]
Get up.
Again.
[ yells ]
Bitch.
[ gurgles ]
BILLIE:
Stop!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Uh-uh.
Billie, shoot him.
What?
Let her go!
Are you two working together
or something?
What's going on?
She's my sister!
What?! [ laughs ]
I did not see that one coming.
I really need to get
better people. Put it down.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. Don't!
Shoot him. Billie...
Put it down.
I don't care anymore.
Just do it!
I can't.
See? At least
somebody in your family
has some common sense!
Kill him! Do it!
I can't!
Put it down.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Good girl.
No!
[ gunshots ]
[ yells ]
Katerina?
No.
[ sobbing ]
It's all right.
[ moaning ]
[ waves crashing ]
Take care of her, Dad.
What are you gonna do now?
Take the rest
of the people home.
And after that?
[ pop music playing ]
♪ I can see you ♪
♪ And you don't know me ♪
♪ Still I know
that you're out there ♪
♪ I can feel it
in every heartbeat ♪
♪ Like you're sleeping
inside me ♪
♪ And all I've got ♪
♪ Is what's in front of me ♪
♪ And I can't stop ♪
♪ I won't be free ♪
♪ Till I awaken ♪
♪ Find what has been taken ♪
♪ Finally awaken ♪
♪ Till I cross the line ♪
♪ It feels like
I've been dreaming ♪
♪ All my life until now ♪
♪ I won't stop believing ♪
♪ Till I find you somehow ♪
♪ Every step I take ♪
♪ Is closer to you ♪
♪ No room for mistake ♪
♪ I know what I must do ♪
♪ And all I've got ♪
♪ Is what's in front of me ♪
♪ And I can't stop ♪
♪ I won't be free ♪
♪ Till I awaken ♪
♪ Find what has been taken ♪
♪ Finally awaken ♪
♪ Till I cross the line ♪
♪ I won't be free ♪
♪ Till I awaken ♪
♪ I awaken ♪
♪ Find what
has been taken ♪
♪ Finally awaken ♪
♪ Find what
has been taken ♪
♪ Finally awaken ♪
♪ Till I am awakened ♪
♪ Till I cross the line ♪
[ instrumental playing ]