Welcome
THE MOTHER OF ALL TOADS
Here we were in France with all
Types of gargoyles on the wall.
- Honey, can we go?
- That's so impressive.
This is the "Green Man" is a
pagan fertility symbol.
You you have to watch the time.
They're so cool.
- Be careful.
- What?
If you have touched it
they might buy.
It may very
like to try once.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Are you American?
Yes.
Enter
wonderful couple from.
- Thank you.
- Darling, you're wonderful.
- Let's see.
- I want her.
- Do you like it?
This is the "older characters'.
What're you talking about?
The "ÄItere characters'
of H.P. Lovecraft.
- The Necronomicon and stuff.
- Yes, you're right.
- Was not that a hoax?
- Of course not.
They come from a very old source,
which has been for generations
Part of my family is.
And I explore traditions, but fits.
He calls anthropology.
If you are interested, have
You come this afternoon.
Honey, we can not
Afternoon. We already have plans.
This is on our way.
I think we get back.
Which we will discuss in the car.
Is that enough? It is
only slightly wrinkled.
It's French.
I do not understand.
Yes, we're in France.
You have to get used to you.
Otherwise, would you rather have in
should remain the States.
Okay, listen, honey, I mean ...
Why do not you go to the spa?
And on the way you bring me
then decreases. It is on the way.
Do not you see, she says, that she
a copy of the Necronomicon has.
That I have to check,
why I'm here.
She has a copy on a
Found market in Mirepoix.
I need to go there. It is perhaps
just another fake.
I have to check it. So do
your thing. Let you make the nails,
go to the hammam. That's okay. But
Now let's enjoy the ride.
We could turn left at Benet
should, as I had said.
I am now, I am left
bent to Benet.
No. Turn left at Benet
You listen to me not.
- Baby ...
- Just keep driving.
- What the hell is that?
- What?
Wow. Look das. you
You show your face on.
- Yes, 5 is a cross.
- This is not just a cross.
It belongs not to the intersection.
Over here was a spiritual ver-
collection site from the time of the Gauls.
Well, you would have our favorite
Holiday paid more attention ...
Then ... we would not have moved.
- Proceed?
Yes! Where are we? What is it for
a place? I do not understand.
We have not lost our way.
Do not you see what goes here?
You Look at the sign,
the market.
The woman has a Necronomicon and
Earrings with the "ÄIteren characters."
This is the symbol of infinity.
You see, that is the co-
connection of two worlds, heaven and earth.
- Yes, it's a fucking night.
What are you talking about? - An eight.
I'm going to Spa.
- You can do what you want.
- This is not a fucking night ...
I see are
They come alone.
Karina had an appointment.
You probably do not heal your interests?
She does not think much of esotericism.
Sit down.
A Pastis from the area.
That is the custom in the region.
The book is very old.
I can not believe it,
but it looks real.
All the women in my family
have used it.
In one way or
the other way.
Oh God ...
Great.
Fantastic. what is it?
The mothers of all the toads.
Do you really have
Go, my boy?
- Yes, it's pretty late.
- Then one more for the road.
The wine is mild you
warm on your way back.
I will not refuse.
It is your stomach
warming and other parts.
I should go now.
Do you like me now, handsome?
Shit.
One day I will have to
something to kill.
What the.
No ...
Why are you in such a hurry
gone, little one?
Stay away from me.
Stay away.
Why?
I can give you everything
give other women and more.
You are not a fucking woman!
You're a fucking freak!
No ...
No, no, no ...
you
What a story.
As imaginative.
Not every horror is
a creation of the divine.
I LOVE YOU
Shit.
Hi, it's me.
Call me back, please.
It is important.
Hey, George, it's me.
I'm with an ugly
Section woken by the hand.
A broken glass or something.
Maybe I'm in a fight
advised. I can not remember.
I can not get Mona.
She does not answer my calls.
He does not sound very good.
Yesterday he had a fight and
can not even remember.
I'll talk to him, a few things
pack up and be right back.
I do not think this is a good idea.
We should immediately go to Paris
We settle down and disappear.
He would look for me.
That you're not, right?
I will bring him even to
that he understands.
Trust me, okay?
My God, where have you been?
Why did not you answer the phone
gone or have called me back?
I've told you a few days ago,
I'm going to my cousin.
You two are not answered the phone.
I have dozens of you
Leave messages.
I needed some time
for me to think.
- And you?
- Yes, I have. It was good.
- That I had to do.
- Well, that makes me happy.
Because I love you so much missing.
What are you doing?
I pack a few things
together, then we can talk.
Why do you need to pack stuff?
You'll stay at home now, right?
So simple is not the
I have to decide yet.
Damn it ...
What I have done such a terrible thing?
Please, tell me!
You did not do anything. It is
to me. Try to understand it.
I'm trying,
But you say nothing at all!
Cut the crap
and look at me!
[What?
- You wear your wedding ring not. - I
know I've forgotten it at Danielle.
I'll get him,
when I go back.
You're not going anywhere, you are to
told you what's going on!
Do you want me now hold captive?
Why will not you grow up?
Stop it!
You ...
Bastard!
You are a real pig!
You were the last five days
not with Danielle! Where were you?
- You're being paranoid.
- You were not there, I know.
You controlled me?
I have to worry
you made. I love you.
You poor fool.
Do you not understand why
I can not stay here?
- Because you kill me.
- How do I kill you?
You do not even lets
for a minute alone.
When I go out, you want to know
where I'm going ...
What I do ... and
when I go back.
If I'm late,
I must explain myself.
I meet someone, you want to know
who it is and what we talked about.
- Do not have a right to know,
with whom my wife talking about? - No!
You call me 20 times a day
to just to check me.
I want to say hi.
And I'm sick of it, that you always
happened to be there, where am I going to show up.
At first I liked the
Attention. It was nice.
But now it's too much,
I can no longer live.
You want to have someone
which is always there for you.
The only live for you. Well,
I'm not. So nobody.
I know you're right.
I'm neurotic.
But only because I
love you so much.
Stop saying that. Do
you even know what that means?
It means that I love you.
I'm sorry that it got this far
is. I wanted it to work.
And we had a great time.
But I can not stay.
[E-Please.
- Give me one more chance.
- No, I can not.
- Please, I'll do anything
what you want. - No.
- I just do not rely on.
- No, you can not.
- Axel ...
- Please, give me a kiss.
- For the last time, then
you can go. - I'm leaving now.
Please, darling, fuck me harder, okay?
Come on!
- I want to hurt you.
- I break not already!
Come on, fuck me harder!
Please, do not ruin me.
Do you, do you love me still.
- I'll still go.
- Why?
I do not understand.
We belong together. I can take you
happy, if you let me.
No, that's not true.
Please stay here and give us more
a chance. I'm begging you.
I can not.
If you met someone
all you need to tell me. I forgive you.
Otherwise it makes no sense.
Go into the living room.
I get to in a minute.
I'll tell you everything, you know what
want to know. The absolute truth.
I will not secretly
sneak out, I promise.
Okay.
That's so mean.
You know where that leads, right?
I think so.
Because I'm falling straight into you.
And I. In love with you
Then everything is clear. We must
just move in together.
We will get married and
spend our lives together.
We will have a home and a family.
All that happy people have.
I'd like that.
- A friend of yours?
- Who?
- The guy you smiled.
- No, I've never seen.
So, the absolute truth, right?
The truth ...
I admit that I last
Week was not at my cousin.
Yes, I was with someone
others together.
I was unfaithful to you, and now I want to
that other person to be around.
So I was not paranoid.
Just because you were right, that means
not that you're not paranoid.
- You admit that you deceived me?
- Yes.
I cheated, I
I lied and cheated on you.
- Who's this? - That 's got
nothing on. Nobody, you know.
- Do you love him?
- Yes.
Shit.
Why did you tell me this
not been said before?
Because I was afraid,
what would you do.
- I would never want to hurt you, you know that
du - No, you hurt yourself Inst.
You threaten with suicide.
Have you throw a handful of pills
and make me responsible.
- It was only once. - Yes, but
I've learned my lesson.
How long has this been?
The first time three years ago.
- The first time?
- Yes, 6 were others.
How many?
Hard to say
One-night stands included?
So, are you saying that
you're a whore and bitch?
Yes.
Do you remember the
internal bleeding that I had?
- The uterine infection?
- I told you.
- You need to eat something. - Sweet,
okay I go. I do not go hungry.
I just want to sleep,
go into the other room.
I stay here when you sleep
If you need anything.
My lover then
was married.
And he had his family
not leave for me.
And we were both safely
not ready for a child. So ...
Was it about me?
There was no one. It was
in me, and then it was outside.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
Why that makes you so cold?
You love children.
Yes, by other people.
Also, I did not want to
always be bound to you.
So I've done things to me
hurting themselves and all around me.
I hold you and leave some
am to my sister to Paris.
Yes.
And you came back,
because you had me missing.
I'm not
therefore returned.
Are you ready?
I do not believe you.
Why do you think I have not since then
talked to my sister?
You say it all
just to get rid of me.
But I still love you.
I saw you at every opportunity
deceived and laughed at you.
I have not even washed,
so you smell the sex and freak out.
What I have done,
you hate me so much?
I always thought it would be
your weakness, your selfishness ...
And ... your passive-aggressive kind
But it's the little things.
The way you're out of your shirt
zuknöpfst top down.
The way you
chew your food.
The nature,
as you fuck me.
Like I was a
fragile porcelain doll
that you put back on the shelf,
when you're done.
You and your gentle
Orgasm tender as a whisper.
I want a screaming
fucked.
Your penis and my vagina
never liked each other.
Have you ever noticed?
In five years, I'm not even
come, and that has never heard you.
Can I ask you something?
- What?
- Are you pregnant?
You think I'm leaving you, because I
get someone else's baby?
- That would be a reason.
- Not for me.
You are cruel and
injured people.
This new guy I'm almost sorry. White
he, with what kind of woman he's sleeping?
He will find out soon enough.
If we had then clarified everything?
Let us now separate ways
before we get even more hurt?
Do you think you could have me
hurt more than you've done it?
I do not know.
I want to find out either.
I'm sorry.
Where would you go?
To him?
You can give me those questions
no longer provide.
Will I be this mysterious
Man know?
I do not know.
I wanted to tell you not,
but now it does not matter anymore.
I think a biopsy last week
and the results are not clear.
- B could be cancer.
- Stop it, it does not work this time.
The major medical emergency?
Why does George
on your phone to?
Hi, George. It's me.
what's up! '
She is here. Yes, come up.
They would be sure to see you.
But give her a minute,
they must still attract.
For you.
Hi, no, all good
I'm going now.
No, please no.
Fucking asshole!
May
Hey.
HI.
Shit.
Mona! Bloody hell,
what happened?
I'm going this time for good-who
. leave You can not stop me.
[Mona!
Oh my God!
George did this to you!
You did not leave me,
and he is on? IPPT!
No, honey, he's not.
I'm going now.
Let's see how you love me
back this time fetch.
No, I meant 5 not so!
I'm so sorry!
Please, do not leave me!
Please come back!
Damn it!
I curse you!
Do not worry, darling.
You will not be alone.
Because I'll go with you.
Son of a bitch!
I ...
I love you.
I love ...
Maybe I'm wrong.
Am I wrong.
Pause. And more.
What's your story?
WET DREAMS
What's going on?
Baby. I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Did you go?
The remote control
damn remote?
No ..
Could you help the
Stealers play tonight.
Then look at the Stealers.
But I need the remote control.
The last time I had me a
Program on lifestyle look.
Valerie Botanelli over
Cancer or some shit.
- You're going out?
- Had I told you.
I have this thing with Percy. The
Christmas bonus depends.
I come to early
Home promised.
You promise a lot.
Jesus Christ, come on,
I slept.
Take some makeup.
You will not even notice.
My mother will notice the fifth
She is coming tomorrow for dinner.
- What do I tell her?
- Tell her ...
- You have to do, they should next
Weeks to come. - Yes, next week.
Why not.
Breakfast is ready.
And this is repeated night after night.
You and your wife served
your cock for breakfast?
Not very Freudian.
Do you meet up with a new one?
Meet with a new one?
You mean, if I fuck a new one?
Yeah, I mean,
fuck you new one.
Not at the moment.
What's with the wife of your
Dreams? With the loving vagina
Is it someone who
you know?
No ..
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I gotta a very
ask sensitive questions.
When did you last
Time someone raped?
I rape always' my
Mother. Of course in my dreams.
I did even people.
I kill people I love.
I should do, what you
to charge for these sessions.
The point is, dreams can
how can be a liberation.
As a safety valve.
They allow us to do things we
could not do in real life.
Sometimes it is the only
Truth that we have.
It is the reality of the soul.
Real life is the distraction.
I will not explain,
I just want it to stop.
Have you tried
to open your eyes?
I'm serious. The moment when
which you realize that you're dreaming ...
You can use your mind ...
try to stop it.
Okay ..
- And how do I do that? - Full
simple. Close your eyes and count.
That's what you get back, right?
Three, two, one ...
wake up.
Over here! Hey!
Carla?
Hey, you ..
I have the remote control
found.
Maxine! No!
Carla, let them free!
Maxine! Carla wait, that thing!
What the hell?
Carla, stop it!
Okay, you get
what you wanted.
Please, let me go.
No, Danny.
What the hell do you want from me?
The truth.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about your wife.
- Let me free!
- The woman you married.
Which you promised to honor her
and love until death separates you.
What the shell?
I dream ...
It is a dream.
Three ...
Two ... ...
. One!
Wow.!
You look great. You
look like a movie star.
- Were you able to sleep?
- Like a baby.
- Apart.
- Thank you.
- What is it?
Smells delicious.
That's it. when
you want, do one.
No, not today.
Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Look.
Maxine.
Can not we
more hurt.
- Poor baby, are you okay?
- Yes.
I gave you a few
Gifts brought.
Carla do not forget,
to feed it.
Good morning.
Breakfast time.
Hold on, Tiger. I just want
to see how you're doing down there.
It looks good.
Do you see?
You were completely ready for
surgery last night.
I thought I'd never see the day
where Donny missed the big game.
I would have taken for you
But you know me ...
You're the expert
with the remote control.
You can not even one
Replace the bulb.
Or is it your own
Women get.
But when it comes to
Remotes are ...
Donny ... is a black belt carrier.
You want to say something?
Yes? Really?
If I pick it, promise
then you tell me not to spit again?
You are not as good at
Keeping promises, Danny.
You will of the one-eyed monster
Mix your legs dominates.
Okay, I'll bite.
what's so funny?
You. You are sick,
damn witch.
I'm going to start with
rip out the tits.
For starters? Wow.
That is a threat.
How you gonna do that?
I mean ...
I am stunned.
No offense.
I just have my eyes
close and count to three,
and then when I wake up,
I will kill you.
Do you understand me, Carla?
I will kill you really.
Ready or not,
here I come.
Three ...
Two ... ...
Three, two, one!
Three, two ...
A.
Three, two, one!
You were right, that was
really a funny joke.
Especially the punch line.
This is my dream, bitch.
You can lock us ... Stories.
Even if they are our own.
Especially when they
are our own.
The power of his, own
Writing stories ...
... Is the power
ennoble his life.
Ennoble his life.
THE ACCIDENT
Why do we die, Mommy?
Treasures, to make room for the new
People who are born every day.
There is limited
Place in the world.
Does that mean grandmother
died ...
... To make room for me?
No ..
That does not mean entirely.
Grandmother died because her body
no longer worked.
And you've helped grandmother,
so long to stay alive.
How?
You were the reason that
she woke up in the morning.
So you happy they're doing.
Yes, I suppose, grandmother
was really very old.
Will I ever get old?
This takes a bit longer.
But this man was not old.
No, he was not.
Why is he dead?
Sometimes things just happen.
Maybe he has done something bad?
People do not die for
that they do bad things.
They are sent to her room,
if they were naughty.
Or they are in the oven, as
the wicked witch in the gingerbread house.
Since you're lucky that you do not
fit into our oven.
- Maybe I let Daddy buy one.
- No!
Oh my God.
Stay in the car.
We're on the Highway
north of ...
No, he is not.
Could be his father.
Okay, they send someone?
Mama is the man
ever wake up?
No ..
I am not afraid.
Perhaps as a zombie
or something?
Not even as a zombie. and if
but then determined to be a good zombie.
Why his daddy did it?
It's like a small
Tommy, when Old Yeller got sick.
Do you remember?
Why do we die?
I really do not know.
What I do know is that,
while we're here ...
... We should be as good as
possible care for one another.
If we die then ...
... We all die happy.
So happy to say
die as much as ...
They lived happily ...
the end of their days?
Yes.
Exactly.
It's like, they lived happily
until the end of their days.
Well, in order to refine his life ...
... You have to live it.
I'm sorry.
It is easier to get into the story
another catch ...
... Live as his own.
Stained VISIONS
I love you.
I only chose women
who wanted to die.
And if you think about it,
I give them a voice.
Something they never had in life.
Thanks to me, is all that they experienced
have, not just disappear.
I keep her story.
I love them.
The most important images that
People see in their lives ...
The key moments ...
their experiences
be in a liquid
stored in their eyes.
And I've discovered that these visions
transferable to other people.
By a simple
surgery.
At the moment of her death, they see
again her life in her eyes.
This has become my work.
I'm her biographer.
I must admit that I always
had a terrible handicap.
I can not dream.
But that does not matter anymore. Their
Dreams give me finally make sense.
To live here is that
Hazard of my trade.
To understand it,
I need as they live.
The fact that I do not
exists, is okay with me.
The only thing that counts,
These are the books.
I'm just a formality.
A formality with a body.
That's my only weakness.
I'm just in the stories
interests of women.
They are the true creators.
Those who suffer.
The predictable stories
the men do not interest me.
No blood, no life.
The strongest memories come
of women who have lived long.
Anything and everything that had
have lost.
Either because they had chosen
or wrong decisions.
These stories to
most hurt.
Then I feel like everything
they felt.
What do the unborn?
What they think or feel?
Find out, could the
Key to life itself.
No, not my baby-making!
Let go of me!
You
What do you have of my baby
taken? What did you do?
Damn ...
My baby ...
Maybe you should wake up at last.
Fetus can not
see, you idiot.
How do you want a vision of something on-
Write that does not even have eyes?
You'll find out more,
should know as a soul.
And you will regret 5,
then wanted to have.
Have you ever wondered where these
Voice is in your head?
That voice that tells you
what to do?
All the people you wrote about the
you are all recycled souls.
There is nothing unique to humans.
Not a bit.
Only creatures with
predestined life ...
. The die, and then another
to live miserable scenario,
created by a Creator with
a very short attention span.
And it is all for his pleasure.
Do you think you write the original
Stories of people?
Nothing is original, you
're just a Plagiatorin.
Shut up!
So I keep my mouth shut,
you have to close your eyes.
Listen to fool around with things
should know that no living person.
Exactly.
There is only one way to really
nothing more to see.
TU!
I suddenly see more clearly
than I have ever done.
It is wonderful to be forgotten,
what I had learned.
No more cravings
have to know everything.
Sometimes it is better to eyes
to close and to be led.
I can not see, but
Finally, I can dream again.
The stories are
to life. - ...
even if the true
World disappears ...
Until there is nothing left ...
as the storyteller.
A storyteller,
whom you trust completely.
SWEETS
It's not you,
but me.
How can such a thing
just as expressionless say?
It's up to you?
What about you?
I need some space.
Okay ...
Hey, I'll give you space.
Look here.
Do you see?
Look.
Do you see? We ...
We have enough space. Can
we not go?
I need some time to myself.
Why are you so selfish?
I'm selfish!
You are selfish!
S me went well before you
you came into my life.
It was fun. But you could
better than I get.
Maybe I want no better than you.
Maybe you think that you know what
Get better as I could?
I'm done.
I feel terribly upset.
Everyone has their problems, okay?
What's on your so special?
We talked about it.
Again and again and again.
You know that I
meet with others, right?
I did not know!
But why did you
asked me for exclusivity?
You have exclusivity
asked, why?
You tell people not yet,
I'm your friend, right?
I'll talk to anybody.
I'll call anybody!
I want to just spend time with you,
because they mean nothing.
You know.
I am not currently ready for a
Relationship. I have yet gentle to me.
You've begged!
I wanted to take it slow!
You have my efforts
challenged!
I have accepted the challenge
and see something I like very much!
Just like you!
I love you. But I'm
no longer in love with you.
What is the difference?
Let's start again.
We can get it done better.
- Please, I love you!
- And I love you ...
... As a friend.
Friends to be something not to.
Sweet, you're breaking my heart.
Do not do this to us!
We are a good match!
We fit together so well.
We are well ...
Ball! -
Stop it.
You're doing it harder,
as it should be.
Why you got me all
presented to your friends?
They seemed to like me.
They said that the chemistry
right between us.
You you want to secure.
I feel only
no longer the same.
Why?
Do you do that with every guy like that?
No, with you it was different.
But one morning I woke up
and something had changed.
I can not help my feelings.
This has happened before,
I'm sorry.
Nothing is ever
time passes ...
I feel in
so special.
S not you get!
You have to remove from me.
I do not want, please.
Please ...
Please.
I love you.
Really, I love you.
Thought for a moment
I, you were different.
Please.
But you're just another
pathetic, little lamb.
Please, give me another chance.
Fine.
See you later.
I miss you!
I miss you so much!
I know that you do.
Baby, good evening.
- How are you 5?
- Terrible.
Do not feel bad.
I admire this woman. You
is one of my best friends.
Michelle Evidenci, and you are?
- We already know.
- Are we?
We have already
seen a few times.
Antonia is a friend.
A good friend.
Well ...
Is pure.
Have fun.
I want to stop eating.
That's my goal.
At least for a few weeks,
to prove to myself that I can.
You have to do everything in moderation.
Unfortunately, I am not so
well is to live in moderation.
I can not help it,
I just love to swallow.
I wanted anyway
a break.
- Soon, I have ever
made, that's okay. - Me too.
Soon.
We could do together.
- That would be a better person
make of me. - Right.
We were both
better people.
What about our friends.
You would not understand.
Friends come and go.
If they do not appreciate,
what I do for me, then fuck it.
They can be replaced.
But let tomorrow
worried about it.
Yes, fuck it.
It tastes too good.
- I do not eat appetizers.
- One of my best friends.
Until I get what I
wants, it's just me.
- How it should be.
- I agree.
I am my own person. And who
does not see this, you must read the book ...
... About me.
It's not that I do not care all.
But no one is as interesting as I ...
me.
It's about me or
nothing. Just me.
Me, me, me ...
Shit!
God!
No, no!
Why?
Please ...
I love you!
I'm sorry.
I am ruined.
At the end ...
... Whatever the case, happened
always one of two things.
It always happens.
The storyteller
continues or ...
. Your story.
Past ... ...
... Before you notice anything.