THE SILENCE OF NETO
You're absolutely right, Al.
Thank you.
Welcome, baseball fans.
Buck Cañiel here live.
This is the moment
of truth for the Indians.
who are trailing
3 games to nil...
Your uncle was
in terrible pain, Neto.
Now he's at peace.
Your papers.
Choy, it's me!
Your Honour, I'm sorry.
I didn't recognize you.
So you made lieutenant?
My brother just died.
Don Ernesto?
Show this to anyone
who stops you.
Thanks, you're very kind.
My deepest sympathy.
- Señora, my condolences.
- Thank you.
Doña Mercedes,
my condolences.
I want to go with him.
My Ernesto!
Don't say that, it's a sin.
The sin is that
he never married me.
He promised to marry me once
his mother and father died.
And there she is,
fit as a fiddle.
What a scandal!
Give her a pill,
take her for a walk...
But for God's sake
get her out of here!
It's okay, Neto. Relax.
And the elder son
said to his father...
"I have long served you
and never disobeyed you.
"Yet you never
gave me a calf.
"But when this son came,
"who has wasted your fortune
on loose women,
"you killed the fatted calf
for him."
And the father said to him,
"Son, you are always with me."
"But it was fitting that
we should feast and rejoice
"because your brother was dead
and has come back to life.
"He was lost
and now he is found."
Mother most Holy,
I am a sinner.
Forgive me.
Last night I forgot
to pray for my uncle.
Please don't send him to hell.
He was a little strange,
but I thought he was great.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
Hey, Uncle! Aren't you
supposed to be dead?
Don't be scared, Neto.
You're all dressed up.
How was your exam?
Don't worry.
I bet you flunked.
I'm just kidding.
Let me see...
You got 98.
Come on, let's go
and have a little talk.
This may be
your best trick yet.
You don't think I'd leave
without saying goodbye?
No way!
Is something bothering you?
Last night I forgot
to pray for you.
You had your mind
on Nidia, you rascal.
She sure is cute.
I had my eye on her myself.
But she wouldn't give me
a tumble. Lucky boy!
So you're just like
everyone else.
What did you expect?
- I thought you had no faults.
- Neto, always remember this.
The worst thing to do
is not to say what you feel.
Remember,
say what you feel.
Remember, say what you feel.
Remember...
six months earlier...
Oh, my God! My God!
What's happened?
What's the matter?
No, no...no!
He's dead! He's dead!
Hi, Mum, we're home.
Hello, darling.
Did you get wet?
No, the rain was over
when we left school.
But there were
some great puddles.
Mario! You're all wet!
And you too.
Hi, kids.
How was school?
Okay, go and get changed.
Go on.
Children, here's your snack.
Elena...
Wow! It looks great.
- You like it?
- I love it.
There are
some great bargains...
I will return, María Elena,
when there is peace.
When justice is done...
and our mission is ended.
I will return, María Elena.
One day I will return.
When there is peace...
The Unforgettable
Adventures of...
...a special bulletin.
The President of the Republic,
Col. Jacobo Arbenz Guzmán,
announced this afternoon
that, as of today,
the government of
the United States of America
has established
a naval blockade...
Who knows
what will happen?
Don't worry.
...to prevent
the entry of arms...
Now we'll never know what
happened to the Villalobos.
I know. They shouldn't
be allowed to interrupt.
Hey, try holding your breath
underwater for a whole minute.
- How will that help?
- It will strengthen your lungs.
Neto, enough talking
on the phone.
Bulletin terminated.
Over and out.
I don't like
talking on the phone.
- Neither do l, Cristy.
- It's not like before, is it?
People used to talk
to each other, face to face.
Guess what I'll do when
I grow up and have money.
Take care of your parents?
Will you... travel?
I'll get a phone in my car
and call the whole world.
What an imagination, Neto.
Hello, Uncle Ernesto?
Hello?
For Mother's medicine.
You might need it.
La Hora! La Hora!
Extra! Extra!
Be careful what you say.
These days you never know
who you might be talking to.
Hi, Chilo. What's news?
I saw Rodrigo demonstrating
at the National Palace.
Put the change
in your piggy bank.
Good afternoon,
Don Eduardo.
Hello, dear.
Hello, Father.
Hi. Did you do
your homework?
Yes, but I have to study
some more.
Did something
go wrong at work?
Things are turning ugly.
You must tell Rodrigo
to keep out of politics.
- It could make trouble for us.
- I'll talk to Rosa.
And if Nidia wants
to see her dad
Sunday is her day off.
Okay, I'll tell her.
What are you doing, child?
Neto, what are you doing?
My exercises.
Exercises?
Are you crazy?
With this report on
our country's impending crisis
we sign off this broadcast
of Guatemala Flash.
Just rumors.
Today when the rain started
I was thinking of
our first quarrel. Remember?
You arrived in Chichicastenango
completely soaked.
And I told my mother I never
wanted to see you again.
My dear...
How silly I was.
Food. Compass.
Gloves. Water.
Rodrigo, please, I'm working.
Teach me to iron?
No, please... I'm busy.
Come on...
Drop that a minute.
Why play hard to get?
The iron!
It's burnt and I'll get fired.
Now what do I do?
What am I going to do?
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Thirteen.
Tomorrow I must do twenty.
- Hurry up, Neto.
- Coming.
Careful.
Fighting for Peace and Honor.
The Three Villalobos.
I, Rodolfo... Macho... Miguelón...
solemnly swear
we will not rest
until the death of our brother
is avenged.
I swear.
Girls, out of the pool.
You too, boys.
Antigua by 5 am...
Santa María by 6.
Then we set off up the volcano,
and keep heading south.
Wherever there's suffering.
- Wherever there's misery.
- Wherever evil prevails.
Wherever danger threatens.
Tamacún the Avenger
will ride again.
All set, Rodrigo?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
I have to stand guard outside.
Did Neto explain?
Sort of.
Here's how it works.
For 5 cents
you can see two pages.
10 cents
gets you five pages.
And for 25 cents...
the whole magazine.
You pay up front.
Slow down, Rodrigo.
There once lived a king
who had a palace of diamonds,
a balcony of malachite,
a great coat of cloth
and a kind and beautiful
daughter, Princess Margarita.
As beautiful as you.
All done?
Here... I brought
the knapsack you asked for.
- Take good care of it.
- Thanks.
I sure will.
What about my commission?
Ten percent.
- Can we go?
- Hold on.
Again?
See how your parents
gave you permission to go?
That's because the whole
was going to be at the pool.
Talking about permissions,
look at this.
Let's see.
It's the same permission slip
as for the swimming trip.
No. The 18th is...
In 10 days.
Exactly. The date of our plan.
I just wrote in the new date.
During recess
when no one was watching.
I used the teacher's typewriter
for the new dates.
Okay, let's go.
The class has already started.
I like Ruth.
What about you?
Me, Maria.
How about you, Neto?
- I know who.
- Me too.
- Ani.
- You're hooked on her...
Ani, what's going on here?
- It was an alley cat.
- Oh, those awful cats!
Back to work, girls.
Why were you at ballet class?
I wanted... to see you.
And... I wanted
to ask you something.
What?
If I could...
If I could walk you home.
What do you think of the clouds?
I like clouds.
Okay.
Really?
Look at that one.
It looks like a goldfish
chatting with a wild boar.
What an imagination.
Just one more bite.
A little more. The last one.
No sweeter sight
than a sweet with a sweet.
- Hello, Don Choy.
- No, wait, Neto.
Your father's busy.
Your money's not welcome.
Choy!
Show these men out.
That won't be necessary.
Government jobs aren't forever.
But money is.
Let's go.
One more taste.
I don't want any more,
Ernesto.
- If only I were a slice of cake.
- Don't say such things.
Mommy!
Delicious...
You know who's upstairs
watching?
Eduardo.
Attention,
Guatemalan National Army.
Here is important news
via Liberation Radio,
the underground station.
This is an outrage.
An organized circus.
Catholics of Guatemala,
Communism denies
the existence of God
to destroy the religious faith
that keeps us strong.
We must fight Communism!
- Dad, will you eat this?
- No, thanks.
Neto, is the glue ready yet?
Yes, coming.
Who invented balloons,
Uncle?
It was the Chinese.
They passed the idea
on to the Arabs
who gave it to the Spanish
and so to us.
The lndians got everything
from the Spanish.
No! The Maya
were great inventors.
They had a way of counting
like our decimal system
to write big numbers
in small spaces.
- Did they have telescopes?
- Of course.
They simply used
two sticks to see...
the moon...
Venus...
the stars.
And what about Tikal?
The Maya
were great architects.
- Better than the Romans?
- Just as good.
Did Rome have lots
of Romans?
Yes. Big Romans,
little Romans...
- Lady Romans.
- What else have you seen?
Many things.
Strange animals, dinosaurs...
pink elephants,
five-legged hippos...
What color were they,
my son?
All beautiful colors, Mama.
They were green...
red... bright yellow...
fuschia!
But most amazing of all
was the time I saw
the Pope in person.
Pius XII?
Pius XII... in the flesh.
Did he pardon your sins?
Elena, please.
What sins could my son have
that couldn't be forgiven?
True.
All that's left
is to canonize him.
Hi, Eduardo.
So you're back
unannounced as usual.
Did you enjoy the pastries?
Hi, Dad.
The kids are about to fly
this balloon. Why not come?
You too, Mother.
No, it's dangerous.
Boys shouldn't play with fire.
They're irresponsible.
Because parents
make them that way.
Besides, it's late, Elena.
Okay, kids,
say good night.
It's time for you
to lie down, too.
Bye, son.
Don't speak to me that way
in front of the children.
And don't tell me how to bring
them up. I'm a good father.
- What are you insinuating?
- Nothing.
Who knows how many
children you have?
What's my life to you?
What matters
is your bad example.
Is it bad to tell them
there's a whole world outside?
At least they won't turn out
to be wandering misfits.
And you want them
to be robots like yourself.
Let them breathe a little.
Their place is here at home
with their parents.
You're just like Mum and Dad.
You selfishly think
children are only meant
to look after their parents.
You're the selfish one,
bumming around the world,
pretending
no one understands you.
Cut the crap.
You know very well I left
to earn money to send home.
Those damned money orders...
Mum would hide them from Dad
so he couldn't tear them up.
And he'd shout...
"I'd trade a million checks
for one hug from my son."
Hypocrite!
As usual.
You can't face the truth.
I'm leaving before
I punch you in the mouth.
No, Neto, no!
I told you not to do that.
While you live in my house
you'll do as I say.
- That's dangerous.
- No, Daddy!
Silence!
Silence now.
That's it. Shut up!
No, I didn't mean it.
It was an accident.
No, Daddy!
What beautiful gondolas,
Uncle.
The postcard reminded me of
the boats on Lake Amatitlán.
But the gondoliers here
don 't dress as well
as they do in Venice.
I've been preparing for a while
for a big adventure.
I'll tell you about it when
you return for my birthday.
That's all for now.
I remain your ever loyal
and attentive servant,
Ernesto Antonio
Yepes Amézquita.
Mom, Cristy's asking
for the punch.
Coming.
Rodrigo!
Tonight you won't get away.
I told you
to leave Nidia alone.
It's nothing, Mom.
Think of your future.
Don't be a fool.
Here are the drinks.
There's a special bottle
just for you.
A drink, Justo?
Ice?
Let's hope for the best.
The children
are what worry me most.
Uncle!
I didn't know you were back.
Twelve already.
Yep, I'm getting old.
And so much yet to see.
Don't turn your back
on life's surprises.
- Then you won't be bored.
- Let's get some cake.
You can have mine.
There's a gift inside for you.
Okay, Uncle.
Neto, come on.
- Did you find the top?
- Yes.
Come on. The ants
will get you out here.
Cristy, the cake looks terrific.
Eduardo...
A candle went out.
Cristy, call the children.
Kids, come and blow out
the candles.
One.. two... three.
Dad, what's that?
It's for his asthma.
This cake stinks
but it tastes good. Smell it.
What a lovely party.
It really is such fun.
My goodness, Neto!
You musn't get so excited.
- You could have an attack.
- Listen to your mother.
If you're not careful, you won't
be able to breathe tonight.
- But I feel fine.
- Maybe for now.
Look.
Your uncle sent you this.
Look, that's Babe Ruth
the day he retired.
New York, 1 May 1954.
Dear Neto, it's time to fly
your first balloon.
I made this one especially
for you. Happy Birthday.
With all my love,
your Uncle Ernesto.
I'm going to fly this myself.
Dad, can I fly my balloon?
Neto, this is
a dangerous business.
But Dad...
Watch and you can do it
when you're old enough.
Make room.
I'm going to fill it with air.
Rodrigo, give me a hand.
Watch, this is how it's done.
Neto...
What are you doing?
You'll catch your death.
Look, Mom.
Here comes a comet.
Oh Neto...
Comets don't come, they go.
Always running away,
like your Uncle Ernesto.
Come, let's go inside,
my little monkey.
He only invited Ani
to his party.
A party just for geniuses.
For geniuses
and revolutionaries.
Geniuses are dopey
and revolutionaries are dumb.
My dad's not a revolutionary.
My dad says
that revolutionaries...
wear red underwear!
- Leave him alone!
- You stay out of it.
- Want to see something good?
- Like what?
Children, stop it.
Everyone inside, now!
Are you all right, Neto?
Today we learn the meaning
of the words "tolerance"
and "dignity".
Any volunteers to read
from the blackboard?
Neto, please.
"There is no human power
"capable of crushing
the will of a people
"unless its leaders
betray them.
"People and government
together constitute dignity."
Juan José Arévalo,
President of Guatemala,
1946 - 1951.
Looks like it's getting cloudy.
Cloudy? You're crazy.
There are no clouds.
Look what they're doing.
Let's get them!
They're throwing down papers!
"For God, Country and Liberty.
Fight Communism."
Alberto, Neto...
a demonstration!
Wow! Hop on, Neto.
Close the door
before they get here.
My love, we must
defend democracy.
Unite!
Unite and fight!
There's no danger,
my darling.
I'm scared, Rodrigo.
Oh, my love!
I'll be back soon.
I hope you die in the war,
Rodrigo, and never come back.
Rodrigo... no.
I have to go.
Whore!
I'm going to tell Dad you're
messing around with Rodrigo.
Child, it's just something
grown people do.
Then, when I'm grown up,
will you mess around with me?
Dirty Indian.
Neto, in this country
everyone is an Indian.
Not me.
Explain to me
what makes balloons fly.
It's very simple.
First of all, balloons were
invented by the Chinese...
My dear Ani,
I'm writing you this letter
in case something
on my arduous journey
prevents me returning.
I would like these verses
to carry to you
my last breath
and eternal devotion.
"Little princess, how beautiful
is the sea, and the wind
"carrying me the scent of
orange blossom, your breath."
"Now that you are so far away,
keep a sweet thought of me,
"as sweet as the story
I wanted to tell you."
You explain things very well.
Quick, it's getting late.
...with much love, Neto.
Ani...
Can I ask you a favor?
Of course.
Keep this letter.
If I'm not at school on Monday,
read it and think of me.
Why?
Good afternoon, Tomás.
I'll come inside in a moment.
Why?
Because I have to go
on a very important journey.
Where to?
I'll tell you when I get back.
Hurry up, child.
Thank you.
You're much prettier in person.
Isn't he sweet?
Stop pestering me.
He's going on a camping trip
with a fake permission slip.
Here, take this and get out.
- I am immortal, silly giant.
- I am invincible, sad knight.
And now I will destroy you
with my evil tortures,
you stupid,
black-bearded fool!
- Raise you five.
- A pair of sixes.
- Two pairs.
- You've won again...
TGW, the Voice of Guatemala,
via the Emergency
Broadcast System,
brings you
this special bulletin.
The Government
of the Republic...
...this afternoon at 4 p.m.
two pirate aircraft,
in flagrant violation of
our national sovereignty...
Thank you, Lord.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou
among women.
Thank you,
Lord of Esquipulas.
We thank Thee for watching
over us in our time of need.
Mother dearest...
I'm so glad you're back, son.
How are you, Ernesto?
What a surprise.
Look how beautiful you are.
When did you get back
to Guatemala?
I just got here.
It was too hot in Morocco
so I've returned
to the Cold War.
Now pour me a drink.
I'm chilly already.
You're so silly, Ernesto.
You never change.
The Lord heard my prayer.
And now He'll send
the Americans
to free us
from the Communists.
Mama, you think anyone
who's different is a Communist.
Ernesto, respect your mother.
Tell Ambassador Peurifoy
to show us some respect.
Boys, don't argue, please.
Uncle!
How are you, young man?
No one believes I saw
the Communist planes.
It's really nothing
but American propaganda.
It's all so simple, right?
And to think, all of this
just to steal a few bananas.
But that's not why I came.
You can't stay here.
The National Guard will be
bombed, and you're too close.
He's right, Eduardo.
Where the hell are we
supposed to go, then?
To my house. Nobody would
think to bomb Antigua.
What about my field trip?
Forget about it.
Elena, get the bags ready.
I'm sure they'll postpone it.
Neto, let's go and pack.
Antigua will be fun.
- Do I bring my schoolbooks?
- There's no school tomorrow.
Quiet, kids!
This isn't a circus, it's a war.
You needn't upset them.
What do they know about war?
Hello.
Is Alberto there, please?
- Machito-Alberto?
- I read you, Neto-Rodolfo.
The sardines' trip is postponed
until the shark is gone.
- Got it?
- Loud and clear.
- Tell Miguelón.
- Over.
Over and out.
The just decision to expropriate
uncultivated land
for distribution
among landless peasants
has made local reactionaries
and rich foreigners desperate
and intensified
a long-standing conspiracy,
national and international,
powerful and antidemocratic,
whose intentions
are to damage
the democratic government
of Guatemala
and to block
its program of reform
which, as everybody knows,
seeks to develop
the economy of our country.
Here, take these.
This one's fixed.
People of Guatemala...
The Communists' land reform
is causing widespread misery.
The government
has cheated you.
We must fight Communism!
Eeny, meeny, miney, mo...
Okay, I'll teach you one.
By Lake Titicaca,
a lady had to caca.
She had no hankie,
had to use her pinkie
and the pinkie is you!
Liberation Radio of Guatemala,
the underground station...
...The Army's honour
is vested in the upholding
of the broadest democracy
and national independence.
- Okay here?
- Yes, fine.
... with absolute faith
and hope in the future...
People of Guatemala!
The government
has denied your rights
by turning labor codes
into an instrument of Moscow
and its Guatemalan puppets.
Down with the gover...
How terrible!
For their part,
the banana magnates,
sending their peasants
like lambs to the slaughter...
How do you like that?
That Arbenz really has balls.
Shouldn't they have left
the banana company alone?
If it were only
about bananas...
What the gringos can't stand
is that we don't lick their boots.
At least we'll have
the satisfaction
of being the first to say no
to the Yankees.
Yes, my friend.
First we water over here.
Like this.
And a little above.
And if you need more water...
What country are we in,
Agripina?
With your permission,
good night.
As your friend and brother...
I shall take your wallet
so that nobody can steal it.
Look at the dog, Neto.
He looks like our dog.
Thank you very much.
You are very kind.
And they said
there was a drought.
Hey, what's going on here?
Hey! What's the story?
My pants are all wet.
I'm getting tired, Uncle.
I feel my asthma coming on.
You and your asthma.
What can I do, Uncle?
I've taken all kinds of pills.
My bum is swollen from shots.
And I still can't breathe.
Between your grandmother,
your mother, your aunt,
Rosa and Nidia,
you've got five umbilical
cords feeding you
so you can't breathe
out of your own nose.
Neto, you're all wet.
Go inside and change.
Nidia, help Neto find
some dry clothes, please.
He isn't made of sugar.
He's a boy.
Mario, what are you doing?
Boys will be boys.
People of Guatemala...
Our country is undergoing
a very difficult test.
Two weeks ago
a cruel war was unleashed
and no government
appears to be responsible.
But we do know who has
committed this aggression
against our dear country.
Elena, Arbenz is speaking.
Everybody come!
It's the President.
...monopolies, in collaboration
with the U.S. government,
are responsible for
what has happened to us.
Pilots and mercenaries
of various countries,
hired by Guatemalan
exiles abroad
have unleashed fire
and death
with no regard
for innocent lives
or our country's integrity.
In whose name have they
committed these atrocities?
Under what flag?
We all know full well.
They have used the pretext
of Communism.
The truth is very different.
Look for it
in the financial interests
of the United Fruit Company
and the other
North American monopolies
with vast interests
in Latin America,
whose greatest fear
is that Guatemala's example
will spread to the rest
of Latin America.
After careful consideration and
with revolutionary conscience,
I have reached a decision
with enormous implications
for our country.
In the hope of halting
the aggression
and bringing peace back
to Guatemala,
I have decided
to resign from power
and to place my command
in the hands of my friend
Colonel Carlos Enrique Díaz
head of the Armed Forces...
So what happens now, Dad?
They give us back the land
the Communist took away.
Oh, yes.
Those vast idle lands where
imaginary cows will graze
and where we'll plant
invisible corn.
Thank you,
Our Lord of Esquipulas.
Tens years of struggle,
tears and sacrifice,
and of achievements
for democracy,
stand in defiance
of the course of events.
Perhaps some will
feel I am making a mistake.
In the depths of my conscience
I believe this is not true.
History alone
will be the final judge.
With the satisfaction
of one who believes
he has done as he must,
and with faith in the future,
I say "Long live
the October Revolution!"
"Long live Guatemala!"
Where will you go, Uncle?
I don't know. To hell.
Maybe to Italy.
I'm ashamed to stay here,
among cowards and traitors.
Father's not a coward.
I didn't mean him.
With him it's another story.
Every time you two talk
you end up fighting.
Couldn't you just keep quiet?
That would be easiest,
wouldn't it, Neto?
But if you have something
to say, you must say it.
How like your mother you are.
You're quiet, just like her...
just like this whole country.
Neto, silence like this
isn't good.
It's ingrained in us
from the time we're born.
But it's up to us to tear it out
from inside ourselves.
Not until then
will we be able to breathe.
Goodbye, Uncle.
Take good care of yourself.
Take care, son.
- Where's Ani?
- Isn't she here yet?
She always comes early.
President Jacobo Arbenz
has resigned.
This affirms the strength
of the Liberation Army
which defeated him
overwhelmingly.
It is with great joy
that we announce
that this crucial objective
has been achieved...
I'll take care of it.
What are you doing
at my desk?
My desk.
Your belongings
are in that box.
That's my fountain pen.
Sorry, it's already been
registered in the inventory.
Need any help?
No, thank you.
I can manage on my own.
Well, hello there.
As of today...
Mr. Rogelio Pérez
will be your new teacher.
- They're in your hands now.
- Thank you, Principal.
You may sit down.
Today we'll learn
the capitals of the states
of the United States
of America.
Repeat after me.
Alabama,
capital Montgomery.
When I say repeat after me,
I mean everyone.
That's better.
Arkansas,
capital Little Rock.
Sir, I have to leave the room.
Let's go on.
Neto, come back here!
I'll have to tell the Principal.
What are you doing?
- Looking for Ani.
- There's no Ani here.
Will you change the new
teacher's signature too?
Maybe.
You can't do that.
It doesn't matter any more.
- This was your idea.
- So?
It doesn't matter any more.
You're on your own
with the volcano trip.
- Biscuit, Eduardo?
- Yes, thanks.
Where are the maids?
They're going crazy
looking for Rodrigo.
What happened?
He hasn't been home
in three days.
Why not?
My parents are acting
as if they know nothing.
Chickens!
People of Guatemala...
In the tradition
of this great democracy...
What is it?
Did you find out anything?
...on the occasion of the
greatest battle of our history.
This will be Radio Liberation's
final broadcast.
"I hope you die in the war,
Rodrigo, and never come back. "
Germán!
Al berto!
Where are you?
Hey, look at this!
You've got to see this!
No, Neto, leave it alone.
That's from the war.
You sound like my dad.
Alberto's right.
It's dangerous.
But it's so beautiful.
You jerk!
Germán...
Germán, what's the matter?
You stupid idiot!
You could have killed me.
Gosh,
I'm glad I didn't kill you.
Hi, Dad.
You seem worried.
What is it?
It's nothing.
It must be something.
Is it about Neto?
Yes.
Lately he's become
so irresponsible.
Your mother says
that's how boys are.
But how would she know,
being a woman?
Yeah. He doesn't like
staying at home any more.
Right.
As if this were a prison.
I love you, Dad.
And I like being here with you.
- Don't worry
- You're growing up, son.
Now that I have a new job
I'll be traveling more.
I want to give you
the house's expense money.
Look after it. You know
how to handle money.
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
Hurry up!
Let's go and play pool.
Not saying hello, Alejandra?
Nice shot. Right, buddy?
Don't choke.
- It wont be enough Mario.
- I gave you Q5.00 yesterday.
Yes, but I spent it. You ate
all the cookies yourself.
- Well, I was hungry.
- Give me one more Quetzal.
No, it's too much.
I'll give you 50 centavos.
This is getting out of hand.
- I'll have to see you father.
- So?
Respect your mother,
you bastard.
- It's none of your business.
- Go and apologize.
Apologize or you'll get it.
Ooh, I'm scared.
- Give me the money.
- It's mine!
I should have it.
I'm older.
I'm the one who should
take care of it.
Boys! Stop fighting.
Neto, let go of your brother.
- Let's go.
- But he started it...
- I don't want to hear.
- It's not my fault.
I gave Mum Q1.50.
He's barely nine.
Why give him money?
It's disrespectful to me.
At least he knows
how to handle money.
What do you mean by that?
You throw money away
on bingo and cards
and buying Neto
whatever he likes.
I play bingo because I'm bored,
understand? Fed up.
All you care about
is your whisky.
I can't take it any more.
Let me go, I haven't done
anything. I want to go home.
Let's go, Doña Rosa.
- That boy could be my son.
- But he's not. Let's go.
Star, are you still in the sky?
Dove, have you flown away?
Where are you?
You've been gone so long.
You left like a sigh.
Is it forever?
Another small one.
This came out great.
Congratulations.
Even Mr. Pérez
won't be able to tell.
Now I'll do yours.
- Mum, sign this for me.
- I'm on the phone.
It's just a permission slip
for school.
- For what?
- The class trip.
Thanks.
There's our volcano.
Let's go.
Leave, Nidia.
Leave.
Don't end up like me.
Go to your people.
You'll be safe with them.
Don't stay here like I did.
Leave, child.
Eduardo,
a telegram from ltaly.
"Ernesto Yepes recovering
from cardiac arrest.
"Valdevere Clinic.
"Arriving Guatemala
October 19 via New York."
That's tomorrow.
Regard, Paola Corinne."
Who's Paola Corinne?
She must be
the director of the clinic.
How awful.
Oh, that Ernesto.
If he doesn't take care
One day he'll give us
a real scare.
He needs to cut down
on drinking and smoking.
So should you.
Don't worry. We Yepes
live to a ripe old age.
We're quiet country folk.
What about Ernesto?
I don't know
what happened there.
He never liked
staying at home.
A real vagabond.
I've never heard you
speak of him without sarcasm.
Elena, the man is ill.
Don't be so self-centered.
Maybe I am self-centered.
But I'm tired of seeing you
so worried all the time.
If I don't worry, who will?
Everything seemed
so beautiful ten years ago.
We couldn't even afford
a cradle when Neto was born.
But we had our dreams.
What happened
to those dreams?
There once was a trio,
the Three Villalobos.
Yes, there were three,
and none was a dodo.
May the best luck,
God willing,
always be there
to guide them
and we in Villahermosa
will always sing this song.
There once was a trio
the Three Villalobos.
Yes, there were three
and none was a dodo...
What's happening?
It won't fly.
There is too much wind.
It's burning.
My balloon's burning.
This thing doesn't work.
- I'm staying here.
- The wolves will eat you.
Let them.
I'm staying here.
In that case,
I'm taking your pack.
They'll have plenty to eat
with just you.
Dad was right. I shouldn't
start what I can't finish.
So what do you want?
- To get to the top.
- Come on, then.
Cut it out.
Thanks, Alberto.
Look who's there.
You're going bad, Neto.
You're a forger.
What about my friends?
They can come.
Why did you come back?
Do you mind?
No. Forgive me.
I just thought
you'd stay in Rome.
With Paola.
I came home
to die in my own bed.
So no one could
blame me for going off...
and dying
God knows where,
not even knowing
where I was buried.
- Don't be so cynical.
- You want me to change now?
Life's a big joke, isn't it?
Why?
I kept running away from
this house to be different.
But I never left it behind.
and I'm ending up
like everyone else.
What do you mean?
It's time for me to pay up.
You never change, Ernesto.
And what guides our life?
I don't even know.
We're all different,
that's about all I know.
Full of dreams...
that we don't
even understand.
Yes.
We're all different.
Do you know
why I really came back?
Only in the place
where we were born
can we come to life again.
Anywhere else
we would remain
incomplete forever
and our pain
would never end.
Come in, Neto.
Don't tire your uncle.
Give me a hug, my boy.
What happened to you?
Nothing.
I came to see you.
So, you climbed
up to the crater?
It was hard, but I made it.
You look great. You did
something big by yourself.
Yes. I never thought
I could do it.
And I didn't get asthma.
Water?
I tried to fly a balloon,
but I couldn't.
You know why?
Because it wasn't a balloon
you made yourself.
I have to go, Uncle.
I have to study
for an exam tomorrow.
That's fine.
Before you leave,
open that trunk.
Those patterns and the
tissue paper are for you.
You have to build
the first balloon you fly...
yourself.
Thanks, Uncle. You'll be there
to help me, right?
I'll be there, just in case.
But it must be your balloon.
For Ernesto,
with all my love.
I'll never forget you.
Elena.
My uncle always said
it's not good to keep silent.
Neto, they're going
to bring him out.
- I have to go.
- Where?
But this time
it was he who kept silent.
Let's go.
Nidia, come on.
Let's go fly my balloon.
- I can't do it.
- Never say you can't.
I have to go.
Keep trying
until the flame catches.
This is the last match.
Don't worry.
The dead remain
in the memory of the living.
Is it filling?
More or less.
There. You see?
Goodbye, Neto.
Goodbye, Uncle.
- Where are you going?
- Back to my village.
Why?
I want my baby to be
born among its own people.
Nidia!
Always let your son
say what he feels.
It's like the one Ernesto flew
when his father died.
The most important thing
my Uncle Ernesto taught me
was to always keep a promise.
To María Luisa,
my mother