- I don't know if I want to do this.
- Relax, Laine.
It's fun.
First, the rules.
You can never, ever play alone.
You can never play in a graveyard
and you always have to say goodbye.
To start, you circle the
board, once for each player.
Then we say, as friends we
gather, hearts are true.
As friends we gather, hearts are true.
- Spirits near, we call to you.
Is someone here with us?
- Debbie, cut it out.
- If a ghost is here...
you can see them through the planchette.
It's the eye to the other side.
If someone is here with us, make yourself known.
- What are you guys doing?
- Get out of here, Sarah!
Calm down, it's only a game.
Goodbye.
Laine, hey.
Deb.
Where are you?
I'm... I'm here.
I've been here.
Just been a little rough...
this week.
You've gotta tell me what's been going on,
and don't think you're bailing on me, again.
We're gonna be late for the game.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I don't think I'm coming.
Oh, well, I'm not leaving
until I get to talk to you.
Fine.
I'll be right out, just gimme a sec.
What's going on?
- You sick?
- No.
- Did you and Pete have a fight?
- No, nothing like that.
- Then what is it?
- Nothing.
Debbie, tell me.
I just don't wanna go out tonight.
No secrets between us, remember?
Remember that game we used to play?
Where you ask questions about the future.
- The Ouija board.
- Yeah.
Couple weeks ago...
I played it.
Just... messing around and...
I don't know, I don't know.
That is just a game.
- You know you've always been like this, right?
- Like what?
Just a total and complete spaz.
You're right, I'm being crazy.
Look, I don't even have to
go to the basketball game.
We always lose, I'm just
gonna come with you, and...
No, don't.
I mean... my folks are gonna be home any minute.
And I'm just being dramatic.
And everything is fine.
Are you sure you don't wanna come?
I have leftovers inside, I'm gonna rock
it out, but I will see you in the morning.
- Thats for sure.
- Okay. Do you want me to order for you?
- And give you the works?
- Uh, huh.
Okay.
- I miss you.
- I miss you already.
No.
Laine, hey, sorry I'm late.
I have a surprise for you.
Check this out.
Oh, you have a map.
Yep, this is the place I was telling you about.
It's up the coast, away from everyone,
we make camp right about here.
Yeah.
Hike down to the beach any time we want.
- The first time I'm here and it is we?
- I want you to come with.
But I thought this was your big
camping trip with the guys.
I know, but I started thinking about it,
and I reaIzed I'd miss you too much.
Okay, you're surfing all day, what do I do?
I'm gonna teach you, by the end of the
week you'll be one with the waves.
- Its gonna be awesome.
- Oh my, no.
I promise, come on. Forget about the world
for awhile, leave it all behind.
- I can't wait to see you run this past my dad.
- I got that covered, too.
Tell him it's a Senior trip. Fully chaperoned.
- Good luck with that.
- What? I can be persuasive.
- Really?
- Yeah, I've been told this.
- By who?
- You.
Every day.
Okay, very cute, break it up, you two..
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hey, Iz, a little more brain juice?
- Uh, huh.
Where's Debbie?
Oh, I think she's running late.
So, what time will you be
leaving that party, tonight?
- I think we're passing.
- Yeah.
- Like, watch a movie, or something.
- No.
Come on, you guys can't.
Lainey's making you bail on me.
You're a big girl, Iz. There's
nothing wrong with flying solo.
Yeah, me showing up alone.
Its not really a good "look" for me.
- And everybody has, you know, "this."
- What's "this"?
Your perfect couple situation.
Look at her. Acting like she's not the one who
breaks up with every guy she goes out with.
I can't help it, I'm a picky bitch.
God!
What's up?
I gotta go, it's my dad.
Let me guess, your sister?
Yep, causing chaos, wherever she goes.
I'm sorry, guys. Come on.
- What's going on?
- I'm so sorry.
Nona wanted to be here for you.
Laine, sit down, we need to talk.
I don't wanna sit down. Just
tell me what's going on?
Laine, sit down!
I don't wanna sit down! Someone
tell me what's going on!
It's about Debbie.
- Nona, can I talk to you?
- Uh, huh.
I don't think I can go in.
This doesn't seem real, she
should-she should still be here.
She's still here.
She's right here.
Here.
I just don't understand.
None of us can.
She told me, she told me that
she'd see us next morning.
Why would she say that if she was going to...?
We'll never know.
I wish she would've talked to
us, about whatever it was.
I know what the police say,
but I can't believe she'd ever...
And that Carol found her like that?
It's just horrible.
They're packed and coming to stay with me.
Can't be in this house and feel right.
Pete.
Laine.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry, too.
I brought flowers.
- Debbie liked this kind.
- They're really pretty.
Do you want me to put them in some water?
No, I'll find her mom. I should give them to her.
Laine.
- You were everything to her.
- Mrs. G.
Sorry, I just...
I just wanted to be in her room.
It's okay.
The hours you two spent in here.
By fifth grade, you-you'd picked out your college.
She used to draw pictures of...
of what our dorms would look like.
Everything was purple.
Yeah, I remember that.
Her purple phase.
Thank you for watching the
house while we're gone.
I don't know when we'll be back.
Here.
I put these things together for you.
She'd want you to have them.
Always remember her.
No, that's it, that's the one, look.
Let me see your...
See? Its good.
Ladies, you need to keep it down in there.
We do have other customers.
We were a lot cooler than we're making this seem.
Right.
Look at my girls.
Oh, my God, I'll gonna fly.
Oh, my girls, look at you.
You have to get on that.
Oh, my goodness!
Why are you always pulling up my dress?
Whether or not you have any
sort of affection inside
of you that you wanna give to your boyfriend.
- You don't think I have any affection?
- I mean, right now, I don't know.
You gonna love me for doing that?
Um-hmm, why?
Really, Sarah?
After everything that happened
today, you have to do this?
Do what?
Sneak out.
Make things so hard all the time...
Look, I just wanna get out of here
and forget this shitty day, alright?
Oh, I'm sorry, but you're not going anywhere.
Mom's not around, hasn't been for a while.
And you don't need to be her? Okay?
It's not your job, to hover over me all the time.
I wish I didn't have to.
Well, then, just don't care so much.
It's way easier.
- Okay, dad, here's your flight confirmation.
- Once the permits get approved
I'll be back. It might be
a few days, though. Okay?
Okay.
Nona knows I'm leaving so call
her if you need anything.
Yeah, I got it covered, dad, don't worry.
Bye.
Have a safe trip.
I'll text you when I get there.
You've class in a half hour,
how long's this gonna take?
Uh, Mrs. G. just wants to check
a few things, so, two minutes?
Sure.
Oh, and-and can you go around back
and and check the other pool cover?
Yeah, I got it.
Hello?
- Hey!
- Oh, my God!
It's me. Are you ready to go?
- I didn't ever hear you come up.
- What is that?
Just something Debbie and I used to do.
- Ages ago.
- It was a joke, right?
We pretended it was real.
We asked it questions, like,
do I have a secret admirer?
Will we be friends forever? Things like that.
One of you just pushing it?
Yeah.
I didn't know she had one.
I have so many questions.
If I had just stayed, I was right here
if I hadn't of left her, you know?
Laine...
it's not your fault.
You just don't know when it's gonna be the
last time you get to talk to someone.
We never even got to say goodbye.
I know.
Pete.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Can you talk?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
I haven't gotten a chance
to check in with you, yet.
You doin' okay?
I guess.
I can't bring myself to erase her voicemails.
I keep listening to them and
it's like she's here, you know?
Leaving me messages, making plans.
Before Debbie died...
did you notice anything going on with her?
Like what?
Acting different?
Yeah, she seemed worried about something.
Did she ever say what it was?
It just kinda started out of nowhere.
I didn't know what was going on.
I'd text her, she'd blow me off.
I thought, maybe she wanted to
break up with me or something.
A few days ago, I went to
her house to try to talk to her.
- She didn't even want me to come inside.
- She did the same thing with me.
Why are you asking me all this?
I guess, I'm just not ready to let her go.
Neither am I.
I don't know.
When I'm in that house, it just feels strange.
- You miss Debbie, I mean, we all do.
- No, this-this is different.
I can't explain it, it-it's like she's there.
Lainey, listen, everyone's still in shock, okay?
But those things you were telling me
the other day, about feeling guilty...
You don't have to keep doing this to yourself.
You ever feel like, even after
someone you love has died,
there's still a way you can talk to them?
But you can't do that, she's gone.
The board, isn't that what
you're supposed to do with it?
But, yesterday you said it was just a game.
If we play the game and nothing happens,
then I'll never bring it up again.
But I really want to try, so...
will you guys just do this with me?
Sarah?
I'm heading out. I'll be an hour.
Sarah!
Yeah?
- I'm going out. I'll be back in a bit.
- Hour. Yeah, cool, got it.
Hey, get outta here!
What the hell, Laine?
For a minute, there, I actually
had a little faith in you.
We hang out! What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with that, is that you're a kid
and that guy is too old for you.
Alright, since you can't be left
alone, you're coming with me.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Bring your stuff. I'll be in the car.
I don't wanna be in this house. Feels wrong.
Well, this is where Debbie died.
We have to play here.
It's okay.
We're all together.
So where are we gonna do this?
In there.
I'm gonna go and get the board.
How are you even supposed to talk
to someone using a board game?
I mean, yo, can you hear me?
Signal's real bad, I only got, like, one bar in here.
Your sister wants to do this,
so just zip it and go along.
- Oh, my God!
- Jesus.
- Pete.
- It's okay.
Just me, I heard you coming through the front.
What the hell are you doing, man?
I have a spare key for the back.
I come in that way all the time.
- So let's play.
- Wait.
There's a few rules, first.
Like: You're never supposed
to play in a graveyard.
Never play alone and always say goodbye.
Can we just do this?
I don't even think I believe in these things.
- But, I still don't wanna touch it.
- Come on, it's only toy stories.
Circle the board.
Once for each of us.
And then you say these words:
As friends we've gathered, hearts are true.
Spirits near, we call to you.
If there's a presence here,
please make yourself known.
Is there a presence here among us?
This is a joke.
Come on, you guys, who's doing that?
- Sarah, cut it out!
- I'm not pushing it.
Is there something you wanna tell us?
H...
I...
Spelled, hi friend.
Hi, friend.
When I was here yesterday, was that you?
Who is this?
Debbie.
Sarah, if that's you, pretending to be
Debbie, then that's really messed up.
- I swear, it's not me, alright?
- Hey, this is freaking me out.
Let's just stop it, now.
I'm sorry, Iz, just-just put
your hand back, please.
Debbie...
was there something I could have done?
Was there some way we could have helped you?
If there's anything you want to tell us,
about what you did,
if you did this to yourself.
Did you really do this?
Guys...
Calm down. It's an old house.
Laine, keep going.
- Debbie, I miss you.
- I miss you, too.
We all do.
If you can hear us, we just...
I don't know, we just wanted
a chance to say goodbye.
Laine.
Iz, it's not even real, okay?
It's just a game.
It's all the lights. They're all out.
Let's be honest...
- was it you moving the planchette?
- No.
- You?
- No!
No way.
For all we know, it was Laine.
Maybe it was really something she needed.
Might not have even known she was doing it.
Is it Debbie, did she do this?
- Where are you going?
- Just a second.
- Debbie, is that you?
- Laine, Laine, please, stop.
Okay? It's not her.
What if it is? What if she's
trying to tell me something?
Oh, my God.
- What happened, are you okay?
- What was that?
I saw a reflection in the mirror and then
someone pushed me from behind.
Can we just get out of here, please!
Come on.
- Why you bringing that home?
- It was hers, I want it here.
What?
It's just... that you need to
believe that was really Debbie.
You were there.
It was weird, right?
Yeah, it was weird.
But I don't know if it means anything.
But, what if it's her? What if
she wants to tell me something?
You wanted us to play, we did,
and now we can leave it alone.
Laine, you said goodbye to her.
I know you'll find the moment
when you're ready, but...
I think you can start to move on.
- Good night.
- 'Night.
I couldn't sleep last night.
We don't have to talk about it.
Had all these weird dreams. Keep
thinking about being in her house.
Iz, I know you didn't wanna be there.
You did it for me...
So thank you. I owe you.
Let's just forget the whole deal.
Yeah?
Yeah, okay.
Nona, what are you doing?
You should never touch these things.
You used it, didn't you?
I-it was just once.
Promise me Laine, do not go
seeking answers from the dead.
- Get rid of the board.
- Yeah, I will. I promise, Nona.
Who is that?
- Goodnight, Hank, see you tomorrow.
- Uh, huh.
Oh, hey, can you grab the
garbage on your way out?
Thank you.
Hi, Isabelle.
Where?
No, no, it doesn't sound crazy at all.
I'll pick you up. I'll be there in a few minutes.
This idea of messages from the board,
is nothing more than our unconscious minds.
It's known as the ideomotor effect,
involuntary motor muscles kick in,
which drive the movement of the planchette.
We're simply telling ourselves
what we wanna believe.
Sarah?
- Was that you?
- I thought it was you.
Dad, you home?
Dad!
Go, get...
Do you have your phone?
- No.
- No?
Shit.
Okay, just be quiet. Just be quiet.
Sarah, stay back, okay?
Isabelle was shaking when I
picked her up last night.
I called this morning to check in. She
doesn't even wanna leave the house.
And I saw it, too.
"Hi friend". Carved right into my desk.
Did we all see it?
Debbie's trying to reach us.
- What could she want?
- If we wanna know...
We gotta ask her.
I think we should say the words together.
As friends we've gathered, hearts are true.
Spirits near, we call to you.
If there's a presence here, make yourself known.
Debbie, we're all here for you.
We all got your messages, we're here.
Can you show us a sign?
Are you here?
Come on, guys.
You didn't kill yourself, did you?
I knew it.
Debbie, if you didn't do this, who did?
Did someone hurt you, did-did someone...?
Who did it?
Who hurt you?
Debbie, why won't you answer us?
I have a question.
On our first real date, away from everybody else.
We told everybody we went to the fair.
But where did we really go?
We went to the lookout.
By the point, in the canyon.
Do you remember that? What I said to you?
This isn't Debbie.
- What do you mean?
- I never took her there, not once.
This is you, Debbie?
Then who the hell is this?
D.
Z.
Is this who we were talking to the other night?
Oh, my God!
Were we ever talking to Debbie?
Laine, we can stop.
When Debbie played the Ouija,
did she made contacted you?
D.Z., where are you?
At the chair.
I don't see anything.
Guys, I think we should get out of here.
Run?
She's coming.
Who! Who's coming?
Mother.
- Sarah, wait.
- What happened in there, Laine?
Doesn't matter because we're not playing any more.
Okay?
We're walking away from
the board, the whole thing.
Debbie played, and now she's dead.
Look, w-what if we made the same mistake?
What if we broke some sort of rule?
Hey. Hey.
We're finished with this, okay?
Operation Clean House.
I get to clean...
the attic.
God.
Right.
Attic done, I did the best I could.
Oh, my God, that was not fun.
However, I did find something.
Along with a lot of old junk
from the previous owners.
Ta-da, it's cool, right?
Oh!
They go together.
She found it in her house.
Do I like my find?
Oooh!
Yes.
Am I cleaning the attic, again? No!
So answer my question, I'm waiting.
R.
She played alone?
H-I-F-R-I-E-N-D. Whoa!
Hi friend.
As you know, our community has been
devastated, the last few weeks.
First, with Debbie and now, Isabelle.
I wanted to talk to each of you, because...
I just want to make sure you
and your friends are okay.
When you lose someone close to you...
there's always help available.
We care about you.
Now, um...
there's a lot of very, very helpful
information in here, about...
dealing with loss, and moving forward.
You have no idea what you're talking about.
Laine, w-we're only trying to help you.
You can't.
I'm not even sure who can.
Trevor.
We need to talk, all of us.
You made us play. Now Isabelle's dead.
I know, and I'll never forgive myself.
This thing...
is haunting us.
Wherever we go...
watching everything we do.
It's coming for all of us.
So who's next?
Hey, look, back there, with Trevor.
- He's right.
- Pete, I need you.
It's just us, now.
What does this spirit wanna do with us?
It's angry. When Debbie played...
she woke up something up in her house.
Okay?
Pete, please, I need your help.
I think that's where Debbie found it.
Laine, you alright?
- Laine.
- I'm coming!
Pete.
Pete, grab this.
It's heavy.
Okay.
Laine!
Hey, this is the family.
For some reason, they're still
connected to the house.
From the look of these photos, I'd
say this is the late '40s, the early '50s.
Is there a way to get any records?
I don't know, property archives or something?
I can try.
We need to find out who they are.
Laine, you should come look at this.
I found this old article.
Doris Zander.
D.Z., D.Z., this is-this is her.
Pete, what's that.
Doris Zander.
She used to live in Debbie's
house, with her mother.
D.Z. was a missing girl.
They never found her.
They suspected the mother had something
to do with her disappearance.
So who is the other girl
in the pictures with them?
Doris had a sister.
She might still be alive.
May I help you?
I'm here for visiting hours.
Thank you.
They told me my niece was here to visit.
I don't have a niece.
My name is Laine.
I'm here to ask about your sister, Doris.
Oh, Doris.
My best friend, Debbie, lived in you old house.
She's not alive any more.
And this gonna sound really strange, but...
But...
I think I know why.
I believe there's a presence in that house.
I wouldn't be surprised if there's more than one.
I found pictures of you and your sister..
You found pictures?
You found my family photos?
Yeah, I can bring them to you,
or send them, if you like.
Please bring them.
I haven't seen my sister's
face... in a very long time.
At least, not her real face.
I believe I saw her, me and
my friends, and her lips....
they were stitched shut.
Mother did that to her.
My mother practiced mediumship.
And if practice makes perfect, let me tell you,
she was pretty damn good,
depending on your point of view.
She conducted seances, she
used spirit boards, anything.
A bit reckless, actually.
Doris loved my mother. She wanted to help.
She was fascinated by it all.
And when the seances got bigger and
my mother really made connections...
she needed a vessel, a
vessel to give them a voice.
Who?
The spirits.
She used Doris.
And then something went wrong with mother.
Chasing the dead and living in all
those shadows, something snapped.
She couldn't turn it off, she
couldnt break the connection.
Mother was consumed by them.
She was insane.
So she did that to Doris.
To her lips.
To stop them from talking.
And then Doris went missing.
Missing.
She never left the house, did she?
No.
No, she didn't.
Mother wasn't herself.
She killed Doris.
And after that, I did what I
needed to do to stop mother.
That's why I'm here.
But that doesn't mean mother is gone.
- How did you see her?
- What?
You said you saw her.
You said you saw her lips.
How did you see her?
You wouldn't have been able
to see her, not unless...
Look, I just wanna stop whatever it is
that is happening, my friends are dying.
No, no, you, you-you opened up a
channel, you-you made a connection.
With what?
- A spirit board, I bet?
- Yeah.
You played in a graveyard.
And now she's awake, again.
Uh, um.
Mother, too.
- And if you could see them...
- Just through the planchette.
Not for long.
They're getting stronger.
The points of connection, in your
case, it's the body and the board.
The link is between them. The energy is growing.
And it is hard to stop.
Mother used to have a secret room.
She sealed it up, after
Doris, down in the basement.
Don't go alone. Mother will try to stop you.
What do I have to do?
You need to cut the stitches from her mouth.
And if it works...
you have to pray that Doris can deal with mother.
Supposed to be somewhere, here.
Pete, grab this.
This is crazy, Laine.
We should just leave, we shouldn't be here.
What?
The shadow.
Trevor!
Trevor.
Pete.
Trevor, Pete!
Laine.
Keep going.
Trevor, I need your help.
- Laine!
- Stay there, I found her.
No, no, no, not now.
Come on. Stop. Come on!
Come on.
No.
- Are you guys okay?
- Yeah.
Where's Laine?
Okay, so our feature sells... I hope
we look back on this and... um...
No, it's so good.
Okay, turn around, what does
it look like in the back?
Hold on, let me see.
- You look so beautiful.
- I know.
- Thanks..
- Oh, my babies, look at my angels.
I miss you, Debbie...
all the time.
Debbie?
Call me ASAP. Something happened to Pete.
Ms. Zander.
My tenacious little niece.
I did everything you said.
We found the body, I cut the
stitches, she sent mother away,
but it didn't work, why didn't it work?
Mother must have come back, because my
friend Pete, another friend, is dead.
She's free.
You lied to me.
Your mother didn't try to hurt us.
She tried to stop us.
Your mother wasn't the one that was evil.
- It was...
- I told her...
that I would help her.
I heard the voices, too.
They tell you...
the most wonderful... awful things.
You're gonna hear them too, little girl.
You'll hear them soon enough, because
she's coming to get you, too.
I always told her, because... I told her.
I always told her.
She's gonna be nice to me.
I was gonna help her.
And now, she's gonna be nice to me.
She's gonna keep her promises.
No! No!
You have to break the connection,
or it will keep coming back for you.
- I'll burn the board.
- That won't be enough.
A spirit this strong could bring it back.
A connection, once made, to a
spirit, is very difficult to break.
The board is just the conduit.
You have to sever the connection on both sides.
- How?
- Your connection...
is through the board and that little girl's body.
The spirit lives through both of them,
so you must destroy them both.
- What? Destroy the body?
- And the board.
And you must hurry.
I'll call Trevor.
Thank you.
- Trevor?
- Sarah?
We're back here.
Wait up.
Sarah?
Laine?
Trevor's already here.
Trevor?
Where is he?
No!
Laine, what do we do?
Laine!
Go get the board.
- I need the body, too.
- Let's burn this damn thing... alright?
- Laine!
- Sarah!
Sarah!
Hey!
As friends we've gathered, hearts are true.
Spirits near, we call to you.
Doris, I'm playing alone, you have to play.
Hey.
- Feeling any better?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I-I guess so.
I just...
I miss them... all the time...
Yeah, me, too.
I guess you never really feel
like you could say goodbye.
Hmmm...
Maybe that's okay.
Maybe there are no "goodbyes".
Not really.
I keep wondering about that night.
That poor little girl.
All of those dark spirits that were in her.
Where do you think they went?