[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Woman screaming ]
>> No!
[ Birds cawing ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Woman screams ]
>> Ahhhhhh!
Ahhhhhh!
>> [ Grunts ]
>> Ahhhhh!
[ Both laugh ]
[ Chuckling ] No.
>> Do you see that?
>> Hmm?
>> That building over there.
>> It's just some old factory.
>> Oh! We should check it out.
>> Are you crazy?
You want to go inthere?
>> Come on. It could be cool.
Let's just go inside for a few
minutes.
[ Door creaking ]
Oh! Cool!
>> Okay. We've seen it.
Let's go.
>> We just got here.
>> Yeah, and I think we should
get out before someone shows up.
>> Give me a break, Josh.
This place has probably been
abandoned for years.
[ Crickets chirping ]
I wonder what they made here?
>> Who cares what they made
here, alyson?
This place is a death trap!
>> What's your problem?!
>> Nothing.
I just -- I just don't think
this is a good idea.
That's all.
>> [ Mockingly ] Are you scared?
>> No!
>> Then stop being such a pussy.
>> [ Sighs ]
>> [ Gasps ]
God! This is place is amazing!
I wish I'd brought my camera.
>> Haven't we seen enough?
>> I'm not leaving until I see
every room.
>> Alyson...
>> What?
>> I just heard something.
>> I didn't.
>> It came from over there.
It sounded like footsteps.
>> If you're trying to get me to
leave, it's not working.
>> I think we should go.
>> You're really scared, aren't
you?
You're kind of cute when you're
scared.
>> We should go.
>> Kind of turns me on.
>> Ooh. [ Grunts ]
Are you crazy?!
You want to do thishere?!
>> Why not?
No one's gonna bother us.
>> [ Moans ]
[ Both moaning ]
[ Door creaking ]
[ Moaning continues ]
[ Metallic creaking ]
[ Gasps ] Whoa! Whoa!
>> What the fuck?!
>> I saw something!
>> Gimme a break!
There's no one else here!
>> I saw something right there!
>> Whatever.
>> [ Panting ]
I'm not making this up!
>> You are so full of shit.
>> I really saw someth-- where
are you going?
>> I'm gonna have a smoke.
>> I'm coming with you.
>> No. Don't.
>> But, alyson --
>> I just want to be alone for a
minute, okay?
I'll be right back and then we
can leave, all right?
>> Sure.
[ Crickets chirping ]
>> [ Sighs ]
[ Lighter clicks ]
[ Jar thuds ]
[ Metallic scraping ]
[ Gasps ]
>> Alyson?
Alyson!
Alyson?!
Jesus.
Oh, my God!
Alyson!
[ Flesh tearing ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Gasps ]
>> [ Weakly ] No.
[ Ripping continues ]
No! No! No!
Ahhhh!
>> [ Gurgling ]
>> No! No!
No! No!
Aaaahhh!
>> [ Coughing, gagging ]
>> Aaaahhh! Ahhhh!
Aaaaahhhh!
Aaaahhhhh!
No! Aaaahhh!
Aaaahhh!
No!
>> Congratulations, Rachel!
You survived your first year of
college.
>> [ Chuckles ]
We should do something to
celebrate, you know?
>> Yeah. Ideas?
Get wasted? Stir up some shit?
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> Wanna come along?
>> Now I know why my parents
always thought you were such a
bad influence.
>> Yeah.
They weren't too thrilled when
they found out we were going to
the same school.
>> No.
>> Rachel! Hey, what's up?
>> Hi, Derek.
>> Louisa.
>> Hello.
>> You all done with classes?
>> [ Chuckling ] Yeah.
That physics exam was a killer.
>> Yeah. Tell me about it.
I was thinking, uh...Me and you
can...Do something tonight.
Yeah?
>> Yeah. [ Chuckles ]
>> I can pick you up around
7:00?
What do you say?
Is tha--
>> sorry, frat boy.
We've got plans.
>> You know, rach, can I --
can I talk to you for a second?
Alone?
>> Yeah.
>> Hey, Louisa.
Can I bum a smoke off you?
>> Get lost, Troy.
>> [ Scoffs ]
Come on.
I'll buy you a pack later.
>> "Later"?
>> Tonight.
>> [ Scoffs ] "Tonight"?
You think I wanna be hanging out
with your lame ass tonight?
>> I don't care what they say
about you, Louisa.
I know you like guys.
Oh, hey.
I don't want no trouble.
>> Too late,pendejo.
>> Nice knife you got there.
>> Yeah, and it's sharp, too.
Wanna touch it?
Now...Who says I don't like
guys?
>> Hey, why are you still
hanging around with Louisa,
anyways?
Huh?
I mean...Everyone knows she's
going nowhere.
>> Derek, she's my best friend.
You know, I mean, we -- we grew
up together.
>> I know. Look.
But you're not a little kid
anymore.
You know, you need to start
making yourowndecisions.
>> [ Sighs ]
Just...Don't pressure me, all
right?
>> Just say you'll come with me.
>> [ Scoffs ]
I'll call you later, okay?
All right?
>> Yeah, we both know whatthat
means.
>> Oh, come on, Derek.
Don't get possessive.
>> I'm not being poss--
>> we're just dating!
Okay?
>> All right.
[ Car horn honking ]
[ Woman shouting ]
>> [ Laughing ]
School is out forever! Whoo-hoo!
>> Whoo! Damn right!
We're gonna get down tonight!
>> You kids crazy or what?
>> Oh, yeah. Okay.
We'recrazy? Look at you!
What are you still doing here?
>> Listen up, y'all.
We're having a party at my house
tonight.
My parents are out of town for
the whole weekend.
The whole place is ours!
Today, it's free rides home for
everybody!
>> Whoo!
>> Sounds like a plan.
What do you say, Rachel?
>> We'll see.
>> Let's do it!
>> I'm all right, Francis.
Hey, do you need a ride?
What about you, homegirl?
You want a ride?
>> Can I smoke in your car?
>> Sure thing.
But that ain't all we're gonna
be smoking!
[ Laughter ]
>> I told you to get lost.
>> Hey. I need a ride, too.
>> Don't worry, Troy.
We ain't gonna be playing no
megadeth in here, a'ight?
>> Don't worry. I'm cool.
>> Nah.
You anything but cool, my man,
but get your heavy-metal ass in
the car so we can be on our way.
>> Whoo! [ Laughs ]
[ Engine revs ]
>> Shit!
>> What's wrong?
>> My folks. They're still here.
>> Ohh.
>> Let me go scope this out.
>> Here.
Put this Anthrax tape in.
>> Dude, give it a rest!
Don't make me kick you out of
the fucking car.
>> We're fucked.
They changed their tickets to
next month.
>> Shit!
>> Dude, that sucks!
>> So now what are we gonna do?
>> I don't know.
We'll figure something out.
Let's just get out here.
>> Nice move, man.
>> How was I supposed to know?
If you're so smart, Louisa, why
don'tyoucome up with
something?
>> We're waiting to hear it.
>> Okay.
I got an idea.
So you know the old factory on
the edge of town?
>> Yeah.
>> It's been a long time since
I've been there, but it's
probably still around unless the
city tore it down.
>> [ Sarcastically ] Yeah.
That sounds terrific.
>> No. I'm serious.
It's a really cool place.
It's been abandoned for years.
>> W-wait. An abandoned factory?
>> Uh...No way.
>> Don't worry.
I've been there millions of
times.
I used to hang there when I was
a teenager.
>> Sounds cool to me.
>> Oh. Wait. Come on, guys.
You guys don't really wanna
party in some condemned
building.
>> Gimme a break, dude.
You're such a pussy.
>> Yeah, really.
You got a better idea?
>> I'm with Louisa...Long as
it's private, okay?
We're gonna have our own little
private party -- someplace where
we won't be disturbed.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> The whole place is isolated.
>> Okay, so there are a lot of
rooms there, right?
'Cause you know me and Francis
are gonna be needing some
privacy.
[ Both chuckle ]
>> Girl, you got a dirty mind.
>> You love it, don't you?
>> There's plenty of room for
everybody, and we can do
whatever we want.
>> Whoo-wee!
Now, that's what I'm talking
about.
>> Me, too.
>> [ Laughs ]
>> Oh, don't even tell me you're
going along with this.
>> What, Derek?
It could be fun.
>> Ugh.
>> Hey!
And who invited you, anyway?
>> Oh, I'll be there. Yeah.
Just to make sure nothing
happens to Rachel.
>> Good deal.
You and Troy can bring the beer.
And I'll stay here and take care
of the girls.
Right, girls?
[ Laughs ]
>> So, what, are we on?
6:00? Huh?
In front of the old factory.
It's right down on Duncan road.
You can't miss it.
>> Hey. Let's do it.
[ Dogs barking ]
>> No!
[ Barking continues ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Mumbling ]
[ Coughs ]
Ugh.
I told him he got the day all to
himself, but he had to give me a
hard time, so this is what
happened...
[ Groans ]
You're a fuck-up!
Don't...
Do you really want...
Kiss my ass.
[ Grunts ]
[ Belches ]
[ Mumbling, chuckling ]
I told him!
It's not my fault!
The guy poured the drink.
Shit!
[ Springs creaking ]
[ Thud ]
Who's there?
Who's there?!
[ Mumbling ]
Damn dog. I don't know!
[ Mumbling ] ...Stupid.
>> You -- you have to help me!
>> What happened to you?!
>> She killed Josh!
Oh, my God!
She's gonna kill us all!
[ Hyperventilating ]
Please!
We have to get out of here
before she comes back!
>> She? Who's she? Who? Who?
>> She's gonna kill you, too,
if we don't get out of here!
>> I live alone.
There's nobody here.
>> Please! Please!
We have to go now!
We have to go!
>> Aah!
>> No! No!
Aaaahhhh!
Aaaahhh! No!
[ Heartbeat thumping ]
[ Metallic clanking ]
[ Clanking continues ]
>> [ Hisses ]
>> Aaaahhhhh!
[ Gnawing, flesh tearing ]
[ Vehicle approaches ]
>> Well, this must be the place.
>> Yeah.
Geez! What a dump!
>> Want one?
>> Nah. No thanks.
I don't smoke.
>> That's right.
You wouldn't want to let down
the team.
[ Bottles clink ]
>> Hey, where's Francis?
[ Vehicle approaches ]
>> Whoo!
[Dance music plays]
>> Whoo! [ Laughs ]
You thought we'd hit you, didn't
you?
[ Laughs ]
>> Hi.
>> Wow. You look...Great.
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> Hey, girls.
You all ready to party?
>>Muy bonita señorita.
>> Wow.
>> Thank you.
>> Get your hands off me,
Francis.
>> Chill, girl. Lighten up.
These here aremyladies.
>> You can have them.
>> Hey!
>> Yeah. Right.
>> All right. All right.
Let's see it. Let's see it.
>> Cheapest thing they had.
>> Aw, dude.
>> Dang.
Leave it to two white boys to
bring the beer.
Well, good thing I brought my
own shit.
>> Yep.
>> Well, we got the tools.
That ain't all we got.
Leticia?
>> Oh, shit!
[ Cheering ]
Now that's the kind of shiti'm
talking about.
>> This place looks kind of
freaky, don't you think?
Look, rach, ain't nothin' gonna
happen while I'm around, all
right?
>> Ohh. Give me a break.
>> Hey.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's party!
I thought you said this place
was wide open.
>> How was I supposed to know it
was gonna be locked up?
Last time I was here, it --
>> yeah. When was that?
>> It must've been at least
eight years.
>> Great.Nowyou tell us.
Hey, I didn't see you come up
with any bright ideas.
>> I knew I shouldn't have gone
with some stupid, fucking
factory.
[ Locks clanking ]
[ Chains rattling ]
Oh, shit! [ Chuckles ]
That was easy!
Sorry, Louisa. [ Chuckles ]
Let's party, people! Let's go!
Man, this party's about to be
on, y'all.
[ Chuckles ]
>> I love this place.
>> Hey! Here's a door.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
We can go in from there.
>> All right.
Derek, why don't you do the
honors of, you know, getting
the door open for us?
>> Go for it!
>> Come on, bad boy!
Show us what you got!
>> Whoo!
[ Clatter ]
[ Laughter ]
[ Scraping ]
>> All right!
All right!
Here we go, y'all!
>> It's dark.
>> Yeah, I'm assuming there's no
electricity in this place, huh?
>> What do you think?
>> Don't worry about it.
That's why I brought these.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Get out.
>> Let's party, people.
The party's officially underway!
[ Chuckles ]
>> Time to party.
[ Creaking ]
[ Loud thud, creaking ]
>> [ Coughs ]
Oh...My g--
so this is party central, huh?
>> This is it!
>> Oh.
You sure do know how to pick
'em, Louisa.
>> Fuck you.
>> I don't know about you guys.
I think a little bit of a smoke
is in order.
Who's coming with me?
>> Are you kidding?!
Baby, this place is fucking
spooky.
>> Geez, leticia!
We've been here for five
seconds!
You're already complaining!
>> If you wanna, I'll give you
guys a little tour.
>> Cool.
What about the wonderbread twins
there?
>> Why not?
>> Troy, guess that leaves you
here to watch our stuff.
>> You kidding me?
I'm not fucking staying here by
myself!
>> What's the matter?
You scared? Scared?
>> Oooooooh!
>> You scared? You scared?
>> Just give me the flashlight.
>> All right, guys. Come on.
Let's go. Follow me.
>> Come on, baby.
>> Let's go.
[ Crickets chirping ]
>> What'd you say this place
used to be?
>> I'm not sure.
I-it's...Been boarded up for a
while.
>> Oh, shit! Damn it!
>> What's up, girl?
>> I stepped in something.
>> Watch where you walk.
There's all sorts of broken
glass and shit in here.
>>Nowyou tell me.
>> It's too late now, girl.
There's no turning back.
>> You doing okay?
>> Yeah.
Just...Stay close to me, okay?
>> I'm right behind you.
>> Aaahhhhh!
>> Jesus, girl!
>> What?!
>> Why?!
>> What's up?!
>> I just walked into a
spider web.
>> Jesus!
I wouldn't be surprised.
There's spider webs all over
this place.
>> Hey, Louisa, any other
surprises?
>> We'll see.
[ Creaking ]
>> Shit.
[ Clatter ]
>> Looks like some kind of a
storage room.
>> Yeah.
People have been dumping their
junk here for years.
Once in a while, you'll find a
bum camped out.
>> Let's just hope we don't run
into anybody tonight.
>> Yeah.
'Cause this is a private party.
[ Laughs ]
>> Troy, what are you doing?
>> Just looking around.
>> Well, there's not much to see
in here.
>> Seriously, is the whole place
like this?
>> No. There's other rooms.
>> Let's check 'em out.
>> Yeah.
>> But this is getting old real
fast.
>> Yeah.
>> Come on, guys. Follow me.
>> Jesus.
[ Glass clinking ]
>> Hey! Wait up!
[ Thud ]
>> It's so dark in here.
It's like these hallways go on
forever.
Seems like it'd be easy to get
lost.
>> Stick with me.
You'll be fine.
>> Now, how big is this place?
>> Don't know.
I mean, I really never explored
this building.
>> Well, I think we've seen
enough.
I think we should head back.
>> Come on, man.
Where's your sense of adventure?
We gotta check out some more
rooms.
Hey, Louisa!
We need something big.
You know, somewhere we can set
up our shit.
>> I hear you.
I think there's...A lounge down
this way.
>> A lounge?
>> Yeah, a lounge.
You know -- a big room with old
sofas and a TV.
I guess it was something like
a...A workers' lounge or
something.
>> Sounds good to me.
Let's roll.
>> I-I think it's down this way.
Follow me.
Shit.
>> What?
>> Must be further down the
hall.
>> This ain't no...Lounge.
This is more like an office.
>> Yeah.
Oh, well. Let's get out of here.
>> No, wait. This is cool.
>> Don't worry.
Take your time.
We'll catch you later.
>> Dude, put that shit away.
Come on. Let's go.
>> Oh, God.
Francis, what are you doing?
>> Making myself more
comfortable.
>> Be careful.
>> Don't worry.
Everything's under control here.
>> "Dyson chemical."
>> Say what?
[ Thud ]
>> [ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
>> Hey.
Since I'm up, guys, let's get
out of here.
This place is crazy.
That's some bullshit.
>> Are you okay?
>> Yeah.
[ Papers crinkle ]
Shit.
Some light would be great, man.
>> Yeah.
>> I think...I can take care of
hey, Troy.
Give me your flashlight.
>> What are you doing?
>> Look, I'm gonna go find the
breaker box, all right?
I'm sure there's...Gotta be one
around here somewhere.
>> Derek, don't!
Just...
>> Don't worry, rach.
Look, I'll be --
>> don't say it, man!
>> Baby!
>> Don't worry.
I'll be right back.
[ Light laughter ]
>> Derek!
[ Sighs ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Thud, creaking ]
[ Scraping ]
>> Fuck!
[ Crash ]
>> What's taking him so long?
[ Sighs ]
>> Who knows?
Maybe he chickened out and went
home.
[ Laughs ]
>> I knew I shouldn't have
invited him.
>> Hey, come on, you guys.
He could be hurt.
We should go look for him.
>> Go ahead.
You know, maybe that's what he
wants you to do.
>> What are you talking about?
>> [ Chuckling ] Come on,
Rachel.
You know the only reason why
Derek came here is 'cause he
wants to fuck you.
>> Thanks, Louisa.
>> Hey.
I-I'm just trying to look out
for you.
Maybe someday you'll appreciate
>> tonight, I'll look out for
myself, all right?!
>> Chill out, girls!
>> God!
>> This ain't supposed to be no
catfight.
This is a party.
What happened?
>> Well, hell, there's an
electric room right down the
hallway, but there ain't no
juice going to it.
>> Derek, what happened to your
head?
>> Oh, it's all right.
You know, I just dropped my
flashlight and hit a table.
>> I told you, man.
You gotta be careful 'round
here.
>> Well, hell, if it wasn't for
your stupid noises...
>> What noises?
>> Oh, come on, Francis.
Man, you know exactly what I'm
talking about.
I heard you trying to spook me
in the hallway.
>> I've been here the whole
time!
>> Yeah!
>> Yeah. Sure.
>> No, he's telling the truth.
None of us have left this room.
>> Look, enough of this spooky
shit.
Look, y'all, we got music, and
we got beer.
So let's party.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Whoo! Sounds like a plan!
[ Click ]
[Dance music plays]
>> Whoo-hoo!
>> That's my girl!
Go ahead and put it on me, girl.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Heads up!
>> It's okay.
>> Come on, Rachel.
>> Her parents want her to stay
clean, sober, and a virgin.
>> Oh, leave her alone, Louisa.
Geez.
>> More for me.
[Dance music continues]
[ Bottle opens ]
[ Snapping ]
>> Come on.
>> Mmm.
>> Oh!
[ Laughter ]
>> You want to?
>> Do you feel okay?
>> I'm fine. Come on.
>> Are you sure?
>> Yeah. Absolutely.
>> Okay. [ Chuckles ]
[ Snapping continues ]
>> Whoo!
>> Don't...Even...Think about
>> [ groans ]
[ Lighter clicks ]
Want one?
>> We can share.
>> You guys getting busy over
there or what?
[ Chuckles ]
>> Fuck you, Francis.
>> Got to hand it to you,
Louisa.
This place is not bad.
>> Yeah.
How'd you say you found this
place?
>> I don't know.
Just stumbled into it one day.
Just thought it'd be a cool
place to hang out.
>> When was that?
>> Why are you so interested?
>> Don't worry about it.
He's just trying to have a
little conversation.
You know, get things going.
>> Don't even bother, Troy.
She's not into guys.
[ Laughter ]
>> No, no, no.
No, I'm asking 'cause I think I
know where we are.
>> Yeah, me, too.
Some broken-down old factory.
>> Yeah, a factory.
Factory on the edge of town.
I thought it sounded familiar
when you mentioned it before,
Louisa.
[ Boom box clicks, music stops ]
But then whenever I saw the
paperwork in that office, I was
sure.
>> Sure about what?
>> The paperwork all said "Dyson
chemical."
Sound familiar?
>> Wait. Dyson?
[ Papers crinkle ]
Wait. Yeah.
It -- they had a factory around
here.
They had...Like, some kind of
accident there -- a radiation
spill or something.
>> This is it, guys.
>> Okay. Wait. Hold on a second.
Do you mean to tell me that we
are sitting in the middle of a
toxic waste dump right now?
>> Worse.
People were murdered here.
>> Murdered?!
>> What?
>> Louisa!
Did you know about this shit?
>> [ Scoffs ]
First time I'm hearing it.
>> About 15 years ago, Dyson
used to own this building.
They were manufacturing
experimental drugs.
They told the public it was
pharmaceuticals, but they were
actually developing biological
weapons -- real top-secret
stuff.
One of the workers got
contaminated and got so sick she
had to quit.
Dyson denied responsibility, of
course.
It was a terrible scandal.
But not as terrible as what
happened next.
A few days after the scandal
hit, somebody or something
walked right into Dyson chemical
and killed everybody there.
We're talking mass murder here.
24 people, all brutally
butchered.
And they never found the killer.
The police for weeks tried to
find some kind of evidence, but
all they found were blood and
bodies.
And their only possible suspect
was the worker who had been
contaminated, but she had a
solid alibi.
>> What was that?
>> She was dead.
She died a few days before the
massacre, apparently of some
strange disease.
So the case was closed, Dyson
left town, and the factory was
sealed shut.
Never opened again.
>> Wait a second.
I never heard about any
killings.
It was just a...Chemical spill
or something.
>> That's what they told the
public.
They paid the press off pretty
good not to release the truth.
>> Then how come you know all
about it?
>> My friend's Uncle was one of
the cops at the crime scene.
He said it was like hell on
earth.
>> All right, Troy.
Tha-- [ Chuckles ]
That's enough, man.
>> But it's true.
>> You're just trying to scare
that's what I think.
>> Yeah. Seriously.
And you know what?
You're doing a pretty damn good
job, too.
>> Don't worry about that, baby.
>> Troy's just trying to creep
us out.
>> Guys, I'm not making this up.
You can check the papers if you
don't believe me.
Ever since this factory shut
down, there have been all kinds
of accidental deaths and
disappearances around here.
>> So, what, you're saying that
this building is...Haunted?
>> Not haunted.
The killer could still be alive.
>> All right. All right.
All right.
Enough of this spooky-ass ghost
story shit.
>> Yeah.
>> Come on, baby.
We'll see y'all later.
>> Yeah. Let's go.
Bye!
>> Hey, maybe we should go find
a place for ourselves.
>> I-I think I'd rather stay
here, Derek.
I mean...This place is kind of
scary, you know?
>> Don't tell me you actually
believe that story?
>> Never know.
>> Well... [ sighs ]
Look, how about this?
Why don't we go take a tour of
this place?
Come on. Just you and me.
>> Derek, I don't know.
>> Come on, Rachel.
You actually think I'm gonna let
anything happen to you?
Come on.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Okay.
Let's go.
>> Have fun, kids.
[ Groans ]
Nothing else to do but get
wasted now.
Oh, shit!
We're fucking dry, man!
>> Any requests?
>> Why?
You gonna go do a beer run?
>> Maybe.
>> You know, I might as well
leave, too, and maybe I won't
come back.
This fucking party was over
before it even started.
>> Do you want anything or not?
>> Sure.
Get some smokes, too!
[ Both laughing ]
>> Okay, I know what you're
thinking right now, and the
answer is "no fucking way."
>> Come on, baby.
A bed is a bed, right?
[ Chuckles ]
>> Forget it, Francis.
Mnh-mnh.
>> Hey.
It's still got spring.
[ Chuckles ]
Besides...[ Chuckles ]
It beats the floor.
>> Somebody probably died in
that bed.
>> What's the matter?
Troy still got you spooked?
>> All right.
Maybe we should just go, okay?
>> Hey, hey, hey.
Wait, baby.
>> What?
>> This is Francis you talking
you know Francis ain't gonna let
nothin' happen to you.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Both laugh ]
>> Oh! Oh!
>> [ Moans ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Both moaning ]
>> I've been waiting all night
to be alone with you.
>> Me too.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Aah!
>> Did you hear that?
>> Oh.
>> Yeah.
Come here.
>> Aah!
[ Woman laughs ]
[ Woman moaning ]
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> What?
Shh! Shh!
[ Moaning continues ]
[ Door creaking ]
>> I wonder if it's true?
>> What?
>> Troy's story.
>> Come on, rach.
It's Troy.
Nah, he gets off on that kind of
thing.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know.
You want to keep exploring?
>> No [Chuckles] actually, I
was...I was thinking we would
stay here.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Okay.
Sounds...Good.
>> Mm.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Wh-what's wrong?
>> [ Chuckles ]
Nothing.
[ Chuckles ]
I just...Don't want to rush
things right now...You know?
>> All right.
That's...That's fine.
We don't have to rush into it.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's play a game.
>> S-sure.
[ Both laugh ]
What do you got in mind?
>> Uh, come here.
You sit here.
And I sit here.
>> All right, and then what do
we do?
>> Then...We ask questions.
>> What kind of questions?
>> Anything you want.
>> All right.
Well, who's first?
I guess it's your turn.
[ Both laugh ]
Rachel?
>> I'm thinking.
[ Chuckles ]
Hold on.
Okay.
When was the first time you saw
[ chuckles ]
>> First semester.
You were sitting in front of me
in English class.
You were in Skinner's class?
>> You were, uh, always talking
with Louisa.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yep.
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> I promised myself that one
day I'd go out with you.
>> Why didn't you say anything?
>> I don't know.
Too shy, I guess.
>> Yeah, right.
I see -- Derek Redding shy.
>> Yeah...
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> ...go ahead and laugh.
>> [ Laughing ] I'm not.
I think it's cute.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay.
Your turn.
Ask me something.
>> I'm hearing things, man.
[ Click ]
Shit!
[ Squeals ]
[ Thud ]
Whoa!
>> God!
[ Laughs ]
That was fast.
Did you get my smokes?
>> I just saw -- oh, my God.
>> You didn't get my smokes, did
you?
>> There's a guy -- a dead guy!
>> Come on. Give it a rest.
>> I'm serious, Louisa.
I just saw him.
Somebody killed him, and then he
tried to kill me.
[ Thudding ]
>> Listen, if you're trying to
scare me, it ain't working.
I'm not Rachel or leticia.
>> If I show you, will you
believe me?
>> All right.
Troy...Come in here.
Very funny.
>> No. No.
I'm telling you, he was right
here in this chair.
>> Maybe he got up and walked
away.
>> No, but he was right here!
I'm not making this up.
You gotta believe me, Louisa.
Louisa?
Aw, shit.
>> Wah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
>> God damn it, Louisa!
>> Gotcha!
Aw, I thought you like scary
shit, man.
>> Man, you guys can do whatever
you want.
I'm getting the fuck out of
here.
>> Troy.
Troy, I was just kidding.
Oh, fuck.
There go my fucking smokes.
>> How the fuck do I get out of
this place?
Aah!
Aaahhh! Aahh!
[ Coughs ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Groaning stops ]
>> [ Coughs ]
[ Sighs ]
>> [ Chuckles ]
>> You good.
>> Yeah.
But you're even better.
[ Chuckles ]
>> [ Clears throat ]
>> Whereyougoing?
You know, nature calls.
>> You know where the John is in
this place?
>> As far as I'm concerned, this
whole placeisa John.
[ Both laugh ]
>> Get out of here.
>> You need anything?
>> Um...Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
How 'bout a beer?
>> Okay. You got it.
If there's anything left.
>> There better be.
Shoot.
Oh! And, Francis...
Don't be gone too long, okay?
>> Don't you worry, baby.
I'll be right back.
>> [ Chuckles ]
Mm.
[ Man screams in distance ]
>> Francis?
Francis, is that you?
>> Did you hear that?
>> Yeah, it's probably just
Francis and leticia.
>> N-- I don't know, Derek.
It sounded like screaming,
like --
>> like I said -- Francis and
leticia.
[ Both laugh ]
Do you want me to check it out?
>> Unh-unh.
I want you to stay right here
with me.
>> Francis?
Francis?
Francis? Come on.
Where are you?
Aah!
Aaahhhh!
>> It's Francis!
>> Aaahhhhh!
>> It's Francis! It's Francis!
Shit. Wh--
[ smack ]
Shit.
>> You scared the shit out of
you didn't have to do that!
Go, go, go and get me my beer,
and don't be playing any more
tricks on me, all right?
And next time, I'm gonna hit you
where it hurts, okay?
>> Shit!
Girl, you must be crazy!
>> Oh, shit.
[ Rumbling ]
[ Gasps ]
Aah! Jesus, Francis!
Oh, God.
>> Jesus Christ, girl, what's
the rush?
>> Where's everybody?
>> I don't know.
Leticia and me -- is there
any more beer?
>> [ Sighs ]
We're -- something happened to
Troy.
>> You trippin' or what?
>> No, I'm serious.
I found his jacket covered in
blood.
>> What?
>> Look!
[ Breathing heavily ]
What?
I just got it out.
You know, just in case --
>> it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Just chill out with the knife
already.
>> Where's leticia?
>> She's down the hall.
>> You left her alone?
>> Francis?
Francis?
You know, you better have that
beer or you're in trouble.
Oh, okay, I get it.
So you want me to come out
there, right, so you can scare
me again?
Unh-unh.
I'm staying right here, okay?
If you want me, you can come and
get me.
>> Leticia?
I know we go...
Leticia?
[ Thudding ]
>> Oh, okay.
Real cute, Francis.
I mean, I ask you for a beer and
you bring her back?
God, you know, I told you I
don't do threesomes!
>> Well, forget about that.
Troy may have been...
We think something may have
happened to him.
>> What?
>> Listen, I found his jacket,
and there was blood on it.
>> All right.
Okay, if this is another one of
your jokes, Francis...
>> No.
>> It's true, baby.
I-I saw it.
>> Jesus.
I -- now what are we gonna do?
>> Well, the first thing we need
to do is find the others.
Do you know where Derek and
Rachel went?
>> No, I mean, we've been here
the whole time.
>> Okay, well, let's start
looking, then.
Come on.
The sooner we get everybody
together, the sooner we can get
out of here.
>> Let's go.
>> No.
I said "no."
>> Man, I don't -- you know
what, I don't get it.
I thought you wanted to.
>> Look...Wanting to make out
with you isn't the same as
wanting to have sex.
>> Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't know that --
>> look, it's okay.
Let's -- let's just not rush
things.
>> Fine.
>> Hey.
>> Oh, thank God.
You guys!
We've been looking all over for
you.
>> Louisa, what the hell are you
doing here?
Geez, we can't have a moment
together without you --
>> shut the fuck up, Derek.
Something happened to Troy.
We have to find him.
>> Well, wait a second.
How do you know?
>> [ Breathing heavily ]
I'll tell you on the way.
Let's go.
>> You think he's dead?
>> I don't know for sure, but
his jacket was full of blood.
>> Oh, my God.
Troy was right.
>> About what?
>> The killer.
Th-th-the guy who killed all
those people years ago.
You guys, he's still alive, and
he's still after us --
>> look, calm down, Rachel.
Look at this.
This is exactly what Troy wants
us to think.
I mean, Jesus, if the guy could
see us now, he would probably be
laughing his ass off.
[ Women scream ]
>> Shit!
Shit!
>> Oh, God!
>> Don't! Don't look!
Don't look! Don't look!
>> Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Who could have done this?
>> Who cares who did this?
Now what are we gonna do?
>> We're getting out of here
right now.
Louisa, you know this place.
Where's the exit?
>> I don't know about an exit,
but I'm sure we can find our way
back to the front entrance.
>> Well, whatever. Whatever.
Let's just move.
Which way is it?
This way. Come on.
>> Are you sure?
>> Yes. Come on. Believe me.
This is it, guys.
>> Let's go!
>> Go, go, go, go!
>> Shit!
Locked!
What are you talking about
"locked"?
>> Get out of the way.
[ Door banging ]
Shit! We're fucked!
That's not working, Francis.
We're locked in!
>> Well, we got to find another
way out.
>> I don't know of any other --
>> well, we have to look for it.
Francis, you and I need to try
and find another place to get
out of here.
>> What about us?
>> Louisa, look, just stay here
and take care of the girls.
>> What?!
>> No!
No, Francis, you -- no, you are
not going!
>> Babe, we got to find a way
out of here.
>> But I want to be with you,
baby.
>> Derek's right.
You got to stay here.
>> I don't want to.
I don't want to stay here alone.
Please?
>> Look, I'll be back, okay?
>> Don't leave me.
>> Be careful.
>> Francis.
Francis, come on. Let's go.
Come on, Francis!
>> Where the fuck are we?
>> Beats the hell out of me.
Man, there's got to be a window
around here somewhere.
Maybe we can crawl out.
>> I don't see no windows.
>> Well, there's got to be
another way out of here.
>> What's this?
[ Door creaking ]
Man, check this out.
>> Oh, shit.
Dude, maybe we should split up.
>> No, I don't know about that.
>> Listen, you go down this way,
and I'll go down here.
One of us is bound to find
something.
>> [ Chuckles ]
If you don't get killed first.
>> Listen, if you find
something, just call me, all
right?
Either way, be back here in
five.
If anything happens, just yell.
>> Don't worry. I will.
>> Let me out of here, you
mother...Fucker!
Aah!
>> Stop it!
>> I can't.
I fucking -- I can't take this
anymore!
I just can't take it!
You're making too much noise,
okay?
>> I don't care.
Anyhow, it's your fault we came
out here in the --
>> stop it!
Both of you!
Look, if we don't stick
together, none of are gonna make
it out of here.
[ Door creaking ]
>> Nothing in here.
What the fuck?
[ Flesh tearing ]
Aah!
>> Francis!
>> Aaaaaaah!
Come on, bitch!
Come on!
I got something for you.
Aaahhhhh!
Aaaahhhh! Aaaahh!
[ Flesh tearing ]
[ Screaming stops ]
>> Open the fucking door!
Francis!
[ Grunting ]
[ Blood squirts ]
Francis!
>> [ Hisses ]
[ Snarling ]
>> God, where are they?
>> Sit down, leticia.
>> No, you know what?
W-we can't just stand around
here, guys.
>> Look, it's all we can do
right now.
>> God, I wish they'd come back.
>> They will.
Look, we just have to wait.
>> I can't -- I just, you know,
I can't wait.
I can't wait anymore.
>> You've got to calm down.
>> Don't tell me to calm down,
Louisa, all right?
That is my boyfriend out there.
>> Derek.
>> What happened, Derek?
>> Where's Francis?
>> He's...Dead.
>> What?
>> No.
>> It killed him.
That is not true.
>> Look, I'm sorry.
>> You're lying!
You're lying!!
You're lying!
He's not -- he's...
>> Who killed him, Derek?
Did you see them?
>> Yeah, I saw it.
>> "It"? What do you mean "it"?
>> I don't know.
You know what?
It wasn't human, Louisa.
I don't know what it was.
It was just some kind of -- I
don't know -- a monster.
I don't know.
>> Come on.
You really expect me to believe
that?
>> Oh, come on!
I saw it rip his head off, all
right?
It was fucking eating him!
>> [ Sobbing ] Oh, my God.
>> What are we gonna do now?
>> We can't stay here.
That's for sure.
>> Why not?
>> Because if that thing shows
up, we'll be trapped!
>> Okay, so where do we go?
>> Okay, I-I've been thinking
that there's got to be another
way out of this place.
>> How?
>> The basement.
>> Basement?
I didn't hear anything about a
basement.
>> I've only been there once and
supposedly, there's some tunnels
in there that lead outside.
>> Aw, shit! You know what?
I really wish you would have
thought of this sooner, huh?
>> Well, I've never actually
been in the tunnels, but I knew
some kids that told me about it.
>> [ Crying ]
>> D-do you know how to get in?
>> The only way in is on the
other side of the building.
>> All right.
Look, let's do it, okay?
But, look, we have to stay close
together.
Derek, if we're gonna go out
there, we -- we got to be
prepared.
[ Clattering ]
Here.
Let's do it.
Here it is, guys.
>> I can't take this anymore.
I can't.
>> Look, calm down.
>> We're not gonna get out of
here --
>> calm down!
>> It's locked.
>> Again?
>> Aah!
Give me that crowbar.
>> Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
>> Oh, shit.
[ Thudding ]
Come on! Hurry up!
>> Aaahhh!
>> All right, get behind me,
Rachel!
>> [ Hisses ]
[ Crowbar clanks ]
>> Aah!
>> [ Hisses ]
>> Oh! Oh, my God!
Aaahhhh!
[ Banging ]
[ Screaming stops ]
>> Aah!
>> Are you all right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm all right. Go! Go!
Oh, my God!
>> Aah!
>> Oh, my God!
>> What the hell is going on
here?
>> They must have been here
before us.
>> Hey, where are those tunnels?
>> This way.
>> Come on!
>> Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on!
>> Aah.
>> [ Snarling ]
>> Oh, shit.
>> What?!
>> It's under all this crap.
>> You've got to be kidding me.
>> Does it look like I'm
kidding?!
[ Thud ]
>> Aaaah!
>> Are you sure it's behind
here?
>> I'm pretty sure.
>> Fuck!
All right, just start moving
this shit!
[ Clattering ]
Look at this shit!
>> Go!
>> [ Grunts ]
>> Back there!
>> [ Hisses and snarls ]
>> You guys, stop!
>> What?
>> Did you hear that?
[ Thudding ]
It's coming.
[ Stairs creaking ]
>> [ Hisses ]
>> What are you doing?!
>> I have to stop it.
>> Derek, don't!
That thing will kill you.
>> I have to try.
>> No.
>> Look, somebody's got to make
it out of here.
Promise me you'll make it.
Promise me.
>> I-I will.
No! Derek!
[ Crying ]
I can't.
>> We have to get out of here.
Now, help me.
[ Floorboards creaking ]
>> [ Snarling ]
>> [ Grunts ]
>> What?
I thought you said there's a
tunnel here?
>> There is.
At least, I thought there was.
>> Louisa.
[ Clank ]
Louisa.
>> What?
>> There is no tunnel.
>> What are you talking about?
>> Derek?!
No!
>> Aaaahhhhh!
>> Derek!
[ Flesh tears ]
>> [ Groans ]
[ Gasps ]
>> Aah!
Aaaah!
Aah!
>> [ Grunts ]
[ Smack ]
Aah! No! No!
[ Groaning ]
Aah!
>> Aah.
[ Groans ]
>> Oh, my God. Derek?!
Derek?!!
Derek, get up!
No! Oh, my God!
Aaaaah! Aaaaaaah!
Aah!
>> Going somewhere, Rachel?
>> Louisa.
>> [ Hisses and snarls ]
>> What are you doing?
>> Nowhere to go now.
>> Get out of my way!
Your crazy lunatic's gonna kill
us both!
>> No, she won't.
Will you, Alexa?
>> [ Hisses ]
>> She'll do whatever I say.
After all, I take care of her.
>> Take care of her?
What the hell is that thing?
Alexa's not a thing.
She's a person, just like you
and I.
>> It's not human.
>> [ Hisses ]
>> I mean, it's gonna kill us
both.
>> Alexa's my sister, Rachel!
That's my sister!
>> You're crazy!
Your sister died when you were
[ crying ] I remember.
>> That's just what we told
everybody.
>> [ Hisses ]
>> No, Alexa, stay back.
>> [ Snarls ]
>> Troy's story was true.
Dyson owned this building, and
Alexa worked for them as a
researched.
One day, she got exposed to
hazardous chemicals.
After that, she got more and
more sick.
At first, her mind went.
But then, after awhile, we
couldn't recognize her, either.
And we kept her at home as long
as we could.
And we tried to keep he sickness
a secret.
>> [ Snarling ]
>> But she got away.
We found her covered with blood,
and we knew what had happened.
And when the police showed up,
there was only one thing we
could do...
We told them she was dead.
She's lived here ever since.
>> How could you?
>> [ Hisses ]
>> Louisa, she killed all those
people!
>> It's not her fault she's like
this.
She didn't want to hurt anybody.
>> No!
>> They did this to her, Rachel!
All I can do now is try to keep
her alive while she gets better.
>> Better?
Louisa, she's not human.
She's not human!
>> I have to help her.
She needs blood to survive.
She needs human blood.
She'll die without it, Rachel.
>> [ Hisses ]
>> No, Alexa.
No! Stay back!
>> That's why you brought us
here?
You brought us here 'cause you
knew she was gonna kill all of
us and she was gonna take our
blood and...
>> It was perfect.
[ Laughs ]
Usually, nobody comes because
this place is so isolated.
And you guys wanted to party.
>> So now you're gonna kill me,
huh, Louisa?
>> She's my sister.
I'll do anything for her.
>> [ Hisses ]
>> Aah! No!
>> Get back, Alexa.
Stay back.
Stay back!
No! Not ye--
aah!
Ah! You bitch!
Stay back!
Stay back!!
Alexa, it's me -- Louisa!
>> [ Crying ] No!
>> [ Grunting ]
Aaahhhh!
>> Aah!
Aaah! Aaah!
No!
Aaaaaaaaah!
[ Groaning ]
[ Blood squirts ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Muffled scream ]
[ Gasps ]
>> How you feeling, Rachel?
Where am I?
>> You're at St. Joseph's
hospital.
You've been here for five days
now.
>> But...How did I get here?
>> You don't remember?
>> Last thing I remember...
I was...
I was running.
I was running, and I was trying
to get out of the factory.
>> They found you on a road,
near the old Dyson chemical
plant.
You were unconscious.
For a while there, we weren't
sure that you were gonna make
Rachel, this is
detective terrell.
He'd like to ask you a few
questions.
>> Hi, Rachel.
Glad you're back with us.
>> Did you, uh...Did you go to
the factory?
>> Yeah, we've been there.
>> My friends -- all my friends.
She killed them all.
>> Well, we found several
bodies, uh, but we haven't
identified all of them yet.
>> B-but wh-what about -- what
about Alexa?
>> Who?
>> Alex-- she's the one who
killed all those people.
She's a -- a monster.
>> Uh, maybe she needs some more
rest.
>> Yeah.
>> No, no, look, she -- she has
these long...Metal teeth,
like -- like -- like fangs.
A-a-and she had these long,
metal fingernails.
Look, she wasn't even human.
>> It's okay, Rachel.
Um...
Why don't you get some sleep,
and, uh, we'll talk more later.
>> Look, she's been living there
for years.
>> Don't worry about it, Rachel.
We're gonna find out who did
this.
>> But I know.
Wait.
How many bodies did you find?
>> Eight.
>> Rachel, I'm gonna step
outside.
If you need anything, just call
me.
>> "Eight"?
>> Aaahhhh!
>> Troy.
>> Aaahhhhh!
>> Francis.
>> Aaahhhhh! Aaahh!
Aaahhhhh!
>> Leticia.
>> [ Gasps ]
>> Derek.
>> Aaahhhh!
Aaahhhh! Aaah! Aaah!
>> Louisa.
Eight.
But...What about...?
She's still alive.
>> [ Snarling ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Metal music plays ]