Jacques, you are my guest today.
Yes.
You are a school teacher,
you like nature
you are a keen
talk-show viewer
and you collect Russian watches
from the 70's.
Yes, exactly.
You are 54 years old.
Yes, that is true.
- You are a widower.
- Yes.
Do you believe in god?
If you mean an old guy
with a beard
who lives
in the clouds... no.
Okay.
What are your goals in life?
To be happy.
That's the main thing.
Also I have a special project
that I'm quite keen on.
I would like to start
my own line of sports clothes.
Interesting.
Please tell us a little bit about
the dessert that you have chosen.
We are all very impatient
and very much listening.
Uh, yes, I have chosen
the strawberry Charlotte.
And tell us in a few words why you
have chosen the strawberry Charlotte.
Well, it is a very simple cake
and very easy to make. Um..
What the fuck?
And the ingredients
are very inexpensive
and they are not
so gross to touch
very well.
This is no good, cut.
Dennis, why do you keep
scratching yourself?
It's getting worse and worse!
What, what?
You've been scratching
yourself like a dog
for the last three days.
What's up?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just a few rashes,
it will go away.
Rashes from what?
Uh, you know, I thinks it's
an eczema breakout or something
but it's actually kind of all
over, it's itching like hell.
But you can't see it
on camera, can you?
We can see it on camera,
it's gross.
How do you expect
to make people want to cook?
You look like a leper!
I don't know, it's actually
probably the costume I think.
You know, Suzy changed the detergent
from what she normally uses so
I guess I have sensitive skin and I've
had a little bit of allergic reaction.
So, I don't know, that's all.
I have asked her to go back to
the old stuff and she said no
there you go, I don't know, I don't like
to tell, but that's what has happened.
Alright, listen, we're gonna to finish
like this for the rest of the day.
We don't really have
a choice, so just..
And go see a specialist.
don't stay like this.
Yeah, yeah, I promise,
I will do it.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
Put your head back on.
Got it. Yeah. I'm ready.
You know I was thinking
of something.
What if I grab your arms from
behind but really discreetly
as soon as I see you starting to
itch and then I can hold them
there and that'll help.
Yeah, yeah, Jacques!
You know, thanks a lot but, uh, you
just focus on being a guest alright.
This is complicated enough
as it is.
Okay, let's go again people
right away.
Denis, whenever you're ready.
Yeah, okay, I'm ready.
Alright, lets..
Okay.
So, the strawberry Charlotte..
What are those sticky things
in the tummy for, daddy?
Nothing at all.
That's why I'm takin'
it all out, honey.
I already told you about this.
It's the same
for all the animals.
The insides serve no purpose.
Yeah. Ah!
Reality! don't touch that,
it's disgusting.
Now go wash your hands
we're about to eat.
Okay.
You're a real pain!
I did not change detergents!
How many times
do I need to tell you?
You know I'm right,
don't think I'm an idiot.
It smells different. I noticed
the smell on the first day.
You're completely crazy,
you have a real problem!
Yeah, I have a problem, I'll show you.
I don't think you realize! Look. See?
Rashes all over my arms.
Rashes everywhere!
I mean, look! See! It itches so
much I can't sleep at night!
Look at what your shitty
detergent is doing to me!
Alright? I'm being eaten
all over! See?
But there's nothing at all.
What are you talking about?
There's nothing there!
Nothing there?
Look at this. You see?
I mean, all of my skin
is covered in bumps!
All that so you can save a couple
bucks on a pack of detergent.
And look at the result.
I can't even wear a t-shirt
anymore because of you!
Everything okay here?
What's the matter?
You know the matter is that
this bitch won't listen to me
and go back
to our old detergent!
This bitch?
Yeah, that's what I said,
yeah. Bitch!
Okay, listen to me, this
is going to be very simple.
From now on, you can wash your own
stupid costume, is that what you want?
Sure, yeah! Whatever, fine.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, good luck.
Okay fine,
I'll do my own laundry.
It's not a big deal.
Um, oh, yeah.
We got some letters for you.
Mainly complaints.
About what?
Well, about you scratching
yourself.
Apparently it doesn't look good
and the fans are not happy.
Okay, I get it.
I'll go and see a specialist.
Hey!
I was real careful not to film
your hands earlier.
And after a while I had
the idea to zoom in
on your face as much as possible
and it really worked. We couldn't
see you scratching yourself
all we would see was your head.
That's nice. But there
are three other cameras.
Forget it. It was a nice
thought anyway, but thanks.
Also, I wanted to ask.
You started off as an actor,
didn't you?
- Nope, not at all.
- No. Shit.
Wait. Why? What difference
does that make?
No, I was just thinking,
as I am about to make a movie..
I'm going to have loads of
little parts to fill so
as you came across great on
camera, close-ups, you know
I was thinking maybe
suggesting, but I guess not.
- Well, no.
- Okay. No problem.
There you go.
Yeah. See you
tomorrow then.
Why was there a videotape
in the hog?
What are you talkin'
about, darling?
Well, I saw a videotape come out earlier,
when daddy was emptying the insides.
Stop talking nonsense.
Come on, eat.
But it's true.
I saw it.
No.
Listen, there can't be videotapes
inside the tummy of animals, darling.
It simply is impossible.
Reality, my sweetie pie,
listen to me.
How could a hog
swallow a videotape?
It's much too big, it wouldn't
go down, it's just not possible!
Well maybe
that's what killed him.
He choked on the tape
and tried to swallow it
but it got stuck in his throat.
No, he died because
I shot him, honey.
And even if he did swallow the tape, it
would have been completely crushed up
by his chewing it, you see?
I mean, he wouldn't have
swallowed it in one piece.
Think about it!
Well, I don't know how
it's possible, but I saw it.
I'm not crazy!
I think you're just tired.
Come on, it's time
for you to go to bed.
Come with mommy.
Come on.
Think about it, honey.
After having dinner
with her parents
the little girl quietly
brushed her teeth
looking at herself in the mirror
thinking back on her day.
She put on her favorite pajamas
"got into her cozy, little bed
"convinced she had seen
that tape
"come out
of the tummy of the hog.
That night the little girl
had funny nightmares."
That's it.
- I like this book.
- I know.
It's time for you
to go to bed. It's late.
Goodnight.
I saw that tape.
Tell Zog he's wasting film.
He shoots too much.
He'll push us over budget.
I'll tell him.
Mr. Marshall says that you
must reduce your consumption
of film or else
you'll go over budget.
You tell him that it is very
tricky to film children.
Reality is only 7, it's the first
time she's been in a movie.
I have to adapt to her rhythms.
He says filming kids is tricky.
That's no excuse.
Why keep on filming such a crappy shot?
The kid's just lying in bed!
Why film her?
He is asking why the camera is still
rolling for such a crappy shot?
I was simply waiting
for her to fall asleep.
I think she was struggling to
fall asleep because of the lights
and the presence of the crew,
and it's not a crappy shot
it is a crucial moment.
She gently falls asleep
and her nightmare begins.
He was waiting for her to fall asleep.
Why?
She doesn't have to sleep!
It's a movie.
She can fake it.
That's what movies are!
It costs money to keep rolling, dammit!
Mr. Marshall, your
appointment is here.
Yes.
I'll see him when we're done.
Have him wait in my office.
Very good, sir.
Give him a fruit.
Certainly.
There you go.
She falls asleep. For real.
She falls asleep for real.
About time!
I'm all yours.
- How are you doing?
- Perfect.
How long's it been?
Ten years?
That's right!
You've hardly changed physically,
I dyed my hair, that's all.
- So?
- Yes!
You've brought me something to read.
Well... No.
I finally decided
to talk you through it because...
Reading makes it seem complicated.
Complicated?
What's it about, brain surgery?
No, no...
Anything but!
Good. Here.
Have a cigar.
No, thanks.
Do, please.
It's not my thing.
I'm not feeling my best, either.
don't be a jerk.
These little ones are tasty.
Mexican.
They dry them for four years!
This beauty cost megabucks.
Really, I don't like cigars.
Have a cigarette at least.
I keep them, for non-smokers.
don't be shy!
I'll light it for you, see?
- Thanks.
- There you go.
Aren't we more relaxed?
True.
So, your movie.
Tell me, when is it set?
It's set... In the present day.
Right now.
Okay.
Do you have a title?
Meaning what?
Waves, like "microwaves."
Okay. "Waves."
Whatever.
Carry on. It's set in the present.
Yes, smack in the present.
Stop, sorry. Give me that.
You smoke so badly, it's annoying.
- I'm not used to...
- It's no fun unless you do it right.
How about we talk outside?
Some fresh air?
Yes, it's rather hot in here.
Precisely. This room is poorly aired.
I'll be on the deck,
doing business with a young director.
No calls, please.
Come on.
Funny, you were the receptionist before.
Yes.
Now you're bringing me a project.
Isn't life amazing?
Give me a second.
Hey Zog!
Less film!
- What'd he say?
- He said, less film.
Oh, tell him to go fuck himself.
I'll film as much as I want.
He says, he will try!
We need to know
what's on the tape!
- Who's he?
- An ex-documentary maker.
I picked him out of the gutter.
He's a handful, but talented.
His movie is stunning.
He lets the camera roll too long,
but he's good.
It's hard to relax, standing up.
don't you think?
I don't know.
This is better.
I'm dying to hear what you've got.
Sit down.
- I'm dying to tell you.
- Go ahead.
- It's set in the present day.
- Yes!
Wait a minute.
Do you smell stale tobacco?
Probably because I smoked.
- Isn't it unpleasant?
- It's kind of smelly.
Makes me want to puke!
Okay, I'll shut up and listen.
I’m ready to go.
Let's go!
Right. So...
Like I said, it's set in the present,
contemporary, on earth.
Here's the idea.
We don't know why,
but TV sets suddenly get vicious.
Which TV sets?
All of them.
All?
All tvs, everywhere.
Every TV on earth?
Yes.
Okay, go on.
So...
People don't realize it, but...
The TV sets beam waves at them
that suck out their intelligence
day after day.
They get completely stupid.
The dumber they get,
the more TV they watch,
and the dumber they get, and so on.
Sci-Fi.
Right.
- That's it?
- No.
That's only part one.
After that,
when the waves have made
everyone on earth completely stupid,
the TV sets decide to wipe them out.
And this is where it gets exciting,
they start beaming waves that kill people.
Wow. The whole works.
Right. Everybody on earth dies.
There's nobody left. No survivors.
No hope.
"The end."
No hope? I like it.
Me too.
There's usually a ray of hope. Not here.
That's my idea.
Go back to the tvs.
How do they kill people?
It's a bit unclear.
It's similar to part one.
They beam very strong waves
that burn people up inside.
How do they react?
What do we see on the screen?
They bleed, intensely, all over.
It's sickening. Blood spewing
from their eyes, arms, chests...
Nice! I love it.
- Are they in pain?
- They're in pain. Agony.
I'm impressed. I love it.
But like I said before,
how do we see the pain?
Hold it!
Tell me indoors, okay?
We'll have a cigar.
Come on.
- I love it.
- You do?
- Really?
- Really.
You're not just being polite?
No, I mean it.
Shit! It's filthy!
- Roughly, this is it.
- Just a sec.
Send Daniel with a stain remover.
Something strong.
So, show me. Tell me.
That's roughly it.
- You draw like shit.
- It's a diagram.
The TV beams the waves
towards the person.
He dies because of the waves.
And then... He bleeds his guts out.
See?
Okay, I get it.
But look,
these wavy lines show us the beams.
Yes, it's beaming.
We can't show it on film.
You can't film invisible waves.
How will people get it?
Easy. We'll hear a humming,
like a microwave.
We'll dub it in post.
[Knock on door]
Okay.
Yes?
You asked for me, sir?
For the rug?
It's too late, buddy. I've
already cleaned it myself.
Please, shut the door,
I have an appointment.
I love it.
No kidding?
I really do.
It fills my head with pictures.
Tvs, waves, people bleeding,
no hope, Sci-Fi... I love it.
You couldn't make me happier.
I've been working on this for years.
Can we go back to the pain?
How do we see the pain
when they start spewing blood?
Tell me.
They groan, I think.
With pain.
How do they groan?
They groan, I think, with pain.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Do it for me.
What?
The groan.
Give me the feel of your film.
Well... I don't know...
Actually...
I haven't...
I don't know exactly...
What kind of groan it is.
To be honest, I didn't think about it.
It's a key detail.
I've been focusing on the plot, but...
You're right,
I should've thought about the groans.
Jason, I know you well enough
to give it to you straight.
I like your project.
I'm game to sign.
Okay. Wow!
I don't know what to say!
don't say, listen.
I'll sign, on one condition.
Find the groan.
It's key.
I want the best groan
in movie history.
Okay.
don't say, “okay.” I'm serious.
I want an Oscar for that groan.
Right.
Fuck the rest.
Do your thing with it,
simplify it, I don't care.
- Wow!
- I'll give you 48 hours.
Get to work.
Call me when you're ready.
If I like the groan, we'll sign.
You'll make your movie.
Is it a deal?
Yes.
Yes?
Are you to old person
that lives in house?
Yes.
Why should I give a shit?
And then what?
That's it.
That's when I woke up
I took out my notebook
and I wrote it all down
and to be honest with you, I don't
know what to think about it.
What bothers you
about this dream?
The military Jeep?
The bouquet of flowers?
Or is it that you're dressed
as a woman, tell me.
None of that.
It's just the presence
of an old man in my dreams.
I'm not used to dreaming about
old people.
I mean I never do that.
What does that mean?
It's really worrying me.
I don't think it means anything.
For me to be honest,
what worries me, Henri
is the length of your dream.
Really? The length?
Let's say it's not
really finished.
It's a very short dream.
You have got me used
to more depth.
Well, yeah. I just woke up
it's not my fault.
Why do you think you woke up?
In your opinion.
Try to stay focused, Henri.
Answer my question.
Why did you wake up?
I just woke up.
There's no reason.
Are you at least sure
you had this dream?
Think about what I just said.
I'll be back in a second.
Can you stop that moronic screaming?
I'm with a patient!
What's the idea?
I'm practicing for my film.
You're a nuisance! Go away!
For god's sake!
Henri, we still have 10 minutes.
I'm good. I think
we had enough for today.
I think, I bored you
enough as it is.
What are you talking about?
Sit down, will you?
We have to finish the session.
No. I'd rather go.
And I'll come back to you when I have
more finished dream for you next time.
I can tell you're not interested
in me at all today.
- Sorry.
- Are you busy today?
What's your schedule?
I have to work.
You mean, recording noises?
Not just noises.
There's more to it...
But whatever. Why do you ask?
You drove my patient away.
At a key moment,
you distracted me and he left.
Sorry hon.
I didn't think you'd hear me.
Stay in your car, please.
Okay, I understand.
All day. I finish at 6.
No screams before then.
- I'll work here, no problem.
- Thanks!
See you for lunch, though?
All right.
Well, okay. You can get dressed again.
I've seen what I wanted to see.
Ah, what is it?
That's exactly what I thought.
It is indeed an eczema attack
but on the inside.
On the inside?
Yes. On the inside
of your head.
What does that mean?
Well, it means a lot
of unpleasant things
that I'm just gonna
keep to myself.
If you wanted a doctor's note,
you came to the wrong place.
You can not play me
for an idiot.
Oh, uh..
What?
Get out of my office now.
Alright?
You've wasted enough of my time.
You are horrible.
Yes, I know.
Thank you for reminding me.
Now, get out, don't come back.
You should be ashamed.
Yeah, exactly I am ashamed.
I can't go to the pool anymore.
People keep looking at me like I
am gonna contaminate the water.
Of course I am ashamed.
Look at me.
I'm sick and you know it.
You've gotta help me!
I can't keep scratching myself
forever, I'm gonna go crazy.
Just stop acting right now.
Because you're not believable
for a second.
You don't have anything
and you know that very well.
So get the hell out of here!
Or I'm gonna file a complaint.
Goodbye.
Groan 44.
Groan 45.
Groan... 47?
And now, the award for
the best groan in movie history goes to...
What the fuck are you doing?
- Huh?
- It's late! Stop dicking around!
I didn't notice the time.
- What a crazy dream!
- Come on, I'm tired.
Listen to this crazy dream I had!
Tomorrow. I have a free slot at 11.
- Just listen, don't analyze.
- Tomorrow!
Jacques, now that our audience
knows you a little bit better
why don't you tell them about
the dessert that you've chosen.
We are all very impatient
and... and very much listening.
Uh, yes. I've chosen
the strawberry Charlotte.
The strawberry Charlotte, in a few words
tell us about the strawberry Charlotte.
Uh, yes. Well, um, it's a very
simple cake and easy to make.
Can you hurry, sugar pie?
We're leaving in 5 minutes.
Okay. Alright.
And they are not
too gross to touch..
Come on, reality, move it.
We're late.
Oh! Fuck.
God dammit.
Do we have a first aid kit?
Okay. Fuck!
It hurts like hell.
What the fuck were you thinking?
- Argh, I really hurt myself.
- Just...
Wait, alright?
don't move just a second.
Hello?
Um. I just spoke to Denis
on the phone.
Yeah, what's up with him?
He's not getting better.
He can't come in today.
And he didn't sound good at all.
He was crying.
What a fucking pain in the ass.
Apparently, he is itching
twice as much today.
Good morning
this is your captain speaking.
The leper is not
comin' in today.
Let's pack it up people,
this day is over.
Shit.
Hey, hi.
What?
Yeah, we don't know each other.
I am the camera 3 operator.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
No..
I... I was just wondering..
Do you think you could do the
same scream that you did earlier?
You know when you hurt yourself.
Aah! Could you do
the same?
Scream exact
the same scream again?
No. I don't think so.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Too bad.
You know I really hurt myself.
Are you stupid or somethin'?
No, I was just asking.
I thought your screaming
was great.
Whatever.
Moron.
I'm sorry.
So, before we look in detail
at its digestive system
there is something really
important we need to understand.
Now, the hog is an
omnivorous animal.
Does anybody know what
omnivorous means?
Uh, I do.
Uh, I know, ma'am.
Okay, serge, tell us
omnivorous, that means
he'll eat everything.
Good. Okay everything.
But what does everything mean?
Can you give us an example
uh, well, he can eat
salad for example
okay good, salad.
Uh, what else?
Rotten fruit.
Good. Rotten fruit. Uh, and?
Mushrooms.
Good. Mushrooms.
Now, some of those
are what are known as plants.
But what else does it eat?
Oh, oh, um..
He also eats other animals too.
Exactly. Animals.
Okay, so this is really
important to remember.
Everybody take your pens.
Good, and I want you to write...
Teacher.
Yes, reality.
A hog can also swallow a
videotape without damaging it.
But it's true.
Whoo-hoo!
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
You know you are not allowed in any
classroom during recess, right?
You broke the rules.
I am very upset
sorry, Mr. superintendent.
I promise that
I won't do it again.
What was on that tape
you wanted to watch?
It's a videotape I found.
It could be that there
is nothing on it.
I just wanted to check.
Let me see it.
No. You'll take it away.
I just wanna see what's written
on it. Give me the tape.
There's nothing written on it.
Well, I still wanna see it.
No!
You'll keep it.
And then I'll never
get to see what's on it.
Reality, give me the tape
or I'm gonna call your parents.
If you call my parents..
Then I'll tell everyone
you dress up like a woman.
Wha..
Me?
Are you kidding?
I saw you.
Driving a military Jeep.
Dressed like a woman.
No, you didn't.
Groan 65.
You're still at it?
I can't believe it.
I'm nearly done.
Just re-listening.
Are you satisfied?
Not especially.
Did Kubrick spend hours
recording himself stupid?
This is research. Why stupid?
Am I stupid?
You tell me.
Did Kubrick research his movies
by taping groans in his pajamas?
I don't give a shit for Kubrick.
He works his way, I work mine.
Why shouldn't I work in pajamas?
Take it easy! I'm trying to understand.
You just look a bit silly.
Okay.
Thanks for your support!
Really!
What do I know about movies?
Kubrick, my ass!
And now, the award for
the best groan in movie history goes to...
Jason tantra!
I can't stand up.
I can’t stand up!
I'm stuck... to the seat.
I'm stuck to the seat.
I'm stuck!
Stuck!
Dirty little fuckers!
Flaunting their boards.
Jason tantra's on the line.
What's he got?
Mr. Marshall wishes to know
if you have anything.
Well no, that's the problem.
I'm running around in circles.
Could you tell him I...
I lost track of what I'm looking for.
It's harder than I thought.
I'm scared
I'll miss the 48-hour deadline.
Can Mr. Marshall reassure me?
Hold on.
He is working,
but he's lost track.
He's running around in circles.
It’s starting to scare him.
He's scared he'll go over 48 hours.
He needs reassurance.
So reassure him.
Why don’t you take a break?
It will do you good.
- You think so?
- Yes.
Why not go to the pool
for a change of scene?
No, but...
I don't like swimming.
I'm no good at it.
Then why not a museum or a movie?
There are many enjoyable movies out.
They'll wash your brain.
Yeah, yeah... maybe.
don't stew in your own juice.
You're freaking out.
It's not good.
He can have 24 more hours.
Mr. Marshall gives you 24 more hours.
Great!
I want an Oscar for the groan!
Mr. Marshall says he wants
an Oscar for the groan.
I know.
That's the problem.
Cheer up.
Good luck.
But then...
How long do I have left
including the bonus?
Hello.
There you go.
Enjoy the movie.
What kind of movie is it?
Is it funny or more romantic?
I'm not allowed to answer
that kind of question, ma'am.
You'll see.
Uhhuh.
Can you move along, please.
You're holding up the line.
Okay.
Hmm.
Hey.
What?
It's the title of my film.
"Waves."
That's your "awesome" title?
Someone had the same idea.
Sure it's your title?
Yes! I know my own title.
It's "waves." Like microwaves.
It's a good time to change it.
"Waves" sounds awful.
You're kidding! I love it!
Excuse me. Uh, when does
this movie come out? Waves?
It's already out, sir.
It's playing now.
Can you move aside please,
you're blocking the other customers.
Uh, we're gonna
change the tickets
because we're going to watch it
instead. Is that possible?
What?
I'm sorry, it started
45 minutes ago.
Yes. It's alright. It's good.
Doesn't matter.
Can we change the tickets?
As you wish.
Not if it's started
and it's called "waves!”
I care about it, honey!
Please move along.
Thank you.
Next.
You're a pain!
God! It's my film!
I swear it's exactly my film.
Fuck!
Be quiet!
You're disturbing everybody.
Two years of hard work!
don't blame me!
I didn't want to see it.
See?
It's my film.
I can't take this.
I'm sorry. Listen to me,
you can't watch this.
Uh, this film doesn't exist yet.
I am the director, it's my film.
I just finished the script
and you can't watch it now.
Move!
This film doesn't
really exist yet!
We haven't shot it yet.
So, you can go and see
another movie. Thank you.
- Go?
- The groans are bad.
They're gonna to be better
when I will work on it.
So thank you, can we stop the...
Get out!
- The screening?
- Move it.
- Go!
- Please.
The groans are... are bad.
You don't understand.
Get the fuck out of the way!
I have to work on it.
This movie doesn't
really exists.
Move it.
I'm tryin' to watch
the fuckin' movie.
Work on it. Find the groan.
It's key.
I want the best groan in movie history.
I'm going home.
You're too embarrassing!
Thanks for the fun time!
I want the best groan in movie history.
I mean it.
I want an Oscar for it. You hear me?
Fine.
Fuck the rest.
Do your thing,
simplify it, I don't care.
-  I don't know what to say.
- Take 48 hours.
Call me when you're ready.
If I like the groans, we'll sign,
you'll make your movie.
Is it a deal?
Great to hear you. Jason here.
- Sorry to bother...
- Just a sec.
Weird! It's you on the line.
Sorry?
This is you on the line.
What do you mean? I'm here.
Where are you?
Outdoors, on the street.
An awful thing has happened.
I don't know how to say it.
It's about the movie.
There's a big problem.
I'm not sure how to explain
what happened.
I may even pass out.
Wait! Breathe deeply, don't faint.
What problem, Jason?
Who are you talking to?
I'm here.
Go on.
It may sound insane,
but I just saw my movie in a theater.
What did you say?
I know it sounds
crazy, but it's true.
I just saw my film
in a theater with an audience.
The film exists. I saw it.
And it sucks.
He says he saw his movie,
I mean your movie, and it sucks.
I had the exact same dream last night.
I saw my movie in a theater
and tried to stop it.
That's it.
- My nightmare.
- Listen Jason, don't panic.
You're in a bad dream.
Relax, try not to think about it
and you'll wake up.
Hello, Bob?
Hello? Hello, Bob?
Fuck!
Baby, aren't you taping?
That groan was awesome.
You should tape it.
Where's the damn recorder?
Look in the lining of your jacket.
The hole, you know?
Where you always lose your keys.
Ah, yes.
Got it.
Ha! Okay.
Damn.
I've stopped groaning.
What, honey?
The pain's gone.
I didn't tape the perfect groan.
Shit!
Excuse me. Hi.
Hello.
I need to borrow your rifle,
just for a minute.
I'm doing research for sounds,
I'm making movies.
You can take this one.
It's an old thing, I don't use it much.
Be careful though. It's loaded.
Okay.
Hey!
You're going to be
late for work.
Shit!
Who was that guy, daddy?
- Where?
- Well, there. Outside.
You were talking to somebody.
I wasn't talking to anybody.
Go back to sleep, sugar pie.
But I wasn't sleeping.
What is that?
That must be my alarm clock.
Well turn it off!
It's unbearable!
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Where are going with that?
I'm going to watch the tape.
Not now.
That isn't the plan.
For now, you're sleeping.
But I am sick of sleeping!
I want to know
what's on the tape!
Shh, shh, shh. You're going
to wake your parents up.
Now come on, go back to bed.
I'm the one who makes
the decisions, right?
I am so sick of this movie!
This sucks! What a pain!
I'd set my alarm, on purpose!
Why can't I watch the tape?
Just be a little patient.
Trust me.
Come on, go back to sleep!
Nobody's gonna want to watch
this scene where I am sleeping!
Nobody cares!
It's for the suspense!
Close your eyes.
Sleep!
There you go.
I'm sleeping.
Great movie!
Jacques, you are my guest today.
Yes.
You are a school teacher,
you like nature
you are an avid viewer
of talk shows
and you collect Russian watches
from the 70's.
Yes. Exactly.
You are 54 years old.
Yes, that's the truth
you are a widower.
Yes.
Do you believe in god?
Hmm? Yes.
Yes.
Mmhmm.
So what should we begin with?
In... in your opinion?
Maybe we could wash
the strawberries.
Personally, that's
my favorite part.
Well, okay.
Let's start.
Do you have any
special technique?
Yes.
I put the strawberries
in a damp cloth
and then I rub them
ever so gently.
Jason, wake up! Hey! Wake up,
man. We've got work to do!
- Jason!
- What's going on with him?
I don't know, he just fell.
Hey everyone, I'm here!
I'm ready to shoot this,
so let's..
Wake up! Hey, man,
it's not nap time.
- Jason?
- We got work to do.
Wake up!
- Sorry.
- Up.
Hey! Come on, wake up!
Sir!
Hello.
Hey!
Woo-hoo!
Sir! Hey come on, wake up!
You're missing the movie!
Sir? Sir?
Come on, wake up!
Woo-hoo.
Wake up!
Sir? Sir?
Wake up, dammit!
I don't have time for this shit!
Come on, wake up!
Wake up!
What's... what's happening?
I'm... I'm confused.
It is indeed an eczema
attack, but on the inside.
On the inside of your head.
Wake up!
Hey, come on, wake up! Sir?
Come on. Wake up!
Ha!
What's the matter, dude?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Hey, come on, wake up!
Sir?
Okay.
We need to talk. Uh, I think
we are the same person.
I've been having some weird
dreams where I'm you.
I... I don't know, I know it
doesn't make any sense but..
I think we are the same person.
I don't know why.
What's going on?
She's about to see
what's on the videotape.
I see that, but it's badly shot!
We can't see what she's seeing.
Why choose that angle?
Mr. Marshall says
it is very poorly filmed.
And he wants to know why you
chose this angle.
Because it's beautiful.
Okay, it's beautiful,
but what the fuck is she watching?
We need to know what's on the tape!
Bob wants to know
what's on the tape.
He has to be patient.
He asks you to be patient.
My Patience is limited.
Does he even know what's on it?
Maybe he hasn't thought it out yet.
Bob is wondering if you
know what is on the tape.
I know perfectly well
what is on this tape
but I'm not going to tell him
before he finds out himself
it'd ruin the surprise.
He has to be patient.
He says, be patient.
I'm warning you, Zog.
The more I wait, the more I want.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
I want to be locked up.
I'm losing my grip.
I need treatment and help.
Fine.
Come with me.
This way.
Here we are!
Make yourself comfortable.
- I'll be back in a minute.
- Thanks.
Shall I take your gun?
Yes, sorry.
Mr. Marshall,
Jason tantra's on the line.
Will he never give up?
Keep it short, Jason. I'm busy.
Sorry to bother you.
I wanted to warn you
I may be late with the groan.
What are you doing?
I have other fish to fry, dammit!
I can't wait forever.
I gave you 48 hours,
plus a 24 hour bonus.
You need a week to find a groan.
How long to shoot a movie?
Yes, but... Everything's
gone wrong.
Nothing fits.
I need time to get myself together.
What doesn't fit?
Are you sick?
It may sound dumb,
but I'm stuck in a nightmare.
I know it.
But then again,
the good news is, if it's a nightmare
I'll have to wake up.
But...
I don't know when.
I can't guarantee to deliver you a groan
as long as I'm stuck in the nightmare.
Good god!
Does that make sense
if you're not in the nightmare?
Do you understand?
Holy shit!
Jason, I'll put you on hold...
Hang on a second.
I'm flabbergasted.
He's a genius.
A fucking genius!
Bob says you are a genius.
You like it?
I don't know how to tell you,
I'm flabbergasted.
It's not finished.
No, but right now
I'm speechless.
My brain is in my socks
as they say.
Hello.
What's that?
- A suppository, to help you sleep.
- No, no...
No need. I'm in a nightmare.
I'm already fast asleep.
No need for a suppository, thanks.
Come on, now.
It's nothing at all.
It won't take a second.
You don't understand.
I am asleep.
Anyway, can't it wait?
I'm on the phone here, see?
It's not plugged in, sir.
Roll over a little. Roll over.
Please. It will help you relax.
There! Not so awful, was it?
Night-night, sleep tight!
Sleep in my nightmare?
Thanks a bunch!
I'll leave you for an hour or so.
Jason, you still there?
- Yes.
- Your groan was perfect!
Your movie is a go.
We'll sign on Monday.
Till then, rest up.
What?
Hello, Bob?
Bob, what groan?
There you go.
That's all for today.
Incredible!
Really incredible!
So beautiful, I could cry.
Let me kiss you.
Thank you.
Words fail me. I'm speechless!
Hey, Zog!
You're a fucking genius!
What'd he say?
He said you're a fucking genius.
Yeah.
Thanks!
His name is Zog?
Yes.
Just Zog? No surname?
Who is he?
An ex-documentary maker.
I picked him up out of the gutter.
He's a handful,
but very talented.
His movie is stunning.
The end
Bye, Mr. Marshall.
I'm very happy.
Call me Bob now.
Get to work, pal.
Here I go.
- 48 hours.
- Yes sir!
- Good luck.
- Yes.
So...
See you soon, Bob.
Yes!
So, do you have
a special technique?
Yes, I put the strawberries
in a damp cloth
and then I rub them
ever so gently.
That way, you don't
damage the skin.
You could show us,
it would be easier.
Gladly.
What's happening?
I'm confused.
It is indeed an eczema attack
but on the inside.
On the inside of your head.