Where the hell are you?
I am going to beat your little
ass if you don't get out here!
I've gone over this for two
days.
I don't remember anything.
Mommy? Mommy?
Look what I got for you.
Shit...
Go away.
GO AWAY!!!
Can you tell me about Jeremy
Dorian?
Where did you two meet?
I don't want to talk about
Jeremy.
Why are you guys doing this to
me?
Why am I still here?
Is he your boyfriend?
Again, my name is Dr. Carter
Moore.
You waived your right to an
attorney,
And I'm just here to speak
with you.
I honestly don't remember
anything.
That's alright. Let's just
start at the beginning.
Jeremy?
Thank you.
Aw, you shouldn't have.
Come on in.
So how long have you worked
here?
About three years.
Keeps me out of trouble.
Trouble? What kind of trouble?
Thank you for the flowers
by the way.
A gentleman always brings
flowers on a first date.
Oh wait, sorry. It's not a date.
It's coffee.
I'm not used to guys being so
nice to me.
Oh, come on.
That is hard to believe.
No ones ever got me flowers
before.
Well, I did.
You did...
Oh my god... Why am I
so nervous?
I guess I don't get out much.
That's impossible.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
God, your shaking.
Why?
Can I kiss you?
I wanna feel you inside me.
Okay.
Shhhhh...
Not now.
Not now. Please stop.
Not right now.
I thought you would never come.
I'm so pleased you did.
I didn't know you wanted me to.
It took some homework
Trying to find you.
Caleb. My boy.
My baby boy Caleb. Look at you!
You have grown to be such a
big boy.
Why do you cover up your hair
like that?
You have such a nice
Head of hair. Just like me.
Not like your father.
Like me.
Caleb...
My boy Caleb...
Where have you been? Huh?
You left me mom.
Gave me up.
I'm here now.
You've come home.
Cay?
Caleb?
Cay, you awake?
There's something I wanna
tell you.
And I woke up, he was gone.
How did that make you feel?
Abandoned.
Alone.
How would that make you feel?
I've listened to everything
Everyone has said. I just
want to go home.
Caleb... You can't go home.
We need to find out what
happened.
I don't know where the blood
came from.
Can I help you?
How are you?
What can I get you?
Ahhh... Cappuccino. No Whip.
So how are you?
What's that?
How are you?
Busy.
It's good to see you.
What else can I get you?
Did I do something wrong?
Yeah. As a matter of fact, you
did. You left.
No note, no phone number.
Nothing.
That was three days ago.
I'm sorry.
That's why I'm here.
Caleb. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you this
upset.
I knew I'd see you again.
Yeah, well I didn't.
Have dinner with me.
Okay.
But let me make this better.
Please...
This has got to be the best
Chinese food I've ever had.
Yeah.
I thought sitting by the
fireplace
Would be kinda romantic.
I really love your place.
Thanks. So do I.
It was left to me
when my mom died.
I'm sorry to hear that.
How'd she die?
Leukemia.
She wasn't my real mom.
I just call her that 'cause
She's the closest thing.
I don't know my real dad
either.
I was adopted.
Spent most of my childhood in
foster care.
You know, in and out,
in and out.
I guess you could say I was a
little troubled one.
And then I met this older
couple.
Karen and Bill. Gave me a
stable home.
They knew I was gay from the
beginning. No problem with it.
Long story short: Karen
Caught Bill cheating and
she kicked him out.
So, shortly thereafter she was
diagnosed with Leukemia.
And two days before my 17th
birthday, she died.
They let me back here when I
was 18.
By leaving me this place, she
made sure I
Would always have a home.
You, mister, are very brave.
I think that
All that stuff you've gone
through,
Has made you into the
man you are today.
I guess.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because I like you.
You're sweet. You're open.
You're honest.
I never met anybody
like you before.
I never told anyone that
stuff before.
Well, I'm glad you did.
Now, are you ready for desert?
Hell, yeah!
Scoop! Not that much! Pick that
up!
Damn. Alright, that's good,
that's good.
I can't eat all that.
What are you talking
about? You can eat all that.
Alright, a little more. A
little more. Oh yeah...
More? No, I'm going over here.
So what is with all these
horses?
Childhood fantasy. I love
horses. This one...
I've had since I was...
4, I think.
It's my favorite.
I've been collecting since...
My entire life.
My one constant.
I used to... hide.
Hide in my closet.
And sit with this one,
and hope and pray
That one day, he would come
to life, right, and just
Take me away from all the hell
that I was living.
You ever ride one?
A few times. In Vermont.
Well, we should go.
To Vermont?
No, nimrod!
Horseback riding.
You'd do that with me?
Yeah...
You do realize this is
disgusting, don't you?
Oh come on, leave poor
Hermie alone.
You know, there is only
one thing
I hate in this world, and it's
nasty, hairy spiders.
Oh come on, he's only a little
bit poisonous.
Don't tap the
glass!
I mean, couldn't you settle
for like a dog or a cat?
No. I don't like yappy little
Paris Hilton dogs and lord
Knows, I ain't into pussy!
What does one do with a spider
anyway?
I mean, you can't take him out
and play with him?
Sure you can.
I take him out all the time.
Let him roam all over me.
Remind me not to be here
when you do that.
AHHHHHH!
Oh fuck! You ass!
You sure you don't wanna hold
him?
No! I would shit myself. Twice.
Come on you big baby, let's go.
Don't tap the glass!
I could stay like this forever.
Me, too.
Tell something about you that
nobody else knows.
I take Lipitor.
I already knew you were old.
No seriously, I wanna know
everything about you.
Okay...
I'm a recovering addict and
alcoholic.
I've been sober for 15 years.
No shit...
I call it a gift that my
alcoholic mother never got.
Wow... she's not alive?
No. She died when I was 23.
From drinking?
Yeah... She was in rehab,
and then she went to a
Halfway house. She wanted out.
She came to live with me.
I couldn't take it anymore.
What happened?
They found her body submerged
in the bathtub after the whole
House flooded.
And for the longest
time I didn't know
If she drowned or...
Drank herself to death.
I'm so sorry.
You know, that didn't even stop
me? I kept using for years
And I just finally got sick
and tired of being
Sick and tired.
So there ya go! There's one of
my big secrets.
Wow...
I wasn't expecting that one.
So you haven't drank or smoked
weed
Or done anything in 15 years?
Not even a little bit?
Nope.
I call that grace.
I never thought of it like that.
That you can do anything you
set your heart to.
Man, I can't believe this is
real.
Well, why don't you pinch me
and find out?
You're such a nerd!
Shut it!
He was like my knight in
shinning armor.
I never met someone who really
listens to me the way he does.
It sounds like you're quite
enamored with Jeremy.
Where is he?
Does he know I'm in here?
Let me ask you
something... would you ever
Intentionally do something to
Jeremy that would hurt him?
No. Absolutely not.
Why would you say something
like that?
I need to see him.
NOW!!!
You're very angry.
I understand that.
You don't understand shit!
You have no idea what it's
like to be me.
That's exactly what we need to
find out.
I don't need to hear this right
now... I don't get this...
Give me that god damn it!
How many times do I have to
Tell you? Not at the dinner
table. There!
Now maybe you'll finish your
dinner.
You are not leaving this table
until you finish every god damn
Bit of that. Do you hear me?
Do you hear me?
But I don't like it mommy.
EAT! Eat! Eat!!
Eat you little pussy boy!
Eat. Eat! Eat! Eat!
Go to bed.
That must have been really
hard for you.
I never told anyone.
Are you sure this doesn't
bother you?
No.
It's cool. And you don't have
to keep asking me.
I just don't want you to be
tempted.
I really needed to unwind
tonight.
I know baby.
You know...
You really need to realize that
there is so much good in you.
Validating that good is...
Not always an easy thing to do.
I just feel alone.
I feel so alone sometimes.
Like I can't...
Shake this feeling of being
abandoned.
But you...
You can change that.
That is all up to you.
Besides...
You, mister, have me now.
Will you stay with me tonight?
I would love to stay with
you tonight.
Come on sleepyhead! Wake up!
I've got a surprise for you.
Yo! Sleeping beauty!
Wake up!
But it's Saturday.
Yeah, I know. Let's go.
Where are we going?
Come on. Up, up up! I've got a
surprise.
I hate surprises.
I heard that!
Now can you tell me what
we're doing here?
Well, since horses are
the one thing
That brighten that beautiful
Smile, I thought you should
have one of your own.
What are you talking about?
This farm is part of a...
an adopt a horse program.
You get to adopt a old or an
abused horse...
Cay, I want you to meet
Nero Fiddles.
Nero, meet your new owner,
Caleb.
You're kidding, right?
She's 15 years old.
She's friendly, healthy.
And I think a big old lesbian.
But just remember, I don't
Shovel shit or anything
like that.
No, of course not.
And there's one more thing...
What?
I just want you to know you
have made me
The happiest I've been in
my entire life.
I never felt this way
about another guy.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Thank you.
That was the first time I ever
heard someone tell me that
With such conviction.
It was a foreign word to me.
I don't even think I love
myself.
Did you ever?
No. No.
Why is that?
I don't know.
I never had love.
Growing up... even when I was
A little kid. Being told,
I was a pussy boy or a faggot
all the time.
It doesn't do much for the
self-esteem.
Who called you that?
My mother. For starters.
You're not a pussy.
And you're not a faggot.
I suck dick...
Is that what you think a
faggot is?
What a faggot is... is
disgusting slang. That's all.
Whatever. I'm gay, okay?
Well, great. That's not a bad
thing.
Now...
You had love.
Genuine love.
Jeremy.
Ponyboy. You know, from
that movie 'The Outsiders'?
I like the name, but can't say
I've ever seen it.
You young ones today. Can't get
no respect.
What about you?
Donnie Darko.
Who?
Jake Gyllenhaal.
When he was a teen.
That whole dark and brooding
thing.
He had all that dark hair.
Had that rebel thing going on.
I had actually got caught
beatin' off thinking about him.
No. Really?
I had hung this 'Outsiders'
poster on my bedroom wall
And I thought I was being all
inconspicuous about it with it
Hung behind my bed.
Ooops.
I'd lay back with my feet on
the pillow and get busy.
My mom comes in with a pile of
laundry and there I am,
Whackin' off.
Choking the chicken,
yeah, go on.
I'd have my shirt pulled up
against my nipples and my
Jeans and my underwear
around my ankles.
She walks in, and I'm so caught
off guard that I roll off
The bed and I fall to the
ground.
Classic.
It was like something out of a
Ben Stiller movie, but...
I mean honestly, the real
experience was not that fun.
You were alone.
Now I have you.
So let me ask you something?
Shoot.
You ever think about finding
your mom?
I don't see the point.
Closure.
I have thought about it
sometimes.
Some day.
I have a new family.
It's a nice couple.
They take really good
care of me.
That's nice, sweetie.
Kinda boring, but they're cool.
What's brown and sticky?
I don't know. Poop?
No!
A stick, silly!
I'm in school.
I try really hard.
It's alright.
I don't really get the whole
Algebra II thing.
What does a perverted
frog say?
I don't know.
Rub it. Rub it.
Rub it.
What do you call a lesbian
dinosaur?
Mom...
Lick-a-lota-puss!
Come on Cabby, duh!
Hey, hey... just one more.
One more. Promise.
And then we will go down to
have applesauce.
Because, I need my sauce.
Okay... what is the number
one cause...
Of pedophilia?
Sexy babies.
Get it? Get it?
It's sexy babies.
It's sexy babies. Sexy babies.
Sexy babies.
It's the babies. The babies.
Why would someone who rarely
cooks have two jars of
Cream of Tartar?
I honestly don't even
know what that is.
I don't either.
So how long do
we cook this for?
A half hour, maybe.
So where did you learn all this
kitchen stuff.
You don't really even seem
like the cooking type.
Magic.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You shouldn't have.
Just open it.
So I saw it in the
drugstore and thought of you.
Oh my god... a Bugs Bunny
toothbrush.
I know, it's silly.
No. It is not silly. It is
very sweet.
I just thought that we could
ummm... take it to the next
Step... level...
I just ummm... you could
keep it here.
With no more overnight toiletry
bag.
No more overnight
toiletry bag.
Thanks.
OH! And...
A key.
To your hole?
No! Gross. No, to my heart.
No, the house. It's the house.
To my heart. To the house.
Baby... Thank you.
Of course.
I love you so much.
By the way...
I found her.
Your mom.
Cay? Cay, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do it.
I'm sorry, alright.
I shouldn't have done that. I
apologize.
Just fuckin' stop. Just fuckin'
stop!!! Why can't you be
My fucking boyfriend and not
my keeper!
You have fuckin' no idea!
So what?
I thought I was doing
something...
So now you know the Caleb...
the Jacob's fucking family
Secret. How do you feel
about it, huh?
You wanna know a secret?
I've been keeping tabs on the
bitch the entire time. In the
Fucking loony bin... that's
exactly where she's been!
I knew that! I fucking
knew that!!!
Just calm down...
NO!
Don't tell me to calm down!
I'm sorry, okay! I thought I was
doing something right.
You have no fucking idea
how it feels.
You have fucking no idea!!!
Enough! Enough, okay!
Shut up!!!!
I'm sorry, alright!
Calm down...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
Forget it...
It's okay...
It's NOT okay.
I know it's not okay,
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna cum...
Shoot it! Go!
10 minutes. That's all I needed
was 10 fucking minutes,
And I'd be comatose.
That's all I needed.
Did you discuss this with
your therapist?
What's the point? I'd just get
another pill, and...
With the right diagnosis
and medication,
It's amazing what can happen.
Let's get something straight!
I'm not her, alright.
I'm not
her.
You're fucking disgusting.
You fucking piece of shit.
You ugly little pussy bitch.
Cum whore. You did this to me.
You...
Made me like this. You did it.
You made me what I am. You!
You! You!
You little faggot!
Little faggot!
I can't stand you.
I cannot stand that I pushed you
out of my vagina.
You ruined me!
You tore up my insides
And stole every piece of me
When you forced your little fat
wrinkly baby
Body into this world.
My heart...
My intestines. My pussy.
My fucking anus.
You're gross.
You are disgusting.
I mean, look at you!
Just look at you!!!!!
Look at you. Devil's spawn!
Worse then even the man who
dumped his sperm into me.
And all for what?
For what? So you could run
around sticking
AIDS ridden dicks in your
asshole you sad pathetic
Faggot! Homo!
I hate you! I hate you!
You didn't go to the hospital?
No, I didn't go to the hospital.
I wasn't gonna leave
you like this.
You and I...
we need to talk.
Do you hate me?
No.
No I don't hate you.
I am the one that you should
hate.
This is all my fault.
I never should have butt in.
This isn't any ones fault.
I did this.
I still cannot comprehend why
You would cut yourself
like this.
Ouch...
Ouch. Fuck...
I don't know.
I guess I just wanted the
outsides to look
Like the way I feel on
the inside.
Oh fuck, that's stupid.
You know, suicide is not
an option.
I wasn't gonna do that!
You know, I look at you
and all I see is pain.
I just want to make it better.
You know, that's just it.
Don't try so hard.
I'm not used to all this.
You know, no one has
ever given me this much.
And...
Every single time I let
someone in,
They just leave me.
So don't try so hard, okay?
What was I supposed to do?
I walk in and I see
you bleeding.
I don't call that trying too
hard, okay.
I call that trying to take
care of somebody I love.
You're not gonna leave
me now, are you?
Did you not just hear what I
said?
I said I love you.
You know, the past 8 months
have changed my life
More than you will ever know.
I'm sorry.
I never want to leave you.
You know what you need?
A lobotomy?
Maybe.
I think you need a little bit
of Nero in the morning.
Yeah.
How's that sound?
Sounds great.
Fairmont Place. Fairmont Place.
Fairmont Place.
Fairmont Place...
That ones mine. Ready?
Wanna see what it is?
He's good for something.
Aw... cute.
It's adorable.
Thank you.
But Daddy's not going to be the
one getting up in the middle
Of the night feeding her,
now is he?
She knows me like a book.
I'm kidding...
Ooh... She just kicked.
This kid has been going
crazy all day. Honey, feel.
Baby, could you grab the
recycling bin, too?
Aw, you didn't.
These are my favorite.
Don't forget the box
that my Mother brought.
I know, I know.
It's in the car.
For the longest time I
I didn't even love myself.
Caleb, you just have to
You have to be completely
honest with me.
If we're gonna make this work.
I like it that way.
Me, too.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you...
Fuck you!
I've been waiting for you.
I'm sorry, baby.
I got stuck in the ER.
Come to bed.
I see how this goes.
Is this my
payback for being late?
Scoot.
Aw, you dirty boy.
You have no idea.
Now kiss me.
Close your eyes.
I have a surprise for you.
Can I open?
Shhh.
Daddy's Angel.
How cute.
How did you get these?
Cay, come on. Let me
explain. Just take these off.
I really don't think I
should be around you right now.
Cay... Cay, wait. Let me
explain. Cay, Wait!
Cay! Caleb!
Take these fucking things
Off me. Cay! Cay!
Please stop. Please stop.
Please stop.
STOP STOP STOP STOP!
Caleb...
Cay!!!!!
Shut up! Shut up! SHUT UP!
You fucking pussy. I can't
stand this shit!
Ahhhhh!!!!!
Ahhhhhhhhh!!!!
Ahhhhh!!!
You're fucking crazy!
What did you call me?
I have been in here for hours.
You fucking psycho!
Please don't hit me.
- Please don't hit me.
Listen to you. You sound like a
faggot. You are a faggot,
Right? RIGHT?
Take these off of me.
Answer the question.
Yes.
Louder. I wanna hear it again.
Very good. Now see, I know that.
And you know that.
But does your wife know that?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why? Why? Listen to you.
Damn, you are pathetic.
You're nothing but a two-faced
liar.
No...
Nothing that we did was a lie.
She's a fucking cunt. A cunt.
That just blows my mind.
And she's pregnant. She's
pregnant, too?
Take that off of me.
Your wife should really lock
the back door.
Please tell me you didn't
hurt her.
She's fine.
What do you think I am?
I'm sorry, baby. I'm so sorry.
SHUT UP! You're not who I
thought you were.
You're just like everybody else.
No. You're not listening.
I'm sorry.
Shut UP! Just stop.
I can't breathe...
Please let me go. I won't tell
anyone. Please...
Just let me go.
I know...
You're too afraid.
What would you say?
I'm sucking some kid's dick?
The Ms. would love that.
How long do you plan on
keeping me here?
Until you tell me the truth.
Have you heard of Brief
Reactive Psychosis?
No... Enlighten me.
It's usually triggered by an
extremely stressful event in
Ones life.
You've had many recently.
The subject tends to hear
voices and hallucinate.
To see and hear things that
aren't really there.
They do things they wouldn't
normally ever do.
Does this sound familiar?
We've talked about your life
growing up. The abandonment.
So... what's that got to do with
why I'm here?
I'm thinking that perhaps the
new details
You've discovered about
Jeremy's life may have been
A trigger for what transpired
with him.
You people keep saying what's
transpired with Jeremy.
I don't know what you're
talking about.
Do you hear yourself?
You have an acute
reaction to rejection.
There's only so many times
I can pick myself up again.
So many credit cards...
Oh, whose Don?
Do you fuck him, too?
Should I take that as a yes?
No.
Ooh, look at that...
It's the first word you
said in hours.
I was beginning to
think you were mad at me.
So what's her name?
Your bitch?
Fuck you!
Why did you get married if
you're gay?
You have no clue about
our relationship.
You're GAY!
You can't make that go away.
Alright, YES! I'm gay! Okay,
there. I said it. I'm gay.
Does she even know?
I don't know.
Why did you marry her?
Because I thought it would
change.
I thought having a baby would
make things different.
Do you hear how ridiculous
that is?
Oh, it's so easy for
you, isn't it?
We grew up in different times,
Cay.
You... you have things like
fucking Glee.
Where I grew up, all I heard
Is that gay equals AIDS.
You're gay, you die.
That kept me hiding.
You wanna know the real
reason my
Adopted mother threw
her husband out?
She caught him fucking me!
He'd been molesting me for
years. You have no idea what it
Feels like to have the man that
supposed to be your father...
Ripping your ass open.
And AIDS? You think I wasn't
scared of dying?
That disgusting creeper shot
his load in my ass constantly.
If you think I wasn't scared of
dying,
Think again, my friend.
Okay...
I should be back by three.
Would you like me to
leave the TV on for you?
The TV... There's no TV.
Okay, before I go... take three
of these.
One, two, and three.
Drink. Drink!
Swallow.
Now I know you know how
do to that.
Good boy.
Open. Come on, open.
Come on...
For the anxiety.
Three should do the trick.
I wanna go home.
You are home.
I love you.
(Phone Ringing)
(Wimpering)
Hey.
Can I get one of these?
I've seen you here.
Because I work here.
So listen. I'm hot. I think
you're kind of hot.
What do you say we
make it happen?
That's stupid. You're stupid.
Plus, I'm married.
Yeah, well, good luck with
that.
It's on the house.
You're a nasty little bitch,
aren't you?
You have no idea.
Get up!
AHHHHHHH!
Come on. Shut up, you pussy.
I hope for your sake you
swallowed those pills.
What the... what the fuck are
you doing?
Get... what the fuck are you
doing?
I thought you'd like it daddy.
Please just kill me.
I don't want this anymore.
Don't be ridiculous.
I wanna die. I can't...
Don't worry. I have something
better for you.
You're about to lose the one
Thing that you worked
so hard for.
Take a sip.
Little more?
It's good, isn't it?
Have some more.
Oh, come on, don't be greedy.
Let's get drunk together.
Do you hate me?
No. No I don't hate you.
I am the one that you should
hate.
This is all my fault.
This isn't anyone's fault.
I did this.
You're not gonna
leave me now, are you?
I said I love you.
The past 8 months have changed
my life more than
You will ever know.
I'm sorry.
I never want to leave you.
Even though I'm really scared...
I do love you.
I'm so sorry, baby.
NO!!!!
AHHHH!!! GET IT OUT!
GET IT OUT!!!!
There was only one thing left
to do.
And what was that?
(Phone Vibrates)
You do and say exactly what
we went over, okay?
Yes.
Everything will be okay.
Jeremy? Jeremy, I'm here.
Leah...
Jeremy?
What's this all about?
Jeremy!!!
Are you okay?
Seems we have something
in common.
Isn't that right, baby?
Somebody tell me what
the hell is going on here!
Go on... tell her.
Please... help me.
Come on.
Go ahead and tell her.
Just like we practiced.
Come on. I...
I...
Am...
A...
Please...
- A...
Faggot.
How are we supposed to be a
family when you have a wife?
We've been fucking for
almost a year.
Tell her how you like to go
down on me.
He sucks a mean cock.
Swallows, too.
Nice throw. You're more of a
man then he is.
Wouldn't it be great if mommy
had a dirty little secret, too?
Cay, it's over.
Stop! Stop!
You wanna fuck with
my family!
I killed her.
I did it.
I didn't mean to do it.
I didn't mean to hurt anyone.
It's the last thing I remember,
was being at Jeremy's house.
And that was it.
Like I said...
Let's start at the beginning.
Are you hungry still?
Are you hungry still? You
wanna play with the cow?
You want your little cow? I
know you do.
I know mamma. Don't you cry.
You wanna eat.
I know you do. I know you do.
I got your feet. I know mamma.
Jeremy?