To get ajun free,
it is going to
cost me 50,000 pounds.
Katherine: What else do
we have, but mei.
Every month in this apartment,
an exclusive party is given
to businessmen,
Who like to take drugs.
Which are provided
by mr adiola.
Mr. Chen employs
migrant girls for sex,
and smart girls to charm.
Miss ashley should go
as hostess to charm.
Get this evidence and we will
have your brother free.
I'll do it.
We will stay right here,
until you come out.
As soon as you get the shots,
you must leave.
(gate closes)
(doorbell rings)
(indistinct chattering)
Is this paula?
Yes.
-You are from london?
-Yes.
Customers like their girls,
from london.
-Are you a virgin?
-No.
Okay. Come.
(indistinct chattering)
Only one rule. Anything they
want, you will give. Okay?
Take off your clothes.
Your clothes. Go.
I'm a hostess, not a prostitute.
We only have hostesses here.
You wanna go, huh? You wanna go?
-No.
-Okay.
So, take off your clothes.
And the rest. Go.
Hurry up.
Turn around.
Put this on.
Bathroom is next door.
(door closes)
(doorbell rings)
(speaking chinese)
(speaking indistinctly)
What are you doing here?
I was looking for the bathroom.
You know where the bathroom is.
This is not your area.
(sighs)
(typing on phone)
(phone beeps)
(speaking chinese)
(door closes)
(bed creaking)
(grunting)
(panting)
(groaning)
(grunting)
(door opens)
(door closes)
(phone beeps)
(music playing)
(speaking chinese)
-I need cocaine.
-This is only for the clients.
I'll pay for it.
If you want.
You must have it here.
(sniffing)
(door opens)
I've done it.
You got them on camera?
(speaking chinese)
Yes, I got everything.
Mr lin, you lied to me.
Would you have gone,
if I told you the truth?
Did you not ask me to do
whatever it takes?
You better deliver for me.
(engine starts)
(vibrating)
-Still nothing?
-No.
Perhaps we should call anderson.
We haven't done the right
thing. Have we?
-I better call anderson.
-What does it take for her
to send a text?
I'll call him now.
It'll be early, but...
-You can ask him how long
that visa's gonna take.
-He won't know that.
Can't just wait here
and do nothing.
It'll take another
couple of days.
We are going as fast as we can.
Not the same for you.
-No, it's not the same.
-I'm losing her.
And you think that too.
'cause I can see it
in your eyes.
As soon as we get out there,
we will see...
No, we will see it in her eyes
too. She's not gonna wanna
come home.
She's discovering something
really huge in her life.
Something that will
sweep her away from us.
I'm not blaming her for it.
I won't.
But the moment she came home,
And mentioned her birth mother.
I just saw this whole scenario,
Opening up.
We've just been holding
her for a little while.
Children do go.
Parents can lose their meaning.
You're right.
I should know this.
-Hey! What are you doing?
-Who is this woman? You again?
(chen on tape)
this is only for the clients.
If you want,
you must have it here.
-This is not me.
-Of course it is you. Anybody
can see this is you.
-This is not cocaine.
-Then, what is it?
I have nothing to do
with cocaine.
This recording is going
to the ministry of
public security in beijing.
These are all lies.
They are trying to set me up.
You cannot show
this to the ministry.
My cousin will be executed.
My office will be shut down.
My whole community
will be banished.
There are four nigerian
witnesses to the murder
of chike alozie.
Tell them to change
their statements.
And I will destroy this.
Mr. Lin, I've been living
in guangzhou, for eight years.
I have a very important
position in this city.
As the president of
the china nigeria
commerce association,
I was approached
by mr quan shin.
And he told me to change
the evidence to protect
his nephew.
Mr quan shin is the head of the
security division in guangdong.
He threatened all of
our lives here.
He said the witnesses
will be deported,
Incarcerated, everything,
if they did not sign.
He even threatened
me with deportation.
You may be deported.
But mr adiola will be executed.
If you do not do,
what I tell you.
Please, I'm trying to protect
my people here.
I'm trying to protect
them from quan shin.
Now you'll have to protect
them from this.
There are 25,000 africans
in my community.
He will punish us all if you ask
me to do this. I can't do this.
That is very bad news
for your cousin.
Joseph, they will execute me.
Tell the truth.
And tell him to do the same.
Why did you get caught
in this stupid web?
Look at what trouble
you have caused me!
Mr lin...
It is a very difficult life,
for us all here.
We try to do the best we can.
-Your life here is not
my problem.
-We are all very poor men
Doing the best for our families
back home in nigeria.
Your families in nigeria
are not my problem.
I should let him take this
to the police.
-They will execute me.
-And I shall let them do it.
You are destroying my life here.
Mr lin...
If I ask these boys to sign...
We will be signing away
our lives here.
We will be forsaking our
families. They will not do it.
-Make them do it.
-Mr lin, I am begging
you, please.
Okay. I will agree.
-I will do this.
Leave it with me.
-I will wait.
-But two of the men
are not here.
-Call the others.
-They may not be able too come.
-Not my problem.
This is making me happy.
This is making me have peace
with my god.
Thank you.
The boy deserves the truth.
Everyone deserves the truth.
(speaking chinese)
They are all saying
I did not kill chike?
-Yes they have changed
their statements.
-Did tao say this thing too?
(speaking chinese)
-And eddie?
-Eddie said the same.
Yes. Eddie my true friend.
All the africans and everyone
working in the club are now
supporting you.
(speaking chinese)
I will be free.
Is it really true?
The judges will have no choice
but to accept
the new statements.
And you have a new
lawyer for the appeal.
Her name is cheng hua.
She will be
at the higher court for you.
Everyone is supporting me now.
(speaking chinese)
She is so happy,
that we are all
together at last.
Now we can really start
to dream.
(speaking chinese)
I tell her about london.
And I'll rock the city.
She doesn't know what I do
when I say I dj with eddie.
(speaking chinese)
I want you both to come
to london. Tell her.
(speaking chinese)
I'm so happy we are
all together.
(speaking chinese)
I'm going to take her away
from this life.
Now she can rest.
Because I will look after her.
We'll do that together.
Yes.
We'll look after her together.
(speaking chinese)
(computer rings)
Mei. Mei. It is mei.
-Mei: Hi mom.
-Both: Hi!
-Mei: Hi dad.
-Hi sweetheart.
-Mei: How are you?
-How are you?
I'm great.
-Dad: Whats happening?
-Mei: I just want to say...
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you for
lending me the money.
I'll pay it back. All of it.
-But I'm so grateful to you.
-Well, we're pleased
to hear that honey.
But what is happening?
What is not happening.
You telling us anything
that is happening.
The detective we hired,
has now got all the witnesses
To make new statements
in support of ajun.
Katherine: Really?
Oh, thats wonderful.
And we're ready for the court.
For the appeal. It's amazing.
-It's amazing.
-Does that mean he's going
to be released?
Mei: Thats what the lawyers
have told me. Yes.
Both: That is wonderful.
So, thank you. Thank you.
Have you spoken to mr. Anderson?
-I don't want to speak to him.
-Katherine: We think
that you should call him.
-Why?
-Why? Because none of us know
where you are.
Where are you, mei?
I'm at qianyi's. I've been
staying with her for couple
of days.
But you are not answering
your phone.
I'm sorry.
It's just been crazy.
Are you all right?
You are not. Are you?
Have you seen your mother again?
Yes. Yes I have.
I have.
It's not that.
-Mei, whats going on?
-I'm okay.
I'm okay.
I went to the orphanage
with her.
Right.
It was...
She cried and...
I held her and...
It was lovely.
It's like a pain in me,
all these years, gone.
That's what it was like.
I can understand that.
Mei: And now,
if I can get ajun out
of prison and free for her...
It would be the best thing,
I could ever
do in my life.
The best thing ever.
Jim: Sounds like your
going to achieve that.
Yes, I am.
I couldn't have abandoned
her and come home.
I had to do this.
Jim: Mei, we are coming
out to see you.
We are going to london now
to pick up our visas.
Why?
-Katherine: Because...
-You don't have to do that.
Well, we are. We are doing it.
And the flight's all booked and
we will be coming out and...
Mom, dad you don't
have to do this.
By the time you get here,
I will be coming home.
Katherine: No, it's already
booked. It's...
We are ready to go.
No! I'm okay.
Please let me do
this on my own.
(speaking chinese)
It looks very positive.
Members of the central
commission for
discipline inspection,
Are coming from beijing.
To open the government's
anti-corruption campaign
here, on the 31st.
This is a request for the
newspaper, I work for
to publicize the event.
It says that, "we, all citizens,
all officials, will be given the
opportunity to report anyone
"attempting to engage
in unlawful activities,
"harming the correct
administration of justice
"or the image of the
people's court."
-This is good timing.
-It is perfect timing.
The campaign is due to start
after li jun's case.
But what I can do, is run the
campaign before his case.
And that will paralyze
any attempt by quan phong,
to subvert our evidence.
We are doing okay.
Mei, I believe we can free
your brother. But...
There may be consequences on
me and my colleagues. So could
you do something for us?
I have a contact at the
new york times,
who is ready to tell our story.
As a british and
american citizen,
Your unique situation
can give her the angle
she needs.
If she calls you,
would you help her?
It will bring us support and
put our movement on the map,
in europe and america.
Would you do that for us?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Qianyi: In case of li jun,
the night club waiter
sentenced to death
For killing a nigerian trader,
11 witnesses have changed
their evidence claiming that
they were coerced
Into giving their
original statements,
Under the orders of a senior
provincial official.
In response, the party central
committee in beijing has sent
out a stern warning,
To the citizens and officials
of guangdong province...
(speaking chinese)
Any citizen or officer
of the law attempting
to corrupt the courts
Will be arrested
And will face a sentence
of life imprisonment.
(speaking chinese)
Quan shin is only
a provincial boss.
With beijing breathing
down his neck,
he's nothing.
He's beat.
(speaking chinese)
-Look, the kiosk is
almost finished.
-When will she hear?
(speaking chinese)
She's just wanting ajun
to come home.
(speaking chinese)
(door opens)
(screaming in chinese)
Did you know this
wouldn't work?
Your friend asked me about
publicizing your group,
To the new york times,
if things didn't work out.
Have you been using me? Did you
get me here to help your cause
or to help my brother?
(thunder rumbling)
(rings bell)
Mr lin.
(speaking chinese)
I thought we can't visit now.
I don't understand.
(speaking chinese)
I didn't understand why she
is looking so worried.
Because the opportunity
to visit is only given
before the execution.
That is why she is so upset.
So, when is this visit?
(speaking chinese)
Tuesday. This Tuesday.
(crying)
(speaking chinese)
(door closes)
Man: Good morning.
Jim: You don't understand
the trouble you are in.
Katherine: There's anything
anyone can
do. Least of all you.
(speaking chinese)
Jim: The chinese authorities
will come for you, if you
do not leave the country.