INTERVIEWER: Simon,
did you play a role
in Brittany's death?
FEMALE INTERVIEWER:
Was there an autopsy performed?
What kind of drugs
was she on?
Simon, had she been ill
for long?
Were there
prescription medications?
INTERVIEWER:
Simon, what killed Brittany?
You did.
You all killed her.
NEWS REPORTER:
Brittany Murphy's
tragically shocking
Hollywood death.
The entertainment world
is stunned by the loss
of this seemingly healthy
young actress.
REPORTER:  She had no history
of a heart condition.
REPORTER:  God knows what other
medication has been taken.
REPORTER:
The toxicology reports
could take weeks to complete.
REPORTER: Of course
it raises a lot of questions
and red flags.
REPORTER:
...who says she was poisoned.
It also sounds like her
difficulty with addiction, too.
( SOBS )
From the day of her birth,
Brittany
was my precious angel.
There's never been
anyone or anything
that means more to me
in this universe.
I raised her alone,
and we didn't always
have a lot at first,
but we had each other.
No, no. I, I promise
this isn't a sales call.
Hey, Ma.
So, what happened is you,
you filled out a raffle ticket.
Yeah, and...
Hello?
Well, hope your day's
been going better than mine.
It was okay.
Ready to go?
Can't you just take
one day off, baby, please?
Ma. No, please.
Ple-e-e-ase.
SHARON:
Honey, I cannot get away,
not until I make at least
one of these appointments.
I have to.
Oh, okay, well, let's see
what we can do about that.
Oh.
( GIGGLES )
Alyssa, Alyssa Cooper.
Hm.
No one over the age of 20,
maybe 25, is named Alyssa.
Means she's a young bride.
Yeah?
Uh-hm.
What?
Brit!
( CHUCKLES )
BRITTANY:
Hi, Alyssa?
My name is Sharon,
Sharon Murphy.
No, no, you don't but you are
not going to believe this.
You remember that card
that you filled out
at the bridal show
last week?
Yeah, well,
congratulations.
( CHUCKLES )
Done!
Hey, you are
really something.
( CHUCKLES )
What would I do without you?
Well, you would sell
a lot less china, crystal,
and what is it?
Cookware!
( CHUCKLES )
Can we go now?
Yes.
Now we've gone to Waterloo
and...
( GIGGLES )
I love that they're having
so much fun.
I know.
It's a good outlet
from all that performance
pressure at school.
Yeah.
And they're so good,
aren't they?
They are!
You know, Morgan's
been pressing me
to let her try out
for this soap opera in town,
but I don't know.
What do you think?
I would just keep it
a hobby now.
They're so young.
They are.
Ma, can I get some pizza
with Morgan?
Please, pretty please?
Oooh, how can we say no
to you two?
( GIGGLES )
Okay.
Are you her mother?
Yeah, I am.
Franklin Turner.
Oh.
FRANKLIN:  I'm shooting
a commercial,
and I think that your daughter
may be exactly...
Yes! I am so in!
( GIGGLES )
I am so jealous!
Uh, could you just
give us a minute...
Yeah, come on.
Let's go, girls.
...with Mr. Turner,
please?
Turn and walk.
But Mom...
Um, I'm a little surprised.
It's usually
Brittany's friend Morgan
who gets
this kind of attention.
Yeah, pretty actressy types--
you know, they come
a dime a dozen,
but your daughter has
an every-girl quality
that we're really looking for.
Plus, she can really act.
Uh, well,
I appreciate the compliments,
but she is really young
and still in school...
I hear you, but I think
she really has something.
Maybe if you just
take some time
and go talk it over
with her dad...
Well, it's just us
since she was two years old,
but I will think about it.
Great, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks.
You are so
going to be tortured now.
What happened to like,
oh, it makes a better hobby?
I know.
This should be an easy no...
But I've been so squeezed
tightly on money.
What about just
one commercial?
Yeah,
I mean one commercial,
but you've got to be careful,
Sharon.
You know that kind of
attention--
it's addictive.
Hm.
It's the attention
she thrives on.
It's got to be no.
It's a no.
Yeah, it's no.
ON T.V.:  All he does
is stare at me all day.
God knows
what he's thinking.
Charlie, eat your peas.
They're chock full
of vitamin E.
Fine.
You can do this
one commercial.
One.
( SCREAM )
Maybe we'll leave a note
for school.
This has got to be
the last time.
Seriously.
I mean, you're treating it
as if school is the hobby.
It is!
Making commercials
is hard work.
Yes, exactly,
and that's why
you don't need to do three
in one day.
It's okay, Ma,
I can handle it.
Uh, no, no.
Okay. You know what,
it isn't okay.
You need to be doing things
like school
and being with your friends
and normal things.
Since when
do you and I do normal?
( SIGHS )
You cannot keep doing this.
Uh-uh.
You're right.
We can't.
Not from New Jersey.
We have to move
to Los Angeles.
What?
L.A. is where the business is.
If I'm not there,
I'm, I'm not in the game.
The game?
What game, Brittany?
Ma, I did not take
all of these acting classes
just to sell cereal.
I, I want to be
a real actress.
SHARON:  I know, you've
wanted it your whole life,
but you are a teenager.
Okay, you, you can do this
professionally when you're 18.
Ma, you don't get it.
Okay.
( GIGGLES ) Eighteen is like
the retirement age in Hollywood.
The right time is now.
Be real, Brittany.
We can't just pick up and...
and move across country.
We don't even
know a soul in L.A.
Honey, listen to me.
Seriously,
what is keeping us here, Ma,
as long as
we have each other?
You could always
sell your china from there.
Cookware.
All right. Come on.
What difference does it make
if we are poor in New Jersey
or in Los Angeles?
( MUSIC PLAYING )
We agreed that we would
try it here for six months.
Are you even
listening to me?
( GIGGLES )
Yes, okay.
You were saying
that you were ready
to cut bait and run,
and I'm not.
( SIGHS )
Look, this world that
we are trying to live in
is not working out for us, okay?
We, we need a reality check.
( SIGHS )
( GIGGLES )
Okay.
Well right here,
there's a guest-starring role
on Murphy Brown .
Brittany Murphy
on  Murphy Brown --
you tell me
that that is not meant to be.
( STATIC ON T.V. )
( LAUGHTER )
Worse than if
we had taken that line!
Oh...
( indistinct ) funnier.
Stop it!
It was hilarious.
Your timing is perfect.
Mom, you are my mother.
You, you've gotta say that.
( GIGGLES )
I am so proud to see
my baby girl on TV,
not even selling anything!
( LAUGHTER )
You still think I need
that reality check?
I mean,
I've got an agent now,
I've got a regular gig
on Drexell's Class.
It's actually happening.
For so long nothing,
and now it's just going so fast.
Welcome to Hollywood.
( SIGHS )
You're either up
or you're down.
There is no in-between.
Joanie and Tosh say hi,
by the way.
Everyone at school
is watching your show.
It's like Jersey girl
makes good or something.
BRITTANY:
Well, the show is okay.
I'm not really
where I want to be yet,
but at least we got out
of that crappy apartment.
I just bought a house...
No way!
Oh my God, a house?
You totally
have to come visit.
Maybe your mom
will let you stay awhile.
Everyone here
is beautiful like you.
( GIGGLES )
Yeah. True.
I could never get a boy
like that, or...
I could never get
a boy like that.
Which one?
Which one's better?
Oh, I don't know, sweetie.
They're both great.
Ma, you're totally
not helping now.
Look, I only get one shot!
Brit, you're putting
way too much pressure
on yourself, okay?
I mean, i-if you don't
get this role,
you'll go back to
Sister, Sister
and, and you might even
get your own TV show.
You have options now.
Sitcoms are
really fun and all,
but if I got  Clueless ...
If you got  Clueless  what?
The world wod
open up to you?
Everyone would love you?
You'd be famous?
What is this
really all about?
I am telling you, Shad,
it's all I can do
to talk to any youse guys.
I could nevah get a...
Thank you.
Uh, I have
two more speeches prepared.
We've heard enough.
Thank you.
I could play it straight,
uh, more heartfelt, earnest.
Oh, that won't be necessary.
( PHONE RINGS )
Murphy residence.
Yes, she's...
Hold on, okay?
One second.
Your agent.
Hey, Rick.
RICK ON PHONE:  Brittany,
I just talked to the producers.
They loved you.
What?
RICK:  Guess what?
You got the part!
Are you kidding me?
RICK:
No, I'm not kidding you.
You have the part, kid.
BRITTANY:
No, that is so awesome!
( GIGGLES )
Okay, okay.
We'll talk Monday.
Thank you.
Oh!
What?
I freaking got it--
Clueless.
I'm going to be
in a real movie, Ma.
( GIGGLES )
Calm down, calm down,
remember your heart.
Sh-h-h-h!
Whew.
My baby girl's
going to be a movie star.
( SCREAM )
( LAUGHTER )
Cut, print that one.
Let's keep the breaks at 10.
've got to finish
the montage sequence today.
That was totally fun.
( GIGGLES )
Yeah, I know
it's a makeover scene,
but man, it's going to take
a whole lot of making over
for that chunky monkey
to look even halfway decent.
( WHISPERS )
Oh, there's my girl.
Ready to go?
BRITTANY:
She's so beautiful.
Yeah, she is.
But so are you,
just in a different way.
Come on.
Don't say that.
I am perky.
I am fun.
And what is wrong with that?
They didn't cast me
because I'm tall and blond
and super sexy.
They cast me because they think
that I'm pathetic enough
that even a makeover
can't fix me.
What the hell?
Where is this coming from?
Oh, honey.
Look, I know you don't have
a lot of experience with boys,
but that's not the kind of
attention you want.
Mom, don't.
You are my beauty.
You are so beautiful...
( GIGGLES )
And most importantly,
over there is Cast Services.
That's where we all eat.
This is like so surreal.
I can't believe
this is your life.
Oh, I want you
to meet someone.
Alicia, this is uh,
this is my best friend Morgan.
She's out visiting.
Love your dress.
So cute.
Oh, my gosh, thanks.
So hey, some of us are
going out after the wrap.
You should totally bring her.
We're so totally
going out with them, right?
Oh, I mean, you can
if you want, you know,
but I've got my acting
and my dance classes, so...
Seriously?
You're still taking classes.
You've already made it.
I'm not like
Alicia and you, okay?
I can't just get by
on my looks.
I have to bring it
with actual skill.
( GIGGLES )
The anniversary.
Yeah.
Can you believe it?
It's been four years.
I can't, really.
You okay?
What's going on with you?
Nothing. Just thinking about
where all the time goes.
Just thinking
about time, huh?
( GIGGLES )
Shut up!
Come on, I know you.
What's wrong?
You do.
You know, there is something
I want to talk to you about.
Okay.
I've been waiting
for the right time, but...
if there is one really.
( SIGHS )
So, last week
I had a doctor's appointment
and they found a lump,
but it's not a big deal
because they're, you know,
they caught it early enough.
Um, it's not cancer?
Oh my God! What?
Look, I'm going to,
I'm going to take care
of everything.
No, I, I need to
take care of you, okay?
You are all I have.
I've got to quit my movie.
No.
Yeah.
That's just ridiculous.
I need to be there, okay.
No, what you need
is to follow your dreams,
sweetie, please.
( SOBS )
What is the point
if I don't have you
to share it with, huh?
I'm right here.
It's going to be all right.
I just want to
stay with you.
But, it is
my last day of work,
and today
is your last treatment.
So, tomorrow everything
will go back to normal.
( CROWD NOISE )
MAN: Brittany,
Brittany, over here.
I can't see you.
MAN:
Well, I see you.
I need you to strut that carpet
like you own it
because you do.
Yes, all right.
Brittany, just remember,
everyone here
wishes they were you.
( GIGGLES )
Now tell us, who are you?
I'm Brittany,
Brittany Murphy.
MAN:
No, no.
Who ARE you?
I'm Brittany Murphy.
( CROWD NOISE )
You know, I've done
like 10 films since  Clueless,
and for some reason,
that is the only one
that people always go back to.
What is it going to take for me
to get a real part, Jackie,
not just some comedic sidekick
or running away
from a serial killer,
but I need something showy.
You know, something
to really prove myself.
I keep hearing about
this Janis Joplin pic.
Yep.
I already pitched you.
The director thinks
you're way too young.
I know I could pull it off
if he just gave me a shot.
Please, Jackie.
This is my chance
to stand out,
for people to finally
take notice of me--
not, not just critics,
but people.
I need it.
Okay.
It's not that you're
just too young.
They want to play Janis
as heroin-chic.
You mean waifish?
Skinny.
I'm having a party
at a loft downtown.
The director will be there.
Maybe you could come by and...
Seriously?
Jackie, don't mess with me.
( GIGGLES )
Really?
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
I am going to
make this happen.
Yes.
Mark my words.
Okay. Okay.
Yes.
So, Elliot,
I was thinking
of making some changes.
( CAMERA FLASHING )
Sorry, uh, do you mind?
( GIGGLES )
No, I don't,
but I'm thinking Jackie
might be a little disappointed
if she's got nothing but
a truckload of Janis pictures.
( SIGHS )
Right. Sorry.
I'm, I'm not usually
the creepy stalker type.
Hm.
It's just, I'm,
I'm such a huge, huge fan.
Of Janis Joplin?
Of Brittany Murphy.
Oh, really?
SIMON:
Seriously.
Uh,  Cherry Falls ,
Trixie, Prophecy II.
You were terrifically
miscast in all of them.
( GIGGLES )
Excuse me?
SIMON:  No, no.
I'm, I'm sorry.
It's just uh,
I thought if I was honest
about your not-so-good work,
you'd believe me
when I said
how remarkable everything else
you've done has been.
Are you actually for real?
( GIGGLES )
Um, is it, uh, okay.
Yeah.
Wow.
I can't believe I'm talking to
Brittany freaking Murphy!
I pulled strings
to get this gig, you know,
to be amongst
the movers and shakers.
What are you doing
wasting your time with me?
You should probably go
move and shake.
Right, yes.
I, uh, I suppose
I should snap a few photos
of the rest of the party.
All right.
( GIGGLES )
Hey, what's your name?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Simon, Simon Monjack.
Stop apologizing,
Simon Monjack.
Right. Sorry.
Uh, did it again.
( GIGGLES )
Nice to meet you.
You're helping out,
remember.
Oh, yeah.
Here, drink some water.
I got a phone call.
Hang on.
Okay. Great.
Take a break.
Hey, Jackie.
Seriously?
Okay, okay.
Yeah, all right.
I'll call you later.
Bye.
What is it?
The Janis Joplin project...
Yeah?
They had to put it on hold--
music rights issue.
( GASP )
I'm so sorry, honey.
Um, but the director,
he really liked me...
Yeah.
So, he's going to put me
in his next movie.
Good.
It's the lead!
Oh?
Starring Michael Douglas.
( CROWD NOISE )
INTERVIEWER: Brittany, hi.
Hi.
Quite a performance
in  Don't Say a Word .
Oh, oh, thank you so much.
So now what about
all this Oscar buzz
that we've been hearing about?
How does that feel?
( GIGGLES ) I don't even know
what to say about that.
Your necklace is so beautiful,
by the way.
( GIGGLES )
Thank you.
Uh, Brittany,
you're not known for being big
on the Hollywood party circuit.
What do you do
in your spare time?
Really, actually
I'm pretty boring.
I just like to stay at home
and hang out with my mom.
She's my best friend.
She's actually
right over there.
Marshall is nothing
like people think.
He's such a sweet
and gentle guy.
And by the way,
he's a really great actor.
Oh, really?
Well, now,
what about these rumors
of an off-set romance
between you guys?
Oh, come on.
( GIGGLES )
This house is where
Justin Timberlake
and Britney Spears live.
Okay, so are we having
tea with them or something?
( GIGGLES )
No!
Actually they're selling
and I'm buying.
SHARON: ( WHISTLES )
We're finally seeing you
for the gifted actress
that you are.
They are finally seeing me
for my inner blond.
Let's be real.
Stop it, okay?
I'm not going to let you
sell yourself short anymore.
That's enough.
You know, I don't care.
I am here
and I am not going anywhere.
I don't care how blond
or tall I have to be.
Anyway, I love it
and what I love about it most
is that it's right
over the hill from Sherman Oaks,
so I can come and see my girl
as much as I want.
Uh, no.
Ma, you are moving in with me.
Baby, I love you, I do,
but it's time for you to
establish your independence.
Do you seriously want me
to move into this huge house
all by myself?
I want you to be
your own person.
I want you
to balance your checkbook,
I want you to drive a car.
I mean, maybe even date.
Okay, all right, fine.
If you're not
moving in with me,
I guess I'm not
buying this house.
Oh, stop it!
Oh, you.
( LAUGHTER )
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Just go see inside.
( LAUGHTER )
Another bad one?
No.
It's good,
it's just not for me.
It's totally male-driven
and I'd be playing
the girlfriend.
Again.
Can I ask you a question?
Uh-hm.
How much success is enough?
We're talking about
money, not success.
You want me to stand
on my own two feet,
well, that's what I want
for me, too.
Only on screen.
I just worry that it'll
never be enough, Brittany.
( YAWN )
Good morning.
Morning.
Still jet lagged, Morgan?
I'm still getting lost
between my room and the kitchen.
You got any bacon?
TOGETHER:
No.
( SIGHS )
What is this?
BRITTANY:
It's a kale smoothie.
It's really good.
I think I'll just get
something when we go out.
Are we still going shoppin'?
Yeah, sure.
Great.
I'll get changed.
Uh, di-di, do.
Oh.
I'm just having such a hard
time relating to her now.
It makes me sad.
People change, grow apart.
I mean,
it's hard to maintain
a childhood friendship,
you know.
Yeah, but I have to.
She's home.
MORGAN:
What about this one?
Uh, I'm not sure
that's your color.
But you could still try it.
Brittany,
you're gorgeous.
Huh! You are...
Oh my God,
I so want your life!
Hey, guys.
How are you today?
It's Simon, right?
SIMON:
Right.
Well, ( GIGGLES ),
come in here.
Come say hi.
All right.
Excuse me.
But, hello there.
Hey.
Um, Guys, can you
give us a minute?
Lucky man.
Thanks.
Uh, you know, those lads,
they're not your friends.
I know that because
they're mine.
I'm nice to you guys
so you'll be nice to me.
Right.
That's what you call
a co-parasitic relationship,
but never mind that.
I honestly can't believe
that you remembered me.
You were quite memorable.
Oh.
Well, uh, for the record,
you look absolutely gorgeous.
( SIGHS )
( GIGGLES )
Come on.
Whatever happened
to that brutal honesty
thing of yours, huh?
All right.
If I'm being
completely honest--
I don't think that you need to
remake yourself.
You're so much more than
blond hair and eyelashes.
I'm not quite sure
how to take that.
It's just how I get noticed.
But that's just it.
Don't you see, I think
that you shine, Brittany.
You've nothing to prove.
( GIGGLES ) It was really
good to see you, Simon.
Likewise.
But, Brittany, I'm serious
about these guys out here.
They're not
all charming like me.
( GIGGLES )
They love to build you up now,
but when they turn--
and trust me, they will turn--
they'll do it with a vengeance.
You're sweet.
Bye, guys.
Have a good day.
( GIGGLES )
JACKIE: " Just Married" ,
it's a comedy.
BRITTANY:  I don't want to do
another silly comedy, okay.
I'm finally being recognized
as a dramatic actress.
I, I, I just need a lead.
It is a lead.
Equal footing,
co-starring role.
Well, who's the co-star?
Ashton Kutcher.
Who's that?
The dude
"where's my car?" guy.
Yes.
Oooh, uh, he has a TV show,
doesn't he?
Yes,  That '70s Show ,
and it's very popular.
Well, do you think
they have, say,
acting chops
to make Brittany look good?
I met him a few times.
He seemed nice.
He's very pretty
which makes me wonder about
our chemistry a little bit.
You being
the beast.
( MUSIC PLAYING )
It's live, gentlemen.
Get something good, okay?
Hey, Ashton.
How'd it go in there, man?
Hey, guys.
Oh, come on.
Give us something, man.
You're killing me.
Oh, Brittany.
Hey, are you and Ashton
an item off set too?
Don't believe
everything you guys publish.
Oh come on,
you guys are wearing rings.
What?
Oh, they're for the film.
They were just having fun.
And so you're uh,
you're not dating?
Take a look at him.
He could break
any heart in Hollywood.
( GIGGLES )
You're so beautiful.
Shut up!
No, I'm serious.
Hm.
What are you doing?
What?
Do you ever take
this stuff off?
You would run
for the hills.
Whoa, we already
are in the hills.
But, yeah,
you're totally right.
I would run.
I'd run.
What?
That's mean.
( GIGGLES )
Whoa!
This power couple
just got nominated.
What? Really?
Yeah.
For what?
For a Razzie Award--
worst on-screen couple.
Oh, that's just mean.
Oh my God!
It's actually
kind of hilarious.
I mean, the movie made
a truckload of money,
so the Razzie people
can suck it.
Well, you may have
just killed my career,
but we must have run
on that together, huh?
Yeah.
Question is,
what are we going to wear
to the acceptance speech?
Oh, there's always
a pair of Oompa Loompas.
Now come on,
let's get out of here.
I want to go do something.
Yes.
You guys go outside.
It is a beautiful day.
You could go hike
in the hills.
TOGETHER:
We are in the hills.
Oh, that's gross!
( LAUGHTER )
I'm gonna get dressed.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I'll never get tired
of this view.
Reminds me of when my mom and I
first moved down here
and we had all those dreams.
( GIGGLES )
Beautiful, huh?
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay, all right.
Oh, no.
You got it, guys.
Wow, okay.
Yeah.
Whoa, you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
It's just a little
dizzy spell, you know.
It'll pass.
You're all right.
You sure?
It always does, yeah.
ASHTON:
All right.
( BRITTANY LAUGHS )
Okay. I completely do not
understand this ritual.
Neither does my mom,
but I still drag her here
every year.
Yeah, well,
it's actually kind of nice.
We get some alone time.
Oh, oooh, except for
everybody staring at you.
They're staring at us.
( GIGGLES )
Thanks, Steph.
Let's see here
what we got.
Um, I ordered this burger
with extra grease...
( BRITTANY GIGGLES )
I'm sorry!
( LAUGHTER )
Who keeps texting?
Oh, the guys.
They want to know if we can
go out with them later.
Out where?
I don't know.
Dancing, clubs
or something.
Hm.
Should I tell them
we're coming?
Oh, not me.
I've got to
get back to Mom.
Okay.
Well, can I go?
I mean, I haven't seen
my friends in months.
Yeah, sure.
( SHOES DROP ON FLOOR )
I didn't know if you
were gonna come back.
Why wouldn't I?
Did you have fun?
It would've been
a lot more fun
if you were there.
Hm. ( GIGGLES )
Everybody asked about you.
Hm.
Yeah, why do I doubt that?
My friends all love you.
I just, ( SIGHS ),
I don't understand.
What happened to us between
when we first hooked up and now?
We were having fun.
I mean, now it's like we go
to some greasy spoon diner
and get the blue plate special
and then pass out.
( SIGHS ) We were playing
newlyweds in a movie.
( GIGGLES ) Okay, that is
like doing a reality show
and then thinking
that the real world
is going to be the same.
All right.
Well, look,
all I know is
that I want to be a part
of whatever world
you're a part of, okay?
Okay. I'll try.
You know I have
two more weeks
before I have to
go off to New York.
Then we better not
waste a second, huh?
( GIGGLES )
Yeah.
Mama?
SHARON: Hi, baby girl.
I'll be right there.
There's my beauty.
I'm so glad you're home.
Hm.
Why didn't you call me?
I would have picked you up.
Mwah!
The studio sent a car, so...
Oh, but where's Ashton?
Uh, well, we decided
to call it quits.
Oh, sweetie,
I'm so sorry.
What happened?
( SIGHS ) We were just
too different, you know?
I always felt like
I was dragging him down.
He likes to be
out and about.
I like to stay at home.
Sweetie, let me make you
something to eat, okay?
That's fine, Mom.
Brittany?
Hi.
What happened?
You fainted.
( SIGHS ) Um, the doctor said
it was a combination of
hypoglycemia
and chronic anemia,
probably from the horrible
periods that you have.
It's not my heart murmur?
No, no, no, no.
We're just going to have you
eat much more frequent meals
throughout the day,
get you
some iron supplements.
Hi.
BRITTANY: Hi.
My God, Brit.
You gave us such a scare.
Oh, girl, I know.
I, I am fine.
What's going on?
The tabloids know
you're here.
I just fainted.
What...?
Why do they care?
( SIMULTANEOUS TALKING )
Stop it, stop it.
REPORTER:
We just want to know.
Get security.
Back off, back off,
back off.
Brittany,
it's me, Simon.
Come here.
I've got a car.
Back away, back away.
Brittany, are you
a drug addict?
Back off, back off.
Hey, back off.
We're doing our job!
Are you better
than us now, Simon?
No. Get out of here!
Sorry. I don't do
that kind of work anymore.
I tried to warn you, Brit.
The paparazzi,
they're not your friends.
( DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING )
I can't believe
what people are saying.
Is Brittany a drug addict?
I have never been so famous.
Or infamous.
Sweetie, you don't have to
read this trash, okay?
Just focus on getting better.
Don't listen to those idiots.
I just had no idea
people could be so mean.
They smelled blood
in the water
and they attacked,
just like sharks.
Yeah.
I honestly thought
that those guys were my friends.
I should have
just listened to Simon.
Thank God he was
looking out for me.
( DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING )
( CROWD NOISE )
MAN 1:  Brittany, Brittany,
over here.
Over here, come on.
I can't,
I can't see you.
MAN 1:  Come on, Brittany.
Over here.
Look right over here
by the light.
All right, but I see you.
I can't see you.
MAN 1:  Come on, Brittany.
Look right here.
I see you and everyone here
sees this, all those people.
They all wish they were you.
MAN 2:  Who are you, Brittany?
Brittany, who are you?
MAN 3:
Tell us who you are.
MAN 3:  Brittany, come on.
Who are you?
( BRITTANY GASPS )
( CROWD NOISE )
Hi.
Brittany, hi.
Good.
How are you?
So, tell me about
where you met Dakota.
Dakota is amazing.
She is only nine years old.
( GIGGLES )
Can you believe that?
Uh, about your recent
hospitalization--
how are you doing now?
Much better.
Thank you.
As you know, some have said
that it was drug-related.
I have never taken drugs.
I, I couldn't
even if I wanted to
because I have
this heart condition.
Yes, but...
I'd, I'd really much rather
just talk about
my movie projects.
( SIGHS ) Okay, well,
what do you have coming up?
I'm about to start a film
called  Little Black Book .
I'm really excited about it
because I get to sing
and then I'm doing a voice
in an animated feature
called Happy Feet .
I get to sing in that, too.
I love to sing.
BRITTANY:
Doing voiceover work
is so much fun!
And guess what else?
SHARON:
What?
I am the new
Jordache jeans girl.
Oh, aw, oh, baby!
Oh my gosh!
How can you take
all these ups and downs and...
I can't.
That's why it's got to be
nothing but up from now on.
Guess I won't be
needing these anymore.
Antidepressants?
Hey, I'll be right back.
Hey!
I just,
Where you going?
I've got to go
to the pharmacy.
Oh, let me go with you.
No, no, no, no.
They're, they're
going to close.
I'll be right back.
Love you.
( DOOR CLOSES )
Love you, too.
Oh!
It's back, isn't it?
Oh, sweetie.
( SIGHS )
I didn't want to
bring you down.
Everything's going up
for you right now.
( BRITTANY SOBS )
Hey, I'm going to get you
through this, okay?
I'm strong, okay,
and I don't want you
putting your career on hold.
I don't have a career
until I know
that you are well again.
Oh, sweetie.
( SIGHS )
( SOBS )
How bad?
It's bad.
( PHONE RINGS )
Honey, you need to
call Jackie.
Have her do
a press release
so that people know
you're with me here.
No, Ma.
Hey, I'm not going to
use your illness.
They can say
whatever they want.
This is my business.
I just need you
to get better.
That's my baby.
I love you.
Some more green tea.
Lots of antioxidants.
Oh, please stop
fussing over me.
Being out of sight,
out of mind
is not a very good thing
in this town.
Did you at least
call Jackie back?
I left messages.
Oh, Brittany.
I did.
( PHONE RINGS )
Well, who is it here?
Oh!
Hello.
( MOTHER COUGHS )
I'm sor--
who...
What? Who's...
No, no comment.
What's going on?
Reporter asking for a comment
of I don't...I mean...
( PHONE RINGS )
What now?
Oh, my goodness.
Should I decline this?
Yes.
( SIGHS )
Some gossip reporter has blogs
that a well-known actress
got loaded out of her mind
at a Hollywood party
and had sex with the
cater waiter in the stairwell.
They're saying
that it was me.
Oh, please.
Sweetheart, that's insane.
You've been
in the hospital with me
morning, noon, and night.
You can't...
I don't know whether to laugh
or cry at the idea
that I left your hospital room
to go out and get loaded
and have anonymous sex.
( SIGHS ) Brittany,
we're going to call Jackie,
and she will know how to
straighten all this out, okay?
How could anyone
who actually knows me
believe that I would do that?
( PHONE RINGS )
( SIGHS )
( PHONE CONTINUES TO RING )
I told you
that would blow over,
just like the last
silly scandal did, right?
You should not be up, okay?
What do you need?
It feels good
to get out of bed.
I'd been laying there all day.
( SIGHS )
Oh, sweetie.
I want you to smile.
At least you got
a retraction, right?
Ma, that doesn't mean
anything, okay?
( DOORBELL RINGS )
People believe
what they want to believe.
( DOOR BANGS SHUT )
SHARON:
What, what is it?
They're,
they're dropping me.
Who's dropping you?
I don't...
My agents...
And Jackie.
No way, Brittany.
She's...
Ma, it's right here, okay?
I'm telling you.
It's over.
I was just thinking because
someone said he was so cute.
All right.
Could I ask you why you
wouldn't want to take me on?
No, I understand.
Thank you.
Yeah, you too.
That was a third-tier agency.
Wouldn't even touch me.
( SOBS )
I, I don't understand.
You're a big star, sweetie.
I was a big star, Ma, okay,
but apparently
everyone has moved on.
Why, because
you took care of me?
No, Ma, it's not
about you, okay?
It-- don't put this
on yourself.
It's Jordache junkie
and those stupid rumors.
Those freaking tabloids.
What did I do wrong?
( SIGHS ) Why do they
hate me so much?
( LOW CHATTER )
Thank you so much
for coming to meet me.
Of course.
As I mentioned,
I'm no longer a photographer.
Well, other than
for my own pleasure,
but I've had a bit of success
as a producer and screenwriter.
I've just had the film
Factory Girl
released this last year,
and that inspired me to write
this script about Sigmund Freud.
Which I loved,
by the way.
Thank you so much.
To be blunt,
I want you for the lead role,
for the opera singer here.
( COUGHING )
You all right?
Uh, she's a wonderful character,
and I love to sing,
but I'm sure you know
that it's impossible to raise
money on my name anymore.
Well, you just need
a fresh start.
We'll find the money somehow.
The most important part
is to find the right person
for the role,
and I know that that's you.
Wow, I appreciate
your vote of confidence in me,
but why do you think that I'm
so perfect for the part?
Your vulnerability.
I know you normally play
much tougher characters,
but I see the vulnerable
Brittany hiding inside of you.
That's the Brittany I want.
( BRITTANY GIGGLES )
Well, we have
talked the night away.
Yes.
Yeah. Um, we're going to
have to table this
until I get back
from New York.
Right.
Um, you're going to New York?
In the morning, yeah.
I'm going to direct
a DVD thing.
It's the best
I can get these days.
I wonder if you remember
the first time we met.
How could I forget?
You were my worst critic.
( GIGGLES )
Yes, but before that.
Your first red carpet.
What? You're not talking
about the  Clueless  premiere?
Yes.
Oh my God, that was you?
I had an inkling
that there was a star
inside of you.
That was a real
turning point for me.
I really felt
that you saw me.
Uh, right.
Um, well,
good luck in New York,
and we'll talk more
when you get back, yeah.
New York--
I detest flying.
I could go with you
if you'd like.
Mom!
Hey.
Hey, Mom.
So, I brought home
two surprises...
Ready.
Surprise number one...
( GIGGLES )
Surprise number two.
Oh, ha.
No. Really.
( GIGGLES )
That's great!
( KETTLE WHISTLES )
( BRITTANY GIGGLES )
On our way home,
we were waiting to board,
and Simon
popped the question.
I still can't believe
you said yes.
When you know no.
Simon is an amazing man.
He has made a fortune
buying and selling art.
Really?
BRITTANY:  Yeah.
I thought you were
a photographer.
BRITTANY:
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I've dabbled
in a number of things.
He's dabbled.
Most recently
writing and producing.
In fact, I've just had
the film  Factory Girl
released this last year.
Have you heard of it?
No, I have not.
So what,
what other things?
All right.
Where to start?
No, no.
Let me help. Please.
Okay.
Thank you, Simon.
Sharon, I know this must
all seem rather sudden to you.
That's an understatement.
You know, Brittany
is extremely vulnerable
and fragile right now.
And you're worried that
I'm taking advantage of that.
I don't blame you
for wondering.
Hm.
Plus, she's always had
a flair for the dramatic,
and you've been
her knight in shining armor
once before, right?
Look, I'm no Ashton Kutcher.
I don't have
Hollywood good looks,
but I really do love Brit
and I want to marry her
with all my heart.
Well, you've gained
her trust.
That's not easy to do
these days.
She knows I have
her best interest at heart.
If you do, could you please
slow this train down.
Hm, I've tried.
Believe me, I've tried.
Can I help it if she finds me
so irresistible?
( LAUGHTER )
Look, I'm sure you know
that Brittany is famously tied
to my apron strings,
but we are a package deal,
like it or not.
Sharon, I would have it
no other way.
( SMACKS KS )
( GIGGLES )
What are you thinking?
I don't know.
I just-- I've so many ideas
running through my head
of ways to
reboot your career.
Hm.
I just-- I want people
to love you again, you know.
To see you
the way that I do.
Honey, the front yard
is too small.
It's not going to accommodate
this big of an event.
Which is why we cut
the guest list down, way down.
Simon says
we should only invite friends
who've been loyal.
Real friends.
Simon says, Simon says.
Where's Simon's list?
I-his family,
they live mostly in the UK.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We're right in the middle
of something really import...
Ma, it's okay.
Did you want a picture?
No, I'm not looking for
a picture or an autograph,
just to warn you.
You're seeing
Simon Monjack?
Is this really
any of your business?
What, are you a reporter?
No!
How well do you know
Mr. Simon "Conjack"--
I mean, that's what
my friends call him.
Has he told you
about his other fiancées,
the broken hearts
he's left strewn
on both sides
of the Atlantic?
Ooh, I assume
that you're one of them.
I think maybe
it's a good idea...
SHARON:
You need to walk away.
Get out of here.
No, not until
I've said my piece.
That's okay.
Has he told you
about the lawsuits,
the unpaid bills,
rent he's skipped out on?
And you might want to
talk to the FBI.
There's a complaint or two
on file...
I'm leaving.
At least
talk to his family.
SHARON:  Leave now!
Ask them
how he went through
all of their money
before he started
bilking everyone else's.
Simon is a manipulative con man
who victimizes trusting people.
You need to know that.
And get that ring appraised.
It is a cubic zirconia,
for sure.
I'm sorry.
God.
That was crazy.
Um...
Uh...
( DEEP BREATH )
You're engrossed, I see.
Um, why did you
give me this to read?
Because it's excellent
and you will be excellent in it.
It's a horror film, okay.
You know
I don't want to do horror.
It creeps me out.
I know, but dear,
we have to start somewhere,
rebuilding you.
To do that, I need you
to trust me.
Something's wrong?
Nope, nothing.
I just want to
get through this tonight.
The script
you don't want to do.
All right.
I give in.
What is it?
I-I'm just really tired
I think
from all the wedding plans.
Okay? Good night.
Love you.
Love you, too.
Thank you.
Uh, I'm a lightweight on that.
All right.
So whose deal is it?
Yours,
you know I suck.
All right, great.
( DOORBELL RINGS )
I'll get it.
( DOORBELL RINGS AGAIN )
Yes?
Murphy residence?
It, it is.
US Department of Immigration
and Customs Enforcement.
Is there a Simon Monjack
living here?
Um, it's all right, Brit.
What's this about?
You have the right
to remain silent.
to an attorney.
Mom, Mom! Si-Simon,
what's happening?
Brittany, get me
an attorney.
I'll be needing a good one.
This is a private residence.
We have a warrant.
A war-- Ma.
SIMON:  Brittany,
call an attorney.
Where are you taking him?
At least tell me
where you're taking him.
Look, I'm not
an immigration attorney,
but I can tell you
it's a legitimate arre.
He's been living here
under an expired visa.
So how do we get it renewed?
It's not that simple,
and even if it were,
there are a lot of other
allegations against him.
What other allegations, John?
( SIGHS )
John, just tell me.
He's alleged to owe
back rent and other debts
in excess of
half a million dollars.
So I guess what that woman
told us was true, Brit.
It's the tip of the iceberg.
I mean, he was charged with
credit card fraud in Virginia,
though those charges
were later dropped.
Which means
they may not be true.
the charges were dropped.
He knows a lot of people,
okay.
He, he, he's been
rebooting my career.
I read a script
that he wrote.
Look, it is true that he has
an executive producer title
and story-by writing credit
on a film,
but he had to sue
to get them.
So I can't say
how legitimate those are.
You are not the first person
he's done this to.
He's a true genius.
He just happens to be
a genius con man.
Brittany,
I've got to ask,
I mean, you're young,
beautiful, wealthy, famous.
I mean, how'd you get tangled up
with a character like Monjack?
Just tell me what I have to do
to get him out.
Brit, I don't know.
I think I need to explain
some of the things
that you've heard
and then I'll get my things
if you want.
I don't want to hear
any of it.
I just want to fix it.
Mazel tov!
( APPLAUSE )
SHARON:  Everyone,
I'd love to introduce
Brittany
and Simon Monjack,
soulmates
and partners for life.
( APPLAUSE )
What is it?
They found out.
Who?
Everyone.
Simon, I wanted to control
when we announced our marriage,
but someone leaked it.
When I was younger,
all I wanted was for people
to pay attention to me.
Now, oh God, I just wish
they would leave me alone.
Oh God!
You just need to take it
in stride, all right?
Fight back
when the time is right.
They're saying you cast
a spell on me and Mom.
Maybe I have.
Honestly,
you must be a bit crazy.
It's the only way to explain
why you'd want to be with me.
Besides Mom,
you were the only one
that I knew for sure
loves me without question.
( SIGHS )
I, I know you don't
want to hear this,
but I want to be
100% honest with you
because I, I really
want this to work.
Simon, don't.
All of those dirty,
horrible, terrible things
you've heard about me--
they're true,
every last one of them.
I guess you could say I've been
a bit of a sociopath.
That doesn't matter, okay?
Hey, the past is the past.
Right.
Right, that's the point.
When I'm with you,
you make me want to be
a better man,
and with you
I will be, I am.
From now on...
let me protect you,
all right?
No more, no more blogs
or tabloids, all right.
Let's shut the haters
out of our lives.
And the fake friends.
Fake friends, too.
Stand up.
Ah, gorgeous.
There we are.
Oh, darling,
I love dressing you.
( HELICOPTER WHIRRING )
Why won't they
leave me alone?
Just get...
make them go away.
Honey?
Hm.
Got some lunch for you.
Uh-uh.
No. Not hungry.
Oh, you have to
eat something.
Brittany,
it's not healthy for you
to just lay around here
all day.
Did you take your medicine?
Yeah, yeah,
I think so.
( SIGHS )
These antidepressants
don't seem to be working
that well anymore.
I'm going to call
the doctor back.
No, Ma. No doctors.
Please, Ma.
( DOOR BANGING SHUT )
SIMON:  See! I've done it!
I finally made it happen.
You, my dear,
have got a movie.
I know.
Happy Feet Two .
I can't wait...
No, no, no.
Wait, what is this?
This, this is a thriller,
small budget
but very, very good.
We leave for Puerto Rico
in a week's time.
So...
But Puerto Rico.
Simon, baby,
you know I hate flying
and over the water.
I know, I know,
but it's all right.
We'll both be with you--
your mom and I.
I'll be doing your hair
and makeup for the film.
We'll make a vacation of it,
all right?
Just read the script.
No, I don't have to.
I could...
I just want to work.
That's my girl.
( GIGGLES )
You did it!
Have you seriously
come back here
every one of the past
18 years?
( GIGGLES )
We missed one or two times
while Brittany was shooting,
but we always came back
to make up for it.
Yeah.
It's exactly the same.
( SIGHS )
Nothing's changed.
( GIGGLES )
BRITTANY:
Everything has changed.
You just don't see it.
Why don't you mind your
own business and bugger off.
Hey, everybody.
SHARON:
Ashton.
Hi, Sharon.
Hey, how are you?
SHARON:
Good to see you.
ASHTON:  Good to see you.
Oh!
Simon, hey.
Come here.
What are you doing here?
It's the one time a year
I know where to find you guys.
Uh, join us.
Uh, I'd love to.
I can't stay very long.
I'm actually producing
a pilot for a TV show.
SHARON:
Congratulations.
That's wonderful.
BRITTANY:
Good for you.
Thank you.
Yeah, we're actually
in the casting process
right now
and your name came up.
I think you'd be great for the.
Thanks, mate,
but we're um,
we're just now rebooting
Brittany's future career.
Don't think it's quite time
to go back to TV.
Well, I hope
you'll think about it
because you'd be great.
Of course
she'll think about it.
Thank you.
SHARON:
It's so good to see you.
You too.
Yeah.
And to have food together.
Okay.
We've got to see
each other more often.
SHARON:
Yeah.
I just want to
say something.
Ashton, wait.
Wait a second.
( GIGGLES )
Hey, Brittany.
How are you?
Are you...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You know
you can't believe
all the stuff
that you hear out there.
Yeah.
And, I'm good.
We're good.
You know, I never stopped
caring about you.
You know that, right?
Yeah. Me too.
But I have my Mom,
and Simon
really cares about me.
Yeah, of course, right.
Hey...
do you think if we had won
that Razzie, ( GIGGLES )
if we would have shown up
to accept it in person...
Definitely.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Get out of here.
( GIGGLES )
I don't want to
come here again, okay?
( SIGHS )
Ever.
Can we go?
( GUNSHOTS )
Simon, Simon!
Wake up, wake up!
There's gunshots.
I can hear the gunshots.
What do you want?
Huh?
SIMON:  Brit, Brit.
Do you hear that?
Simon, do you hear that?
It's just a car backfiring.
( YELLING )
Leave us alone!
Brittany, stop.
Stop it.
Leave me alone!
Brittany, stop.
It's just a car.
OFFICER:
So basically the bangs
were just a generator
misfiring.
It's from all those
bloody power outages.
Officer, I swear,
I heard gunshots.
I did.
Ma'am, is there any reason
that you'd believe
someone would
want to harm you?
Darling, you're safe,
all right?
No one's going to hurt you.
Thank you so much,
officer.
Sorry for your trouble.
Okay.
You folks try to have
a good evening.
You too.
Here.
What, what is that?
It's just a beta blocker.
These are your heart pills?
Yes. It'll calm you down.
I'm so embarrassed.
Brit, there's no need
to be embarrassed.
I'm right here,
all right?
You're safe.
I'll never
leave your side.
( WHISPERS )
You promise?
I promise.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
SIMON:
Wake up.
Is she sleeping?
No, uh, we'll need
another five though.
It's just the jet lag.
Yeah, yeah.
Take your time.
Thank you.
Um, it's all right, baby,
but it is important
that you remember your lines
this time, all right?
Shall we go over them?
You told me that this was
going to be a thriller.
Simon, I told you
I don't want to do
another horror film.
It's changed a bit
since I first read it,
but don't worry,
you are going to be
wonderful in it.
All right?
Promise.
Just give me a moment.
It is important
that we're mindful
of Brittany's
mandated breaks.
Her mandated breaks?
Yes.
( LAUGHTER ) You're,
you're kidding me, right?
No.
Okay.
We're in Puerto Rico.
This is not the Fox lot.
I'm aware of that.
This is an ultra
low-budget film, man.
I'm well aware of the budget
of this picture.
I can't get my star
of my movie
to know one line of dialogue
for more than five minutes?
She knows her lines, okay?
That is when she's
not too busy sleeping.
Are you drunk?
Are you kidding me?
Of course not.
Simon, please.
It's just how
unprofessional you are!
I'm calling a wrap
for today, guys.
Uh, we'll pick up
everything tomorrow.
You don't need
to do that.
Mandated breaks.
She'll be fine
by tomorrow.
It's all right.
We'll go home.
We'll get a bit of rest,
all right?
DIRECTOR:
Good morning.
BRITTANY:  Good morning.
How you doing?
Great.
Good morning.
Um, there has been
a slight change of plans.
You're not allowed
back on set anymore.
Uh, what?
It's, it's all right.
I'll sort this out.
She's not going on
without me, so...
Hey, that's completely fine,
and I understand,
but we don't need her anymore.
She's been replaced.
You can't do that!
Yes, I can.
I can do that
because we're making a film.
Very little time to make it.
Nobody's going to
put up with her drama.
How dare you!
No, let's just go, okay?
This whole thing has been
a train wreck anyway.
Take care.
( MUSIC PLAYING )
( COUGHING )
Home.
Bloody airplanes.
Yeah, now you know
how I feel.
My head
is about to explode.
Okay, off to bed
with you two, okay?
I'm going to make some soup.
Oh, baby,
you don't have to do that.
I insist.
The least I can do
is open up a can
and heat up some soup, huh.
It's my turn
to take care of you.
I'm worried about her.
She's acting like
nothing happened.
I mean, these mood swings
are getting worse and worse.
I'll talk to the doctor
about her medication.
Meanwhile,
off to bed with us.
Survived two bouts of cancer,
but for some reason,
she acts like this cold
is going to kill her.
Simon?
What's going on?
Simon, what's wrong?
Mom, ma, come here!
SHARON:
What?
BRITTANY:  Simon, please,
Simon, please!
SHARON:
What-- is he having a seizure?
No. I don't know.
I think he's having a heart--
a heart attack or something.
Help me get him
on the floor.
I'm going to perform CPR.
( GROANS )
Oh my God!
Call 9-1-1, mom,
call 9-1-1.
Okay, okay.
Oh, Simon.
( GROANS )
We have an emergency.
Don't die, I need you.
Someone's having
a heart attack.
Simon, Simon.
Please, please, no.
I know it was just
a mild heart attack,
but it was quite
the wake-up call.
We have got to
get you in shape.
( COUGHING )
Both of us then, right.
No, it's just a cold.
I will live.
That's the spirit, Brit.
You've been acting
a bit manic lately.
Have you been
taking your meds?
No, I decided
to go off them.
They make me feel
spacey and stuff.
Where are you going?
The premiere
for that little film
I did last summer is tonight,
Across the Hall .
Remember?
I thought you
begged out of it.
That was before I...
When I thought I was going to be
shooting in Puerto Rico,
but now that I am here,
I feel like
I should go support it.
Plus Mama's better enough
to take me, so...
Oh, I don't like it.
( GROANS )
But at least
take your meds.
( GROANS )
A bit of this cold medicine
works wonders.
Simon, honey,
you go back to bed.
Okay? You have a fever
and a bad heart.
So do you.
On both counts.
All right. Look...
Hm?
I'm not going to let you
face the wolves alone.
I'm coming with.
Okay?
First, let's find you
something
just a bit different to wear,
all right?
Perhaps you go back to blond.
BRITTANY:
And so in that way,
it already had
a cult following.
Good-bye.
Thanks so much.
Excuse me, Brittany.
Hi.
Hi. How are you?
I'm good, thank you.
Let me ask you.
So with all of these rumors
and innuendos
that seem to follow you,
how do you rise above it?
High heels.
( LAUGHTER )
No, no.
Um, seriously,
I have a wonderful
husband and mom.
I spend more time with them
than anybody else.
They keep me grounded.
Any plans for the new year?
I'd like to be
somewhere cold.
I miss the winters back East.
Actually, I do have
a New Year's resolution.
I want to have a baby,
start a family.
SHARON:
Britt, don't ruin a good night.
Stay off your phone.
Bloggers are still saying
I was difficult
on the set of "The Caller".
They fired me.
They're saying
you were drunk, Simon.
People cannot tell
the difference
between a freaking
SNL parody and the truth.
More people
saw that sketch
than my last five films
combined.
I thought we swore off
looking at the online trash.
Come on.
How are those cramps, baby?
BRITTANY:
They're worse than ever.
Oh my God!
What?
They're saying I've been
replaced on  Happy Feet Two .
They, they can't do that,
right, Simon?
They can't-- that is all
I have right now.
Well, sweetie,
it's probably not even true.
No, mom.
It's all over the place,
it's everywhere.
I hate this city.
Maybe it is time
for us to go home.
I could do Broadway.
Maybe even some community
theater if I had to.
Simon, we could
start our family.
No more anniversary dinners
at that crappy diner, Mom.
Let's go.
Let's get out.
Are you really
serious this time?
I'm on board.
I just want to see you happy,
right?
BRITTANY:  They won.
They got what they wanted.
Darling, it's been
almost two weeks.
( SIGHS )
You're only getting worse.
( COUGHING )
Here you go, hon.
Okay.
Sweetie, we need to
call the doctor.
No.
Yes.
Please, Brit.
Listen to your Mum.
No. They will just
call me a drug addict.
I don't, please Mom, no.
Okay, then I'm just going to
call him again about it.
I'll be right back.
Yes.
( COUGHING )
Here.
Brit, just take a sip.
( COUGHING )
Brit, Brit.
You sound very bad.
We can't let...
Should we take her
to the ER?
( COUGHING )
No, no hospital.
SHARON:  Sweetie, we cannot see
the doctor till Monday.
( COUGHING )
No! They'll call me
a junkie again.
SHARON:
Sweetie.
( COUGHING )
You're all right.
( CHOKING NOISES )
Brittany.
Sharon.
( YELLING )
Sharon!
We need your help, Sharon!
Baby?
I don't know
what she's saying.
You can't breathe?
Okay, okay.
Sit down.
( COUGHING )
Okay, baby, just sit.
Brittany, sit down.
Don't leave me.
I don't-- I really don't
feel good right now.
Just stay with me.
Okay.
( indistinct )
We'll see what we can do.
Prop up the pillows
really high so she can...
( COUGHING )
Don't leave me, Mom, don't.
No, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just try and relax, please.
Just try to relax.
Just relax.
( DOOR CLOSES )
She's still in there?
Yes.
I got her some tea.
I think we just
need to get all packed up
and get the hell
out of here, right?
Oh, yeah, I'll fly back,
wrap everything up.
( RUNNING WATER )
( THUD )
Brit?
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
Brittany,
I have some tea for you.
Oh my God!
( SHOUTS ) Simon!
( MUSIC PLAYING )
( HOWLS )
Oh my God!
( MUSIC PLAYING )