I've heard that you get
a lot of letters from kids.
-Have you gotten these
kind of visits and letters
-Sure.
-from kids that
you don't know?
-Sure
Why do you think
these kids write you?
Because I am those kids.
What is it about you
that they...
I am a child.
I never grew up.
I never lived in your society.
I never went to school.
I never had
a mother and father.
I raised myself up.
What do you think
it is about you that makes
people want to be a part of
whatever it is
you're a part of?
I'm brand new.
Everything I do
is always brand new.
♪
Okay, you get the tickets,
I'll get the reservations.
Okay?
Okay, good.
Talk to you soon.
-Lindsay.
-Yeah.
Um, did you get
the Rodel file?
-Yes. I set it on
your desk behind you.
-Okay. Thank you.
Um, also, Pat McGroin called
and he said that he had to
push back his meeting.
Pat McGroin.
Yeah.
He called earlier today.
"Pat my groin?"
This is my brother.
He's playing a joke on you.
Well, he sounds like a riot.
Anyways, um,
he's coming to town tonight.
So that's why he's
messing with us right now.
I didn't know
you had a brother.
Yeah. Conrad.
Never...
Never heard the name.
♪
Uh...
Max drew this
in our class today.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
Is there anything
going on with him at home
that might be
upsetting him in
any way or...
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you.
Are you, by chance,
going to Los Angeles?
-No.
-No? Sweet.
Are you, by chance,
going South?
I'm looking for a ride.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
If you keep doing this,
they're going to kick you
out of school.
Is that what you want?
Max?
Hey, hey!
I'm talking to you.
Hey, baby.
How are you?
Did you have a good day?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Good.
-You okay?
-I'm good.
Expect for the fact that
our son's a sociopath.
♪
And when does he get here?
I don't know anything.
I don't know
what he's doing here.
I don't know where
we're gonna put him.
What, we can
put him in the office?
I... I wanna
work this weekend.
I can't have him
in the office.
-Well, maybe you shouldn't
work this weekend.
-It's besides the point.
It could be
five in the morning
before he's here.
All right. Then it'll be
five in the morning when
he gets here. That's fine.
I'm just saying,
there's like no heads up,
there's no consideration
for anybody else.
It's like with Dad's funeral.
Maybe that's why he's coming.
He's coming to make amends
and apologize for
not being at the funeral.
-Yeah, that's probably
why he's coming.
-Oh. Sarcasm.
No, I'm just saying...
I'm, like...
I appreciate
the positive spin,
but, like...
I think it'll be fun.
It'll be the first time
we've spent
real quality time
with him since...
probably... Well,
probably our wedding.
-Oh, my God.
-What?
The wedding gift
that he gave us?
That... thing.
Oh.
Ow. Fuck.
That's... No, now
you've gone too far.
That's good right there.
-Like that? This?
-Yeah. Yeah.
Ooh, that's a lot.
- It's too much.
-No.
We should maybe, like,
not put it over the mantle.
No, no, no, it's fine.
And well, anywhere
you put it in the house,
it's gonna look
out of place, so...
-Okay. I just feel like
he's gonna figure it out.
-Above the mantle's...
No. No!
It's gonna make him happy
to see it there.
- Okay.
-You heard that?
-Yeah.
- He's in the house.
-Why are you whispering?
'Cause I don't want him
to see what we're doing.
You gotta hide the toolbox,
you gotta get away from
the painting.
What... How do you know
he's in the house?
Because the door
downstairs is open,
that's how he got in.
-I thought we just
left the door open.
-No, no, no, no, no.
He's in here.
When we were kids,
he would sneak into the house
before I got home from school,
and he'd scare
the fuck out of me.
It's happening right now.
Okay, just...
You need to settle down...
You fucking dick.
--Is the knife necessary?
You just shit your pants,
didn't you?
-It's good to see you.
-Hi. It's good to
see you, too.
Wow. Are you serious?
What's that doing there?
It's hanging up.
That... Wow.
People comment on it
all the time, right?
It's really meaningful.
That was so nice of you guys.
I don't paint anymore,
but that one's not bad.
What are you talking about?
I don't paint, you know.
It's like, what's the point?
-You quit? Like,
you quit being an artist?
-Why?
Well, um,
I'm writing a book
called On The Road and...
-Two? On The Road 2?
-On The Road 2.
I know who
Jack...Jack Kerouac is.
I know. I know.
I mean, seriously,
I actually sold all my stuff,
and, um, just...
Got rid of everything,
all my art supply stuff,
my records, and...
Yeah, anyway.
Wait, what about your boss?
Your boss is cool
with you doing this?
Like, she just is cool
with you taking
three weeks off?
Well, you're gonna love this,
but I actually quit my job.
That makes me feel
so much better that
you've quit your job.
- I think it's awesome.
-      -I know!
How irresponsible to quit
your job at the bookstore!
No, it's not irresponsible.
This is the time in your life
where you're supposed to be
untethering yourself.
You know, when you're 40
you gotta break free.
-You're being sarcastic
and it's just mean.
-I'm just... I'm...
-I'm not being mean.
-You are being mean!
You're being sarcastic
and condescending.
You don't have anything
to worry about. All right?
I am worried. You...
You don't have a house,
you don't have
any possessions,
you don't have a job.
I have a job with an
environmental organization
in Death Valley.
- Are you serious?
-Oh.
Yeah. I just thought
I'd pass through
and say hi to you guys.
-That's really good.
I'm happy for you.
-Yeah.
You wanna come,
get set up in the office?
-Why?
-For sleeping.
Um,
well, I just thought
I'd camp out there.
You're gonna camp
in the backyard?
Is that okay?
Um, I guess.
All right, well, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go to bed.
I have to get up early.
I have a huge day tomorrow.
Speaking of that,
I wanted to talk to
you about tomorrow.
Uh, I mean,
I know it's Friday,
but I was hoping
you could move
some things around.
Because I have an idea.
Something for us to do.
- Okay.
-Yeah.
Well, you know Charles Manson?
Uh, yeah,
I know who Charles Manson is.
Well, there are these sites
all around the city,
um, that I was hoping
we could go to.
I have it all mapped out.
It's amazing 'cause,
like, no one knows
that, like, right there,
you know, that's
the LaBianca house, you know.
Or the Tate house.
Wait, these are
the murder site houses?
You... You're acting
so uptight, this is
a thing people do.
No, they don't.
No, this is the thing that
weird conspiracy people do.
Trust me, I have friends
that come into LA all the time.
We've never...
- Manson has never even come up.
Okay. Uh, guilty, Your Honor.
I am interested in this,
and you're my brother,
and I just thought
we could do this together.
I'm just gonna
be in town tomorrow.
Then I'm going out to my job.
Charles Manson
set into motion a wave of
terror in Southern California.
In two nights,
Manson's murderous spree
took the lives
of at least seven people,
including actress Sharon Tate.
Manson was portrayed as
a guitar-playing ex-convict
with a following of
runaway young women,
his so-called family members.
The cult, or family,
spoke of launching a holy war
against the rich
and the powerful.
The Tate-LaBiance murders
were bizarre and merciless.
They triggered a public panic
and raised the specter
of drug-crazed youths
slaughtering their victims
at random.
Hey.
What are you doing
in my yard?
- It's mine.
You remember me?
I'm your uncle, Conrad.
No? Oh. How old are you now?
Mmm.
Eight? Seven? Six? Five?
You're going back in time.
You're a time traveler.
Seven? Wow.
He's always been
into stuff like this.
Like, even when he was a kid,
he was into "Faces of Death".
You know what that is?
Yeah. It's horrible.
Yeah, and like,
death metal, and...
I don't know. He was
into 9/11 for a long time.
It's just, he's like...
Just anything with death in it,
you know. He's like
all about it.
-So.
-What's the camera for?
I was thinking
I could get him
to take some pictures.
-In an artistic way?
-Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Get the ball rolling,
kinda, inspire him.
Well, that's kind of sweet.
What's the painting you put up?
What do you mean?
You haven't seen that before?
No.
Huh. Oh.
Figures.
What's it about?
Well, it was...
It was a way to show
how I felt growing up.
Like, I felt sort of
like this little kid there,
- with a weird face
that didn't belong.
Why didn't you belong?
Well... You know
I was adopted, right?
No.
My parents, your grandparents,
they couldn't have kids.
And so they adopted me.
But then
a couple of years later,
your grandma got pregnant
with your dad.
He's their real son.
And they were so happy
that he was born, that, um,
they sort of forgot about me.
That's not nice.
No.
Okay, so I've got
the whole day planned out.
First we go to the Tate house
then the LaBianca house.
Then, if you're into it,
um, tomorrow, we could drive
out to the desert together.
What's that book?
Well, this is Helter Skelter.
You know, the classic.
It's got all, um,
the police reports
and testimonies,
stuff like that.
-It's actually Mom and Dads'.
-Really?
Yeah, it was in Dad's office.
I went into it one day
and I opened it up.
It was just, like,
so weird, you know,
these dead bodies,
they're all whited out,
you know.
It's almost more scary
that they don't show you
what the thing is.
And then there's all these
pictures of Charlie
from all the different times
he was in prison.
And then there are
the Manson Girls,
who are just so fucking hot.
Look at that.
But at the same time,
you know that if
you got with them,
they could probably cut
your dick off, too, right?
That sounds...
Sounds very enticing.
It's got everything.
It's got murder, sex,
it's got it all.
What about, um...
What's going on
with those kids?
The Manson Girls have kids.
Most of them
were Charlie's, actually.
Wow.
Oh! Dude, um, turn here.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe that
we're at the Sharon Tate house.
-Look, look.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
-Yeah?
Look what I got.
What... What is that?
You wanna maybe
shoot some photos?
Turn it into
an art project, maybe.
-Yeah. Maybe. Cool.
-Yeah.
--The amount of excitement
you have right now
is like, seriously
disturbing to me.
Oh, my God.
Hello.
Dude, this is like
a historic spot.
I can't believe
we can just walk right up.
-Whoa.
-Oh, my God.
That's enough.
We can just...
Do you have to go
right up to the thing?
Why?
It's a public street.
--I don't think it is.
It's just like in the books.
The gate is here,
everything. Do you see that?
That's where Sharon Tate's
house was, right up there.
That's where it happened.
Man, I wish
I could get closer.
We don't need to get
closer than this.
This is fine.
Well, good thing is
lot of the stuff
happened here.
Oh, my God!
This is probably the same
pole that Tex climbed up.
See, they thought there was
gonna be an alarm,
so he climbed up
with wire cutters, and he
snipped all the wires.
He jumped over,
and then right then there was
this young kid driving away.
He was just randomly
there that night.
Never been there before.
And Tex, like,
starts stabbing him
through the window.
But he scooches back,
put his hands up.
So Tex has to shoot him
four times in the chest.
--Okay. You know what?
I'm gonna go back to the car.
-Why? Hey.
-Because--
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry.
No. You can do whatever
you want. I'm just not
gonna be part of it.
Stop, please.
Wait, okay? I'm sorry.
Just take a picture of me.
-All right?
-Why?
I wanna get...
I might do a self portrait
from this.
-Are you fucking with me?
-No, I'm serious.
All right. Here.
Let's do it right here.
I want to get
the gate at least.
Dude, it's the same
fucking gate.
That's amazing.
A lot of it
happened on the lawn.
Okay, stop talking
so I can take
the photograph, will you?
Okay, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
This guy's gonna
call the cops.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
-God damn it.
-Oh! Come on.
Charles Manson killed
people right here.
You have to be
fucking respectful about that.
He wasn't even
here that night.
He wasn't at the Tate house
or the LaBianca house.
-Well...
-He didn't kill anyone.
Then why is he in jail
for murder?
Exactly!
-I mean, it was
a fucking conspiracy.
-Okay. Keep your voice down.
It's because of his ideas.
They couldn't have
someone that free
being, living out amongst us,
'cause it would make
everyone else feel like,
"What are you gonna
do with your life?"
-Keep your voice down!
-I don't give a shit about
those fucking people.
Hey! Charles Manson!
- God damn it!
Charles Manson!
Hey.
I'm sensing some tension.
Look, sorry.
Let me take you
out to lunch, okay?
I know a really good place.
Are you gonna talk about
Charles Manson the whole time?
I don't have to.
♪
There's like no limit to
the amount you can work,
which is like,
part of the deal
when you become a partner.
And, you know, the money
is commensurate with that work.
But it's... It's like,
when do you stop?
You know what I mean?
Like, when does it end?
Hey, guys, I'll just
pick that up
when you're ready.
Okay. Thanks.
-I got it. I got it.
-No, I got it.
Come on.
-Really?
-Yes.
-All right. Thank you.
-I told you I was
taking you out.
So, wait, before we go,
I got to tell you,
um, this table that
we're sitting at...
This very same table.
This is the same booth
that they ate at before
they went home that night.
Who? What are you
talking about?
Sharon Tate and her friends.
They ate here before that
same night they went home.
And then,
Tex and the girls came.
- Yeah, okay. Yeah.
-Got it. Got it.
-Oh.
So that's why we're here.
Oh, come on.
It's just a fun fact.
You think it's a fun fact,
but it's not.
I mean, it's, like,
really disturbing.
Okay, I'm sorry,
but I mean,
it is something that I've
been thinking about that...
I mean, a lot of people
ignore death,
and it's something
to think about
and not just shove away.
Are you...
Do you hear yourself
right now?
I mean, you... You're talking
about not ignoring death,
and embracing it.
But when it comes to
Dad's funeral, you don't come.
Like, what is that?
You know, we weren't
getting along. I mean...
Do you know the last time
that he called me?
When's the last time
you called him?
I gave up calling.
Why? What's the point
of calling? And it's, like,
there's nothing going on.
There was no exchange
going on.
Even if you're not gonna
go to the funeral
for Dad's sake,
you could have come for Mom.
Mom's way better off,
you know.
How would you know?
You don't know.
You're just talking
out of your ass.
Mom was a fucking basket case.
She found him on the floor.
She was, like, hysterical
for weeks.
She was a wreck, I was a wreck.
I had to do the flowers,
I had to do the casket,
I had to do the cemetery,
I had to do the announcement,
-I had to do the invites.
-Okay.
You know what I mean?
I don't want to talk
to those people.
Okay.
So, you can understand then...
No, I can't understand.
Look, you didn't want
my help, you know.
I mean, you're glad.
You're taking care
of everything again,
and you look good,
and Mom loves you.
And that's the dynamic
that you have, and,
"Oh, fucking, Connie.
I know." You know.
I mean, that's fine.
Yeah, that's...
Your dynamic is just like,
oh, yeah, it's impossible
and, you know,
everybody hates you.
Don't they?
This car taken?
Dude, I'm sorry. Okay?
Look, um...
Let's just go back to my house.
I'm gonna go do my thing.
Why don't you take the car?
You can do whatever,
the rest of the stuff
you want to do today.
I think we should
smoke together.
All right?
I am not gonna smoke weed.
Why?
-I'm not in the mood for it.
-That's the point.
I think you need this, man.
-You have the day off, right?
-Yeah.
Okay.
So let's enjoy the day.
You're right. I didn't
deal with Dad's death. Okay?
It's really good.
How do you feel?
- It's pretty good.
What are we doing?
We're going to Leo
and Rosemary LaBianca's
old residence.
- All right.
-Is that it?
-God.
This is the
LaBianca house, man.
Holy shit!
Come on. Come on.
I bet the kitchen is on
this side, and the kitchen
is key here, okay?
Because that's where they
wrote on the fridge in blood,
"Helter Skelter".
- Oh.
-      -That all came     from this kitchen.
Oh, my God.
I gotta get into the kitchen.
Go, go. Go.
I wish we could get closer.
Get up.
Oh, dude.
There's the owner
of the house.
- What do we do?
-I got an idea.
What? What? Are you sure?
-Hey, um, excuse me.
-What are you doing?
Okay,
just let me handle it.
Hi.
Um, we are...
Can we talk to you
for a second?
No, I'm sorry.
- Oh.
-No.
-Um...
-What are you doing?
Just chill. Um...
We are the grandchildren
of the LaBiancas.
You're the grandchildren?
-You'll have to forgive me
for being so defensive.
-Wow.
You can imagine we have
a lot of strange people
coming here all the time.
-No problem.
-Yeah.
All is in the past,
you know.
-Thank you.
-Oh, you're welcome.
It's amazing that
you let us in.
I just thank you so much.
- Yes, what he said.
-Nice to meet you.
-Good to meet you.
This is Conrad.
-Hi Conrad. I'm Janice.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
Beautiful skin.
Thank you.
Sorry, it's
a little messy in here.
Oh, no, it's beautiful.
What are you talking about?
This place is gorgeous.
Oh, well, I like to
keep it neater than this.
This is where the body was.
LaBianca, the guy.
They carved into his stomach.
They stabbed him right here.
Shut the fuck up.
Um, he was just saying
that this area right here,
we have a photograph
with us playing with
trains right here.
This guy was so cute
in the photos.
- Yes.
-Of course.
-Just being in this room
is so cool It's really...
-Yes.
...you know,
special for us.
I'm sure this is not
a subject you're fond of,
but I was just wondering,
you know, after
what happened here,
do you ever feel, like,
you know, just creeped out,
you know?
No. Not really.
It is strange, knowing
that Charles Manson was
actually in the house.
Wait. What?
Charles Manson
was in the house?
Yes. He's the one
who broke in.
That's weird,
because I had heard
that Charles Manson
was not a part of
the murders at all.
Well, no, he just came in
and tied them up, but he
wasn't part of the murders.
You know, at the Tate house
I told you it was such a mess.
And so they wanted to...
-He just wanted to make
sure it was like cleaner...
-Yeah.
You know, for... When the...
For the LaBiancas.
-Mmm-hmm.
-I mean, Pop Pop.
You know.
Um...
I must
sound like a freak.
I just... I mean,
I've researched it
because it's our family.
Anyway,
it fucking sucks that
that happened, obviously.
He's sorry.
Um, do you have...
I mean, duh,
obviously,
you have a kitchen,
but could we take
a quick look at it?
The kitchen?
Gee, I'm sorry, it's...
It's a real mess.
Right now I'd really
rather you didn't.
I mean, I don't mind
if it's a little messy.
Maybe some other time.
But, you know, it's fine.
Like, I mean--
No, no, it's okay.
It's okay.
This is more than enough.
Well, I mean,
this was kind of
the whole point.
I guess, just 'cause
of the memories.
-But...
-She doesn't want
us to go in the kitchen.
Okay. Sorry. Yeah.
No, it's all right.
I understand.
Maybe another time.
You know what?
Thank you so much
for doing this for us.
You're very welcome.
You know, I actually
wanted to let you know,
when we were coming in,
I saw that your retaining wall
right at the front here
was sloping a little bit.
So, on the way out
maybe I could show you that.
'Cause my wife and I went
through the same thing.
It was really easy to fix.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Did you need to go
to the bathroom?
Um, you had to go.
Oh, yeah. Okay, great.
I'll go to the bathroom.
-Yeah.
-I'll met you guys at...
-Cool.
-The retaining wall.
-Just over here?
-To the left.
This is so easy to fix.
Is it the one
with the bricks?
Yeah, you gotta
catch it now, though.
♪
Hey.
-Who are you?
-Who the fuck are you?
I'm sorry. I just... You're...
Is that
a Charlie Manson t-shirt?
Hey! Nick!
Dude, abort!
-What are you doing?
-Get the hell out of here!
Hey!
Frank!
Frank, what are you doing?
I wake up from my nap
and this guy's in our kitchen
taking pictures
in a Charlie Manson shirt.
What?
-I'm sorry. I can explain.
-Explain!
Hey.
Excuse me.
This is why we end up
feeling like prisoners
in our own home.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I mean, you did
choose to live here.
I mean...
I had no idea what we'd be
getting ourselves into when
we bought this place.
I don't understand you.
A horrible thing
happened here!
And you want
to celebrate that?
Haven't you ever lost anyone?
I was, like,
telling somebody the other day
my dad's dead.
-I was, like,
trying to be cool about it.
-Mmm-hmm.
But it's, like, weird
to say it, you know.
I don't know.
It's just weird.
But here we are,
here, a perfect family.
This is the best shot
of you guys.
Like, you, Mom and Dad.
This is, like, what's
always in my head.
Yeah.
I hate that fucking photo.
You do?
-Yes.
-Why?
You can see how
he fucking felt about me.
He's not even touching me.
He's just posing
for a photograph, man.
Okay, do you want to fucking
argue about the composition
of the photo?
We're talking about reality,
and how the guy was
kind of a dick.
I personally think
that you expected Dad to do
everything for you as a kid.
-But, like...
-No, just to love me, maybe.
He's an army guy, all right?
And he has, you know,
he has that power thing,
and that's part of his setup.
Like, you had to add that
to that a little bit,
if you want...
That's not love.
That's not raising someone
to be their own person.
That's making
a little fucking clone.
So, uh, so what,
I'm dad's little soldier?
That's basically
how you see me?
I mean, you have a kid,
you got the wife.
You know, everything,
which is good. I'm just...
-Yeah, I have a kid
and a wife.
-It's a lot of good things.
You made him happy,
he gave you money
because you were going
-to "law school" and that's
such a great thing to do.
-"Law school?"
You don't put air quotes
around law school.
It's a real thing.
Which is how I earn a living
and buy food
to put inside the people
inside the house.
Yeah, it seems like it's
working out great for you.
That's it, huh? Hey!
You know, dad wasn't
the only one in the family
who treated me like
a fucking outcast, okay?
You did your fair share
of treating me like
a piece of shit.
Do you know
where the Melatonin is?
No, I'm sorry, I don't.
I don't understand
how it disappears.
Like, who takes the
Melatonin?
You seem really agitated.
Is something wrong?
Conrad basically thinks
that I threw him under the bus
our entire childhood.
And that I got
special treatment.
Yeah.
What do you mean, "Yeah"?
You know that you and your dad
had a really strong bond, right?
-Mmm-hmm.
-And I can understand
how Connie
probably felt
excluded from you guys.
Okay, he excluded himself.
But that doesn't...
Why?
That's what he does.
He likes to, like,
act like the outsider,
and like, push people away,
and poke and prod people.
He gets off on that shit.
Why would he get off
on something like that?
Because he's
messed up in the head.
-Genetically, probably.
-Dude.
Like, I looked into
his adoption one time,
and it said that he
was a ward of the state.
That's so mean.
Stop it.
You asked me,
and my answer is
I think there's
some weird chemistry
going on in his brain.
Well, I think that
no matter what Connie,
or anyone ever does,
they will never
measure up for you.
No one's good enough.
Great. Okay.
Can I get a pillow?
Good talk.
♪
I'm just a messenger
of the truth.
God's messenger?
Life's messenger.
But we use the word "God".
"God" hooks
all the other words up.
I'm the pope.
I'm ten times the pope.
I'm 50 times the pope.
But I'm the pope
in the hills and the mountains.
I'm already out of here.
This enclosure here?
I'm out of here.
My body is stuck here,
but my thought
is already gone.
Cool. Battle?
Mmm-hmm.
Wanna meet him?
We're friends.
Oh, cool.
I'm so glad
that we're friends now.
I've been watching you
and I like the way you fight.
I admire you.
-Here!
-Escape! Chuck!
What's this?
Oh, this is a book,
uh, Helter Skelter.
Are there pictures?
Um, yeah.
Um, a couple.
Hold on, hold on.
Let me see which ones
are okay to look at.
Wait, wait.
Yeah, there's a nice
picture of a family.
Are they real
brothers and sisters?
No, they're, um,
they're not a real family.
It's actually better
than a real family
because they went out
and found each other.
What are they doing
in the middle of this desert?
Well, they...
They wanted to get
away from society
and from people
that didn't understand them,
you know, because that was
like hurting them,
other peoples
perception of them.
So they went out here
and they got a big bus,
and you know, they cared
about the environment.
They wanted to get back
into touch with something,
you know, more real.
What are all of these
dead people?
Oh, um, they're just
some people who just,
I don't know...
They were in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Like Grandpa?
No. Grandpa died
because he had a heart attack.
Um, these people
were actually killed.
But Grandpa, like,
killed himself in a way
because he was...
worked himself up
all the time.
What are you guys
talking about?
Oh, nothing,
just hanging out,
playing...
We're reading Helter Skelter.
There's really cool pictures
of dead people.
All right,
before you start,
I was just looking at the book,
he asked me questions.
He's curious.
What am I gonna fucking say?
-You're showing him dead bodies?
-I was trying to...
You're showing him
the Manson family?
What else are
you gonna show him?
I'm sorry,
but he's the one who
kept asking me questions.
He's a child.
He's gonna want to do
whatever you want to do.
You just say no.
If he wants to look at it
you just say no.
That's what you do.
Why? I'm not gonna
fucking lie to him.
Why don't you just
open up Internet fucking porn
- and show him everything
that's out there.
It's not funny, dude.
He's having a really hard time
and I don't need you
putting your shit on him.
Okay. Well, why is he
having a hard time?
"Why is he
having a hard time?"
He's a child.
Growing up is hard.
People have hard times.
Okay, yeah.
It has nothing to do with
like how you treat him.
You are so clueless right now,
you have no idea
what you're talking about.
-You don't...
-What are these words
coming out of my mouth?
Oh, my God, dude.
You are so fucking
out of touch with reality.
-I can't even deal with it.
-Yeah, fuck you.
Are you gonna go
to your job or not?
Okay. That's it?
What else?
Yeah, all right. Cool.
♪
So, um,
I'm gonna drive you
out there, okay?
Okay. I mean...
What?
She guilted you into it?
Kind of, yeah.
♪
Who's this?
Is it okay?
Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's Charlie.
That's him singing?
Oh, it was his main thing.
He was so into music.
That's what he wanted to do.
Like, in LA,
he knew Neil Young,
and like, Dennis Wilson
of the Beach Boys
really liked him.
He was so close to
getting a record contract.
I mean, I don't know,
it just fell through.
Yeah.
He's like a frustrated
artist, basically.
I mean,
every artist is frustrated.
You know,
like, it's frustrating.
Is that how you feel
about your stuff?
Boo-ya.
I mean, you know,
it's like, what's the point?
Well, I mean, you know,
the point is you've been
doing it your whole life
and you're really good at it.
Dude.
-Okay.
-What?
You are. You've been
amazing at it
since you were a kid.
Like the painting
in your house, right?
Yeah, it's fucking amazing.
♪
Fuck.
Shit.
♪
Fuck!
-Jesus Christ!
-What?
A cop.
Pull over.
I wasn't even
fucking doing anything!
Well, pull over.
Dude, I can't. I can't!
Why?
-Pull over.
-Fucking shit! Okay!
Dude, um,
we got to switch seats.
-What?
-Dude, come on,
switch seats with me.
-Why?
-I just... I was
trying to help you out.
-Roll it down.
-Okay.
Hello. Hi.
Do you know why
I pulled you over, sir?
Um, yeah, I know
I might have swerved
a little bit.
But I was just, like,
dropped a CD.
You know, it got
all scratched up and I was
trying to clean it off.
Anyway, but it's back in there,
we're fine. Thank you
for the reminder.
Uh-huh. Can I see
your license, registration
and insurance, please?
It's really not necessary.
I mean...
Here's the registration
and insurance.
Sir, please keep
your hands on the wheel.
Okay.
Just do what he says.
And the license, sir?
You do not have
a drivers license,
is that what I understand?
No. Are you gonna
give me a big lecture now?
Do you realize it is
a serious offense to operate
a vehicle without a license?
I can take you in right now
and impound this vehicle.
I'm so happy
you have such power over me.
Have you been drinking, sir?
No, I have not
been drinking, sir.
All right, watch the tone.
We've just had
a really tough ride.
My brother and I
are not getting along well.
Okay, I need you to put
your hands on the hood, please.
-I'm trying to talk to you.
-Do not resist me.
Do not resist me.
I'm not fucking...
Jesus Christ!
-Do you have a weapon on you?
-No!
Does that feel good,
to fucking grab me, you pig?
Stop talking!
You're free to go.
Jesus,
that guy was such a dick.
The cop that
you called a pig?
He was.
How much was it?
Um, it was not cheap.
Shit. How much?
-Thousand.
-Thousand?
Yeah.
I talked them
down to 600, though.
- Really?
-Yeah.
-That's great.
-I know, it's what I do.
All right.
Here, I'll pay you back.
Hey. Hey.
Three, four, five...
Six.
What are you doing with
thousands of dollars?
I told you,
I sold all my stuff.
You can keep it.
You're gonna need it
more than me.
♪
This is, um,
not what I had in mind
when you said "their office."
It's a home office.
They work out of their home.
Jesus. All right.
This is probably it.
I don't think anybody's here.
Hello. We're coming in.
Hello, it's Conrad.
Careful.
There's probably like
a dog in here or something.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
There's nobody in here.
Can't you just call them?
They don't give out
their phone number.
Why not?
Because they're...
They have to be careful.
They... They have a website,
but they don't give out their
email and phone number.
Why do they
have to be careful?
Because they're
an environmental group.
They get harassed.
Environmental groups
don't get harassed.
-You're so naive.
-Look.
This doesn't feel like a job.
It feels like a terrorist thing.
Dude, it's a non-profit.
What do you want me to say?
Just help me look around.
-For what?
-I don't know. Just...
Clues.
♪
Blackbird and Sunshine.
Whoa. Come here.
What?
-What is it?
-An address.
That's 6259 right there.
It's gonna be right here.
Is that it?
Yeah, that's it.
What? That's
a fucking tattoo parlor.
They probably have tattoos.
Okay. So what do we do?
-Do you have the photo?
-Yeah, but we can't
just wave it around,
like, "Oh, FBI."
Right.
Um... Oh, what if
we did, like, a bait-and-switch?
-Yeah.
You know what
I'm talking about?
No. What do you mean?
So this is
your first tattoo?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
All right, yeah,
you look kind of Irish.
Maybe some of those
Celtic designs, or
you could go with something
a little more American.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Hey, I was wondering
if you could take a look at
this photograph right here.
I'm a little busy
right now, dude.
Can it wait a second?
Sure. No problem.
You, uh,
doing a pentagram?
You want one?
-Maybe I do.
-Looks like it'd suit you.
What can I help you with, man?
I'm just looking
for this guy.
He's a buddy of mine.
Haven't seen him
in a long time.
Does he come around
here at all?
Never seen him.
You?
Anything else
we can help you with?
No.
Excuse me.
Have you seen
this gentleman right here?
Uh... No, sorry, pal.
Cool. Thanks, man.
Fucking cop.
I know that guy
in the picture from somewhere
but I can't think of where.
It's that creepy guy who's
always chilling at The Palms.
Dude at the bar.
He's a scary motherfucker.
Seriously, when I
said bait-and-switch,
I was mostly just trying
to, like, make you feel good.
'Cause you were so panicked.
Dude, it was
exactly as you said.
The... You left,
and I'm like, "What the..."
I was like,
"I'm right here."
Well, no one would ever
believe that we're together.
Yeah.
All right.
Check it out.
You're a nut, man.
He's not going to come, man.
Stop worrying.
He'll either come,
or we'll talk to those people
and we'll figure it out, okay?
-Don't mind hanging out?
-No, I don't.
I'm enjoying myself.
I'm enjoying
whooping your fucking ass.
--Listen to this.
You wanna hear a sound?
Listen to this sound.
Right?
Oh, God.
So...
I got to tell you.
I am sorry about
what happened with Max.
I was not trying to...
You know,
that wasn't my plan.
The book was there,
he asked me.
I mean, I know
I shouldn't have,
but I told him.
I get it. I get it.
I'm sorry I yelled.
You know, I'm...
I overreacted.
And I'm just...
I'm worried about him.
He's, you know...
Sometimes I worry
he's not totally normal.
You know? I mean, he's, like...
Talks about death a lot.
-Mmm-hmm.
-And he's into weird stuff.
He drew this picture
with people, like,
you know, bleeding
out of their faces. Right?
Well, Dad died.
-Yeah.
-He's dealing with that.
You know,
he's working it out
in the drawings.
Yeah.
He's dealing with
the idea of death.
It's like a real thing
for him now.
He's fine.
I mean, he will be.
You got to be there
for him, though.
That's fucking deep, man.
You just dropped it
on me just now.
It's true.
-Dude.
-What?
That's Blackbird.
That's him.
I'm gonna check it out.
Why is this girl
wearing a Manson t-shirt?
-Is she?
-Yeah.
She's wearing
the same t-shirt
that you had on.
I...
I hadn't noticed that.
I'm gonna just go over
and talk to him.
Wait, wait a second.
What the fuck is going on?
I...
I don't know. I mean...
I'll tell you after, okay?
I just gotta talk--
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Talk to me first.
What is that?
Tell me what the fuck
is going on with that
Manson t-shirt.
Okay,
the environmental group,
they have a slight
association with Charlie.
He just started the group.
He started
the environmental group?
Yes. This group is picking up
on the positive aspects
of his philosophy.
He was actually
talking about the environment,
you know,
before a lot of people.
You're coming out here
to work with Charles Manson?
-Dude.
-See, I knew.
I fucking
bring up Charles Manson
and you fucking freak out.
Everybody freaks out!
Everybody freaks out
when you bring up
Charles Manson!
Fuck! Where did he go? Oh.
Shit.
Come on!
He's getting away.
Okay, here's the deal.
I am willing
to follow this guy,
but you don't
get out of the car
until I say so.
That's him!
Okay, okay. All right.
Shit,
go around this guy.
All right, I'm not
gonna get too close.
-Yeah, yeah.
-We'll just wait and
let's just see what happens.
What is the plan?
What are we doing?
I gotta show him
this letter I have,
and it'll be fine.
-Blackbird should
know who I am.
-What's with the names?
Blackbird.
Charlie gives
everybody nicknames.
He's turning, he's turning.
Go, go, go.
Nice!
Where the fuck did he go?
Go... Go faster.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up. Hold up.
He must have
gone around back.
Hold on a second.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where'd he go?
-Hello?
-He was just here.
Can you slow down?
Hey!
Fuck!
Shit!
Go, go, go!
Hey!
Motherfucker!
Hey! Hey!
Leave him alone!
Wait! I'm Conrad!
I've been writing to Charlie!
He told me!
He told me I could
work with you guys!
I'm Conrad Morgan!
Please don't hurt us.
Morgan?
You're Captain Morgan?
-Yes.
-Charlie fucking talks
about you all the time.
Every day.
-Every day he talks about you.
-Okay. Yeah.
- Come on.
-      -I'm sorry.
Lean back.
This eye.
-Okay.
-You've gotta just
keep it open for me.
Okay. No, you have to open it.
-It's, like, burning.
-There we go. Quickly.
-Okay, go.
-It sees the thing
and it retracts.
I know. They're like
two little angry clams.
What?
They're chomping down.
-Other eye.
-Okay.
One, two...
--Now blink that eye.
Breathe.
In through your nose.
--Out through your mouth.
--Now I can see you.
Good.
You look better.
Your eyes are so blue,
like icicles.
I'm gonna go
put this stuff away.
Thanks.
Oh, my God.
What did she say?
She said, "I don't mind
that you saw me naked."
You can't do that.
I think that's
Blackbird's girlfriend.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I'm afraid you're gonna
get hit in the head with
a fucking lead pipe, you know.
And what's with...
You wrote a letter to Manson?
-Yeah.
-And he wrote you back?
You know, I mean,
we have stuff in common,
like, you know, he...
never knew
who his dad was and stuff,
and had a tough time
growing up.
I know it sounds weird,
but, yeah, just...
I was not doing that well
and I wrote him,
and he wrote me back and...
that's pretty cool.
The things he said, it was...
It helped me a lot.
And what did he say?
Conrad, come here.
I'm gonna talk a walk with you.
There's something I want
to show you.
Something that you're
probably gonna be
pretty excited to see.
Can my brother come?
Suit yourself.
Conrad, I don't know
if you're aware of this,
but, uh, they threw
Charlie into solitary
couple of weeks ago.
-So I haven't
been able to reach him.
-Uh-huh.
He's supposed to
get out pretty soon,
but you never know with
these fucking pigs up there.
Yeah.
Why'd they
throw him in solitary?
Why?
You think they
need a reason why?
Yeah, they don't
need a reason,
you know, with Charlie.
Well, he's in
the legal system.
I would think that they'd
have to have a reason
to put him in
solitary confinement.
They like blaming Charlie.
He's their Christ
on the cross.
And they ain't
never gonna take him down.
-I don't get it.
-Don't be a jerk.
♪
Holy shit.
Is that what I think it is?
- Sure is.
Oh, God.
- What is it?
-    -It's the bus.
The Manson family bus.
♪
I can't believe
it still exists!
Can I go inside?
Sure.
I'll just be a minute.
Well.
Jesus Christ.
I can't believe it.
Is this the same stove?
-This is the original?
-Yeah. That's it.
-Oh, my God.
-Nothing changed.
Piece of history.
Why don't you try
Charlie's old seat over there?
All right.
Charlie drove everywhere
in this thing.
Drove all over California,
stopped by the side of the road,
picked up kids that
had been kicked out
of their homes, you know.
Yeah.
He helped a lot of people.
You know, this world is
more of a mess now
even than it was then.
We got these guys
down at Washington,
can't get out of their own way.
Rich people,
snacking on the poor.
We got fire coming out
of our water faucets
'cause of all the fracking
that's going on.
We got fish belly-up
in the rivers and streams.
We do a lot of
talking about it.
But we're not doing
very much about
any of those things.
That's one
beautiful place, huh?
Yeah.
Well, I'm working
with some people, they're
gonna preserve and protect
every bit of this.
And you're gonna be
a real good addition
to the group.
Welcome home, brother.
Hey, y'all.
Welcome home.
Hey, beautiful.
Nice night for a walk.
Yeah.
We had a good time.
♪
Hello, y'all.
It's who you've
been waiting for.
This is Conrad.
Uh, well, first off,
thank you so much for
welcoming me into this.
Um, I guess like
a lot of us, maybe...
I've been struggling
to find my way.
And, um...
Well, you found your
way here, that's good.
Yeah. Thanks.
And we sure do
need you, don't we?
- Yeah.
-        -Absolutely.
Thanks. I feel
a part of you guys. Right?
I mean...
Look at you
bunch of freaks.
--Right?
That's what they think.
We're not the crazy ones.
And it is so good
to be here around people
who don't have
all that fucking judgment.
And are okay
with seeming crazy.
Anyway, thank you. I...
I feel like I've found,
uh, you know, a home.
- Thank you.
-     -Hear, hear.
♪
-Hey, man.
-What's up?
-That's a nice fire, right?
-Yeah.
You having a good time?
Listen, um,
what the hell is going on?
Charlie told them about me,
-and, you know...
-What did he tell them
about you?
Just about me, you know,
and just...
I mean, stuff that...
Whatever.
I'm not gonna go into it
'cause it's like, annoying,
to you, I know. I don't wanna--
No, I kind of feel like...
Are you not telling
me something?
No, it's just,
you know, the...
Well, it's like
a personal connection
that we have.
-Look, um...
-Dude, just come in
and have a drink.
I gotta go, man.
I gotta get back.
-It's getting late.
-Okay.
Then, I guess, "See ya."
No, I just...
What I'm trying to say is
I don't... I feel weird
about leaving you here.
Well,
'cause you're judging them.
Come on in, have a drink.
-I'm not judging them.
-Connie.
Connie, I've been
looking for you.
Hi. How you doing?
-Come back inside.
-Okay.
Dude, come on in.
- Come on.
I wanna talk to you.
-Come in.
Just give it
an hour, man.
He's shy.
♪
You haven't seen the site?
Have you seen our new site?
-No.
-Have you seen the lab?
It's really good.
You did a bang up job.
-Hey.
-Hey, man. What's up?
You're, uh,
you're Conrad's brother,
aren't you?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Dude, he's off the hook.
He's absolutely amazing.
Yeah. Awesome.
-Is this your website
for the group?
-Yeah.
This is our new website.
-It says Helter Skelter.
-Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. How does that fit in
with the environmental thing?
Helter Skelter is basically,
it's what's going on
in the world right now.
It's the chaos
that's happening.
We're trying to
stop it from happening,
but it's happening.
It's happening fast.
Do you feel that?
It feels so good.
Yeah.
When I'm around you
I feel like...
Like, even if you're
far away from me,
like, on the other side
of the room, I feel like
I'm touching you.
Wow.
You just met me.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I feel like that, too.
That's why we can even
talk about it. That's why
we even notice it.
-You know?
-It's actually been
a long time for me.
You know, feeling
like this with somebody.
I don't know,
I felt it like right...
I mean, not when
I was pepper-spraying you.
-Shortly thereafter.
-Right. Shortly thereafter.
-Yeah.
Give a guy a minute
before you fall in love
with him.
Yeah.
Well, you'll be easy
to fall in love with.
You're so strong.
Jeez.
You're so brave.
You're so beautiful.
♪
Uh, do you know
where my brother is?
Uh, no.
He's gotta be
around here somewhere.
Hey, Nick.
Can I ask you a question?
Your brother tells me
that you might be able to
give us some legal advice.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Yeah, what do you
wanna know?
-He said you're a lawyer.
-Yeah.
We wanna file a petition
for a new parole hearing.
Yeah. I mean, I'm not
a criminal lawyer,
so, you know...
I could look at papers,
maybe.
That would be excellent.
That'd be great. Thank you.
Of course.
I wanna get him
out of there.
I wanna get him introduced
and reunited with his son.
Oh. Who's his son?
Come here.
You know,
maybe you don't know this,
but old Charlie,
he had quite a few kids.
And they locked him up
and they took
all the kids away.
And they put them
with new families.
Like yours.
Yeah, I think
my parents would have known.
I mean, they have to
reveal that legally.
They didn't reveal
anything back then.
Nothing.
Conrad was a ward of the state
and he was adopted just
like a normal kid.
See that baby?
That's your brother.
I need to talk to my brother.
-Okay.
-Um...
I'm gonna go back
out to the party.
-Okay. I'll meet up with you.
All right.
-I'll see you later.
Um, you kind of
interrupted something, man.
Is it true?
Blackbird fucking
told me just now.
That's real?
Yeah.
You're not gonna
fucking tell me?
I don't know, man.
I just, like, fucking
can't say anything.
I mean, you're...
Look at how you're
fucking reacting!
Hey, Conrad.
Charlie's on the phone.
Dude, I gotta go.
♪
Hey.
Yeah, he's right here.
I'm gonna put him on.
He's out of solitary.
Hi.
Yeah, good to
talk to you, man.
What the fuck, man?
What are you doing, man?
Get your shit,
get in the fucking car now.
I sense you're
very angry, man.
This is not really the time.
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
Yeah, I'm out of my mind
'cause I want to have
a fucking phone-call, man.
Sorry, everyone.
Um, can we get him
back on the line?
You're not
fucking talking to him!
- Okay! Dude, maybe
just have a fucking drink.
Why don't you just
get in the car and drive
the fuck out of here? All right?
Do not pick it up!
Do not pick that phone up!
You're trying to just
fucking fuck this up for me.
Fine. Pick it up!
Pick it up,
you fucking idiot!
I mean...
I'm just trying to talk
to my father here. Okay?
Hello.
Dad was right about you.
♪
Fuck!
Imagine if we had
a baby together.
Can we name it "Manson"?
What?
-Nothing.
-Is that weird?
-No, it's...
-That was weird.
That's just a lot.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to say that.
I didn't...
Forget I said that.
Okay?
-It's okay. Yeah.
-Everyone's Manson.
Man's son, you know?
-Son of man.
-Every baby.
Every baby is man's son.
You know, Charlie
always say that
everything is love.
Everything is love.
Hmm.
Even how you
just felt right then.
Even that, that
pulling away part is love.
You can feel
that way with me.
♪
Hey. What are you
doing here?
I'm getting back to work.
What do you mean
you're getting back to work?
Hey, look at me.
What happened?
Um...
-Just...
-Just stop working.
What happened?
Um... I need to do this.
Tell me what's going on.
Why are you here?
What happened?
What are you doing?
You're acting crazy.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
What happened?
I fucked up.
I fucked it up.
- Baby, what happened?
What happened? Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm just
a horrible person.
What are you talking about?
You're not a horrible person.
I don't know what to do.
♪
Conrad, come on.
We're running late.
Be right there.
I wanna see my brother.
I don't think
he wants to see you.
Connie!
He went to visit Charlie.
Connie's dad.
That's a whole
new look for you.
Yeah. Uh...
Hopefully, he doesn't
think I'm an idiot, you know.
I think he'll like it.
Make him feel
right at home.
♪
Home sweet home.
We're here for
the visiting hours.
ID?
Okay.
Hey, Connie!
Connie!
Hey. Sir,
can I get in here?
Not without a pass.
Just go home, Nick.
Dude, come here.
I need to talk to you.
Just one second. Please!
Fuck him.
We got five minutes.
Let's go. We gotta go.
-Connie!
-I gotta go!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Please! I just need to talk
to you for one minute!
It's so important.
Just one minute!
I'm gonna
handle this, all right?
Oh. Oh, God.
What?
Did he shave your head?
No!
Is this another fucking
thing you're gonna
come down on me about?
No. Look...
What?
Okay.
That stuff with Dad that
you were talking about before.
Dad was an asshole to you.
He treated you
like a piece of shit,
and I did, too.
And I threw you under the bus.
And... I'm just...
I'm ashamed.
I came to tell you
that you're right about me.
And about me
being like Dad.
And about the way
that I am with you,
and the way that
I am with Max.
And I just...
I... You're right,
and I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna
do it anymore. Okay?
-Okay.
-I'm gonna be a really
good brother to you.
I don't know how
to fucking do that,
but I can, like,
follow your lead.
You know how long
I've been wanting
you to say that?
Conrad,
come on! We gotta go.
Come on. Come out here
and give me a fucking hug, dude.
Let's get in the car,
let's get some
fucking McDonald's.
That's, like, the funnest
thing you can think of?
I don't fucking know
how to have fun, dude.
That's why I need you, dude!
I need a fucking Happy Meal.
Come on, just come on.
Let's get in the fucking car.
Dude...
I... I gotta go in, man.
You're going in there?
He's my dad.
I gotta see this
through, all right?
I'm sorry,
I'm fucking...
Charles Manson's son.
It's fucked up,
but that's who I am,
you know.
It would mean a lot
if you understood.
-Or try.
-Okay.
I know what I'm doing.
All right. I'm gonna go inside
and see Charles Manson.
And I'll be back out.
And we'll talk.
We'll still be brothers.
All right?
All right.
I love you.
Ah, I can't say it.
♪
Somewhere out there,
there's at least one son,
that we know of,
that's your child.
Look in that camera.
What would you
say to that kid?
What do you say
to your son out there?
This could be
the first time he's
ever seeing his father.
What do you say to him?
You gotta catch it
on your own, boy.
Train's hard.
The road's rough.
And that's it?
That's all I knew.
That's all anyone
ever told me.
And you wanna
hear something?
He'll do it better than me.
Whatever he does.
He'll do it a little better.
Kids do, don't they?
Yeah. That's what
makes them such a gas.
They always
seem to get through.
♪ The home is
Where you're happy ♪
♪ It's not where
You're not free ♪
♪Your home is where you'll
Be what you are ♪
♪'Cause you just born free ♪
♪ Now they'll show
You their castles ♪
♪ And diamonds for all to see ♪
♪ But they'll never show you
Their peace of mind ♪
♪'Cause they don't know
How to be free ♪
♪So burn all your bridges ♪
♪Leave your
Whole life behind ♪
♪ You can do
What you want to do ♪
♪'Cause you're
Strong in your mind ♪
♪ And anywhere
You might wander ♪
♪ You could make
That your home ♪
♪And as long as you've
Got love in your heart ♪
♪You'll never be alone ♪
♪ Just as long as you've
Got love in your heart ♪
♪ You'll never be alone ♪
♪