Transcript by Jesslataree
swsub.com
... we continue our series
this morning called...
Okay, Zack. Belly up.
- Morning.
- Put me down.
- Pancakes?
- No, thanks.
- How did you sleep?
- Good, you?
No, I tossed and turned.
It may be the mayor story
stressing you out.
The stories don't stress me out.
Deadlines? Maybe.
There's been an accident on Van Ness,
you wanna take Corero.
Great, thanks.
And Katie?
Happy anniversary.
Happy aniversary to you, Mr. Vasser.
You thought I forgot.
- Never crossed my mind!
- Yeah, you did.
- Bye, Dad!
- Take care. I'll see you tonight.
Come here, you.
- And Katie?
- Yeah?
Try not to be late.
That's funny.
Your Dad's a funny guy.
Vasser!
- Where is it?
- You're the one
who's all anal
about getting two sources.
That's the mayor, we have to nail him.
It's the age of the blog, Hugh.
You get the story first,
you get it right second.
Well, lately we've done neither.
- I'm pushing it to tomorrow.
- Hugh, come on!
Don't you have
a wedding aniversary tonight?
- I forgot to pick up her ring.
- I've seen this movie before.
I don't need you
when it comes to my marriage.
Yes, you do.
Yeah, you're right.
You got an aspirine?
I got a killer headache coming on.
Taxi!
North Beach, Luna restaurant.
Thanks.
What's going on?
Come on, you idiot!
Owens made an amazing catch.
That game was eight years ago.
Dude, I'm gonna have to cut you off.
Livia!
How long have you been in here?
- I don't know.
- This ain't no Bed & Breakfast.
Do you want a ride?
Yeah, Luna restaurant.
I know...
Champagne, please.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Now, if it was our anniversary...
Wait, it is.
Maybe we should skip dinner.
Bad idea.
You'll need your energy for later.
... and then, Like-a-Mink...
Sir, your table's ready.
A friend of mine had the winning horse.
A friend of mine had the loser?
Are you all right?
Kind of fell asleep in the cab,
I had this...
weird dream.
- It all took place in here.
- Really?
The last day I saw Livia,
I couldn't take her to the airport,
she took a cab.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Look at you.
Is there such a thing
as too beautiful?
You're good.
Happy aniversary.
They said it wouldn't last.
Here's to getting it wrong.
- How you doing?
- Good.
What number
are you gonna play for recital?
It's a song, not a number.
You ready?
I think so.
You're gonna do great. Now remember,
practice + confidence = ...
- Success.
- Very good.
You're gonna be there?
Count on it.
That looks expensive.
It has extended us quite a bit, yes.
Well, open yours first,
I'm not following a velvet box.
I'm in the process
of upgrading your wedding ring,
- this will have to hold you.
- You stole my wedding ring.
- You filled out an insurance claim.
- I didn't mail it.
I'd better be in my A game.
That may not be enough.
Get off!
Where am I?
Golden Gate Park.
Someone had fun last night.
Let's go, people. Get up!
You know the drill.
Get up, now!
Katie?
Good morning and welcome to Today,
some of us got back from China
a little slower
but all are present,
including Willard Scott,
who's going to be stepping in
with the weather.
John Palmer will give us details
on those NFL strike talk
the rest of the day's news...
And then after weeks of hearings,
the Senate Judiciary Committee
has scheduled a vote today
on the nomination of Judge Walter...
Get out of my house.
- Get out of my head.
- What do you want?
Waking up would be nice.
Wake your ass up,
I'll knock you into next week.
Yeah, okay. Good.
- Good, do it.
- No, just leave.
That didn't work.
Take the shoes.
Just get out of here.
What's today's date?
October 6th.
What year?
1987.
Sorry to bother you.
- What are you doing here?
- I can't find Dan.
- When was the last time you saw him?
- Last night.
I woke up this morning
and he wasn't there,
he didn't show up to work,
missed the deadline,
he hasn't called,
it's just not like him.
I heard you guys
were having some problems.
That was a while ago.
Could there be anyone else in his life?
You mean like another woman?
I have to ask these questions, Kate.
No one I know of.
Except maybe Livia.
Yeah, well... he married you.
And Livia's been dead for like, 9 years.
I don't think he left me, Jack,
if that's what you mean.
So what do you want me to do?
You're a cop and his brother,
you tell me.
It's a little early
to file a Missing Persons.
All right.
I'll talk to some of the guys and...
put the word out.
Thank you.
You okay?
I'm okay, yeah.
I think so.
Maybe you should go home.
Sleep it off.
I almost killed myself...
over a woman.
Crazy, uh?
They can make you do that some times.
What's your name?
Dan.
I'm Neal Gaines.
Neal.
Thanks, man.
Lot of time left in the clock.
Move on.
And no kidding.
I'll be fine.
I'll take something to sleep.
I'm just running out of things
to tell Zack.
I'm home.
Zack might still be awake.
Where have you been, Dan?
I don't know.
- You don't know, because...
- I don't remember.
Just going to bed last night
and having this long vivid dream.
I save this guy's life,
Neal something, and then I woke up.
So you're saying
this is some sleep disorder.
I don't know what else it can be.
Unless I was drugged.
Something's happening to me,
I can't explain it.
Like the other night,
I fell asleep in one cab
and woke up in another.
Maybe you should go see Dr. Paulin
in the morning.
- Yeah, I will.
- Unless...
you're hanging out with Eddie again.
You can tell me the truth.
I have been here,
here in this house, in this city.
No, you've been gone for two days!
Two days?
Maybe you could have...
lobbed in a phone call.
I couldn't.
Why?
This was 20 years ago.
- So?
- I'd rather not get into it.
Really?
You missed the deadline on your story,
you scared the hell out of your wife,
and there's not gonna
be any accountability.
You said
the story wasn't time sensitive.
It wasn't then, but now it is.
You'll get it today.
All I need...
is a second source,
it just takes a phone call.
What's going on, Dan?
I mean, is it gambling
or... something else?
It's not gambling,
and it won't happen again.
Finish the mayor story.
- I want it by noon.
- Right, thank you.
And yet, you're standing.
Dan Vasser for Gary Tucker?
Thank you.
Well, how long?
You said that last time.
He exists.
You've reached the offices
of the of the brain psychiatry.
Our directory has changed,
so listen carefully...
I won't like being nervous.
Just remember that the other kids
are gonna be nervous too.
And remember,
the more you know the song,
the less nervous you'll be.
Practice + Confidence = Success.
- Exactly.
- Dad's car looks like that.
Dad's car looks like that one!
You can see a late model blue Mustang
directly below me,
which appears to be the car
that started the collision.
- Hello?
- Katie, it's Hugh.
Is Dan around?
He's two hours late on a deadline.
- No, he's been in a car accident.
- Is he okay?
I don't know, he...
ran a red light, hit two cars and...
he left the scene, Hugh.
- Oh, God.
- No one else was hurt, thank god.
I think Dan needs help.
No kidding?
There's a facility in Auburn
I know is good.
Auburn is for drug users.
Hold on. See this guy next to me?
Beam me up Scotty
Is there a problem?
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Neal, I think we should...
Nicole, please.
I want to make this work.
- I do too.
- I love you
- and I want to start a family with you.
- But not now.
You always say that.
Neal, I've made up my mind.
I'm not keeping it.
You know where I stand.
And you know what I want.
- Fine, Nicole.
- Neal!
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Livia?
Do I know you?
Not yet.
You're freaking me out with the staring.
The hooker outfits is my day job,
I'm a student by night.
Sorry.
It's just...
You look like someone I once knew.
You once knew?
Didn't end well.
Well, don't take it out on my gratuity
Try to spill any more drinks on me
and I won't.
Sorry, I'm just... having a bad day.
You shouldn't stress about school,
you'll be a great lawyer some day.
Who said anything about law school?
I thought you did.
The conversation's over.
Hey, Neal!
What did he do to you?
Nothing, he owes me some money.
You?
Knocked me up.
There's not gonna be a baby shower.
Got that right.
I told him from the start "no kids,"
I just...
I just got this job.
We went through the same thing
with Zack, my son.
Do you regret it?
Having a kid?
I'd do anything right now
to be back to him.
- Good luck with that.
- Thanks.
You too!
So... were you high
when you ran the red light?
- Is that why you took off?
- It's not drugs.
I told you the truth
and I go on these...
- These trips
- Through time.
Go ahead, you can say that.
That's exactly what I mean,
I'd rather people think
I'm a crack addict than think I'm crazy.
Where did you trip to this time?
- You'll never believe me.
- Try me.
Remember that guy I told you about?
His name is Neal Gaines.
Now I think I am tracking his life.
I think I just helped him
start a family.
Well, that's great! How about
sticking around and saving this one?
No, I've got from thinking that...
that you ran out on us to wondering
if you're lying bleeding in some alley.
I've stuck with you
for some pretty tough times.
But at least back then
you came home at night.
It's not ready.
Here's the thing,
it was supposed to be ready last week,
I need that ring today,
so I need you to do it now.
I'll sit here all day if I have to
but I'm not leaving without it.
It's not my birthday.
So I'm gonna go with an...
- intervention?
- Don't be mad.
- Where's Zack?
- At my Mum's.
Everyone's here
'cause we care about you.
Everyone here is getting it wrong.
I've been where you've been.
I guarantee you you have not been
where I have been.
Guys, I know you all care about me
and I appreciate it
but substance abuse is not my problem.
And don't say I am in denial,
even though I am in full denial mode.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll still be here when you get back.
Come on.
Seriously. If any Vasser
has a drinking problem, it's me.
Can I talk to you a sec?
You're the last person
I expected to come to my defense.
I didn't.
I'm here to arrest you
for felony hit-and-run.
Can I call my lawyer?
I'm pretty sure you can't do that.
Where have you been?
- Am I under arrest, or not ?
- I bring you in for questioning.
Katie did a story on how you ask
questions at this precinct
and believe me, I need a lawyer.
You don't need a lawyer
'cause I'm not gonna charge you.
No one saw you flee the scene, in fact,
one witness says
no one wasn't even driving
so, short of nailing you
for not setting the parking brake,
I got nothing.
Sit down.
So...
Why don't you tell me what the hell
is going on and we can all go home?
I wish I knew.
Katie says you disappeared for a couple
days and didn't even know it.
Something like that.
And you went back in time.
It's just these dreams,
but I'm glad you two are talking again.
- She came to me.
- This may work out great for you.
I wouldn't do that to a brother.
You only have yourself to blame.
Can I go now?
Sure, Dan.
But...
tell your wife I tried to listen.
I saw Livia.
On this...
On this last... trip,
or whatever.
I wanted to tell her not to get
on that plane, but I didn't.
I said something about her life
that hadn't happened yet.
I spooked her.
I might have blown my chance
of her liking me before we ever met.
Anyway...
Forget it.
Get some help.
Seriously.
Dead?
Taxi!
18.97.
- Just-- Keep the change.
- Thank you.
Howard Street.
Howard next.
I locked myself out again Mrs. Shay.
Hey, what are you doing here?
You're never home during the day.
I needed something for work.
The fitness hearing got cancelled,
so you wanna go off
to the restaurant together?
I can't, I...
- I'll see you there
- Okay.
I was talking to Gerald.
He agreed. Napa's too expensive.
And he knows
about these old officer's quarters
and a procedure that's better.
For what?
Our wedding reception, dummy.
Livia...
Unless you have changed your mind
about marrying me.
- Never.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, why?
- You look different.
- Different?
Tired.
It's been a long week.
You wanna talk about it?
Wouldn't know where to start.I
I don't know if I can save the week,
but your day's about to get better.
I gotta go.
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm on a deadline.
We'll finish this later.
How did you--
It is you.
How did you get out of here?
Don't go in there.
This way. Now.
Stop!
They found the plane in the water
but not your body.
So, did you even get on that plane
or am I just talking to a ghost?
It's me.
I left before it went down.
- What?
- Do you know why you're here?
- No.
- You now who you're following?
Some guy and his family.
Stay on it. Go with your instincts.
What if I get it wrong?
You will, that's part of it.
Just don't mess with anything.
I don't think I'm not supposed
to be here.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
I need a favor, it's kind of urgent.
Like what?
I gotta find someone
and I only have a name.
- I tried information.
- You're asking,
"Can I violate protocol
and use the police database
to help out my kid brother?"
I forgot that you weren't just recently
a prick, that goes back years
- Excuse me?
- Nothing, listen.
At least two people I know
are gonna die tonight.
- You're kidding. How?
- I don't know.
This is gonna sound crazy
but I know they're gonna die in 1997
and there's only a few hours left.
What are you talking about?
Forget it, I just need you
to help me find someone.
His name is Neal Gaines.
Hello, are you there?
- Who is this?
- What do you mean?
- You're not my brother.
- Of course, I am.
You're not,
'cause I'm looking at him right now.
You know, we're having lunch at Luna,
if you want to come by and meet him,
get pass, we'll kick your ass.
Hey, guys. Quiet, I wanna make a toast!
- What?
- Thank you.
I wanna make a toast to Dan and Livia.
You guys make wanna just say,
Gee, this stuff that's better
left in a Hallmark card, but...
champagne has emboldened me, so...
Dan, I've never seen you
so happy as you are with Livia.
and now, hanging around her,
I can see why.
She is loving
and brilliant and beautiful
and that's why I hate her.
And Livia,
- May I--
- * your brother's.
May I say you have as a future husband
a smart and handsome...
and passionate man who makes me
and you and all of us laugh.
So I hope that your commitment
to one another
will stand the test of time.
and Y2K
'cause you know that's gonna be bad.
I shouldn't of had that third glass
so I'm just gonna finish up by saying...
to an enduring love.
To an enduring love.
- Cheers.
- Thank you.
Was I good?
I'll be right there.
There's been a break in this last
new case, and the * want to talk to me
This is an engagement lunch.
I know, Dan has been working on it
for the last 6 months.
I'll... hook up later.
- Take in 1998 like it's 1997.
- Baby.
You can't leave on that.
- Hey, you forgot something?
- Yeah.
More champaign?
Can I talk to you for a sec?
I need an adress and a phone number
- that's not listed.
- Why?
That's for the deep background
in the Harris story.
Why don't you ask Jack?
I already did, he's not helping.
You're deputy D.A., you have access.
It's really important.
- What are the names?
- Neil Gaines and Nicole Gaines.
I'll try, I can't promise anything.
And my cell battery just died.
So I'm gonna meet Mrs. Harris
at the noodle bar,
can you call me there?
And...
I need some money for a cab,
I forgot my wallet.
Okay, that's a first.
I love you.
Me too.
- Hello?
- Hey.
So, it's a Neal Gaines who works
at Foogade & Town Realty
at 7298, 3rd Street.
- 7298, thanks.
- You owe me.
I do. Bye.
Neal?
Neal Gaines?
Greg Flooler.
I went to high school with you.
I haven't seen you since the reunion.
- I don't remember you.
- Sure,
we went to Berkeley together,
you married Nicole and you had a kid.
How are they?
They're moving to L.A. today.
Really?
Right.
So you guys are splitting up?
Do you still love her?
That's why I'm not gonna let her go.
Take Jacob inside the house.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
He just jumped in front.
He was gonna do it.
He said he was coming to kill us
if we left him.
He said it this morning.
Hey, it's me.
I need a ride home.
What do you mean, Jacob Gaines?
Neal Gaines' son.
Jacob graduated pre-med
from Stanford at 17
and I'm thinking he's gonna go on
and map the human genome or something
but instead...
You know what I'm looking at?
A schoolbus wreck in Gilroy, last year.
Jacob pulled out six kids,
performed a tracheotomy on one.
It was all about
protecting Neal Gaines' son.
And you think you had something
to do with this?
You're gonna lose KAtie.
Right? You know that?
Not without a fight.
- I think you need to leave.
- Just give me 5 min.
We'll talk about this tomorrow.
Not in front of...
- Hey!
- Dad!
I'm glad to see you.
You're back for good?
Mom and Dad need to have a little talk,
okay?
I'll come say good night, okay?
Just bear with me.
I'm not what you married.
And I'm sorry about that.
When did we put this patio in?
Right after we moved in.
Seven years ago, right?
Right?
What are you doing?
Saving my marriage.
Not really.
I'll always come home.
www.tvsubtitles.net