translation: Mr.lamasat
6 basement
and how is it? -
Doctors want to know what you gave him.
what happened, he is okay?
whatever...
now already tell it's okay?
hard to believe
values ​​stability.
Irene, because they are quite sure?
Yes. Doctors gave me
confirmed a few hours ago.
boy will live.
So when can you be here?
Damn,
boy jumps death shovel
and you're worried about your class?
not hack 'on me, and
problems with my boss give me already.
Please, Irene, still stay there,
I need some time.
headlights!
do the headlights.
do the headlights!
you can see us.
you Ted?
- Yes, come on.
Let's bring the matter to an end.
Well, Ted.
asshole.
exactly what you've asked for, is not it?
DANGER
trespassing
yawn eight times.
eight short.
I told you that the special rule of Harvard University is.
not.
This rule applies always and everywhere.
you know that this is true for both the night shift:
every time liquor yawn.
okay. Is good.
Do you have data with Infizierungsquoten?
- I'll do it until now.
I'm still sitting on a graph with
deviation values.
Ryan?
Ryan. - Yes?
nine short for me and one for you.
I hope you have a good foundation,
need today.
remember that loser
not allowed to liquor GPS.
not. Ward, and I want to
can not fill with Absinthe again.
not forget that Absinthe
Be a variety of medical healing.
of these, however, does not help one
ghost in the next morning.
not look.
Is bad for your eyes.
could open my eyes again?
Dad!
what's going on? Dad?
he recover?
with her husband, and the rupture of the large intestine,
and there was bleeding in the abdomen.
in about an hour
he survived the operation.
and what does he have?
unfortunately he was suffering from colon cancer.
What's the matter, Mother?
hard to believe, is not it?
my little treasure goes to Harvard.
call me so, if you're there, okay?
Do you also have your jacket? - Mom
I can handle it.
I just wish I could be a dad.
Do you know?
he is.
Believe me, in this second
he looks down on us.
come here.
house.
Hey, Beth?
hey.
God, what time is it?
we still have ten minutes.
what, ten minutes?
Ryan, since the management
but not my report.
why not for
raised previously? - Relax.
house, hey. Everything was good.
I've taken.
you be without me?
Thank you.
we can, but skip the meeting
easy?
attractive.
seems very, very seductive.
Let's go.
ULTRITEK
lab
hello, 'I've just learned.
start clinical trials in six weeks. - In six weeks?
I told you still need
at least four months. - Exactly.
ULTRITEK
lab
but this morning came
initial report on the experiences of mice
and hits now equal to the Supervisory Board.
looks as if the drug
would qualify for those bestseller.
when you can in the market?
- the closest in four months.
our Board of Directors
demanding quick results.
we are going to market
do not need half as long.
months?
No, absolutely impossible.
should go.
I am writing after the meeting again.
Hey, Ralph.
did you win?
4:1, Reese has scored twice.
morning
they play against Long Beach, in the quarterfinals.
there was an urgent need for me
sales forecast sent along.
Is this a joke?
I do not care if it is in Barbados.
I need the data directly.
morning. - Good morning.
hey.
this is your first meeting with him?
Ryan, you're right or left handed?
- Using the right hand. Why?
because you will not need the left.
even if you do not
eaten alive,
It is good to see any
limbs you could do without.
right. - Coach in waiting.
Thank you.
best offer takes the house.
have divided us, me and Pete.
It takes on technical analysis...
Believe me,
best is the single point of contact.
So go forward, forward courageously. - Well.
Well. As you know, the reason
Currently we alkylating agents
severe hair loss,
above-average risk of infection
and severe weight loss.
we have developed a new method,
improves the effectiveness of the medication
at a time and one of the side effects
reduced, without the slightest doubt.
If you want to look at it?
- When I asked in the market?
test series with tissue cultures
is not yet complete...
then leave your report
here temporarily, and we will contact.
Well, that's all.
Thank you.
starts UltriTech
patient tries to six weeks.
Why? Experiments with humans?
yet
thought they would be the first in four months?
seems as if they have
miracles and mid-heavy.
any chance,
because we can not keep up.
've been making recently,
test tissue samples.
I'm afraid you do not quite understand how
threatening situation.
keep your cool, okay?
for more than eight months
now we have poured our ass.
and do not even ask for it.
Fuck with side effects.
we are making great progress so far.
- Oh really? Ryan, is that so?
drugs, as well as all the rest:
Letsipan, Nostaran, Triclostan.
this is all just poison,
is pasted on a beautiful name.
if they were "marzipan" call,
if they promise them more buyers.
What do you expect?
There is a miracle cure?
What is wrong with you?
- What do you mean?
at Harvard University, we all agreed.
We wanted to be different.
we wanted to share
to find an effective treatment.
look around again, Beth.
Harvard is long gone.
This is about profit.
afraid
on ScopaMed cocktail brainwashing
you sipped a little more often.
long but is no longer necessary.
thou hast promised?
and when are you going
me to admit that?
sorry if you cut,
but the new ones will be there.
Yes. All right.
If we do not  before UltriTech
relationship with a drug to market,
this company go down the drain.
but authorities
human experiments allow only
in the case of a report of toxicity.
in itself,
three months experimenting with mice.
skip rat experiments.
No, certainly not.
this is impossible.
our agreement so I wanted to explode?
moment.
What you requested, I have done.
and we agreed on:
this time only.
I'm sorry,
but for the second time not to do so.
is the son of a passionate football player, I hear.
Why?
would be unfortunate if you would miss their games.
What does that mean?
not sure how easy,
prison to see how his son grow up.
So you're threatening me with the police.
forget
because we both stuck in it. - We both?
never. No, Ted.
you are alone.
not even under
path leads to me.
your word against mine.
which is before the jury
perhaps more credible?
general manager
a successful business,
ten million annually
donate to the poor,
or biochemistry
with his ex-wife addicted to drugs?
for two years and is now clean.
Ted,
there is only one, what I ask.
make it easy again.
which included,
it the last time?
you would be right
convince your son's life?
when everything is ready in the basement,
call Carlos.
night in order to deliver new.
here, your father.
What was the name of this camp for football, of which
constantly talking about, again? Madrid like?
Youth Camp Real Madrid.
You can even tonight
bag pack your gym?
We fly tomorrow to go early.
we fly to Spain?
you and me.
will need your passport. This is why...
- my mom has a pass, I ask them the same thing.
No, no, no.
tell her something.
This is our little secret.
we keep this to ourselves, okay?
Yes, of course.
see you tomorrow morning.
dad? Thank you.
yes?
just been delivered.
and the rest of the ship?
This  everything.
I was ten.
Sleep again.
will test for us here
novel agent for chemotherapy.
even marketing experts
think of something better
We continue to call it love:
ER-WYE-THREE-FOUR-ONE.
In the first step, we extract
cell culture bottles in the freezer compartment
The temperature in the incubator for two hours.
then
living cells counted.
Yes, there
then waits until the security field.
and when you listen to?
I will not leave the store without you.
three weeks ago in
vacant, Beth.
have something for you,
if you are interested.
meckerst you're constantly on the job
and if you are honest,
there's no reason one
does not stop here. But you can stay.
in UltriTech want you too.
and even want
search box.
under any circumstances and allows you to
depending idea come to enter this room here.
I suppose you know what damage both
havoc oncogenic virus in the bloodstream?
good, but mentally
multiplies by ten.
particular strain of
Merkel cell polyomavirus,
we have developed here, cause
and accelerated tumor growth.
In other words, if you are infected you,
hope to have something to be desired.
George, hand me out a lot?
this installment has ended
carried to the bench sterile,
where the virus then you need to inject the cells in the culture.
Why are you doing it for you hard?
we both get better jobs,
earn much more than that.
We finally
afford an apartment together.
or ScopaMed UltriTech,
where is the difference?
what you merely as a Funk?
for hundreds of years, you tell me
you want to develop a cure.
but this is nothing but talk.
you give blame ScopaMed,
but you know how it is in reality?
do not have the courage.
because it can be so,
to fail.
House Wakefield, par excellence
Biochemistry his Ph.D.,
can fail, with drums and trumpets
. - You are such a fool.
No, I'm just honest and admit:
I want a good life and
a good job. I have not hidden.
I am no different from the others,
but... - and my dreams are stupid?
not. Absolutely not.
I would like to heartily
and with all the violence that success.
but if this process does not work,
have at least try.
and? What's going on?
In fact, a lot of talk, but for
protein degradation is still dramatic.
verify the results of the phosphate.
In writing to me, okay?
house is still in the house, right?
minutes before and she was still there, but...
have für'n few hours
leave the company,
and I in need of a deputy.
- Clear. Yes, I do.
house!
pause for a moment?
in fact I wanted to today's times
time to go home.
please.
Only for two hours.
Well. Okay.
hello, my friend.
like last time.
must now
dad home again. - This is really beautiful.
our
bake chocolate cake with cream paint,
and I still have
jelly beans draufgepackt.
he likes, such as licorice flavor.
he might again today
home, is not it? - I'm sorry, no.
We spent only
perform EKG and...
now unpleasant side effects of chemotherapy
is an increased risk of heart attack .
- and this means in plain text?
chemotherapy
hurt the heart of your husband.
that heart disease is not curable.
in eight months, and he is
cancer and chemotherapy
shade
become his country.
in a lot of blood...
and he had to pass the time.
says he does not care as long as he
only survived, and now...
since you tell me if
survived cancer,
then died of heart disease?
our drug,
still keep it stable for a period of time...
Thank you stayed with it,
you certainly have a lot to do.
sorry. - It's okay.
house and we go home.
- What about the father?
and he can not even with.
Was probably come tomorrow.
But you promised me, he comes home after
. - Yes, I know. But unfortunately...
you would be so kind again?
you'd better stay here.
left me! -
Mother and father but cares.
left me!
house. House?
you know what about
cell cultures missing?
Ted is it will not back yet?
Oh great. Well, so should
yet to come, and I ask for time.
Pat here.
hello. We expect actually still
delivery. Tonight.
Do you have the application number?
- No. organized TED.
if it happens to you
passed? - No, not yet.
well, then he is still in the workplace,
Could you please put me through to him?
The way I see it here, he was one and a half hours
sixth in the basement.
sixth in the basement?
Are you sure? This is quite
closed for many years.
have anyway on the screen.
Well, you could probably go down
and ask him about the number?
I like to do,
but we do not have access even down there.
Well. If you see him, tell him,
he wants to call me? - If I did.
and?
and he is still on the road.
thousand dollars immediately.
then again
1000 $ after treatment.
During the treatment you need
stay here in this room.
be done on your own personal safety.
I will not hurt you.
lie down on the bed again.
take fucking money back.
post again.
we call it today?
Ryan and honest...
... Do you really think
UltriTech funded research?
say so,
fell as your name, I saw,
as if they had just
super jackpot in Las cracked.
Well, I'm with you. - Really?
just like that?
and you do not want to only two or three
nights sleeping on it for safety reasons?
not.
No, you're right.
I want to continue with the search and
I've been waiting a very long time.
I was scared.
I was afraid if I were not successful, DASS ..
Hey, you know, you're not alone.
right.
Thank you.
New York is sure to please you.
I know a little bit of pizza
on the Lower East Side, where...
you could have been thinking,
to live in the state of Montana?
on your farm? - Lack of guidance yet
of course, but maybe in the future.
so you before,
to settle?
No, I'm just asking because...
Now, before you ask any further,
should not correct to kneel?
No, I want you, but no application
make, it's just a question for you.
should I do it?
what a marriage proposal?
Why? You've got to
do not happen to have a ring there?
not.
but I know the mortgagee in
James Wall, who may still have homework.
really? - Yes.
really.
Ted!
Hey, you glow Yes.
have infected me with the virus.
Oh, my God. And how?
- Is completely unimportant.
I'll call an ambulance.
- They can not do anything for me. - Is right.
only one thing still preserves life.
and that would be?
- Go to my computer.
use the following login data!
Username: Lionel Stanton.
Password: Asagolabius.
O God, your hand.
I think I broke three fingers.
- on the one hand I connect you at the moment.
I'm sorry,
I want you both there with reinziehen.
ACCESS TO secure files
AP: Laboratory 18.24
station security camera
a file should be called DCA.
Have you found it? - Yes!
Yes, I think so.
in any section
been designed for?
Thus, the molecular structure
I've never seen.
This is the active ingredient of the drug.
for one, that cures cancer.
you Schweinepriester.
I just said "the treatment of cancer?"
moment. Wait a minute.
so...
claim that through this molecule
here is cured cancer?
Oh my God, this is incredible.
who developed it?
Lionel.
Lionel?
that does not make any sense.
I mean, a cure for cancer,
so you can earn billions.
we can make billions already.
If this drug comes
cancer than ever before in the market...
then no one needs to
chemotherapy drugs we have.
SopaMed
will probably bankrupt.
Since when?
How long have you had?
Since when, Ted?
for a ten-year-old.
shit.
you also only have the slightest idea,
how many people at this time
have suffered and belted miserable?
km from children's
was terrible as they lose their parents?
How many
mothers and fathers were forced to
just watch her swoon,
how their children suffered the torment of hell,
and you have a chance to finish it?
- I know only that very year.
I did not have any choice, my son...
- not! Puke on me!
FILE ON USB STICK COPY
finish
What do you do? - I'm doing this,
what you are before a ten-year-old has had to do!
will publish it. - Wait.
18 laboratory BLOCK?
Yes - No
wait!
Let's look briefly again.
What is there to think about?
- you want to publish a simple?
This is not a question!
- For anyone but deserves recognition.
Why?
want me to write:
in love, for you, Lionel Stanton?
not. - And I will be anonymous
download server of the University, which is fine.
I just say, house,
were not actually have thought through.
this is a big deal.
cure for cancer
there is a Nobel Prize.
Ryan.
people who are dying, and we can put an end to
, and in fact now.
I know. I know that, but what if it did not work
stuff?
thinking about the millions of patients
people in this world.
What if you put into the net
then nothing worth?
would be better if we know for sure.
right?
how long it takes to manufacture?
about forty minutes.
I have a job for you and your team.
when? - At the moment.
If you've passed through the main gate,
moved to the back of the building.
in the loading dock, and you will find a box
with everything you need for the job.
Where is the target?
- Laboratory eighteen.
symbols GPS data and access
you will find in the package.
and do not forget Yes,
must look like an accident.
and how they look?
very good.
Just two steps to the goal.
We are on the road.
VIRUS ALERT
check - news
VIRUS ALERT TRIGGER?
Yes - No
virus has broken out
So the alarm!
not!
you must bring it to an end. - If we
are dead, we offer something to the end!
Ryan!
will come back.
come.
Access Denied
my card does not work!
- Tried my visits. - For the moment.
Access Denied
Hey!
we are still here!
spread your
your men into two groups,
and gives each floor
down from the fifth floor.
Hey! - Hey!
- Get us out of here!
is to break down the door! Help!
us out!
This has no purpose,
they're all gone.
wait, I have an idea!
I have this range already
examination, and here no more.
one team,
meet at the main entrance.
way there, go!
ACCESS-CODE 7239
Come on!
ALARM virus outbreak
statement: armed - a statement: NORMAL
this is a good thing, right? - Of course.
Hey!
Did you hear that?
you take care of this,
that people go to the 100 meters back.
that is, the required safety distance
, okay?
Come on, open the door!
all of you will be a little farther back, please!
I understand well,
you're all shocked.
disaster management team has already arrived.
currently investigating the building.
but due to the risk of
may have possible contamination
spread outside this area can
, nor shall any one,
out of the building,
disasters give us the OK.
mobile phones!
moment!
How do you feel?
Do you have a fever, sweating her?
you? - No, I feel fine.
- And that was more than ten minutes.
If you have been exposed to the virus,
'd like to show her symptoms already.
This has been an exercise!
O God.
man, I've been chasing us fear.
- Is the end of the exercise?
what exercise? - That was just a practice
emergency, right?
They are the ones who are still only
here and there? - Yes, I think so.
we have to make sure.
- but we may have yet to come out?
not, we just check
and other laboratories,
person may be included.
Grant is here with you.
Come on guys, let's go.
ACCESS-CODE 5627
I do not understand,
Why should you have to wait your search here.
they are not of the disaster.
what is?
- No idea.
but every bet
We are the only ones here in the building.
Why? It is believed about...
- and we were locked up in the lab,
magnetic cards have not
works, and this is the crux of the matter?
they believe there mixes with Lionel?
I do not know.
but I know I would not be here,
when workers come out of there.
is that the only way out? - No.
Is there a way. - Which one?
you can see the guy from
distract us?
what the heck.
I would have short times to the bathroom, Grant.
- unfortunately not.
is just around the corner, and if you
stand there, keep it in mind.
OK, but hurry, please.
it's okay.
and she knows exactly what she's doing.
Why are you hiding it?
grant, we still
Z minus fifteen minutes.
Please confirm. Ended.
granted!
to make your subject and then
get down to the main entrance.
Where is the exit?
say,
has mixed her treatment.
there is no time, at any moment and
back, tell us immediately. - Do not!
not without drugs.
Where are you going? - Back to the lab
I do not leave here without this formula away.
find another way out. - House!
house!
okay.
grant, do you hear me?
can not even be too far away.
looking there,
intend region.
second.
there is one of these.
Oh, no.
Go do not go there alone.
If we all go,
notice us much sooner. You two wait here.
put this away.
where your friends?
wait down at the entrance.
I'm sorry, my friend.
Not planned to see.
What did you do?
I killed him.
You saved my life.
house.
house, I would have done,
what is required, and the consideration of my face.
you have done what they should do, okay?
okay? Everything is fine.
Oh, shit.
seems that we need
serum rather than we thought.
here below is the bomb.
seems to be high in five minutes.
and then it will spread the virus real.
we have to defuse.
- Do you know how to do it? - No.
then we have to get out of here.
I know
laboratory where we can finish the means.
This is completely tamper.
if they really want to kill us,
why they have not done
at the entrance?
will kill us,
determine police.
but die in the accident,
keep the secret of the tomb.
No, no
If we now call the police.
Let me guess.
line is dead?
could be anywhere else.
steal, do you hear me?
this other output, as long as we need to
about until then?
20 minutes, but this is the
16 minutes more than we have.
so we need more time.
bloody hell!
I ll try with my code.
curse.
Son of a bitch!
one floor down there is still space
security. - What is the benefit?
since we are certainly not pure.
Scheißegal.
Even goes a step aside.
do not think so.
burn in there.
how to burn?
- Fluorine, sulfur acid.
Let's go grouse hunting.
- You're not going to shoot them.
in less than five minutes will
virus spreads throughout the building.
this does the job for us.
all we have!
let me times.
The only question I still
can save, is the treatment. Hurry!
only three minutes!
clouds.
45 seconds!
try the other hand.
nine!
eight!
seven!
six!
five!
four!
three!
two!
now!
contamination detected
Come .
- I forgot a little something.
in the laboratory in the basement 6
you can quit.
6-storey underground?
- As is the output.
this is completely impossible.
- And on top of that very process.
okay.
Well, then you do not believe me.
but it will not be long,
even men again.
you will not be very happy
when they discover their mate.
be produced
treatment and I promise I will take you out of here.
Well, we're in business.
I want to hear it from your mouth, Beth.
promised Ted. - Yes, well.
very good.
if I'm not to spill things,
find me rather than a plastic bottle.
I have!
as well, and we follow you.
okay.
term here!
they are there.
Come back again!
we just go over there to get out!
- No, we must be disposed of somehow.
okay, I do not need two
plastic bottles with screw caps.
and fills it half full with warm water
.
Let's talk with our man,
we will do you no harm!
We know he is in there!
here, and warm water.
What is nonsense?
We break into the store and good.
I think so too.
Well, forward, boys!
hunker down!
they're plastic bottles only.
go!
the elevator does not work,
then we must take the stairs. Go!
will still catch
's alive?
I guess that this was "no."
what's going on?
cursed.
to proceed, and you fucking door!
I correct?
This is the only way out?
in our room maintenance
floor above.
since the must-have tool!
have checked every room.
Come on, please.
hello? - Hey, boy. - Dad?
we have to go very soon.
You can even pack but already
and wait for me outside the front door,
within a few hours and I'm there.
- you, Dad, will teach me Spanish?
Why? - Speaking at a training camp
certainly all Spanish, what do you think?
Yes, of course, no doubt,
course will teach Spanish.
you, Reese? - Yes?
I love you, my son.
I love you too, Dad.
bingo!
do not know,
how to deal with it? - Clear.
I think what.
You have shown your father.
he had to wait until I was eight,
me because before the mask was too big.
welding wire and mask
We also have to take with them.
when we're through, we welding
the other side of the door. - A good idea.
now they will have to rise.
did you weld shut the door?
- There's no time!
okay? - Well.
blast door hinges off.
everything okay? - Let me take a brief pause. -
There is no time, Ted!
chemistry lab
equal right around the corner, behind the offices.
should talk to you alone, Ryan.
Come on, we must go.
- Should we continue?
one minute more.
Well, then you will get it before,
I kümmre him. - What, seriously?
Yes, we immediately thereafter, Beth.
okay.
What is it?
stick?
house has a heart
absolutely in the right place,
but they do not think
tomorrow is still in the future.
even if we get out of here, chasing
Lionel us more, and he will never give up.
if the drug on the market,
go ScopaMed broken. He said he could never be.
Well.
If we set ourselves apart abroad
we might have a chance
but because we need coal.
- you want to sell drugs?
never since they will participate.
- Of course not.
but without the money and we are as good as dead
you just do not think about the future far enough.
This is the reason to have a low
decision.
I promise you, when you were here with
whole skin outside, they will be grateful to you.
Ryan, and here no one doubts
at your wits.
you're also smart enough to follow
house.
I do not follow her,
applied only once.
she did not tell you?
- What you can not say?
she did not start with us,
If we do not offer you a job, too.
thought he knew de
Well, I know a few people,
may buy the agent.
from? - UltriTech.
UltriTech? - Not what you think
I have never been spies or so for.
Ryan, I'm a huge pile of shit on
UltriTech or ScopaMed.
We are all on our own.
listen, I convey to you the deal UltriTech
across the stage, and we share the fifth session, okay?
okay.
A condition I would have. - What?
agent working under my name.
what you want?
already clear.
And the Nobel Prize for medicine goes to Ryan Earl.
A million dollars as an encore.
- It's me, but not on coal.
not, in the end I want to
deserve recognition.
I completely
plowed just like home.
of me is the process of
to reduce side effects.
Well, I agree. You reap
glories, but only if you promise
you together
house means herstellst now.
I've already promised.
- the house, and I have my doubts.
was there once and indifferent.
And do it
Well, come on. Come.
moment! What were you doing here?
- What is the question?
this afternoon, I've been here before!
Yes, you are.
I should check to see whether we can put
laboratories old repaired.
I do not believe one word of what you say!
Lionel has his little secret
keep a ten-year-old himself,
But last year, he reveals to you.
what I did,
that this man trusts you?
house, and this does not help us more than that.
We need to help him.
Do you trust him?
- Yes, I do.
then come with me, and I have to show you something.
we do not have time for that.
was right.
Now we need to the lab. - Ryan! Please...
We are more effective when we split.
Radio me when you find them.
What the hell are you doing?
- Ryan, are you following me easy!
Do you still believe in the story of Ted?
it dead
wait!
Do not touch me!
Well, well, everything is fine!
please do not hurt me!
let me go!
I will not hurt!
I'm going to hurt you in any way.
I'm just your shackles here!
No, no!
so, he did. Even.
you are free.
where he Alfredo?
which is Alfredo?
- my husband is gone......
help, please! - Everything will be fine.
we make the same drug for you and Alfredo.
Oh, damn!
I've lost my stick USB.
Need me in my earlier...
Is... fell out of my pocket.
Come on, we need to find it!
wait!
you know I just formula
you downloaded on your laptop above. - And?
I find myself on the corporate network,
also have access from here.
help the woman out of bed.
my poor husband! Please...
you have to find him!
He does not speak your language...
tell me your name? - Clarissa.
Clarissa, and I promise you,
find your spouse.
you can stand?
Yes. - Let's go.
very good...
copy this file to disk...
finish
fine...
you can not run.
that's okay, I have a formula.
thankfully.
we lack a two-step, yes?
we come right back, okay?
House, we have to go.
now come at last!
come back again.
not!
bring me medicine!
then both of you are free and you can go!
go on!
Phytomenadione!
exactly what we need.
not move or will stab for!
give me an injection.
just take and that is to Clarissa.
take with this is for you!
- I ask you, Alfredo, wait!
let him go quietly.
- needs an injection but also!
syringe he will bring Clarissa,
which explains everything
and then we can deal with it.
knock knock!
come out!
Clarissa!
Do you smell that?
No, you can not smell natural.
What do you mean? Spanking Me?
I am a bad time?
Are you okay? - Yes.
Ryan!
Is finished?
Yes.
come, let's go to the next room,
there is less smoke.
Clarissa?
Clarissa, this is done, I have medicine!
Oh no! No, no, no!
Hey, Clarissa!
Clarissa!
What about the father?
but you promised me,
when he gets home!
you'd better stay here.
- Leaving me!
left me!
- No, wait!
you know I just formula
you downloaded on your laptop above. - Yes.
I find myself on the corporate network,
also have access from here.
O God...
here is...
shit, but here there is no cable network!
from here is not in his power in the laptop!
What is there to think about?
- you simply want to publish?
Yes, this is probably not a question!
- For anyone but deserves recognition!
this does not help us.
We need to help him.
Do you trust him?
Yes, I do.
God!
stop it!
What do you do?
- I want the formula!
Write a comment
- I've had to have all the time!
It's not what you think...
Why lie to me?
tell her the truth, Ryan.
we decided to sell the formula to UltriTech
and earnings per share.
house, I've done it for us.
Lionel is not us but
just let them get away!
That's why we need money
for a new life, 'understand it yet!
Are you crazy?
- please! Think about it!
How can you?
millions of people at this moment in the family home medical, and
and hope and pray
because they desire
one week just to live longer.
only one day
or just an hour!
parents who did not experience how
register their daughters to college.
not to mention the graduation ceremony...
you also do not know who she married.
weighs never
newborn grandson.
not.
do not do it, please.
Oh my God!
I'm so sorry incredibly!
my son Reese...
he had a brain tumor,
was unfit for work altogether.
A year ago, he had then
of bleeding in the brain sharp.
Lionel did not,
he would have died from it.
gave me medicine,
If you're in the back
illegal human experiments that lead.
I've let myself in it.
I never wanted to,
that someone takes damage.
I just wanted my son to live on.
today, has asked him to do it again.
He threatened to kill Reese.
I did not have any choice.
have hopes that I could get away with Reese.
start a whole new life.
in a distant land.
What a silly idea.
for the rest of our lives we have been on the run!
was constantly lived in fear of our pursuers.
this is not the life for him.
it's worth, but why...
... better.
Thank you.
here, contact the FBI.
you have me and Lionel.
wait, and I'll help you. - No, that's okay.
skin of representation Yes
not so fast, and drugs.
you must first past offices,
then the second door on the right.
the way to the tunnel emergency
through the boiler room.
because the right and again,
and follows through to the end of the tunnel.
then I came in the woods.
early to practice football, is not it?
Come on.
Yes, exactly
pharmaceutical company ScopaMed, and right.
okay.
you are traveling.
and you are absolutely sure
we are here is not it?
he says:
tunnel emergency is right at the back. - Hey!
moment! Moment.
This is a drug.
Without the virus will kill you!
and you might be,
but let's run.
your negotiating position is unfortunately not very favorable.
take this.
take over!
okay...
not, Pete!
with an open wound
I still infected for a long time.
I'll get you a syringe. - Do not!
please think after.
you've got the formula!
but if it kills you,
people will never learn.
you have to get out of here!
have to achieve
immediately to safety! - Do not!
Ryan! Go! - Do not!
can not die! - Ryan!
listen, you take Das.
and whatever happens,
not come again.
do not go! Ryan!
Ryan!
O God...
Come...
drawing.
Air here is great.
hello to you in the party, pal.
Do you have a call? - No.
our team handles it already.
Hey, you have no power here!
Mr. Lionel Stanton? - Yes.
stand accused of murder,
I was under house arrest.
not!
No, wait!
you may do so.
our
bake chocolate cake for you.
with cream paint...
and jelly beans......
Well, you're sleepy?
Finally you're awake again.
hurt you...
- No, I'm fine.
when I was gone?
four days.
and Ted?
not.
I found it here with you in the woods.
and I think that belongs to you.
not.
all people in the world to which it belongs.
As I mentioned earlier today and the two universities
mysterious formula by e
received from an anonymous sender.
it seems, and this is in fact
to be an effective drug for cancer.
course, even
need extensive testing
but at the moment there are all the important breakthrough
about.
yesterday
held 9 Montana Beer Festival
The crowd was phenomenal as always.
in memory of Ellen Gould and all the brave souls who fought
against cancer.
hope we find one day in the drug.