We have got to stop
meeting like this.
Whoo.
Just came in from county hospital.
Yeah? What do we got?
Well... it's a little hard to tell.
Oh. Burn victim, huh?
- Yeah.
- Huh.
- That has gotta be the worst way to go.
- Yeah.
Would you like the honors?
- Oh, well, you are too kind.
- [LAUGHS]
You can take off now if you want to.
Hey. I got 10 minutes left, okay?
- Stop trying to get rid of me.
- Believe me, I'm not.
You're more than welcome
to stay all night if you want.
Not that you would want to stay
all night. I'm sure you have plans.
I'm just meeting some
friends for drinks.
I mean, it's nothing special.
Oh, yes, that's right.
It's, uh... it's your birthday.
Yeah. It is my birthday.
Actually, in two hours,
it is my birthday.
Hey, you should take a look
at this before you take off.
- Why? What is it?
- It's crazy.
Seriously, I've never seen
anything like it before in my life.
And I have seen some pretty
crazy things come through here.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah. I'm ready.
- Happy birthday.
- [LAUGHING] Oh, my God.
Oh!
My God, that's so, so sweet.
It was nothing.
This is not nothing.
Really, I mean,
you should come tonight.
I'd love for you to meet my friends.
I-I'd love to, but I'm, uh...
I'm working the graveyard.
I'm pretty sure that Holden would
kill me if I took a leave of absence.
MALE NEWSCASTER ON COMPUTER:
Told analysts and investors...
it's an even wider than expected
loss in the second quarter.
Cake! Finally!
- Hey! Were you in on this too?
- Of course I was.
- Aw.
- Happy birthday, babe!
Aw, thank you.
Not that I would forget
it was your birthday.
Seth hasn't shut up about
it for the last month.
Two months, Professor X. Two months.
Professor X. I like that.
You're lucky I'm stuck
in this chair...
or my boot would be halfway
up your smart ass by now.
Oh, yeah? Who told you I
was into that kind of thing?
Hey! You two stop flirting.
Go get a room already.
All right. And on that
note, you are done.
Are you sure you two will
be able to cope without me?
Yes. Get out of here.
Go make some bad decisions.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, can I get my phone, please?
- Yeah.
- [COMPUTER: MALE NEWSCASTER]
- There you go.
- Oh, thanks.
FEMALE NEWSCASTER: Breaking news
of what police are referring to...
as a series of brutal murders...
- at the derelict Blackwell Hotel...
- [PHONE RINGING]
- involving a group of youth offenders.
- Yeah?
[SCREAMING]
FEMALE NEWSCASTER: Nine fresh bodies.
Police reports now indicate that dozens
more in various stages of decay...
are being found
throughout the building.
That could bring the death
toll up to a few dozen.
These murders look to be linked
to a series of murders...
Yeah, we're watching it right now.
In an ongoing investigation
into the God's Hand killer...
Okay, will do.
Which is in direct reference to the
religious articles found at the scene.
Well, there goes our quiet night.
- How many bodies?
- Nine.
Decomps don't need to be
pieced together to I.D.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna stay and help you guys out.
No, no, no. It's your birthday.
Go out and celebrate.
No! I'm more of a cake and
cadavers kind of gal.
- Mmm.
- I'm just gonna make a quick call though.
[PHONE BEEPING]
- [LINE RINGING]
- Come on, Tamara.
Yeah, right about now I wish I was
writing a book about you asking her out.
- I'm gonna ask. Okay?
- Right.
And I'm gonna get
feeling back in my legs.
Hey, it's Tamara. You know the drill.
Hey, Tam, it's Amy.
Okay, don't freak out, but I'm gonna
have to take a rain check on tonight.
Ooh, look at that. Ooh.
- Knock it off. She's gonna hear you.
- Oh, look at that. Look at that.
- Stop, she's gonna hear you.
- Hear what? This?
Stop, stop! Don't be a dick.
- Stop!
- Amy, put it in. Amy, put it in.
- I swear I will shank you with this.
- Wanna borrow my chair?
But it's going to be
pandemonium here.
- You gonna feel this?
- Do it. Do it.
- I'll do it.
- Here she comes.
- What are you guys doing?
- BOTH: Nothing.
- [LAUGHS] Liar. Here.
- Yeah. No problem.
- All right, let's get to work.
- [BEEPING]
All right.
- Let's do this.
- After you.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[MONITOR: SUSTAINED TONE]
Clear!
[BEEPS]
- We're losing him.
- Clear!
- Again!
Do we really want to save this guy?
Clear!
[SUSTAINED TONE]
He's gone.
You know, I really appreciate
you staying and helping.
[CHUCKLES] Don't worry about it.
We'll get it done twice as fast.
This is the last one.
We've got a Jacob Goodnight.
Hey, this is the psycho that did it.
All right.
- [GASPS]
- Shoot! Shoot, shoot.
AMY: Scared me.
- Hey!
- Uh, I'll take the stairs.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[BELL DINGS]
No, no. Aah!
Oh, God.
[CLICKING BUTTON]
[SIGHS] Come on.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Seth?
- Boo!
- [BOTH SCREAMING]
You're such an asshole.
- You're gonna get your butt kicked.
- No, come on.
I'm unscareable.
- Oh-ho-ho! Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- We'll see about that.
- You can try your hardest.
- It ain't gonna happen.
- Oh.
All right.
[BEEPS]
Good.
- Seven feet.
- [WHISTLES]
[GURGLING]
- [GASPS] Oh, my God.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Aah!
Here. Here.
Uh, it's a... it's a death rattle.
You'd think he'd have
bought me dinner first.
Why don't you let me finish up here?
You've done enough for today.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
Just save me some cake.
Okay.
But I'm not making any promises.
[BOTH LAUGH]
MAN: [WHISPERING] Amy.
Holden?
Are you in here?
Holden, are you calling me?
Holden?
Hello?
[SHRIEKS]
ALL: Surprise!
[LAUGHING, CHATTERING]
You guys, seriously?
[SQUEALING, LAUGHING]
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday!
If Amy can't come to the party,
then the party shall come to Amy.
Oh, my God. Awesome.
You're already drunk.
No, I... Why would you say that?
Yes! Seriously, I could
lose my job over this!
- How did you guys get in here?
- Happy birthday, Amy.
There he is, our fellow conspirator.
Hey! We can't have Twitter trending
photos of dead bodies tonight.
- ♪♪ [SPEAKERS: DANCE]
- Oh, you guys!
Yeah, you can't smoke in here.
- Why?
- You just can't.
There's too much flammable liquids.
Well, well, well.
I did not expect to see you here.
You didn't think I'd miss my
sister's birthday, did you?
- Plus, Kayla insisted.
- Ah.
Oh, well, in that case,
I guess you can stay.
Although I did expect it to be in
a bar, not in a morgue, but...
Yeah, well... Let me guess.
Tamara's idea?
What? No!
- Whoa!
- [LAUGHING]
I'm just saying that I'm
living your dream job.
I know.
- Hey. Hi, Seth.
- Hey.
It looks like I made it to
your birthday party after all.
You did. Let me introduce you around.
I want you to meet my friends.
- This is Carter.
- Hey.
- Kayla.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Oh, my gosh!
This is our bartender, Tamara.
And that's Will.
- That's my brother.
- Oh.
So, are my eyes fooling me, or are
you standing around without a drink?
No, no, I shouldn't.
I got some more work...
No, you should. Just one.
Just one. No, you can have two.
- All right, I'll have one.
- Well, cheers!
- Cheers, guys.
- Cheers!
- Happy birthday!
All right, let's get
this party started, yo!
KAYLA: Yes!
- ♪♪ [CONTINUES]
- [LAUGHING, CHATTERING]
- Do the white man dance!
- Oh, yeah!
- ♪♪ [CONTINUES]
- [LAUGHING, CHATTERING CONTINUE]
She likes you.
- Excuse me?
- My sister. She likes you.
Yeah, you know,
we just work together.
Right. [SNICKERS] Hey, man, look.
Look, I'm not trying to be a jerk here.
But look, I don't want to
see her waste her life...
working the graveyard
shift at the city morgue.
Okay? She's better than this.
She deserves better.
All right? She deserves more.
She deserves someone
who can offer her more.
Sure.
Yeah, absolutely.
I gotta get back to work.
♪♪ [CONTINUES]
TAMARA: Tamara's always in charge
of drinks. That's all Tamara does.
Here. Drink.
♪♪ [CONTINUES, FAINT]
Oh, gosh, my feet are sore.
Mmm. Hmm.
Hey.
So tell me, what exactly
happened today?
It's trending on Twitter that some
guy went totally postal across town.
Baby, you promised in the car.
No, it's... it's cool, yeah.
It's something else really.
My girl is somewhat of a connoisseur
of psychopathic behavior.
She's been online all night learning
everything she can about this guy.
[GIGGLES]
Interesting.
Yeah.
- It is interesting.
- Uh-huh.
You'll have to ask Seth or Amy about it.
They just brought in the bodies.
Bodies?
Oh. Like how many dead?
Unknown. But nine ended up here.
They got the killer though, right?
Oh, yeah. Sure did.
Yeah, we got him on ice downstairs.
Mmm.
That's good. That's good they got him.
He won't hurt anybody else.
Oh, well. Anyway...
Baby, don't get too excited.
Oh, I am very excited.
- I want to see him.
- Okay.
- [WHISPERING] I want to see him.
- Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Don't squeeze me
like that. I have to pee.
That just goes right through me.
Where's the little girls room?
- It's down the hall and to the left.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go with her and make
sure she doesn't get lost.
Hey.
What did you say to Seth?
We were just talking.
Yeah, I don't need the whole
I'm-a-concerned-brother routine.
I'm just looking out for you.
That's the problem, Will.
I don't need you to.
Okay? I can look out for myself.
Christ, Amy, you dropped
out of med school for this.
You should be saving lives,
not dealing with dead bodies.
What? What are you... What is this?
Huh? What, do you think I
owe something to the world?
I owe something to you?
I owe something to Mom?
No. No, I don't.
Okay? You owe it to yourself for
always taking the easy way out.
I am taking the easy way out
because I chose a career...
that you and her just
don't approve of?
I like my job!
I do. I like my life.
I know that you guys think that
you know what's best for me.
But it has always been
me taking care of me.
And you, of all people,
you know that.
Happy fucking birthday.
WILL: Amy.
Amy!
- Amy.
- Will, just...
Don't. Just ease off.
I just wish she'd listen
to me once in a while.
Neither of you guys
listen to each other.
At least you outgrew her.
She can't beat you up now.
That's how we talk to each other.
Well, cheers.
No. You have to look
the person in the eye.
I mean, otherwise it's
seven years of bad sex.
- Cheers.
Much better.
[SIGHS]
Experts say that serial killers...
are triggered by, like, some kind
of chromosomal abnormality...
that starts to express
itself during... Whoa.
Puberty, I think.
[LAUGHING, MUTTERING]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
"She deserves someone
who can offer her more."
[SIGHS]
[SQUISHING]
[BELL DINGS]
- No, wait.
- Oh, Yeah.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Look what we have here.
- I don't know about this.
- Mm-mm-mmm.
- Fuck.
- I do.
Just shut up. I will totally
make this worth your while.
♪♪ [WHISTLING]
♪♪ [HUMMING] Oh!
[GASPS]
That's so inappropriate! Oh, my God.
♪♪ [HUMMING CONTINUES]
[GASPS]
Who do you think this is, huh?
Huh? Who do you think this is?
Hello.
Is it? Is it?
Oh!
It is! It's him! This is him! This is him!
I saw him on the news!
Jacob Goodnight.
I really don't think
this is a good idea.
Oh, really? What about this?
This is probably not a
good idea either. Right?
This is probably a terrible idea.
[WHISTLES, GASPS]
[CHUCKLES]
He killed, like,
eight people. Uh-huh.
Why'd you do it, big boy? Huh?
Did Mommy make you do it?
- Baby.
- Yeah?
Please get off the
dead guy. I mean it.
[CHUCKLING]
You know his mom...
Margaret, I think.
She was this weird
fundamentalist religious nut.
Was all obsessed with, like, sin...
and punishment.
And not like in the fun way.
In the fun way.
[LAUGHING] That is just disturbing.
[LAUGHS]
She used to keep him in a cage and,
like, ceremoniously torture him.
That's mean.
I'm sorry.
Hmm? You're dead? [GASPS]
Oh.
Tamara! What the fuck are you doing?
What? God!
Are you jealous?
Oh, my God, you're jealous. [LAUGHS]
You shouldn't be jealous...
of that.
Of him.
He's all cold. Blah. Cold.
You're hot.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hot.
Cold. Hot.
Hot. Hot.
Hot, hot, hot.
Hot, hot.
Hot. Hot.
Hot. Uh-huh.
♪♪ [WHISTLING]
- That's pretty bad.
- What?
I am totally keeping pace with you.
[LAUGHS] Yeah, well,
it's a marathon. It's not a sprint.
That sounds like loser talk...
from someone who can't
keep up with a girl.
Are you cheered up now?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm cool. I just...
I worry about her. She's my sister.
I think it's sweet
that you care so much.
Kayla, come on.
Don't. It's fine. I'm...
I'm gonna go find Amy before
I make a bigger fool of myself.
Come on. You don't
even know this place.
You're just gonna get lost.
- Why not?
- What?
Why don't you like me?
I like you.
But...
You're like a sister to me.
♪♪ [SPEAKERS: ROCK]
♪♪ [CONTINUES]
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Baby, baby, get your ride ♪
- Yeah! Yeah! Yes! Yeah!
- Come on. Come on!
Oh! Yes! Oh! Yes!
- [GRUNTING, MOANING]
- Yes!
[GRUNTING, MOANING CONTINUE]
Yes! Oh! Oh!
That's it! That's it!
- Come on!
- Yes! Yes!
- Right!
- Yeah!
This is it! Oh!
- Jacob?
- I'll be anyone you want me to be!
Jacob?
- No, no, no, look.
- [LAUGHS]
- [EXHALES]
- Where's the body?
- What?
- Shut up!
It's just the guys messing around.
No, no, no. No, no, wait. Hang on.
How could they move the body?
- I don't know.
- [TAMARA SCREAMS]
- CARTER: Shit!
- TAMARA: Shit.
Okay.
Listen, take my hand.
Don't let go. Okay?
There's the door.
I see light coming through.
- Someone's just being a dick.
- Okay.
If someone's just being a dick...
why are you whispering?
- What?
Ow! Shit!
Guys?
You down here?
- Okay, let's go.
- Okay.
Oh! Ow! Ow! Ow!
CARTER: Shh. Shh.
Did you hear that?
[SCREAMING]
[TAMARA SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
Once your soul's clean,
you'll be the hand of God.
I see that! I see what you're doing.
[WHIMPERING, SOBBING]
What are you doing? Let go!
Ungrateful bastard! You hear me?
Don't you see the sin?
[SOBBING]
I s... I see it.
[JACOB CONTINUES SOBBING]
- [CARTER GROANING]
- [JACOB SOBBING]
[WHIMPERING] Oh, man, I'm sorry.
I see...
it!
Please! Please!
No, man! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I m sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
All right? Please! Please! Let me go!
- Please let me go!
- I see it!
- [GROANING]
- [JACOB ROARING]
[CRUNCHING]
[GASPING, CHOKING]
[TAMARA SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING]
[WAILING] Oh! No! Oh!
You guys! No!
Oh, God! This is bad! This is so bad!
This is so bad!
You guys! You guys!
[TAMARA CONTINUES SCREAMING]
What the hell?
[TAMARA SCREAMS, DISTANT]
- Hold on.
- [SIGHS] What?
- I heard a scream.
- Oh, did you?
Oh.
I didn't hear anything.
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- Oh, God. Tamara.
She's just messing around, right?
We should check it out.
Seriously?
- What?
- I don't know.
I panicked, and then
I just attacked him.
Oh, my God, Kayla. Really tactful.
I know.
But it still counts as
progress though, right?
Any of you jokers down here?
Look, I'm not gonna
do this all night!
Help! Help!
Help!
[YELLS, WHIMPERING]
[CHAIN RATTLES]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMING] No! No!
[HOLDEN SCREAMS, MUFFLED]
- That doesn't sound like messing around.
- That came from downstairs.
Come on. This way.
[BELL DINGS]
Where did the body go?
- What body?
- The...
- Jacob Goodnight.
- Jacob who?
The guy who killed everyone
at the Blackwell Hotel.
Hey.
Gross!
Oh, my God!
[SCREAMING]
What the heck?
- [SWITCH CLICKING]
- [SIGHS]
[CLICK]
That sucks less.
My God! Who did that to Carter?
[GASPING] Where's Tamara?
- Oh, my... Oh, my God!
- When was the last time you saw her?
I don't know! She left with Carter!
Okay, the first thing we
need to do is call the cops.
But our phones are
locked in the office!
- Oh, God!
- Okay! Calm down!
[STAMMERING]
Give me your... Give me your lighter.
- Here you go.
- Thank you. Okay.
- Okay.
Okay. We have to find them.
Come on. Let's go.
[KAYLA SOBBING]
- [SOBBING CONTINUES]
- Okay, guys, quiet.
Give me a break.
[KEYS JINGLING]
♪♪ [WHISTLING]
Hey, guys?
Amy?
Holden?
Amy's friends?
[CLANKING]
KAYLA:
It's not working! What do we do now?
Okay, we're here. We need
to take the stairwell here.
Is that the only way out? What if
whoever did that to Carter is up there?
The stairs are the only way.
We head up now,
we can be out of here
in 10 minutes flat.
- No!
- Amy, no, wait! Amy! Wait!
[KAYLA GASPS] What is that?
[GASPING CONTINUES]
- Shh.
- [KAYLA CONTINUES GASPING]
Shh!
- Amy, don't go over there.
- Shh!
[WHISPERING] No.
Oh, my God!
- Okay. Okay.
- [HOLDEN GASPS]
- Oh, God.
- [HOLDEN COUGHS]
[WHIMPERING] Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- I don't know what to do.
- [GASPING, COUGHING]
[KAYLA WHISPERS] Amy.
Oh, God.
[WHIMPERING]
I'm sorry. I don't know what to do.
WILL: Let's go.
[SOBBING]
- Let's go.
- Let's go this way.
Christ!
- [SIGHS]
- [CLANKING]
Who's there?
[CLANKING]
- [SCREAMING]
- Oh, my God.
Hey! Oh, my God! Come here.
Come here. It's okay.
[SCREAMING]
Are you bleeding? You're bleeding!
It's not my blood. It's Carter's!
You're gonna be okay.
We're gonna stick together.
No! He's dead! He killed him!
- Who?
- Jacob. Jacob. Jacob Goodnight!
No. No way.
- Jacob Goodnight is dead.
- No! It was him!
- He's a goddamn corpse!
- It was him!
Jacob Goodnight is not dead.
He's not dead. He's not dead anymore.
He probably faked it so he
wouldn't have to get locked up.
I don't know. He's in here now,
and we really pissed him off.
Whoa, whoa. What do you
mean, "We pissed him off?"
I thought he was dead.
Tamara, what did you do?
He got up while Carter
and I were, you know...
KAYLA: Oh, my God! Are you kidding me?
You did it in the morgue?
I thought he was dead!
Shh!
Uh, have you s... have you seen Seth?
No. No. No.
We have to go find him.
Oh! Oh! Where's... wheelchair guy?
Holden... Uh, Holden's dead.
[WHIMPERING]
Oh, God. Oh, God. Please tell me
you know how to get out of here.
Yeah. It's just a little
bit further. Come on.
Oh, man.
[CLANKING]
What the hell?
[SETH SCREAMING, WHIMPERING]
Come on. This way.
[TAMARA BABBLING]
Stupid door! [GRUNTS]
- Now what are we gonna do?
- [CHATTERING, SHRIEKING]
It's a security door, Will.
That's not gonna work.
Is there another way out?
- Oh, my God! We're trapped!
- I don't want to do this.
Hold on. Let me think!
- [THUDDING]
- Amy!
- Open the door!
- KAYLA: Open it!
WILL: Open the door, Seth!
Come on, come on, come on!
- You okay?
- [SHRIEKING, CHATTERING]
- Why are you locking the door?
- Jacob Goodnight is alive!
He killed Holden and Carter.
[SCREAMING]
- No!
- [GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERING]
- Let's go!
- Go, go, go! Amy!
Come on! Let's go!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
This way.
- [WHISPERING] Here.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Go!
Come on!
Slow down!
[GASPING, WHIMPERING]
Guys?
Amy?
Will?
[SOBBING] Somebody? Please.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God. Oh, my...
Shit.
- You know where you're going, right?
- Yeah.
Usually.
Look, just stay close. Nothing
ever good comes of splitting up.
- Let's go. In here.
- Will, slow down.
- Amy, get in here!
- What? Why?
No! No! No!
Great, Will! Now we lost everybody.
It's not my fault your
friends can't keep up!
- He's out there!
- So are my friends!
And if they have any sense,
they'll hide, like us.
You are so selfish.
I've seen you pull some
pretty low crap...
but I don't even know
who you are right now.
Because I don't want
to just charge out...
when there's some mass murderer
hanging out? Think about it.
I'm not letting him kill you.
[WHIMPERING, SOBBING]
- Please.
- [FOOTSTEPS]
- [CLANKING]
- [WHIMPERING, SOBBING CONTINUE]
Someone help me. Help me.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [GASPING]
Oh, my gosh.
[DOOR HANDLE RATTLES]
- Shit. Okay.
- Oh, shit.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Come on. Come on.
[THUMPING ON DOOR]
It's locked. It's locked,
it's locked, it's locked.
Okay.
[WHIMPERING] Wait! Wait!
[CHOKING]
[CRUNCHING]
[NECK CRACKS]
And he's told you what to do.
Are you insane?
This is not what God wants.
Don't you see it?
[CHOKING]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
MARGARET:
Open your eyes and wash the sins out.
I can't.
I won't!
Oh, thank God.
That's the voice of God.
And he's told you what to do.
Why would God...
help you?
Touch her. This is how to touch her.
Once your soul is clean,
you'll be the hand of God.
Touch her.
You're a dirty whore!
No. No.
Look at her. Haven't you learned anything?
Do you see the evil in her eyes?
Don't you see the sin?
KAYLA: Please.
I see the sin on you.
[CHOKING]
- KAYLA: Please.
- I see it.
[CHOKING STOPS]
TAMARA: This place is a goddamn maze.
SETH: This way. Come on. This will
lead us to the east stairwell.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay, you need to get out. Okay?
And I need to find the others.
What? No. Wait, wait! No, Seth.
You have to come with me. You have to.
We'll go out, call the cops. They'll
come back and take this guy out.
No! I can't live with myself
if something happens to her.
Okay? You get help.
Oh, shit. Shit!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, he's really mad.
Oh, he's really mad! Oh, my God!
- He's really mad.
- Come on. Come on.
Shit!
- Don't you have the keys?
- No! Not to this area.
Okay. Well... Sorry.
[DOOR CREAKING, SLAMS SHUT]
Here. Here! Come on! Come on! Go!
Go, go, go!
Shit. We're stuck.
- We're stuck in here!
- Hide here.
- It's a terrible hiding spot.
- Shh.
Okay, I'm gonna be right over there.
No! No! Don't leave me here. Please.
I'm not gonna leave you. I promise.
Okay. Shh!
I'll be right there. Just hide.
Okay.
- Shh.
- Shh. Shh.
[DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WHISPERS] Hey. Hey.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GASPING QUIETLY]
Shh-shh-shh.
Oh, shit.
[GASPING]
Okay, we need to do something!
There's nothing we can do about it!
You are such a prick!
- [LOUD BANGING]
- Hey!
Amy. [GASPS]
Go! Run! Run!
- [TAMARA CHOKING]
- Amy!
Come on! Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
Go! Let's go! Come on!
Come on!
Let's go! Come on!
Go! Go! Go!
Oh, no! Will! Will!
[GROANING]
Oh, no!
[GRUNTING]
No, no!
[SCREAMING]
Amy, run!
No! I'm not leaving you!
Run, goddamn it!
Get outta here.
We gotta go! Amy, we gotta go!
Will!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[BONE SNAPS]
[SCREAMING, GASPING]
[WILL SCREAMING, DISTANT]
Come on.
[SCREAMS] Oh, my God!
[AMY SOBBING]
- [WILL SCREAMING]
- [THUMPING]
He's alive. He's still alive.
- I have to go back!
- No!
No, Amy! He's gonna kill us both!
No. I'm not running anymore.
I'm not leaving my brother.
- Well, you're not going alone.
- Come on!
[WILL SCREAMING]
Are you sure about this?
I could still hear him.
Oh, God. Come on.
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
He's still alive.
Amy, slow down. Slow.
On three, okay?
Okay, one...
two...
three.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Shit. Oh, come on.
Son of a bitch!
Come on.
That doesn't help much. Come on.
Okay, I got it.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Hey!
[MUFFLED GROANING]
Are you ready?
Yeah.
[MUFFLED GROANING] Amy! Amy!
Okay. Okay. We're gonna
get you out of this.
- Run!
- What?
Run! Run! Run!
[SCREAMING]
[CHOKING, SCREAMING]
Oh, Will!
No! You bastard! He's my brother!
- [SCREAMS]
- Amy!
Amy, go!
[SCREAMING]
- Let's go!
- Hurry!
- Let me see it!
- I'll live. But we gotta get out of here.
- Let me see!
- We've got no time!
- We gotta go!
- Come on!
[CLANKING]
Damn it. Give me your keys.
Hold on.
Come on.
Seth, come on!
[GROANS]
Shit. Okay.
All right. [GROANS]
- [BANGING, THUMPING]
- Shh-shh.
[FOOTSTEPS]
- Give me the keys.
- Here. Be careful!
Come on.
Go.
I don't see him.
Amy. Hey.
[SOBBING]
Oh, hey, I'm sorry.
They're all dead.
Yeah, but we're alive.
And we can make it.
We can get out of here.
But I need you to be strong
for me, like I know you are.
Okay?
We are gonna get out of here alive.
Hey.
I'm not gonna leave you.
[BANGING]
We just keep moving.
Okay.
SETH: Okay.
Shit.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Is it the right key?
I don't know. They're all
starting to look the same to me.
- It's the wrong one.
- It should be the right one.
Come on, come on.
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Son of a bitch!
- Hurry. Hurry!
- Piece of crap! Come on!
- Damn it!
[GROANING] Come on! Come on!
- Lock it! Lock it up!
- [SHRIEKS]
Run!
[DOOR CLANKING]
Oh, God!
[METAL CLANKING]
Hey.
If we have to run, can you?
Potentially.
Okay. Listen to me.
Get up here.
If I don't do this now...
you are gonna bleed out.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna cauterize the wound.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
This is really gonna hurt.
No, lie to me. Please.
Do you have your wallet on you?
Yeah. I'm down to my...
last five bucks.
Five bucks.
How were you planning on
taking me out on a date?
Well... Well, I mean, I...
I thought that I...
- [GROANS] Son of a bitch!
- Sorry.
Shall we?
- You know what you're doing, right?
- Yes. I do.
I wanted to be a doctor
before I dropped out.
Why did you drop out?
If you don't mind me asking.
Because we all end up here.
No matter what you do.
We all die.
[AMY SIGHS]
- [GROANS]
- Sorry.
- Aah!
- All right.
Bite on this.
Move back.
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
- [MUFFLED SCREAM]
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay. Okay.
- [SLAPS TABLE]
- All right.
Okay, it's done.
It's done. You all right?
Oh, God.
Well, I'm gonna thank you for that?
Seth, look.
Oh, Jesus! Come on!
- [GRUNTING]
- Amy.
- You go get the cops.
- No! We're both gonna go!
Amy, I can't fit through there.
No!
- Do you have your car keys?
- No. They're in Holden's office.
Look. You take my keys, okay?
When you get out,
you go and get help.
- No, I'm...
- It's not open for debate. Okay?
It's our only chance to
get out of here. Okay?
I'm parked out front.
The crappy blue thing?
Yeah, the crappy blue thing.
Goddamn.
Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
He's out there.
- Did he see you?
- I don't know.
[THUMPING]
He's going back up to the cars.
Yeah, of course he is.
I should have parked
around the side today.
Side.
- Seth, we can get out on the side.
- What?
Come on.
[WEAPON SLICING]
Amy? Amy?
Amy! Amy, no, no!
No, no, no! No, you're okay!
Hey! Hey! Stay with me!
Hey! Hey!
Amy! Hey, hey!
Amy.
[GROANS]
Amy!
Amy, come on! No!
Hey! Hey!
[SOBBING]
You bastard.
No.
[CRYING]
Oh, no! No! No! No!
[DOORKNOB JIGGLING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[YELLING] No!
[JACOB GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
You're not so tough.
- [GRUNTS]
- [JACOB GROANS]
Good night.
[SOBBING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SCREAMING]
- ♪♪ [PIANO]
- ♪♪ [GIRL SINGING MELODY]
♪♪ [CONTINUES]
GIRL: ♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ You'll never catch me ♪
♪ Round and round ♪
♪ We all fall down ♪
♪♪ [GIRL CONTINUES SINGING MELODY]
♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ You'll never catch me ♪
♪ Round and round ♪
JACOB: I see it now.
♪ We all fall down ♪ ♪
♪♪ [ROCK]
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ These actions ♪
♪ Mean much more ♪
♪ Than words do ♪
♪ With verses ♪
♪ From passages ♪
♪ Are read aloud and heard ♪
♪ I hear you ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But I can't see you ♪
♪ No, I can't see you ♪
♪ I hear you ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But I can't see you ♪
♪ No, I can't see you ♪
♪ In your hands ♪
♪ These lost souls ♪
♪ Will learn all these lessons ♪
♪ These sinners ♪
♪ Their memories ♪
♪ Are burned alive in faith ♪
♪ I hear you ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But I can't see you ♪
♪ No, I can't see you ♪
♪ I hear you ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But I can't see you ♪
♪ No, I can't see you ♪
♪ There's just no place to hide ♪
♪ And there's just no will to try ♪
♪ My eyes are opening wide ♪
♪ My hands are crucified ♪
♪ There's just no place to hide ♪
♪ And there's just no will to try ♪
♪ But I will open me wide ♪
♪ My hands are crucified ♪
♪ And I think I'm going blind ♪
♪ And I think I'm going ♪
♪ Blind ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I hear you ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But I can't see you ♪
♪ No, I can't see you ♪
♪ I hear you ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But I can't see you ♪
♪ No, I can't see you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪♪