If you were a man
I'm Dick Nolan and invention
things for a living
I'm a reporter
It is the strangest story
you have covered
He started the day that Margaret Ulbrich
she left her husband quencher
And it seemed the best thing to do
Let Jane
honey
You did it!
Are you here!
Look at you now
DeeAnn
-- I know
But I had to adapt and not use
a name that my mother would call me
So you're excited
for all this?
You've established?
How about this Jane?
Jane is fine, is going
a little sweet school
You know, it's really difficult without
his father and all that
Do not know if we can ,,,
-- Come
These better so
Between us never fall me
While Frank
You were a bridesmaid
-- Exactly, so I could not say anything
But if I see him around again
I'll tell
Now come on, you have to have fun
To go to Hungry Eye Jazz
For Italian food
Vanezi
For salvation try
Buddhist temple
For art gallery Sixth
Only show modern art?
All show only
modern art
And in the basement are expressly
I express that is?
I have no idea
You have much to learn
Back then women
they did not leave
Not without a job or prospects
All she had was her
paintings in the trunk
And his daughter in the backseat
good luck
We receive many ladies here
Then your husband approves you work?
My husband and I are separated
Separated?
I realize that I have not
work experience
but really
I need this job have a
daughter support
I'm not very good convincing but
if I like painting
If I could
Show my portfolio
study in
The Art Institute Watkins
Nashville
I did some illustrations
Classes in New York, this is ,,,
A cake I made
And ,,,
This is a portrait coal
If you understand that this is a
furniture company?
They are very nice
-- Yes
Your equipment is adorable
Thank You
How much?
For the special $ 2
I'll give you one
All Right
-- All Right
Let
What's your name?
-- My name is Dylan
Dylan
And how old are you?
I am 9 years
9 years, and ,,,
Even if it could be
respectfully disagree
I like this piece
traditional
Reach out more
Come on, good!
They want to touch it?
Let
Come on, do it!
Do not worry do not break
Worth $ 35
Excuse me a second?
Here
-- Thank You
Thank You
Worth more than the change
You should sell
so cheap
Well I'm just glad
he liked
You passed that point
Your heart is in your work
What's your name?
Margaret
But not you rather flirt
those girls over there?
No, I likes you Margaret
Ulbrich
You know Margaret Ulbrich?
You're underestimating
Let me show you how it's done
little girl
You would have them do your portrait the
world famous Margaret Ulbrich
Queen of the Bay
In mere minutes capture your soul
Do Not
Dont you wish you were your
in this beautiful painting?
That's me
And that's me
And that I was until my mom
He became a Chinese boy
my apologies
I did not understand the situation
Well I better go before Mr, Ulbrich
come and hit me in the eye
Mr, Ulbrich is no longer in the image
Good night, Henry
Sorry for not calling to book
Lucky I have a table list,
madame
Good evening, welcome
Plz follow me
And do I have to pay a dime because
I gave the chef a painting
You know what he said?
-- What?
He said nobody paints my country
as the great Walter Keane
I can not believe you
lived in Paris
The best time of my life
I've never been on a plane
You have to experiment
these things
You have to catch them
I wanted to be an artist so
I went alone
I studied painting there
I lived in a studio
I survived on bread and wine
You're a romantic
Yes, I am!
Of course go there
was not easy
I had to quit my job
Leaving my wife
Yes
these decisions
are not easy
I have never acted
freely
I was a child and then
a wife and then a mother
All my paintings are Jane
because she's all I know
Do not belittle your work
Have an amazing talent
You can see someone and capture
on your canvas
You can paint people
I can only paint things
I mean, my streets are ,,,
lovely
But at the end of the day
They are just a collection of buildings
and sidewalks
Walter, I bet you can
paint whatever
When you look at me so
You could fall in love strongly
Sorry
This goes really fast
I have not been on a date
in a while
Jane, honey, stop moving
Mother after all this time must
know how my face looks
Hey, your canvas is blank
You can not rush inspiration
Do not bother Mr, Keane creativity
comes from within
Do not worry
She does not bother me
I can ask you a question?
What about the large
and crazy eyes?
Oh
Well, I think you can see things
Eye
The eyes are the window
soul
Yes but
The pints in a way very
out of proportion
Okay
The eyes are like Express
my emotions
I have always painted well
When I was little I had surgery
I leave me deaf for a while and
I could not hear so
I stared
Trust the eyes of people
Walter?
Hey, Walt, I thought it was you!
I'm glad to see you
Hear about permissions
for Thursday
Yes? excellent
I'll architects
Ok
What was that?
I did not want you to know
I am in commercial property
You're a real estate agent?
Yes
I am a successful agent, the top of the
office, 3 years on the job
And you ashamed?
Any fool can fix
a sublet
Everything I've ever wanted is
keep me as an artist
I tried to start from scratch
But I did not succeed
I'm just a Sunday painter
Thank You
Sign in here
Put it here
Here?
-- If there is great
I would like that is not
in the way
namely
In something I'm working
You can see
I'm working ,,,
hello
What happens?
Frank wants to take Jane
He says I'm not a proper mother
And ,,,
-- You're perfect
He told the court that
She lacks a suitable house
And that is beyond my
capabilities
As a single mother
Will you marry me?
Do not think of a reason
to say no
Because I have a million reasons
to say that if
I know it makes no sense
But think how much
enjoy ourselves
And I will cherish, girls
Margaret
I'm on one knee
Come on, you say?
Let's get married
We could be in Hawaii
the weekend
Oh, Hawaii, marriage
I do not know Walter I'm crazy about you
but I am very overwhelmed
Why we would go to Hawaii?
Because you're a princess
And you deserve to get married in paradise
You were right
It's paradise
Only God could create these colors
I told you!
We can not stay here
forever?
I do not know if forever
But I guess I could
Fix a week
There was a waterfall and the air was
so fresh you could taste
And this was an ancient altar
That is a statue of Kane
the god of creation
I prayed
Those are Walter and Jane built
the sandcastle together
Well, this happens
very fast
In the time you moved here
I have been on 2 appointments and you and you married
Well I guess there was a gap in
Walter filled my life
Walter has filled many things
It's got all the skirts
art
You're talking about my husband
I know, why I mentioned
I'm not naive
I am naive but
I know who I married
Walter can be impulsive but
It is a good provider
Yes wonderful with Jane
I'm just looking to start from scratch,
I am a divorcee with a girl
Walter is a blessing
Thank You
These on the threshold of incredible success
The theme of the composition is
spontaneity
The image has no center
visual attention
It is very gestural
-- Definitely
Heavily influenced by Tashes
Listen to a famous was
here looking
Well, I'm not allowed to say
Christ
Do not go here right now
please
Ruben
good Morning
You have a moment?
Walter, you're missing the word, quote
I can come back later
You'll love my stuff today
I have not seen that before?
No that was painted at 5
This is the 6th Street
I do not understand, you lived in Paris
for a week
As you can continue taking
paintings?
Everything is here
And here
Well it will not go up here
Walter know you do not go
these representations
You are very literal
Art is a fashion
-- If it is
People want Kandinsky
or Rafko
They do not want
Street scenes
How about this?
My God you've come
to a new period
Do Not
They are from my wife
Why your eyes are so big?
As large gumdrops
and quiet
It's expressionism
Surely you recognize
Well, I'm glad that
have been found
Then you say
I say no, it is not art
It is not art?
I paint for a magazine,
you know the turtle draws
Win a contest
How dare you? A lot
People you may like
If someone but not
enters through
Now please clean this before
good taste police come
It is a secret society of owners
galleries and critics
We will meet on Sunday
to eat something
And recite what is great
As at hearings
McCarthy
I point to this painter
I exiling that painter
There is no man's land
I think people buy
art that touches
If you live in a fairy tale
People unable to discover anything
Buy art because it is in the
time and place indicated
Ok, a welcome to Cal Jader
Well, sure to stay
for the show's 1:00 a,m,
Enjoy, enjoy
apology
Hey I love Banducci
music tonight
this brilliant
-- Thank you, thank
Walter Keane
I am a painter
I was watching your walls
They are very empty
Maybe you're right
What color would seem like good?
No, no
I am an artist, used to live in Paris
Now I have moved to
USA
And I look ,,,
An exhibition debut
I like my club as is
If your stuff is so good
sees it in a museum
I respect that you are a
businessman
Not a charity
such
If I rent your walls?
Walter, Margaret?
Ready?
An art lover
Beautiful, that I can do
for you sir?
Just looking for the bathroom
Thank You
Look at that girl
This sad
It is poor?
It has been forgotten
Makes me want to mourn
You're Keane?
Yes, I am
You're a great painter
Thank you, thank you very much
Your work is very powerful
There are so many emotions
in those eyes
Is something wrong?
Do Not
I did not realize you were talking
the picture of my wife
Oh I get it
The artist does not want to get rid
your favorite piece
Oh honey, thanks
I love him
I had not delayed
Hey Picasso
Good place no?
Thanks for that closet
where I put brooms
Are you talking about? It's just
When people drink have
to relieve themselves
It is insulting
When people see art not
should think about defecating
Hey, careful what you say
Hey, there are ladies present
Never hit a deposit
before
Sorry, laughed Banducci
our art so I fell
Since when are you like? the artists
should handle criticism
you are right
He was already in a bad place
He had taken a couple of drinks and
someone thought I painted your big eyes
What?
I do not understand because
would you do that?
It was a misunderstanding
And then I did not want to compromise
sale
Well do not do it again
Hey
-- Me you do not have a bad time
I only came for my stuff
Can you believe it?
We are exhausted
I even have a chef
It is a Monday!
Walter
We arrived to home page
People are here because
want to see the paintings
Vera adult men fighting
I'm sick of you Keane
I'll see you in court
Son of a bitch!
I'm going to sue
-- I'm tired of you
And your paintings
I'm going to sue for insulting
and offend my great paintings!
Walter Keane was not a
subtle man
But the subtle does not sell
Yes sir
It was a good circus what they did
Dick Nolan, examiner
Hey friend, not you
remove the dream
I take these things with a spoon
gives me something to write
In my column
I thought you wrote only
celebrities
Banducci is famous
and you hit
So you're a celebrity
now
Buy me a drink
Hey Gary
Then, Walter
Tell me about your work
When I was in paris
No, that does not
I refer to the homeless kids
awake
You were a success
That night!
I sold all your big eyes
They love you
Need more paintings!
Walter!
-- Now!
Quiet, this is an opportunity
We must seize
as a team
Go to clubs
You do what you love
Get out
I love you
They know a poet once said
The eyes are the windows to the soul
That's why I paint so great,
I've always done well
If you are interested in that style
I'm working on pieces
I have a blond kid
In a yellow dress
They break your heart
Walter
Honey, why are you here?
why lie
Excuse
Wouldst credit for something
that is not yours
Just trying to close a deal
These kids are part of my being
I am a seller in addition to them
they could not meet the painter
I can not know because
You told me to stay at home
We're making money, your pocket
or mine, what is the difference?
You take so lightly
Not at all
It is no credit, you mean your
you painted? Well I do not care
For me di a monkey painted them
Well I'm glad you can talk
but without an emotional connection
I just want to share
with the world
Wish that they are gathering dust
or hanging in someone's living room?
Who is this man?
That's Dino Olivetti
He's a genius with disks
but not what you think
He does not speak any English
Hey
Good to see you
Mr, Olivetti is delighted
with paint
Want to know who
is the artist
I am what
$ 5,000
We won $ 5,000
And it was not even one
of good
Do you mean one of the YOURS?
No, no, no
Well, our, one of our
We are now hanging in the collection
Italian industrialist Dino Olivetti
With your support comes credibility
And with credibility
Comes respect
What about honesty?
Good painting says "Keane"
I am Keane
You're Keane
From now on
We are one and the same
My sources say the mayor
should expect a big surprise today
On behalf of the children of the world
I present this painting
Mayor of San Francisco
My man on the street tells me that
Soviet ambassadors in the city
Could Talk
In the interest of peace
through culture
Dono this painting people
of the Soviet Union
The Onion
9:30
Crawford Joan has a
Dinner reservations
Ms, Crawford in recognition of his
cinematic genius
We gave this painting!
The cat is out of the bag can reveal
that our local illuminator, Walter Keane
He has opened his own gallery
Rubn drown when you see this
I remember when my mom
He painted it
Segura? It has had to
long time ago
Of course I'm sure
It was in our old apartment
I was on a kitchen bench
Honey're confused
I painted it
My mother did was using
my blue dress
Many little girls have
that dress
Honey, you have a good eye
I painted it but I tried to imitate
the style of your mother
You know how used styles
to paint?
Well you did a good job
hello
Sorry, there had never
done this before
So I do not know ,,,
I was raised a Methodist, if that
a problem can go
No, no please
Do we throw people here
Ok
That worries
Okay ,,,
I lied to my daughter
Why would you do that?
My husband pushed me to do
Only he had never lied before
I'm not that kind of person
Your husband is that kind of person?
I do not think so
He likes to tell stories and
maybe you exaggerate but
He is a good man and
Just trying to save money
buy a house for the family
And the girl, this lie
It will cause damage?
Damage? Do Not
Do Not
No I ,,,
I do not ,,,
Just looking for some answers
Well, the modern world is
a complicated place
occasionally
The children should be protected from
certain truths
Do Not
Not
It seems that her husband tries to do
best of an imperfect situation
She was raised Christian, you know what I mean
The man is the head of the family
Maybe I should
Trust your judgment
I think it's scary
ugly and rookie
exact
I love him
We arrived early
Do not tell me?
Thank You
Hey sweetie
That good party
It's happening
Where is your material?
We decided that this single
would be the show of Walter
Oh
You did?
Why would you do that?
Oh because Walter is more
set
Weird, you know?
Walter does not seem the type to paint
adorable kids and hungry
It's really good to see you
Thanks future
Your husband has enough talent
Your pints too?
I do not know ,,,
Curiosity causes me your ethnic
How long will I take
paint that piece?
That?
Probably months ,,,
First I thought, sketch
Then find the time
alone with the oils
Oils?
Is not acrylic?
Ah that, if
Yes, it's like
A mixture of ideas
Spinning in my head
So where
you get your ideas?
A do you mean?
I mean
Because they are all images
of children?
Our art critic John Canaday
With a perspective on the
Walter Keane work
Keane's work is
completely without distinction
Not a member of society
Artists West
There is someone important
It is only known for his appearances in
gossip columns
Mr, Keane is why
society needs critical
To protect against such atrocities
Mom?
Mom!
I can go ?,
You can not
Mom is busy right now
What are you doing?
Hey sweetie, come
You need to respect
privacy of your mother
Sometimes adults need
time alone
Come
That's the ice cream truck?
Go for a good ice cream!
Out of this world!
I do not feel comfortable with this
I used to do it differently and now ,,,
Jane is fine, went to where the ice cream ,,,
It has new shoes even
a fund for college
maybe
Only this dizzy all
madness of the last days
I need your help
I want to go on television to
defend our art
Wait, come out on TV?
Yes but, you say?
I mean, that forces me to paint
This?
Maybe you have an obsession
with little girls
adorable
Sorry
Imagine painting them
in the corner
Yes
Perhaps the winter warmth
help me
Walter, art is personal
Which requires a grown man
to paint something?
Because I ,,,
I lived surrounded by six sisters
I grew up in an orphanage
I ,,,
I lived in a world
Where adults were gone
and the kids and kittens
They ran wild for
desolate landscape
What about your streets
why you painted?
Well, I lived, I experienced
Not only were streets and flowers?
Of course not
It was after the war
Destruction everywhere
Travel by continent
The slaughter was horrible
My mind was marked
and my art too
Nothing in my life
He has had much impact
As the sight of the children
The war destroyed
innocence
without parents
homeless
Fighting for trash
This is how my life as a painter
It started suddenly
Thenceforth
I painted
The lost kids
With big eyes
those eyes
That always have their
tantalizing quality
How many sales today?
Sales?
None with this public
These people just look,
They can not afford these paintings
But we have given many
posters
I started charging for posters
First five cents, then 10
If people are crazy
But then I started thinking
You would rather sell a painting
$ 500
Or a million posters reproduced
cheaply?
People really do not care
if a copy
They just want art that touches
And we could sell anywhere
Where!
It stinks here, should open
window
What time is it?
6:30
You have there? let me see
Walter No, it's personal
Personal? We are married
We should not hide
each other secrets
Put it up there,
put it up there
It is a style completely
different
Yes, it is
It looks like you
Well, it's ,,,
a self--portrait
I would not know how to explain it
I was thinking that
Maybe I could
Signing myself
That sounds a little confusing,
do not you think?
I mean Keane
I know
But when people ask me
if pinto
I do not know how to respond and be nice
to say, this is mine
Who told him big eyes?
-- Nobody
If you tell someone this
empire collapses
You want to return the money
We have committed fraud
I know
My God, I know
I think about it every minute
of my life
I kept half of the deal
I have not told anyone
Please
Just let me have this
I did not know you painted, Margaret
Yes, do not talk about it
Unfortunately people do not
buy female art
What about Georgia O'Keeffe?
Then Margaret, where
you get your ideas?
Well, the world around me
And I just ,,,
I love Modigliani ,,,
-- Modi what?
Modigliani
Please, it's gossip column,
cling to familiar Angulo
Check out the
little Jane here
That talent!
Look at us to Keane
When you open our veins
bleed oil
Ah a little taste
The fourth member of the
painters Keane
Lily honey, how are you?
I'm fine, Dad
I lost a tooth
Really?
You got into a fight?
No, I fell
Okay!
The tooth fairy is something
I'll deal or your mom and handled it?
She handled it
Well, well
Well, Jane
Come
Come show him the room
of the children
and then
You girls can
have a good time
Walter
You never told me that
had another daughter
I did not? clear
Lily is my first marriage
apology
Sorry, sorry
Walter
I can talk to you?
What's happening there?
That's Lily
Sure that I mentioned
No, you did not
It will move here?
Do Not
His mother go to Vegas
the weekend
I should have it opposes
once a month but
I do not set according to his mom
How could you lie with
something so big?
As it is a very sweet little girl
-- I bet it is
Well I held your daughter
and never said anything
I'll pretend you did not say that
Ok?
Sorry
Please only finish
with this
I have met many
celebrities
And only a certain type of creature
You can live in that light
Walter had that ability,
Margaret? not much
I painted this
Really?
It is very
evocative
sensual
MDH
You are very
mysterious
Yes
Do not use my name because people do not
serious female art
MDH are my initials
And
I'm interested in numerology
As you know, the 7 is a good number
Seven?
Luckily my
maiden name is
Doris Margaret Hawkins
Letter M is number 13
alphabet
D is the number four
H is the number eight
And if one has a
and three from 13
An orgy color
And some ,,,
Sunbeam, sorry
Which makes 4 + 4 + 8
Da 16 and then 1 + 6
da 7
Margaret?
just a moment
Wow, that these babbling?
Divisions?
Could you please help
the world and close your mouth?
They are only interested
in big eyes
Two nuts that fell from the same
tree is insufferable
Why go hungry while
they print money?
Because the nut is a genius
Sell paintings
And sells paintings and images
sells postcards of the images of paintings
I bet you could make a
10 minutes
Would question your sincerity
Ah, customers do not
will realize
Christ is a movement
Hello, DeeAnn
My God, I thought it was
the wrong direction
I know, is a very large entry
I can honestly nor
believe I moved here
I know
We have two acres
a pool
five rooms
I found excessive
Since only ,,,
There are three of us here
Been so long
since I've seen
I know
North Beach is 30 miles
The same would be 300
Well, probably're busy out
with all your rich friends
Please, these are friends
Walter
He brings people here
The Beach Boys came
Are you hungry?
I am thirsty
When we moved I thought
a bar was something extravagant
but
You'd be surprised that both
you can use
So Walter is?
I could not be happier
It has everything you ever dreamed
And you too
fabulous
That is your art studio?
Do you want to go there
I want to look
I want to see what it looks workplace
a successful artist
Oh no, no
DeeAnn? Please do not go there
sight
You can not go in there
Walter pint here too
Walter is at home now?
What the hell happened?
Nothing, I ,,,
I just ,,,
I invited DeeAnn by ,,,
You know I do not like anyone
see my work before finishing
How dare you call
fraud
Shut up, you're a liar, Walter
Get out of my house, my big house
Go to continue looking briefs
fisherman
Fuck
I do not want back
never invite
I will not do
Well, Jane I go to work
I can go?
No, I never can go
I should not even ask
And as you came you here?
Do not you hear
allowed visits?
This has come not?
You're the only living soul
I can tell you my secret
Okay
I painted I
I did it
All and each
All big eyes
I
And no one but you will know
And I will paint another one now
Look what I've come a girl
crazy talking to a dog
A productive day
today
I ran into a hot gossip
The Madame Chiang Kai--Shek
come to town opposite Taipei
I think we should introduce
a painting
Dick's interview
To hell with Dick
I met a new type
UPI
maybe
She would like one of your
street scenes
I know why I did not think you could make a
Trash Chinatown
With adorable and little girls
Something like a mixture of eyes
large and Chinese
Do Not
No, she is a dignitary
and she deserves
A piece that comes directly from you
You think so?
Well, maybe you're right
Probably not have a scene of paris
hung in his palace
Unless the madame and
have a S, Cenic
What did you say?
-- A S, Cenic
Is the painter who did all
your previous work
It was my nickname in Paris
To all my friends paint him
liked both my scenic view
They called me, well they could not
pronounce it properly
I called S, Cenic
The more you lie more
little you look
How dare you accuse me
lying
I am proud of my
previous work
So why paintedst
about the name?
A council never use basis
of water on a oleo
It goes fast
You sound a crazy love
God
You've seen me painting
I have not done
I always thought
He had done it but it's like
a mirage
From a distance you look like a painter
But up close there is not much there
I went to Paris
I studied there
I spent hours and hours
In the Louvre
Looking at the grandeur of the masses
-- Walter
Have you ever been to Paris?
I just wanted to ,,, become
an artist
Just never turned out well
I do not want to sleep here
There are three additional bedrooms
in this house
Go to choose one
The more of these there behind?
I do not know, maybe three thousand or so?
You can print more?
-- Excuse me Miss
How much is this painting
Go, for I pay?
If Mr, Keane
Not even one of mine,
one of hers
This does not change anything
another truth
Who cares?
Maybe it's time to shake
things
And start putting my name
MDH below
Do Not
Absolutely not, and hate me
by letting the first
Shut Up
Do not raise your voice
Oh, I will speak
As strong as you like
Do not do it or I'll kill you
What?
If you tell someone
I watch, I meet people
Remember cousin Banducci,
the seller of liquor wholesale
Are you threatening me?
All Right
Kill Me
My God, I have kept your
secret for years
And not once have I ,,,
You know how hard this
It has been for me?
I have no friends
I lied
My own daughter
Life imitates art
A king crying
Walter, do you want?
Everything with you is calculated
We are back where we had
first date
Look, do not deny it, I need you
you're the one who has the gift
Now, there is an opportunity to ,,,
Oh my God
I am excited
The New York World's Fair
70 million visitors
The opening day, I will show
my masterpiece
That masterpiece?
exact
Where he has been all
this time?
Da Vinci Mona Lisa has its
Renoir has his lunch Fishermen
Where is my final statement?
You sound like crazy
An artist not only announced
his masterpiece
Why not?
Miguel Angelo did not know that to something great
to paint the Sistine Chapel?
It took four years
But this is the best part
It is for UNICEF
UNICEF sponsored the entire education
Finally we will reward the
kids of the world
When people ask me, 'why
It was stood ?, fear, lack of trust? ''
Margaret was trapped in a
lie had helped create
And other coverage was worse
that crime
Why were promised a canvas
this size?
Because it must meet all
kids, all races
Hundreds of faces
Marching to infinity
Latest from Walter Keane
The publisher says it is good for
out a coffee table book
You know, something elegant
The teachers of tomorrow need
my portfolio early
My artistic evolution
-- Yes
Where are all your
preliminary sketches?
All that time you spent in
art school which seem to have
Made all these young experiments
these portraits coal unfinished
They should be here
somewhere
I know you're being
sarcastic
Just some ideas ,,, orphans paints,
early self portraits
Get out of here try to work
Mom?
What about dinner?
Mom're home?
Mom?
Jane
What are you doing in the study of Walter?
I know
You know nothing
I'm not a girl
Jane
Five, six pages
There is something here that I see?
It's like the hula hula
no disappears
It will be unveiled at the large pavilion
Hall of education
International artist and celebrated
has been selected
To represent aspirations
of the children worldwide?
This is absurd
And who was on the committee
selection?
Well, there was a committee
so to speak
Just went to lunch with him,
Jerome and I
And the wife of Jerome
Technically not invite
presentations
Mr, Keane just us
contacted directly
Let
The World's Fair opens Thursday,
paintings for sale
On Friday divorce request
Why are you always so
miserable?
Okay
I will enjoy my afternoon
Ms, Tisdale
Walter Keane
I just wanted to thank you for hosting
This lovely evening
Well, you are welcome
Hey Keane
You've seen the New York Times?
Honestly I've been so busy all
day preparing for this occasion
I think you should read
"Terrible"
'' Grotesque "
"Disgusting"
As someone could say something
so cruel?
That you care?
My name is trailing
by Iodo
It is he here?
If, which is probably
that all ,,,
Who wrote this shit?
Mr, Keane
This is not the way
You may want to write
a letter to the editor?
What are you afraid of?
Just because people do
like my work
That means it's bad?
-- Do Not
But neither becomes art
Art should raise not please
Particularly if you are in
classroom education
You have no idea
Why someone becomes critical?
Because you can not create
Oh go
That tone is not ,,,
-- Do not give me that
Do not know what to put your
emotions out there
Naked for all
the world to see
That emotions?
It is synthetic work
Your masterpiece is an infinity
Keane
What makes it an infinity
garbage
What's wrong with the child
denominator?
That this country was built!
I have to sue them all
all
I'll sue this fag critical
Take that UNICEF
With your small boxes
nice money
But you'll be happy, right?
You made me the ultimate betrayal
Me down with that picture
crossed from
Sentimentality garbage
Walter for
You made me look bad
You made people laugh my
Open up, open up!
Let me in!
I can see you
I'll take them with smoke
They will fly as a
atomic bomb
Where are they?
I'm so sorry
Not be the mother I could be
I should have done this years ago
Where are we going? Is very cold
Where we're going we do not need much?
Hawaii
Really?
Yes
If it is a paradise because there
There are many birds and flowers
And beautiful colors
We will make a new life
for us
Ok?
That's my girl
Hello?
You were hard to track
I thought I'd never find you
Walter
I'm a little hectic, I received a
strangers papers in the mail today
It is a form of legal separation
and appreciate that it will sign
Yes
Do not you being a bit
impulsive?
Walter want a divorce
It hurts to hear you say these words
Sorry it come
this
Okay
I guess
I could accept separate
if you
You agree to spend the rights of all
painting produced
If that's the price
Really?
Ok
Well then we have to consider
future earnings
God, Walter, the more
need money?
If you want me out of your life
listen to me
You'll have to paint 100 paintings more
with the name of Walter Keane
Jane
I'll go to the post office,
You want something?
There I go surfing with the gang
I think Jane friends
They are a bit wild
Calm down mom
You're impossible
Bring me all the way
to Hawaii
I make some friends and all
what you do is complain about them
Maybe you need to make some
Know that he could not have
friends at home
That was why hide
pleasant pictures
Hello, we are visiting all
in the neighborhood
We have an important message
We have something to share with you
About the wonderful things the
kingdom of God will do for mankind
Well from my point of view I do not see
much good, just pride, theft
And be bad to each other
You know what it says on Timothy
1 to 5?
In recent days
Critics times that are
difficult deal
They'll be here
Because men
worship themselves
Sounds like my ex husband
We like to get ?,
It says right here
A worshiper of Muhammad should be
honest at all
I can not believe you left
People go home
It also says
No lies, tell the truth
If you were a thief, do not ever steal
Shit, this is crazy
All these copies
You're like Warhol
Do Not
Warhol's how I
That fool stole my act
my art
The manufactures
Had a factory before knowing
it was a soup
Oh if we have a special guest
Today, a worldwide celebrity
Let's give a big welcome
Margaret Keane
So it's true that your husband Walter
It is a big seller of paintings in the world?
Do Not
Big Lolo
Everything you just said
It is false
one
Walter and I are no longer married
And two
He is not a painter
But is not the one who makes the
crazy eyes?
Do Not
But if he has taken credit
that for 10 years
I am
The only painter in the family
You must be kidding
They know that bother me? Margaret le
broke the news to a big press buttons
And there is an excellent reporter
Celebrities like me
I knew it
Expected
Margaret has gone mad
You have to help
I need a story
A national story to calm things
I do not know Walter
What he said was quite explosive
It is crazy!
Not even make sense
While I was studying art in Paris
She was a girl in Tennessee
sight
My early drafts
Orphans Berlin 1949
Margaret Why would he do that?
You are sick in the head
He left me to go to the jungle
He went with religious fanatics
Witnesses Muhammad
Really do not know much about them
No celebrate Christmas
They can not salute the flag
do not let Jane go to the prom
It makes me look crazy
He says I copy it,
he taught me how to paint
Using a projector to trace my
work and fill colors
And how much of that is not true?
all
I feel good about myself
For the first time in years and I can not
Walter let me remove it
And what if it demands?
$ 17 million
The art world is altered
Today the lawyers present their
opening arguments
For Margaret Keane
against Walter Keane
And what according to the newspapers
Be the case that could produce more
riots in Hawaiian history
Mr, Keane
Is not worried about the charges?
I am very upset
But luckily I have to this company
news to look after my back
Hope all this trial is
removed by noon
My only concern is
Have someone psychiatric help
this woman
the need
-- Well, sorry gentlemen
Excuse me please
Margaret Keane is a figure
published
Wherefore must prove that the
statements of our newspapers
They are aware of probable falsity
Now there is no evidence to suggest that
our editors knew that these
Assertions were not true
We would like to introduce 692 items
in which
The Ms, Keane
Credited Mr, Keane
As the painter called
'' kids with big eyes "
Few years ago these back?
The Ms, Keane has made these
statements
since 1958
This is a very strange case
These paintings hang in museums
all over the world
Accredited Mr, Keane
And true import
The Ms, Keane has contributed immensely
to confusion
It seems impossible that such shares become
the standard level for liability
So the charge against
is removed
Thank you Your Honor
Good luck Keane
Good luck?
Where do they go?
We were accused of responsibility
To you I was accused of slander
Mr, Keane?
Seems to have no advice
Would you like a moment to
order their affairs?
I've always careful to myself
I do not need a group of suits
hire to defend my good name
Proceed!
I was worried about my
old friend Walter Keane
The Hawaiian heat may have
cooked his brain
All he knows cuts
and lawyers
It comes from Perry Mason on TV
I am the sole creator of my art
This is my life
My contribution to the world
Mr, Keane
I told you should ask
question witnesses
If you act as your own lawyer
You can not make statements
at this time
If, fine
It is difficult to keep everything
this in order
Ms, Keane
As expected someone to swallow
his fantastic story?
Mr, Keane
Ms, Keane
Seems to be a lucia
And reasonably intelligent
woman
So as you can possibly
Having come so far with a
farce like that?
I was forced to it
You do tapeworms
I had dominated the
He was going crazy but you
was what I wanted
I was afraid and
He saw no other option
so I followed the game
I can remind you that this
under oath?
Just give me
I allowed
Take credit for big eyes
They were a reflection of my feelings
And showed in the boy
But I was weak
No I thought I could leave
and maintaining
For myself and my daughter
And he said
Nobody would support payments without
personality
Maybe he was right
You eras
very talented
To be charming
And you're a genius in sales
and promotion
It seems that described two
different men
One is a sadistic ogre
and the other
A lovely gentleman
That is you Walter
You Jekyll Hyde
That is a blatant statement
I demand that the deleted
log
denied
Now, you were cheeky
Criticabas me constantly,
me you desgastabas
Saying you'd kill me
if he told the truth
Well, now I do
your Honor
I ask for a mistrial
You're a liar
do not even know what the truth
This is not a domestic problem
Perhaps it is
But the rest of us have
interest in seeing as resolved
I regret my excitement
I am an artist
maybe
your Honor
I call as my witness
Mr, Walter Stanley Keane
Swear to tell the truth and nothing
but the truth?
Yes
-- May God help you
Mr, Keane
There seems to be many hints
And conflicting testimony
On the genesis of big eyes
you mind
Clarify this short
Who gave life to these paintings?
Well I created these children
The choreography is not necessary,
just sit and testify
I had a wonderful life
He was an artist
And a friend of many
celebrities
however
When I remember everything
To define that really mattered
It was dedicated to the
kids hungry world
It all started in
Berlin
After World War II
orphans
They were chewing a bare wire
their bodies
lacerated
His fingers wrinkled
Her big eyes
The Ms, Joan Crawford
Made ,,
-- Mr, Keane!
sit
Marilyn Monroe
I will not lie ,,,
Jerry Louis calls me and tells me want
I paint it to me and my family
Miss, Natalie Wood
I was approached
And he said
This is the best painting I've
seen in my life!
It ended
I have not finished
In fact if
I can not stand one more story
It is not testifying,
He is wandering
The court records are already quite
full no nonsense stories
We can stay here until
die of old age but
It is obvious that this case is summarized his
word against that of Ms, Keane
Mistrial?
Do Not! Not a mistrial!
In my opinion
There is only one way to clarify this
Both paint
Well bring them over here and put
on both sides of the bench
Now, I do not seek a masterpiece
I do not know much about these things
I am a lawyer not a critical
art
But an hour is enough?
If Your Honor
Ok then
Both have the same supplies
So without further ado
Ms, Keane, Mr, Keane
The court is yours
Mr, Keane?
I just put the environment
I hope the muse arrives
Well his muse has 58 minutes
Mr, Keane, right?
My old shoulder injury
I just go on, have a ,,,
that muscle
I have been taking drugs
Inflammation
Do not think I can
painting today
The jury found in favor of
Margaret Keane at all points
Charges of defamation
emotional stress
And I hurt your reputation
Thank you, thank you very much
Margaret, as you call
painting?
Show 224
Margaret, you could give me
your autograph?
Two things he cared to Margaret,
his daughter and his paintings
And after all the crazy twists
his life took
He loved the final
for both
Walter never accepted defeat, he insisted
who was the true artist
For the rest of his life, died
in 2000, bitter and penniless
Never produced another painting
Margaret found personal happiness
and remarried
After many years in Hawaii, moved
San Francisco and opened a new gallery
She still paints every day