It's your birthday!
Go Treasure!
Where the hell y'all think y'all at?
Treasure. Got that paperwork
for your transfer.
-I ain't sleepy yet.
-Me neither.
Back to your bunks!
Move!
You're gonna be all on your own tomorrow.
State Women's Facility?
I tell you, I wouldn't work
in that motherfucker for nothing.
My moms is in there.
Serious?
She doin' life.
I ain't never met her. Just pictures.
-Damn, why ain't you never said nothin'?
-Never knew.
-Remember Shadow?
-Yeah.
-She got transferred to State last year.
-She got me word.
Motherfucker. So that's what
your stabbin' Takisha was all about?
You tryin' to get up in there?
I ain't tryin' shit, Leonard.
It's done.
I'm goin' home.
Treasure Lee?
Happy birthday.
-Gate open.
-Transfers coming in.
All right, ladies, step on through the door.
Line up on the green line, facing the glass.
Quickly!
Toes on the line!
Drop your bags.
You've all been legally sentenced
to pay your debt to society...
...here at the State Facility for Women.
We have some rules for you to learn.
Inmates, that is you, are required to obey
all written and verbal orders...
...given by any staff member.
Smoking is not permitted in any building...
...except in the unit day room.
All out of the showers.
Inmates are not permitted
to enter any housing unit...
...to which they are not assigned.
Physical contact...
...physical displays of affection, horseplay,
or sexual activities of any kind...
...between inmates, employees, visitors,
or volunteers is prohibited.
Treasure Lee?
Your number is 2879.
You answer to that during the count.
You put it on all your stuff.
You understand?
Open your mouth.
Inmates will not interfere with any staff
member in the performance of their duties.
Hands.
A disrespectful gesture,
30 days in disciplinary confinement.
-Tanya Pierce?
-Yes, sir. Do I...
Your number is 2880.
You answer to that during the count.
You put it on all your stuff. Understand?
Participating in,
or inciting a minor disturbance...
...30 days in disciplinary confinement.
Okay, bend over.
Bend over.
Possession of escape paraphernalia...
...60 days in disciplinary confinement.
You can't use that same thing on all of us.
This would be an example
of interfering with an officer...
...in the performance of her duty.
-But it's not sterile.
You're right.
The doctor'll be in tomorrow morning...
...we can check you in then.
In the meantime,
why don't you spend the night in the Hole?
Frank, get in here.
We got a princess checking in.
Put her in disciplinary for the night.
My advice to you, girls, do your own time.
Don't bother other prisoners
or try to break a badge. It'll only backfire.
Just mind your own business...
...not your neighbor's.
Try to work your program
to reduce your sentence.
Lee?
You take the white girl's bag,
she's your roommate.
Let's go! Move it out.
All right, ladies, new fish.
You're on the floor.
COs don't like it much
when we try to spruce up the place.
My daughter gave this to me.
It's some kind of violet.
She's working on my case.
Gonna get me out of here.
See, I told you she'd be black, praise Jesus.
-So who sleeps on top?
-Me.
You don't think I'm gonna let Mama Cass
climb up over me every night, do you?
I'm Doodle. Doodle Aldridge.
So?
You must've transferred
from the Youth Authority, right?
All y'all young girls got attitude all day,
ain't got nothin' upstairs.
Whatever.
I'll check you threes later!
Ladies!
New fish.
Yo. Double G!
Sister, my sister.
You know you need to come over here
and get this mattress next to me.
Yo, I wasn't studyin' no floor.
You'll learn.
Come over here, sit next to me.
That's right.
You can put some of your stuff
in that locker over there.
That ain't mine. Some white girl
got sent up the Hole right off.
Is that right?
But I was watchin' it.
Ever.
The name's Leisha.
Hip.hop geisha.
I'm about to be up out
in six months anyway...
...back in the studio, laying tracks.
Yeah, all right.
So what, I gotta ask
for your name, or what?
Treasure.
So, you straight? Everything okay?
-Meet everybody?
-Yeah, except...
That's Patrice. She's a Xanax zombie.
Depressed. Trying to sleep her way
through her nickel.
-You know a sister named Shadow?
-Shadow?
That's my girl.
-Was you from East Side?
-We was up in Youth together.
Okay.
Check this out, baby girl.
This here ain't the same.
As long as you remember that,
you'll be all right.
Yo.
You know a lifer named Brownie?
Shit, girl, don't ask me nothin'
'bout no Brownie.
I'm about gettin' up out of here
in six months, I ain't about no Brownie.
Besides, she up in Unit A anyway.
Damn.
Every time that go off,
you got two minutes before line up.
Yeah.
Yo, Shadow!
Girl! What's up?
You made it!
Happy birthday! Sorry I missed that shit.
Count!
-Leisha, you take care of my girl, now.
-I was gonna.
-I'll see you in the morning.
-All right.
On the line, ladies.
Cell 3!
4437.
6293.
4527.
-3820.
-Cell 2!
2477.
834.
1537.
2542.
-2879.
-Cell 1.
4187.
6289.
1787.
1642.
Count clear.
My sister.
You know I was only kiddin'
about you bein' trouble, right?
You want some, Doodle?
I'll take it if you givin'.
Wait a minute,
you know how much they go for in here?
Yo, me and Shadow used to sell 'em
for $5 a cup up at Youth.
$5? Here they be charging $8,
sometimes $10.
Some girls do a little bit of anything
for a Cup of Noodles, baby.
Let me have a bite, Doodle.
Here.
You can have the whole cup and more.
After you move to the floor.
Deal.
What the fuck is this?
-Open 2.
-On the gate.
-Where did that come from?
-I don't know.
You don't know.
Let's go.
Come on, move your ass.
You ain't dead yet?
You ain't got no Momma/
After this, we go into the yard.
Unless you got something hooked up
for you over there.
-All right. Lookin' forward to that shit.
-Okay.
Down there's the commissary.
Downstairs is the cafeteria.
Over here...
...library.
Computer room, books,
you know, shit like that.
That's Miss Johnny Cochran.
She knows a lot about legal shit.
And she also run a group therapy session.
All fresh fish got to attend that.
Fuck that.
It's mandatory, Treasure.
She's the only one that can pass you out.
We can take vocational classes.
I'm reading and shit.
You should check it out.
You get saved up in here?
Yo, you gotta work your program.
You stay outta the mix.
Every day you take a class
or you work up in prison industry...
...you get a day off your sentence.
-Whatever.
Okay. We just left Administration.
Now, Unit A is on top.
It's lifers.
Bad-ass criminals.
That's where Brownie lives.
Yeah.
But we second floor, we Unit B, we G.girls.
Unit C is in the basement.
That's the Hole. Crazies. Old fucks.
Yo, what's up with that shit?
-I know. And he a married fucker, too!
-Shit.
-Hello, Fluffy.
-That's Sugar.
The gang girl's doorknob.
Everybody gets a turn.
Shadow, what you said about me?
I know you ain't talkin' about me to this...
Where did you come from?
You know what? Please, Sugar.
Make a fist.
That's Brownie.
You down with Brownie?
Why you always gotta play
for somebody new? I'm right here.
You just so tame.
Can't play no ball?
Yeah!
All right!
Told you 'bout playin' ball with me.
It knocks the wind out of you.
Somebody come play with us
before I get upset.
I'm gonna get you.
That's me.
Treasure, what you doin'?
Girl, you cannot play ball.
Shadow, hold my shit.
-You can play?
-Yeah.
Come the fuck on.
Fuck up off me.
That's all right!
That's all right.
What's up with that?
-Bitch.
-Let's go, guys, let's go.
You got it, she ain't got nothing.
Cut the nonsense! I don't give a damn!
I said, "Cut the nonsense!"
I ain't gonna let you two bitches
fuck up my court time.
You heard Moms,
what the fuck is your problem?
-You my problem, cracker bitch!
-Cracker?
-Get out of my face!
-Nigger called me cracker!
I don't give a fuck! I said cut it out!
What's your name, girl?
Treasure. Treasure Lee.
All right, Treasure Lee.
Next time, you play for us.
We'll kick ass.
Okay, guys, let's settle in! Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I been doing time since I can remember.
You know, 16, first trip to Juvenile.
I didn't go straight from Juvenile to prison,
I went home and...
...committed another offense
to bring me here.
-I'm dealing with it.
-I'm a multi.violator.
I started doing time in 1959...
...and I went straight to a Federal pen.
There was no Youth Authority
or none of that stuff.
A group of gals
got a hold of me and schooled me.
I learned how to do time.
I did time until I was 38 years old.
After all the time I was out,
I started using again.
Ended up back in the streets
and back in the system.
When I came in here,
I was going down on somebody for $5...
...and I thought he got cheated.
That's how I felt about myself.
I can promise you,
you keep coming back to this fucker here...
...you're gonna end up,
if you live long enough to get this old...
...that's all there is out there.
I'm not fuckin' angry.
You keep asking me that. I'm not angry.
I was 16 years old with two fuckin' kids...
...begging for help,
and know what you told me?
"Just wait." How fuckin' long could I wait?
These girls got a chance and you'll
sit there and blow smoke up their ass?
Don't try that shit.
I don't think nothing.
I ain't got nothing to say.
I'm not like these other females in here.
Let's make this game interesting.
Let's start a kitty.
Hell, no. No betting and no gambling.
I only got six months left
up in this motherfucker.
I ain't about fuckin' up my time.
Yeah, we know.
I wasn't talking to you anyway, Leisha.
I was talking to Sugar.
Here we go.
You know I'm a player.
I'm down for it all.
Ain't that right, Shadow?
Can we play cards,
and y'all do that foreplay shit later?
Later when?
Why don't y'all give us a little privacy?
You like a dangerous type, huh?
I see why they call you Sugar.
'Cause you like brown sugar.
You all sweet and shit.
Excuse me.
Are y'all supposed to be in here?
Shit.
What?
Someone I do not wanna see tonight.
What you doing?
I'm playing cards. What you doing?
You know what I'm doing.
I'm sitting in the back of the church
waiting for your black ass.
I ain't about meeting you there every night.
I never said we were exclusive.
Maybe she found something
a little sweeter.
You know what they say.
"The darker the berry..."
You can go back to the asshole
you crawled from, bitch.
-Excuse me?
-I said...
A fight! A fight!
A nigger and a white!
White can't fight,
'cause the nigger's all right!
A fight! A fight!
A nigger and a white!
The white can't fight,
'cause the nigger's all right!
Fuck!
You bitch!
Get away! Break it up!
Enough!
Back it off.
I'm not going in there!
-Open the door.
-Fuck you.
Open the door!
You're dead, bitch.
Quiet!
What's going on out there?
Fuck you!
Ain't nothin' in the Hole.
Welcome.
Welcome, girlfriend!
Yo! What's your name, baby?
Fuck.
What's your name, girl?
My name is Treasure.
Mom.
Next time, you play for us.
Margaret "Brownie" Lee.
Treasure.
It's me, Brownie.
Yeah.
You a bold motherfucker, you know that?
Fuckin' with my girl Kit.
I want you to come see me
when you get out.
I got a feeling about you.
What kind of feeling?
"Bold motherfucker."
Damn straight.
"What's your name, girl?"
"My name is Treasure."
"Treasure Lee."
I'll see you when I get out.
519.
4437.
6293.
4527.
3820.
Cell 2.
2477.
834.
1537.
2880.
2542.
2879.
Cell 1.
6289.
1737.
1642.
Count clear.
What's the best way to get to Unit A?
Unit A?
Girl, you just got out of the Hole,
30 days, fool.
I ain't ask you what you thought about it.
How do I get there?
Hook me up.
Tag, too.
Can we please just play?
Baby wants to play.
Come on in, girl.
What you want?
Beer? Wine cooler? Something harder?
I thought we was gonna talk.
Alone.
We can talk in here.
We all family here.
This is my wife, Wee.
My daughters Kit and Scar.
So this "come see me" shit...
...ain't got nothing to do
with your being my fuckin' mother.
You jumping the gun now, girl.
You can't become a member
of the family overnight.
This ain't Juvie up in here.
I don't know what you're thinking, but...
...you've got some auditioning to do.
We got to get to know one another.
I ain't about auditioning for nobody.
I been getting to know you
for a long time, Moms.
This nigger's tripping.
Shit.
Let me see that shit.
That ain't Brownie.
Think we all look alike?
Shut up and give the girl back her picture.
I'll see y'all in the day room in a minute.
Step.
I never had no mother.
I never had no family out there either.
I came in here alone,
and I had to learn a lot of shit on my own.
And now so do you.
I liked what I saw the other day.
So I invited you here to find out
who you were...
...and to see what you got.
But if you gonna be jumping the gun
and acting all crazy...
I don't know what you heard, but...
Jumping the gun?
What the fuck you talking about?
Do you see
I'm trying to tell you something?
I've been waiting a long time for this.
My whole damn life,
I've been waiting to find you.
They're telling me I'm crazy
for liking it in here.
For trying to get over here next to you.
Fuck all that.
This is all I know. Know what I'm saying?
I'm up in this motherfucker 'cause of you.
My flesh and blood.
Listen here, you crazy.ass bitch.
I ain't got nothing to do with you.
If you in here...
...you in here because of you
and nobody else.
I don't even know who the fuck you are.
So bounce.
Now.
I called you here to say I'm sorry.
Fuck you, you sorry.
I am sorry, Treasure. I didn't know.
They took you from me
the minute you were born.
Why didn't you try?
Listen.
I said I was sorry.
That's what you wanted me to say, right?
This isn't easy.
So?
I was dealing...
...with so much anger
when I first rolled up.
I had to get my head on straight.
I had to find a way to do my time.
How to do your time alone?
You're right.
I failed you.
Baby...
The difference between me
and most of these people in here...
...l'm playing ignorant,
and y'all are ignorant.
Let me tell you something,
I got a degree in Business already.
Wait...
Let her finish.
I wrote a script already.
Hey, I might star in the motherfucker.
What a Business degree got to do
with acting, motherfucker?
with acting?
-Let me tell...
-Wait a minute.
What a Business degree got to
with acting?
I have goals, but the thing is...
...I don't want to just run
the streets anymore.
I've been running the streets
for a long time.
And now I want the things
I said I never wanted.
I never wanted to strive for normalcy.
Now I want a house.
I want a car.
I want some of the simple things.
My dream is...
I'm living it out. I'm getting with my mom.
I want to get up out of here.
Get us a place in the 'hood.
Get a fuckin' fly.ass truck.
And just chill, and do our thing together.
I want you to take it off.
-Are you Treasure?
-Yeah.
Grab the damn box, dumb shit.
And smile.
Act like we're friends.
Now pick up the box and go.
Whatever anybody wants.
But I won't sell drugs. I don't do that.
What you want?
I'm getting it.
So you easy then.
Come on.
There's got to be something
on the outside you want.
Can you get me a Walkman?
Maybe some music? Some blues?
Blues?
All right, I thought you were new school,
and here you are old school, just like me.
Write that shit down. I'll give it to Nelson.
Nelson, that fucker. Act like he all hard.
That fucker is hard. Do you hear me?
You try to disrespect him...
...he'll come down extra hard
on you so nobody suspects.
Now, you be clear on that shit.
He's still the one with the keys.
You hear me?
Yeah, okay.
You best.
Will you blow on it?
Blow on it yourself.
Mom?
Can't you get me transferred over here?
Can't we cell together?
All in good time, baby girl.
I got plans.
Let's see.
We'll shade that in later.
After that heals.
You go on over to Kit's and help her
move some shit out to the yard.
Crank?
No, junk.
Shit, Brownie know you doin' this?
She just told me
she don't be dealing drugs.
She won't sell them...
...but she won't
let that money get by either.
So I get my hands dirty, whatever.
Except there's too much business lately,
so I guess you're up.
I get Unit A and the badges.
That's most of them.
You and Sugar get the rest.
All right.
You know,
I'll have to show everybody you're cool.
How you hook up with Brownie?
I came in here the same as you...
...but I didn't have no gang girls.
It was me against them.
Them is everybody.
Brownie offered me a hand,
and I took it for life.
You know Brownie was in the Hole
for a year after she first rolled in?
A year?
Word.
I think it messed with her head.
What did she do?
187.
Took out a celly from what I heard.
That's cool.
I love her like a mother, for real.
I'd do anything for her.
She inking me a tattoo...
...just like hers.
Yeah.
That's cool.
Hey, Kit.
That's my sister, Treasure.
Shit. Hell, yeah.
What up, G?
Geeking it with the library crowd.
What?
What you think?
What, you dealing for Brownie now?
I should never have told you
she was in here. Shit.
What the fuck?
Who's the one who started me
taggin' and sellin' rock?
What's that say on your fist?
You should be dealin' with me.
Fine.
Treasure, I changed.
And you haven't changed.
So let's just let it go.
Peace.
I don't want to let it go, Shadow.
You my dog from back in the day.
What you studying?
I said, what you studying, bitch?
I was thinking about making a camera.
-I want to take pictures inside.
-You gonna make your own camera?
You're a strange motherfucker.
What you need?
I said, what do you need?
I'm going to hook you up.
I can make the box myself.
But I need this Polaroid photo paper...
...and this here rubber thing
and all this shit on this list.
Yo, just write it down.
I don't think you can get this in.
Write it down, all right?
All right.
Treasure?
Yeah?
Be careful.
I don't trust her.
Who, Brownie?
She's my moms.
I've been wanting her all my life.
Just be happy for me.
-Who the fuck are you?
-Who are you?
-I asked you first.
-Min So.
Yo, Patrice, what happened to Mama Cass?
Fuckin' freakazoid.
They say she was paroled.
Her daughter got her out.
You're the one they told me about.
Treasure.
Yeah, whatever.
We speak English up in this chumpy.
Is this your violet?
No.
Violets can grow in a place like this.
Not so much water and every...
So it is yours.
I told you it wasn't mine,
but I was taking care of it, though.
What the fuck you got back there,
pork fried rice?
No, chicken. Can you believe it?
Because I have a special diet, they let me
cook in the kitchen and bring food back.
Now I'm going to make fried rice to sell.
To sell?
You ain't selling nothing
up in this motherfucker.
You need a hook up for that shit.
There ain't no takeout window up in here.
I just need to find a way to protect myself.
And how you plan on doin' that?
All right, miss fancy lady.
Thanks.
Smell that.
Nothing like the smell of freshness.
Fresh from California.
Yo, Granny used to grow
kale and tomatoes.
Remember that little garden
she had on the balcony?
I was never around, girl.
I was always on the street and in trouble.
Those are your memories.
Mine aren't the same at all.
She was always telling me:
"You're no good.
"You're going to end up in jail,
just like your father."
I made sure her wishes came true.
That's exactly what she told me about you.
Except she said you was dead.
You believe that?
Probably trying to protect you.
Keep bad things from you.
Keep bad things from me.
All that nonsense...
...that was in the past,
you got to let that go, baby girl.
You're here now...
...and we together.
And we gotta make it here...
...by any means necessary.
I used to dream you would...
...escape and take me away with you.
I didn't understand...
...why you wouldn't write,
why you wouldn't ask about me.
Now I know.
Fucking bitch, Granny.
To find you now...
...that's like a miracle.
Treasure.
My blood.
Yeah.
"How many months do I love my mama?
"Every month of the year
-"It's January
-"January
-"February
"March" Come on, y'all.
"April, May, June
"July, August, September
"October and November
"On the 25th day of December
"Every month of the year
"How many months do I love my G-girl?
-"It's January
-"January
-"February
"March" Come on, y'all.
"April, May, June
"July, August, September
"October and November
"On the 25th day of December
"Every month of the year"
Where the fuck is Kit?
Here she go now.
What? I know Sugar got my money.
Shit, fire, fuck, man, it's worse.
Ain't nothing worse for you than
if that little hooker ain't got my money.
-Brownie, the package is gone.
-What the fuck you mean, it's gone?
They stole it, all right?
The bitches stole it.
-Who?
-Rosita and them, the Spanish girls.
Are you fucking kiddin' me?
-Are you trying to steal from me, Kit?
-No, I swear to God...
After all I've done for you?
You stupid bitch!
You are such an idiot!
I hate it when you call me that!
You better get used to it
until you get this shit worked the fuck out.
I'll see you back at the unit.
-Aren't we going to settle with Nelson?
-What you got to settle with Nelson?
You ain't got nothing.
Now, Treasure, she got something.
She's gonna stand with me.
I don't like this one,
little fucking smart.ass.
She's here to learn the ropes.
This is my kid, Nelson.
Jesus fucking Christ.
You make me sick with your little
make.believe family bullshit.
We real blood.
-You think you don't make us sick?
-Cool it.
I know your type, I've seen you before.
You ain't special, little girl.
You were damaged before you were born.
Stop it, both of you.
You gotta learn how to control your kids.
It's like a fucking documentary
for the Discovery Channel.
Ooga.booga niggers.
Fucking look at them.
They're two generations away
from swinging in the trees...
...bones in the nose.
You can think what you want.
I don't want to hear it.
You'd better, celly.
We gotta stick together.
They already outnumber us.
You think they ain't racist?
You think they ain't saying
the same shit about you?
Come on, let me get this picture.
No, bump that.
Come on, y'all, kick me a beat.
Check it.
"See, I'm L.E.I.S.H.A
"When I grab the microphone
"Baby, I don't play
"'Cause I'm the baddest mother in the land
"You turn your back,
I'm gonna take what I can
"Ain't got a plan if you fuck with me
"You'll be erased,
I'm a doer, so I won't get the cake
"In two weeks, I'm a be kicking' it
Sippin' the Guinness stout
"'Cause 2542 is about to be out"
That's what I'm talking about.
Word.
Come on, man,
I want to do a whole prison series.
I got to go, I'll check y'all later.
Where you going?
I've got a business to attend to.
What's up?
Tripping. Bump back. Come on.
Take a little picture.
Please.
You see I'm trying to get my eat on.
So what you think?
Girl...
The chink can cook.
That's why I let her follow me around.
I told you.
I'll see about
getting her transferred up in here.
-What about me?
-Did you cook this?
Treasure.
Come on over here.
You're over there pouting.
Come on.
You want some of this?
I got it all back.
It's just $50 short.
Don't you make another sound.
-Moms, ease up.
-Shut up, Treasure.
Now, you go get my fucking $50.
Do you hear me?
I said, "Do you hear me?"
Yes, I hear you.
Now, go get my fucking money
before I put you out.
I'm going to take care of this.
Damn, $50.
I could get you $50 just like that.
Don't you worry about Kit's problems.
Worry about yourself.
I'll put you out just like that
if you fuck with my game.
Hey, peace y'all.
Don't stay up. It's always crackin', right?
-Word.
-I'll miss y'all.
-We love you girl.
-You know I love you all, too.
And you know what else?
Y'all check for me on BET.
I'm gonna be hitting with the viddy.hoes.
G, baby, G!
Yo, take one of that after.
One gang tat photo per prisoner.
Sorry. Just stay still.
It ain't no gang. That's my family.
Family.
We used to be family.
We still are. You're my sister.
You're the only person
I ever told about Brownie.
Yeah.
I wish you never did.
Do your thing and step,
because I ain't got time for this.
No worries.
What?
Am I doing something wrong?
Do you want to do something else?
I'm alone in the store.
She come in.
I always thought, "Maybe she steal."
I don't know, but she come in.
Of course she steals, she's black.
Not everybody steal like that.
This girl, I know.
Continue.
She take a box of food...
...and put it inside her blouse.
I can't take it anymore.
I tell you, I can't take it anymore.
So I grab her arm, I say,
"You pay for that, or you put it back."
She hit me.
She did, she hit me in the head.
Hard.
I don't remember.
I guess I got a gun.
-I didn't mean to.
-Sure, you didn't.
You're so full of shit.
You don't know how you got the gun.
Fuck you!
I'll take your fucking ass out!
You know, we're women here.
We have a common fucking bond.
And we could use that
and come together...
...rather than to fight like this
over some bullshit.
Because there's lots of other issues
that we could unify.
I ain't mad at nobody about nothing.
Min's my girl, we live together.
Should a bitch steal from me,
I'd shoot her, too, you know?
Why you hawking me?
Ain't nothing up.
Don't be looking at her.
Watch what you're doing.
What in the hell
are you two KKK bitches up to?
Nothing is up.
Damn, you treat me like I'm your yard dog
or something.
-You are my dog.
-No, I'm your daughter.
At least I used to be.
Cut that jealous crap.
Jealous of what?
Of you pretending to care
about Treasure here?
Shit, that don't bother me none.
'Cause I know what's up.
I've come to find the truth about Brownie.
The only person Brownie cares about
is Brownie.
That's it! I am through with you.
Get this shit! Let's go!
Brownie, wait.
Yo, where the hell's Min?
Transferred back to Psych.
Glad to get rid of the chink.
-Watch your mouth.
-Whatever.
She was chang, chow, chang.in'
all afternoon, driving me crazy.
-I said, watch it.
-You watch it.
Is it big bad Treasure
who's gonna fuck me up?
Better yet, get her big bad mommy
to fuck me up 'cause she's a...
'Cause she a what?
Go on and tell me what she is.
-Why'd they take her?
-Hell, I don't know.
She got some letter from her son,
talking about going back to Taiwan...
...Korea, wherever those people come from.
And she lost it. How about that?
Jesus.
Jesus ain't got nothing to do
with those people.
What you know about Jesus, bitch?
I know enough to know you're
damn enjoyin' this all to hell.
You and all your sacrilegious leslies.
Got the nerve to defile the church.
What are you thinking?
What's wrong with you?
You should shut up.
Can't change the word of God.
You can do whatever you want to me,
but you can't touch the word of God.
He sees everything.
Did he see you fucking the CO?
Did he see you fucking a married man?
You see that, God Almighty?
You see what's up in here?
I'm liking it over here.
Ain't no thing.
Just wanted to spend a little time
alone with my girl.
Ain't no thing but a chicken wing.
That's right.
Chicken wings and a side order...
...of macaroni and cheese.
Cornbread with lots of butter.
Stop, Treasure.
Damn! You making me hungry.
Let me see that.
That looks good. It's coming along.
But I need to shade it a little in there.
So it looks more like mine.
Bad!
See?
It's gonna be good.
King me!
Come on, baby.
We're going to a party.
Do it!
Do it now!
Spanish bitches.
Teach you to steal from me.
Don't fuck with me.
Rosita.
I wouldn't go in there if I were you.
Moms and I got business to attend to.
Whatever.
But I warned you.
Trying to fuck me up,
I don't understand all this bullshit.
It could've been you.
What you talking about?
What am I talking about?
Sabrina wrote me up.
You told her you was with me.
I thought I could trust you.
You can. What happened?
What happened?
You tell me.
It was you and Kit, wasn't it?
You two bitches are trying to fuck me up,
aren't you?
-Aren't you?
-Come on, we blood!
You and me ain't shit. I'll show you blood!
I'll show you your blood all over this cell!
What?
You gonna cry like a little bitch now?
You should've listened to Scar.
Scar listens to me.
Fucking Kit!
The biggest pain
I've ever had to deal with...
...is the feelings to do with my kids.
I have three sons.
My two oldest boys were taken from me
when I was in the second term.
My youngest boy, I was pregnant with
when I was in the Federal pen.
They didn't want a mom
that was an ex.convict.
They don't want a mom
that's a prostitute or a burglar.
Treasure, do you want to say anything?
I don't feel like it.
Why not?
I just don't.
My kids hate me.
Why?
I don't know. I've made mistakes.
We all make mistakes.
I'll pay for it the rest of my life.
Everybody say:
"You got so much anger."
When my kids needed me I wasn't there.
The drugs...
It was pretty much the drugs.
The last time my daughter told me:
"I hate you."
People say, "Why are you so angry?"
I've always been able to reverse...
...everything that I did.
I can't reverse the hatred in her face.
No matter what I do, no matter what I say.
I can't get through to her.
It's like that?
Yeah, it's like that.
Wanna get you in with me.
Been trying to figure out
how to go about that.
Telling me I don't mean nothing
to you was a good start.
I just lost my manner.
You know that, baby.
"Baby."
You picked the wrong person
to lose your manner with.
You always hurt the one you love.
Listen, I thought you turned on me.
I found out...
...it was Kit.
She told the warden
about our little pillow fight.
I just spent my first night in the Hole
in a long, long time.
Kit's gotta hear about this.
I need you to take her down.
It's gotta be done.
Otherwise we gonna lose
the control we got right now.
And you gotta do it.
You do this and...
And what?
When?
When the time is right.
Come on, you pussies!
What I got to do to get a game going?
Who's gonna play?
Looking for a game?
How about skins versus shit?
What you talking about, cracker?
This is skin...
...and that's shit.
You gonna regret that.
You think so?
I doubt it.
I think things around here
have been upside down for too long.
Too uncivilized.
Too tribal.
COs think so, too.
-Yo, Moms.
-Shut up.
This the way you play me, Kit?
You taught me everything I know, Moms.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Me and Kit. One on one.
Do what you gotta do, Boo.
Do what you gotta do.
Come on.
Okay, we gonna work this shit out.
They don't fuckin' want you.
You ain't a part of their family.
Watch for my signal.
After you kick her ass.
So get to it.
I don't even think we need the ball for this.
What the hell are you doing?
I kicked her ass good.
I didn't give you the blade
to kick her ass good.
I can't believe you punkin' out.
I can't believe this shit!
-It's not like that.
-I'll tell you what it's like.
You need to get your ass over there...
...and finish this shit off.
Hello, Treasure. Do you know who I am?
-You're the warden.
-Yes.
-Arnold.
-I need to know what happened.
-What about Brownie?
-She's in very serious condition.
Does she need blood?
Yeah, but that's not your concern.
She's my mother.
-Why didn't I know this?
-I don't know.
-I thought y'all were a play family.
-They are. Not me.
She's my mother.
You gotta let me help her.
-Why did you assault her like that?
-Me? It was Kit.
Take me to her before she dies,
goddamn it!
Hey, John, I need the paperwork.
Leisha.
What happened?
Hell, I don't know.
I was at my cousin's party.
We was partying, too.
Four days later, the police are shaking me:
"Tell me. Is this your pipe?"
I'm like, "What pipe?"
"That pipe!"
2879.
That's me.
You can go.
What's going on?
I'm gonna give my blood.
We appreciate the offer, but you're type A.
Phyllis Stubbs is type B.
You got the wrong fucking chart.
Brownie Lee is my mother. Margaret Lee.
Sorry.
-Listen to me, bitch!
-Stop it!
Show me the chart.
Just do it.
You calm down.
We'll straighten everything out.
I don't see nothing about no child.
They took me away from my mother.
"Phyllis Stubbs-42.
"1974. Five years for fraud.
"1978. 25-life. Second degree murder.
"1980.
"Life without parole
for the fatal stabbing of Margaret Lee."
-Treasure, calm down.
-No!
Guys, help me.
Calm down.
Guys, handcuff her.
Handcuff her.
Treasure.
This woman you thought was your mother,
do you realize who she is?
She murdered your mother.
I'd like to help you, because I'm sorry
for all you've been through.
But first, we're gonna have to talk
about you and the others.
We've been watching Officer Nelson
and his...
...relations with inmates
for some time now.
If you'll help us out...
...we'll transfer you
to a minimum security prison.
"Prisoners who wish to no longer
be associated with prison gang activity...
"...must give names
and provide information...
"...regarding any criminal activities.
"Having become an informant...
"...the prisoner must rely
on the Department of Corrections...
"...to protect them."
Keep it up, Treasure.
Yo, Shadow.
Stand perfectly still, right?
Let's go, Treasure.
Yo, new fish, you got a smoke?
What's your name, girl?
Brownie.