You want to put
some money on it?
I'm telling you,
my brother can run faster
than all you guys.
He's so little.
All right, five bucks.
Let's go.
Hey, drew, come over here!
Ready, set, go!
Yeah, drew.
Nice job, there you go.
All right, you guys
all need to pay up.
No, no, no.
He cheated.
Mom?
What's wrong with dad?
Dad!
Good work,
and then two more!
You said four and we're done.
I meant six.
Or did you want eight?
Complaining again, Jacobs?
It's the same thing
every day, asshole.
You want to go for 12?
Yeah, sure, I'll go for 12.
We may lose whitehall.
Oh,  I'm  the loser?
No, I think you're  the loser,
not like your brother.
What'd you say?
Hey!
Enough!
The hell with this.
You run the laps yourself.
You're done here.
Let the loser go.
Hey. Hey, drew!
Drew!
Eric's just being an ass.
Come back.
Come on.
Lisa! Come on back.
We don't need him.
Come on!
I'm done with this.
Go on, tell me what I missed.
Same old thing.
Whitehall's strides
are too long,
he needs to get up on his toes,
and that girl runs on her heels.
So you let that
Jacobs kid go, huh?
What's up, man?
Drew.
I'm gonna need you
to pick something up
from Eli tomorrow.
Why don't you
get in the car
and do it yourself?
You know why.
A parolee can't be
driving on these runs.
Watch out.
Mom's salary doesn't
cover the mortgage.
You're gonna have to
start pulling your
weight around here.
And I don't want
to see Eli right now.
You don't have
the money, do you?
Hmm. You know...
These are terrible.
Ugh. Mm-mm.
Can't do it.
Oh, God.
I can't eat it.
Hey, sweetie.
Why don't you go to bed?
It's time for you
to get moving.
Let's go.
You know that's impossible.
I've tried it...
Many times.
Come on, let's go, ballerina.
So Eli's got a bag
for you, all right?
What should I say
about the money?
Just tell him
I couldn't get
down there today.
Hey, don't be too long.
I got something else for you.
Hey, Chuck.
I'm here to see Eli.
Flash.
Want the shit?
What's up, man?
You're making
a habit out of this.
It's just part
of your workout
routine now.
He runs all
the way here from
rainier valley, Chuck.
You got some money for me?
I'm just making
a pick-up for Wes.
Wes.
That name sounds familiar to me.
I feel like I know the guy.
He never comes around here
anymore, though.
I think he must be
mad at us, Chuck.
It's not like that, man.
Not like that?
He's busy.
It's not what you think.
He asked me to make
the pick-up...
he's busy?!  I'm  busy!
I hope I'm wrong,
but I think we both know
why he's not coming around here.
You know what I
can't get used to?
People making decisions for me.
Your brother's deciding
who picks up what,
when and where?
I don't want to see
your goddamn face
here, drew.
I don't want to see your face.
Tell your brother that.
You understand me?
Yeah.
Go on. Chuck will
sort you out.
Be careful with that.
Hey, Jacobs!
You ran all the way
from the docks?
Same clip?
Yeah, so?
That's about
a five-minute mile.
That your school bag?
Eli doesn't want me
making runs anymore.
He says he wants to see you.
You know,
he should really
stick to gutting fish.
Don't worry about me, though.
I'm a big boy.
A big boy can run
his errands himself.
You keep running
your mouth like that,
see where it gets you.
You letting that
Jacobs kid go...
that was a bonehead move.
I learned all my moves
from you, Coleman.
Drew, Lisa...
Would you like to share
your findings with
the rest of the class?
It's a trick question.
It's x - 4, not 6
like you put in
the formula.
That's right.
My dude!
Shut up, peanut.
What was that?
That?
That was easy.
That was easy?
Oh, okay.
Wow.
Excuse me.
My head doesn't work like that.
Um, I gotta go to
track practice.
I'll walk you.
Men's relay
is really struggling.
They could use you
out there.
It's not gonna happen.
I'm done with the team.
Besides, coach wouldn't
let me back.
I don't... Get you.
You could get a scholarship.
Not if it means
running for a jerk.
What do you know about Coleman?
I know he lives on my street,
hassles coach Rickard,
which makes him
all right in my book.
He used to coach track.
I heard he was pretty legendary.
Yeah, so?
Well...
Well what?
Well, he's not coach Rickard.
Lisa, I'm done with track, okay?
Besides, I don't think
Coleman's much use
anymore anyways.
He had this kid...
he was a bit older
than me.
And then one day he was gone.
Car accident.
What are you gonna do, drew?
Just gonna give up?
All right, varsity girls.
Down on the field, let's go.
Wes?
Wes.
Come on, man.
What?
Come on.
Let's go.
30 yards, 20, 10...
He did it!
He broke the record!
William Coleman has broken
the state high school record!
Wes!
Look at this lawn, God damn it.
How many times I gotta tell you
to mow the lawn, son?!
This goddamn lawn needs mowing!
It's a jungle out here!
Where's your goddamn lawnmower?
I'll do it myself.
Look, I know I owe you money,
and I will
get you the money.
Just chill out.
So this is where
the magic happens, huh?
This is where you
smash your bitches?
You know, I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed.
You're embarrassing me.
Sit down.
Oh, what's up, drew?
That's the guy right there.
Big drew.
That's our boy.
That's the future.
He's a keeper.
Oh, hey, cool.
Baseball cards.
We should trade.
Chuck, do you
collect?
Flash, tell Chuck
about your brother's
ball-playing days.
This guy...
he could really play, seriously.
Talented.
The whole package.
Could never hit that
changeup, though,
could you?
Well, I'm not playing!
I want my money.
You think
a five-minute mile
is fast?
Well, if you run
ten of them, yeah.
But you can't run with a temper.
You gotta be in control.
Or you beat yourself.
Well, I never
get beat, so...
no?
You're not on the track team
anymore, are you?
I'd say you got beat.
But you are fast.
Fast enough to win state?
State fair, maybe.
Quit worrying about
who you're gonna beat.
Running's not about that.
Running's running.
That's it.
Is it?
Yeah.
Oh. Jeez, I'll have
to read your book.
Want to prove me wrong?
Ballard locks, 5 P.M.
Magnolia side.
Get in the water.
What?
Seriously?
Go on, get in the water.
Go on.
Why do I have to...
get in the water.
That's great.
Thank you.
Okay, that's good.
That's good, that's good.
Okay, see you those rocks
down there?
Run there and back
in 15 seconds.
That's it?
You do 100 of them.
Clock's running.
Go.
18. Doesn't count.
What do you mean,
it doesn't count?
Don't look at me. Go.
Ah.
That counts.
Yeah.
How many...
how many have I done?
How many?
54.
That's it.
I can't do it.
You done?
I'm done.
I can't do any more.
Where are you going?
I was right.
This stuff's impossible, man.
Hey!
come on, I need you
to come with me.
So get up, let's go.
Let's go.
This fool owes me
a lot of money.
So just keep your eyes peeled.
You see anything, let me know.
Where is the money? Huh?
In the sofa.
There we go.
That wasn't hard.
This what you're looking for?
Huh? This? Yeah,
I don't think so.
Clean that shit up.
Let's go. Let's go!
Look, if I didn't
need your help,
I wouldn't ask for it.
But it was worth it.
Look at that.
Mmm.
I finished it.
Even though I bonked.
You bonked?
Ha ha ha!
Do you have any idea
what bonking is?
You didn't bonk.
You got lazy.
When you bonk,
your muscles just
run out of gas.
You got nothin', nothin'...
But your heart.
Hmm.
But...
I've never seen anybody
do more than 50 of
those shuttle runs.
Why'd you leave?
Uh...
Tell someone
they can't do it,
and they won't.
Running's not just physical.
It's in your head.
Um...
What do you know about boats?
Which one's yours?
We're walking to it.
What's with the leg?
You know the water's
that way, right?
Aren't you chatty?
Sweet, huh?
Wow.
Yep. A couple
of repairs,
I think I'll take her to Alaska.
Think this boat's
gonna make it
to Alaska?
Get up there and wait for me.
Go on, don't touch anything.
I gotta see somebody
in the office.
You wait for me.
Thank you.
This guy makes me run in water,
and then he takes me
to his boat and
drops me off.
Sounds like he's
a senile old man.
Guess his glory days
are behind him.
Could still be
your best shot
at college, though.
Let's play some basketball, yo.
I think I'm done
with it anyways, man.
All right, let's go.
Are you quitting?
You don't much like
being told what to do,
do you?
You don't listen, either.
I heard. You told me
to wait, and I did.
I had to see if you
were worth my time.
Guess I got my answer.
You still can't even
tell me why.
Patience.
It takes a lot of it
to be a runner.
Are we going to the track?
Absolutely not.
I have my own special place.
What are you doing?
What the hell's it
look like I'm doing?
These are coaching shoes.
Coaching shoes. Right.
All right.
Run down to the big
white ship, turn left.
That's your first interval.
You get one minute's rest.
Then the next 1/4 mile.
Then you go all the way
around these docks.
All the way... come here.
Now, see the pole
with the sign on it?
That's one square mile
to the inch right there.
All right?
All right.
You start at the cleat.
Okay?
All right.
Go.
What was my time?
Don't worry about it.
Was it under 50?
Not that fast.
Look, you got
one minute to rest.
Hey, slow down.
You look like you just
robbed a bank.
Focus on each quarter,
pace yourself.
Quarter of what?
Mile.
Who's running the mile?
You.
No, I run the 400.
Listen, you want a scholarship?
You want to go
to college?
Yeah.
Then you run the mile.
The mile's your race.
You run it fast enough,
you can go anywhere you want.
Can back on the line.
Focus on each quarter.
I just told you...
get back on the line.
Now.
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
You averaged 67.
That's not bad.
I'm dying. I'm dying.
You're not even close.
You gotta run these in 58.
All 10 in exactly 58.
Ohh, God, this hurts so bad.
Everything hurts!
That's what's holding you back.
The pain.
You gotta learn
to overcome it.
You gotta embrace it,
run through it.
Then you can let it go.
Run through it, right.
Run through it.
I'm dying!
God, you're aggravating
to be around sometimes.
Jesus!
Aah!
God!
Mom?
Drew.
He wouldn't
let us take him
to the hospital.
Yeah, well, it seems like
you have a pretty good
handle on it.
What should I do?
I don't know.
Call the cops.
Want to walk with me?
What happened to you, gimpy?
It's a long story.
What's that?
This is an early
acceptance letter
to Cal Berkeley's art program.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's awesome.
It's expensive.
And with my family...
they can't afford it.
If I don't get that scholarship,
this doesn't really matter.
It's...
Bittersweet.
Uh, but I can always
become a street artist
if it doesn't work out.
At least I'm not gimpy.
That's true, that's true.
Well, I think you're
very talented,
so I think you'll be fine.
Seriously, what happened?
What's with the leg?
I'm actually training again.
You're running?
Yeah.
I've been training with Coleman.
I'm impressed,
Mr. Jacobs.
In your hectic running schedule,
do you have time
for a birthday party?
Yeah.
At my house?
Yeah, of course.
It's, um...
it's Friday night.
Friday night.
Mm-hmm.
I'll be there.
Bye.
You're made
for the mile,
not the 400.
And the sooner you realize that,
the better off you're gonna be.
I'm running the 400.
Drew?
Found.
Ohh, boy.
Let me see the guitar.
Come on.
This is it?
That's it. Everything.
This is the last time,
man, I swear.
I'll sing you a little
running-away song.
Goes a little something
like this.
A-one, a-two,
a-one, two, three.
hey, lazy George,
you on break again?
Let me get one of those.
We good?
Yeah.
Hey, Calvin,
go help our boy out.
Hey, for this week.
Flash.
Good for this week.
You know, if I'm your brother,
I wouldn't send you around
to see a guy like me.
You wouldn't understand.
Try me. Try me.
Oh...
That's for you.
Look.
What'd you think?
This is over?
You were done?
You think that's it?
No, it's not like that.
You're in this now.
You, me and Wes...
we're in it together.
Would you like a cigarette?
Give him a cigarette.
Good for lung capacity.
He ain't here.
So you can just...
Turn around and
shuffle on home.
What a prince.
Wheeler-dealer, huh?
I know what's going on here.
I know who you are and
where you're headed.
Just don't take
your brother with you.
Ah, you're so pathetic.
What's that? Hmm?
We've got a deal, right?
Yeah, we've got a deal.
If I don't win,
next time I'll run
the mile,
not the 400.
Yep.
I'm not losing this one.
Training again.
Watch and learn.
All right, let's boogie, folks.
We've got a special guest
in the 400 today.
You all remember
Mr. Jacobs.
Runners, to your marks.
Set.
Go!
Come on.
Come on, whitehall.
There you go.
Took you long enough.
You can't beat whitehall
in the 400.
But if you train hard
and listen to me,
you'll be a great miler.
Hey, drew!
You made it, man.
Good to see you.
What's crackin'?
What's up?
Good?
You're being all antisocial.
Bad race, right?
Sorry, man.
Hey, chill out, man.
Chill out, man.
It's a party.
You need a drink.
Come on, man.
Yeah.
Come on, baby, let's go.
It's gonna be a good night.
Hey, Lisa.
Can I borrow her for one second?
Hey, drew's here.
Let's go. Let's go.
Hey, can I talk to you
really quick, please?
Are you sure?
She's fine.
Hey, how are you doing?
I'm good.
You look really sexy tonight.
Hey, Eric, what the hell?
Get out of here, man.
Are you serious?
Get the hell out, man.
Get off him, man, come on.
Chill, man.
Drew.
Come back in.
He's gone. He had
way too much to drink...
don't make excuses for him.
He's got his hands all over you.
You're just gonna
let him do that?
Actually, I was about to...
Take down whitehall myself.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm.
So you're tough now?
Am I tough  now?
Oh, like nails.
Like...
okay.
About as dangerous as this eye.
How is it?
Um...
Bad.
Really?
It's pretty.
I should go.
I gotta train in the morning.
I'm gonna get back anyway.
Okay.
Good night.
Coleman?
You home?
You forget practice?
Some kind of a test again?
It's a nice collection.
You listen to all these?
This your son?
What?
Were you as hard on him
as you are on me?
He must've hated you.
You have no right
to talk about my son.
That's my son.
What happened to your eye?
I fell.
You fell?
Yeah.
Oh.
You fell?
Yeah.
Hey...
I hope she was worth it.
You're still here, huh?
How fast to get
a scholarship
to u.C. Berkeley?
You don't have a chance.
You don't listen.
It took me this long
to get you to do the mile.
What if I run it in four?
I'll do whatever you say.
Don't cook anymore.
Ugh.
You got something.
You got...
you got something in here.
It's so deep in there.
And you gotta beat it.
You gotta face that fear.
You've got to.
Because if you don't,
you're gonna be me.
And, buddy, you don't want that.
But if you do,
I don't care if you
never run another race
in your life,
because if you do
face that fear,
it'll change your life.
I promise you.
It's the hardest thing
you'll ever have to do.
But you gotta do it.
Oh, you gotta do it.
And then...
You'll be able to push
right through the pain.
You'll go right
through the door.
And when you're
about ready to pass out
and your legs can't move
and your lungs can't breathe
and your eyes can't see,
you'll know that it's
just the beginning.
And it's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
That's all I've been
trying to teach you.
Okay?
Okay.
When do you want to start?
You're gonna carry
that tire underwater.
That side to this side,
20 times.
That's a start.
Next time, you do it in one go.
All right.
63, not bad.
Not bad? That's
four seconds faster
than when I started.
That was impressive.
I hate to break it to you,
but I don't think
this boat will
make it to Alaska.
Oh, you don't?
Why don't you just...
Shut up and keep working?
How about that?
Why am I doing all the work?
Well... Uh...
Wax on, wax off.
That's really good.
Remind me again
why I couldn't
have the steak.
You're not building
muscle today.
So... Here,
I'll give you that.
Oh, thank you.
I don't eat it.
I think I'm done.
Can I get you guys
anything else?
A little more of this
lovely pasta, darling.
Keep eating. Mmm.
So...
How's it going with you
and that girl?
We're just friends.
What?
Eh...
Oh, grow a pair.
Why don't  you grow a pair?
Come out. Come on.
It's so early.
I know.
You up for a run?
That's actually pretty fast.
Oh, is it?
I didn't know that you played.
I can play a song.
Would you like
to hear a song?
I would love to hear a song.
It's, um, not about you.
And it's Charles St. James
leading the pack on lap 3.
He already has the state record.
His coach thinks he'll
break four minutes
this year.
Am I gonna have to race him?
You're gonna have to
beat him at regionals.
Only the winner goes to state.
St. James
now increasing his lead
as they come around
for the final lap.
My, oh, my.
You know, I really
appreciate you coming over.
I know you've been spending
a lot of time with drew, and...
why are you doing this?
Well...
Because he's fast.
He's fast?
Oh, he's fast, yeah.
He's a really good kid.
Um, I used to be a photographer.
And this little boy
used to sit for me for hours.
No.
Oh, yeah.
He was a great subject.
Really?
But he would get so angry.
Oh, my God.
So surprising.
I was six years old.
You were wonderful.
I got some beautiful images.
Did you do these?
Yeah.
What is that bottom one?
That's me.
That cute boy.
Fucking miserable.
Oh, I loved photographing...
Hey.
Hi, mom.
What's he
doing here? Hmm?
What's he doing here?
Wes.
Hmm?
No, sit your ass down, old man.
Punk.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
So what's for dessert?
James, I am so sorry.
I don't know what to do.
Look, I'm sorry, too.
I...
I don't want drew to
end up like his brother.
But if he keeps running
and he stays focused,
he can get away from all that.
Eli's money.
I need you to run it
to him tonight.
You go yourself.
I got a meet tomorrow.
Good luck.
You're still gonna
run it to him.
Right now. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
This isn't all of it, right?
You're short.
Looks like about half.
If you were me,
tell me what I'm
supposed to do here.
What would you do?
Hmm? What?
You leave. But this
is not over for you.
It's not over for your brother.
The winner of today's race
will go on to compete
at the state championships.
Stay with him...
Whatever it takes.
You give it everything.
Now's the time, son.
Leave everything on the track.
Runners, take your marks.
And into a smooth start
is Charles St. James,
as he goes out in front.
Keep up!
And newcomer drew Jacobs
is staying right on
St. James' tail.
Come on, drew. Come on.
Atta-boy.
Come on.
Keep up. Go!
And it's St. James.
Another great time.
Charles St. James is going
to the state championship.
Coleman.
You quit.
You pulled up. You quit.
Quit? That was
the race of my life.
Well, you quit.
You gave up, I saw you.
Look, I don't know
if could've beaten
the guy or not.
That's not what
I asked you to do.
What I asked you to do
is give it everything
that you had.
Someday you're gonna
look back on this time,
and you're gonna hate yourself.
Because you didn't push harder,
you didn't try harder,
you didn't take this
incredible opportunity
that's been given to you.
But now you got nothin'.
And you've given me
no reason to continue.
There's no state
championship. I'm done.
You're done with me?
I don't know why I ever
listened to you, man.
Why don't you take
a look at yourself?
You got nothin'.
You got no family.
So why don't you just go back
to that piece-of-shit
rat hole of yours
and drink yourself to death?
How could you send me to Eli's?
How could you
send me there, Wes?
He's gonna come after us.
You know that, right?
I told you not to
worry about Eli.
He likes to make threats and...
and cut you open.
He is nothing special, drew.
When are you gonna stop
lying to yourself?
Lying to myself?
You're one to talk,
because that old man
over there...
he is not our father, drew.
I lost the race.
Thanks for asking.
Are you upset about the race?
I'm fine.
I know you're fine.
I just need to be
alone right now, okay?
I get having bad days.
But if it's about
something else, you can...
you can talk to me about it.
Talk to you?
Hey, what do you
want me to say?
You don't understand
the first thing about
what I go through,
so just go back to
your little doodles
and your perfect life.
I don't need to be fixed, okay?
I'm not some pity project.
I didn't think
that you were one.
Drew, get up.
We gotta go.
Drew, we gotta go.
I'm not going anywhere, Wes.
Drew...
Don't piss me off,
not today.
What are you gonna do?
Get your ass up!
Do you want me out of
this house, is that it?
You gotta let go
of this pathetic
little dream of yours!
Wes!
Get off of me!
Stop it!
What was I supposed
to do when dad died?
What was I supposed to do?
Let's this family
fall apart? No.
I'm the one who took
care of everybody!
You got something in here.
It's so deep in there.
And you gotta beat it.
You gotta face that fear.
You've got to.
It's the hardest thing
you'll ever have to do.
If you do,
it'll change your life.
You'll be able to push
right through the pain.
Open that door.
And when your legs can't move
and your lungs can't breathe
and your eyes can't see,
you'll know that it's
just the beginning.
I did it.
I ran...
And I ran, and I ran.
And I faced it.
And then I just
broke right through.
And it was so beautiful.
You were right.
Wow.
Good for you.
You did it on your own.
And that's just the beginning.
Ohh.
Will you do this for me?
You still want to break
four minutes?
Hey...
You don't need me.
I'm asking for your help.
You bet.
No more riding in cars
for you, son.
Coleman said you could
use a running partner.
Did he?
He's gonna need
all the help
he can get.
Look, about the other day...
you can make it up to me later.
Want some water?
Oh. Oh.
Jeez, I'm so sorry.
I keep...
I'm just missing.
I'm missing.
Wes!
Wesley!
911. What is
your emergency?
I think I made a mistake
treating you like family, Wes.
Stay inside.
Wes.
What the hell
are you doing here?
What do you think
I'm doing here, huh?
Huh?
Oh, a slugger.
Huh? Big hitter,
here he is.
That's more like it, big hitter.
Not in my house, man.
Who pays the bills
on this house?
Huh? Everything you got
is 'cause of me.
Hey, flash, who pays
the bills on this house?
Get back inside.
How about I pop him in the leg?
Get back inside!
Go back in the house!
Coleman!
Eli!
Coleman. Coleman!
Coleman!
Are you okay?
Look at me.
Wes, go get help, please!
Oh, God,
you're hit.
Oh, you're hit.
Coleman, hold on.
Where's my glasses?
Wes, please,
we need help, please!
Please! Hold on,
Coleman! Look at me!
Hold on!
Where's my glasses?
Look at me.
Please.
Please. Look at me!
Wes! Ohh!
Help!
Please!
No! No!
Hey.
Do you know what I'm best at?
Nothin'.
Not a damn thing.
I don't want you
to come back here.
Do not waste what you got.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank you for coming today.
You didn't have
to miss the meet.
I wouldn't be anywhere else.
I wish you could've
gone, though.
I still think you could've
beaten St. James.
It's not about the meet.
It's not about winning.
It's not about
St. James.
There's something I gotta do.
Welcome
to the Washington state
high school
track and field championship.
Today's the big day for all
the best high school runners
in the state.
All eyes are on
Charles St. James
and whether he can break
the four-minute mile
and possibly beat
the state high school record
held by the late all-star
miler William Coleman.
I'm a poor substitute
for Coleman.
But since he can't be here...
this counts as much
as the state meet to me.
How did you know?
I knew you'd do this for him.
Take this.
Okay.
Three, two, one... Go.
St. James is once again
taking the lead early.
And as we move into lap 2,
St. James still staying
within record time.
Last lap.
St. James is still first.
He's giving it all he can!
He wants this record!
St. James at 4:02!
The record is still
up for grabs!
3:57.
Welcome to the n.C.A.A.
Collegiate track and field
championship.
In Lane 1, we have
Mike spade from Denver.
In Lane 2, Charles St. James
from u.C.L.A.
In Lane 3, drew Jacobs
from u.C. Berkeley.
In Lane 4,
Bob Jones, u.S.C.