Maybe the cap you
started with was too thick.
We have time.
We'll find one that fits.
...It's not gonna last.
I'm thirsty.
My tongue is swollen up bad.
I never thought our hiding place
would outlast our well.
Is anyone out there?
Can anyone answer me?
Can you hear me?
Anyone?
Anyone...
He)” Upstairs!
I'll check the attic.
Sure.
Don, there's nothin'.
There is no water here.
- Dave, what about--
- Let's just go.
Water.
Thank you.
Is anyone else with you?
The others,
they left you here?
Oh.
You could rest here awhile.
You can't walk
out of the valley.
Even if you weren't injured...
I'm not trying to walk
out of the valley.
My sister's on the far side.
I just need enough water
to make it to my sister.
She isn't well.
You can't stay here, either.
I'm okay.
I have my plan.
They're always hunting.
You stay put,
they'll find you.
Or your well will go dry,
whichever's first.
They're hunting in the south.
It's safer to go north.
Keep it.
Wait.
Stay lucky.
I'm good.
Where's Dean?
Hunting up some food.
He's getting worse,
isn't he?
Kendal...
Remember when this
was all rice paddies?
Catching all those frogs?
Do you think it'll
ever rain again?
So you found a wreck?
Yeah, just outside
the pumping field.
It's new.
Two, maybe three weeks.
We should be able
to find something.
Thanks.
You know I can help you.
Heard Island.
All that cold water.
That's a good spot then.
Plane lands on a
bright green field,
pumping lightly along
until it comes to a rest
next to a low stone wall,
built hundreds and hundreds
of years ago
by the earliest explorers.
There's a stone building
not far in the distance
with a cold stream connecting
the snowcap mountains above
to the blue-grey sea below.
And if you wipe the steam
off the cockpit window,
you can see penguins
and sheath piles
and elephant seals
covering the black mange.
...And I'm scared.
Can anyone help?
I'm on the Dover farm.
And someone is outside.
He's got a mask.
I'm so scared.
Can anyone help?
What's going on?
Someone's at the Dover farm.
You shouldn't go.
You always did.
You'll be okay without me.
It's not me I'm worried about.
Stay lucky.
...And I'm scared.
I'm so thirsty.
Please come.
Our well has gone dry.
We have no more water.
There are others
hiding out there,
parasite drinking my water.
Pick up the radio
and try again.
Please, let these two--
Pick up the radio
and call out again
or I'll have these two shot.
People used to show mercy.
Wells go dry.
People change.
There are no more farms.
There's no more farms,
they're all done in.
Please.
You don't want to kill her.
There's a man of God in here.
We're not going to hurt you.
You must be thirsty.
They're always thirsty.
Give her some of my water.
Come on.
Mr. Carson!
It's a trap!
Ah!
This is a fine house.
My grandfather
always admired it.
Search it.
Then on to the next.
We're finished here.
They're like rats
eating a sandwich.
You! Keep tearing
this farm apart.
We'll take the kitchen.
Look how sweet, father.
Someone closed her eyes.
Pray for her, Cadiz.
Pray for each of these
desperate, thirsty souls.
You'd think after
ten years of no rain
they'd give up.
There can't be many left.
We're going to hunt them
from dry well to dry well.
If they're alive,
they're consuming my water.
And they can't consume my water
without my consent.
Distributor cap didn't fit!
I wouldn't let them
follow me here...
You know that, right?
Not like we want
anything with you, anyway.
We found the Cessna.
It's ours.
Just the same,
maybe we'd let you come with us.
Maybe.
You have a good spot here.
I'll grant you that.
But we have water...
And you don't.
That's why I'm safe here.
You're too small
to be on your own.
I'm safer on my own.
Okay, I am not
going to argue with you.
I mean, you seem to be
doing alright.
But Dean and I,
we're not like the others.
You try loosening
the inlet flange?
Refill it with water
to prime it?
It's not the pump.
It's like the well gave out.
Just isn't filling anymore.
When you were at the compound,
were the derricks pumping?
All of them.
And the truck came.
Never seen them fill it so fast.
You don't need the plane.
You move at night.
Take as much water
as you can carry.
You can reach
my uncle's place in,
I don't know,
about three or four weeks-
Stop!
You know I'm dying, Kendal.
Without enough water,
my kidneys are done.
I'm not going anywhere
without you.
Move over.
I'm not going to leave you here.
I'm going to find it.
This is the Birch farm.
This is the Birch farm,
land grant 2371,
calling for Mr. Carson.
We'd like to request- noon
today- to the refugee camp.
...Birch farm.
...371.
We'd like to request...
...Refugee camp.
The Birch farm.
I guess that leaves
us and the boy.
You don't have to go.
I need to see what happens.
If it looks okay,
maybe we should call in, too.
I drink the tears of those
who have gone before us.
And my spirit is quenched.
We're done here.
The well went dry.
We took it as far as we could.
But it has been six months
of terror and hiding.
How many dead?
With Simon gone,
there's nothing for us here.
Just come with us.
They can help Dean.
Flacker says they
have medicine.
You never knew family.
We can start again.
Make a new family.
I hear Carson has a daughter.
We can send them to get Dean.
It's his kidneys, girl.
Same as his sister Pia.
There's just no way you kids
are getting out of here.
I can find Dean more water.
Things might be better
outside the valley.
If we go north,
there has to be water.
You still have faith.
That's good.
We hid a day's worth of water
on the north side of the house.
Welcome to it once we're gone.
Didn't your people
have a plane?
Used to.
Shot down over
the pumping field.
Burned out there
for two days straight.
Guess that's one way out.
Welcome, Mr. Carson.
Thank you for
responding to our call.
We are unarmed and ready.
Good.
If you'd like to look around...
Then shall they begin
to say to the mountains
fall on us,
to the hills cover us.
For if they do these
things in a green tree,
what shall be done in the dry?
I know this is hard,
but just isn't enough
water, you see?
Listen to me.
These were old people
and they're going to suffer.
You understand?
I had to do it.
You're different.
I can tell.
Now, tell me,
is there anybody else
on the farm?
Huh?
Come on now.
Listen, if we're going
to have a relationship,
that's based on trust.
You have to come clean.
Please don't.
Otherwise,
what's the point?
Yeah, there's one more.
One more.
Use the heat sensors.
You look like a man who prays...
Sit, daughter of mine.
I believe this is going
to be the last holdout.
As far as the eye can see,
this valley has Carson's buried
under every acre of it.
And I'm not going to stop
until it's all ours.
They suffer less
this way, don't they?
These little people?
Think of it as an
extinction of a species,
like the passenger pigeon or
the ivory-billed Woodpecker.
Your world is about
to get so much better.
What could be better than this?
This one is yours, my love.
Now, is that everyone?
Hmm?
Yes, sir.
Ah!
How is the pump?
It's slow.
But okay.
The usual.
Did you get hurt?
Nope.
Good.
I know why our pump is failing.
Why?
They're draining the aquifer.
All those pumps going
around the clock.
They're sucking the water
right out from under us...
But it's our well.
If the company drains
all the water,
drive all the
squatters away,
they control
the whole valley.
Maybe we should call Carson.
Maybe the company
camps aren't so bad.
We can't.
Carson's not taking
people to camps.
He's the one that's been
doing all the killing.
It's not Christmas yet.
Says who?
That's good.
We should go back inside.
They'll be hunting soon.
Wait.
I want to visit her grave.
Tomorrow.
I need to say goodbye.
I miss her.
You were just crazy enough
for her to like you.
I wasn't near as
crazy as your sister.
No one was.
Do you think it
keeps us here?
Her grave?
Of course not.
Let's go back in.
Listen...
When the time comes,
I want you to burn my body.
Don't bury it.
Not like this.
Nothing ties you to this house,
you understand?
You'll burn my body and
go to my uncle's place.
It's what Pia would have wanted.
Okay, I promise.
But I'm going to get us both
out of here long before you die.
Come on.
I'll be right back.
Hello the house!
Whosoever killed
in the trenches.
Whosoever left a
man's lifeless body
to the wind and
the vultures,
without the dignity
of a burial,
come forward.
Confess thy sins,
dearly beloveds!
We bring mercy.
Whosoever wants to
live another hour.
Whosoever wants
to see another day.
Come forward!
Step into the light!
I did what I could do.
Search it and gas it.
The attic.
Above us.
Go! Go! Go!
Up the stairs!
Hurry!
The sun's been pounding this
side of the building all day...
Gas it, then we'll move on.
Don't put--
Don't put it there.
Put it on the siding.
There's no sense in destroying
the beauty of the craftsmanship.
Respect the carpenter.
Onward, then.
Next property's north,
northeast.
The King track.
I know.
I'm going to get you water.
Come on.
Keep moving.
Ah!
Alby!
Pssst!
Are you okay?
I watch them in the shadows
waiting for me
to make a mistake.
I won't make a mistake.
- Everyone makes mist-
- Shh...
Wait for dark.
Then leave.
You're not helping me like this.
Will you show me where you hide
in case I need to find you?
They always come looking
after you've been here.
I don't need you to come by.
But we're going
to get out of this,
you, me and Dean.
I'm going to come for you
and we'll leave
this place, I promise.
Promise doesn't mean a thing.
What is it?
Vagrants.
Heading for us.
How do they look?
They're in bad shape.
It's okay. They'll see
that Carson's been here
and they'll take off.
We'll just wait.
They won't find anything.
And if they die
on our doorstep?
We've got a good store of water.
You say the pump's
in good shape.
Why not help them?
What if it's just another
one of Carson's traps?
We've got plenty of water,
right?
Right.
We have the water.
I'll give them a flask.
Just in case.
Not everyone is as
charitable as you.
It's long gone.
We're not going to
make it to another barn.
We won't survive
the noon sun.
Oh, come on.
We'll wait out the heat.
We got another farm in us yet.
Come on, all the wells in
this valley can't be dry.
Don't please.
Wait, wait,
please don't kill us.
We don't have guns.
Only knives.
We mean you no harm.
We're just very thirsty.
Why did Carson send you?
That liar?
We're not with Carson.
We're just thirsty.
Carson hit our farm
some time back.
Folks thought he'd help them.
We're the only ones
that survived.
Our well's been long dry.
And we had a good
store of water
until they ran it
into the ground.
We held on a week
before moving on.
Every well we've come to
in this valley's been dry.
You done?
Here's the deal.
You'll walk in front of me
to that tower over there.
I'm going to pass
you my flask
and when it's dry,
you'll move on.
You won't look back,
won't come back.
So you been visited, too.
Keep moving.
Those notices they post,
instructions,
they're all lies.
It's a trap.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
Thank you.
From the bottom of our hearts.
We wouldn't have made it
to another well.
How many of you are here?
I'm on my own.
Come with us, then.
Safety in numbers.
We owe you.
We're trying to
get to the mountains.
You've got a gun.
Improves all of our chances.
I can't.
Why not?
Looks kind of lonesome here.
Whoever you're waiting for,
they ain't coming back.
You guys should start
back on your way.
Thank you,
from all of us.
Thank you.
Were they in trouble?
Thirsty people at the end.
Carson's already killed
everyone else at their farm.
We're done, aren't we?
We're doing fine.
No.
You've been giving me
your water for a week.
So what is it?
What is it?
The pump's dry.
HOW long?
Two days.
How long can we survive
on the water we have?
A week.
Maybe.
Why wouldn't you tell me?
I thought you'd be gone already.
I need to try the wreck outside
the pumping compound gates.
For the missing distributor cap.
We've tried so many--
It's too dangerous.
There's nowhere else to try.
At least we'll know.
I just don't know how to
get that close to the gates
without them spotting me.
Do they still dump their
waste oil by the fence?
Yeah.
I know how you can get close.
What's the one thing they fear
in a world without water?
Who did this?
How did they breach the fence?
Go on. Fan out and find out
who breached the fence.
This is ridiculous.
Find them!
Come on.
Get out there.
Get the rest of the men.
What's going on?
We did it.
You did it.
Shut up.
I'll carry you the
whole way if I have to.
I got it all worked out.
We can't leave just yet.
We'll be too slow
over open ground.
- We'll wait for dark.
- Kendal.
We can have the plane
prepped by daylight.
You, me, Alby,
we're getting out of here.
Kendal.
Beautiful,
but there's no time-
- One more story...
- Later.
I promise.
Here, I'll go get water,
but drink this.
You can have as
much as you want.
Didn't I say that anyone with
water to give must have a well?
Mm-hmm.
Shh.
You hid it so cleverly we had
to wait for you to get a drink.
We're very sorry about
how this turned out.
Let's end this.
There's not enough
water for her, too.
When you're right...
...You're right.
Ah!
Hmm.
They're coming!
Run!
Come on.
Stay quiet.
And no matter what,
don't you ever dare come back.
I'll come back.
Dean!
Well, hello there.
We heard shots.
Where are the others?
It's just me now.
The others are dead.
Our well just ran dry
and we were fighting
for the remaining water.
Hmm...
Just ran dry.
And you killed the
others yourself?
Confess, son.
It'll only take the pain away.
I killed them.
You're a fighter.
I like that.
You know how I knew that
you were here all the time?
I mean, not you specifically,
but someone?
Birds.
Birds go where
the water is, so...
You afflicted with something?
The boy looks ill.
I remember this house.
Look at this.
This door frame is beautiful.
Sturdy.
Good one.
- I built it.
- Oh.
With Mr. Miller.
Wow, Mr. Miller!
You don't say.
Well, my hat's off
to both of you.
Mr. Miller left the land to me.
But not the water.
You see, there was a time
when a man owned the land,
he controlled the water,
but things are different.
The water's mine,
so the land is mine.
Empty-
Then go check the barn.
Get down!
Get him!
Put it down.
He's wounded, Cadiz.
Agh!
For shame.
Such a shame.
Dad.
Look.
Throw water on it.
Will this land never clear.
Carson, this land's
been blighted
- since before you were born.
- I know.
It's not your fault
the company no longer
takes in refugees.
It's not your fault
the rain won't fall.
Sometimes I just wonder...
I just wonder that
maybe I could've saved-
- You have to kill them.
- I know.
It's a mercy.
- The vagrants only suffer.
- I know.
I suppose if it wasn't me,
it'll just be someone else.
I didn't want this for you.
I know.
We're almost done.
Let's move on to the next farm.
Yes.
Cadiz can mark this one as ours.
Good.
Mark it. Let's go.
Of course.
You two go on your way.
Agh!
Ah, fuck!
Alby!
It fits.
Come on!
I got the cap for the plane.
Let's go.
No.
Ah!
Get the boys!
Alby, hide.
Agh!
God! Blood!
I must say,
I am pleased.
Finally a holdout
has come to me,
instead of cowering in your
hiding holes awaiting judgment.
Take a look, Brooke.
Look at her.
Yes, father.
Strong!
You must be the very last one.
The wells are all dry.
There's no one left.
My legacy is complete.
The valley's all yours, Brooke.
Daddy...
Come on,
come on.
Be strong.
Your future is secure.
This is Carson land.
Always was,
always will be.
And it'll rain on
generations to come yet.
I must apologize,
I would love to leave you
in this world.
But my daughter,
she can't stand competition.
Agh!
Ah!
It's just you and me now.
See, just you and me.
Agh!
And Dean?
He's going to
stay behind.