(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(BEEP)
JANINE: (ON ANSWERING MACHINE)
Hi, I'm trying to
reach Jeff Buckley.
My name is Janine Nichols.
I work at Saint Ann's
Arts Project in New York City.
JANINE:  And um...
We're putting together
a concert, celebrating
your father's music.
If you get this message,
can you please call me...
JEFF: Hello.
JANINE:  Oh, hi.
Um...
Hi.
Is this Jeff?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, great. I am Janine
Nichols at the Saint Ann's
Arts Project in Brooklyn.
Hi.
Hi!
Listen, Hal Willner
and I are putting
on a concert tribute
celebrating
your father's music.
And we'd love
for you to come.
Yeah, you know,
I don't really know
my father so...
Oh... Um...
Okay, I think it's
going to be great.
We have Richard Hell coming.
Does that mean
you want me to play?
Well, Hal really is
the one to say
about that.
I'm sure he'd love to take
a listen to you though
when you get here.
Well, you know what?
Why don't I give you
my number, and
you can think about it.
Because who is better
than you to be here?
I mean it'd
really be something...
Well, I don't...
I don't really play
my father's music.
What are you saying,
is that like
a church church?
Oh, yeah, it is.
But we just use their space
It's not like we're praying...
♪ The midnight cries
♪ I just came to chase
♪ the blues
♪ away
♪ for a while
♪ Just like a child,
you'll cling to me
♪ From every sound along
that rushes near
♪ It's just the breeze
Hi. Excuse me.
Do you know where
Saint Ann's church is?
♪ That licks your skin
and rubs your breast
♪ And as we lay
our rivers flow away
♪ Your woman fear
♪ Lord, I just came to chase
♪ the blues away
♪ for a while ♪
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
RICHARD:
♪ Someday I'll be all right
♪ When I leave the... ♪
How many times do we
have to go through this?
It's two measures ahead.
I can't sing it two
measures ahead. Nobody's
fucking listening.
Okay, can we
try it again?
♪ Someday I'll
be all right
No, no, no,
no, no.
That's where I hear...
I want the church organ
to come in.
If we use that church
organ, we'll have to put
five mics up there.
Really? That seems crazy.
Where's Hal?
Come on, lets...
RICHARD: Anybody know
where Hal is?
I don't know what
he's saying.
Can you just use the Fender?
Fender, Yamaha.
I don't... It might
be a Yamaha.
(SIGHS)
JANINE: I don't...
It's not a 700-pipe
organ, you understand?
You're here.
Yeah.
Hi. I'm Janine.
It's great to
meet you.
Hi, I'm Jeff.
Nice to meet you.
This is Jeff.
This is Tim's son.
Wow.
This is Richard.
Nice to meet you.
You know what,
it's a synthesizer.
It can do whatever
you need it to...
I got it.
Hi. I'm Jeff.
I'm Jen.
Trust me,
beautiful.
Nice to meet you.
You might want to
come on back.
Let's meet Hal.
HAL: Bach had 18 children.
Listen...
You get to meet Hal.
You look
just like him.
HAL: They're gonna
be here on Friday.
They said they would be
here on Friday. That is
what they're telling me.
Yeah.
What about, um...
What about Friday morning?
Can you come in and rehearse
on Friday morning?
No, no. Tech
is Thursday.
Come in on Friday
morning. That's fine.
Okay. Bye.
I'll see you then.
Hey. Wow!
That is spooky.
You're like a ghost.
Who me?
Yeah. You look
just like him.
(PLAYING CASPER THEME SONG)
♪ Casper the
friendly ghost
(HAL CHUCKLES)
♪ The friendliest
ghost, you know ♪
Your dad's guy
is coming too. Um,
Lee? You know
Lee Underwood?
Lee, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. We're going to
get you guys together,
and uh...
Well, I actually have
some stuff prepared...
Yeah.
Who was the
conga player from...
The guy who played
the congas for
Art Blakey.
JANINE: No.
We have someone.
Yeah. Get him here
on Thursday.
Tech in here.
You know the cool thing
about Art Blakey?
(PLAYING ART BLAKEY MUSIC)
That's it.
HAL: That's it.
Right. Right.
The cool thing
about Art Blakey,
Art Blakey said,
"It takes more courage
"to write a happy song."
We can tech on Friday.
There is a noon mass, Hal.
Who cares about mass.
We're giving them the father
the son and the holy ghost.
So, are we using...
Yeah. Get him
together with Gary.
Just get him together
with the house band.
Hi.
I'm Jeff.
I'm Carol.
Um, I didn't actually
know Tim had a son.
Neither did he.
So that makes two of you.
Oh. Well, I'm sorry
about that.
No. Um...
(CHUCKLES)
(MAN SINGING
IN THE BACKGROUND)
JEN: So...
What songs do
you wanna play?
Uh, I don't know.
I don't even play
my father's music.
I know it.
You know, but
I don't...
I don't play it.
I get that.
And yet I'm here.
Okay.
Hey, this is your uh,
schedule.
Contact details. That's
where you're staying.
That's your per diem.
That's a lot of money.
Not in this town.
Shit. I think we could have
a lot of fun with this money.
Not in this town.
♪ Long afloat on
shipless oceans
♪ I did all my best to smile
♪ Till your singing eyes
and fingers
♪ Drew me loving to your isle
♪ And you sang
♪ Sail to me
♪ Let me enfold you
♪ Here I am
♪ Waiting to hold you
WOMAN: Tim?
TIM: I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
I just needed to
get my other guitar.
How are you feeling?
You okay?
WOMAN: I didn't get
much sleep.
I'll um... I'll call you
when I get there.
Okay.
I'll call you in
a couple of days.
(HONKING)
I'm gonna throw
my stuff in the back.
Okay. I got the map.
I have the schedule.
♪ Did I dream you dreamed
about me?
♪ Were you hare
when I was fox?
♪ Now my foolish boat
is leaning
♪ Broken lovelorn
on your rocks,
♪ For you sing,
♪ "Touch me not,
♪ Touch me not,
come back tomorrow
♪ Oh, my heart... ♪
Tim!
Janie.
Where are we?
We're in the desert.
But...
You have a
gig on Friday.
I want to see it.
Come find me.
We can't have any unscheduled
stops today though.
Unscheduled stops
cannot be scheduled.
Tim!
Tim?
(GIGGLING)
My wife,
she just...
She hates my music.
I don't get it.
No.
Why?
She just hates
my music.
That's okay.
Do that again.
Will you dance with me?
Come on. Dance with me.
(GUITAR PLAYING)
(SINGING SOFTLY)
♪ You've got the untortured
mind of a woman
♪ Who has answered
all the questions before
♪ You've got the free-giving
ways of a woman
♪ Who has kicked all
the heartache out the door
♪ And, Janie, don't you know?
♪ Janie, don't you know?
I been trying
WOMAN:
♪ You've got the untortured
mind of a woman
♪ Who has answered
all the questions before
♪ You've got the free-giving
ways of a woman
♪ Who has kicked all
the heartache out the door
♪ And, Janie, don't you know?
MAN: Okay, let's go back
to the first chorus.
No, it's good.
WOMAN: Are we gonna
do the two verses?
MAN: I would like to.
Um... I don't know.
(INDISTINCT SPEAKING)
MAN: Let's, let's try
it again from the top.
(CAROL CLEARS THROAT)
Well, now that
the son is here,
I think we should ask
the son what he thinks.
MAN: Let's play
and see what happens.
JEFF: Hey, Lee.
Hey hey.
What you been
up to, partner?
(SCOFFS)
Shit, I've just been
herding some
cattle, man.
Polishing my spurs.
Good to see
you again.
(BOTH VOCALIZING)
GARY: Start the verse now.
MAN: Wait a second.
I don't know...
That's when you should
come in with the lyrics.
Right there.
MAN: Hey, just
a second, guys.
So, uh...
What's up
with California?
What's up...
Sun and surf guy.
I was born there.
His love of water.
LA?
Anaheim.
He's up north.
I don't know.
I love LA.
But no one will
fuck me in LA.
(LAUGHS)
I'm serious.
I don't think
you're trying hard enough.
No, no, no.
I try very hard.
And, this is
how I know.
There are people in New York.
Who will fuck me in New York.
Who will not
fuck me in LA.
I will fuck
you in LA.
(CHUCKLES)
MAN: Okay, guys.
All right, guys. Let's take
it from the intro, you
can try your verse.
From the top.
MAN: Hit it.
(VOCALIZING)
♪ If a fiddler played you
a song my love
♪ And if I gave you a wheel
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Uh-huh. Walk away, walk
away, walk away.
MAN: Everyone, walk away
for a minute.
LEE: Where did you learn
to play that thumb piano?
Berklee, man.
Undergrad.
You know,
you got to put
all that shit
behind you.
What shit?
You know, all that
stuff about your dad?
What the fuck,
Lee...
Look, I get it.
He wasn't around.
It's not like he beat
the shit out of me
every day.
When I was with him,
there were these nights
after the shows
when he would have me
drive him to your house.
He would have me
wait in the car.
What he was doing
was sneaking into
your room,
to sit there,
and watch you
sleeping in your crib.
Okay. That's weird.
I don't know...
I swear to God.
I don't know why
you wanna tell
me that, man.
(AMP BUZZING)
(BUZZING STOPS)
(CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
JANINE: All right. What
do we have? Hey, Allie.
What's next?
Song of the Siren?
ALLIE:  Song of the Siren.
All right.
Bring in the scrim.
Oh, no.
I don't know
about the scrim,
Janine. I really don't.
It's too big.
It's so big, man.
It's like it's a drive-in
movie theater right
here in the church.
It blocks Jesus, I can't...
I want a red sound...
JANINE: Yeah, where's
the violinist?
We haven't got
her yet, so...
Let's go ahead and
rehearse  Siren
and tell the guys to
bring in the scrim anyway.
Okay.
HAL: Not the
fucking scrim, man.
I think it's gonna
be great. Let's just
have a look at it.
If we don't like it,
we don't do it.
All right. Will you go
hunt her down because
we have to move this along.
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
I'll be just a sec.
HAL: I'm starving.
Bring me some
licorice and
beef jerky.
So,
California boy.
Joni Mitchell
masturbating on a rock.
Laurel Canyon,
orange juice.
That's it.
That's my life story.
How'd you know?
Oh, my God.
I totally wrote
the program notes.
So, I, like, know
everything about you.
How did you
get to be the
slave, here?
I'm not the slave.
I love working here.
Like these people
are incredible.
So, you know.
Also I have a huge,
huge crush
on your father.
Huge, huge?
Huge, huge? You sure
it isn't just huge?
Huge.
No, I never
exaggerate
my hyperboles, ever.
No?
He would have
liked you too.
You always walk,
like that?
You know, you waste
a lot of time that way.
You're like an alligator.
Really?
Yeah, alligators can run
like 30 miles an hour,
but, only in a straight line,
and they can't turn
and you're...
Like. Yes, you.
Really?
♪ You don't remember
what to say
what to do
♪ You don't remember
where to go
what to choose
♪ You wheel, you steal
♪ You feel, you kneel down
♪ Down
♪ All the stony people
♪ Walking 'round
in Christian licorice clothes
♪ I can't hesitate
♪ And I can't wait
for Pleasant Street
♪ Sunshine
♪ Reminds you
♪ Concreted skies
♪ And you find
yourself falling
♪ Back to yesterday's lies
♪ Hello
♪ Pleasant Street
♪ Don't you know
she's back again ♪
Hey.
The '60s were bullshit.
What? Dylan?
Mingus?
Boom.
That's '50s.
♪ You ask how much
I need you
♪ Must I explain
♪ I need you... ♪
(CHUCKLES)
♪ It's some kind of wonderful,
Yes, she is
♪ Some kind of wonderful ♪
Let me tell you,
one more thing.
And the '70s,
were almost big,
big bullshit.
Except for one thing,
and I don't need to
tell you what that is,
(GROANS)
(SCATTING)
The '80s, I don't
even need to tell you.
Except for The Smiths.
(SCATTING)
That's the '70s.
♪ Metal Guru, is it you?
♪ Sitting there in your
armor-plated chair, oh, yeah
♪ Metal Guru
(CHUCKLES)
(WHISPERING)
♪ is it you?
Jeff?
(HUMMING)
No, no, no
no, no.
Oh! (LAUGHS)
This is it.
I found it.
This is...
♪ Valhalla I'm...
(VOCALIZING)
♪ All I'm telling you now,
the greatest thing
♪ You ever could do now,
is share a smile
♪ For someone who's
blue, now... ♪
(MUFFLED SINGING)
(IMITATES GUITAR)
♪ 'Cause I love you, baby
How I love you, darlin'...
♪ Oh, little girl
Oh, little girl
(VOCALIZING)
♪ That's the way
it oughta be
♪ Momma said,
that's the way it
♪ oughta stay
(VOCALIZING)
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
To where to now?
I have to get back.
Oh, what?
I have to go.
(STUTTERING)
But we're going forth.
No, Hal is under the gun.
We are going forth,
not back. Come on.
They need me,
Jeff.
We have to go forth.
Where?
Anywhere. One of
your slave haunts.
Anywhere.
I have to get back!
No. We have to
go forth.
Wait.
(CHUCKLES)
♪ You don't remember
what to say
what to do
♪ You don't remember
where to go ♪
Don't worry,
I'm the alligator.
Wait.
(LAUGHS)
No.
Hey, no. You're
the alligator.
(LAUGHS)
You're
the alligator.
WOMAN:  I knew it was you.
Hey, baby.
Did you call before?
I was so afraid
I missed your call.
No, listen. It's so
packed here, you know,
everybody is asking about you.
(WOMAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
WOMAN:  How are you?
I'm okay. I love you.
You, too.
Where are you?
Are you in the little room
with the bougainvilleas?
You look so beautiful
in that house, baby?
Hey, listen.
Listen to me.
We are about to start,
so I have to go,
but I love you.
Tim.
I love you.
I'll talk to you soon.
JEFF: Were they...
Were they musical shows?
Acrobatic shows?
Do you have
stage fright?
JEFF: What? Are you
not gonna tell me?
Dog shows?
(SHUSHES)
What?
This is a cemetery.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
All of the names
are listed on the wall
and then...
(WHISPERS) I was like,
there are dead people...
Everywhere.
Isn't it cool?
Horse shows?
What shows?
What kind of shows?
Okay.
Uh...
I wrote these plays,
and one of
them was good.
I...
Played a boat,
and I sang naked.
And my mother brought
all of her friends,
and there was a
lot of nervous laughter
my aunt laughed.
I thought, it
really had something.
I did.
That led to a
great stint on public
service television
for bulimia.
You're a beautiful girl.
(IN DEEP VOICE)
Don't put me down.
You're beautiful throat.
(CHUCKLES)
So, sing me one of
your songs then?
No.
Sing me one of
your naked songs.
No. Why don't you,
tell me a story?
I don't hear
you singing.
Tell me a story.
What?
What kind of story?
I don't know,
it can be about anything,
but I'm gonna
keep my face
completely expressionless.
Yeah?
Okay.
Uh... Well,
this is a story about
a boy who had
windshield wipers,
on his eyes.
The only person
in the world
with windshield wipers
on his eyes.
One day,
it started to rain
and rain and
rain and rain,
oceans of rain.
Nobody could see
anything, but the boy,
and so, the boy
had to see
everything for everybody.
He got so tired
of seeing so much.
So, he went home
and stuck his head
in the oven.
And then,
they melted off down,
and then,
they became
chin swords.
And then someone asked
him to open a can.
And then, and then soon,
everyone was asking
him to open cans
and he had to go around
opening cans all the time.
He got really tired of that.
So, then he went home
and stuck his head
in the freezer,
and broke them off,
and put them in his pocket
and went to school.
That's it.
How was that?
It was great.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Let's get
something to eat.
I can't.
I gotta go.
No, no, no, no.
I'm starving,
I gotta...
Come on.
We gotta...
I...
I can't.
You're meeting someone?
I'll see you tomorrow
at rehearsal.
You're meeting someone.
Bye.
(TV PLAYING)
(FLIPPING TV CHANNELS)
For America right now
it's important to be
in Vietnam.
Because you never know
what's gonna happen.
What about
the Vietnamese?
I support the
Vietnamese people...
What the hell are
you talking about?
You care?
You care so much
you want to kill them?
You don't understand,
I'm from a communist...
Are you tilling me?
Telling you what?
No, are you tilling me?
Are you tilling my head?
Are you planting
something in my head?
(LAUGHING)
MAN: So you support murder?
This guy supports murder.
You don't even know what
a party is in this country.
I know what a party is.
Oh! What is it?
Yeah, it is...
Listen, listen, listen.
Listen, do you know
where this guy is from?
He's from Yugoslavia.
They've got Tito over there,
he's fucking living this shit.
Yugoslavia...
This Tito dude, you know,
he's torturing people,
there's mass graves.
It's not like
Vietnam, man.
MAN 2: Fucking right, man.
TIM: Fucking right.
He knows what he's
talking about. Yeah.
Yeah.
Drink up.
Cheers, comrades.
(LAUGHING)
No, we're not actually
really a band.
We're a fake band.
WOMAN: Okay, stop it.
No, I am... No!
WOMAN: I saw you sing.
I, that wasn't actually
singing. I'm a chauffeur
to an Irish nobleman.
Yeah, and Lee is
his stonemason.
(LAUGHING)
And
Carter cleans
the horses' hooves.
Fuck you.
Oh, yeah, man.
Niggers love
cleaning.
No.
Don't I know it.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(PLAYING JAZZ)
(CROWD CHEERING)
That's a real rhythm.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
GARY: Come on.
It's Gary.
I got you a
cup of coffee.
Now I am
drinking it.
Okay, now I am
really drinking it.
Hey.
Church is a madhouse.
Schisms, heresies...
Look, you got
fortune cookies.
This hotel
stinks, Gary.
"Everything in life
is somewhere else,
"and you get there in a car."
I need reading glasses.
Thanks.
Have a fortune cookie.
It's good with coffee.
Times  is coming.
Oh. The  Times.
Want anything to drink?
Uh...
Water,
water is fine.
Want ice?
Huh?
You want ice?
Gary?
(STAMMERING) Where did
you find all this stuff?
It's like Hong Kong in here.
It kind of finds me.
(PLAYING GUITAR)
What is that?
A little punk,
a little reggae?
I thought you were
doing metal in LA.
I thought, uh...
No?
How are things
going out there?
♪ I ain't got
the change
of a nickel
Oh, yeah!
♪ Ain't got no bounce
in my shoes
♪ I'll work anywhere I'll tell
boss I ain't fickle
♪ I ain't got nothing
about to blow on ♪
(VOCALIZING)
That's right!
That's cool.
You should use
that for one of
your father's songs.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Hey, I got
something here,
try this.
It's a little raw.
This thing is sort of
like a waltz, all right,
it's in drop D.
(TUNING)
There's a groove, right?
I got a section
that's sort of
like church bells.
Go on.
Here's a little arpeggio.
I'm not sure if it
will fit in here, but...
(VOCALIZES)
(VOCALIZING)
(CONTINUES LOUDLY)
(PHONE RINGS)
You should join my band.
Thought I just did.
So what are we doing?
Phantasmagoria?
GARY: What are we gonna do?
Nobody has a clue!
Thanks for coming, guys.
Everything's dandy.
Can we have
a song list
from you?
(EVERYONE TALKS INDISTINCTLY)
(MOUTHING)
LEE: Were you
ever there?
RICHARD: Yeah.
Cafe Wha?
Go there?
I play there.
HAL: Gary,
Jeff, I need you to see...
Hey, Allie, can you just
put this in there for me?
You gotta see this,
it's Tim live,
at the Folklore Center.
Are you adding a song?
We can do this.
I have to get away.
Um...
Doing  Once I Was...
You think we could...
Yeah? Could
he do it?
GARY: This kid could
do anything.
LEE: Rose Bowl's
like 100,000
people.
RICHARD: You want
that, though!
(CHUCKLES) I want
the Night Owl,
30 people, they're
so close you can
smell them.
LEE: You're off
by an undertone,
and you're dead.
And Tim was never dead.
Fuck the room.
Fuck it, it's not
about the room.
Fuck the room,
see, that I like.
No, listen. Nusrat...
Nusrat used to play
in a Sheraton
business center.
I mean this
gross, little place,
there's a shopping mall.
I know that shit,
that shit is fucking real.
It's a shopping mall.
He made it sacred.
What?
I didn't say anything.
It was just him and a rug.
A rug.
Yeah.
There's always a rug.
Fuck the rug.
JEFF: It was unbelievable.
His voice shook the planet.
And people floated
money onto the stage.
JEFF: They crumpled
the bills up.
Throwing down the
capitalists out there.
Your dad was into
the qawwali music
ALLIE: Hey, guys,
here's the tape.
Do I stand over there,
or will it just pick up?
SOUND ENGINEER:  Uh, I think
it will just pick up.
These guys always
have faith.
(PLAYING GUITAR)
Hey, watch this.
♪ Once I was a soldier
♪ And I fought on
foreign sands for you
♪ Once I was a hunter
♪ And I brought home
fresh meat for you
♪ Once I was a lover
Can we get rid
of the fuckin' bubbles?
Call somebody at  VH1.
♪ I searched behind
your eyes for you
♪ But, soon there
will be another
♪ To tell you
I was just a lie
♪ But, sometimes
♪ I wonder, just for a while
♪ Will you ever
♪ remember me?
♪ So now you have forgotten
♪ All of our rubbish dreams
♪ I find myself searching
(INAUDIBLE)
♪ Through the ashes
of our ruins
♪ For the days when we smiled
♪ And the hours that run wild
♪ Through the magic
of our eyes
♪ And the silence
of our words
♪ Sometimes
♪ I wonder just for a while
♪ Will you ever
♪ Remember me?
♪ Oh ♪
WOMAN:  Train number 267,
making stops at Croton-Harmon,
Poughkeepsie, Rhinecliff,
Hudson, Albany, Troy,
Amsterdam, Utica, Buffalo
and Niagara Falls.
There's a train
at 9:00 that we could get.
I'm not too worried
about getting back.
You're just gonna
stay in Amsterdam?
You know, frankly,
and I don't mean
this in a bad way,
but this, this whole thing,
this whole concert
is fuckin' ridiculous.
Like all these people
paying tribute to Tim.
They don't even know him.
They never knew him.
Lee played with him,
Lee doesn't know
him, Lee is...
How does anyone
know anybody?
We're all a million things.
It's a...
It's my father there
and that's his father.
He used to beat
the shit outta that boy.
Every day.
I don't know...
I mean, he spent his
entire life abandoning
the people he loves.
Writing love songs.
Fuck, I mean I get that,
I do, I get that,
but you know...
He made six albums by
the time he was my age.
So like what the fuck?
What am I doing here.
I don't...
Why am I here?
And then all these people
like, "You look like him.
"You look like him,
you look like him."
You do.
You do, you look
like him.
So?
Where you going?
One for you,
one for me.
No, thanks, I don't...
I don't want that.
I went to see
this, uh,
Kabuki
performance the
other day, it's like,
Japanese theater.
Yeah, I know
what Kabuki is.
This, uh,
one actor was
like 70 years old.
And his performance
was, like, exquisite.
Like the way
he moved an eyebrow
just affected you,
it was so weird.
And I knew that I needed
to get something from him.
You know what I mean?
And the next day I went
along to the theater, and
after the curtain
he appeared,
and I sauntered
up to him,
and I asked him,
I was like,
"How did you do this
one magical thing?"
I was like, "How
did you do it?
"How did you
prepare for it?"
And he was like,
"Prepare?"
And I was like, "Yeah,
for the performance."
And he said,
"Well, every moment,
of every day is this."
The performance
is no different.
Yeah, I like that.
You do that.
No, hardly, that's...
No, that's bullshit.
I haven't done anything.
You are able
to do that.
(SIGHS)
Your father
did it too.
My father was
a total phony.
You can't say that.
I can't say...
Why not?
My father was
a total phony.
Did you know him?
Yes.
Yes, I knew him.
No, did you actually,
like, meet him?
Met him twice actually,
once when I was one year old,
he dropped by my birthday
to give me a rattle.
How's that?
And then
second time I was
eight years old,
he invited me to come
see him perform at
the Troubadour.
It was his wife actually
who invited me to
come stay at their house
for three weeks.
Which I did,
and I never saw him.
I didn't see
him once. Why?
Because he was
at the studio every day,
to make this album,
and he didn't invite
me to come along?
No. Why?
(CHUCKLES) Maybe
because he knew
I could fuckin'
out-sing him then.
And as for his music,
my theory is that he just
found some hippy's
notebook on an acid trip.
When he ran out of pages,
that's when he OD'd.
(LAUGHS)
I'm serious,
I'm serious.
I'm totally fuckin' serious.
All I want to do...
♪ If a fiddler played you
a song, my love
♪ And if I gave you a wheel
♪ Would you spin for my heart
and loneliness?
♪ Would you spin for my love?
♪ If I gave up
all of my pride for you
♪ And only loved you for now
♪ Would you hide my fears
and never say
♪ Tomorrow I must go?
We got a
couple of hours.
You wanna sample
the local Dr Pepper?
Hey, how you doing?
BARTENDER: All right.
BARTENDER: May I
help you folks?
Can I get a shot
of Dewar's and a beer.
BARTENDER: All right.
And a Dr Pepper.
Ha! We've only got Pepsi.
That's all right, thanks.
So where do
you come from?
I come from
the '70s.
From the time of
big, big, bullshit,
apart from one thing.
What?
I don't know,
I don't know.
Say it.
I have a mother,
I have a father, um...
They fight over
the dishwasher.
How long have you
had this place here?
BARTENDER: Oh, 43 years.
43 years?
Oh, my God.
BARTENDER: My uncle left it
to my brother and me.
I'll be outside.
BARTENDER: We used
to have food in here.
BARTENDER: Now,
it's all microwave.
That's a shame.
We should go.
Jeff.
Where are
you going, Jeff?
Hey, guys, do you know
where 237 Mechanic Street is?
Yeah, it's down
there? Thank you.
Hey!
My father used
to live down there.
Okay?
Can I have your lighter?
Yeah.
719.
Thanks.
(PHONE RINGS)
TIM: Pick it up.
WOMAN: No, no!
Mmm-mmm.
(PHONE RINGING)
WOMAN:  Tim?
Hello.
Tim?
Hey, Mom.
Mary had the baby.
Have you talked to her?
Do you want me to
tell her anything?
Uh, um, yeah.
WOMAN:  You have a son, Tim.
What're you doing?
I'm fine. Everything
here is great.
So, listen.
You can tell her
that I'll call her?
♪ I'm not sleeping
♪ And you are sleeping
♪ And it's not
a good position
♪ To be in
♪ So take your
green, big pen
♪ Jam it once again
♪ Into your eye
♪ Till you see the why
♪ You're not living in
♪ The world of men
♪ And women who survive
♪ So take your green,
big pen
♪ Take your paper plate again
♪ And write it down
♪ Write it down
♪ Won't you say it?
♪ And I'll paint it
♪ I'll remain it
♪ Won't you say it?
♪ Just say it ♪
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS
IN DISTANCE)
♪ I lit my purest candle
close to my
♪ Window, hoping it would
catch the eye
♪ Of any vagabond
who passed it by,
I don't know what
you were thinking,
having ice
in your whiskey.
♪ Before he came I felt
the ancient fear
JEFF: Where are
we going now?
I think you should
get some sleep.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Well, am I never
gonna see you again?
♪ "Oh, tell me stories,"
♪ I called to the hobo
♪ "Stories of old,"
♪ I smiled at the hobo
♪ "Stories of cold,"
♪ I wept to... ♪
(ALARM BUZZING)
(ALARM STOPS)
(SOBBING)
(AUDIENCE CHATTERING)
ALLIE: Here you go.
Allie.
(APPLAUSE)
(BAND PLAYING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Are we wild yet
or what?
I mean, was Tim
wild or what?
(CHEERING)
♪ You don't remember
what to say
what to do
♪ You don't remember
where to go
what to choose
Uh.
(VOCALIZING)
♪ Down
♪ All the stony
people walking round
♪ In Christian
licorice clothes
♪ And I can't hesitate
♪ And I can't wait
♪ For Pleasant Street ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Gosh, it's very clear.
Ain't it?
Praise God!
You remember Tim, huh?
Fallin' off like flies.
(CHEERING)
♪ Comme la chanson est belle
Chantez la mademoiselle
♪ Dansant dans le Moulin Rouge
♪ Love is a leap, she sighed
♪ Someday I'll be your bride
(MUSIC CONTINUES
IN THE BACKGROUND)
TIM: (ON FILM)  We've got a
problem of business, you see.
Okay, so, we got oil
in Los Angeles,
spouting out of the ocean.
And it's killing all sorts
of sea life and everything
like that.
But it's a problem
'cause we need oil,
it supplies a lot of jobs.
And, like, the ocean,
you just look at it.
Well, those were
accidents that happened.
TIM:  They're not accidents.
They just passed a bunch
of bills...
♪ I'm as puzzled
♪ As the oyster
♪ I'm as troubled
♪ As the tide
♪ Should I stand
♪ Amid the breakers?
♪ Or should I lie with
♪ Death my bride?
♪ Hear me sing
♪ Swim to me
Ready?
Yeah.
♪ All my heart
♪ Is waiting
♪ To hold
♪ You ♪
Hey, I added
a second verse.
(CHEERING)
♪ I never asked
to be your mountain
♪ I never asked to fly
♪ Remember when
you came to me
♪ And told me of his lies
♪ You didn't
understand my love
♪ You don't know why I try
♪ And the rain
was falling on that day
♪ And damn the reason why
♪ Hey
♪ As I die I can't remember
♪ Where I saw the rain
♪ I'm sailing all my sins
♪ And I'm climbing
all my fears
♪ And soon now I'll fly
(CROWD CHEERS)
♪ I never asked
to be your mountain
♪ I never asked to fly
♪ And through his eye
he comes his love
♪ And tells her not to cry ♪
(VOCALIZING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ Aren't you the girl
♪ Who used to call me names?
♪ Who used to play at games?
♪ Weren't you the one
♪ Who said she'd never fall?
♪ Who's crying not so tall?
♪ Oh, I know
♪ What it's like
♪ It's happened
many times to me
♪ Oh, to me
♪ Oh do you ache inside?
♪ Do your eyes wanna cry?
♪ Do you want me back again?
(CHEERING)
(VOCALIZING)
(SCATTING)
♪ If a fiddler played
you a song, my love
♪ And if I
gave you a wheel
♪ Would you spin
for my heart
and loneliness?
♪ Would you spin
for my love?
(WOMEN SCATTING)
♪ If I gave up all
of my pride for you
♪ And only loved
you for now
♪ Would you hide
all my fears
and never say
♪ Tomorrow I must go?
♪ Everywhere there's
rain my love
♪ Everywhere there's fear
(SCATTING)
♪ I can clearly see
that our paths have changed
♪ Our sands are drifting away
♪ Must I beg to you
for one more day
♪ To find our lonely love
♪ Everywhere there's rain
my love
♪ Everywhere there's fear ♪
(VOCALIZING)
(CHEERING)
Thank you.
When, uh...
A long time ago...
A long time ago,
when I was a little kid
my mom sat me
on a bed
and she put
a record on,
and it was, like,
the first time I heard
anything that had
my father's voice.
I must have been
like six, I think.
And I was bored.
I was bored.
What can I say, I mean...
What can you expect from
somebody's who was into  Sesame
Street  at the time, you know?
♪ Ooh
♪ Once I was a soldier
♪ And I fought
on foreign sands for you
♪ Once I was a hunter
♪ And I brought home
fresh meat for you
♪ Once I was a lover
♪ And I searched behind
your eyes for you
♪ And soon there'll
come another
♪ To tell you
I was just a lie
♪ And sometimes I wonder
♪ For a while
♪ Do you ever
♪ Remember me?
♪ Oh
♪ And though
you have forgotten
♪ All of our rubbish dreams
♪ I find myself searching
♪ Through the ashes
of our ruins
♪ For the days when we smiled
♪ And the hours that ran wild
♪ And the magic of our eyes
♪ And the silence of our words
♪ And sometimes
♪ I wonder
♪ For a while
♪ Do you ever
♪ Remember me?
(VOCALIZING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Thank you.
I'm Jeff Buckley.
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
He was trying
to show me that,
you are too fast.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
WOMAN: Bye!
♪ I'm as puzzled
♪ As the oyster
♪ I'm as troubled
♪ As the tide
♪ Should I stand
♪ Amid the breakers?
♪ Or should I lie with
♪ Death my bride?
♪ Hear me sing
♪ Swim to me
♪ Let me enfold you ♪
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Hello.
Hey!
Hal insisted
no limousines, so
you gotta...
Where did you go?
I got you this
to read on
the plane.
What is this?
What are you
talking about?
I don't know. I think
it's your time, you know?
What are you
talking about?
This is it.
You got it.
You should get in.
You're gonna miss
your plane.
Listen to me, I never want
to spend a night like
that alone, again. Okay?
I want to write songs
with you.
Okay.
♪ Lilac wine
♪ Is sweet and heady
♪ Like my love
♪ Lilac wine
♪ I feel unsteady
♪ Where's my love?
♪ Listen to me
♪ I cannot see clearly
♪ Isn't that she coming to me
♪ Nearly here
♪ Lilac wine
♪ Is sweet and heady
♪ Like my love
♪ Lilac wine
♪ I feel unsteady
♪ Where's my love?
♪ Listen to me
♪ Why is everything so hazy?
♪ Isn't that she
♪ Or am I just going crazy?
(LAUGHS)
♪ Lilac wine
♪ I feel unready
♪ For my love
♪ For my love ♪
♪