1536 - MEXICO
PACIFIC COAST
Eight years!
Hey, little ...
How old are you?
19 years, sir,
two spent in this country.
Countries ...
In these countries ...
In this land ...
And your master?
Leave, leave ...
How?
He became what,
your captain?
Ah, Narváez ...
Death!
And with him, more than 600 men.
It has been hard ...
Living so many years
among the wild ...
Eight years ago in Florida
What assembly, gentlemen!
What meeting?
What grace and sweetness ...
And our clothes, sumptuous
are enhanced with the gold of India!
Blessings Cross
and the holy Veracruz
and the Lord of truth
and the Holy Trinity!
Blessed is the soul
which the Lord provides!
Blessed be the day
that the Lord sends us!
Ships?
All lost!
Is that all Spain
that remains?
These boats are Spain ...
Where ...
are the other boats?
Ahoy, mateys!
There!
I see a shadow!
It Narváez!
- Here!
- Captain!
Ahoy, mateys!
- Here!
- By Here!
Here Captain!
Over here, Captain!
Another annoyance, Alvar Núñez?
Captain, at this speed,
can not follow you.
So what do you suggest then?
To tie a rope to our raft.
Considering ...
that your men are younger
and more robust.
Listen, Treasurer
This is no time
give orders.
From now
that everyone here ...
This seemed preferable
to save his life!
You're the captain!
And those lives ...
you were assigned!
Think men in the boat!
They are sick and exhausted.
Give me the oars!
Grab it!
You are warned, Don Alvaro.
It's every man for himself,
there is more authority.
Here ends Spain.
Ramez, you!
Captain Narváez,
the smallness of your soul
equaled
the enormity of your selfishness.
Heals your language
fucking priest!
I tend,
but my last words
will be for you.
Here ends Spain
you say?
Well,
ends here for you too
hope of eternal life!
Good navigation, laddie!
Stop!
What assembly, gentlemen!
What meeting?
Stop, you get drunk
for days!
Stop! And then die!
Go to hell!
Leave him alone!
Ground!
Earth ...
A place to die.
Loosely based
THE STORY "SINKING"
Cabeza de Vaca (1542)
Nothing.
I did not find water.
Estebanico will seek.
In this direction.
Hurry.
Álvar!
I understand these cases,
they come
Boat Captain.
They are full
of junk and merchandise.
Some stuff
we would be very useful.
What the hell are they doing here?
Go ahead, Esteban.
What happened?
He died.
It is witchcraft.
- It must burn.
- How?
Move closer to the boxes.
Put it on fire.
Brother Suárez ...
- These objects of witchcraft ...
- It was a good Christian.
Drag them.
All!
It must be buried.
Timber!
You can not burn.
Collect all the wood
as you can.
- Come ...
- I said no!
Stop, Alvar.
His body is still warm.
You're crazy!
Why not burn my blood?
It's the same blood!
I act in the name of God!
I know what I do!
In the name of God? You answer
your actions to Him.
This is bad.
What they want me,
these dogs?
Do not take it!
Let me go!
Remember ...
Go to Panuco.
Still to Panuco!
Do not take it!
Remember ... Panuco.
Yes, towards the sunset!
My God!
What am I doing here?
In these lands,
in this world!
My God!
What am I doing here?
I am the slave
a son of a bitch Indian.
From a sorcerer!
A monstrous creature ...
Cursed be the day
I met you.
A sad event
bad thing.
That's right, laugh!
In my country,
You would have been impaled.
Laugh ... Laugh ... Laugh!
I speak, I speak ...
Because I am
more human than you.
Because I have a world
although I am a wreck.
I have a world!
And a God!
Because I also believe ...
the Creator of Heaven
and Earth.
Because you also
He created you, God!
I am Alvar Nuñez Cabeza de Vaca,
Treasurer Charles I of Spain,
Charles V of Germany
and master of India.
And that ...
India ...
I'm from Seville.
And this ...
This soil
And that, the sky.
And this ...
A plant.
And what else?
This is sand ...
And in the distance, the horizon ...
And the sea
Somewhere.
Sea ..
"The sea was slack ...
full moon "
"A Moor born under this sign
do not lie "
When I was a child,
and adolescent
my mother ...
Me said:
telling lies,
it is a sorry.
"Question me, King,
for the truth, I tell you. "
I will tell you, sir,
even if it costs lives.
"If you wanted, Grenada ...
With you ...
I would marry. "
"And as dowry
I'd give Cordoba ...
And Seville "
"I'm married ...
King Don Juan ...
I am married and not widowed "
"And the Moor
I am the wife ...
Much good I wanted "
Hands.
My hands.
The anchor. The anchor!
What is the raft?
Who's in charge here?
Alvar!
Here ends Spain.
Why did you leave me?
Since I have to condemn
I want to condemn me in peace!
You still disown your grandfather, Alvar.
But there is no other way to win!
To have won the rabble
increased wealth of the crown
and paved the way for your priests,
I'm in hell!
I've burned!
It is as dead as a stone.
Hear me, Alvar.
Leave here.
You can do anything!
Let's go!
He must go.
What are you doing?
She's dead as a stone.
It feels the suffering here.
What happens there, negro?
Negro!
- It is here ...
- Who?
The dead!
Death is here ...
The death ...
It is a musket ball ...
- You do not resurrected?
- No, Alonso.
He ...
We can not revive it.
Better stop talking
resurrections.
It may reach
Christian lands.
If you tell what has been experienced,
we believe you mad.
We will kill you.
They lock you up.
You come home in Spain
covered with chains.
Is that a threat?
No, this is not a threat.
This is what awaits you!
We'll have ...
Telling lies.
Alonso!
There!
We are Christians.
Servants of Her Majesty!
We are soldiers.
Like you!
Mr. Cabeza de Vaca
is the treasurer of the expedition.
It was wrecked in Florida!
Pray!
Mr. Cabeza is the treasurer
shipment.
What a day ...
Are we?
What day is it?
178 captain.
We need more,
80 more at least.
My God, what's that?
The treasurer of the expedition
de Narváez.
A Christian dressed as ...
We see these things here ...
Treasurer, we construct
a cathedral.
The captain is counting on you
to find her slaves.
Your Indian love you,
you won
esteem.
Mille ... five hundred ...
half ... six ... Year ...
Eight years!
Eight years ...
Your request ...
Offense more faith
it offends my ...
What faith are you talking about?
From this, or ours
faith of Spain?
The only one.
Faith.
Spain ...
This is Spain.
This ...
This is ...
Spain!
That captain
is ... Spain.
Your Justice
I have seen at work
on all roads
of this land.
This land ...
It is eight years.
Eight years.
Three, four, eight ...
Put this man under guard!
We are soldiers!
Health!
You have to see,
things these years!
Indeed.
Tell us.
You have seen cities of gold?
These eyes have seen.
Big and yellow.
From such brilliance that I was dazzled
for two days.
Temples,
The streets and houses ...
Everything was solid gold!
Cities of Gold ...
You were a prisoner?
Few days.
I was paired with Indian
with three breasts.
Three tits?
Besides that,
they were voters.
Women with three ...
Boobs.
In this city,
gave me a witch
ointment pestilential.
We will pass on the stick,
and an hour later,
you fuck with the force
twenty asses together!
You do not believe me, eh?
These cities, Dorantes
where are they?
Yes, where are they?
These cities?
My Cities of Gold.
Eternal youth
Rivers liquorice
female golden
manna as sweet
that milk fell from the sky ...
I know where they are
these cities.
Go, tell us.
There, in the north!
Tell lies ...
Like them ...
Estebanico ...
Why we do not say
truth?
It Araino!
- Where are you?
- Sir!
Stop!
What have you done?
Let them, bastards!
There is nothing to be learned.
Son of a bitch!
Why?
For Reload-Paradise