Based on a true story.
4, 1967 JUNE Saville Theatre, London
There is so much
contest this time.
- The Queen, The Who...
- I do not know...
I do not see it as
contest... not.
But think yourself better than
all of them?
A YEAR BEFORE
Cheetah Club - New York
Sorry to bother you.
Is Linda Keith?
Is Linda Keith.
Fantastic!
I was there with my friends
and saw immediately that it was you.
Can I have your autograph, please?
Dedicated it to Ted?
Not you rather before a kiss?
accounts with your friends that was the closer you got
to make a brooch to the Rolling Stones.
That's what you want, right?
I'm here with friends,
at this table here.
Do you want to join us,
a few drinks?
- Are you lemons?
- Honey, I forgot the lemons.
- No lemons?
- No lemons.
Come on, you know I need
of lemons.
Howlin 'Wolf?
Robert Johnson?
T-Bone Walker? It is a promotional copy,
completely fresh.
Whatever you want.
I trust you.
Roberta.
- Dylan?
- Yup...
Hair like him.
Jimi?
Want to try something?
One thing... the first time
not see in the mirror.
These types-ignited, you know?
- They were true to what they believed.
- Just as your eyes for me.
- No...
- Yes.
- Even very good.
- Yup?
Of course, because
is your real name.
I think Jimi James
sounds very...
- Canto-author...
- It's just for show.
Why do you need it?
I go on stage and I have to act.
Yes, because you can not take the stage
and act?
- Because you have to be a character?
- It's one thing, you know...
It's not. It's not a thing.
It's nothing.
Are you up there with hair arranged
and a leopard pattern shirt.
- It's leopard, is a cheetah.
- Really?
Yes... you know, Cheeta Club.
Shirt cheetah...
Really?
Not got there.
Will you continue on that stage with your
cotton shirt, you will be hidden there.
Of course, there are many other guys.
I just do not understand...
Why not?
I know where this is going.
- Where? What do you mean?
- Nowhere.
You're so serious!
We are just enjoying ourselves, you know?
Do you think I'm wrong?
- In some things, yes.
- Yup? Yeah.
You know, if you're done with
standards of cheetah and leopard...
- Drop the Curtis?
- Yes
Why.? For I would...
I find it quite adequate.
But it's the only thing I can say
of him.
You're bad, you can not take so personally.
It's just a thing.
I know, I have nothing to
lead to chest.
The more it takes to get you to you and R
your cotton shirt in an empty club?
's How it is.
Got Curtis, and me
is just a concert.
Gain enough, we all have things to pay
.
- Yes, but what if camest forth out?
- Are you stoned.
- No!
I'm asking you if that camest forth out
tocarias music?
I do not know... it's like you ask me if I had
a spaceship was going to Venus or Mars.
It's nothing. I'm asking if you could
play your music as you do?
If you could do things my way...
I did it, you know?
It was something new.
It was my own thing,
you know? Yes...
But I can not drop the Curtis
now, so...
The guitar is it, so...
I'm not even a guitar, you know?
Jimi.
Jimi!
- I want to go to The Village you.
- There's nothing there.
- Can I borrow a few bucks?
- What?
I will not play tonight,
so do not consi...
You spent the last dollar that you had that damn
disc!
- Dylan?
- It's my money.
And you caught it, salts
and do what you want?
Not lend you anything.
Did you hear?
- If you want something, waves me with you.
- There's nothing there.
Shit...
It's good you bring me food.
Thank you.
Do not ever over
whitey albums.
Jimi?
MANAGER / PRODUCER OF ROLLING STONES
- And do not you stayed unimpressed.
- It's nothing.
- Did you see how he plays?
- Is less than that, is rubbish.
- God...
- The hands of it are amazing.
- Is an amazing guitarist.
- It's not that they are missing.
And what was he playing?
A improvisation full of nothing.
It lost more money with him
than I do.
He is bright.
What will I do?
I am hired by your boyfriend.
When he returned from the tour,
I inform you that I share my time between
and he your friend?
Linda, I realize more than
what you know.
I'm tired to call me
"the manager of the Rolling Stones"
as thou "a girlfriend of Keith Richards
"
like a
description of employment.
Identity is a fantastic thing.
I encourage you to get a head.
But for God's sake, a bit of description
not hurt anyone.
- Anda. Beautiful?
- Have a good night.
- Come on!
- Because people care?
To spend that time
come see you?
Did you find it really fun?
Think it's attractive
doors to look directly at people?
- They had a strange skin.
- Are you that only you look at your skin.
Are you up there and not say anything
.
And when you decide not speak out more
than an inaudible whisper.
- I'm Keith, you know...
- I'm not asking you to be you Keith!
I pray thee, thou mount there and you
apoderes stage
as who really aspires
something.
Yeah... okay.
Okay.
You know that already do not have anyone
to come see you play?
You can look at me when I talk to you
?
- I do not have anyone.
- Thank U.
That tells you something?
- Yes? I can not believe it.
- I heard you!
Talk low, is
during another show.
Okay, thank you!
Yup!
You know I've never been
in Harlem?
I like to see other places, but
never been in Harlem.
- You could invite me.
- I would like.
There's nothing there for you.
Wander through New York.
It's kind of...
Everyone knows everything!
Only speak of the two.
It's humbling, very humbling!
For you to be, and I pity
it, really I have.
And he's a drug addict.
Know that?
's Always that!
Will you let her walk so
for America?
Chas.
Chas, hello.
I am Linda Keith.
- The Keith Richards girlfriend.
- Hello There!
BASS PLAYER OF THE ANIMALS
- How are you?
- Well, are you?
I'm fine.
I think for me it's over,
after this tour.
We were not anywhere,
lost Alan.
Out...
- No, he's afraid of flying.
- Really?
Will play the new album
for us?
- Yes
- E is called?
- House of the rising sun.
- Okay, here are The Animals.
No... over.
I see the written headlines.
Our manager robbed us shamefully
.
- What does he say?
- Spending money to make money...
It is money that never see.
I want to be manager of some musicians.
I treat them well and paid the bills.
- And you? You're still model?
- Occasionally... yeah.
To the chagrin of my father, the girls
British should not do that.
I'm not sure what it is supposed
do, but apparently
be model and walk with the Rolling Stones
are not viable options.
Things are coming.
Always come.
Or so I was told.
You talk seriously about leaving for
act to manage?
Because I have something for you.
You can try you for
put something else?
You go up there for a reason...
I do not know, maybe...
Will you sing? Would have much
offerings cantasses.
My voice is...
is terrible!
Also Dylan! He
has turned out well, do not you?
Chas really likes blues.
So if you're in the mood
can touch something...
Bluesy? Sure... whatever you want
that touch, I play.
I look like your mother?
I do not know.
Your thing, Jimi.
Your way.
He's kind of quiet.
So if you do not speak much
light not the chest,
's not in his nature.
- Of Course.
He thinks not... well it
does not like singing.
And think you have a voice
quite weird, but...
not think it's anything weird
.
- I need another, you want too?
- Absolutely, yes.
Thank you for coming to Wah coffee.
We have a very good show for you
.
To begin this evening,
Jimi James and the Blue Flames.
Damn!
So, no holes in the clubs
RnB in Harlem?
No, my, they're very restrictive
there.
They managed to get the blues there,
do not know who took him home.
- They fuck them.
- Fuck! I like him.
- You're brilliant.
- Thank U.
- Linda told you what to play?
- No... just told to play.
I heard almost everything there is to hear and...
Dismantle you all with your
hands, man. Jesus Christ!
- Nobody brokered you?
- No...
Jimi, you're not much of commitments
it?
- No.
- For...
- Linda told you I search...
- People who would like to work.
What do I broker, but was never
manager in life.
- I have never been touted.
- Neither Even Steven.
Okay... go for a tour
within 3 months.
I think it would be great if you came with me to London
.
London... there is already there so many people
good playing.
But you do not got to you.
Of that you can be sure.
No one bothers you because of this chord
, or that...
They would be crazy to see what
you do there.
All that play there're
the stream of blues...
But do not want to be caught
this type of labels, you know?
He is playing blues. Or RnB,
or soul... all are cages, man.
I'm not saying it has to be...
You do not have to do with style, you know?
I want my music
enter the person's soul.
For me are colors.
I want people to feel the music
the same way that I see it.
They're just colors... the rest is a bit
painted science fiction here and there.
I do not want to scare you...
early.
I have to take you to London.
Already know you a pimp seriously?
Yes, pimps use it on the streets.
Yes... use.
I will use it on stage.
Say, "Look at that pimp with
guitar upside down."
Is a type looking for you.
Says called Keith.
- Richards?
- Allen.
Leave it up... I think.
Yup.
- Who is Allen?
- Is my father.
- You're kidding, right?
- No...
- Are you serious?
- Yup!
Shit...
What beautiful work...
You do not want to say anything before?
This is Mr. Jimi Hendrix.
Pleasure.
Tidy your things.
Tidy your stuff...
So, my...
Come on!
It's all arranged. Can you
leave work and some decent concerts.
Initially it will not be much money,
but I take care of the expenses.
I do not know, my...
- You wanted to come to London before.
- Yes, but that was before.
So what changed?
You do not have much to say, do you?
A speech... the other listens.
You know Eric Clapton?
- If heard of him?
- Not if you know him.
Course, Clapton is a myth.
If it is to London, you present it to me?
He, Beck, the Townshend...
- No... only the Clapton.
- Okay, so we get.
- You passport?
- No, my...
- You birth certificate?
- Do Not...
Do you know how to have a copy?
Your family has a copy?
I have to call my father.
No... not you'll call.
If not we have the birth certificate
not you got a passport.
I do not know, but I will not call you.
Okay... I do some calls.
Shit families, uh?
You know, my father did not recognize me if he saw me
now, you know?
I have not spoken to him Condo
much time, you know?
Nor should know I'm alive
or not.
24, 1966 LONDON SEPTEMBER
CLAPTON IS GOD
How was your trip?
No, I'm not ready...
I am a mess.
The next time you're
will be a mess...
- How is he?
- Life is a party.
We are at night, then?
At about 21. In the Scotch?
No, I still have work visa
can only play a few minutes.
- Jimi, we go to the hotel.
- What time shall we meet?
Arise.
Come on.
You have to see what the Chas brought.
Seems a savage.
Can I have a drink?
- I have spoken with Jimi!
- Stop crying.
I will have with you the Scotch!
Hello, how are you?
- You like it here?
- Yes, yes... and you, are you okay?
It's the kind we saw in the afternoon.
- You want a drink?
- Yes, a glass of wine.
Fantastic!
Did not you will have a light?
Chas probably have, there'll
back in a minute.
Excuse.
- You got a light?
- I have.
- Have you met Jimi?
- Hello No...
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure.
- Where are you from?
- Well, I come from Seattle.
Seattle? This exist?
- You know California?
- Yes, I have heard of that site.
Well, is just north...
- I like your style.
- Thank U.
- This is very cool.
- Thank you very much.
- Yes, I like that.
- Thank U.
Shirt I like too.
Bought these clothes in America?
How is there?
Yes Or rather, heard of there..
Do not make me laugh!
- Seattle, Washington. That's where I am.
- Where the president live?
No... no, it's another Washington.
Is Washington DC.
Do you mind to tell him to
out of my place?
Can ask you to leave
my place?
- She is just...
- I did not ask.
I'm just being social
, love.
Why do not you be social
elsewhere?
Why not forsaken the store,
your cow? You know her?
Yes, it is a friend.
Why do not you tell your friend Condo for
go annoy the fuck?
Anyway, there never was...
Anyway, you have a beautiful mouth
.
- I can tell you something?
- Yes, says.
My Salts place ?!
From one point of the sea to the
circles of your mind
A new force acts on the planetary transformation
A new radio for
a new world
An average of 96.3 Khz wave
takes the force of conscience
on the radio Caroline
Fuck!
Jesus Christ...
What are you...
Linda, no!
What the fuck was that ?!
It was my guitar...
Sorry for last night.
I think I left my emotions
take the best of me.
It's all cool, no problem.
You were one day, Jimi!
One day in London, and already did
a jetty of nonsense!
I do not planned anything.
I have experience in putting
things in a certain order.
... You take away me from a club
was not planned.
I could not have planned it.
Is how things are.
People are not predictable.
Sometimes are... and everything is cool,
and sometimes prefer to stay
drugged instead of being mothers.
This was a very short trip.
From your mother let you, the foderes
all the girl that you see.
This is how you intend to proceed?
Will be your crutch?
I have no intentions here.
I've seen what they do to people.
"I plan to do this and that."
And bad things do not result,
let them all fucked.
No... I'm not with them, you know...
I have my own thing, my own
time, my space and everything is beautiful.
- The rest is just...
- Reality!
We can change the world!
If you could, the only thing that would make was
put a little more color on the streets.
Other than that, we have to accept things as are
.
But what will happen is
get started stumbling around...
and you'll realize that this is enough.
What will be brilliant enough to
make you win the day.
And things as there are accepted but
is what you try to say, Jimi!
You can not let other people decide
your life.
This is your life!
Please footholds it?
- Have disses you.
- I say, yes.
And I hear you?
That tell me to be myself?
What is the alternative? Can not you see me say
to you follow everyone else.
- Why you should listen then?
- Because I love you.
When I saw you at the Cheetah Club
were twenty people in a room for a thousand.
And these twenty people talked, drank and
ignorant of what was happening on stage.
And I wanted to turn me to them all
and say, "They'll be all crazy?"
Do not you see?
Do not see what he can do ?!
I think none of us means
whatever that is for you.
Never heard anything that you said.
I always hear.
Always.
What is it?
What?
The first night we spent together
, I told you
"Whatever you do, do not
see yourself in the mirror."
You were me pedrar instead of me saying
soon as you look in the mirror
would pass through me.
Come on, that's not fair.
No experience needs to be reckless.
And become in a bathtub
to pass you,
is no way to find that
speak the truth.
What did you see when you looked in the mirror
?
... My shit maradas.
Seemed to Marilyn Monroe!
Yes...
Watch the press, Jimi...
They can be extremely fierce.
It is better to have a deal with them...
The Oldham is extremely smart, you would not harm
doors near it.
Chas should have thought of this.
It is very good, Chas.
You're in very good hands.
See if the hear.
Do you want to leave?
It's different, really it is.
Is a good time to explore.
The Beatles have just done one tour
, left this space.
And you the Kinks, the Small Faces...
Everything became... Rock n 'Roll direct.
More raunchy. I think people
're more receptive to it.
It looks like the world is.
Aged too, right?
Not?
- I like your hair.
- I am a hairdresser.
- Yes?
- Yes.
I love it.
I know all about hair,
yours is cool.
Is natural or permanent?
Just be honest, do not lie to me.
It has its own life, look.
's Cool, it's like Dylan.
I like him very much.
Really?
Thank U.
The way the announcement was made...
- This seems to you a heron?
- No, honey...
You do not have to be anything, you know?
It's beautiful the way it is.
The way it was written, I thought that was a
audition for Animals.
The Animals?
Because you thought that?
No... I'm an animal, but not
"The Animals".
The pay is good?
I'm dry.
- Dry? What do you mean dry?
- I mean bankrupt.
I like this term. No, the concert
not pay much.
Nothing to do about it.
We're broke, but we're cool.
Yes, we have the right style.
Do you prefer to walk with us and be
bankrupt... and be cool?
I'd rather be here bankrupt.
What do you think?
I
I have an international
call to you and to
Jimi Hendrix to Mr. Al Hendrix
- Is Mr. Hal Hendrix?
- Well, yes...
- accepted the costs?
- Where does the call
- Father!
Accepted costs
- Yes...
- might talk
- It's Jimi!
- Who
The Jimi! Your son Jimi!
Can you hear me?
- Who?
- Is your son, Jimi
See this, guess...
Guess where I am..
I'm in London.
I am in London, my!
- I am? ?
- Where
In London, England!
A type caught me a
club where he walked to touch.
Now is my manager and I
my scene happening.
- That's funny?
- I'm making a record
It's funny to you!?
- No, not try to be funny
You think I'm an asshole...
Father, you know what.?
Wait, someone wants to talk to you.
Come here. Tell him, talk to him.
Hello mr. Hendrix.
Speaks Cathy.
- Who is this?
- A friend of Jimi
She was eager to meet him, the
Jimi will not stop talking about themselves.
He's here to do sensasionais things,
now has a manager and is
to start a band.
I heard him play, by the way.
Must be very proud.
- Very proud...
Yes, it is in England
Yes!
If you are in England, why the hell I
call collect at the destination ?
I do not accept the call radius
payable on target
If you want to talk to me about England, tell him
to write me a fucking letter
This guy must think I'm crazy...
I
- Jim?
- I
- I am!
- Yes...
Where the hell did you get the money?
If you are there, it is because you stole
No, do not steal anything, man.
I'm really doing something here.
Yes...
I have to go.
I have to go, okay?
I'll call you later.
All right, gentlemen.
Let's review the situation.
The Redding is entering
replace bassist, right?
It is a good musician and is
willing to join.
Right. And the battery? We have to keep the dishes
to beat, or not?
Yes... We're still looking for
drummers.
There arrive... spending time.
Time spent is money spent.
Yes... there are things we need...
Jimi Hendrix and the Experience.
Yes, quite like.
- Your name is Jimi, as J-I-M-I.
- Yes, I like it that way.
It was a pleasure to give you the idea.
- No, I thought...
- Your success is payment enough.
We have other things to discuss,
to speak truth.
- We have?
- I made some contracts.
Things signed when
tried to do some...
We heard some gods old and Jimi reveals that...
were things I did... to play,
nothing serious, you know?
When you say "some contracts"...
I made a recording with Curtis.
And I had to sign something.
- I was doing work background...
- They're a pair of contracts.
Technically it still belongs
these types.
Yes, and I'm with a guy...
I was just doing one session.
It's nothing you need to worry
.
Okay, when you say "this kind"...
To whom are you referring to?
Juggy Murray.
- Do not tell me...
- Yes
Okay... we're here
a beautiful situation..
Looks like I'm going to solve it
America.
- What are you...
- The Jimi Hendrix Experience.
Yes, it's better that way.
The chakras are cleaner,
faster.
Says it in a nutshell.
Cherish it, not Jimi?
The economy of vocabulary?
Yes, of course.
When I return, I can also have a record contract
there for you.
So deal with
join "experience".
1 OF OCTOBER 1966
REGENT STREET POLYTECHNIC
Is it?
It?
- Is it up there?
- Oh yes, God Himself.
Let's see if he wants to talk a bit
?
Let's go before the concert start
.
Yes... asks if
I make a jam with him.
Yes, I want to play with him.
Go get the guitar.
Go there. Jimi! This was a
please your friend here.
- A favor your friend!
- Yes, fine.
- Hello, my. I am your big fan.
- Thank U.
I'm a big fan.
- You can connect there.
- No, no... here is fine.
I was thinking about doing a jam.
Know the Killing Floor?
From Menace Boy?
You know the Menace Boy?
I do not know them very much.
Come on, man. Are the blues, you have to know these songs
.
I teach you.
We have a guest who
will touch us.
Came directly from America.
What's your name again?
- Jimi Hendrix.
- Mr. Jimi Hendrix.
Damn...
- Eric...
- He is that good?
Give me that.
Now ladies and gentlemen,
your and my favorite,
King of the continents, Tommy Putin.
A big round of applause.
Cathy... look here.
What do you think?
- Sorry... stopped.
- What?
Was working Condo little
and now left to give.
It's broken.
Neither is complete.
- Can arrange it?
- Not worth the money spent.
- It is good to me?
- You're very handy.
- Thank you, I buy it? .
- Yes
How much is this, man?
- He is aggressive, I must say...
- In good or bad way?
See how
was always looking for Jimi?
- This is only... is aggressive.
- What did you think of Hensley?
Is just right.
- Also liked him.
- I said that I liked.
Is just right, but plays
always safe.
Thanks for the concert, but still
I am learning on bass.
It would be nice to have someone more experienced.
It would be nice to find someone
to show some respect.
This is now your band, is it?
It's called The Jimi Hendrix Experience,
. "The experience of the two types
who came from America"  not
We all know our place.
I do not wanna make a big fuss of it
.
He's not afraid, yes.
I do not condemn the can for it.
For me reminds me
more Elvin Jones.
Yes, it is more oriented
for jazz!
Yes, so it will not be that thing "rock"
that everyone tries to do, you know?
Exactly.
Would you then put more experience in
Experience.
He's right.
I can say what you want, you know?
Okay... look.
Hensley... and Mitch.
Yes... and the Little Richard...
Why are called the The Breakaways
This is the Jimi experience Hendrix
singing...
You will sing, I will not sing
You must sing.
Are you here choirs.
No, we should put
The Breakaways to sing the melody
I agree, and we support
But I could not go
the high tones. What tone should they arrive, Jimi?
Fifty. As far as I know they're there
500, gives three hours right?
- Two hours, Chas...
- Two? Come on, you're hurting me.
- I'm doing you a favor.
- I understand.
- This is the best equipment there...
- I can see that.
- But give me three hours.
- Not tale, Chas, because I know you.
You know me, so not all.
They're there five hundred pounds.
- He has not even tuned the guitar.
- I'm about!
- But no one else booked...
- Two hours.
If you finish in two hours...
Recording.
We can download some lights?
To create a certain environment
, you know?
As my voice sounds
that side?
- We have to record the track, Jimi...
- Okay, okay...
With lights or not.
You have to sing faster than
raids to catch the bus home.
Okay, here goes...
- No, do you want to download the lights
Please, yes. I think
help. Thank U.
Recording.
Why are the lights off?
Jesus Christ, we are recording!
Who writes the shit
of darkness? I knew there.
Good to know, you're not completely stupid
!
Only you doing ignorant!
Now get out of here for us to do something different
to burn money, you bitch!
Okay? Come on...
This time without laughter.
- Yes, that was good.
- Were awesome, girls.
See you later.
I like what they did, it was great.
It was cool...
He talks to me like that, call me
goat and not say a word!
- What are you talking about?
- I am the radius of your girlfriend!
- What did you want me to do?
- You should defend myself!
Fuck you, ruined me
take the woman!
Fuck you!
Would you hit me?
It's all right.
Has passed, man.
You see? She is crazy.
It's crazy...
What is wrong with you?
People come
energy that acts on stage.
It's what they call it?
Energy...
But it seems very tiring.
You're having fun?
Yes, it's work as another
whatever.
I go up on stage every night and
consumes a lot of energy as they call,
but if not we give all...
We must put all our individuality
what we do, you know?
has a new album about to leave
Yes, they'll all buy.
But there is so much competition.
The Queen, The Who...
No, I see no way
competition.
But the Beatles have mentioned that
find it amazing.
Want to talk about it?
That's right. Fries...
fries and eggs, right?
And drink as much tea!
What is it with tea, man?
We drink tea because it was what
drank while invadiamos India.
That's why we're always agreed
, they'll never sleep!
- Caffeine, caffeine...
- The tea makes you not be awake!
Alcohol is that you
is being awake.
No, alcohol gives you sleep.
At least I give.
Not do anything. No need
much to put you to sleep.
Since not drink with your cooked...
- What they are up to?
- What you mean? Nothing.
All.
Something.
- Imbeciles playful...
- He's bothering her?
No... as you can see.
Thank you, buddy.
- They're together?
- None of your business.
- Like them well done?
- Disappears, can head!
Now I was upset.
Is drunk?
Want to take a complaint
disrespect Condo authority?
- Was in the Army?
- Yes...
- I'm a soldier.
- What war was?
At all.
I am in constant war with gray.
Only becomes the
little minds.
But it's out of fashion...
- You having fun?
- Yes, we are to have fun.
- Put garbage in the bin, please.
- Sorry, Officer.
- My father was in the army.
- Yup? God... God bless you.
Died to wear that uniform.
This? Is that this is the Victorian era.
His father died to deal with donkeys
or clear skies?
- Not You...
- Stay away, not worth being.
You're a disgrace to all
men who used this uniform.
Take it.
Put yourself walking...
in your bike.
I have no bike...
do not have bike.
Them you should not have given
your coat.
You should not have given them.
You do not know how.
You never had to go through this.
No need to talk about it.
- It was a great concert, amazing.
- Yes
It is said that the very Paul McCartney
recommended you personally.
There are only two bands
represent England.
- Who is the other?
- The The Who are the other.
Of course... yes...
Monterey... never been there!
Is hot?
No, it's Northern California.
But do not worry about it.
Should I buy a matching jacket.
Do you think I should buy a coat?
- We should go buy new coats!
- Who else is playing?
Otis Redding, The Mamas & the Papas...
is the thing John Phillips.
Yes, I know.
The The Who, as I said.
Refferson Airplane... and you.
Jimi! Come on, give me a smile
, son!
- Today is a good day.
- Yes, yes...
It's a great day.
You know, playing guitar is about what you do on stage
Electric're up there
not want to know anything else
Come that energy, all the feel
I think we should just...
It was what I expected. The beginning of a new era
Go again to put it in place.
What are you doing?
- What time is it?
- I do not know... a couple.
Two hours...
The Salvation Army Band is
playing outside. Let's hear?
- I want out.
- Yes, alright...
I want to go out with you.
's Two hours!
I heard you at first.
It's two hours and you stay sitting there.
You look good. Never want to leave!
- Woman, play every night.
- You play music, that's not socializing.
Do not give me shit, come on.
- I want to hang out with people!
- I do not hang out with people!
It makes me feel uncomfortable.
You're just saying shit and balelas.
I leave you embarrassed?
I'm always on the bullshit!
But if you do not speak the Dylan or
Howlin 'Wolf not you care in the conversation!
There are other things that we can talk
, you know?
Okay, what you want to talk?
Do you want to talk? Speaks.
I have friends!
- Right...
- I have people who leave.
For God's sake...
I'm sick of it.
". No short arms, so I'm cool
You're bored, that's what you are!"
Buster...
Fuck you .
You know what?
Sai but is already here!
I'm not to put up with this shit
.
- Is it good? You like?
- Yes, yes... like, it's cool.
It is about what?
"The City and the Stars" talks about
a being super smart coming from the universe.
It is just there, you know?
Condo hold.
And one day will descend from space and
save us all from ourselves.
And teach us... not to hate, but to love
even seriously.
This is profound.
- I know, it seriously.
- Oh, yeah?
Yes, there are a lot of things out there that do not even know
.
As other people in other solar systems
they've got the same things as us.
No bad feelings, you know?
It is as if our negative vibrations from affecting
the way you live.
- It's all...
- Yes, negativity betrays us...
Yes, but the solar system is
undergo a massive change.
Will affect land within
thirty years.
And our friends are gonna
space come and show us the way.
- The path?
- Yes...
In fact...
What are you doing?
- We were just...
- What did you? Jimi!
Jimi, wake up!
Opens ohos!
What you this?
Jimi, come on, get up.
Wake up! Jimi, wake up!
Only smoke some herb.
Jimi, you have to get up now.
Get out of here!
You have to get up, come on!
No, everything's cool.
We just hang out.
- I miss you.
- We were just talking.
We talked about child stars,
and science fiction.
He wanted me to stay with him until you arrived
.
Would you stay with it?
He just buy it.
Okay...
I realize...
- You're cool, you can stay.
- No, I'm fine.
No, it's okay.
Okay.
- I saw him play. It's good.
- That's incredible.
Yes, it will be a rock star
one day.
He is a rock star.
It is one.
- Okay...
- Where does that accent?
- Milwaukee.
- I do not know.
There's nothing to know.
- They're together Condo long?
- Since coming since September.
This is a long time in
years groupie.
I'm not a groupie,
'm his girlfriend.
Well... girlfriend,
fine.
What is the secret?
Us plenty of fun.
We are always happy.
That's the secret.
You should see what I fled.
God...
Teeth direitinhos and conversation
complex. Boring...
The easiest are always
the most boring.
You've been with some
rock star?
- Yes, I've been to many.
- What was the most durable?
Once was with the same type
a five and half months.
Five and a half!
Yes...
- What happened?
- Met a prettier girl.
But without problem.
I met a musician even better.
Turns all r Returns the largest
and better.
But do not have to worry about that you
.
Why will not know
a better musician?
Because he will never know
prettiest girl.
We are not even
tables, my
Not we played in the Top 100
or anything, man.
The newspaper needs to associate
music to a face!
You need to be seen there.
No, you said that if we are to consecrate
have to conquer London.
- Was what you said!
- We won half of London!
But we are at risk if
not conquer America.
What is wrong with you, man?
You start with one thing and you end
another bullshit any.
- What is it, man?
- I'm you to cheat!
Not with the place where the disk is
!
Look, I gave everything I had
to bring us where we are today.
Spent up at the last pound
to bring us here.
- So this is about you?
- It's about the payment.
For me, yes. And for you.
For us, for the guys.
100 songs, my...
Not one!
Hold to Monterey.
Can be?
- Could be?
- Yes... yes, my... yes.
I like him, though.
You know, you should let it grow
wild, like an angel.
I'll leave.
I have not cut the most.
And do as before,
put ointment.
- Yes...
- control it.
Casts well your face.
not seem remotely different
I brought someone to see you.
- What's up, man?
- How are you?
Enter.
You know Jimi, right?
Will be a rock star one day.
Oh, wait. He is a rock star
!
It's what your girlfriend
say, right?
Why do not you get to Jimi
some herb you have?
- Damn...
- We have many guests.
- Where are the papers?
- In the drawer, where are forever.
I saw you play. Jimi Hendrix, yes...
Very good.
So, what do you think of London?
- It's a good scene.
- A good scene?
And where is this good scene?
I touch the Scotch... and Bag O'Nails
the other night, man.
- The people there are very cool.
- Yup?
Here appreciate how music
different than in America.
In America still... still
all separate in America.
There is a scene for a type of music,
and one scene to another kind of music.
And when you try to mix everything
are uncomfortable with you, you know?
Here, just...
They give you more freedom to play!
And love it. You-let do what
want, when you want.
- What? They leave you?
- Yes
Sorry, but you just said
you have freedom to play..
When there is freedom nobody leaves you
do anything, you just do.
There's nothing in the drawer.
Is within the drawer.
Better search.
But you know that... good for you.
Vieste, you are have fun.
In the name of England, good in
name of black England...
- Welcome.
- Thank U.
Seems to me that you had not much
chance to see the black England.
Bridgestone, Notting Hill...
not divide things as black or white
England.
But... it is so.
They divide.
Or perhaps you have not had your
share of threats here.
I read what the newspapers say
your music.
"Wild, tribal, violent..."
words, my...
They're just words.
To me not bore me the words.
But do not use when talking about
Jeff Beck or Eric Clapton.
When they play blues is acceptable.
But as you touch blues...
You're a violent abomination
and black. Thank U.
England is different
America.
Our problems with
racism are more... subtle.
This new
England was built in the Windrush.
Have you heard that?
You do not know what it is?
- The Windrush?
- No, never heard.
After the war, the Caribs...
and the Indians of the West
were brought to England.
That's why you see ads all over the
side labor and employment.
"Come here, work
hard for a better life."
- These are new possibilities.
- But there was no possibilities.
Not exist or decent accommodation
payments.
- There is a class system here.
- Notting Hill, my...
It was hard work, yes.
But anything better life.
Yes, but it is difficult to
all, right?
People are just people.
They're like animals.
The animals are animals, right?
The stick his nose where it is not
due to smell the heavens of the other...
Yes, animals are animals.
Even animals have never been...
Look... I say this from brother to brother
, okay?
For they are not more than just
curiosity. And that's the truth.
They make you not go to the stage,
they want you there. In the electric chair.
This is low, man.
You've been playing with whitey, when are
British blacks who need inspiration.
- Inspiration, my...
- Why do you think joke?
- I can you tell me what I am...
- You could be a symbol.
I do not understand, what you're talking?
- Just play guitar.
- Plays music for your people.
- My people?
They're all my people.
What...
Each of them are my people.
Jimi... people around you
this time, do not understand.
If you go up on stage just to be there
, you are wasting you.
Music should represent
protest notes.
No doubt, man.
The protest is everywhere.
Everyone wants solutions now.
Okay, so you go up on stage with
all stratagems, is this the solution?
I'm sick to speak of stratagems.
World not just a big fat
ploy.
Wars, you know? Napalm bombs
and all that stuff...
You have people who are burned
direct on TV.
Right across our faces Rs.
All this violence...
is not my scene, man.
Okay, so what?
To sit down and do nothing?
It would be like you.
Faria exactly the same as you.
Said shit and smoking weed.
The herb is good, but the shit you say my...
Do you really want to change things?
When the power of love takes
love for power, that's where things change.
29, 1967
SPALDING MAY, LINCOLNSHIRE
Toca something!
Plays a fucking song!
Come on, buddy!
Where is the show?
- I paid to see this shit.
- Cala me that...
"Characterized by awkward silence,
tuning guitar obsessive,
And obscene gestures, the fans think what
lost musically during this concert. "
- Jimi...
- is not in tune, my
Toca something, my
Get thee.. . fuck, I'll tune this guitar
not to take me all night
"On hearing the first album,
the answer is. little"
"Jimi Hendrix is not a great composer
not a great singer. "
" is solemn when you're not angry.
Vago, when it's not archaic. "
" The quality of the songs is equivalent to
the purism of their letters. "
"The song that gives title to the album is
little lyrical and unambiguously primary."
You're really facing
play any shit, right?
Not you care how it sounds.
Go away then, my!
- Do not take long, did you?
- The single or revenge in America.
- And together you a critique of these...
- I do not mean anything.
I can already see the movie.
The people asking me if
he deserved the invitation to Monterey.
Why are we here ?!
Why do all this?
Mitch?
- Where's your girlfriend?
- I do not know.
She stopped a lot around here.
There are people sigh you
ears. The fill-in...
I do not even want to know.
It's a lack of respect, you know?
Escape you will...
The Jimi should be
Subtle touch the theater.
Brian Epstein wants to celebrate the new album
Beatles and the boys are gonna be there.
If Jimi has a performance like last time...
We can lose Monterey. In a second
.
Come here.
- Come here. Arrives here.
- Go on.
Sit down.
Sit with me.
Come, sit down.
- You want to come have a drink?
- I...
No, she's fine.
She does not want anything.
Yes, I do not want anything.
- See you in a bit.
- OK.
I'll just call a person,
okay? I'll be back.
I am? Me.
Yes, dear.
You come here? Yes, the site is good.
Is half full.
More people will come here
a few hours.
- Jimi, great show.
- Thank you very much.
I have to go.
Thank you, thank you.
What is this ?!
What is this?
Fouls me concerning ?!
Who lines?
Who were talking about?
Fouls me concerning ?!
I said to take
away!
- You'll be fine.
- Yes.
- It will all be fine.
- Yes, thank you.
- Are you cool?
- Should I take...
Should I take these for pain.
And these sleeping. Later
not now, I do not sleep tonight.
I wrote them for you.
You write lyrics that have nothing
be with you and everything is supposed to be okay?
I never doubted you.
Was not me, it was you.
Was you... it was your chance!
Only you can blame you.
Is plotted.
All in all, the blame
's all yours.
You think to walk with a star
rock just behind fun.
It's them that make it real,
but never for themselves.
His whole life is to
fucking brooch.
You can not continue to think
on something that is not.
He walk the fuck around. And later
or earlier back to fuck you.
But it will not come back to fuck you,
will do it just to mess with you.
Why would you say that? Why would you say such a thing
?
Because I'm your sister.
I will leave you to pieces
to think he loves you
when in fact only
love yourself.
Are you worn out, dear?
You seem to be.
You know what you need?
Come here.
Do you have any... let me see here
.
Yes, you have some.
You know what? Let me take some
.
Take a few. Will put you to sleep
instantly.
Maybe take a few myself.
I feel all...
If you need anything,
I'm really out there.
4, 1967 JUNE THEATRE SAVILLE, LONDON
- Sorry, my...
- Have a good show.
Jimi... gives a fucking
good show.
Put it to give. Let's open with
this is the track that gives name to the album.
We put it in E and took
music to heaven, man.
This Condo came two days.
A half hour concert
want to learn a new song?
We can, come on, man.
The Beatles're in the audience.
It is an insult!
Only if estragarmos all! Come on.
Let's have fun while we live, man.
So, we can start with you
the dares some rhythm...
- Quaternary.
- Yes...
- You start for me, right?
- I give you four.
Yes, I like that.
And I will do a solo at the end of
first verse, even before the chorus.
- All right.
- Even before the chorus?
I like these pants.
It's beautiful, man.
Ladies and gentlemen, the hosts:
The Jimi Hendrix Experience
Ears!
Watch the ears!
Can you see them up there?
I have to go.
- Jimi?
- Yes...
I have to go with you.
We have a tour to follow.
If it works... we'll see.
Only the festival then.
I'm just going to the festival and come direct
home.
- You should rest.
- No, I'm fine.
- Rest.
- I was able to come to you.
- Never been to San Francisco.
- Is Monterey.
Also, there's nothing there for you
. Not gonna like.
You know, I'll be back soon and.
It's nothing special, okay?
- Are you nervous?
- No... of course not!
- Are you excited?
- I still think crazy...
All they'll be there...
Simon and Garfunkel, Otis Redding...
- Janis Joplin, come my...
- And you!
Yes... believe that?
Yes, I believe.
- Want to go?
- The Monterey?
- Yeah, you should go.
- What your girlfriend think of that?
Maybe you have not told you?
Maybe secretly in
wanna together.
- Did you hear the Red House?
- Yes
You know I wrote it for you..
Note up?
Keith wrote the Ruby Tuesday
to me when we finished.
I have these men all the
write me songs.
After going home and
hear them alone.
What is it with you?
Can act for a thousand people
but are not honest for one.
Can sing everything but...
Do not come between the lines.
Why do you want to go with you?
It makes me not go running
pack.
Good times.
We have a good time here.
It would not be anything... it's all
very restricted.
- It's all very formal?
- Yes.
- So how would there?
- More loose.
More  loose?
How uncertain?
When booting things, I think
if you will continue to notice my presence.
Yes... of course.
Things you love are with you.
Whether you want it or not.
You have a disturbing way of being.
Very simple and profound.
I do not think it's a good idea
I go to Monterey.
So, think themselves better than they
No, there's nothing to do with
be better or something like that
It has to do with inspiration
And I'm inspired by everyone,
by all kinds of people
For me it is art.
And this is to show something never seen before
, or something you see every day
Show it otherwise, you know
So I should be able to pick up on any song...
Should I be able to undress and submit
in a way that never hast heard, you know?
It has everything to do with inspiration,
and inspire others
translation and subtitling:.
André Leitão