I devote myself to Allah
and pray for Him
to grant my habitation among the excellent,
forever in heaven.
My heart, I rinse
in the light of the law and faith.
And my patience guides me right
When I'm lost.
Come on, girls!
Stand on your places.
And again....
Wadjda!
Come closer!
Let's see...
Repeat the first two verses.
Do you not want us to hear
your voice? Go outside. Go outside!
Again.
Don't forget the keys, and don't lock
upstairs. Dad will be late from work.
- Okay?
- God willing.
It's a long way and you're always late.
I have to drive other people too.
If you're late again, I won't wait.
- Mom is not late. You just got here.
- Ignore him.
I'm not talking to you, little girl. I'm
talking to your Mom. I tell her every day.
Watch out!
- Soon you'll be a pro.
- Where have you been all week?
Jar has something for you.
A volcanic rock from the Rub Al-Khali desert.
It's magnetic.
Dad! Mom has been waiting
for you all week.
The door upstairs is unlocked.
What a mustache! It would make great
advertising for shaving cream.
It's good. A real mustache even
a falcon could land on it.
Or maybe an airplane.
Thank you for breakfast.
Finally, I got my sandwich back!
Watch it!
Who said you can catch up with me?
Did you really try to overtake me?
If I had a bike you'd see.
Girls, stop!
Why are you laughing and talking so loud?
You forget that women's voices must
not be heard by the men outside.
How often must I repeat it?
That a woman's voice is taboo.
- Sorry, Miss Hassa.
- We won't do it again.
Wadjda!
Where is your headscarf?
Did you come to school
with the head uncovered?
Stop it, girls, don't laugh!
Good girl! Come on up!
Come up and play with us.
Wadjda!
- Don't talk to me.
- Wait a moment, please...
I brought you this.
We are not even yet. When I get my
bike and win the race, we're even.
- Do you know that girls don't ride bikes?
- Double loss if it is against the girl.
You! Go play somewhere else.
800 Rials.
Too expensive for you.
- Hello.
I'll make some lunch for you.
Oh, God! A three-hour drive
in a car without air conditioning!
This trip to the world's end
is killing me.
- I don't like that face. What's up?
- I want a bicycle to ride with Abdalla.
Have you ever seen a girl on a bike?
I'd rather sell fruit at the hospital
than endure that ride again.
- And when I come back,
I hear "I want a bike."
- Where are the bracelets?
- I only did ten. My back was killing me.
That'll be two Rials each.
I had so much pain in my back,
When I sat down, but I made them.
God save me, for you! Take it.
It's your turn.
Watch out, girls.
There are men watching us.
- What? Maybe they think they're Superman?
- If you can you see them, they can see you.
Respectable girls go inside.
The others stay where men can see them.
What are you doing here? Go to your class.
Don't you see there are men up there?
- Did you hear? Thieves broken in at Miss Hussa.
- It was her lover not a thief.
Her father thought
it was a thief and called the police.
- If he said it was a thief, then it was a thief.
- I knew you were going to say that, Salma.
The only man that would show
interest in you would be a thief.
Wadjda.
Can you bring this to my brother?
It's my pass.
- I'll give you ten Rials.
- Twenty.
God, you are something...
He's waiting behind the school
and is in a white pickup.
Wadjda.
Tomorrow you are wearing a headscarf
otherwise you'll be sitting in the sun.
I will, God willing.
Cover the face.
- Are you Abir's brother?
- I am.
Do you have the card?
Here, Abir said
you would give me 20 Rials.
- Really?
- Yes, so help me God.
Okay, here you are.
Huh? Even your money stinks of
cologne.
"I long for you, my dear."
Did you know that there's a new invention
called a tape recorder.
- You want to buy something?
- I'm not sure.
First, I need to look around.
- No tapes. Only CD.
- Thank you. See you tomorrow.
Do you believe me or do I need to swear?
I can not find words to describe you.
Love's loveliness is within you...
- Wouldn't you like to be a singer?
- Me, a singer? God forbid!
I have saved 87 Rials so far and
only need another 713.
Could you lend it to me?
Oh, no! Not the bike again!
Stop nagging me, please!
Ms. Hussa said I must have
a headscarf, and cover the face.
That was neat! A veil!
Maybe we can marry you after all?
Very funny!
Come...
Try this.
Mom, it's too long.
Hold it like so, from the bottom.
Oh, no! A thief, a thief!
A thief jumped Miss Hussa's fence
to see her.
We don't know, it may have been a thief.
You should be ashamed to say that.
A thief.
A thief! a thief!
I need to buy a nice dress
for your cousin's wedding
so that women will think twice before
they start fantasizing about your dad.
Forgive me, my dear Leila.
I'm truly sorry.
Iqbal, our driver, is so rude.
Today, he screamed at poor Aisha.
She cried throughout the journey.
Abir. Mariam's daughter?
They caught her with a man?
Do you know who he is?
Ah, I know who he is.
A womanizer like his dad.
Is he as good-looking as his dad?
You have to admit he is good-looking.
The religious police?
Mariam must be totally destroyed. They
should have married her off long ago.
That kind of girl is always
a nuisance.
Leila, I have to go now.
My husband has just arrived.
But I want a minute by minute
account of Abir's shenanigans.
Take care. Goodbye.
What is it?
Don't worry. We'll marry
you away someday. Go and say hi to Daddy.
Oh, God, why did I change my game?
I lost.
- Are those your marks or did you fake them?
- Really. I'm good with math.
The proof? Pythagoras theorem is God's
miracle. The triangle never changes.
It sounds like you know
what you are talking about.
Now, I'm saving for a bike.
I lost.
Where is dinner?
What a beauty!
- A superstar is here.
- Get out! What do you mean "superstar"?
Your mom spends her days
looking for a bride for you?
I doubt that she tries so hard.
- Come play with me.
- I don't know how.
Let me play.
Tapes with love songs.
Bracelets for football clubs.
Are you organizing a fan club or what?
Don't you know these things
are banned in school?
Abir always behaved so well.
She never caused any problems.
Did you know that yesterday the religious
police came and found her with a stranger?
Did you arrange the meeting
between Abir and this man yesterday?
- No, ma'am, I didn't.
- Don't lie.
I'm sure you were involved.
I just don't know how.
What shall we do with you now?
Expel you?
One moment, Miss Jamila.
I'm not finished with this girl.
You can go back to your class now.
We'll see what we'll do with you later.
Madjda, replace those worn shoes, have
regular black shoes like the other girls.
What's this?
The religious club's Qur'an competition.
I really don't know
what to say, Principal.
All of this for the sake of a bicycle?
As long as I live, you won't have one.
Should I wait until you get kicked out?
Turn off the damn radio
and those infernal songs.
Those songs only mean trouble.
You are not better than Abir.
Soon, her parents will marry her off.
Do I have to pay? Can't you pay
yourself for once?
I already paid for your driver. Your money
is into savings.
How are you going to pay for your new
bride's dowry? Some kind of groom you are.
Do you think I yearn to
support two families?
Give me a son and everything will be
well again.
But we both know that won't happen.
Forget it, but don't count
on me next week.
Don't come back! Go home to your mother
and keep looking for a bride.
Lady, I'll wait for you for an hour. If
you're late, you'll have to get a taxi.
That's enough, Iqbal. We get it.
Who is that little girl, Iqbal?
That little girl is my daughter.
I haven't seen her in the last three years.
She is going to school now.
I never went.
- It shows. You can't behave yourself.
- Shut up.
It's you who doesn't know how to behave.
I make better bracelets than these.
Can I get ten Rials per piece?
No. I get them from China.
100 for 10 Rials.
- But not with our country's colors?
- You mean like these?
- Can I try it?
- Sure.
There's a women's fitting room
at the far end of the corridor.
If it's too large, we can fix it.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Would your father like it?
Let's go back to the clerk,
so that they can fit it up a bit.
Let's go before Iqbal gets angry
and leave us behind.
Don't worry, he won't leave.
Pass me the dress.
- Who was the boy you spoke with about the bike yesterday?
- What boy? What are you talking about?
You know very well. I don't want you
to sell my bike to someone else.
Here. I mixed an audio tape for you,
because we are friends now.
But don't sell my bike to anyone.
God willing.
Ms. Hussa will explain the rules
for the Qur'an competition.
It's in about five weeks.
I'll send around a sign-up sheet.
- Ms. Hussa....
Good news, girls. The prize has been
increased to 1,000 Rials, from 800.
You must memorize the first six sections.
The competition is in two parts.
First, the terms and background
to God's revelation in the verses.
Second part is the recitation.
The recitation should be with
the correct pronunciation.
I repeat, correct pronunciation is a must.
Good luck in your endeavors.
What do you want?
I've thought a lot about what you said.
I'm willing to change my ways.
God be praised! Why all of a sudden?
I want to become a member of the
religious club.
How much?
Only 80 Rials.
Cheaper than a bike, right?
Is 62 okay?
"Choose the right answer.
What are sabianerna?"
"Wrong. Retry.
Okay, brother!
What are sabianerna?"
- How should I know?
- Iqbal!
We pay you every month,
whether you drive me or not.
Why do you speak like that to me?
Have you no shame?
How so? Do you believe that you are
the only driver around here?
I'll get another driver tomorrow.
Guys! I 'll be late
to school. I must go.
Abdalla, how do I get to Derah?
Come on.
Hide your face.
I'll say you are my sister.
Your sister? No one will believe you. I am
too cute to be your sister.
"I can't arrange transportation today.
Could I take a leave of absence?"
I still have some leave coming to me.
Certainly. Next month
I can sub in for others.
That's very kind of you.
See you tomorrow. Take care.
- Do you know where the driver Iqbal lives?
- There are many drivers named Iqbal here.
I hope we are going in the right direction.
That could be Iqbal's car.
Yes, it's his.
What do you want?
Iqbal?
This is not my business.
Speak with him yourself.
All right.
- You? What do you want?
- Iqbal, why did you do it?
Go away.
- Where is your permit?
- What? Why do you want it?
It's a good job. Drive Wadjda's mother
again, and everything will be all right.
Do you know my uncle, with the mustache, I'll speak with him.
He'd be interested about your permit.
"My uncle, with the mustache..."
He knew who I was talking about.
The mustache is like a trademark.
They say the son wrapped explosives
around his waist and bam... He died.
- Clueless type! That must have hurt.
- Dying for a man of God is like pinpricks.
And then you ascend to heaven
and get 70 virgins.
Is it true?
Pang! 70 bikes!
You are wrong.
Doesn't work that way.
Come on. Did you missed us?
You've been away for two weeks.
Do you think about us or somebody else?
If you have the moon,
Why are you looking among the stars?
Okay. Take care of yourself.
Keep studying.
Hello? Hello, Leila.
So. will you come?
Can you bring the money you owe me?
Is that true? Do you work at the
hospital across the street?
Does your husband let you work
with other male colleagues?
What do you want?
My uncle asked me to hang some lights across
the street and attach them on your roof.
Hang them on the neighbor's house's
roof instead. Not on our roof.
They do not have a pole to attach them to.
Your roof is the only one that has one.
Wait a minute.
Mom....Mom...
Thank you, sweetie. You can be
a darling sometimes.
Abdalla wants to hang some lights
in our roof, for his uncle's election.
Tell him no. He does not represent
our party and we won't vote for him.
Okay, I'll let you do it on condition
that you bring your bike in the morning.
Hello, Wadjda.
You've grown so much and look so beautiful.
- Where's your Mom?
- She's coming.
- How's school?
- I don't like it but it's okay.
Traitor! You live next door and
don't tell me?
I've had it with Iqbal! Three hours
in his car every day it's too much.
In addition, the hospital has
good hours and good pay.
And the driver waits for me.
When is the party?
Next month. I'm going to buy a dress
for Wadjda uncle's wedding.
The future pretenders will also be there.
God help them. You'll break their hearts.
By the way, they are hiring at the hospital.
It's next door and we could be together.
My husband is jealous. He wouldn't
let me work with male colleagues.
Stop it. You always blame everything
on your poor husband.
- What's this?
- Training wheels. It'll help you learn to ride a bike.
I have to hang up the lights,
so I can't push you.
You think I'm a too little?
I took off the training wheels.
I'll give you five Rials
if you stop crying.
OK, girls. Let's start.
You all have your Qur'an?
Before we begin, if you have your period
you can't touch the Qur'an without Kleenex.
It's no laughing matter.
You are young women now.
I said stop.
You take it by the edge with a Kleenex,
not with your fingers.
Page 87.
Start with Surat al-Nisa, Ayat 59.
Let's start with a new face.
Wadjda.
Wadjda, start reading.
- "O ye who believe!"
- Louder.
"Believe!"
- "Obey God and..."
- "Obey Allah and obey the Messenger..."
- "..And those charged..."
- "...with authority among you..."
- ".. If ye "branch"..."
- What "branch"? You read it wrong.
- ".. If ye differ in anything..."
- "... among yourselves, refer it to..."
- ".. If ye differ in anything,
refer it to Allah and His Messenger."
That's enough. - Noura, continue.
"O ye who believe! Obey Allah and obey the
Messenger, and those charged with..."
"... authority among you.
If ye differ in anything" -
- "among yourselves, refer it to Allah
and His Messenger..."
So much pounding about a bike
and you can't even ride it.
I want to buy one. I have a plan.
- What is it?
- An antenna for all radio stations.
My uncle will speak
with two famous Qur'an readers
who "get one's heart to melt."
You have not heard mother sing.
She should have her own show.
We'll talk about this later.
- Where's the nail polish?
- I hid it there the other day.
What are you doing here?
Why did you have your hand under her skirt?
Go to my office immediately!
Wadjda, wake up, sweetheart.
Get up, we'll say the morning prayers.
I saw girls cycling on TV.
Why don't you give me the money for a bike?
I know you have money.
I saw it in the drawer.
Girls don't ride bicycles. You will not
be able to have children if you ride.
You don't ride and yet you
can't have sons.
How can you say that?
I almost died when I had you.
Wash before prayers.
Girls!
Who knows where the 'Tajwid'? Page 92.
- Which verse is it?
- Verse 88?
"He who..."
- What kind of 'Tajwid' is it?
- Idgham?
- Moughanna.
- Excellent!
What are you thinking, Wadjda?
This competition is very difficult for me.
I listened to the Qur'an
on the radio yesterday.
"If the learning of the Qur'an is difficult
for you, God will reward you twice."
Good.
- I want you all to look Wadjda as an example -
- Someone who endeavors
and is committed to God and His Prophet.
- You are making progress.
- Thank you, miss.
Sorry.
Wadjda, Miss Hussa wants to talk to you.
Put down the Qur'an.
You will be surprised, but you remind me
of myself at your age.
And look at me now.
Close the door.
You still insist that you did not
do anything behind the school?
We were reading magazines. Ask her.
I'm not sure, miss.
I was far away.
Thanks, Wadjda. You can go back now.
Give this folder to Miss Jamila.
Close the door.
This is a warning. If you sign it
you get to stay in school.
In the name of God, I congratulate you all
for your efforts this semester.
I remind you that the school is
a place of learning and morality.
Listen carefully.
Two students were found in the backyard
where they committed a sin.
The two are...
Faten Khaled and Fatima Abdalla.
To avoid similar occurrences -
- May you no longer bring flowers
to school -
- And you may not give each other
either love letters or fan mail.
And you can't hold hands.
Have you understood?
Then you can go back to your classroom.
Your bags are there.
Don't touch me.
I'd like to have my hair cut like
Lubna Abdul Aziz.
You should have it cut, then.
Your dad loves my long soft hair.
My Mom saw the lights
but said nothing.
Your Mom?
What about your dad?
I think they like your uncle now that he's
been in Radio Qur'an.
- I'm bleeding.
- Whereabouts did you get hurt?
I'm bleeding from the knee.
How many times do I have to say that bikes
are not for girls.
You think you can behave like the boys?
And you? Why did you let her ride?
Come back! Take your bike away!
I'll tell your uncle about you.
Get up.
How do you dare letting a boy come in
the house when no one is home.
If you Dad knew, he'd kill you.
Do you want the men to hear you?
Remove the bread from the oven.
Oh, how nice of you! They are impressed.
You always make me so proud.
Hope it's good enough for you.
Turki, Saleh Ali Abdurahman.
Abulazziz, Rashed, Abdalla.
My Dad....
Interested in Dad's amazing family tree?
You are not included, only the men.
When you're finished
clean up after yourself.
I don't want him to be mad at us again.
WADJDA
Give me the photos.
I said 'give it here."
Stop it. What's going on here?
- Salma has her wedding photos.
- Congratulations. May I see them?
Are these from your wedding?
Is this your husband?
- How old is he?
- Twenty.
Quiet, girls. Don't laugh.
Photos are not allowed in school.
Let's start.
Sura an-Nisa. Page 97.
Wadjda, start reading from verse 115.
- I will try to recite.
- Fine! Close the Qur'an and start.
"And whoever contradicts
and opposes the Messenger"
"after the right path has been shown clearly to
him, and follows other than the believers' way."
"We shall keep him in the
path he has chosen,"
"and burn him in Hell."
"what an evil destination."
Amazing! But you have to work on
your reading and Tajwid - recitation.
If you are aiming to win
you must recite as Salma.
Salma, read verse 115 again.
"And whoever contradicts
and opposes the Messenger"
"after the right path has been shown
clearly to him, and follows other
than the believers' way."
"We shall keep him in the
path he has chosen,"
"and burn him in Hell.
What an evil destination."
"Verily! Allah forgives not (the sin of)
setting up partners in worship with Him"
"but He forgives whom he pleases
sins other than that"
"and whoever sets up partners
in worship with Allah,"
"has indeed strayed far away."
Excellent.
- Are you mad at me now?
- I have homework to do.
Wait a minute. I brought you a cask.
Such as like on TV.
Want to ride a little? Behind the tent.
We have a while before people come.
Abdalla, look!
The shopkeeper told Khalid and
his father that the bike is reserved.
He keeps it safe for me.
The correct answer.
Choose the correct answer.
What are sabianerna?
I know the answer.
The correct answer.
Finally!
You've never listened to me.
Why should I listen to you?
Get dressed, we're going out.
Don't let the Qur'an be left open.
The devil can spit on it.
Will you be Working with Leila? Cool lab
coats, as in "The Matrix," but whites.
Quiet, I only want to give her something.
Wadjda!
Hello and welcome.
Leila, why do you not hide your face?
Never mind!
Let me get an application form for you.
Welcome!
- How are you?
- Fine, thank you.
It's a great job and there are only
a few places left. You should...
Leila, stop. I just wanted to say hi.
I'll call you later, you are busy.
- Take care.
- Where are you going?
Take care.
- I thought you were going to work with Leila.
- Stop it.
"Among His signs is that He created for you
wives of your own kind.."
- "..That ye may dwell in tranquility with them."
- No honey, try this. Listen.
"... and He has put love
and mercy between you."
" In that there are signs
for those who reflect."
I'm so shy.
I can not recite for everyone.
You, shy? If only it were true.
Look, there's Daddy!
- Where?
- There! There!
Do you love him?
- Who? Your father?
- No, the boy next door.
I don't think it's me
who is in love with the boy next door.
That's not funny.
You didn't answer. Do you love him?
I was in school
when he asked for my hand.
All the girls went crazy when they saw
his photograph. They were so jealous.
He is the first man in my life.
Hopefully also the last.
You are beautiful. He will fall in love with you
all over again when he sees you in that red dress.
Don't worry. He will never take
a new wife and break my heart.
Let us practice for tomorrow's competition.
The words should come from the heart. Ignore
those around you and recite from the heart.
I'd like to be there tomorrow
when you win.
But I'll have to commute
to the end of the world again.
Generosity?
Wrong answer.
Next.
What does "sadakatouhonn"?
- Wedding gift?
- Right.
Salma.
What is "Al-Furkan"?
- Qur'an?
- Right.
Wadjda.
What does "da'ab"?
Custom.
Right.
Noura.
What does "zaygh"?
Weakness.
Right.
Next.
What does "hawban kabiran"?
I'm sorry, Yasmin.
Go back to your seat.
What does "hawban kabiran"?
Something big?
Wrong. Go back to your seat.
- What does "hawban kabiran"?
- Great injustice.
Right.
"If we had ordered them this:
"'Kill yourselves'
"or get out of your homes '
"They have not done,
except a few of them."
"If they had done what
they exhorted..."
"This is the Scripture whereof
there is no doubt."
"This is a guide for the righteous,"
"who believe in the unseen"
"and do prayer"
"and spend,
what We have given them."
"Those who..."
Thank you, Salma. God bless you.
Wadjda.
Verse 7, "Sur'at Al-Baqarah" Starting on
"God has sealed their hearts..."
"God has sealed their.."
"God has sealed their hearts and
their ears and covered over their eyes."
" A severe punishment awaits them."
'We believe in God ' " -
- "And the Last Day
though they do not believe."
"They are trying to deceive God
and the believers."
" But they deceive none but
themselves and do not realize it."
" Their hearts are sick and
God lets their disease getting worse" -
" and a painful punishment awaits them
for their constant lies."
"When they are urged not to sow discord
on Earth, they answer."
"We just want to improve and make amends."
"No, it is they who create discord
and spreads depravation."
"But they do not realize."
It was excellent, Wadjda.
God bless you.
Will you say your prayer next to us?
- Congratulations.
- The winner is yet to be declared.
You won. You're their favorite.
Their votes will be unanimous.
Wadjda, come up!
We kept a place for you in the front row.
Coward.
Fall in line.
Stand closer together.
Leave no room for the devil.
God is great.
God hears the prayer of thanks.
Quiet, girls. Silence!
Finalists in the competition.
Noura Saleh, Salma Abdul Aziz
and Wadjda Al Saffan.
And now... the third prize goes to...
Salma Abdul Aziz.
Congratulations.
Winner of the second prize is....
Noura Saleh.
Congratulations, Noura.
Wadjda, the first prize goes to you.
You won thanks to your dedication and the
fact that you have been so diligent.
I hope everyone here
today learn from your example.
Congratulations.
And what do you intend to use
prize money for?
I want to buy a bike at the store
down the street.
What did you say?
I want to buy a bike, but without training
wheels because I can ride a bike.
Wouldn't it be better to donate the money
for our brothers in Palestine?
A bike is not for girls.
Especially not for the benefit of girls
who are afraid of their honor.
I'm sure your family will not allow it.
The money will be donated in your name and
May God reward you for the good work.
Now go back to your place.
That's all girls. You can go now.
So nothing's changed after all.
Do you think your behaviour
will go unnoticed?
Your silly attitude
will haunt you forever.
You mean like your "fancy" thief?
Didn't you win? Where is the money?
In Palestine.
- I'll give you my bike.
- How can race with one bike?
Wadjda....
You know I want to marry you
when we grow up, right?
So. You're finally home.
- What's with the new haircut?
- Your mother does not answer my calls.
Can I see?
You won? I don't think that's true.
You are my little darling.
Why are you crying? You won after all.
Wait a second.
- Hello?
Are you ready?
I'm so proud of you,
my little heroine.
I have tried to call your mom all day.
When she comes home,
tell her I love her.
Hello? Hello, Aunt Leila.
No, I don't know where she is.
Yes, she is usually home by this time.
Okay, I'll tell her.
Goodbye.
Congratulations, I heard the news.
They said you won.
I couldn't believe it.
When you go after something,
no one can stop you.
- I did not get the money.
- Why did you say you wanted to buy the bike?
Anyway, you don't need them or their money.
What happened at grandma's? I thought
the marriage was not until next month?
It was not your uncle's wedding.
It's okay. He has made his decision.
It's just you and me now.
Let's buy the red dress
and go fetch Dad.
The dress is no longer needed.
Besides, I already spent the money.
I hope it is right.
The shopkeeper had held it for
a brave little girl.
I want you to be the happiest person.
You're all I have left in this world.
- Abdalla.
- Goal!
Catch me if you can.