filmeuy.com
Free Watch Online & Download Movies
"eva knew this might be
The last time
She saw him...
The last time she saw
The man
Who had stolen her heart."
[sighs]
Oh, eva,
You're killing me.
[phone buzzes]
[♪♪]
Ah! Gabriel august.
I've already
Pre-ordered my copy.
I know! I set aside
That whole weekend
Just to read it.
I'm almost as excited
About the new book
As i am about
Seeing his face.
I bet
He's so handsome.
[they sigh]
I can't do it.
I can't let the world know
That i'm gabriel august.
It's part of
The deal, liam.
You knew that
When you signed.
Yeah, but i never thought
The first book
Would actually be
Successful.
[laughs] i did!
Didn't i tell you it
Would be a best-seller?
I just assumed you were
Being nice.
I've known you
Since you were born.
I don't need to make nice.
You can't stay
Anonymous forever.
Readers form connections
With the books they love.
They want a relationship
With the author.
You're a success, liam!
Why can't you embrace it?
The manuscript
For your next book is due,
And i haven't seen
Any chapters.
Oh...
I've written plenty of
Chapters,
And then...
Promptly
Thrown them in the trash.
Well,
You are gonna have to find
The inspiration somewhere,
Because you still owe
Harris-kingsfield two books.
You're sure there's no way
We can just get 'em
To postpone the whole
Gabriel august reveal?
It's been almost impossible
Holding them off this long.
It's time.
Why don't you go
Up to the cabin
In portland
For a couple of weeks?
And i'll see if i can
Get the reveal moved out
There.
You wrote first star of
Evening
There in less than a month.
I wrote it as a joke.
You wrote it because
Katherine broke your heart.
Portland has always been
A great place
For you to get
Your center again.
Just like it was
For your parents.
I remember when
Your mom told me
They were buying
A place up there.
I thought they were crazy.
So far from everything.
But it became
Their little hideaway.
Get out of town for a while.
Clear your head.
And get ready for
The best chapter of your
Life.
The next one
Is gonna be a great one.
[announcement]: this will
Serve
As the final boarding call
For flight 782 to denver,
And continuing on
To portland.
[breathless woman]:
I'm here!
-welcome aboard.
-sorry.
[attendant]: here,
I'll take your bag.
[woman]: that cab driver
Dropped
Me off at the wrong
Terminal.
I can barely walk in heels,
Much less run.
[attendant]: 1-c,
Right up here in first
Class.
[woman]: are you sure?
[attendant]:
Your upgrade went through.
[woman]: you're kidding.
That never happens.
[attendant]:
Must be your lucky day.
[woman]: thank you.
-hi.
-hello.
[relieved sigh]
First class.
I feel so special.
They'll even bring you
A glass of champagne,
If you want.
No. No.
I... I shouldn't.
Well, maybe just one.
But i have
Lots of work to do,
So i won't--
Don't worry,
I won't be talking your
Ear off the whole time.
Do you live
In new york?
No, i'm heading home.
Portland.
I was just in the city
For a couple of job
Interviews.
Ah. I hope they went well.
We'll see.
Everybody was really nice.
Maybe too nice.
I... It's just so hard to
Know
What people are really
Thinking.
I wish they would just
Say what they mean.
Things would be
So much easier that way.
Not always.
Sometimes the truth hurts.
Hurts a lot less than lies.
Sounds like the voice
Of experience talking.
That obvious?
[chuckles]
Champagne?
Two.
Definitely.
To a great flight.
With lots of
Fabulous legroom.
[clink]
[♪♪]
You seem very focused.
Is it good?
It wants to be.
If that makes any sense.
The new
Gabriel august?
Thought that book
Wasn't out.
Mm. I got
An advance copy.
You read
Gabriel august?
[laughs]
No, but
I've heard of him.
Yeah, you don't...
You don't really seem
Like his typical
Demographic.
So you don't like this one?
No. I... I do.
It's just his first book,
First star of evening,
Was so good.
Really?
I-- i think the first novel
Was such a success
Because it was just so
Honest.
You really felt like
You knew those characters.
Sounds like
I should give it a read.
Absolutely.
Just... Maybe skip this one.
It's a little
Disappointing.
It doesn't feel real.
It's like...
He took the first book
And stuck it in a blender
And mixed it up and
Put a new title on it.
Oh! That's harsh.
I guess.
I hate to see such potential
Go to waste.
Have you heard about this?
He has this whole
Marketing gimmick.
He's very mysterious.
It's a little ridiculous.
You think it's a gimmick?
What else could it be?
I'm sure he has his reasons.
Whatever it is,
I guess it's working,
Because along with
Every other woman in
America,
I am actually curious
To find out who he really
Is.
[announcement]:
Ladies and gentlemen,
The captain has begun
Our descent into portland,
And we'll be landing
Shortly.
[sighs]
Well...
This has ruined me.
I don't think
I can go back to coach.
I'm going to finish.
[airport bustling]
Hey!
Hey there.
You look like
You're in a hurry.
Staff meeting at work.
I'm barely gonna make it.
Do you want me
To help you with your bag?
Looks like you're the one
That could use the help.
Oh...
Sorry. I gotta run.
It was really nice
Meeting you.
Yeah. You too.
[♪♪]
It's not usually
So jammed up
At the taxi line.
Just my luck.
My boss'll kill me
If i'm late again.
I'm happy
To give you a lift.
My mom always told me
Never to accept
Rides in limos
From strangers
I met on airplanes.
Your mom gave you
Very specific advice.
Come on. It's got just
As much legroom as first
Class.
We can even
Split the tip,
If that makes you feel
Better.
I don't even
Know your name.
Liam.
Sophie.
Well, i guess
We aren't strangers anymore.
[♪♪]
So...
You said
You live in new york?
Mostly.
I like spending time
In portland, though.
I love it here.
What do you do?
Um...
Freelance
Project consulting.
So, do you have
Any plans for tonight?
Uh... [laughs]
Actually, i do.
My two best friends have
Their engagement party.
Well, they were
Just friends for years.
This whole falling-in-love
Thing
Has kind of came out of
Nowhere.
It's taken
A little getting used to.
But it's a good thing?
It's a great thing!
[horn honks]
Looks like the street's
Blocked ahead.
I can't be any later.
The office is only
A couple of blocks away.
I-i think i'm gonna
Hoof it from here.
Oh. Right, okay.
Well, if you ever w...
Right! We were
Gonna split the tip.
Oh, stop. Stop, stop.
Stop.
Okay, my friends
Are never gonna believe
That i got to fly in first
Class
And ride in a limo
On the same day.
Do you mind if i take a
Picture?
Uh, no. Of course not.
[snap]
Thanks.
Wait. My turn.
[snap]
[♪♪]
Well...
Bye, i guess.
Thank you.
Happy to help.
-bye.
[♪♪]
I'll be right back.
How was new york?
Actually, pretty good.
The job interviews
Went well?
A couple of the magazines
Were interested.
I'm just not sure
I want to move to new york.
You may not have a choice.
I don't know how long
This paper's gonna survive.
Really? What's going on?
Berkmann fired
Four more staffers
While you were gone.
He keeps getting worse
Instead of better.
[♪♪]
[keys clicking]
Sophie, who are you?
He's cute!
Not as cute as you,
Of course,
But he's definitely hot.
Who is he?
We sat next to each other
On the plane,
And then he ended up
Giving me a ride.
In a limo.
I can't believe
You rode in a car
With a guy
You just met.
He was in first class.
How dangerous could he be?
So when are you
Gonna see him again?
It wasn't like that.
I don't even
Have his number.
Why not?
Are you not into
Hot guys anymore?
Okay.
It's nice if a guy
Isn't too hard on the eyes,
But that kind of thing
Being really important?
Never again.
I wonder why
Was he in a limo.
You think he's famous,
Or just rich?
Neither.
He was some kind
Of consultant.
He's...he's just
A regular guy.
Hey, man.
You want to play
Man coverage on the
Outside?
Fine by me!
Just don't be surprised
If i shred the secondary.
Harris?
You mind changing
That channel?
[♪♪]
Heads up, st. Louis!
You're next!
Come next sunday,
We own you.
There we go, eh, baby?
[harris]: good riddance.
You were too good
For that low-life anyway.
You okay?
Sure.
I love seeing my ex
On tv screens
Everywhere i go.
I also love
Having the whole world know
That he cheated on me.
But the thing
That's so annoying
Is that i had no idea.
I mean,
How could i have had no
Clue?
He was a sneaky rat,
That's why.
So what am i supposed to do?
Just assume that every guy
I meet is lying to me?
Not every guy,
Just most of them.
You just gotta wait till
The right one comes along.
Trust me, you'll meet
Someone much better.
Maybe
She already has.
"limo guy"
Sounds interesting.
Honey, that--
That's a terrible idea.
She's just been
Through a big break-up,
A public break-up.
She should just
Take her time.
No! No way.
Sophie needs to get
Right back out there
And start dating.
-no, she doesn't.
-yes, she does.
Okay. Will you two stop?
I will be fine.
I would've preferred
Not to have
The whole world read
About my love life
On practically every
Gossip website, but...
That's what you get
When you date a famous
Person.
I promise you, though,
I'm totally fine.
"totally fine"?
Well...
I'm getting there.
It's only been a few days.
I'm really starting
To get into it, though,
Get that old
"gabriel august" engine
Revved up
And racing again.
So it's going well?
Absolutely. Portland
Was a great idea.
Good.
I was starting
To worry about you.
You haven't written a thing,
Have you?
Why do you think that?
Because you sound
Way too relaxed.
Maybe you should
Shake things up a little,
Go out with friends,
Or on a date or something.
Well, i did meet a nice
Woman
On the plane.
Perfect!
Call her up.
I don't know her last name,
And i have no idea
Where to find her.
Can't ever just do anything
The easy way, can you?
Oh!
I changed
The gabriel august reveal
To jasper's bookloft
Out there in portland,
So you won't have to fly
Back to new york for it.
So this is really happening?
It'll be liam and jackie,
Just like always.
But i'll be the one up there
In front of all those
People.
I know
It's gonna be hard
For you to let go of
This gabriel august
Mystique,
But you can't keep
Leading two lives like this.
This is a good thing.
Have i ever steered
You wrong before?
Is that a trick question?
I'll call you
When i get out there,
And you can show me
Your town, mr. Portland.
Is it a date?
Yeah. It's a date.
-bye.
Well,
As you've probably guessed,
We got our new numbers back,
And they're not pretty.
Circulation is down 23%
From the same time last
Year.
So, going forward,
I have it from on high
That we need to spice things
Up.
I need your pieces
To jump off the page.
Get noticed.
If you want to do
A feel-good fluff piece
On a pee-wee baseball team,
Scrap it and find out
When the trail blazers
Are firing their coach.
They want us to make noise,
Get retweeted or facebooked,
Or whatever
The kids are doing these
Days.
Books, movies,
Restaurant reviews--
Nothing's just "okay"
Anymore.
They're either fantastic
Or the worst thing
You've ever seen.
I'm talking extreme
Opinions.
But you don't want us
To write reviews
We don't believe in, do you?
Well, if that's what it
Takes,
Then yeah.
It's how we generate
Web hits and subscriptions.
Look, i don't love it,
But it's the hand we're
Dealt.
All right, i'll have
New assignments
For all of you in a few.
Make me proud.
Sophie.
Got something for you
That might be interesting.
After your little speech,
I'm almost afraid to ask.
That review you're doing
On gabriel august's
New book?
I'm not gonna turn it
Into a hatchet piece
Just to get more tweets.
I've got something
Even better.
I just found out that
Jasper's is hosting
Gabriel august's
Little coming-out party
Tomorrow night,
Right here in portland.
I want you to cover it.
We'll run it with the
Review.
Wait. He's revealing
His true identity here?
Why portland?
It's your job to find out.
[♪♪]
[hushed conversation]
Deep breaths.
This is a good thing.
Once this is over,
You can stop
Leading two lives.
I'll never just
Be liam bradley.
All everyone
Will care about
Is gabriel august.
That's who i'll be from now
On.
It's going to be okay.
I promise.
And it's gonna feel so good
To finally get this
Off your chest.
Okay, i think it's time.
We don't want to
Keep them waiting.
I'm gonna go
And make the introduction.
You wait here,
I point to you,
And that's it...
And the world
Meets gabriel august
For the first time.
Okay. I'm as ready as i can
Be.
You're gonna be great.
They're gonna love you.
You should take
That seat in the front.
Got it.
[jackie]:
If i can have your
Attention?
I think you're all
About as excited
To be here tonight
As i am.
With millions of books
Sold worldwide
Over the last three years,
Gabriel august has touched
All our hearts.
He has made us fall in love,
And he has made us cry.
It's my pleasure
To introduce to you
The man behind
These incredible stories.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Please allow me to introduce
You all
To the writer
You've come to know
As gabriel august.
[applause]
[applause tapers off]
I had a feeling
I might find you here.
This was always
Your favorite spot to write.
I can't fool you, can i?
No.
And you'd best remember
That.
Liam, what
Were you thinking?
I was standing there
Like an idiot,
Pointing at no one.
I'm really sorry.
I just... I panicked.
Your publisher
Is furious.
They're threatening
To release your name and
Information themselves.
Well, they can't
Do that!
Well, they won't, not yet.
I told them if they did,
We'd sue them,
And we'd make
A big, ugly public
Spectacle.
You must not be
Very popular over there.
It's not my job
To be popular.
It's my job to look
After my clients,
Even the ones
That make me crazy.
More bad news.
Mm.
One of the first reviews
For by the lighthouse.
It's pretty
Disappointing.
"tepid attempts
At conveying human
Emotion..."
-it's her!
-who?
Sophie. The girl from
The plane and limo ride.
That's why she was
At the bookstore!
To write about
Gabriel august.
-this is incredible.
Incredible?
I'd hate to hear
What you think a bad
Review looks like.
I gotta go!
We'll talk soon.
Liam!
I gotta find her.
We still have to talk about
Rescheduling your reveal!
I'll call you later!
Li-- [frustrated sigh]
[♪♪]
Sorry.
Liam?
Sophie!
Sorry. That--
That was totally my fault.
No, no. It was all me.
They need to pass a "no
Texting
While walking" bill,
Like new york.
They have those there?
Right.
So where're you heading
In such a rush?
Home.
I just got off work.
I write book reviews
For the portland record.
Really?
That sounds interesting.
Look, i realize we just met,
You know, again,
But maybe you'd like
To grab a bite to eat
Sometime?
I--
That's really nice,
But i have a lot
Of work to do.
Aw, come on!
You eat, i eat.
Let's eat
At the same table.
Persistent,
Aren't you?
Well, i'm usually not,
But it seems like
This might be worth it.
One meal couldn't
Hurt, right?
I suppose not.
I think
I'll take that as a yes.
[♪♪]
[quiet shock]: no way....
So you just ran into
Him on the street?
That's, like, fate.
Okay, don't
Get carried away.
But here's
The interesting part.
His parents
Are devon hillman
And helen bradley.
The movie stars?
You're kidding!
-no.
-are you sure?
I saw a picture
Of him with them.
Well, that's why he rides
In limos and flies first
Class.
His parents were
Celebrities.
He was just 19 when
They died in that plane
Crash.
That was so sad.
It was awful.
Do you think it's weird
That he didn't mention it?
To hide something
So important?
You hardly know him.
Why would he tell you
The most traumatic
Story of his life
When you guys haven't even
Been on a date yet?
[groans] i know.
You're right.
I mean, i'm just...
You're being paranoid,
That's what.
Not all guys are hiding
Things like james.
You need to
Give liam a chance.
Oh!
Who's this liam?
The guy that sophie's
Going on a date with.
It-- it's not a date,
It's just dinner.
Why are you holding back?
You either like him,
Or you don't.
I-i do like him.
I just...
I wish i knew him better.
Hello!
That's what a date's for.
To get to know somebody.
I thought i knew james.
I never liked that one.
That's right.
You didn't.
You guys knew
There was something wrong
Before i did.
That's how i'll know--
I'll introduce him to you,
And you can tell me
What you think.
You want us
To crash your date?
Brilliant, right?
Yeah. Let me
Check him out first.
Thank you.
[doorbell chimes]
Just because you don't
Answer the phone
Doesn't mean
I'm gonna go away.
I honestly was not
Trying to avoid you.
Okay, maybe i was, but not
For the reason you think.
I was actually writing
Today.
That's great.
Well,
It wasn't great,
But it was
Something, anyway.
The words,
They are coming.
I don't like them
Once they're on the page.
So kind of less of
A writer's block issue,
And more of
A heart-not-being-in-it
Issue?
And don't you look dapper?
Yeah.
I found her. Sophie.
We're going to dinner.
You really like this girl,
Don't you?
I haven't seen you
Like this in ages.
Oh...
You know, i felt something
When i met her.
Something strange.
She's not like other women.
She's interesting
And...
And unique.
And she tells it
Like it is, right?
How did you know that?
I know you pretty well
After all these years,
Honey.
I feel nervous around her,
But it's a good nervous.
Yeah, i'd be
A bit nervous, too,
If i was going out with
Somebody
Who hated my book so much.
Ah. It really
Hasn't come up yet.
I'm going to let you get
Ready for your date, liam,
But please be careful.
I worry enough
About your ability
To lead
One double life.
I don't think you have
The heart for a second.
[♪♪]
[doorbell chimes]
Hi.
Hi. These are for you.
Thank you.
They're beautiful.
Come on in.
Hi!
Um, hello.
Uh, it was
The strangest thing.
I was getting ready, and--
Drew and i
Were in the neighborhood
And wanted to return a book
To sophie.
This one.
[chuckles]
Where are my manners?
Um, drew and nina,
This is liam.
No limo tonight?
Uh, i have a car here
In town.
So you have a place here
And a place in new york?
You don't really
See that very often.
Exactly what kind of
Consulting do you do?
Drew, you don't need
To interrogate
Poor liam here.
(sotto)
I thought that's what
I was supposed to do?
How about
A glass of wine?
Wine sounds wonderful!
And it gives us
The opportunity
To get to know
A little bit more
About liam here.
Great!
So how long were
You in guayana?
I did the full
Two-year volunteer rotation.
It's really
An amazing country.
That must've been
Tough, though.
Volunteering was
The hardest thing i ever
Did,
But i wouldn't trade it
For anything.
Wow.
You're full of surprises.
Well, this has
Been fun.
We should all go out
When we have more time.
Absolutely. And drew,
I'm going to hold you
To your offer
To play hoops.
I'm no lebron james,
But maybe a dwayne wade.
All right,
But i will warn you--
Once i lace up,
I'm more like 6'6" with
A 40-inch vertical, so.
[laughs]
Have fun
Tonight, kids.
Bye!
And thanks for, um,
Bringing the book back.
I think they liked you.
Well, that's great,
But they're not the ones
I'm trying to impress.
I like you too.
Now, that's what
I like to hear.
[laughs]
You ready for dinner?
I have the perfect place.
I was surprised.
Nina and drew and i
Have been friends forever.
So what made them
Start to date?
Actually, i think
They'd been in love
For years,
But they were both
Just so afraid
Of ruining
The friendship
That they never
Gave it a chance.
How's the cobbler?
Mm! Wonderful, harris.
As always.
Everything is delicious.
You mean that,
Or are you just saying
What you think i want to
Hear?
No, it was really good.
[phone rings]
Oh. Sorry.
I've got to
Take this. Work.
[♪♪]
So, liam...
You ever been married?
Um, no.
Why not?
Something wrong with you?
[chuckles, then stops]
So no alarm bells
Went off for either of you?
We loved him.
Even drew,
Who was prepared to duke it
Out
With him beforehand.
How's dinner going?
We're having a nice time.
But he still hasn't
Mentioned his parents,
And he keeps
Changing the subject
Every time
I bring up his work.
Give him time.
How's it going with harris?
It doesn't look good.
Maybe i shouldn't
Have left him alone.
Well, let me know how it
Goes,
'Cause he seems really
Great.
Bye.
That's her recipe
For peach cobbler
You're eating.
It's the best
I've ever tasted.
Honestly.
Am i interrupting?
Not at all!
Come. Sit.
I was just
Telling liam here
The story of lola
And why i named the
Restaurant
After her.
I thought you didn't like
To talk about that.
Well, the story's
Not for everyone,
But liam here
Seemed to understand.
I'm sorry
You lost her so soon.
Well, it's better
To have loved and lost
And all that, right?
I like to think
She's here with me every
Day.
Nice to meet you, liam.
You too.
The next time,
You've got to try
The chocolate mousse.
It's not to be missed.
Can't wait.
What?
Wow.
He must really like you
To open up about lola.
Is that a good thing?
Yes.
It's...a great thing.
[creek trickling]
Harris actually
Liked him?
Loved him.
Sounds like he passed
Your little test, right?
With flying colors.
But he still won't
Talk about his work.
Or his family.
It's like
He's an open book
About some things,
And then completely
Mysterious about others.
It sounds like
Problem isn't him,
It's you.
What are you
Talking about?
I get that you have
Trust issues.
Who wouldn't
In your position?
But you need
To be careful
Not to project
Your stuff onto liam.
It's not fair.
Okay, well, what about
Just-- just one more test?
I felt so much better
After he met
You guys last night
And you liked him.
Sophie.
Okay, just hear me out.
I want to see him at work,
Just find out what
This whole consulting thing
Is all about.
I mean,
What could it hurt?
Come on!
[♪♪]
[phone rings]
Can't talk now.
Finally in the zone.
Thrilled to hear it,
But we still need to meet
To go over the details
Of the rescheduled reveal.
Today's not good.
So, today at 1:00,
At the river village
Restaurant,
I've booked
A lovely outdoor table.
You can walk over
From the marina.
Can't we do this
Later this week?
See you at one.
[beep]
[♪♪]
[phone ringing]
Hey!
I was going to call you,
But didn't want to
Bother you at work.
I was worried about
The same thing.
I'm not interrupting,
Am i?
Not at all.
Really enjoyed last night.
Me too. I--
[ship's bell clangs]
What was that?
Are you--
Are you at the marina?
Uh, yeah.
I'm, uh, meeting a client at
River village restaurant at
One,
A business meeting.
A client?
Um, that's good.
Maybe we can figure out
A time to see
Each other again.
Yeah. I'd like that.
Um, i've got to go.
Bye.
[♪♪]
So i've rescheduled
The reveal
For friday at six,
And i will handcuff you
To me if i have to.
It's such
Terrible timing.
Sophie and i
Are just starting
To get to know
Each other.
You haven't told her,
Have you?
Once she finds out
I'm gabriel august,
That's all i'll be to her.
That's all i'll be
To everybody.
[jackie]:
How can you know that,
If you don't trust her
Enough
To tell her the truth?
Well, you know how
It was with my parents.
People treated them
Differently
Because they were stars.
Hi.
Oh, no.
This is not happening.
It's her.
She's pretty!
Hey.
Sophie.
This is a surprise.
I-i was, um...
Covering a story
Just around the corner,
And remembered you saying
You were having lunch here,
So--
So you just stopped by?
That's weird, isn't it?
It was all very spontaneous.
Um...
I'll leave you to your
Lunch.
-you're jackie billicks.
-yes.
The literary agent.
Oh, um, i have to say,
I'm not used to being
Recognized
Outside of new york.
I saw you speak in 2011
At the brooklyn
Publishing symposium.
You were so inspiring.
Jackie,
This is
Sophie atkinson.
It's wonderful
To meet you, sophie.
I actually write book
Reviews
For the portland record,
And i probably owe you
And gabriel august
My review
Wasn't very favorable.
No apology needed.
You were
Just doing your job.
I can't believe
You didn't tell me
You knew gabriel
August's agent.
Well, it's great to meet
You.
I'll let you two talk.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
This is just
A social call anyway.
Please join us. Please.
Oh...
Thank you.
I keep telling gabriel
That he'll feel better
If he tells the world
Who he is,
But men, you know?
So stubborn.
But-- but it is
Really happening?
Oh, yeah. Next friday.
If i have to drag him
Kicking and screaming.
[sophie laughs]
Okay.
At the risk of
Sounding like a teenager,
What is he like?
[laughs]
Well, he's, uh, smart.
Quite smart,
When he wants to be.
He is genuinely talented,
He's very handsome.
He's also obstinate,
He's private to a fault,
And sometimes he exhibits
The same amount of
Judgment as my beagle.
[both laughing]
I felt bad,
Writing
The review i did,
But the truth is,
I really want his next book
To be great, like the first
One,
And maybe not having secrets
Will help.
Maybe his next book
Will be his masterpiece.
I hope so, sophie.
Well, i've got a deadline
That needs some love.
Jackie, i'm so glad
We got the chance to talk.
Same here!
And next time
You're in new york,
Give me a jingle,
We'll have lunch.
I would love that.
I will see you later?
I can't wait.
I'll call you.
Napkin...
[chuckling]
Wow...
Thanks for that, jackie.
You need to tell her,
Before this--
Whatever
This is between you two--
Goes any further.
Well, it's easier said
Than done.
I never said
It was gonna be easy.
It's so beautiful
Down here.
I never think
To do this.
I come here every sunset.
Helps clear my head.
It's one of my favorite
Things
About the city.
Why portland?
I have a feeling
You could be
Just about anywhere
Right now.
Oh, yeah? Well, i could
Ask you the same thing.
Portland's my home.
The truth?
The truth.
I spent some time here
As a kid.
Always loved it.
What?
Okay. I'm really bad at
This,
But i have
A confession to make.
Oh. Good confession
Or bad confession?
I actually know
Who you really are.
Oh. I see.
You're not mad at me?
Why would i be mad?
Because i didn't
Tell you the truth.
You're entitled
To your privacy.
I imagine growing up
With famous parents
Must have been hard.
You meant my parents.
Right.
Yeah, it was
Complicated.
Life in the spotlight
Can be rough.
Believe me, i know.
Yeah?
I had a bad experience
Dating a famous person.
Actually, we were engaged.
It ended a few months ago.
Engaged?
I probably should've
Mentioned it earlier.
No, not at all.
Were you okay?
It was hard at first,
But i'm much better
The last few days.
I'm glad
To hear that.
One of the magazines
I interviewed at
In new york
Asked me to come
Work for them.
That's a big change!
Well, i may not
Have a choice.
It seems like the daily's
Days are numbered.
Aw, it sounds like
A great opportunity.
I was thinking of it
More as a huge disaster.
I just mean, you know,
It gives you
A chance to figure out
What it is you
Really want to do.
Maybe make a change,
If you want.
Sometimes i'd give anything
To just start over.
This is me.
You know...
You're really easy
To talk to.
Not always, but...
It's easy with you.
[♪♪]
Thank you.
For what?
I don't know...
Just being liam bradley.
[♪♪]
John, if you have time,
I'd love to meet.
I have some ideas
About a website,
And i need some tech advice.
Tuesday's perfect!
See you then.
[indistinct exchange]
You should come.
It's so much fun.
I'm afraid i'm not
Much of a dancer.
Mm, i'll give you
A few pointers.
You'll be an expert
By the end of the night.
Remember, 8:30.
It's called frankfurt,
Over on burnside.
Hope to see you there.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
[♪♪]
Hey!
Oh, hi!
You just missed
This totally gorgeous guy.
Did i?
I think he liked me,
But who knows?
It's so hard to tell
Sometimes.
But i asked him out!
Do you think
That was too forward?
I don't know.
What did he say?
I didn't give him
A chance to say anything.
I hate being rejected.
Guess i'll find out
Tonight, huh?
Come on. Berkmann'll kill us
If we're late.
[♪♪]
[phone starts ringing]
Uh, i...
Wasn't sure
If you would call tonight.
I stopped by
Your office earlier.
I thought you might want
To grab lunch.
Oh yeah?
Um, sorry i missed you.
[car horn honks
Over phone]
It sounds like
You're in the car.
Are you going
Somewhere special tonight?
Uh, no.
Just clearing my head.
I'm actually way behind
On this project.
I'll probably spend
Most of the night working.
Working?
That doesn't sound very fun.
Yeah, not looking forward
To it.
But we're still on
For tomorrow, right?
I guess.
If you still want to.
Of course i do.
I'll see you then, okay?
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
[♪♪]
[music filtering out from
Club]
[♪♪]
[mutters to self]:
Working all night, huh?
He could've just told me.
Sophie?
Oh.
You're not...
This isn't--
This is my friend peter.
What are you doing here?
Good question.
[♪♪]
I felt like
The world's biggest jerk.
I should've trusted liam.
You're not the world's
Biggest jerk.
I mean, there have to be
At least two bigger ones.
You--
You were completely right.
This was just about
Me being scared.
Hey!
Don't beat yourself up
Too much.
Nobody blames you for being
Careful about who you date.
But eventually you need
To take a leap of faith
And jump back in.
And that's exactly
What i'm gonna do.
I'm seeing liam tonight,
I'm just going to come clean
About everything
And tell him
The truth.
You think
That's a good idea?
What kind of relationship
Can i hope to have
If it starts out
Being dishonest?
Are you sure
This doesn't fall into
The "what-he-doesn't-know-
Won't-hurt-him" category?
We just don't want to see
You
Get hurt again.
I need to do this.
You have to
Tell her the truth.
I am tonight.
How are you
Going to do it?
I'm taking her
To the cabin.
I'll tell her there.
I just hope she
Doesn't freak out.
I mean, if she thinks
I've been lying to her
This whole time--
Stop.
Liam, you're doing
The right thing.
Look at
The bright side.
This will make your big
Reveal a whole lot easier,
One way or another.
And i'm proud of you
For doing that too.
Not like
I have much choice.
Okay. Hugs.
Like the good old days.
Mm.
I'll let you know
How it goes.
Yeah. I'll be
Thinking of you, kiddo.
Good luck.
It's so cozy.
Makes me
Want to curl up
With a good book
And a glass of wine.
I always came here
With my parents.
Do you have
One of those spots
Where you go to
And you just feel safe?
Forest park.
There's this old wooden
Bridge
Surrounded by trees.
When i get stressed,
I just stand there
And listen to the water,
And all the troubles
Melt away.
It's a magical place.
It sounds wonderful.
Everybody needs
Some place to escape to.
Exactly.
That's what it's like
For me out here.
Dinner awaits.
It's beautiful!
I didn't realize
You were such a romantic.
Ah, i didn't either.
This is delicious.
Mm. I can't cook
To save my life,
But i am fantastic
At ordering well.
Uh, look, there's
Something important
I need to tell you,
But i'm not really
Sure how to say it.
More couscous?
I'm fine.
Right.
Uh, all right, uh...
The thing is,
When we first met,
I didn't think things
Would progress so far.
Liam, wait.
Before
You say anything,
I... I have to
Tell you something.
I...
Haven't been totally
Honest with you.
You haven't?
Remember how i told you
I recently went
Through a bad break-up?
You're getting back
Together with him.
What?
No!
Absolutely not.
Never. I just...
The whole thing
Actually hit me
A lot harder
Than i admitted.
He was a professional
Athlete,
And the break-up
Was very public,
And...
Pretty humiliating,
Honestly.
My terrible love life
Went viral.
That must've been awful.
Yeah.
A word of advice--
Never date
A famous person.
I won't make
That mistake again.
The worst part,
Though, was that...
This man that
I thought i loved
Ended up being someone
Completely different
Than i thought he was.
I guess i just lost
My ability to trust men.
And so when i met you,
I was like,
"wow, too good
To be true."
And so i've kind of been
Giving you little tests
Just to prove
That you aren't...
Too good to be true.
Tests?
Yeah.
This is embarrassing.
I... My friends
Interrogating you.
Me dropping by
During your lunch
With your client.
I kind of arranged
Those things
Just to help myself
Make sure
That this was real.
Oh! And the girl
You met
In front of
My office, tabitha,
We actually
Work together,
And i overheard her
Asking you out.
You're the only woman
I wanted to go out with.
I know that now.
And i should've
Trusted it
From the beginning.
I'm so sorry, liam.
I don't know
What else to say.
So that's it?
That's what you haven't
Been honest about?
You hate me,
Don't you?
Sophie,
I don't hate you.
I'm falling in love
With you.
Okay.
That went better
Than i thought it would.
[♪♪]
I feel so much better
Having that out in the open.
I've been so nervous all
Night.
There was something
You wanted to say to me.
What? Oh. Oh, nothing.
Are you sure?
I'm so sorry.
I feel like i kind of
Hijacked your moment.
Ah, it's not important.
More wine?
Please.
I can't wait to see
What's for dessert.
What was i
Supposed to do?
You were supposed to
Tell her the truth.
Well, this athlete
She was engaged to
Broke her heart,
And half the country
Was talking about it.
She swore she'd never
Date a famous person again.
What do you think
She's gonna do when
She finds out who i really
Am?
I can't just dump
All this on her.
You've run out of time.
The reveal is tomorrow
Night.
Well, then,
Let's postpone it.
We can't.
Get me a meeting
With the publishers.
I'll find a way
To change their minds.
It won't be easy
To convince them, liam.
Well, i'll find a way
To convince them.
I have to.
They can't do that.
Unfortunately,
The suits call the shots,
And they can do
Whatever they want.
But just to cut
All the book reviews?
That-- that doesn't
Even make any sense!
They want more space
For video games and movies.
They're even making me
Create
A whole new section
On celebrity gossip.
Book reviews just don't
Have enough juice these
Days.
Look, i've been
A team player, phil,
Covering music and movies,
Whatever you needed,
But you know the book
Reviews
Are what i love.
That's the reason
I came to the daily.
What can i tell you, sophie?
It's a business.
Lots of people read books!
I mean, sure,
It's a changing industry,
But--
No more book reviews.
I wish
It was different.
Then i don't know
If i can stay.
I need to figure out
What it is i want to do.
Well, that's a decision
You're gonna have to make.
But make it quickly.
I got a paper to run.
[♪♪]
[sophie]: so you don't think
It's a stupid thing to do?
Not at all,
But it's a big step.
I'm terrified.
But i think it's what i
Want.
You were right,
That's what's important.
Well, it sounds
Like a good plan.
I'm gonna
Go with my gut.
I guess it worked
With you yesterday.
That's right.
Look, i-i found out
That i have to go to new
York
For a meeting tomorrow,
So i'm a little frazzled.
I fly out in a couple of
Hours.
Wait. New york? Why?
Just a contractual thing
I need to address,
But i have to do it
In person.
How long will you be gone?
Just overnight.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Well, do you think
You might be up for a date
Night
Tomorrow night?
How about an early dinner?
Say, 5:30?
Sure. I'm down
For the early bird special.
Have a safe flight.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
That sounds
So romantic.
Dinner
By candlelight?
Yeah. It...it was.
He told me he was
Falling in love with me,
And then we kissed.
Wow!
And you want to know
The best part?
I trust him.
Oh yeah?
Not a "he passed
The test" kind of trust,
A trust where
I want to kick myself
For having ever given him
A test in the first place.
I never thought
I would
Feel like this
About someone again,
But he just
Keeps surprising me.
This is so great.
I'm so happy for you.
He's on a trip
To new york for one day,
And i already miss him.
What am i in, high school?
You are in love.
Oh.
Okay, enough
About my love life.
I have something
I want to show you.
I put it together
Last night,
And you have to promise me
That you will be nice.
"rivetingreads.com."
What is it?
My new business.
Your new business?
What about the paper?
Well, liam said something
To me the other day
About following
My dreams
And doing what
I want to do,
And i think this might be
It.
This is so fantastic.
I have a meeting
With my editor later,
And then it goes live.
Looks like
Liam's good for you.
Mm-hmm.
[♪♪]
So how are you
Holding up?
I'm nervous.
Yeah, so am i.
You're not supposed
To admit that to me.
[laughs]
Liam, i'm not gonna
Sugarcoat this.
These people are sharks.
And i don't even know
If they care enough
To do what you're asking.
So expectations are low.
All right, then.
Liam, jackie.
It's great to see you both.
Hey, are you as excited
About the new sales as we
Are?
Um, yeah.
Yeah. You should be.
Please, have a seat.
So...
What can we do for you?
First off, thank you
So much for your time.
Anything for one
Of our favorite authors.
I'm not so sure
How to put this,
But for some personal
Reasons,
Um...
I'm asking that you
Reconsider having me
Reveal myself as gabriel
August.
Uh...
You do know the reveal
Is scheduled for tonight?
Oh...
I know.
And i'll eventually
Go through with it.
Just not tonight.
I give you my word.
Well, we don't really
Need your word, liam.
We have a contract
That guarantees it.
Right.
I just need you to delay
The reveal a few more weeks.
Liam's not
Being unreasonable.
He's just asking
For more time.
Jackie, he has already
Canceled once.
This has all been timed
To the release of the new
Book.
We've built
A marketing approach,
Not to mention a substantial
Amount of effort and money,
Around revealing
Gabriel august's identity.
And obviously,
Once that happens,
The demands
On liam's personal life
Are going to be extreme.
I just need a few more
Weeks.
That's all i'm asking.
[♪♪]
Liam.
They won't do it.
I'm sorry.
I fought for you
In there,
But the machine
Is just too far along
For them
To stop it now.
The reveal
Is on for tonight.
I'm really starting
To hate gabriel august.
You need to talk to sophie.
I'm meeting her for dinner
Tonight at 5:30.
That'll be
Cutting it close.
-we'll make it.
-okay.
Okay, so are we clear
On the plan
For later tonight?
Jasper's bookloft, 7:30.
Actually, make it 7:00,
So my blood pressure
Doesn't get too high.
I'll be there.
Bad news?
She's got a work meeting.
She just canceled dinner.
-what are you gonna do?
-find her.
I have to tell her before
I make the announcement.
You call me!
Let me know how it goes.
[recording]: it's sophie.
Tell me what's on your mind
After the tone. [beep]
Hey, sophie.
I got your text.
I'm back in town.
I really need to talk to
You.
Like, right away,
Face-to-face,
So call me the second
You get this, okay?
I know, but if he said
It was background,
You got to keep
His name out of it.
That's journalism 101!
Yeah. Okay.
Okay, let me know
How it shakes out.
Sorry i couldn't
Fit you in earlier.
I had to keep a reporter
From getting sued.
What's up?
I wanted to let you know
That today is my last day.
Your last day?
So you're leaving the paper
?
I'm starting my own website.
One where i get to do
The kind of reviews
That i want to do.
Can you make a living
Doing that?
Well, it may
Take me a few months
To get enough advertisers,
But...
I'm going to give it a try.
Well, i hate to lose you,
Sophie,
But i have to admit,
I'm a little jealous.
Having the freedom to write
About the things you love
Sounds like the perfect job.
So you're not angry?
I hope whatever you do next
Makes you happy.
Thank you for everything.
Don't suppose i could
Talk you into
Showing your gratitude
By giving me an article
On the gabriel august
Reveal tonight?
I can't.
I'm already covering it
For my own website.
[♪♪]
Call sophie.
[phone dialing]
[recording]: it's sophie.
Tell me what's on your mind
After the tone.
[phone beeps off]
[office bustling]
Hey. It's tabitha, right?
Hey, you kind of stood me
Up.
Actually, to be fair, i
Never
Said i was going to meet
You.
You work with
Sophie atkinson, right?
-you know sophie?
-yeah, is she here?
She was,
But she just quit.
Cleaned out her desk
About 20 minutes ago.
[groans] do you
Know where she went?
Jasper's.
To find out who gabriel
August really is.
Thanks.
Come on...
[quiet conversation]
[♪♪]
[horns honking]
Come on.
[phone chimes]
No.
Call jackie.
[phone ringing]
Where are you?
I'm on my way.
Meet me at the back door
Of the bookstore in 5
Minutes.
Okay.
[♪♪]
What is going on?
I can't go through with it.
-why?
-because she's here.
Oh, you didn't tell her yet?
I tried. I called, i texted,
I went to her work.
She's out there.
I can't let her find out
Along with everyone else.
Take a deep breath.
I will handle this.
Stay here.
Hello, sophie.
Hi, jackie!
How exciting is this?
Yeah, very,
And a little
Terrifying too.
I can imagine.
Is he going to show this
Time?
He's already here.
It's really happening, then?
Oh, i'm presuming you're
Here
To cover this for your
Paper?
Not exactly.
I'm not
With the daily anymore.
I'm actually here
Covering it
For my own website,
Which just went online.
Congratulations.
You let me know if i
Can help in any way.
Thanks.
I may hold you
To that.
In fact, um...
How would you like to
Scoop your old paper?
What are we talking,
Exactly?
Um, how about
The first real
Exclusive interview
With the real
Gabriel august himself?
Never meant to mislead
You...
I hope that we can--
Liam?
What are you
Doing here?
Oh, my gosh. You are
Not gonna believe--
Gabriel august
Will be here any minute
To chat with me.
Jackie got me
An exclusive!
I'll be quick.
I just need to say
What i wanted
To tell you earlier.
Actually, it's what
I've wanted to tell you
For a long time.
Liam, what--
What's going on?
You're the first thing
On my mind
When i wake up in the
Morning,
And the last thing i think
About
When i go to sleep,
And you're in there
A lot in between, too.
So, um, although it's...
Way past the time
I should have told you this,
Here it goes.
That crowd is here for me.
For you?
I'm gabriel august.
[laughs]
And i'm j.k. Rowling.
Nice to meet you.
[jackie]: we don't want to
Keep you waiting in suspense
Any longer.
Ladies and gentlemen,
In a minute,
It will be my pleasure
To introduce to you,
For the very first time,
The real man
Behind gabriel august.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want you
To find out this way.
That's crazy to hear.
You're serious.
I wanted to tell you before.
I should have.
I never meant to hurt you.
I promise.
How could i
Have missed this?
Sophie, please.
I can't do this.
No, please,
Just let me explain.
Please talk to me.
Wait!
Sophie, i love you.
I need to leave.
I wanted to tell you.
I swear.
Here he is... Liam bradley!
[applause]
I can't believe
I let this happen again.
[♪♪]
[applause continues]
♪ seems you're a magnet
For tragedy ♪
♪ a vulnerable heart
That shaped who you are ♪
♪ a masterpiece
♪ cracks on the canvas
The lines on the face ♪
♪ the only hint
♪ the only trace of the
Hurt
That happened to you ♪
♪ that happened to you
♪ can't sleep
♪ can't keep him
From coming in the back
Door ♪
♪ board up the heart
And bag up the tears ♪
♪ and bury them
♪ yeah, you're walking on
Air
♪ numb to my touch
♪ how long have we been
In darkness? ♪
So, sophie,
How are you holding up?
I'm fine.
Really.
So you keep saying.
The new website is
Keeping me super busy.
I still can't believe
He was lying to you
All that time.
I can't believe
I didn't see it.
I mean, i told the guy
About lola.
You don't think he'll put
That
In some book one day, do
You?
He's probably forgotten
About us already.
He's got plenty
To keep him busy these days.
I'm not saying
That what he did was okay,
But i can sort of understand
It,
Given the circumstances.
Honey, you can't
Be serious.
For all we know,
He was just using her
To get a good review.
[nina]:
Or maybe he wanted her
To get to know him
As a normal person,
Not some celebrity author.
I-i don't know
What to say.
I really liked liam.
Not too often
I'm wrong about people.
It's not your fault.
It's nobody's fault
But my own.
I'll bring you a slice
Of lola's cobbler.
That always makes things
A little better.
Thanks.
Look.
I know it's been
Really rough,
And if i were in
The same place,
I can't say that
I'd feel any differently,
But it's hard for me
To believe
That he didn't truly
Care about you.
I'm not sure
What to think anymore.
But i do know one thing.
I can't go back to this.
Whatever we had,
It's over now.
[♪♪]
Hi.
I'm guessing this
Isn't a coincidence.
Well, i remember
You telling me
How much you love
Forest park.
That it was magical...
Your place to escape.
And...nina told me.
But don't blame her.
I called and practically
Begged her to help me out.
I just wanted to talk
To you before i go.
You're leaving?
Going back
To new york.
I can't be in portland
Without you.
And i can't take back
Being famous now.
But i've been
Thinking a lot lately
About how things
Went with us, and...
And what?
We both made mistakes.
We each came into this
A little broken in some
Ways.
But we both know
We've never felt this way
About anyone before.
If you can find
A way to forgive me,
I know we can
Work past this.
I do forgive you, liam.
So you'll give us
Another chance?
Part of you
Belongs to the world now...
Whether you like it or not,
They're always
Gonna be there.
I did that before,
And you know
How badly it ended.
I'm not him.
I'm liam bradley.
And i love you.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
I-i can't do this again.
On that plane
When we first met,
You told me that
First star of evening
Was good
Because it was honest.
I probably said
A lot of things.
I'm sorry if i was--
No. No,
You were right.
I've spent the last few
Years
Pretending that
I wasn't gabriel august,
That i was better than that,
That i was meant
To write real novels
About people's real lives.
But what's more real than
A love story with a sad
Ending?
I should go.
I have a plane to catch.
Goodbye, sophie.
[♪♪]
[woman]: don't
Close the door!
I'm here.
[♪♪]
[thinking]: one moment,
He was alone and lost...
And the next...
She was there,
Filling the empty seat
Beside him.
[♪♪]
Oh, my gosh!
You're gabriel august,
Right?
Close enough.
Do you mind
Signing something for me?
Happy to.
You're gonna miss your cab.
Oh, there'll always be
Another one.
I think
You're gonna like it.
I know i do.
That's the first time
I've heard you say that.
This isn't
Vienna sunset!
No, it isn't.
And you've put your
Name as the author!
Noticed that,
Did you?
I know i'm not gonna
Like the answer to this,
But what happened
To vienna sunset?
Kindling.
[laughing]
Liam! What have you done?
What i should've done
Before,
Written something
That's honest and real.
A book that i believe in,
One that i am proud
To put my name on.
So i can see we're gonna go
A few more rounds
With harris-kingsfield.
You up for it?
Ha! Nothin'
I like better.
I can't wait
For you to read it.
I love seeing you like this.
Excited and passionate...
It's been a while.
I feel great, you know?
Well, as great as i can.
I feel good about the work.
No word
From sophie?
No.
Well, give her time.
Anything's possible.
You really think so?
I do.
Well, i better
Get rolling.
Let me know what
You think of the book.
You know i will.
Ahh.
[♪♪]
[inhales sharply,
Sighs]
Hey, hon.
Cancel all
My appointments today.
And book me the first flight
Out
To portland.
Oregon. Thanks.
[beep]
[♪♪]
I'm pretty sure the plural
Of "goose" is "geese."
It's not gooses?
You'd think so,
But alas.
You're the boss.
How long until
The broken truth chronicles
Review is done?
Mm. You can't rush genius.
So how long until
The broken truth chronicles
Review is done?
[doorbell chimes]
Jackie.
Hello, sophie.
This is such a surprise.
I don't want to take up
Much of your time,
But do you have a minute?
This is
Really impressive.
It's a labor
Of love.
I've been
Working a lot more
Than i did
At the paper,
But i like
My boss better.
[laughs]
You okay
Otherwise?
[sighs]
It took a while,
But...
I think i am now.
I feel good.
I'm happy for you.
It's great seeing you,
Jackie,
But i am guessing
There's a reason
You flew all the way
Out to portland.
Liam is still
In love with you, sophie.
Wow! You don't beat
Around the bush, do you?
Well, i think it's best
To say what i mean,
And i think you, of all
People,
Would appreciate that.
Did liam put you up to this?
He would kill me
If he knew i was here.
How's he doing?
Better.
The first few months
Were difficult.
It was a lot to get used to.
I can imagine.
Women must've been
Throwing themselves at him.
There was only one woman
Whose opinion mattered,
And she wasn't
In new york.
Why are you here, jackie?
Liam misses you a lot.
And i'm guessing
That you miss him
Just as much.
And...
I thought you'd
Want to see this.
What is it?
His new book.
Really?
A new gabriel august book?
A new liam
Bradley book.
The first,
Actually.
Return to forest park.
He took your advice,
He wrote something honest,
Something he believes in.
His book speaks
From his heart.
And he dedicated
It to...
Someone
Very special to him.
Take care, sophie.
[♪♪]
We finally
Put a face to gabriel
August...
And now you want
To kill him off?
Oh, i wouldn't put it
Quite that way,
That is precisely
What we want.
The book that he was
Contractually obligated
To give us
Is not
A gabriel august novel.
Actually, if you look
At the contract closely,
I think you'll find
That liam bradley
Owes you a new book,
Not gabriel august.
Gabriel august
Is liam bradley.
Liam.
Where's vienna sunset?
The ashes might still be in
The fireplace in portland.
[jackie]: i don't think
It's gonna do you much good.
But we think you are gonna
Love
Liam bradley's new book.
[liam]: ted, i understand
This is a business,
And your profit
Is the bottom line, correct?
Correct.
[liam]: then i hope we have
Some good news for you.
You know i'm a fan
Of test-marketing
My clients' new books.
To be perfectly blunt,
I found liam's new book
Emotional
And incredibly gripping.
So i commissioned
A market evaluation
Research,
And the results
Are in your hands.
It achieved the highest
Rating
Of any book
They've ever tested.
You know, market research
Doesn't guarantee success.
It's the book business, ted!
There is no guarantee
Of success.
But this is as close as it
Gets.
It comes down to this.
Gabriel august
As we all knew him
Doesn't exist anymore.
Liam bradley does.
And to be honest,
I feel like
I'm just getting started.
I want harris-kingsfield
Along for the ride,
But one way or the other...
I'm still moving forward.
[♪♪]
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I feel like
It's all my fault.
If i hadn't introduced
You to liam,
You never would've
Told him about lola.
I can't believe
He wrote this
In his book.
It's okay.
No, it's--
It's not.
Sophie...
I told him it was okay.
Liam called me.
He asked
My permission.
He...
You talked to him?
He's a good man.
I know you two had
Your problems.
He's a decent guy.
He...
Made me look
Handsome and sexy,
Like i told him to.
How could he not?
So?
How is it?
It's beautiful.
And smart,
And funny, but so sad.
Uh...
It's liam.
When you were
Going out with james,
I kept my mouth shut.
Figured you knew
What you were doing
Without my help.
You couldn't have
Been more wrong.
To know much
About relationships.
I only loved
One woman in my life.
You found
Your one true love.
I know that now.
But when lola and i
Were together,
It wasn't always
So clear.
Loving someone's
The hardest work
There is.
Oh, i messed up plenty,
So did she.
We disappointed
Each other sometimes,
We said things
We regretted later,
But...
We never
Let that
Keep us apart,
No matter how bad things
Seemed at the time.
It wasn't true love
Because it was easy.
We fought for it.
What am i supposed to do?
[sighs]
You're the only person
That can answer that.
[♪♪]
So?
Do i finally have
A happy author?
They're all
Out there for you.
The real you.
Thanks to you.
You made
All this happen.
Well, that's sweet,
But this had very
Little to do with me.
Your parents
Would have been so proud.
You think so?
I know it.
So, do i have to drag you
Kicking and screaming
Out onto
The stage again?
No.
This time,
I'm actually
Looking forward to it.
Shall we?
Let's go knock 'em
Dead, kiddo.
[crowd chatting quietly]
Thank you for coming out.
[applause]
Thank you.
I know this is a bit
Unusual,
But we have some wonderful
News
To share with you today.
You recently
Met this gentleman
As the author behind
The gabriel august novels,
But today, we're here to
Talk
About an exciting new
Direction.
I'll let him
Tell you all about it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Liam bradley.
[applauding]
I love writing.
From as far back
As i can remember,
I was scribbling things
Down.
I've been very fortunate
To find people like you
Who actually want
To read what i wrote.
[applause]
But for too long,
I've stayed in the shadows.
Well, i'm happy, and...
Actually pretty nervous...
To say
That those days are done.
My new book is called
Return to forest park,
And as you can see,
The only name on it
Is mine.
Yes, sir?
So, are you just continuing
The gabriel august romances
Under a new name?
Not at all.
There is some romance in it,
But this book is different.
It's more
A novel of discovery,
About a man
Finally finding himself.
Is it autobiographical?
I refuse to answer that
On the grounds
That i may incriminate
Myself.
[audience chuckling]
Let's just say it's honest.
Yes, miss?
Does this mean
You've walked away
From your deal
With harris-kingsfield?
No. I'm thrilled
To be staying
Under the harris-kingsfield
Umbrella.
They've been
Incredibly supportive,
And i look forward
To a long future together.
[sophie]:
Mr. Bradley, it sounds
Like return to forest park
Is more personal than
Your previous novels.
It does.
I've learned a lot
Over this past year,
And i hope that shows
In this new book.
I'd say it's the most
Personal
Book i've ever written.
It must be hard,
Being thrust into the
Spotlight
Like this.
Are you worried
That it might change you?
Change isn't always
A bad thing.
I know i've been
Changing a lot lately.
Sure, all this is
Challenging,
But i've finally
Learned to be comfortable
In being liam bradley.
And what you see
Is what you get.
Can your fans count on that?
My fans can rest assured
That i would never do
Anything
To hurt them.
Because some of us still
Have
Deep-seated trust issues
That we're working through.
And i'd like to
Help with those
Any way that i can.
[♪♪]
Are you sure
You're up for it?
Absolutely.
It may take
A while.
That's fine by me.
'Cause i hope to spend
Every day
For the rest of my life
Showing my fans
Just how much i love them.
You want to get
Your camera ready.
I think you're gonna want
To get a shot of this.
Speaking as
A big fan myself...
That sounds like
A wonderful new chapter.
[applause]
[♪♪]
Don't worry about them.
All that matters
Is right here.
[♪♪]
Woohoo!