[clock ticking]
- [sighs]
- SO YOU'RE NOT FEELING SO GOOD.
- NO.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I'VE BEEN
PRETTY DEPRESSED RECENTLY.
- MM-HMM.
- KIND OF ANXIOUS.
JOYLESS.
- AND HOW ELSE--
WHAT OTHER SYMPTOMS
ARE YOU EXPERIENCING
OF DEPRESSION?
- JUST NOT SLEEPING TOO MUCH
AND...
MY WIFE WORKS A LOT AND...
I DON'T REALLY LIKE MY JOB.
- MM-HMM.
- AND...
- HAVE YOU TRIED ANY
OF THE SSRIs?
ANTIDEPRESSANTS.
- NO. NO.
- OKAY, WELL, WE CAN...
TAKE CARE OF THAT FOR YOU.
- I GUESS MY CONCERN IS THAT
I'M HAVING A PARTICULARLY
HARD TIME RIGHT NOW.
- RIGHT.
YOU'D LIKE A BENZODIAZEPINE
OR A, YOU KNOW, CLONAZEPAM,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WE CAN, YOU KNOW--
WE CAN HAVE YOU FEELING MUCH
MORE COMFORTABLE VERY QUICKLY.
- I GENERALLY TRY
TO STEER AWAY
FROM WESTERN MEDICINES
IF AT ALL POSSIBLE.
- DO YOU HAVE A HISTORY
OF ADDICTION
OR ALCOHOLISM IN YOUR PAST?
- NO.
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
- BUT ARE THERE ORGANIC
ALTERNATIVES?
- I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- WELL, IN YOUR AD,
IT SAID THAT YOU COULD PRESCRIBE
MEDICAL MARIJUANA
IN CASES OF ANXIETY.
- SURE.
- IS THAT SOMETHING
THAT'S A POSSIBILITY
THAT YOU THINK MIGHT BE
GOOD FOR ME...
IN MY SITUATION?
- SURE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
MEDICAL MARIJUANA?
- THAT'S PROBABLY A GREAT IDEA.
[light guitar music]
¶ ¶
- ¶ YOU'RE EVERYTHING TO ME ¶
¶ I'M EVERYTHING TO YOU ¶
¶ ¶
¶ WE'RE EVERYTHING ¶
¶ THAT COULD EVER MEAN ¶
¶ ANYTHING ¶
¶ ¶
- HEY.
- WHAT'S UP?
- FILES.
- OH.
- YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
- JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE DONE WITH 'EM,
LIKE, JUST PAPER CLIP THEM.
DON'T USE STAPLES.
JUST PAPER CLIP THEM.
BUT DON'T, LIKE,
MESS UP THE PAPERS.
LIKE, LAST TIME, YOU PUT
THE HAMMY'S IN THE BURGER PLACE,
AND THEN I HAD TO REDO IT, SO--
- OKAY.
- ¶ YOU'RE THE SHOOTING STAR ¶
¶ IN EVERY WAYWARD NIGHT ¶
¶ FOR YOU, MY TURTLE DOVE ¶
¶ TAKE ONLY THRONES TO FLIGHT ¶
¶ FOR ALL THE TIMES WE'LL KNOW ¶
¶ AND ALL THOSE PLACES
I WILL GO ¶
¶ YOU'RE STILL ALONE ¶
- HEY.
- YOU KNOW, THAT SPORTING GOODS
THING IS A MESS.
- I'M SUPPOSED TO TAKE THAT,
AREN'T I?
I GOT TO DEAL WITH THE HAMMY'S
AND THE BURGER PLACE STUFF,
AND I GOT TO FINISH THIS ONE,
AND THEN I'LL GET RIGHT ON THE--
- ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
HOW'S THAT?
- FUCKING BRUTAL.
- I KNOW.
- ¶ I'M THE WISHING WELL ¶
¶ YOU COME TO EVERY DAY ¶
¶ CLIMB INSIDE THESE SHEETS ¶
¶ AND NEVER GO AWAY ¶
¶ FOR ALL THE TIMES WE'LL KNOW ¶
¶ AND ALL THOSE PLACES
LEFT TO GO ¶
¶ I'M STILL ALONE ¶
- HOW YOU DOING?
- HEY. WHAT'S UP?
- YOU LIKE WORKING HERE?
- UM, YEAH.
- YOU TELL EVERYBODY
I'M AN OLD PRICK?
YOU DON'T LIKE WORKING
FOR THAT OLD PRICK?
- I DIDN'T TELL ANYBODY
THAT YOU WERE AN OLD PRICK.
- YOU SAID YOU DON'T
LIKE WORKING FOR THE OLD PRICK.
HOW MANY OLD PRICKS WORK HERE?
- WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
- IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO WORK FOR ME,
GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE, OKAY?
YOU'RE NOT DOING A FAVOR
FOR WORKING FOR THE "OLD PRICK."
- OKAY. OKAY.
- WATCH IT.
¶ ¶
- I'M SO GLAD WE DID THIS.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
IT'S NICE.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT
FOR A WHILE.
THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
- YEAH.
XANA IS SO CUTE, MAN.
CONGRATS ON THAT.
- THANKS.
- IS SHE SLEEPING OKAY?
- YOU KNOW.
- YEAH. YEAH.
- [laughs]
- I DO.
- I'M TELLING YOU, YOU SHOULD
REALLY CHECK OUT THIS STROLLER.
- MM-HMM.
- YOU KNOW,
SAY YOU GUYS ARE IN EUROPE
AND YOU WANT TO GO SHOPPING,
SO YOU PUT IN THIS ONE SEAT,
AND YOU GO.
DO-DO-DO-DO-DO-DO.
YOU KNOW.
AND THEN IT'S TIME FOR DINNER.
AND THEN IT'S TIME FOR BED.
AND YOU POP IN THE BASSINET.
IT DOES EVERYTHING.
- HOW MUCH IS IT?
- IT'S, LIKE, 1,400 BUCKS.
- OH. HMM.
- I KNOW.
- COULD BUY A BOAT FOR THAT.
- A REALLY SMALL BOAT.
- WELL, I MEAN, I'D RATHER
HAVE A STROLLER THAN A BOAT.
- SO HOW ARE THINGS WITH--
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU DO EXACTLY?
- I'M A MUSICIAN.
- RIGHT ON.
- TANK AND I
ACTUALLY HAVE A BAND
THAT WE'VE HAD SINCE WE WERE 19.
- NO WAY.
CAN I COME SEE YOU PLAY
SOMETIME AROUND HERE?
YOU GOT GIGS COMING UP SOON?
- NOTHING IN
THE IMMEDIATE FUTURE.
RIGHT NOW
WE'RE REALLY FOCUSED
ON RECORDING
AND WRITING NEW SONGS.
- RIGHT. RIGHT. RIGHT.
- WE SHOULD EAT.
- RIGHT ON.
[laughter]
- CHEERS TO
A FANTASTIC BARBEQUE.
- YEAH.
- YOU WANT
TO HEAR SOMETHING COOL?
- SURE.
- THIS GUY ACTUALLY MARRIED US.
- NO WAY.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- I KNOW.
- YEAH, I GOT ORDAINED ONLINE.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DID WE DO
BEFORE THE INTERNET, RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- BABY MONITOR.
VINO.
[static hissing]
OH, JESUS CHRIST.
OH, FUCK.
FOR YOU.
- WOW.
- AGGRESSIVE POUR.
[laughter]
- SWEETIE, DINNER WAS AWESOME.
- THANK YOU.
- IT WAS.
- WERE THOSE TOFU DOGS?
- TOFU DOGS.
- MM-HMM.
- ALL RIGHT, COOL.
I, UM...I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
YOU GUYS KNOW HOW I EAT,
OBVIOUSLY.
AND THAT'S ALSO HOW I THINK.
I HAVE A VERY HOLISTIC ATTITUDE.
AND I'M CURRENTLY
STARTING A BUSINESS.
THE COMPANY'S
CALLED "FACE FOOD."
IT'S FOOD FOR YOUR FACE.
IT'S 100% ORGANIC
AND WILD-HARVESTED AND RAW.
BASICALLY, THE BELIEF IS,
YOUR SKIN IS THE LARGEST ORGAN
IN YOUR BODY,
AND IT ABSORBS MORE
THAN YOUR MOUTH,
SO WHY FEED IT TOXIC CHEMICALS
WHEN YOU CAN FEED IT FACE FOOD,
A TOTALLY HOLISTIC SKIN CARE
LINE THAT YOU CAN LITERALLY EAT?
FORGIVE ME FOR BEING SO BOLD,
BUT I KNOW THAT YOU BOTH
ARE EXTREMELY SUCCESSFUL,
AS I CAN SEE FROM YOUR BEAUTIFUL
CHILDREN AS WELL.
I'M LOOKING FOR 100K
AS AN INVESTMENT.
- TANK. TANK.
GUYS, THIS IS SO AWKWARD.
- NO. NO. NO.
- HE'S ASKING YOU FOR $100,000.
- NO. NO.
- LET THEM SPEAK.
- LOOK, WE GET IT A LOT.
IT'S FINE. IT'S FINE.
- THANK YOU. LISTEN.
YOU GUYS CAN TAKE THAT
AND READ THAT OVER.
LITERALLY, I JUST WROTE THIS ON
THE WAY OVER HERE, BUT I HAVE--
- SURE, MAN. SURE.
DEFINITELY.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK.
SURE.
- YEAH.
[nervous laughter]
- SHIT.
- UM...
OKAY.
I WAS LIKE, "AM I GONNA DO THIS?
AM I NOT GONNA DO THIS?
YES? NO?"
YES. OKAY.
ONE OF MY PROFESSORS AT SCHOOL
RECOMMENDED ME FOR A JOB.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YAY.
- RIGHT ON. CONGRATS.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
- YEAH.
- NICE.
- MY FINAL WRITING REQUIREMENT
WAS CHOSEN TO BE PUBLISHED
IN A KIND OF PRESTIGIOUS
HEALTH LAW JOURNAL.
IT WAS LEGAL ISSUES
RELATING TO AIDS,
AND HE GAVE IT TO THE POLICY
AND GOVERNMENT RELATIONS STAFF
OVER AT MASSER.
THEY KNOW THEY HAVE
A STRANGE PUBLIC IMAGE,
SO THEY WANT TO GET MORE
AIDS RESEARCH DOLLARS--
- WAIT, MASSER DRUG COMPANY?
- YEAH, BUT THE THING IS--
- BABY, WHEN WERE YOU
GONNA TELL ME?
- I'M TELLING YOU NOW.
LOOK, I WASN'T SURE WHEN
THE RIGHT OCCASION WAS,
AND IT HAPPENED VERY FAST--
- WAIT. WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
CLOVER, SO YOU'RE GOING
TO WORK FOR MASSER?
MASSER HAS NO INTEREST
IN CURING AIDS.
THEY WANT TO KEEP
PUSHING THEIR DRUGS ON PEOPLE.
THIS IS BLOWING ME
THE FUCK AWAY RIGHT NOW.
- THIS IS REALLY WEIRD.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
- YEAH, IT'S REALLY STRANGE
FOR YOU TO BE TELLING US THIS,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- NO, BECAUSE I JUST WENT
FOR MY SECOND INTERVIEW
WHERE THEY TALKED TO ME
ABOUT IT, AND I WAS LIKE,
"OH, I'M GONNA TALK TO HIM."
- DIDN'T HEAR ABOUT
THAT FIRST INTERVIEW.
- WE'RE TALKING 401K,
LIFE INSURANCE,
THE BEST MEDICAL BENEFITS
THAT MONEY CAN BUY.
- RIGHT. YEAH. COOL.
SELL YOUR SOUL FOR SOME MONEY.
- SOUNDS LIKE IT COULD BE GREAT.
- I AGREE.
I THINK IT'S GREAT.
RIGHT, HONEY?
- YEAH, I THINK
IT'S REALLY GREAT.
- YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
- THIS IS SO STRANGE.
IF YOU KNEW HER...
IF YOU KNEW HER, YOU WOULD
UNDERSTAND HOW STRANGE THIS IS.
[alarm beeping]
- UH, REMEMBER,
WE NEED ORGANIC BABY DIAPERS.
- [sighs]
HOW ABOUT THAT?
HOW ABOUT THAT, ROCK STAR?
[knocking on door]
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT, KID?
EAST L.A.
ECHO PARK. HEY.
- HELLO.
- HELLO, ALLISON.
- HI, HONEY.
- HOW YOU DOING, DARLIN'?
- [fussing]
- I'M GONNA PASS HER
OVER TO YOU.
I GOT TO GET TO WORK.
- [crying]
- BABY CAKES.
- THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO.
- HI, RADKO, IT'S LONNIE.
- WHAT ARE YOU
CALLING ABOUT NOW?
- I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA BE
ABLE TO MAKE IT IN TODAY.
- OH, GOD. NOT AGAIN.
NOT AGAIN.
WHY?
WHY YOU CAN'T COME TODAY?
- I'VE GOT SOME
FAMILY STUFF GOING ON
THAT I'M GONNA HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF, BUT I WILL BE IN TOMORROW.
- WHAT THE FUCK'S WRONG
WITH YOUR DISEASE?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR FAMILY?
- RADKO, PLEASE JUST STOP
YELLING AT ME.
- YOU'RE TORMENTING MY ASS!
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
- I JUST--REMEMBER MY DAUGHTER?
- SHE WORKS HERE?
THEN I DON'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER!
- SHE'S FEELING
REALLY ILL TODAY,
AND WE'VE GOT TO TAKE HER
INTO THE HOSPITAL.
- ARE YOU FUCKING DEAF NOW?
YOU HAVE WAX UP YOUR ASS?
- OKAY, JUST LET ME TALK
FOR A SECOND.
I'M GONNA TAKE CARE OF HER.
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE SHE'S OKAY.
I WILL BE THERE FIRST THING
TOMORROW MORNING.
- OH. COME IN TOMORROW.
TOMORROW!
AND DON'T TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR DAUGHTER.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER.
- OKAY.
- OKAY, LOOK, I'D BETTER GO.
I HAVE WORK TO DO.
- THANK YOU, RADKO.
THESE HASH BROWNS ARE AMAZING.
- YOU KNOW A THREE-LETTER WORD
FOR "DISTANCE,"
STARTS WITH AN "F"?
- "FAR"?
[grunts]
[knocking on door]
YO. OH.
- WHAT'S UP, MAN?
- WHAT YOU DOING?
- RELAXING.
- RIGHT ON.
- I THOUGHT WE WERE
GETTING TOGETHER THURSDAY.
- OH, YEAH, NO, WE WERE, BUT--
SHIT, THE FUNNIEST THING.
I WENT INTO WORK TODAY
AND STARTED WORKING,
AND THE T1 LINE WENT DOWN.
WE'RE, LIKE, A, YOU KNOW--
WE'RE, LIKE, A FUCKING
RENDER FARM OVER THERE.
THE T1 LINE GOES DOWN, AND THEN
WE CAN'T SEND ANYTHING OUT,
AND, YOU KNOW, WORK JUST KIND
OF GRINDS TO A STANDSTILL,
SO RADKO SAID,
"YOU GUYS CAN GO," SO--
- SO WHAT DO YOU WANT, MAN?
- I JUST HAD SOME FREE TIME.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
WE COULD RECORD TODAY.
- OKAY.
- YEAH?
- YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, BUDDY.
[upbeat rock rhythm track]
¶ ¶
YOU FEEL IT, RIGHT?
- WE COULD ABSOLUTELY LAY
SOMETHING DOWN OVER THIS.
CAN I EAT SOME OF THE FACE FOOD,
OR DO YOU NEED THE FOOD--
- IT IS EDIBLE.
IT'S 100% EDIBLE, BUT I
UNFORTUNATELY NEED ALL OF IT,
THOUGH, BUT I--
- LIKE, JUST--COULD I HAVE
HALF AN AVOCADO?
- NO, MAN.
I NEED THOSE ACTUALLY.
I'M SORRY.
- TANK, ARE THOSE
GIRLS' UNDERWEAR?
¶ ¶
- WHERE?
- DUDE, RIGHT THERE
UNDER THE SEAT.
- LOOKS LIKE IT.
I--YEAH.
THAT'S BIZARRE.
- TANK.
- THAT'S TOTALLY BIZARRE.
- WHY ARE YOU BEING BULLSHIT?
- I'M NOT BEING BULLSHIT.
- DON'T BE BULLSHIT.
- NO.
IT TOTALLY SEEMED BULLSHIT.
THAT IS FUCKING WEIRD, THOUGH.
- OKAY.
THERE'S SOME EXPLANATION
FOR WHY YOU HAVE
GIRLS' UNDERWEAR ON YOUR FLOOR.
- WELL, THERE HAS TO BE,
'CAUSE THEY'RE THERE,
BUT I HONESTLY DO NOT KNOW
WHY THEY ARE THERE,
WHICH IS WHAT MAKES IT WEIRD.
¶ ¶
- CHECK, ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
CHECK, ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
LITTLE MORE.
[music volume increases]
ONE. ONE. ONE.
¶ ONE ¶
YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT. COOL.
¶ ¶
- [humming]
GOD DAMN, MAN.
- DUDE, THAT WAS FUCKING SICK.
- BRILLIANT.
- OH, I WISH I COULD DO THAT
EVERY DAY.
AH.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
NEED TO GO BACK TO REALITY.
- BUDDY.
- YEAH?
- I WANT TO TELL YOU A STORY.
- UH-HUH.
- THERE'S A YOUNG MAN
WALKING ACROSS A FIELD,
AND HE RUNS INTO AN OLD MAN
WHO'S PLANTING
AN APRICOT SEEDLING.
AND HE ASKS THE OLD MAN,
"WHY ARE YOU PLANTING
SUCH A NEW TREE?"
AND THE OLD MAN SAYS,
"BECAUSE I LIVE EACH DAY
AS THOUGH I WILL NEVER DIE."
AND THE YOUNG MAN SAYS
TO THE OLD MAN,
"WELL, THAT'S FUNNY,
BECAUSE I LIVE EACH DAY
"AS THOUGH I WILL DIE TOMORROW.
WHICH ONE OF US IS RIGHT?"
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- THINK ABOUT IT, BRO.
- CATCH YOU, MAN.
- YOU DRIVE SAFE.
- THIS WASN'T ON THE FLOOR--
[both speaking indistinctly]
- WAIT. WAIT.
[both cheer]
- GUESS I GOT COMPETITION.
- GET KIWI.
- YOU'RE A KIWI.
- ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE HOME, LITTLE BABY.
[sighs]
- HEY, BABY.
- HI.
MMM.
- WHAT YOU GOT
GOING ON OVER HERE?
- DINNER.
I COOKED MOST OF IT.
I JUST FIGURED
WE COULD USE A MINUTE
TO PUSH THE RESET BUTTON.
- THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
- I'LL MAKE YOU A DEAL.
GO PUT YOUR SWEATPANTS ON,
AND I WILL PUT HER DOWN,
AND WE WILL RECONVENE HERE
MOMENTARILY.
COME HERE.
OH, COME HERE, MONSTER.
COME HERE, MONKEY.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU WANT SOME MANGO CHUTNEY?
[laughter]
GET IT IN THERE.
- WHAT IF IT CHOKES ME?
- TAKE YOUR HAND DOWN.
[laughter]
COME ON.
FUCKING HIGH FIVE.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU ARE SO TALENTED.
- WE SHOULD TAKE THAT SHIT
ON THE ROAD.
MAKE US SOME MONEY
LIKE TED AND MARY.
- THEY ARE FILTHY RICH.
THEY SPENT $1,400 ON A STROLLER.
- BULLSHIT.
HOW MUCH DO YOU NEED
A STROLLER TO DO,
BECAUSE IN THE TERM ITSELF...
- STROLLING.
- IT'S JUST STROLLING, RIGHT?
- EXACTLY.
- BUT I DID HAVE QUITE
A SCINTILLATING CONVERSATION
WITH TED ABOUT THE TRIALS
AND TRIBULATIONS
OF COMMERCIAL VOICEOVER.
- OH, WELL, THAT IS FASCINATING.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
- WELL, EVIDENTLY HE'S VERY BIG
IN THE BUSINESS.
I THINK--
- WAIT, IS HE REALLY?
CAN'T YOU TELL?
WASN'T THERE SOMETHING
ABOUT HIS VOICE
THAT WAS A LITTLE PAVLOVIAN?
IT WAS LIKE HE WAS SPEAKING
AND HE WAS TALKING TO US
AND HE WAS TELLING STORIES,
AND HE WAS A NICE GUY,
BUT ALL THE TIME,
YOU WANTED TO BUY SOMETHING.
- TOTALLY.
I THOUGHT HE WAS JUST TRYING
TO BE, LIKE, A DUDE'S DUDE,
LIKE MAYBE HE'D BEEN HANGING OUT
WITH ALL THOSE GIRLS TOO MUCH,
LIKE HIS LITTLE GIRLS AND--
- NO, HE REALLY TALKS LIKE THAT,
AND THAT'S--
I MEAN, THAT'S HOW THEY HAVE
THE RANGE ROVER.
THAT'S HOW THEY HAVE
THE PORSCHE.
- THAT'S WHY THEY
CAN GO TO EUROPE.
- THAT'S WHY
THEY ARE ABLE TO PURSUE
THE BOURGEOIS AMERICAN DREAM
THAT WE ARE JUST A LITTLE
ARM'S REACH AWAY FROM.
- FOLLOW YOUR PASSION,
YOUR DREAMS.
GO TO EUROPE.
FOLLOW YOUR PASSION
AND YOUR DREAMS.
GO TO EUROPE.
- WELL, BUT HERE'S THE THING,
WHICH I THINK IS KIND OF SAD,
HIS DAY JOB HAS BECOME,
YOU KNOW,
HIS ABSOLUTE LIVELIHOOD.
- MM-HMM.
- AND I THINK THAT'S WHY--
I WAS TALKING TO HIM,
AND I REALIZED THAT'S WHY
IT'S SO IMPORTANT FOR ME
TO KEEP THE DAY JOB
AND, YOU KNOW, THE DREAM,
THE PASSION, THE MUSIC KIND
OF SEPARATE FROM EACH OTHER.
- OH, I KNOW, SWEETIE.
YOU'VE GOT A SWEET LOOK
ON YOUR FACE.
- NO, I JUST--
WE RECORDED A SONG.
- YOU RECORDED A SONG?
- YEAH, I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
WE ALWAYS FUCK AROUND
A LITTLE BIT,
BUT WE ACTUALLY RECORDED, LIKE,
A SONG-SONG.
- IT HAS BEEN FOREVER.
- I KNOW.
AND IT'S NOT DONE.
WE HAVE TO GO BACK AND RE-TRACK
SOME OF THE VOCAL STUFF,
BUT, I MEAN, IT'S, LIKE--
WE GOT DRUMS, AND WE GOT BASS,
AND WE GOT A TAMBOURINE,
AND, LIKE--
AND TANK'S PLAYING GUITAR,
AND I'M SINGING,
AND I THINK IT'S KIND OF GREAT.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
- DO YOU WANT TO HEAR IT?
- YEAH.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- OF COURSE I WANT TO HEAR IT.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
- ROCK ME OUT.
AH, THIS IS EXCITING.
[upbeat rock music]
¶ ¶
- ¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER ¶
¶ CRUSHING MY SOUL ¶
¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER, BABY ¶
¶ WAKING UP EVERY DAY TO PLAY ¶
¶ THIS ROLE ¶
¶ I SHUFFLE IN THE MORNING ¶
¶ TO GET TO SCHOOL ¶
¶ MY BOSS LOOKS THROUGH ME ¶
¶ LIKE A CURIOUS FOOL ¶
¶ LIKE A FOOL ¶
¶ LIKE A ¶
¶ FOOL ¶
¶ ¶
¶ LIKE A ¶
¶ FOOL ¶
¶ ¶
¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER ¶
¶ CRUSHING MY SOUL ¶
¶ INVOLVE THE SOUL CRUSHER ¶
¶ 'CAUSE YOU'VE GOT TO ROLL ¶
¶ YOU LOVE THE SOUL CRUSHER ¶
¶ BUT IT CRUSHES YOUR SOUL ¶
¶ YOU HATE THE SOUL CRUSHER ¶
¶ 'CAUSE IT MURDERS YOUR GOAL ¶
¶ KILLS YOUR GOAL ¶
¶ KILLS YOUR ¶
¶ GOAL ¶
¶ ¶
¶ KILLS YOUR GOALS ¶
THIS IS A GOOD PART.
¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER ¶
¶ CRUSHING MY SOUL ¶
¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER,
MOTHERFUCKER ¶
¶ WAKING UP EVERY DAY
TO PLAY THIS ROLE ¶
¶ PLAY THIS ROLE ¶
¶ TO PLAY THIS ROLE ¶
¶ ¶
¶ I'M DONE PLAYING THIS ROLE ¶
¶ FUCK Y'ALL ¶
¶ ¶
- YEAH.
- RIGHT?
- YOU RECORDED A SONG.
- I MEAN, I GUESS IT COULD FEEL
REPETITIVE,
BUT I THINK IT'S KIND OF
RADIO-FRIENDLY AND, YOU KNOW--
- IT HAS A GOOD RHYTHM.
- THAT, LIKE--
¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER ¶
- IT'S VERY CATCHY.
- ¶ CRUSHING MY SOUL ¶
¶ IT'S A SOUL CRUSHER,
BABY DOLL-- ¶
[both moaning]
¶ TO PLAY THIS-- ¶
- YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
- UH-HUH. UH-HUH.
[both laughing]
- NO.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- GET ON ME.
- COME ON.
- YEAH.
- YOU COME BETTER
WHEN YOU'RE ON TOP.
- UH-UH.
- YES, YOU DO.
- NO, I WANT YOU
TO GET UP ON ME.
GET ON ME. COME ON.
HOP ON.
- JUMP UP.
- HOP ON.
HOP ON.
- GET UP.
- I'M RIGHT HERE.
- COME ON.
COME ON!
- [laughs]
I'M SO TIRED, AND MY BACK HURTS.
- I'M TIRED TOO.
- [laughs]
OKAY. OKAY.
- OKAY?
OKAY.
- [laughs]
[alarm beeping]
- HELLO?
- RADKO, IT'S LONNIE.
- LONNIE, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT TIME IT IS?
- YES, I KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS.
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT I'M
GONNA BE ABLE TO MAKE IT
INTO THE OFFICE TODAY,
BECAUSE I'VE GOT--
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU WON'T MAKE IT IN TODAY?
YOU KNOW, RONNIE,
THAT I'M TRYING TO RUN
A FUCKING BUSINESS HERE?
- UM, YEAH, NO, I KNOW,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT TODAY.
- YOU WERE FUCKING OUT
YESTERDAY, AND WE NEED YOU!
- YEAH, I KNOW, BUT I'M NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO MAKE IT TODAY.
- WHY THE FUCK?
- BECAUSE I'M DEALING
WITH SOME FAMILY STUFF STILL.
- WHAT FUCKING FAMILY?
- LOOK, I'LL BE IN TOMORROW,
AND I'LL PICK UP THE SLACK.
- JUST--JUST COME IN
AFTER LUNCH THEN.
- NO. I--
- WHY?
- YEAH, NO, I--
- WE NEED YOU HERE BY 1:30!
- I UNDERSTAND, BUT I CAN'T.
- WHY CAN'T YOU?
WHAT THE FUCK?
- RADKO--
- FUCK! FUCK!
YOU'RE THE WORST
FUCKING EMPLOYEE
I'VE EVER HAD IN MY LIFE!
IF YOU AREN'T HERE BY 1:30,
YOU'RE FIRED!
- RADKO--
- FUCK!
- RADKO, MY DAUGHTER DIED
LAST NIGHT.
- WHAT THE FUCK DO YOU MEAN
YOUR DAUGHTER DIED?
- I HAVE TO GO.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- I'M IN THE HOSPITAL.
- I HAVE TO GO.
- MORE COFFEE?
- NO.
[pulsing dub music]
buzz!
[lock clicks]
¶ ¶
I GOT A PRESCRIPTION.
I HAVE ANXIETY.
- MM-HMM.
DO YOU WANT TO BUY SOME WEED?
- YEAH, PLEASE.
UM, WE HAVE HEADBAND,
SILVER HAZE, PINEAPPLE KUSH,
MASTER KUSH, BUBBA KUSH.
I LIKE THE BUBBA KUSH.
- DO YOU GUYS COME UP
WITH THE NAMES FOR THOSE?
- UM, NO.
- IT'S PROBABLY THE SAME GUY WHO
COMES UP WITH THE CRAYON COLORS.
- HA-HA.
THAT'S FUNNY.
- UM, YEAH, I WANT SOMETHING
TO MELLOW ME OUT
AND BE SUPER INSPIRATIONAL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS BEST FOR THAT?
- WE'LL GET YOU, LIKE,
A HEADBAND.
- OKAY.
- AND THEN ALL THE KUSHES,
THOSE WILL REALLY, LIKE--
THOSE WILL BE--
- THOSE ARE PRETTY.
- THANK YOU.
- ARE YOU, LIKE, AN ARTIST?
- UM, OH, I--
I LIKE ART, YOU KNOW?
DO YOU LIKE THE ONE
WITH A LOT OF COLOR
OR THE ONE WITH LESS COLOR?
- I LIKE THIS, 'CAUSE IT'S KIND
OF GOT A NATURE THEME TO IT.
IT'S, LIKE, LAKESIDE,
BUT IN A FOREST.
- OH.
OH, YEAH.
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE THAT.
WOW.
[chuckles]
- WE SHOULD
DO SOMETHING TOGETHER.
- LIKE ART MUSIC?
- LIKE MUSIC ART.
WE COULD DO A SHOW MAYBE
WHERE MY BAND WAS PLAYING MUSIC
AND YOU WERE JUST OFF
TO THE SIDE PAINTING,
BUT YOU GOT INSPIRED
BY WHAT WE WERE PLAYING,
AND SO YOUR PAINTINGS
WOULD REPRESENT THE MUSIC,
BUT THEN I COULD LOOK
AT THE PAINTINGS
WHILE I WAS SINGING AND, LIKE,
MAYBE COME UP WITH SONGS
ON THE SPOT,
AND I COULD SING THOSE
INSPIRED BY YOUR PAINTING,
SO IT WOULD BE KIND OF
FEEDING ITSELF,
JUST A PINWHEEL OF INSPIRATION.
- WOW.
YEAH, WE SHOULD--
WE SHOULD DO THAT.
- WE SHOULD TOTALLY DO THAT.
- YOU'RE SERIOUS, THOUGH?
- YEAH, TOTALLY.
- 'CAUSE, LIKE,
I CAN DO IT THIS WEEKEND.
- THIS WEEKEND?
UM...
WELL, THERE'S A LOT
OF STUFF THAT WE'D HAVE TO DO
BEFORE WE DID IT.
I MEAN, WE'D HAVE
TO GET A VENUE.
- SO, WELL, LET'S START
THIS WEEKEND AT LEAST.
- WELL, WE'D HAVE TO GET
A VENUE,
LIKE, SOMEWHERE TO PLAY,
AND, I MEAN--
- LET'S JUST PLAY ON THE SIDE
OF THE STREET.
- I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A FULL BAND.
I JUST HAVE ONE OTHER GUY
THAT I'M PLAYING WITH,
SO I WOULD HAVE TO FIND SOME
OTHER MUSICIANS TO PLAY WITH US.
- OKAY.
- I'M ACTUALLY GOING
OUT OF TOWN THIS WEEKEND
WITH MY WIFE AND MY KID.
- OKAY.
- I HOPE THAT'S OKAY.
- YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
[laughs]
- I HAVE A BABY.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH.
- HOW'S YOUR HIGH?
- UM, IT'S GOOD.
- OKAY.
- WHAT TIME IS IT?
- HEY, LONNIE.
OH, MY GOD.
HI, IT'S FAYE.
WE JUST HEARD THE NEWS
ABOUT XANA.
OH, GOD.
I'M SO SORRY.
- LONNIE, HEY, MAN.
IT'S PATRICK.
UM, JEEZ, I JUST HEARD THE NEWS
ABOUT THE BABY.
I'M SO SORRY.
- HI, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
IT'S MARK.
LISTEN, I'M JUST CALLING
'CAUSE I JUST HEARD THE NEWS
ABOUT THE BABY.
I'M REALLY SORRY
TO HEAR ABOUT EVERYTHING,
AND IF THERE'S, YOU KNOW,
ANYTHING I CAN DO--
- HEY, WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
- CAN I JUST GET A BEER?
- SURE.
- CAN I ACTUALLY
GET A WHISKEY TOO?
- YEAH, SURE.
- THANKS.
HOW YOU DOING?
- ALL RIGHT.
THANKS FOR ASKING.
- HEY.
- OH, F--HEY.
OH, SHIT, MAN.
I'M JUST--
- I TOOK THE HEAT ON THAT
SPORTING GOOD THING FOR YOU.
- OH, ON THE--
- IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
IT'S OKAY. I WAS HAPPY TO--
WITH EVERYTHING--
HOW OLD?
- UM...SIX MONTHS.
SIX MONTHS OLD.
- I'M, LIKE--
I'M--
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
I'M OVER HERE, AND I'M GOING,
LIKE, "WHAT IS THIS?"
YOU KNOW, "WHAT IS THIS?"
THIS. THIS.
- YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
- UH...I DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
- YOU KNOW,
YOU JUST GOT TO PUT--
- NO, THERE'S--
NO, THERE'S NO LOGIC.
THERE'S NO LOGIC.
- JOE, I'M GONNA BE OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT, LONNIE.
OKAY.
- YEAH, UM--
- NO, I--I--
- JOE, LOOK, IT'S AWFUL.
I MEAN, IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS
THAT'S EXACTLY LIKE THEY SAY.
YOU CAN'T IMAGINE IT UNTIL IT
HAPPENS, AND THEN IT HAPPENS,
AND YOU JUST GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO COPE--
- AND THERE YOU ARE.
THERE YOU ARE.
- YEAH.
UM...
HEY, MAN, I'M SORRY, BUT WE GOT,
YOU KNOW, MEMORIAL STUFF.
WE'VE GOT TO SEND OUT SOME,
LIKE, E-VITES
AND SHIT LIKE THAT.
- FOR A MEMORIAL?
- YEAH. YEAH.
IT'S--
- E-VITES?
NO, NO, AGAIN, THAT'S NOT--
NO, IF THAT'S HOW YOU GUYS
ARE DOING IT--
- NO, THAT WAS CLOVER'S IDEA.
- I THINK I'M GONNA JUST
KIND OF GO AND--
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST--
- HEY, LOOK--
- NO. NO. NO.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
[voice cracking] I'M OKAY.
I'M OKAY.
I'M OKAY. I'M OKAY.
- JOE.
- NO. NO. NO. I'M ALL RIGHT.
- NO.
- HEY, BABES.
- HEY, BABY.
- SHOES. COUCH.
- [grunting]
[sighs]
SHE ASLEEP?
- YEAH, SHE'S DOWN.
WHAT'S THAT?
- THAI.
- MMM.
- HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
- USUAL. YOU?
- YEAH. USUAL.
YOU HUNGRY?
- YEAH.
- LET'S EAT.
[engine turns over]
[engine revving]
- [laughs]
- HEY.
- [cooing]
- [fussing]
- HEY.
[blowing random notes]
¶ ¶
[whispering] YOU WANT TO GO
BACK TO SLEEP?
[knocking at door]
- HEY, JEANNIE.
- HI.
I BAKED YOU THIS QUICHE.
- OH, THAT'S SO SWEET OF YOU.
- YOU LOOK REALLY AMAZING.
- WHY, THANK YOU.
ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
- HEY, JEANNIE.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
BABE, I GOT THIS.
- YEAH?
THIS IS NICE.
- YEAH, I GOT IT.
IT'S A WORK THING.
THAT WAS VERY SWEET OF YOU.
- SHE'S SO COMPOSED.
- YEAH.
WE'RE TRYING TO HOLD IT TOGETHER
AS BEST AS WE CAN,
BUT THERE'S A LOT GOING ON,
SO I GOT TO GET BACK TO IT,
BUT I'LL SEE YOU
IN THE OFFICE SOON.
OKAY?
THANK YOU.
THANKS, JEANNIE.
- [crying]
- IT'S OKAY, BABY.
IT'S OKAY, BABY.
- [crying]
- IT'S OKAY, BABY.
DADDY LOVES YOU.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, KID.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- ¶ IT'S A HORROR SHOW ¶
¶ AND EVERYONE TELLS ME SO ¶
- TANK!
[knocking on door]
[acoustic guitar music]
- HEY.
- HOW YOU DOING?
- WHAT'S UP?
- THOUGHT I'D COME SAY HI.
THAT T1 IS STILL DOWN,
SO I'M NOT GOING TO WORK.
YOU WANT TO GO LEARN TO SURF
OR SOMETHING?
- NO, I'M GOOD, MAN.
YOU OKAY?
- WHO'S IN THERE?
- NOBODY, MAN.
JUST PLAYING SOME TRACKS BACK.
YOU KNOW,
LISTENING TO SOME STUFF.
- NO, DUDE, WHO'S IN--
WHO'S PLAYING IN THERE?
- NOBODY.
LET'S JUST--YOU WANT TO TALK?
- WHY ARE YOU BEING SO WEIRD?
- I JUST--I'D APPRECIATE
A PHONE CALL MAN, OKAY?
GIVE ME THE HEADS UP
THAT YOU'RE COMING THROUGH.
- TANK, YOU DON'T HAVE A PHONE.
- WELL, I'LL CALL YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
- ARE YOU, LIKE, CHEATING ON ME?
- WHAT THE HELL DOES THAT MEAN,
MAN?
- I MEAN, ARE YOU PLAYING
WITH ANOTHER BAND IN THERE--
- NO, I'M NOT PLAYING
WITH ANOTHER BAND.
- WHO'S THE CHICK THAT'S
SINGING, AND WHOSE IS THIS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- SHE'S IN MY SPOT.
IS THAT HERS?
- I DON'T--
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING, "HER"--
LISTEN, MAN, SOME THINGS
ARE BETTER LEFT UNSPOKEN, OKAY?
- OKAY.
EVERYBODY'S CHANGING.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN, MAN?
- I DIDN'T HAVE OFF
FROM WORK TODAY.
I JUST DIDN'T GO.
I DIDN'T GO YESTERDAY EITHER
OR THE DAY BEFORE THAT.
- WHAT YOU MEAN YOU DIDN'T GO?
- I MEAN, I DIDN'T--
I SAID, "FUCK IT."
I DIDN'T GO.
WHOO.
BECAUSE I CAN'T.
- WHY CAN'T YOU GO TO WORK?
- YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE I JUST
REACHED MY MAXIMUM CAPACITY
FOR PRETENDING LIKE I CARED.
AND I GO HOME,
AND CLOVER'S ALL WEIRD,
AND SHE'S, LIKE,
HALF A STEP AWAY FROM A PANTSUIT
AT THIS POINT, AND SHE'S TAKING
THIS JOB FOR MASSER.
THIS ISN'T THE LIFE
THAT WE WANTED.
- OKAY, SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WHAT AM I GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
LET'S GO HANG OUT.
- GO HANG OUT?
- SHIT, LET'S GO ON TOUR.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
MAN?
YOU'RE A FATHER.
YOU NEED TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR YOUR ACTIONS.
- BROTHER, I LOVE YOU,
BUT WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU
TO TALK ABOUT RESPONSIBILITY?
YOU LIVE IN A WINNEBAGO
ON THE BEACH.
- YEAH, AND I'M NOT RESPONSIBLE?
I CHOSE THIS LIFE
BECAUSE I WANTED TO LIVE
A LIFE OF FREEDOM.
YOU MADE YOUR CHOICES.
YOU HAVE A FAMILY.
YOU HAVE A WIFE.
YOU HAVE A BEAUTIFUL BABY GIRL,
AND IF YOU WANT
YOUR LIFE TO CHANGE,
YOU NEED TO BE HONEST
WITH YOURSELF AND YOUR WIFE.
YOU CAN'T KEEP RUNNING AWAY
FROM SHIT, MAN.
- MM-HMM.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- YEAH, I AM.
- YEAH.
I'LL CATCH YOU SOON.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I LIKE YOU
A WHOLE LOT.
I LIKE YOU SO MUCH.
AND I'M REALLY SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO
IF YOU WERE REALLY DEAD.
- [fussing]
- YEAH.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
- WOW.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL OUT HERE.
LOOK AT THOSE EYES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HONEY, WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
- YEAH, SHE STARTED
DOING THAT LAST WEEK.
- SERIOUSLY?
- SERIOUSLY.
- [cooing over radio]
- I WAS WILLING TO LIVE
IN THAT TOMATO PATCH FOREVER.
YOU BAILED.
- WE SPENT 36 HOURS THERE.
- OH, MAN.
- WE WERE SO FUCKING HIGH.
- HOW WAS IT SO COMFORTABLE
TO SLEEP THERE?
- IT WASN'T.
WE WERE JUST HIGH.
- OH.
I FEEL LIKE, DEEP DOWN,
WE WERE SO COMFORTABLE THERE
'CAUSE THAT WAS WHERE
WE WERE MEANT TO LIVE.
- FUCK,
THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
- AND WE HAVE FUCKED
EVERYTHING ELSE UP SINCE.
- NO.
- [sighs]
SHOULD I TAKE THIS JOB?
- ARE YOU REALLY ASKING?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, YOU SHOULD.
- IS IT THE RIGHT THING TO DO?
- I WAS PISSED OFF
WITH THE WAY YOU TOLD ME,
BUT YOU MADE A GOOD CASE.
FUCK, YOU GET IN THERE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO PROBABLY
DO A LOT MORE GOOD
THAN YOU WOULD ELSEWHERE.
YOU'LL HAVE A TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF RESOURCES,
AND IT WILL HELP OUR FAMILY OUT.
- I JUST HAVE
THIS PERFECT VISION...
YOU KNOW, OF US,
THE US THAT JUST, LIKE,
PACK UP A CAR,
JOIN JEFF AND ALICE AT
THE ADVOCACY GROUP IN PORTLAND.
I MEAN, I HELPED START
THAT THING.
[sighs]
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW ENOUGH
TO GET ANYTHING DONE.
- I MEAN, WE WERE KIDS.
I DON'T KNOW THAT, WITH HER,
WE'VE GOT THAT LUXURY ANYMORE.
- I KNOW.
AND...
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO TAKE OVER A LITTLE BIT
AND BE ABLE TO SUPPORT US.
YOU HAVE BEEN CARRYING
THE HEAVY LOAD FOR A LONG TIME.
- UM...
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
AFTER WE HAD OUR FIGHT
THE OTHER NIGHT...
- MM-HMM.
- I GOT REALLY CONFUSED.
- AND SO I STARTED
THINKING ABOUT...
UM...
I STARTED THINKING ABOUT MAYBE
MAKING A CAREER CHANGE TOO.
- MM-HMM.
- LIKE, I FIGURE
MOST OF MY FRIENDS
WHO ARE MAKING SERIOUS BANK ARE
DOING IT IN THE GAMING INDUSTRY,
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE--
- GAMING?
- YOU KNOW, LIKE VIDEO GAMES,
ONLINE GAMING.
- DO YOU EVEN PLAY VIDEO GAMES?
- I DON'T KNOW
THAT THAT'S THE SOLUTION.
I JUST FEEL LIKE YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULD BE MORE RESPONSIBLE.
- VIDEO GAMES?
- I LOVE YOU.
YOU HAVE VERY GOOD INTENTIONS.
- CAN YOU SAY BYE TO MAMA?
- HAVE A GOOD DAY, BOO.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
NICE PANTSUIT.
- GREENEX. YOU BET.
GREENEX. YOU BET.
[knocks at door]
- HEY.
- HEY, JEANNIE.
- BROUGHT YOU SOME CANNOLIS.
- OH.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
- AND A LATTE.
- THANK YOU.
I MEANT TO CALL YOU AND TELL YOU
THAT THE QUICHE YOU BROUGHT OVER
WAS DELICIOUS.
- [stammering]
I DID WHAT I COULD, SO--
YOU'RE JUST REALLY STRONG.
I REALLY ADMIRE YOU FOR THAT.
- YOU GOT TO GET BACK
ON THE HORSE, YOU KNOW?
OH, THANK YOU, JEANNIE.
- YOU STRONG MAN.
- THANK YOU, JEANNIE.
- YEAH, I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
- YOU GUYS NEVER CALL.
- MIND IF I SIT?
- BE MY GUEST.
NICE SUIT.
- FUCK OFF.
I'M SORRY I'VE BEEN
SUCH A SHITTY FRIEND.
- IT'S OKAY.
I'M SORRY FOR JUDGING YOU.
- WHO'S VW IS THAT?
- SERIOUSLY, CLOVER,
YOU AND LONNIE HAVE TO STOP
COMING BY UNANNOUNCED.
- THIS IS, LIKE, THE FIRST TIME
I'VE BEEN HERE IN YEARS.
- WELL...
FOR FUTURE REFERENCE.
HOW'S SCHOOL?
- I'M ALMOST DONE.
ALL I REALLY HAVE LEFT
IS THE BAR.
- YEAH?
FANTASTIC.
- HOW'S FACE FOOD?
- CAN I SHOW YOU SOMETHING?
- YEAH.
- YEAH?
ONE SECOND.
- HEY, GUYS.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I'M OKAY. HOW YOU DOING?
- WELL, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, OKAY, LONNIE.
- OKAY.
- OKAY, WE'LL JUST START.
HOO.
WE ALL CAN'T BEGIN TO IMAGINE
WHAT YOU AND CLOVER
MUST BE GOING THROUGH.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
EVERYTHING THAT EVERYBODY HAS
DONE HAS JUST BEEN TOO SWEET.
- IT'S NEVER ENOUGH,
AND WE DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE LEAST WE CAN DO IS--
- EVERYBODY HAS BEEN SO
WONDERFUL TO ME.
I JUST--I CAN'T THANK YOU
GUYS ENOUGH FOR--
- WELL, THOSE OF US
IN THE OFFICE THAT WERE ABLE TO,
WE TOOK UP A COLLECTION FOR YOU,
AND WE GOT A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR YOU AND CLOVER--
- OH, NO.
NO. NO. NO. NO. NO.
IT'S--GUYS, IT'S OKAY.
- NO. COME ON, LONNIE.
- GUYS, REALLY. IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
- THIS IS SOMETHING SPECIAL WE
WANTED TO GIVE TO THE FAMILY.
- GUYS, REALLY,
I CAN'T TAKE THIS.
- LONNIE--
- IT'S OKAY.
- THERE'S NO MORE IFS, ANDS,
OR BUTS ABOUT IT.
- THE COOKIES AND THE LATTES
AND THE CARDS.
I REALLY CAN'T TAKE THIS
FROM YOU.
- WE DIDN'T BRING COOKIES.
WE JUST--
THIS IS OUR COOKIE. PLEASE.
- WE THINK THAT THIS COULD
REALLY HELP YOU GUYS OUT,
AND IT WAS SOMETHING
THAT WE WANTED TO DO FOR YOU,
SO, YOU KNOW.
- YOU'RE NOT A RICH MAN,
AND WE KNOW THAT.
- MM-HMM.
- THIS IS THE LEAST
WE CAN DO NOW.
PLEASE.
THIS IS FROM OUR HEARTS, OKAY?
- YEAH.
YEAH.
- PLEASE TAKE IT.
- OKAY.
OH, THANK YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU.
[sighs]
- THAT'S FOOD.
- IT IS. IT IS.
FOOD FOR YOUR FACE.
- CAN I TASTE IT?
- SURE.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- IT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
- THAT'S ACTUALLY TASTY.
- DO YOU WANT MORE?
- OKAY, I'M READY.
- YOU READY?
- YEAH.
- NOW JUST SIT BACK, RELAX,
AND TRY TO FOCUS ON YOUR BREATH.
NOW, WHAT THIS IS GONNA DO IS,
IT'S GONNA TONE AND TIGHTEN
YOUR PORES AND ALSO REALLY
INTENSELY MOISTURIZE.
- WE WENT CAMPING THIS WEEKEND.
- YEAH? WHERE'D YOU GO?
- IT WAS JUST UP NORTH.
OH, IT WAS NICE.
- OH, I'M SURE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S, LIKE, TO GET OUT
OF THIS CONCRETE JUNGLE,
OUT OF THE CAR,
AND OUT INTO MOTHER NATURE
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
FOR A CHILD, REALLY.
- YOU KNOW, I THINK
THAT'S THE MOST QUALITY TIME
I'VE SPENT WITH XANA.
- YEAH.
- I DIDN'T REALIZE
I WAS MISSING IT.
[lock turning]
- THERE WE GO, BABY.
- HI, BABY.
- HI, DEAR.
- HOW YOU DOING?
HI, XANA.
OH, LET ME TAKE HER FROM YOU.
OH.
HEY.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
- IT WAS ALL RIGHT.
- YOUR FACE LOOKS GREAT.
UM...
DO YOU WANT TO MAYBE GO
GET SOME PIZZA OR SOMETHING?
- YEAH.
LET ME GET OUT OF THIS.
- OKAY.
[sighs]
AH, LITTLE GIRL.
HEY, COME ON.
COME ON.
IT'S BETTER OUT HERE.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
HEY, JEANNIE.
HOW YOU DOING?
NO, XANA'S FINE.
SHE'S OUT THERE PLAYING
WITH HER DAD.
OH.
I MEAN, SHE COULD USE
A FRESH DIAPER
JUDGING BY THE SMELL
OF HER, BUT--
- OH, OH, I THINK THAT'S FOR ME.
BABY, GIVE ME THE PHONE.
- AH.
THANK YOU, JEANNIE.
- WHO WAS THAT?
[laughing] WHAT?
WHAT?
OH, DUDE, I KNOW EXACTLY
WHY YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME
LIKE THAT, WHICH--
OBVIOUSLY, I WOULD LOOK AT ME
LIKE THAT TOO, BUT IT'S NOT--
IT'S THAT--
DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN I TOLD YOU,
LIKE, SIX WEEKS AGO
THAT TONY LOVETT, THE GUY
FROM SFX, HE'D LOST HIS SON?
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT?
OKAY.
WELL, TONY LOST HIS TODDLER,
AND WE TOOK UP A COLLECTION,
AND I GAVE HIM 50 BUCKS.
I KNOW I PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T HAVE, BUT I JUST--
I WAS THINKING ABOUT XANA,
AND I WAS THINKING, YOU KNOW,
IF IT HAPPENED TO US,
JESUS CHRIST,
SO MY NAME WAS ON THIS LOG,
AND THERE WAS A SEPARATE KIND
OF DONATION SHEET FOR HIM,
AND JEANNIE SAW THAT,
AND THEN SHE THOUGHT THAT
SOMETHING HAD HAPPENED TO US
AND TO XANA,
AND THAT'S WHY--
THAT WAS WHEN SHE CAME OVER
WITH THE QUICHE.
SHE THOUGHT THAT WHERE WAS
THIS WHOLE OTHER SITUATION
WHICH NEVER EXISTED.
WHAT?
I'M EXPLAINING TO YOU
WHAT HAPPENED.
I'M TELLING YOU--
YOU DON'T BE--
- WHERE'S THE MONEY?
WHERE'S THE MONEY?
GET OUT.
[door opens]
[door closes]
- UM...
- SIT DOWN.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
- DOES IT MATTER?
- YES.
- I...
I WOKE UP THE MORNING
AFTER WE HAD OUR FIGHT,
AND I DROVE TO WORK,
AND I LITERALLY
COULDN'T MAKE MYSELF GO IN.
I JUST COULDN'T BREATHE.
AND I TURNED AROUND,
AND I GOT BACK IN MY CAR,
AND I CALLED MY BOSS,
AND I TOLD HIM THAT SHE WAS SICK
AND THAT I NEEDED
THE DAY TO TAKE CARE OF HER,
BECAUSE THAT SEEMED LIKE...
- THAT'S OUR BABY.
- I KNOW. I KNOW.
I HAD A REALLY GOOD DAY,
AND THEN I CAME HOME,
AND, LIKE, I HAD TIME TO COOK,
AND THEN WE HAD A FUN TIME,
AND FOR A SECOND, LIKE, FOR
A SPLIT FUCKING SECOND THAT DAY,
I FELT KIND
OF LIKE MYSELF AGAIN,
AND I LOOKED AT YOU,
AND YOU LOOKED KIND OF
LIKE YOU AGAIN,
AND I FELT LIKE, "OKAY, OKAY,
MAYBE I CAN DO THIS.
MAYBE ALL I NEEDED
WAS JUST THAT BREAK."
AND I WOKE UP THE NEXT DAY,
AND I WENT, AND...
AND I COULDN'T--
I JUST COULDN'T GO BACK.
I JUST COULDN'T.
IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
AND SO...
- LONNIE.
- SO...
I CALLED MY BOSS, AND...
AND I PANICKED.
IT, LIKE,
HAPPENED IN A BLACKOUT.
I PANICKED,
AND I SAID THAT SHE--
THAT XANA HAD DIED.
AND I WANTED TO TAKE IT
ALL BACK, BUT I COULDN'T.
I COULDN'T TAKE IT BACK.
I COULDN'T TAKE BACK
WHAT I'D DONE.
- LONNIE.
- AND I'M NOT--
I'M NOT PUTTING THIS ON YOU
AT ALL,
AT ALL.
BECAUSE I'M THE ASSHOLE HERE.
BUT YOU'VE MADE CHOICES
THAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
AND I FEEL LIKE I'M STUCK.
I'M STUCK IN SOME FUCKING...
COLLEGE DREAM
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T HAD TIME
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT I WANT OR--
I JUST HAVEN'T HAD TIME,
AND I'M NOT BITCHING.
IT'S WHAT A MAN SHOULD DO.
IT'S WHAT A MAN SHOULD BE,
IS BE ABLE TO TAKE CARE
OF HIS WIFE AND HIS CHILD,
AND THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO BE
ABLE TO DO FOR YOU GUYS.
I WANT TO BE ABLE
TO DO THAT SO BAD,
BUT, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I CARE ABOUT ANYMORE.
MY MUSIC SUCKS.
- YEAH.
YOUR MUSIC SUCKS.
- OUCH.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT I'M DOING
SUCKS PRETTY BAD TOO.
I'M NOT PROUD OF MYSELF.
I'M NOT PROUD OF MYSELF ANYMORE.
I'M NOT PROUD OF ME,
AND I'M NOT PROUD OF YOU.
- YEAH.
- I WANT TO BE PROUD OF US.
- WE'RE ALLOWED
TO CHANGE THINGS, RIGHT?
- UM...
- WE DON'T JUST HAVE TO KEEP
OUR HEADS DOWN UNTIL WE'RE 60...
BECAUSE IF WE CAN'T FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO MAKE OURSELVES HAPPY...
SHE'S GONNA BE M--
SHE'S GONNA BE MISERABLE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT YOU ARE GOOD AT?
- WHAT?
- PRETTY FUCKING GOOD DAD.
YOU'RE A PRETTY
FUCKING GOOD DAD.
AND I LOVE YOU.
FUCK.
- I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
- [cooing]
[light guitar music]
¶ ¶
- ¶ SHE HOPES THAT THIS
COULD BE THE ONE ¶
¶ ¶
¶ SHE HOLDS IT UP
IN FRONT OF THE SUN ¶
¶ AGAIN AND AGAIN ¶
¶ ¶
¶ THE BEST OF US
ARE UNDER ATTACK ¶
¶ THEY FORCE YOU DOWN
ONTO YOUR BACK ¶
¶ AGAIN AND AGAIN ¶
¶ ¶
¶ HOLD ON ¶
- BE RIGHT BACK.
[knocking on door]
- HEY.
- OH.
HI.
IS TANK HERE?
- YEAH, HE'S SLEEPING.
DO YOU WANT ME TO GO GET HIM?
- NO, NO, THAT'S OKAY.
I'M LONNIE.
- HI, I'M SEVEN.
- HI, SEVEN.
HE'S TOLD ME VERY LITTLE
ABOUT YOU.
- [laughs]
WHO'S THAT?
- OH, THAT'S CLOVER AND XANA.
- HI, CLOVER AND XANA.
- HEY, CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND GIVE THIS TO HIM?
- OKAY.
- JUST TELL HIM
IT'S FOR FACE FOOD.
- OH, OKAY.
HE'LL LIKE THAT.
I JUST GOT HIM
SOME FRESH AVOCADOS.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
- WHERE YOU GUYS HEADING TO?
YOU GOT SO MUCH STUFF
IN YOUR CAR.
- I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE THINKING ABOUT
MAKING A MOVE.
- WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO?
- WE HAVEN'T QUITE
FIGURED IT OUT.
MAYBE PORTLAND.
- OH, I LOVE PORTLAND.
I MET AN OWL THERE ONCE THAT--
YEAH, REALLY SHOWED ME
WHERE TO GO, YOU KNOW?
- YOU MET AN OWL?
- YEAH.
OR IT MET ME.
- RIGHT ON.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
IT WAS REALLY NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT TO COME IN?
MAKE YOU SOME TEA. NO?
- NO. NO.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
- OKAY.
- HEY, TELL HIM HE WAS RIGHT.
- TELL HIM HE WAS
THE RESPONSIBLE ONE.
- [laughs]
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TELL HIM THAT.
- BYE.
BYE.
[light guitar music]
¶ ¶
- [whistling]
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com