* (Music playing)
* (Radio playing)
(Horn honking)
What the fuck?
(Mumbling)
- (Insects chirping)
- (Wolf howls)
(Mumbling)
Better than the radio.
(Laughing)
Hey, lady, you need a ride?
Come on.
Hey, Jesus, girl.
You all right?
You're all wet.
Where you going?
Er, yeah, okay, me too, me too.
(Baby murmuring)
You got a baby there?
Is it a boy or a girl?
Nice, I guess you're not
really the talkative type, huh?
It's okay, let me put
on some tunes, huh?
(Tuning radio)
What's wrong with the radio?
(Turns radio off)
Looks like... Whoa, looks like
there's an accident up ahead.
Wait here, I gotta see
if everybody's okay.
God, looks like...
This looks bad.
(Squelching)
Hey, hello?
Aw, man. Hey, hello?
Hey, you okay?
Miss?
(Under his breath)
Shit.
Hey, miss, you okay? Miss?
Oh, God.
(Baby groaning)
(Baby screaming)
(Tires screeching)
(Police radio chattering)
What do we got?
Well, we got three dead.
Looks like car one
side-swiped car two.
Car two hits the pole,
Sends this woman out the window,
Baby follows.
Baby? Jesus.
Yeah and the weird thing is,
Car one guy actually
seems to have gone off
And then come back
a little bit later.
Hope it wasn't to apologize.
So he finds her and then
gets hit by a third car.
Police Officer:
We got a lead on that?
(Dog barking)
- (Keys jingling)
- (Sarah sighs)
Sarah: I can never
remember which one it is.
Chad: You must be in
charge of a lot of doors.
Sarah: (Laughing)
Yeah. Ah, here we go.
Chad: Finally.
(Door unlocking and opening)
(Slamming)
(Sighs)
Okay.
Sarah: Sorry we had
to use the back door.
The only one that
hasn't been condemned.
That's okay.
I'm just glad you could
show me the place.
Well, follow me.
Watch your step there, please.
(Rat squeaking)
Sarah: We'll just continue
through here.
Chad: Okay.
Okay, so this is it.
The crown-jewel
of Wayville Hill.
Erm, built in 1827.
Just five years before the
cholera epidemic of 1832.
- (Slamming)
- It's charming.
Yeah. So, of course,
the power is off.
So is the heat.
The city just can't afford
to keep the boilers running.
But we can turn that
all back on for you,
If you choose to use
this in your movie.
Yeah, no worries.
I like it just the way it is.
Good.
Okay, well we should get going.
If you'll just come with me.
Each nurse would be in charge
of one floor to herself.
She'd have one or two people
Below her to help out.
But that way, it kept things
Nice and consistent
for everyone.
Chad: This place is huge.
Sarah: Yeah, three
wards, 500,000 square feet.
And enough equipment to treat
hundreds of sick patients.
Chad: It doesn't
look that old,
For something built
almost 200 years ago.
Sarah: Well, the
building has gradually
Been renovated over the years.
I mean up until the county
closed it, 32 years ago.
We're gonna go in here.
And what happened here?
Nothing you didn't show in
your movies, Mr. Winchester.
Chad: Oh, so you're
familiar with my work?
Yeah, a little bit.
Got guts.
(Chuckles)
(Slamming)
Sarah: You know,
this institution
Helped a lot of people.
Chad: I heard they weren't
always that helpful here.
Sarah: Yeah, well it's like
my dad used to always say,
"You can't make an omelet
without cracking a few eggs."
Chad: Yeah, I guess.
Oh, yeah!
Welcome to the asylum.
I'm just gonna get some
video footage here, okay?
Sarah: Yeah. Yeah.
Chad: Okay, let's do this.
Hello to my future self,
To the producers
watching this with me.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Mom.
(Chuckles)
I'm standing in one of
the freakiest places
I've seen in a very long time.
Wayville Hill Sanitarium,
West Virginia.
Well, fortunately not everything
is so depressing down here.
(Laughing)
Hey, it's Grandma's upholstery.
So according to a friend
of a friend of mine,
Who lives in the county,
Wayville Hill Sanitarium
became infamous
For its atrocious experiments
conducted on the patients,
Between around 1925 to 1928.
The most popular case is
the one of a Mary Weaver.
It's even said that Mary's ghost
Still roams these corridors
searching for something.
(Laughing)
Classic.
Here she is.
Sarah: Come
on, it's this way.
So, according to the
medical archives,
Mary was in room 502,
Which should be at the
end of this corridor.
Ah, here it is.
Oh, this is great.
(Laughing)
Oh, wow!
Oh, my God.
Even the cheesiest horror flick
Wouldn't have
something this obvious.
Oh, this is good stuff.
Did you do this for me?
Sarah: Don't
flatter yourself.
Chad: Here, give
me a hand with this.
Sarah: Okay.
(Eerie breathing)
(Bumping)
Well, that sucks.
Well, I don't know
what you were hoping for.
I don't know,
something sexier.
Can you introduce
yourself to the camera?
Hi, I'm Sarah Davis.
I work for the county of
Tucker, West Virginia.
Chad: Tell us where we are.
We are in room 502 of
Wayville Hill Sanitarium.
Chad: Can you explain
to the people watching this
Why I so very badly
wanted to come here?
Because of the
story of Mary Weaver.
Chad: And what is that?
Back in 1927, the body
of nurse Mary Weaver
Was found dead in this room,
Laying in a pool
of her own blood.
It's said that she
committed suicide
After a psychotic breakdown,
Following the
murder of her baby.
After she became pregnant,
She was admitted to this
hospital for anxiety.
The doctor in charge believed
her unborn baby was the devil.
So immediately
upon giving birth,
He slit the baby's throat
as she watched helplessly.
He didn't even bother to cut
the umbilical cord first.
She completely lost it,
And was locked in this
room, to rot and die.
It's said that she just
rocked back and forth,
Begging for them to
give her baby back.
One night, she managed
to break the window,
And using a shard of glass,
She disemboweled
herself completely.
Chad: Cut.
Damn, you're good.
That was good.
What about the other rooms?
Erm, yes, well, the infirmary
is down the hall.
I'm in.
(Eerie breathing)
Chad: So, is it true that
if you listen closely,
Sometimes you can hear her
hum songs to her dead kid?
(Laughs nervously)
Sarah: Well,
yeah, that's part of
The folklore of this place.
But mainly it's
just scary stories,
Told to frighten little kids.
Chad: Well, that's a shame.
Maybe if we're lucky,
We'll get a chance
to hear something.
(Chad humming)
Mary? Mary?
Oh, look at that.
That's a creepy shot.
(Chad humming)
Mary: (Whispering)
Sarah.
Chad: Hey,
I think I found it.
(Gasping)
God!
Chad: (Laughing)
What?
Come on. Follow me.
Sarah: Okay.
(Wheelchair squeaking)
- (Rats squeaking)
- (Dripping)
Chad: Now this
is more like it.
Do you think this is where
the doctor killed that baby?
Sarah: Maybe.
If I remember correctly,
This is the only place
in the sanitarium
Where a woman could give birth.
You know a lot
about this place, huh?
Yeah, my father used to bring
me here a lot, as a child.
You know,
before they closed it down.
Really? He worked here?
Like his father and
grandfather before him.
I am the only one
that didn't go...
(Glass crunching)
Into medicine.
So, would your
great grandfather
Have been here during
the Mary events?
Sarah: Yeah, I guess.
I've never really
given it much thought.
That's my great grandfather.
It looks like he's the only
doctor in all these photos.
Yeah, that's because
he was the only doctor.
The county couldn't
afford any more.
Shit.
So the doctor that killed
Mary's baby would have been...
My great grandfather.
(Screaming)
(Eerie breathing)
That was not a hum.
What the fuck?
That was not a fucking hum!
We need to leave.
We need to leave, now!
(Slamming)
What the fuck was that?
Who's there?
(Eerie whispering)
I said who's there!
Oh, shit.
Mary: (Whispering)
My baby.
Chad: You gotta be
fucking kidding me.
(Screaming)
Fuck, come on.
Why won't this open?
(Growling)
Mary: (Whispering)
Sarah.
- (Growling)
- (Gasps)
(Mary whispering)
No, what do you want from me?
(Crying)
Leave me alone.
* (Tinkling music plays)
(Mary humming)
(Eerie breathing)
(Whispering)
Give me back my baby.
(Dripping)
Sarah: Chad? Chad?
(Whimpers)
(Crying)
Oh, my God.
Mary: (Whispering)
Sarah.
My baby.
(Sarah screaming)
Mary: (Whispering)
My baby.
Sarah.
(Sarah screaming)
Give me back my baby.
(Mary humming)
I want my baby.
(Yelling)
Give me back my baby!
(Slamming)
(Gurgling)
(Screaming)
Man: I don't
like this, Erin.
I'm coming home.
Erin: I'm fine.
We knew this was gonna
happen sooner or later.
It's fine.
I mean, even if you
rented a car and drove,
You wouldn't be here
until tomorrow morning.
Man: Let me call
Kelly, she'll at least...
I don't need a babysitter.
I'm fine.
Look, I haven't heard
from them in a long time.
I'm sure there not
just gonna suddenly
Show up because you're not here.
I'm safe.
I'm inside. I'll just lock
the doors and be just fine.
Man: Will you promise
me you'll take at least one?
Yes.
(Deep breath)
(Beeping)
(Water running)
TV: Tell me I'm
stupid and pathetic
And just leave me alone.
TV: They've
investigated my mother.
Thank God she's dead.
TV: Those are really...
TV: They have
writing samples...
(Thudding)
(Banging)
(Water stops running)
(Floorboards creaking)
(Water running)
(Banging)
(Floor creaking)
(Phone ringing)
Apparition: Put it down.
You know they can't help you.
Operator: 911,
what's your emergency?
Apparition: They'll
only put you away again.
Operator: Hello?
Hello, is anybody there?
Sorry, wrong number.
Apparition:
It's been a while.
Do you miss us?
Why can't you
just leave me alone?
Apparition: (Child's voice)
We're a part of you.
We always will be.
I don't need you anymore.
Apparition: You've
always needed us.
You're nothing without us.
I'm not listening to you.
You're not here.
Go away.
(Crying)
(Splashing)
(Splashing stops)
(Floorboards creaking)
(Phone ringing)
Philip: Hello?
Clerk: Good evening, sir.
Just checking to see if you
need anything in your room.
No, I'm fine.
Clerk: We can give
you a wake-up call
In the morning if you want one.
No, I'm fine.
Clerk: Okay, well enjoy
your stay at Sleep Well Hotel.
Thank you.
Clerk: Bye bye.
TV: During what can
only be described as
A crime of passion and jealousy.
Police describe the scene
as tragic and frantic.
Police in Wichita are
looking for this man,
Mr. Philip Davenport, age 31.
He's believed to be at
large in the metro area.
And he's wanted
in connection with
The deaths of at least 12 women.
- (Knocking at door)
- Police are urging anyone
With information
on his whereabouts
To please call
Crime Stoppers at...
Hello?
(Knocking at door)
No, thank you.
I said, no, thank you.
(Police siren)
Cop: Get down on the ground!
Now! Get down!
(Yelling)
(Knocking)
Philip: Shit.
Who is it?
I told you I didn't
want room service.
All right? The sign
says do not disturb.
Do you speak English?
I'm trying to get
some sleep in here.
Clerk: Front desk.
Yeah, I wanna
make a complaint.
Clerk: Okay, sir,
what's your concern?
My concern is your housekeeper
keeps knocking on my door.
All right? I told you
not to send anyone.
I am trying to sleep.
Clerk: Sir, all the housekeepers
left a few minutes ago.
It's probably just a kid from
One of the rooms next to yours.
There's a policeman on-site,
I could send him over?
No, no. Look, it's fine.
Thanks. Look, I just
wanna get some rest.
Clerk: All right,
good night, sir.
(Knocking)
Philip: Hello?
Who is it?
Please, please leave me alone.
I just wanna be left alone.
No way.
I'm not in the mood for tricks.
Who are you?
I couldn't control myself,
all right?
There's nothing good
about what I do.
I do it because I have to.
It was you.
You must have killed the others.
The police said there were 12.
I only killed seven.
You're just a copycat.
Trying to take
credit for my work.
I don't take
pleasure in killing.
I just let things
get out of hand.
I bet you do it for
enjoyment, don't you?
All right, if you must know.
I do enjoy it a little.
Not as much as you, I bet.
Not even close.
Who are you?
How do you know me?
Just leave me alone!
(Knocking at door)
(Gunshots)
(Thudding)
Shit.
(Phone ringing)
Hello?
(Eerie whispering)
What are you?
I understand imitation's the
greatest form of flattery,
But why are you helping me?
(Eerie whispering)
Coming for me?
(Police siren)
Where do you come from?
(Eerie whispering)
What?
Join you? I don't understand.
How? Where?
(Eerie whispering)
(Clanking)
Is this where you come from?
Partners.
(Distant yelling)
(Clanking)
* Won't live a lie
* And refuse to accept it
* Can't move
can't feel nothing *
* But the weight of the world
* I'm glued to this scene
* Can you take back
* All of the time you
didn't know you lost *
* Would you give back
* For one more chance
to take a chance *
* Don't worry, don't worry
* I'll be just fine
Hey, wait,
turn it down, turn it down
It's coming up here.
On the right.
Oh, hey, let me guess.
Is it after a tree?
My god, what are you five?
Yeah.
So, Carissa,
pretty cool of your parents
To let us use the
camp for the weekend.
Yeah.
Jess: Did you come
up here a lot as a kid?
No, not really.
Not since my parents
got a divorce.
I'm sorry.
(Giggling)
Who's ready for an
awesome weekend, huh?
(Laughing)
Hell yeah, woo!
(Music blaring)
* Don't worry, don't worry
* I'll be just fine
Jess: You ready to go in?
Yes.
Yes, yes I am.
Derek: Amazing, it's incredible!
Tristan: Yeah, don't worry.
We'll take your stuff.
- Derek: Thank you!
- Tristan: Yep.
- (Jess screaming)
- Derek: The orange bag.
- Come on!
- (Splashing)
- Jess: Oh, my God!
Derek: Feels good, right?
Jess: Oh, my God!
- Oh my god it's...
- (Screaming and splashing)
Your pill.
There.
Does it feel good to be back?
Talking about the
cabin or in general?
Both, I guess.
I guess I'm not sure.
Do you want to talk about it?
What's there to talk about?
Look, I'm sorry.
I just guess I don't know
how to talk about it yet.
I don't know how
I feel, you know?
I want to have a
good time, really.
That's the point, right?
Listen, maybe
we shouldn't have
Come up here so soon after...
No, it'll be great.
I'll adjust, okay?
Thank you.
For what?
For being you.
For loving me.
Now let's have a good time.
I'll be fine, I promise.
Last one in
the water's a rotten egg.
- It's cold, oh, my God.
- It's beautiful.
- (Yelling)
- (Laughing)
- (Splashing)
- Don't, don't, don't, don't.
- Come on, come on.
(Screaming)
(Scratching)
(Vomiting)
(Toilet flushing)
(Footsteps)
(Scratching)
Derek: I'll be
right back, guys.
(Scratching)
(Banging)
Hey. Scare you?
No. Towel?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
You look tired.
I didn't get much sleep.
A lot on your mind?
There was something
in the walls last night.
It was scratching.
Raccoon?
I'm not sure. Maybe.
No one's really been up
here to care for the place.
Well, you want
me to take a look?
Sure.
Where'd you hear it?
Carissa: It's in the bedroom.
Okay.
(Knocking)
Well, I don't see anything.
You didn't hear anything?
No. You have a ladder?
Maybe it's in the attic.
Yeah.
Derek: So it's like,
it folds out, right?
How does it...?
(Laughing)
Well,
there's your problem, Riss.
Isn't that a bat house?
How long has that been there?
You okay?
What?
Carissa: Don't you
think they're, kind of,
All over each other?
Are you kidding?
It'd be the same if it was us.
That doesn't make you worry?
Riss, okay...
Look, I know you've been
kind of messed up lately,
Dealing with a lot of stuff.
But that...
That guy, there...
That is something you don't
have to worry about, okay?
You're right.
Yeah.
You're always right.
You always know how to
make me feel better.
Yes, I do.
You know what?
I think it's grilling time.
Mm-hmm.
(Strumming guitar)
This reminds me
of freshman year.
You guys remember that?
How could I forget?
June 22nd, Bobby Mitchell's...
Hey, isn't that the
first time you guys...
You told him? Jerk!
Yes, of course I told him.
It was high school.
And like you didn't tell Riss.
Riss?
Sorry, what was that?
It's nothing.
I don't think we
were friends then.
I think I'm gonna
go lay down for a bit.
You okay?
I'm tired. It's getting late.
I'll go with you.
No, stay. Have fun.
Are you sure?
Yes, now have a good time.
I'll be better tomorrow.
She's been acting
really strange lately.
Do you guys think she's
gonna try something?
Jess, please!
Give her some more
credit than that.
What is your problem?
Nothing.
Tristan: Guys, she's fine.
She's just going through a
bit of a bad spot right now.
I gotta give her her
meds in like a half hour.
So, I'll check on her then.
Man, she's lucky to have you.
Shit, I would be
lucky to have you.
Tristan: More for us.
(Scratching)
Stupid fucking bats.
I'll never sleep.
Tristan: Hey.
Do you hear that?
Bats in the wall,
they just keep scratching.
- There's...
- Shh! Listen.
There's nothing here.
I swear they were there.
You must have scared them off.
Why are you back so soon?
I came to give you your meds.
I can do it myself, you know.
I'm okay now, really.
I appreciate all
you're doing for me,
But you can't treat
me like a child.
Yeah, yeah. You're right, I...
Sorry.
Okay? I do trust you.
Here.
Hey, get some sleep.
All right? I'll make us
breakfast in the morning.
Okay, I love you.
Tristan: I love you, too.
(Scratching)
Carissa? What are you doing?
(Scratching stops)
Carissa: (Sighs)
Oh, my God.
I had a nightmare.
I must have panicked.
Tristan: What are you
doing with your pills?
It was the scratching.
It started again. I panicked.
(Scratching)
(Screaming)
- (Jess screaming)
- I got you something!
Morning, sunshine.
It's breakfast.
He's a trophy is what he is.
I'm gonna smell
like fish all fucking day.
Derek: Morning, Riss.
Morning.
Derek: How'd you sleep?
What do you think?
This is Lance.
Lance Bass.
(Laughing)
(Guys chattering)
Tristan: I think
it's the same thing.
Derek: I am taking a piss,
so, be right back.
Babe, you should
probably take your meds.
Can you stop doing that?
I thought we talked about this.
All right, it's just that
you scared me yesterday.
I didn't know how many you took.
Why? What happened?
Are you serious, Tristan?
I took one, okay?
I'm sorry I didn't ask
your permission first.
Whoa, didn't mean
to piss you off.
You've been acting
weird all weekend.
Me? You've got to be joking.
After what I just came out of?
Yeah, so I overdosed.
And now I feel like all
you've done is babysit me.
Like you've all put
me under a microscope.
Well, you have been acting
kind of strange lately.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Am I not perky enough for you?
You've been looking at me
like I'm some sort of psycho!
Oh, do you think she
might try something?
I didn't think
you could hear me.
Carissa: Well,
sweetheart, I did.
And I've noticed how you've been
All over my boyfriend this
weekend, you fucking whore!
Bitch!
Are you seriously gonna let
her talk to me like this?
Fuck you!
Guys, what the hell's
going on? Where's Riss?
Why would you tell her?
Shut up, Jess.
She doesn't know.
Doesn't know what?
What's going on?
What the hell's going on? Jess?
You...
You slept with
Tristan, didn't you?
Derek, it was only once, okay?
I cannot believe
I didn't see this.
You know what? Carissa saw
it the whole fucking time!
How could you do this to me?
How could you do
this to Carissa?
It was a mistake, Derek!
Derek: No! You know what?
We are done!
This is fucking done!
And you...
Fuck! Fuck!
(Car engine starts)
Tristan: Everything was fine.
You had to open your mouth.
Babe, I'm sorry.
Don't call me that. Don't, no.
(Whispering)
Mistake.
Tristan.
(Scratching)
(Slamming)
(Carissa whimpering)
(Carissa screaming)
Tristan: Carissa?
Jess, get a towel or a
blanket or something.
Okay. Okay.
Go to my room and
get a clean shirt.
It's just her period.
Tristan, her pills are
all over the floor up there.
What?
Baby, what did you do?
Call Derek.
What if he doesn't answer?
Leave a message.
* Fuck you, you're dead to me
(Phone buzzing)
* Stand in my way,
you're like a barricade *
* But I, but I,
but I won't stop *
What?
Jess: Derek, you
need to come back.
What do you want me to say?
Jess: No, Derek,
it's Carissa.
There's blood everywhere.
(Crying)
We need you here.
Derek?
Fuck.
(Eerie whispering)
(Vomiting)
(Toilet flushing)
(Eerie whispering)
(Scratching)
(Gasping)
(Choking)
(Scratching)
(Footsteps)
(Eerie whispering)
(Door opening)
(Jess sobbing)
(Scratching)
I'm so sorry.
Carissa?
Don't you hear it?
Carissa, what are
you talking about?
The scratching.
Don't you hear it?
Is that blood?
Where's Tristan?
(Jess screaming)
(Dragging)
(Thudding)
(Carissa groaning)
(Screaming)
(Carissa screaming)
Carissa: Please,
make it stop.
(Groaning)
(Screaming)
Derek: No!
(Slicing)
(Eerie screaming)
Police Operator: 911,
state your emergency.
911. Hello?
Is someone there?
Yes, I'm here.
Someone's been on
my lawn for about,
I don't know, like,
30 minutes now.
Operator: Okay,
ma'am. What's your name?
My name is Melissa,
Melissa Crow.
Operator: Okay, Melissa.
Are you able to identify
the person outside?
Can you describe
what they're wearing?
It looks like a man.
But there's a mask on
his face, if it's a man.
He's wearing white
shirt and pants.
He looks pretty dirty.
Operator: Has this man
threatened you at all?
Is he carrying a weapon?
Yeah, he has a knife.
Operator: Okay, Melissa.
We're sending someone over,
Based on the location
of your cell phone.
Someone should be there
within a few minutes.
I need you to stay
on the line with me
Until the police arrive.
Are all of your doors
locked? Are you safe?
Melissa: Yeah,
my doors are locked.
I'm just in my living
room right now so...
Oh, my God.
I think he can see
me through my window.
Is anyone gonna be here soon?
Just cause he's standing there,
And he's walking closer
and he's right there.
He can see me.
- Operator: Okay, Melissa.
- Melissa: Yeah?
Operator: Please
try to remain calm,
And get to somewhere safe.
Are you alone in the house?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm alone, just me.