911.
What's your emergency?
H-Help.
There's...
accident...
I can't hear you.
What's your location?
There's been an accident.
Please come now.
What is the nature
of your emergency?
Hello? Are you still
on the line, sir?
No. Kind of ate way
too much at dinner.
Oh, okay.
Very special.
Just a little.
All right.
I'd like
to propose a toast.
To Christine on her
high school graduation
and her admission
to Oregon University.
Cheers.
Our little girl's
growing up.
I love you guys.
Oh, a little something
from your mom and me.
Is this
what I think it is?
I don't know.
It's exactly
what I wanted!
I think that's
enough wine for you,
graduation girl.
Thank you, guys.
Um, well, since
we're all in such
a great mood,
I thought it would
be a good time for us
to talk about something
that means a lot
to Christine and I.
Um, as you guys know,
I love her so much,
and... and we really feel
like now is...
is the right opportunity
for us to start
our family together,
and we really want
your blessing for that.
I think it's important
for a young woman
like Christine
to finish
her education
before taking
a serious step
like marriage.
Mom, please.
I want Christine
to have her independence.
James, I can't
think of anybody
I'd rather have
in the family than you,
but Ellen's
probably right.
You both should wait.
I completely
respect your guys'
point of view,
um, but I
feel that...
that I've
been on my own since
I was 15 years old,
and I have a great job
at the mill,
and I know I can provide
in every way possible.
James...
life is far more difficult
than you realize.
To this day, Doug wishes
that he had completed
a proper education.
Look, I know
that I didn't complete
the proper education...
It was my education
that allowed me
to launch
a very prosperous
publishing company.
James, I understand
your perspective.
I do. I get it,
but Ellen's right.
You're both too young.
Wait.
That doesn't sound good.
I would like
to get home before
this gets worse.
James, buddy,
would you mind being
the designated driver?
I think you're
the only sober one
at this table.
Yeah, sure, Mr. Webb.
That's fine.
"So foul and fair a day
I have not seen."
"Macbeth."
James, look,
I'm sorry, okay?
I had no idea they were
gonna react that way.
Yeah, well, I kind of
expected you to chime in
instead of just letting your
mom tear me a new one.
I mean, we talked about
what we were gonna say.
Okay, but you did an amazing
job in there, okay?
I'm... I didn't have any idea that
it was gonna happen that way.
Yeah, well...
I'll talk to her.
Well, your parents are
never gonna respect me,
'cause I didn't get
a precious college
education like you did.
That's not fair, James.
Well, I know you're
just gonna go and find
some trust-fund frat boy
and leave me, so...
Is that what
you really think?
James, you're the man
that I want to marry.
I love you.
I would never do that.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I love you.
Christine, let's go!
Watch your step now.
Drive safe.
Look at our sleeping
beauty up there.
Doug, don't break
her present before she
gets a chance to use it.
Will you relax?
When it rains this hard,
it usually only lasts
a few minutes.
I'm sick
of your comments
about my lack
of education in front
of our daughter.
I don't like your tone.
My tone?
Yes,
your condescending tone.
You started it.
You sound like a child.
Then stop treating me
like a child.
James!
James, there's a train!
We don't know
if there's any more
brain damage.
She has a small blood clot...
...in her brain,
so we have to keep
a close eye on her.
Dr. David,
please stop
in the west wing
patient lobby, Dr. David.
Hi.
Hey, Christine.
It's me. It's Bill.
Susan's here, too.
Hello, sweetheart.
Honey, you've been in a very
serious accident.
Where's everyone else?
James is
right down the hall.
He's doing real good.
What about Mom and Dad?
Bill, what about
Mom and Dad?
Bill, what happened?
No.
No. No.
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry, Dave. I...
Be careful in there.
I just mopped
the shower area.
Okay.
I'll just be a minute.
Get a move on, girl.
I got places to go.
Pervert.
Dave, where the fuck
are my clothes?!
James, pick up your phone.
Come on. Come on!
Oh, my God.
What?
No.
Christine.
No! No.
Fuck.
Hi, honey.
Hi.
Anything from
the state lottery?
No, no such luck.
Rats.
Oh, Christine got
a letter today, though,
from the Office
of Student Housing.
Huh.
Looks like a dorm
probably opened up.
Sounds like you're
trying to get rid of her.
No.
I just thought
you should know.
Do you want anything?
Baby, what happened?
What are you doing here?
Oh, my God.
How did you get here?
You were there!
I mean,
I don't understand!
What are you
talking about?
At the pool!
The pool?
I... I heard your
cellphone ring there.
My cellphone?
I told you yesterday
it got stolen
at the mill, remember?
I put it on the table,
and somebody took it.
I don't know
what happened to it.
Okay, okay.
Calm down, okay?
Take a breath.
I am breathing, okay?
Okay, well...
You don't understand, okay?
My clothes were stolen,
and I tried to call you
to get you to help me, a-and
your cellphone rang there.
And then somebody knocked me
in the pool, and then they
chased me to the car!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's going on?
How'd you get
in here, asshole?
Bill, just, please,
it's my fault, okay?
I'll explain later.
Yeah, thanks
for the backup, Bill.
I got this one
under control.
Bill, please.
Guys, stop.
Just please leave.
Dickhead.
Sweetie...
I didn't mean
to scare you.
I know.
I'm glad you're here.
I just wasn't expecting you,
that's all.
Hey...
It doesn't make sense.
Who do you think did it?
I don't know.
I don't really
want to talk about it
anymore, though, okay?
Okay, that's fine.
I just want
to go to sleep.
All right.
Sorry.
It's all right.
Okay, night.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Thought you
were going out.
Yeah.
I am.
Here you go.
How's that?
Thank you.
Of course.
It's good to see you.
So, Mr. Anderson,
how's Ryan doing?
As you know, he's still
at the university
studying
English literature,
and, uh, he's getting
pretty good grades,
but he still doesn't
have a social life,
and he spends
most of his time just
locked up in his room.
Have there been
any improvements
in his behavior?
No.
In fact,
it's getting worse.
Worse in... in what way?
The violent behavior.
Dr. Webb,
I'm getting concerned
for the safety
of my daughter.
So based on
your sessions with him,
what's...
what's wrong with him?
Well...
Ryan is suffering
from extreme bouts
of frustration
that are accompanied
by a very distorted
sense of reality.
Uh, during these episodes,
he is unable to distinguish
real from unreal.
In other words, your son
has delusional paranoia.
Dr. Webb, before we
go any further,
there's some things
you need to know.
Well, the truth is
my wife disappeared
under what they
called suspicious
circumstances,
and to this day,
no one knows what
really happened to her.
What was their relationship
at the time?
You're sick!
You need help!
There's nothing
wrong with me!
Stop it, Ryan!
Leave me alone!
Stop it!
Let go of me!
Ryan,
you're hurting me!
unlock the door!
I'm okay, Dad.
Damn it,
you open this door
right now!
Dad, I'm okay.
It was a nightmare.
Ryan, listen to me,
buddy.
Just listen
to me, please.
You can't
do this anymore.
Now I want you
to unlock the door,
and I want you
to let me in.
Dad, go back to bed.
Ryan, talk to me.
Go back to fucking bed!
I can't peek?
No peeking.
None of that.
Okay, don't trip.
Don't trip. Whoa.
Whoa what?
I'll tell you.
Ready?
Okay.
Check it out.
What do you think,
huh?
Whose is this?
This is the bedroom
right here, okay?
Okay.
And we got campus
two blocks away,
and we got plenty
of time to furnish it,
and when we're married,
you can move in.
It's amazing.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You like it?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
I can't wait
to marry you.
This has been
the most amazing day ever.
Well, I got you,
didn't I?
I wasn't expecting it.
James, what
would you do
if you lost me?
What?
Could you ever
fall in love
with someone else?
I don't think I could,
and I need to know
that you feel the same.
How could you
even ask me that?
I proposed to you,
didn't I?
I know.
I love you.
Do I get to pick
my fiancée up for dinner
tomorrow night?
No. I want
to cook for us
tomorrow night, okay?
Okay. I get off
at, like, 5:00.
Okay. Just
come over after.
All right.
Okay.
Christine.
Give me the ring.
Give me
the fucking ring!
Oh, my God.
Open the door!
Bill! Open the door!
Open the...
Oh, my God.
You're wide awake.
What are
you thinking?
Just wondering
who'd stalk my sister.
Are you sure that's
what's happened?
What does that mean?
Ever since the accident,
she's been
displaying signs of
post-traumatic stress.
I really think
she needs help from
a professional, honey.
I really think
she's a strong girl,
and she just needs
our support.
She has our support.
I...
I just wish
you'd think about it.
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
You know
what tonight is?
It's a prime night.
You want to try?
Um, sure.
James.
Babe, what are
you doing here?
Sweetie, it's dangerous
for you to be here.
I told you that. You're not
supposed to come here.
Please don't be
mad at me, okay?
What is it?
James,
my ring was stolen.
W-When?
Last night
after you left,
someone came
after me again.
Why didn't you tell me?
Who was it?
Was it the guy
from the pool?
I can't tell you, James.
I can't tell you,
'cause you're gonna think
that I'm crazy, okay?
Baby, no, I'm not.
I'm not.
What is it?
James, I saw my father.
My father was there, okay?
He's the one who took
the ring from me.
I don't understand.
So be honest.
Do you think
I'm going crazy?
Sweetie,
you're not crazy.
What the hell?
I'm on it!
James!
Help me! James!
Could somebody just
fucking help me!
Wait. What...
Somebody!
What's going on?
I saw him again!
What's...
I saw him!
He was in here!
Who was in here?
Is there somebody
in this house?
in my house?!
Yes!
I saw him.
James, come with me.
Okay, Ed. Yeah, thanks.
Thanks a lot.
What did he say,
honey?
Said he's gonna
keep an eye on her
till we figure out
what's going on.
I don't know
We checked the place
up and down.
I couldn't find
a handprint, footprint,
broken lock, nothing.
Honey, this is
the third episode
without any evidence
of an actual threat.
Meaning what?
Well, you know
hallucinations
are a sure sign
to a psychotic break.
Psychotic break?
Listen to you.
What?
She's not making
this shit up.
I'm not saying she is.
Why does this have
to be about Christine?
It was dark. Anyone could
have been there.
Where was James when
the lights went out?
You're taking this
the wrong way.
You know, I gotta
be honest with you.
I think you're
jealous of her.
You think...
I'm jealous of Christine?
Why would I be jealous
of Christine?
Because she's
getting married,
gonna have a family
of her own,
and apparently
that's something
that we're having
a hard time doing.
Fuck you, Bill!
Fuck you!
Fuck you.
By the pricking
of my thumbs,
something wicked
this way comes.
You destroyed our family.
How dare you disobey me?
You're a disgrace.
Lying whore.
Susan!
My gun is missing!
Okay, I'm sorry
about last night,
but did you
take my gun?
Yeah.
I was planning
on shooting you
in your sleep
last night.
This is not funny.
This is serious.
I can be suspended
for a lost firearm.
Okay, look,
I didn't take the gun.
It's probably
around the house.
I'm telling you
I've looked everywhere!
It is not here!
Okay, last night,
when the lights went out,
where was it?
I know where it was.
Prick.
Campus security.
Ed Young's office.
I'm sorry, Mr. Webb.
He's in a meeting
So then I got out
of the pool, and...
Mm-hmm. Watch this.
Never turns toward
the security cameras.
Never shows his face.
This is somebody
who knows the building,
knows the setup,
where the cameras are.
Is there any way
to enhance this?
No. It's too dark.
But don't worry about it.
We turned it over
to local law enforcement.
They're better equipped
to handle this stuff.
Yeah. Thanks.
I appreciate it.
You'll be hearing
from a detective
later this week,
okay?
Bye.
Hey, Bill. It's Ed.
Oh, hey, Ed.
Did you get a chance
to talk to Christine?
Yeah. She just left.
Could you I.D. anyone?
Nah, but I
know who it is.
Tell me
it's James Campbell,
'cause I need a reason
to put a bullet
in that kid's head.
Who?
Her boyfriend.
I heard them arguing
after the attack.
She can place
his cellphone
at the scene that night.
She never mentioned that.
She's in denial.
That's interesting,
'cause I got
two hooded suspects on tape.
What?
I'm thinking both of our boys
were at the pool
the other night.
Call you back. I gotta go.
Okay, Ed. Thanks a lot.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, it's good.
So how long
is your shift?
My shift, Donna?
My shift lasts all night.
Oh.
See about that, huh?
Johnson!
Dave Johnson!
Hey. Unh!
Johnson!
Aah!
Hey, sweetheart.
Hi.
You want to talk?
Sure.
I miss them so much.
Sometimes I want
to wake up,
and it'd all
just be a bad dream.
Life can be
so cruel sometimes.
Yeah.
What's that?
Pictures
from my graduation.
They're
the last pictures
I have of them.
My family was
everything to me.
I want to have a family
with James one day.
I want to have kids
and grow old together.
That's my dream, too.
Might not ever happen.
You may not
know this, but...
I made a promise
to my mom and to myself
that I wouldn't
be intimate with a guy
until I was married.
That's a really
tough promise to keep.
I'm proud of you.
I just can't believe
they're not gonna be
there on my wedding day.
My dad won't be
there to...
to walk me
down the aisle
and give me away,
and my mom won't
be there to help me
pick out my dress.
They will be there.
They wouldn't miss it
for the world.
You have to believe me.
I promise.
Thanks.
All right, come on.
Let's put
this stuff away.
Yeah. Yeah.
Get some rest.
Yeah.
Ah, I got it.
I got it.
Excuse me.
Officer Webb?
Do I know you?
I'm Sergeant Ellis
with Internal Affairs.
Please step
out of the vehicle.
What's this about?
Do you know a member
of the EPD by the name
of Ed Young?
Yeah. So?
When was the last time
you had any contact
with Officer Young?
Called him last night.
I didn't reach him. Why?
Officer Young is dead,
Mr. Webb.
What?
He was killed yesterday.
An Oregon State Police
service revolver
registered in your name
was found at the scene.
My gun was stolen.
I've read the reports.
Excessive force
three times.
Questionable shootings.
This conversation is over.
James, stop.
You're being bad.
Baby, don't.
Don't. Mm.
No, James. Stop!
Get off her, asshole.
What the...
What the fuck, man?
Bill, what are
you doing?
You could have
hurt him!
Are you
following me? Bill?!
Yes, I'm following you.
This lover boy's
in some serious shit,
and now we both are.
Ed Young's been killed,
and my weapon and
James' cellphone
were found at the scene.
Yeah, well,
his cellphone was
stolen the other day,
so obviously
it wasn't him.
And you believe that?
Yeah, I do believe that.
Well, for your sake,
I hope he can prove it.
Hey, so listen,
I got a call from
a detective yesterday.
He asked if you were
working here Thursday.
Ah, shit.
Are you serious?
No worries.
I covered for you.
Ah, thank you,
Mr. Anderson.
Hey, listen,
I don't want you working
with your head
hurting like that.
Damn,
that was a cheap shot.
You listen to me.
If that Bill Webb
gives you
any more trouble,
if he even
looks at you funny,
you let me know,
'cause I got
some boys that'll put
some manners on him.
Might have to
take you up on that.
Hey, could I ask you
something, Mr. Anderson?
Shoot.
Why you always
looking out for me?
Well, sometimes,
I look at you,
and I see
a little bit of me
when I was your age.
Tell you the truth,
I been hoping some
of that would rub off
on my son, but...
Anyway, help Ryan with
the overnight shipment.
Then you take the rest
of the day off, okay?
Okay. I appreciate it.
Ryan!
Yeah?
Come help James.
Sure.
So my dad says
you got engaged.
Congratulations.
Yeah. Thanks, man.
She's hot.
I see her on campus
from time to time.
I bet you do.
I'll have
to introduce myself
next time I see her.
Yeah, you should.
Hi, sweetheart.
Let me know what time you'll
be home for dinner tonight.
Love you.
No more tears now.
I will think
upon revenge.
I'm sorry.
I know
it's my fault.
Hello, Bill.
I knew
I'd find you here.
You think you know me.
Listen, I know we
didn't grow up together,
and I was in the Army
by the time that
but, uh, I just
thought I would try...
They're trying to stop me.
What?
The messages,
they're from
Shakespeare's tragedies,
all the stories of evil deeds
and doomed love.
What has that
got to do with...
Mom's favorite thing
in life,
her passion was poetry.
Can I give you a little
brotherly advice?
Don't let
your feelings for James
blind you to what's
really going on.
I mean, these threats
aren't coming
from beyond the grave.
No, it's not James.
It's Shakespeare.
She's trying to warn me.
Hello.
Hey, James has
been in an accident.
He's at the hospital.
Oh, my God.
I'll be right there.
James has been
in an accident.
What? What happened?
Christine, wait!
Code blue,
room 203.
Code blue, room 203.
Yes.
It's on your right.
Okay, thanks.
My God, James.
My God!
You okay?
Sweetie.
What happened?
I'm okay.
All right, somebody
ran me off the road,
but the doctors
checked me out,
and I'm
gonna be fine.
You don't understand.
I can't lose you.
I know, sweetie.
It's okay.
Baby, you're
the only thing I care
about in this world.
I mean, why are we
waiting to get married?
I don't know.
Let's just do it.
I don't want to spend
another day without you.
Okay.
This mean...
Yeah.
Okay.
Love you.
I love you more.
Are you ready
to kill for me?
I'd die for you.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
You okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
Leave me alone!
Oh, for God's sake.
Wanted me to be
Dr. Webb,
it's John Anderson.
Uh, I'm sorry
for the short notice,
but is there
any chance you could
meet with me today?
I'm booked today.
Will tomorrow work?
Uh, it's... it's important,
and I just need to talk
to you for a few minutes.
I gotta get this
figured out.
I'm ready
to discuss more...
more ways of treatment.
What's going on?
I'm afraid Ryan
put my daughter
in some real jeopardy
this time.
Oh, God.
What happened?
I'm meeting with detectives
tonight to figure it out.
A female student
was attacked
at the university pool
last week.
Cops say they
can I.D. my daughter
outside the pool
at the time
of the attack.
Dr. Webb?
Are you still there?
Let's meet at the Crescent
Café at 10:00.
Thank you, Doctor.
I appreciate it.
Ryan, Dave's here!
Hey.
I need to borrow
your car Saturday.
Done.
What's wrong
with your truck?
It won't start.
Zeal, let's go, honey!
Morning, Pop!
You scared me, baby.
You trying to give me
a heart attack?
Ah, you ready
for school?
Yep.
What do you got there?
It's my disguise.
Your disguise, huh?
Can I see it?
It's a secret.
I can't show you.
It's a secret?
You're gonna keep
a secret from your dad?
Ryan said
he's teaching me to be
his partner in crime.
He did, huh?
Yeah, I want
to talk to you
about that
on the way to school.
Hey, Donna.
Hey, hon,
you got a second?
Yeah, what's up?
Look, I'm meeting
Susan in a minute
to discuss Christine.
Is everything okay?
Bill, I can't live
like this anymore,
and I want this
resolved tonight.
What? Tonight?
Honey, I need more time.
She's in a really
fragile place right now.
She knows about us, Bill.
I can sense it.
No, you're
being paranoid.
She's just
really unstable.
She's here. Gotta go.
Donna. I really
appreciate you coming.
Absolutely.
It's my pleasure.
How are you?
I'm good.
I really need
your help with this.
Yeah. I find the whole thing
rather intriguing.
Well,
you're not living it.
By the way,
how is Bill holding up?
He's, um...
Well,
he's a basket case.
Wow.
Any news from the doctor?
Uh,
not good news.
Looks like it's gonna
be just Bill and me.
I'm so sorry.
So we're gonna get
your brother some help.
You understand?
Okay, Pop.
I'll miss him.
Don't want to be late.
Ms. Airlie will
be upset with you, huh?
Yep.
Did you finish that project?
Yep. I finished it.
All right.
Give me a kiss.
Love you.
Have a good day.
What the hell?
Ryan!
Hi, Mr. Anderson.
Eh...
I don't know,
though.
I... I will think
about it carefully.
So, uh,
Christine's case,
please,
tell me
what you think.
I'm just
too close to it.
Well, based on
what you've described,
I'm thinking D.I.D.
Interesting.
A severe trauma can
trigger the splintering
of a single personality
into two distinct
personalities.
You know, often
the second one is created
'cause the original can't
handle the issues at hand,
but it operates
as its own entity,
you know,
with its own agenda.
Well, then explain
the hallucinations.
Cognitive leakage.
I mean, any event
that threatens to expose
the original mind
to the alternate mind
must be blocked,
so the hallucinations
are kind of like...
psychological
rationalizations.
Hmm.
I have
to think about it.
You should trust me
on this one.
You know, it was
less than 100 years ago
that people thought
the mentally ill
were all possessed
by spirits of the dead.
I have got to get
back to the office.
Okay.
Great to see you.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Bye.
John!
Help, please!
Help!
Next we'll discuss
the supernatural symbolism
Shakespeare uses
in "Macbeth."
For example,
the witches represent
Macbeth's inner evil.
The brooding darkness
symbolizes the darkness
in Macbeth's heart
and the evil nature
of his horrible deeds.
Uh, go ahead, Ryan.
What the hell?
Susan?
Demon!
Susan.
There's... There's evil
in the house.
Are you sick?
Did you take these?
There's a demon
in the house.
Yeah, yeah.
How many of these
did you take?
Shh. Shh.
All right, come on,
let's get you out of this...
No! No! No!
There's evil
in this house.
I saw it
with my own eyes.
She drove
the big red truck.
What truck?
John Anderson,
she mowed him down.
She killed him.
I saw it with
my own eyes.
John Anderson's
dead because of her.
What are you talking about?
All right, come on.
No, she's possessed!
She's possessed!
She's possessed,
honey.
She's possessed!
Hey, do you know
where your, uh, dad's at?
He was
in an accident
yesterday.
Is he all right?
He's dead.
Oh, my God.
What are you
talking about, he's dead?
Hit-and-run.
Where?
Oh, for God's sake!
Does it matter where?
I'm really sorry
about your dad.
I'm Christine,
by the way,
his fiancée.
Yeah. My dad
was all excited
about you guys
getting married.
He wanted me
to give you this.
Thank you.
I'm really sorry
for your loss.
Let's go.
Take care.
"James, congratulations
to you and Christine.
"I know we're
both a little
strapped for cash
"until
business improves,
so I'd be honored
"if you would accept
my cabin as your
honeymoon getaway
"and my wedding present
to you.
Best wishes, John."
You've been
fucking amazing.
Pretty soon,
we'll be together.
Can't wait.
So tell me
about our fall guy.
I'll take care of Dave
Saturday night.
Mm.
What's his motive?
Uh...
obsession.
Couldn't deal with your
marriage to James.
Perfect.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
Hey, it's a shame Susan
couldn't make it.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I guess
she came down
with stomach flu
or something.
Take good care
of Christine,
'cause if anything happens to
her, I'll kill you,
and I'll make it
look like an accident.
You guys have fun
at the cabin!
Give me a call when you come
up for air, huh?
I will.
Bye, big brother.
Bye.
So that's over with.
Mm.
Got mixed emotions,
but she seems
to be happy,
and I guess that's all
that matters, right?
Everyone was disappointed that
you weren't there.
Well, your sister is
a very sick girl, Bill.
Oh, God,
please just don't.
Just don't.
Donna was right.
You talked to Donna?
She's developed two very
distinct personalities.
You know, it's interesting.
Two sides...
Chrissy and Christine.
Now, Chrissy
is the evil one...
and she absorbs
all of Christine's pain
and settles all
of her grudges for her.
That's ridiculous.
You know what?
I still don't understand
why in the world
she would ever
kill John Anderson.
Susie, you really gotta
stop taking those pills.
I know what I saw, Bill,
and Monday morning,
I'm going to the police,
and I'm going
to tell them everything.
Yeah, you do that.
You're just gonna
make a goddamn ass
of yourself.
We did it.
Yeah, we did.
Can you believe it?
Nope.
Why are you so sad?
It's nothing.
Why are you crying?
Just love you so much.
Hey, wait.
What?
I have a surprise
for you in my car.
Go get it?
What is it?
It's a surprise.
I can't tell you.
It's in my trunk.
Okay.
Go.
I love you.
It's the blushing bride.
Hey, big brother.
Could I ask you
a favor?
Yeah. What's up?
If you can't,
I understand. I just...
Is there any way you
could come scope out
the cabin tonight?
Tonight?
Yeah. Is that
too much to ask?
Is everything okay?
I think so.
Maybe I'm
just paranoid. I...
just feel like
someone's following us,
and I don't want
to bother James.
Give me 30 minutes
to get up there.
Thanks.
I owe you big time.
Motherf...
James.
What?
Zeal, scram.
You little bitch.
It was you the whole time,
wasn 't it?
You don't even
have the balls to pull
that trigger, Ryan.
You know that.
What do you think, Ryan?
Think if you kill me,
she's gonna want you, huh?
Think that's
what it's about?
You're nothing
but a little freak.
Christine?
It's a terrifying
feeling, isn't it?
Lying helpless,
waiting to die?
It's how they felt,
James.
What are you
talking about, baby?
My parents, James.
Baby, have you
gone crazy?
Maybe.
Ah, look at our
sleeping beauty
up there.
James,
be careful, please.
Will you relax?
When it rains this hard,
it usually only lasts
a few minutes.
How you doing
up there, buddy?
Uh, the highway's flooded.
I gotta take this exit.
By the way, I'm sick
of your comments
about my lack
of education in front
of our daughter.
I don't like your tone.
My tone?
Yes,
your condescending tone.
You started it.
You sound like a child.
Stop treating me
like a child.
What's going on, buddy?
Well, the car stalled.
What?
- Well, there you go.
- Oh, thank God.
Hey, watch out!
You're in reverse!
There's a train!
James,
what are you doing?!
James, there's a train!
James!
Sorry!
God. Oh, my God.
Oh, no! No!
No!
Just take
responsibility
for what you did,
James.
Christine,
I did it for you.
For us.
They were never gonna
let us be together.
You know that.
And I thought it
was gonna make it easier.
I really did.
But I was wrong.
I wish
I could take it back.
I'm sorry.
Give me the gun.
No, Christine, please.
You know, it didn't
have to be this way.
This is your fault,
James!
Christine, no, please!
No, I loved you.
I loved you.
How could you do this?
This is unreal.
That wasn't the plan.
Your prints
are all over the gun.
Just shut up, Ryan!
Ah, fuck.
Okay. Okay.
Holy shit, Ryan!
Is that a cop?
Oh, shit. They must
have heard the shot.
Get him in the car.
Oh, shit. Now what?
Now what?
Th-They're gonna
call his radio.
There's gonna
be no response.
Then they come
looking for him.
Listen to me. Just calm down,
all right?
If we get...
Just calm down.
It's gonna be, okay.
Just trust me.
Trust me,
Ryan, okay?
Just get rid
of the girl,
and wipe down
the gun.
Okay, trust me.
Shit.
Hey.
Bill.
Bill, he's here.
What?
He's... He's
in the house.
You have
to hurry.
He's gonna
kill me.
Stay on the phone
with me.
Tell me exactly
what's going on.
I'm almost there!
He shot James.
James is dead.
Who shot him?
Ryan.
Ryan Anderson.
Bill,
please hurry.
He's gonna
find me.
Where is he?
Are you in the house?
Yes, I'm locked in the bedroom.
Hurry.
Okay,
I'm five minutes away.
Just don't...
Chr-Chri...
131.
Go ahead, 131.
Code three,
1822 Roaming Wood Road,
Cottage Grove.
Send every car
in the area.
Roger, 131. En route.
I gotta get Dave's car
back to town.
Wow.
How are you
gonna get rid of him?
Oh, I...
I'll do him
with the shotgun,
and I'll, uh...
I'll dump a bunch
of your stuff
around his trailer,
make him look like
the classic stalker.
There's tire tracks
all over this place.
And what about
our other loose end?
Don't worry
about a thing.
She's...
She's taken care of.
Perfect.
Yeah.
Take this off.
Come here.
Choke me.
What?
Don't stop.
Choke me.
You're k-kidding.
No!
Hey!
You're a fucking dead man! No!
Listen to me.
I need you to tell me
what's going on.
Susan says that
you've killed someone,
that she can
place you at the scene
of a homicide.
Now if you need help,
I can help you,
but you've gotta
be honest with me.
The police are gonna
be here any second.
You're in a lot
of trouble, Bill.
Miss Webb,
what was the nature
of your relationship
with the two victims?
Miss Webb?
So do you know
this Ryan Anderson?
What?
Did you know
Ryan Anderson?
No. I think he worked
at the sawmill with James.
We found this
in the front seat
of one of the cars.
Do you recognize
this weapon, Mr. Webb?
Might be mine.
It might be yours?
How did it get here?
I don't know.
We got
two dead bodies,
one young man in his
early twenties,
one in his fifties,
a Sheriff
both shot
execution style.
Shotgun wounds?
Definitely.
Do you know anything about these
bodies, Mr. Webb?
I want an attorney.
And what about
our other loose end?
Don't worry
about a thing.
She's...
She's taken care of.
Susan says that
you've killed someone,
that she can
place you at the scene
of a homicide.
We're almost done,
sweetheart.
Just one more
little thing.
Hi.
Hi, Mommy.
Thank you,
Mr. Blooms!
Take care, Susan.
Thank you.
Bye.
Oh! Oh, I missed
you so much!
So what did
you learn today?
I learned how to play
"Mary Had A Little Lamb."
No way.
Yes.
'Cause you are
my little lamb.
You can't catch me!
Yes, you are!
Yes, you're
my little...
By the pricking
of my thumbs,
something wicked
this way comes.