Carolyn upstairs?
Yeah.
She told me she feels like
she's living at the zoo
when you do that.
Like a bear.
Oh, a lion.
Don't forget about tonight.
No, I have an interview before,
but I will come straight home.
For the record,
that's a lion, Carolyn!
You caught the
seaweed in your mouth!
Oh, we have a new champion!
Oh!
Oh, Mommy look!
Did you see?
I caught the seaweed!
We won!
I didn't see it coming.
She vanished, he vanished.
He'd been seeing
a doctor downtown.
It seemed to help him.
He had been so depressed.
And then one day he was gone.
This doctor had taken
a number of patients
and gone to Glass Lake.
How many patients?
Uh, 10, maybe 15.
When I had just showed up, boy
they were not happy about that.
And Anthony said that
he wasn't coming back.
He said that after
Jenny's death,
he couldn't face the world
away from this place.
What did he mean by that?
Did you contact the police?
They said no law
had been broken.
I feel something
horrible will happen.
Something horrible's
always a possibility now.
But if you know
it's going to happen,
shouldn't you try to stop it?
Sorry.
Tom?
I know, I know, I just
got stuck in an interview.
What are you doing?
I know, I'll just... I'm
sorry, just two minutes,
I'll be right back.
I called to say
we're not coming.
Why?
Everybody knows I work late.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Why are you being such a...
Drop it, Alice!
Fucking drop it!
Tom.
You know, you can be a
real asshole sometimes.
I'm going for a walk.
Fred, hi, sorry I couldn't
get back to the office.
No, no, I mean... her
husband left her,
she found him at some
clinic, and she's
convinced the place is evil.
Yeah, I don't really think
there's a story there.
Yeah, that's OK.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Tom?
Tom, I'm back.
You hungry?
Game four
of the American
League championshp
series... is there a fight
left in the New York Yankees?
The setbacks...
Tom?
I'm sorry!
I'm... I'm sorry!
Sure, get ahead of you.
Luke, you all right?
You on the wagon, or something?
You look kinda sad,
just sitting there.
Want to spark it?
Be right back.
Do you want to spark it?
What kind of question is that?
No, no, no... we'll take
a cab, we'll take a cab.
We'll pick up the
car in the morning.
It's not a big deal,
it's not a big...
Zak, look at me!
You OK?
What the fuck?
My baby?
I want to see my baby.
I want to see Tasha.
Don't budge, don't move.
We're gonna get you out.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Fucking shit, fucking waste
of fucking.
Fuck you, fucking
shit, fucking cunt!
You fuckin' hole, you fuckin'
hole, fuck you in your hole!
Fuck you in your fucking eye!
Fuck you, you fuck!
Gordon!
Fuck!
Fuckin' son of a bitch!
Fuck you!
Is that Wayne?
That's Wayne!
Wayne!
Wayne, hey!
We were just talking about you.
I can believe it.
You OK?
Oh, you're not pissed
about New Year's?
You're pissed.
Come on, honey.
No, he's pissed.
I don't know who you are.
I should know, but I don't.
I'm James, and this is Sheila.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I don't know where I am.
Where am I?
Let's... why don't
you come with us?
Let's take you home.
Come on, come on!
Hey!
OK!
Ah!
No!
Jenny!
Help!
What is it?
When I had just showed up,
they were not happy about that.
And, uh, Anthony said that
he wasn't coming back.
He said that after
Jenny's death,
he couldn't face the world
away from this place.
When I showed just showed up,
they were not happy about that.
And Anthony said that
he wasn't coming back.
He said that after
Jenny's death,
he couldn't face the world
away from this place.
Where?
Uh, near Glass Lake.
But you don't know what
kind of clinic it is?
Hmm, find out.
There's no story there,
you said that yourself.
Well, maybe I was wrong.
We're not going to pay for it.
Fred...
You need to take
time to grieve.
Well, what do you
know about grief?
I'm sorry.
This is bull shit.
Alice...
May I help you?
What are you doing here?
Um, I was walking
by the tracks.
I saw your chimney.
Where are you going?
Who are you?
I don't know.
Well you should keep on going.
You don't want to be here.
And be careful on the
tracks... walk off to one side.
Hey, babies.
Hey... good babies.
Charlie!
Charlie, get back here!
Jesus, Charlie!
You're not Charlie.
And you're Betsy.
Tell me you're Betsy,
for Christ's sake.
I'm Betsy.
Put your bags down.
What are we doing?
Here.
The boy was good at this.
Charlie?
I can show you a trick.
Here, it's like the
shoulders of a jacket.
See?
What?
I don't know.
Oh, Wayne... who
the fuck are you?
Who is this, Wayne?
Betsy.
She came over the tracks.
From where?
So what did you guys talk about?
I told her to go away.
That was good advice.
Why didn't you follow it?
How did she get past the dogs?
Nobody gets past the dogs.
You see the dogs?
You always travel with no ID?
You know what an ID is?
Yeah, well, where's yours?
That's not a
rhetorical question.
Why are you so mean?
I don't know who I am.
I don't know how I got here,
and I don't know who you are,
but I wish you'd stop
being such a shit.
OK.
We'll feed her, give her $50,
and drop her at the station.
I want to stay.
Why?
Do you like being abused?
I can do laundry.
Come on, it's pathetic.
We could call the police,
hand her over to them.
That's just what we
need, Tony... fucking cops.
So who's going to take
her to the station?
No, no, no, please no.
I just want to stay
here with you, please!
Please, I just want
to stay here with you.
I can't go back to...
you have to let me stay.
I can't go back
out there... please,
you have to just... I
just want to stay here with you,
Please, I just want to be
here. Anything but that.
Please just let me stay
here with you guys.
I just... please, please,
I don't know what...
Sshh, it's OK.
Here, here, here, here, here.
Take it easy, take it easy, OK?
Now drink it.
You'll feel better.
OK.
I want to
see elbows and assholes!
Elbows and assholes!
Everybody up!
I want to see
elbows and assholes!
Here you go, darlin'.
Neal wants to see you before
he goes to the market.
I'll be back in 20 minutes.
Comforters, they're
making the comforters.
I spoke with the
folks here about you
staying with us,
for now that is,
and I think they'll
be OK with it.
Thank you.
Don't thank me, yet.
You know, it's been said
that our humanity lies
in what we've done, and
what we've experienced.
Have you ever
thought about that?
If you believe
that... I do... then
it might go without
saying that if you
strip a person of
their experience,
they become destructive.
So you need to remember yours.
The people here are in the
last stages of their recovery,
and they know very well from
what they're recovering.
So you're going to have
to remember something
about what happened
to you, or I'm
wildly irresponsible for letting
you stay... for both our sakes.
That's Charlie.
You understand?
So... OK.
All right, then.
So we'll get you back
and you can meet people.
And then you can work
the kitchen tonight.
Charlie, this is the young woman
that showed up last evening.
She doesn't remember her name.
And this is Charlie.
Charlie, would you... why
don't you bring her back
and introduce her?
Good.
Why don't you just go
back the way you came.
You can do that,
don't you think Alice?
Do you want to quilt
sewn by one of those.
God, no.
Do you want me to be
sewing your clothes?
Honey, you can sew
my quilt anytime.
Does anyone have
left-handed scissors?
Honey, we don't.
You struggling?
Oh, honey, I'm sorry I don't.
Oh, Julie.
Have you noticed that not one
man has volunteered to do this.
Would you want them to?
Could you imagine Neal?
We have a new helper here.
Oh, I know who you are.
Come on over here, honey.
We can use all the
help we can get.
I thought there were
no more newcomers.
I wasn't just
talking about her.
Now, this is Anthony's, and
you can just cut strips out
of this old sheet.
I mean, it's easy.
I mean, I know she might
not know who she is,
but can you talk?
Jesus, Julie.
Give her a break.
I can talk.
Oh, I'm know how to use words,
but you don't know who you are.
Julie, you don't know anything.
I know one thing... this sucks.
Wait a minute... wait a minute!
Oh, you're kidding.
I can feel it coming.
Hillary, no...
Julie's sulking.
Go to hell.
Oh, Jules.
Come on, young
lady... give it a try.
Come on... you can do it.
She's a keeper!
Now, who's this?
It's a mystery, Wayne.
No, it's Betsy.
Huh... isn't it?
Luke here was just telling
us about the first time
he was kissed.
Watching a basketball
game, it's just so romantic.
No, man... we
fucking took a vote.
We said no more.
You said that was it...
she can't fucking stay!
All right, sit down, Charlie!
You said that was fucking it!
Fuck that!
Cool down, Charlie.
Fuck you!
Sit down, Gordon.
Cool down, asshole.
You guys... sit down, Gordon!
He's right, though, Neil.
Charlie's crazy, but
he's right so this one.
We don't know
anything about her.
Let's don't talk
about this now.
We just don't have
the time or the energy
to go through the process that
we've all been going through.
Please, not now.
OK, if you just... please.
I agree.
What happened?
It's Gordon and Charlie.
Like brothers.
I had all brothers.
They'd bring their
friends home from school,
and they'd go to
all of my underwear.
I did that once.
Not yours... not your underwear,
but a sister of a friend.
They have this laundry chute
with these two little doors...
one from the bedroom,
one from the bathroom.
If you kept them both
open, you could spy
on Jack's sister taking a bath.
We got into so much trouble.
Oh!
Son of a bitch!
Now, you sit down.
Holy fuck!
Charlie, fuck!
Get away from me!
Get the fuck back!
Blow the stupid
whistle, Charlie!
Blow the fucking whistle!
Blow the whistle Charlie!
Blow the fucking
whistle, Charlie!
Thank you, mother
fucker, thank you!
Do you mind finishing up here?
We're almost done, so...
It's no problem.
I'm sorry.
It's OK, I'll finish up.
You want coffee?
Yeah, I'd love some.
How do you take it?
Just black.
Black like my heart.
Give that a rinse, please.
There you go.
I'll be back.
You have something
you want to say to me?
You believe in
cause and effect?
It's like when something
happens and then
that's just...
that's just who you
are for the rest of
your shitty life.
Do you believe in that?
You're a fucking cunt, Alice.
These are decent
people, and they're not
messing with anybody.
And you're not going
to mess it up for them.
No, that is not true.
I like everyone here.
Oh yeah, you like
everybody here?
Yes.
Yeah, fucking Luke
stabbed his best friend,
you fucking like him?
I like you.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You're wrong.
You are...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, man.
Not here... no, not here.
Hey, cinnamon
girl... where are you?
It's just Gordon.
I'll go out...
I'll go out first.
OK?
Hey, Alice...
Thank you.
Sorry, I let myself in.
It's all right.
Will you sit?
Listen to me... when they ask
you if you remember anything,
do not say a word.
Do you understand?
I- I'm going to die here.
But it doesn't matter, because
I'm going to die anyway.
I'm sick, I'm very sick.
But you're not.
All these people... they're
all going to kill themselves.
And you want to do that?
Do you?
Trust me, you don't.
What's going on here?
We're building beds.
They're a little
small, aren't they?
Then they're just right.
You want to try one?
No, it's OK.
Here, come.
OK.
They're not soft.
It's going to be
nice though, right?
Here, put these on.
Now sing.
Just sing along with the song.
Oh, no, I can't sing.
I don't even know the song.
Trust me, it feels good.
It's good practice.
Helps you focus.
Sure.
But for what?
To let go.
Of what?
Can I have those back?
Sorry.
Why haven't you
told anyone else?
You know who I am.
I figured you'd
do that yourself.
Charlie, what are you doing?
He just drank out of the.
That's nasty..
Good morning.
I got it!
That's a penalty!
Kick it in!
Shoot!
Nice and easy!
I got it, hon.
Oh, Charlie, learn
to walk, buddy!
You see that?
Everybody see that?
Pick 'em up.
Shoot!
She's a keeper.
She is a keeper.
We won, Charlie.
I'm sorry, you suck.
I think we've got a
ringer there, Neil.
Well played.
You played.
I guess.
All right,
let's get ready for dinner.
Wayne, did you forgot about me?
Do you remember
my request, Wayne?
Gordon?
Could you get everyone's
attention for me, please?
I have something
I'd like to say.
Right now?
Uh, please.
Absolutely.
Everybody listen up, listen up.
My sister here of the
great leg has something
she would like to say.
Just for the record, I
taught her everything
she knows... you better
fucking believe that.
Why don't you just get
a, Gordon?
Eat a fat dick, sir.
Here she goes.
Thank you.
Uh, I just wanted to say
I remembered my name.
My name is Alice.
Actually, I've
known it all along.
I was pretending not to,
but I'm ashamed of that
because I think all of
you deserve much better.
Partly, though I don't
know what Alice means.
I don't really know who I am.
I... I feel things since Tom
died, but I don't really
know them.
I don't know if that
makes any sense.
Almost all the time when I'm
by myself I think about Tom...
crammed in that tub, he was
really just too big for it.
And um, in his suit.
He had the one suit.
Called himself the
last gentleman.
And the mess, oh, the mess.
And that gun... I didn't
even know he had it.
Um, I didn't even he was...
Anyways, I keep wondering if
I'd done something differently,
if I hadn't walked out
that night after we fought,
maybe something
would be different.
But I don't know.
Maybe.
Who is Tom?
Tom was my boyfriend.
I was interviewing
your wife that night.
It's, um, why we fought.
I was late coming home.
I'm a journalist.
Oh, dear god.
I lied to myself
that I was coming here
to investigate a story.
I'm not here for that story.
Please, I would... I would
very much like to stay.
Alice... Alice, that's right?
Yes, I'm Alice.
You know what we're
doing here, right?
Do you agree with us?
Uh, yes.
Because most of
humanity doesn't.
People are disappointed,
horrible things happen.
And they move on, and go
on living all the time.
And they'd find us diminishing
and absurd, fraudulent.
And it's OK to feel that way.
It's OK.
You understand?
So do you still
want to stay here?
Yeah, I do.
OK, so you should take
your dinner with you,
and I'll come and find
you when we're done.
Why?
I like it here.
Well, the folks here have
voted for you to stay.
We're all out of our
minds, of course,
but you already knew that.
Thank you.
Why not?
Don't let her stay, Neil.
It's not right!
It's her decision.
You should know better.
Have you seen the way
she looks at Charlie?
Seems to me she's
made up her mind.
What kind of things?
When I'm having a
good day, like today,
I remember a lot about my wife.
She was pretty, my wife.
You know, like you.
Is she still?
Do you have kids?
I have photos.
Ah, Jesus Christ... stop it!
What?
It's supposed to be
refreshing, right?
You're a... you're a...
A what?
Not that way, Wayne,
it's the other way.
Asshole is the word
he's looking for.
Will anybody notice the light?
They'll think it's just me.
How long have you been here?
15 minutes.
No, I mean here with everybody.
I, uh, I met Neil awhile ago.
I was one of the first
ones at the clinic.
Why were you at the clinic?
Uh, because I was
fucked up, again.
How fucked up?
What's with all the questions?
I didn't ask you
about Tom, did I?
Maybe you should.
I didn't exactly
get to question him.
So who are you talking to?
Are you talking to Tom,
or are you talking to me?
You don't get it, do you?
When you finally find this,
you... you hold on to it.
You don't just sit around
and fucking talk about it.
That... that I don't understand.
Fuck!
You want to talk?
My brother, my older
brother, my only brother,
is serving life in prison for
killing both of our parents.
My... my dad died when I
was three, my real dad.
But my step dad
started fucking me
when I was like...
like seven or eight.
And he would use broom
handles and glass bottles,
he told me it was
because he loved me.
So I guess I... I guess
I sort of believe him.
And maybe it was
love... I don't know,
fucking seemed to make him
happy, but... but it hurt.
I guess that's what
he didn't know.
It really... it
really fucking hurt.
Where was your mother?
She knew.
So... so when my brother found
out, he killed them both.
First him, and then her.
Any other questions?
What's your last name?
Wolf.
What?
What, that's my last name?
Hey... I'll be right back, OK?
Oh, hi.
Don't worry, they won't bite.
Alice, this is Pete and Lulu.
Hi.
Hey, hey, hey... you're very big.
Ah, they're not so big
once you get used to them.
Hi.
It's good you told
the truth to everybody.
You know the last
thing I said to Tom?
You're an asshole.
Did you mean it?
He probably deserved it.
I should go.
Will you be all
right, walking home?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Excuse me, Lulu.
Rachel?
Rachel!
Rachel, are you all right?
No.
How can I help?
Leave.
Neil!
I couldn't find you.
What's going on, Alice?
Let-let-let's get you in.
I'm not going back.
Well, you can't stay out here.
You... great healer.
Help me up.
Hand me that, would you please?
Don't touch.
Please.
I can... Rachel, we
can carry you back.
OK.
Rachel!
No!
Rachel?
OK, you pull that
cover down, Alice.
Pull it down to take it off
there... take it all the way off
and put it on the chair.
Take that off her, will you?
She's got another here.
Where, I don't know where.
OK, then I'll lift and you pull.
OK.
Neil, here.
Here let me... you lift her.
I'll take care of
the rest, Alice.
Thank you.
Charlie?
You're back.
Something terrible has happened.
Rachel's dead.
Neil killed her by accident.
She was trying to leave,
ad she was hitting him
with this big stick.
And he tried to yank it from
her hands and he killed her.
What are you you saying?
Neil killed Rachel.
But he didn't mean to.
No, no.
Where is he?
He's in the house with her.
I feel terrible.
I don't...
Come here.
Charlie.
Get under here.
Till they ring the bell.
You're shaking.
She was dying, Alice.
Rachel was dying.
Everybody knew that.
But Charlie...
Just close your eyes.
We'll find out about it, OK?
I'll go first, OK?
The expect me.
It's like that every time,
Wayne, I'm telling you.
Day in and day out.
Alice, we've been
waiting for you.
Here, sit here.
What's going on, Neil?
Shouldn't we wait for Rachel?
Let the man speak.
She died.
What?
When?
Rachel died last night.
How?
She had walked outside alone.
She must have fallen down.
Alice helped me carry her in.
I know how much you loved her.
I loved her.
This is the time.
We should all leave together.
Tomorrow, with Rachel.
As she'd want.
She's in the bedroom.
You should go see
Rachel if you'd like,
and then we need to
prepare everything.
Charlie?
Charlie, Neil's not
telling everything.
Rachel did not just
die, she was fighting.
I don't believe you.
I was there.
I'm telling you what Neil
said is not what happened.
What the fuck,
Alice... he loved her.
What is that for?
Charlie?
Charlie... what are you doing?
You are not going to shoot them.
Please, Charlie, we
can get out of here.
We can leave right now.
And maybe we...
No!
You don't want to do this.
Oh, you stupid fu...
Shut up, Alice!
You do not want to shoot them!
What are you doing?
Just stop it!
May I speak with you?
She was a patient of mine.
And you married her.
We found this place
to help people.
You still consider
yourself a doctor?
Do you still consider
yourself a journalist?
This is all about you, isn't it?
Yeah, most things
are, don't you think?
The people here are happy
knowing that they'll
be dead sooner than later.
You're selfish.
No, the people in
my profession who
prolong the lives of terribly
tormented people are selfish.
You know this?
Do you think the
people here are unhappy?
They're joyous.
What were you doing
outside last night?
I was wondering what Rachel
was doing in the driveway
last night.
She was dying, Alice.
She didn't believe
in you, anymore.
Is that why you lied to
everybody this morning
about how she died?
We're not so
different, Alice, you
and I. What are you
doing with Charlie?
I mean, you then maybe you
could take care of him?
Make his life a
worthwhile pursuit?
Rid him of his bad memories?
It's about you,
as you would say.
And you?
Why are you going
through with it?
Because it's the one
sure way not to fail them.
And imagine... I wouldn't have
to answer questions like yours.
And Alice, you know, sometimes
when people stop in your life,
there's nowhere to go.
It's too late.
You're out of your mind.
...Jump in the ocean,
oh, nobody's business but mine.
Ain't nobody's
business but mine.
Ain't nobody...
Hey, you all right?
You can come in.
You ready for tomorrow?
Oh, yeah.
I've been ready for
quite some time.
Do you ever think there
might be a way other than...
You're not going to ruin
this for us, are you?
No.
Here, give me some more.
OK, here we go now.
Scottish humor for you.
Hey, hi!
Alice...
Here?
Yes, please.
Looking very beautiful
and fetching, my dear.
Thank you.
I have a toast.
Ah, Charlie, shut up.
Oh, shut up yourself, Gordon.
Gordon, you've had too much.
No.
Shut up.
To Alice.
And to all the other
dogs in my life.
Ah, you don't know
when to quit, do you?
I bet your pardon?
That boy doesn't know
how to handle his liquor.
Hey come on.
We should all go
and sit by the fire.
Very good idea.
Come along, darling.
Hey Alice... I wanted
to ask you something.
How was my wife,
when you saw her?
She didn't want to lose you.
I'd have ruined the rest
of her life, you know?
Thanks, though.
Alice!
Hello, Alice.
Charlie.
Will you dance with me?
Dance with him, hon.
It'll be good for his soul.
Charlie?
Don't say it, Alice.
Don't say anything.
You all right, man?
Haven't said a word all night.
Yeah.
I'm fine.
If you want to go...
now would be the time.
I can walk you past the meadow
and you can follow the tracks
and just go back
the way you came.
Come with me.
Then I'm staying.
Alice?
So remember,
concentrate on the song.
That'll help.
All right, well,
let's get started.
OK.
It's OK.
Wait!
Goddammit, wait.
Stop, stop.
What are you doing, Charlie?
Charlie?
I'm really sorry, everyone.
I'm really, really sorry.
I won't let anybody
bother you, OK?
Alice, you have to come with me.
Wait, hold on a minute.
Let her go.
Good bye, Alice.
Good bye.
Hi, hi.
Hi, baby, hi, baby.
Hey, I'm going to get
you out of here, OK?
OK?
Yeah.
Oh, Charlie.
Come on.