It was my greatest victory
the dream of every commander
I have deluded myself into thinking
I could reunite all the kingdoms
under a single flag
but further battles would be
needed
there was more blood to shed
for the first time I felt lost
it was too late to turn back and too early
to declare that foolis war over forever
my crown could no longer have stood
the weight of more lost lives
so it was that in the depths of
desperation I raised my eyes to heaven
praying that someone infinitely
greater than me could help me
the gods stayed silent but that very day
someone else decided to listen to my pleas
what evil thing is this?
Who are you?!
When someone answers your
prayers call it evil
I'm here to give you more power to trample over
all the principles on which your voice rests.
How valuable this tendency is
for us king Wolfkhan.
What do you want from me?
Why are we here?
How do you know my name?
It's very simple
I want to thank you and propose a pact that
will put an end to your foolish remorse
thank me? What for?
For the blood you have spilt
over all these years
the blood of brave warriors but
also blood of the innocent.
Guilty of only being on the
wrong side of the conflict.
You have been an unwitting
messenger of death
who has made us again as
powerful as we once were.
Do you want to end the war early and reign
as the sole one over the whole continent
we are ready to give you what
you want. But on one condition
each of you heirs must be
sacrificed to our dark lord.
How can you even think I could
accept so foul of an offer?
Don't lie to yourself.
You already have.
Ahhhh!
Ahahahahahaha!
"Over the years,.
The memory of that day faded.
Almost into nothing, years of
great victories followed.
The destructive fury of our
swords was truly awesome.
Nothing seemed capable of
stopping us.
One warm spring the birth of
luna, my daughter
the overwhelming joy that invaded
my heart however was chilled,
by a terrible discovery.
On luna's chest, there was a
mark, like a scar.
The demon, had kept it's promise
and now I had to keep mine.
Please, can you help me? I'm trying to find the king.
I have an important message for him.
Sword!, where's my sword?
The gladiators already warming up in
the arena and the king has no sword!?
Out, everyone, out of here.
Marion, where are you, you
witch.
Your majesty you really must see
her.
She looks exactly like your dead
queen.
I couldn't believe my very eyes.
Could it be lorna your lost
daughter?
Look, I have kept her in a cell
apart so no one else may see her
you must see her your majesty.
I knew you peasants from the lands to the
east could handle a hoe but not a sword.
If you insist I'll show you where we
yocals from the east stick our hoes.
Leave him alone kayne
you'll have a chance to show this
puppet a lesson at the tournament
better listen to your little
girlfriend yocal
besides, it would be more fun
watching you eat the mud
in front of an arena full of
people.
So, on his deathbed,
the man who I believed to be my father
for all those years, told me a story.
He said when I was a little
baby,
he saved me from drowning in the
kooney river.
He said Miles before he saw some type of
mysterious hooded figure throw me in.
This is the only thing I have
from my past.
This little stone.
Since then I have traveled around
the world looking for this stone.
I knew if I found it
I'd also find my real parents.
I just wanted to ask them
why they did this to me.
May I burn in hell if ever we
were guilty of such infamy.
The truth is, someone kidnapped you
a few days after you were born.
Everything we did to find you
came to nothing.
I thought I had lost you
forever.
But fate has decided that we
meet again
welcome home luna.
Keymock will now shine even more
brightly than ever before
what you need now is rest.
Your arrival comes the day before a
great tournament that I've announced
to celebrate 10 years of peace
in our kingdom.
It's the perfect way of blessing
the festivities.
Tomorrow, we shall speak for
now, rest.
Guard, take her to the royal apartments. Make
sure that no one enters without my consents.
I advise your majesty to treat this
situation with the utmost caution.
What do you mean?
I don't know but, for now I
prefer to remain silent.
But there is something about this
situation that I do not like.
Good!, good!
Keep quiet, now don't put a dampener
on things for no good reason.
Now more than ever, is a time
for our kingdom to celebrate.
As you wish, your majesty.
It's amazing how closely you
resemble each other.
The same light in your eyes the
same rays of sunshine in your hair.
Looking at you makes having her
back with me, my daughter.
You both look so happy in this
picture.
Yes we were.
Your birth brought great joy to
our hearts.
You should have seen us, we were
like newly weds.
She would have only be born just
a few days.
Yet already she had begun to plan
every moment of your future.
How, how did my mother die?
Part of her died the day when
you were kidnapped.
And then there was that night,
but you have plenty of time to learn the
history of your family my daughter.
Today is the Eve of a very
festival here in keymock.
And your return would make it an
even more memorable event.
I want everything to be perfect.
In the meantime, I have a
surprise for you.
A surprise?
Yes, I had our best tailors make
a special costume
so that everyone can see the beauty
of king Wolfkhan's daughter!
People of keymock!
For centuries history has taught
us that no army is invincible
with the coming of our kingdom history
has been forced to re-write it's pages
the crowns of the most powerful rulers, have
had to bow down before our implacable force
thanks to our great warriors, keymock now
stands unopposed for splendor and glory.
By any other kingdom.
That is why, it is our duty now
to celebrate their courage
but there is another reason to
be happy,
truth, that the past gives back more
thank just thoughts of war and blood.
The past can even give us hope
of a better future.
This, is luna! My daughter,
found again!
And now, let the tournament
begin!
Your majesty
marigon, bringer of doom, you're
missing a great show
I asked to talk to you majesty
on a matter of the utmost
urgency.
Go on speak, what have you got
to say that's so important.
I prefer to talk to your
highness in private.
Make your words carefully remember you are
in presence of the princess of keymock
from her there shall be no
secrets.
I would not dream of offending
our princess.
So happily amongst us yet again
it is simply a matter concerning
our lands
it would only bore the princess
and distract her from the show.
So be it, out of my way.
These issues had better be
really important.
Ahhhhh!
So say what it is you have to
say to me.
She is not your daughter.
What is this nonsense you are
spouting.
Luna is not the person she says
she is.
How dare you!
I'll tear our that serpent
tongue of yours.
She does not bare the scar on
her body she was born with
you see.
It can not be.
What do these inscriptions mean?
They speak of an ancient
prophecy.
That ruled before the kingdom of
keymock.
But why does just looking at it
terrify you so much?
Yes, I know that
I tried to convince myself that
it would be the nightmare.
I made a pact with it
keymock will prevail all
kingdoms. And soon.
And in exchange the demon asked
for the lives of your children.
So that's why luna was snatched
away all those years ago.
Now I finally understand what
happened even after then.
Yes, it was the price I had to
pay.
But how did you?
Tell me what the prophecy says.
The prophecy says that if human
sacrifices take place.
That the noble blood spilt will
awake farmwort
a huge titan who will take his armies and
conquer the earth. Chaos will begin.
Only the children of the pact
can kill the monster.
But it must happen before the
human sacrifice begins.
It's time someone knew the
truth.
Ahhhh!
I always knew that sooner or
later it would come to this.
But I never thought it would
happen in this way.
Ahhhh!
When is this ritual to take
place.
I do not know my king
the book says nothing about when
this will happen.
It has already begun.
Har!
The winner is har!
If luna had had to lose you must
act now
but this time you must trust me.
Beware witch, I have already made
to many mistakes in my life.
The day is coming to a close.
And with it the first part of
the keymock tournament.
Let the evenings feasting begin.
At least I fight for a good
reason.
Tomorrow I show you how you use
this.
I like you brother.
But tonight the tavern waits for
us.
Aneheel
what?
Listen to an old story.
Two lovers lila and machnan
asked a priest in neeheel to
marry them in secret.
But neheel fell in love with
lila.
And corrupted machnan to convince lila
to kill herself to prove her love.
Lila kills herself but machnan
runs mad with pain.
And neeheel feeds on it
becoming a demon
and so they call neeheel those demons
who live on the suffering of man.
And how do you fight them?
Only a demon can fight another
demon.
Lila chose the way of hell to
come back to defeat neeheel.
But it's just another children's
story. Nothing else.
Are you still thinking about
that story for children.
Things can change
the whole world changes
and I'm beginning to fear that
every night could be our last.
Things end only when we want
them to.
The king
what you looking for has never
been written
you know that don't you.
I never understood how you
thought you'd find the answers
to all of your problems in
ancient history
who are you?
Who am I?
It's a great question
you should know
aren't you supposed to know
everything
maybe.. Hmmm
maybe the more important
question is
what do I know about you
maybe I know that your prepared to
tell the king everything about me.
Maybe hmmm..
I know after my poor mother
passed away,
you tried to make decisions that were
supposedly in the best interests of the kingdom
or maybe I know about your most
deep and darkest secret
every single servant that passes through
here has to get specially approved by you
I know, I know exactly what you
want.
I know exactly what you
fantasize about
could you imagine a night of pure
pleasure with the king's daughter no less
I mean I know you've been with
almost every servant here
but...
Let me ask you something
when was the last time you saw a
body like this
what do you want from me?
Are you going to kill me?
No, but I'm afraid he is.
Kayne
follow me
destiny often takes roads that
are unknown to us
only one single person in the
world can follow through a nation
that for too long awaits a
solution
that person, is you kayne.
And your arrival here in keymock is
a sign that none of us can ignore
just as no one must know your
departure
welcome to the second day of the
keymock tournament
to consecrate the greatness of
our king
the first warriors will be val
from the alterious
and teela from romer
clean all this up
let not a trace remain
and not a word to anyone
the tournament must go on as
though nothing has happened
after all no one is going to
miss her.
Except me old friend, I will.
The next fighters are the great
istithias from cornio
and the great hadran from
harcol.
Gunnar
kayne, what are you doing here?
You answer that question
that's my business
shouldn't you be back at the
tournament with your little friend?
I've got a sword to find
you don't know what your getting
yourself into
no!
You don't know what you've done,
don't you understand?
That was the only way to
the sword is mine
who gave you the viewer, you don't
understand that weapons power
get back
kayne, you're a very strong man
with your sword
but fight me like a real man, no
weapons
I told you hero, should have
stayed down
still playing you two?
Finally
beyond the fall
beyond the light
beyond time beyond space
the truth
that which you are, but you do
not know
twins, 2 twins have cost the
queen her life
take them away, in opposite
directions
brothers, that's what you are, blood
units you, a pact separates you
only the hands of the sons of the pact
can hold that which must not be seen
the sword with guide your
journey
the sword of the pact with seal that which
must not be seen in the darkness of oblivion
hey hey, its over, I am here
with you now
its over, what ever it was
you too were like that moments
ago, what happened
it was a nightmare
it was like something I already
knew
do you want to tell me what's
going on?
Father
luna, excuse me, I just wanted to make sure that
your room here is well worthy of a princess
oh yes it wonderful, just like a
dream
I just want to be prepared for
the rest of the tournament
I cant wait to see how it turns
out
yes of course
so, you're the children of king
Wolfkhan, but how?
He kept it hidden from us for a
reason
but what do I know? All I know
is was a lie
but how did you get here?
The night that we were, ahh,
sleeping, I had a visit from Morgan
the witch of my, our, father,
she told me of a sword
and how it would remind me of a
past that would belong to me
and how I was connected to it
she also gave me a crystal viewer, for
which I could overcome the swords power
and she showed me how I could
claim it
the king, the king himself told
me about this sword
it's the only weapon I can use
to win the tournament
and whoever won the tournament,
also takes his kingdom
he sent you here separately
a better chance the sword would
be captured
but what does that sword do?
Find a father
conquer a kingdom
prevent a monster from
conquering the world
well what are we waiting for?
Once you have found the sword
you must search for the two
waterfalls
follow the sun at sunset and
the darkest part of your sole
the doors to hell will close
only the sole asks to go beyond
the entrance
sacrificing his eternity to the
black world of the demons
teela what are you doing?
Put the sword down
to prove my love for you I have
followed you to the gates of hell
you must complete our mission if not I
will return and I will show you no mercy
teela, no!
Ahhhh!
It's time to go brother, there's
no turning back from here.
Yeah!
Teela.
Teela!
You are alive
my beloved this is how it must
be
I have but a few hours left in
the land of men
I will go and stop har
only a demon can fight another
demon
looking for me father
LA LA luna?
Ye ye yes!
Or maybe you'd prefer to call me
hell.
Father
what is that?
You, you useless coward!
How dare you try and hide your
descendants from me
your game is over human
and now, well now its your
children's turn
how dare you interfere with the
plans of the dark lord
I will crush you like the
cockroaches you are
victory is mine!
No one stops the coming of
warmond
Donna, what are you doing?
Comeback
know you know what you have to
do my sons
its what you were born for and the reasons I
had you brought up far away and in obscurity
but blood calls and destiny will
be fulfilled
no!
No!
Teela
I knew you'd make it
yes, but at what cost?
I cant loose you again.
Now you must look after your
people, king of keymock.