Subtitles by Renatinha Tankinha.
**Some words used in this movie have been written
as they are said, as they are fictitious words ***
- As the eternal cycle of
day and night continued,
morning light unveiled the ravages
of time self-inflicted calamity.
A world that was nothing more than a baring
indecent of rock floating in space.
Then came the thundering
engines of the scout ship
bringing the first echoing sounds in over a
million of years, to this arid landscape.
For the celestial explorers, this
was just another place to chart.
Catalogue and investigate, like the
thousands that had come before it.
They hoped to find something.
Evidence of life, perhaps.
An ancient fossil signified that
life had existed here, long ago.
Then, the faint signal
emanating form their device
posed a question: Was this the
product of an unknown intelligence?
They followed the signal,
which grew stronger,
their scans indicating that just ahead
was an object of massive proportions.
Kneeling over the source of
the signal, they carefully
brushed back the sand
and discovered a hatch.
But to what?
Once the handle was carefully
turned, the hatch opened.
Musty light led into the dark abyss
exposing hundreds of metallic
pods lining the chamber walls.
Their fellow travelers were beckoned.
And today, a wonderment
of the parts contain
the remnants of a long
lost civilization.
Affirming that this third planet from
its sun was once abundant with life.
With the impending end of their world
their parts have been engineered
in the hope that they would
one day be discovered.
In the living embryonic lifeforms induced
with state of suspended animation
would somehow be reborn into a new world.
For the inhabitants of this
new world once known as earth,
it would be a new beginning.
Anew age for mankind.
Humanity would live,
once again.
- Evidences are roaming
that there's a coverup,
and that there are aliens
visiting and so forth.
I...I think we do need to recognize
a new era has begun for mankind.
- I happen to be privileged
enough to be in on the
fact that we have been
visited on this planet.
And the UFO phenomenon is
real, although it's been
covered up by governments
for quite a long time.
The United States government
knew a whole lot more
about UFOs than it was
telling the American public.
There's an intelligence involved that
there was a highly evolved technology
that to a degree we were carrying a
dialogue with this intelligence.
- 'Cause I read NATO military material that
indicated that the UFOs were not only real,
they represented something far beyond
anything I had ever imagined before.
-Could I get...$60 on pump four, please?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
I understand over the years...
some peculiar things have been
happening around these parts.
Cattle mutilations,
strange lights in the
sky, things of that sort.
-No, I don't know anything about that.
-Really?
Okay.
Set to go? - Yes, sir.
-Son of a bitch.
Yes..
-May I ask why you chose me?
I've known who you are for some time now,
you seem like an honest man.
-I'm all about the truth.
And if what you're about
to tell me is the truth,
am I to understand we're
all in a very grave danger?
-Yes.
In five days,
human existence as you know it,
will forever change.
-Why don't we start with your name?
-Jaelen.
-Jaelen?
So, Jaelen, who are you?
You're speaking of the
Phoenix Lights incident?
Are you trying to tell
me you were aboard that craft?
-Yes.
-And where may I ask are you from, Jaelen?
- A star system in the
constellation Zanaté.
I'm Andromaden.
We were six.
Our task was to monitor human conditions
and to determine the
degree of infiltration.
-Infiltration by whom?
-Alpha Draconians.
-Draconians?
- Andromadens are one of
139 planetary systems
that comprise the
interstellar alliance.
We are and have always
been the watchdogs of
the universe for nearly
two million years.
And we have been at war with the Draconians
for nearly 100, 000 of those years.
They are a malevolent species
whose prime directive is
to conquer and destroy.
Entire star systems have been
wiped out by their aggression.
- And now we've become a target?
- You've always been a target.
Three million of your population
are comprised of these beings.
They are the one percent that control
corporations, government, media...
Years ago, the nation's leader
struck a deal with the Draconians.
In exchange for global control,
virtual enslavement of your people,
a selected few would be granted
amnesty from the coming onslaught.
They would be allowed to live out
their existence underground,
many have already begun to do so.
- And this onslaught, is this
what's gonna happen in five days?
- Two days ago, a Draconian warship reached
the outer rim of your solar system.
Their army is coming here to
establish complete dominion.
It has always been our intent
to shield you from this threat.
But we are entrenched in
war and we haven't the
means to bring the fleet
here to protect you.
It is to be your darkest age.
As I promised.
It's documents, photos,
videos and maps
of every secret military
underground base on the planet.
And plus complete data base of
all occupants of those bases.
- And you believe that this is
enough to convince the public?
-Regardless.
In five days, they will all believe.
- And you mention there
wasn't an excuse for it?
-Jaelen!
-Please stop it.
Stop it!
-I don't know any of it.
Just please...
-Where is he?
Where?
- I'm special agent John Walker
here on government business.
May I borrow a pen and
a piece of paper?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
The gentleman in room 15 is
under my protective custody.
There are people looking for him.
If anyone should come
inquiring, I'd appreciate
if you'd give me a call.
It's a mater of national security, you see?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Are you feeling better?
You gonna tell me what happened?
-Not now.
-Okay.
-What time is it?
-It's... uh... half past three.
- We need to go.
- Where?
- We're meeting someone.
- Who?
-A friend.
- You mentioned that there were six of you.
Where are the others?
-Gone.
-As in left or died?
-Died.
- Well, I'm very sorry.
- We were hunted down one by one.
All that they died for is this.
It's a Purean.
It contains a collective
data of human progression
as well as Draconian war plans.
Information that could be very helpful
in our cause in overcoming them.
- And how are you gonna
get that to your people?
- A rescue ship arrives tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
-At sun fall.
-So you're going home?
-No.
I'm not.
Turn left up here.
Your camera.
-Your friend, is he...
-From here?
No.
She's Arctorian.
- I don't think I've ever
met an Arctorian before.
Is she part of this
interstellar alliance?
-They are.
-Are they here to help us?
-Very much so.
-Good.
That's good.
-They're here.
-My God.
-This is Robert.
- The one you spoke?
- Yes.
- I am Tonjura. I am
pleased to meet you.
-It's an honor to meet you.
- We would like to extend
our deepest regret.
We cannot help you in this matter.
We are not a violent species.
And not equipped for war.
I'm sorry, Robert.
- The Arktorians have always been here.
Silently monitoring human progress,
along with several other races.
But now they're all returning home.
-You mean evacuating?
So now we really are alone.
-Yes.
Thousands of years of
accumulated human data
ends here.
- You could have gone back with them.
Why didn't you?
Or at least given them the Purian.
- They've fulfilled their
duties to the council.
This is not one of them.
And as I stated before, I'm not leaving.
-Is this John?
John Walker?
- Yes, yes, this is John Walker.
- It's Denise from the motel. You
told me to call if anyone came inquiring.
Well, there are government agents
inside this room as we speak.
Well, you didn't tell
them anything, did you?
- No. I didn't. But these
guys have real badges.
-Denise, I owe you big.
There's government agents
in your room right now.
Somehow they knew we were there.
Any idea how?
-Yes.
- Alright, We're gonna have to ditch this
car and hitch a ride into Albuquerque,
- What's in Albuquerque?
- A friend.
Whatever it is you're not telling
me, Jaelen, I need to know.
We're running out of time.
-I was compelled by her.
I began experiencing feelings
I never had before.
As if I were meant to find her.
I felt myself avoiding better
judgment that this was wrong.
A forbidden code of
conduct in my task here.
I allowed it to happen,
I wanted it to happen.
Andromedans enforce a very
structured mating ritual.
A choice for companion is never
our own and never random.
We're conditioned this way from birth.
Therefore there is never
the opportunity for...
-Falling in love?
-Yes.
- But did she know the
truth about you?
-I didn't have the time.
But I couldn't stay in one
place for to long, so
the day approached when
I had to tell her.
I haven't been entirely
honest with you.
-What do you mean?
-There are people looking for me.
- Who's looking for you?
Do you need any help?
-I'm not from here.
I'm not from Los Angeles,
and I'm not from the United States.
I'm not from earth.
The people looking for me
are getting close.
They also are not from earth.
-What do you...
What do you mean you're not from earth?
I don't...
- Listen, I care about you deeply.
- Then why are you telling me?
- To protect you.
-Uh... your
...association with me, I fear I'm
putting you in danger as well.
-Danger?
How can you...
how can you expect me to believe this?
Please, just...
make me understand.
-Alyssa...
there are things...
there are worlds outside of
this one you have no idea of.
And I am from one of these worlds.
I knew I would never
see her again.
I was devastated.
But we are more connected
than I even imagined.
She could hear my thoughts. She
could feel my pain in losing her.
-You were... telepathically linked?
-Yes.
Without my intention. It just happened.
Soon, we found each other again, and
we left together, heading west.
- Then what happened?
- My worst fear.
They found us.
I managed to get away unharmed,
but she was not so fortunate.
-So you're saying that
she's... - Dead?
No.
But they took her.
-Do you know where she is?
- She's a prisoner underground
at the Base of Dulce.
And they have been torturing her.
- So the telepathic link between the
two of you is how they tracked you?
-Yes.
-Look... uh...
I have no idea what you must
be going through right now.
You never told me her name.
-Her name is Alyssa.
And she carries my child.
- I've been an associate of
Chayton's since the early 90's.
He's devoted his life to
researching anomalous phenomenon
has established a strong
following in the UFO arena.
He was one of the
first to get hold of
the secret flying disk file of the FBI
and sensitive documents
from the CIA, air force,
army and other
government agencies.
The price he's paid for being
the truth to the public
are death threats, imprisonment
and getting shot at.
He is a good man,
and I trust him
as I would a brother.
- Thanks a lot, Derek. I appreciate
it. Can you give us a moment?
You don't know how good it is
to see you, my friend Chayton.
-Likewise.
You look good.
-I'm a lot better than I feel.
Uh... this is the gentleman I
was telling you about. Jaelen.
-Welcome.
-I'm gonna show him the footage.
-Why don't we start with your name?
-Jaelen.
-Jaelen?
So, Jaelen, who are you?
- Our task was to monitor
human conditions.
And to determine the
degree of infiltration.
-Infiltration by whom?
-Alpha Draconians.
-Draconians?
Jaelen!
Jaelen, what's happened?
Jaelen...
-They took it, Robert.
They took our baby.
-Alright we gotta... we gotta go.
- I'll take you to my house.
- That'd be perfect.
-It's safer.
- Our army is coming here to
establish complete dominion.
It has always been our intent
to shield you from this threat.
But we are entrenched in
war and we haven't the
means to bring the fleet
here to protect you.
It is to be your darkest age.
- Man, look at that. Look at
that. Look at that.
That's amazing.
-Open that one.
-Wow.
That's amazing.
Wow.
- We're gonna set the
world on fire with this.
-And I think soon.
- There, I got it.
- Dude, we got a helicopter.
Right behind there. See?
-Oh shit, we gotta go.
-Wow!
The mother lode.
- I think you're right.
No, wait, wait, wait. Go back.
Jaelen.
Is this her?
-It is.
-Who is she?
- A young woman Jaelen had the
good taste to fall in love with.
- You do have a good
taste, my friend.
-She's being held at the Dulce Base.
I'm quite sure her friends and family
would be interested to know that.
- How soon would you
be able to upload?
-Right now.
-Where are the files going into?
-To an old compadre of mine.
- They'll upload to sixty [ indistinct]
globally. The initial launch
should reach about 6 million people.
What's ETA?
-Just under four hours.
- By morning the flood
gates will be open.
35.39 degrees north.
And 106 .54 degrees west.
- Southwest corner of the
Haines Canyon Reservoir.
-Remember. Sun fall.
You'll give them the Purean.
And Robert,
you can go with them.
- Like you, Jaelen, there are
people that I can't leave behind.
Not with what's coming.
- Where will you go?
- Into the wolf's den.
To be near the woman he loves.
The Dulce base.
-Are you sure you're not human?
How will you get there?
I will take you.
Jaelen?
-I'm fine.
-Are you sure?
[SPEAKS NATIVE AMERICAN TONGUE]
Robert.
[SPEAKS NATIVE AMERICAN TONGUE] Jaelen.
[SPEAKS NATIVE AMERICAN TONGUE] Alyssa.
[CONTINUES SPEAKING NATIVE AMERICAN TONGUE]
-Despite the circumstances, I'm
happy to have known you, Robert.
-The feeling's mutual.
-I hope that we've made a
difference, you and I.
-We have.
Jaelen,
I'd like to wish
you good luck, but...
-Luck won't help me.
A miracle, perhaps.
-Where will you go?
-Chicago.
I've got a niece there
that I'm quite fond of
and a brother who hasn't
spoken to me in twenty years.
He doesn't believe in all this UFO crap.
-I see an exoneration in
your near future, my friend.
-Human eyesight has been
deceived for thousands of years.
-How so?
-The moon is an artificial construct.
it is a base where Alpha
Draconians and other races
have been manipulating human perception
by means of a projected signal.
In your way of understanding,
they've hacked into the
human consciousness.
They programmed exactly
what they want you to see.
-Corroborating the stories
that NASA adopted
photos of bases on the
moon's dark side.
-The role of NASA in this deceit
is greater than you imagine.
-Stop right there.
-You know it's coming.
You know we're gonna lose. It's inevitable.
What do you think you're gonna do?
What do you think you can do?
I'm a human being just like you.
-No, you're not.
-Are you there?
-Yes.
-He...
took our baby.
-I know.
I'm so sorry.
-Where are you?
-I'm coming to you.
-Aren't you going home?
-No.
-But they'll...kill you.
Please...
stay away.
-I can't.
-If I don't hear from you again,
I love you.
What will life be like there?
-Harmonious.
Tranquil.
Our planet is a single continent.
Two suns...
no seasons. It's a
constant temperature.
-Are there any oceans?
-There is one.
Our water's of a different
consistency, different color,
it contains all the nutrients that we
require. There is no need for food.
Though we're at war, we
will live in a safe zone.
Our child will be shielded
from the dangers coming near.
Time is different there.
your lifespan will be three times
what it is here on Earth.
-Really?
-We're free of all diseases
and all the illnesses.
-It's starting to sound like paradise.
-With you there, it will be.
-Get out of the vehicle now!
Cross your legs, put
your hands on your head.
Cross your legs!
-Chayton! Chayton!
Robert...
Robert, can you hear me?
Robert, are you there?
-Jaelen.
-I'm speaking to you with my thoughts.
-Where are you?
-They have me in captivity.
And Robert...
they killed Chayton.
There was nothing I could do.
I'm inside the base.
I'm where I need to be.
-Yeah. Yeah, it's me.
Now, listen to me very carefully.
In about 40 minutes you'll
have the files to upload.
Text me when it's done, but
do not, I repeat,
do not do anything until you hear from me.
If you don't hear from me
by this time tomorrow,
launch.
Is that clear?
Yeah.
-I'll keep this brief, Jaelen.
Knowing the impossibility
of rescuing your companion,
I can only imagine that you came
here in the hopes to see her.
To be with her.
This was a misjudgment.
We will not grant this union.
As for yourself,
like your five companions before
you, you will be dissected
and studied by our scientists,
in hopes that we might better
understand your telepathic abilities.
You may be aware that
one of our duties here is to see to the...
appetites of our hosts.
Your companion will be
euthanized, and parts
of her extracted,
for the delicacies.
As for the son you've fathered,
he'll be taken to Capella,
where in manhood
he will serve as a Draconian agent.
He and ten will father hybrids
who will also serve in this capacity.
So you see, you
will be serving a
significant contribution to
the Draconian cause.
And for this
we are grateful.
-The Dulce Base is located
beneath the Archuleta Mesa
It's size is 4.6 miles in diameter.
The base has seven levels.
The last two of which are
designated for lab experimentation.
These tests are carried out
by humans and Draconians.
It's the sixth level where
Alyssa is being held.
One of the secret entrances
is on the Mesa itself.
The location was delivered
to us by one of our allies
contained on the disk drive I gave you.
-Can't you just get her to
walk in the back door?
-Unless they find me first.
-What makes you think
they won't kill you?
-It's a chance I'm willing to take.
-She must be a very
special woman.
-Yes.
I'm here, Alyssa.
Where are you?
Why don't you answer me?
-Welcome, Mr. Casey.
-Check him.
-And who, may I ask, are you?
-Marek
Thai is Trea.
-Let me guess: Draconians?
-We are.
-Well, then I'm certainly
not pleased to meet you.
-It's clean where I found this.
-Whatever your reason
is for coming here,
understand
we have no intention nor
interest in keeping you alive.
-So I'm dead either way, right?
-Correct.
No one will be spared.
-Why?
-The Earth's position in
the solar system provides
us with a strategic and
tactile advantage.
-Robert, the human role in the
universe is inconsequential.
-That may be so, but we
have a right to exist.
-Only if we allow it.
-And we don't.
-Well, before you start
waving your victory flag,
might I suggest examining the contents
of the drive you hold in your hand?
I think you'll find it very consequential.
-Alright.
Take him.
And Robert,
Jaelen had something
we very much want.
It's a Grey stone that
contains crystals.
-What? You mean the Parean?
-Yes. You wouldn't know
where it is, would you?
-Sure. it's right here.
-Alright, 300 self-retraining
tractor, please.
-Preparing  Euthanization.
-It's time, Jaelen.
-Good.
So...
-So, it would seem that your
drive contains sensitive
information that some of
you find distressing.
However, all it can serve
is to tell people what they'll
find out anyway in four days.
-I mean, yes...
but you're forgetting one thing.
The locations of all your hidden
bases and their secret entrances.
What do you think? I just waltzed in here?
I want you to think of tens of thousands
of me storming your underground
castles with automatic weapons. You'll have
one hell of a shit storm to contend with.
And don't think for one
moment it won't happen.
Vengeance and survival at all costs
are two very profound
impulses we humans have.
-I see.
So am I then, to understand that this
information has not yet been released?
-No, it hasn't.
But if I don't make a phone call,
it will go viral to a few million people.
By sun down, your phones will be ringing
off the hook and in a few days,
you'll be running from
a shower of bullets.
Now, I also have the power to
keep it from going out at all.
And then you cowards can hide down
here in your underground fortress
without any worries.
-And why should we trust you?
-Because I'm not so
eager to hand out doomsday
news to the world.
These last few days of life
are all we have left.
Why spoil it?
-Indeed.
Alright.
What are you terms in
exchange for this?
An arrangement's been made.
-No...
When I know they're safe.
-Yes.
It's done.
-You're safe now.
We are grateful.
-Yeah, it's me.
Launch.
-You have betrayed
your promise to me!
-On behalf of the 7.1 billion humans on
this planet earth that you have condemned,
Fuck you!
-The day that was
mankind's darkest came
and the invasion began.
At first,
the take over was not so easy.
The resistance from
humans was formidable,
but in time, futile.
Most of the underground bases
were stormed, many died,
Within weeks, the genocide had begun.
By the time our fleet
returned months later,
nearly one half of all humans
had been exterminated.
In a battle that raged for many days,
our fleet managed to rescue
nearly three million humans.
It was our only return to earth.
By now, it is certain that the remaining
human population is long gone.
The ones rescued
represent all that is left of mankind.
The Arcturus constellation is a planet
very much like Earth and non-inhabited.
Known as Boötes,
it is here where humans have
already begun their renaissance.
Free of war, instability, and oppression.
the rebirth has been prosperous.
As the Science Officer of
the Andromedan Council,
I often frequent with Alyssa at my side
to monitor human development.
And I am often reminded of the final
passage of one of Robert's short stories.
For the inhabitants of this
planet once known as earth,
it would be a new beginning,
a new age for mankind.
Humanity would live...
once again.
The end