[Music playing]
While conditions for women
have improved in the West,
Here in Ganzar,
they're among the worst
in the world.
It's no exaggeration
to say that these women
Live their lives
essentially as slaves.
[Static]
Am I still on air?
Damn!
MAN: I'm sure
reception
will improve
Once we get
out of this pass,
Ms. Prescott.
No. I mean, do we
think the warlords
Are gonna put
their guns down
Just because I'm here
for an election-year
photo op?
We're wasting our time.
It only takes
one pebble to start
an avalanche.
Thanks,
Agent Fortune Cookie.
What the he is this?
Reynolds.
Camelot One to Camelot Two.
What's the holdup?
I'll take care of it
in a second.
We gotta move this cart.
Jones is down!
He's got a gun!
Get down!
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Gunfire]
Webber,
get Elise to safety!
Elise, you okay?
Think I'm okay.
I'm activating
the homing beacon
in your watch.
You can run due east.
Someone will be by to get you
within 30 minutes!
You're coming with me,
aren't you?
I gotta cover you! Go!
[Gasps]
[Gasping]
I like your watch.
May I see it?
Get up.
You can imagine
what can happen
To a pretty thing like you
in these mountains.
What are you
gonna do to me?
Heh. That depends
on the President
of the United States,
Or, as you call him,
Daddy.
[Chuckles]
Move.
[Telephone rings]
[cellphone buzzes]
Kendall.
When?
I'll be there
in 10 minutes.
Woman: Put me up to speed.
Two hours ago,
the First Daughter's
convoy
Was hit by militants
in the mountains
near Ganzar province.
Approximately
30 minutes ago,
The White House
received that
via email.
Hello, Mr. President
and presumably members
Of the U.S.
intelligence agencies.
You may call me Ulrika,
Though I assume you have
a thorough dossier already.
But I want you to say hello
to my new houseguest.
I will make you
a simple offer.
My country is in disarray.
It's fractured.
We need a strong leader
to unite it,
And that leader
shall be me.
But I need your help.
I ask of the U.S.
To liberate my country
from its shackles,
Eliminate the rivals,
pretenders to the throne,
And install me
as the legitimate President.
You do this,
and I will become
A very, very good friend
to America.
You've got 48 hours from
the receipt of this email.
Do not play me for the fool.
If I see as much
as one drone,
One G.I. footprint
in the dirt,
Then I'll start mailing
pieces of her
Back to you.
Ohh.
Even such grotesque things
Are of great value
To any number
of America's enemies.
Holy fuck.
Yeah, that about
says it.
[Sighs]
Tell me the President
Is nowhere near
the Situation Room.
Oh, he wants blood,
But has
recused himself.
Now, as far as the press
is concerned,
He's going through
a routine medical procedure.
The good news
is we've managed
To keep a lid
on the kidnapping so far.
So what do we know
about this woman?
She's one of five
significant warlords
in the territory.
Now, we don't know
her place of origin,
Date of birth or if
Ulrika's even her real name,
But we do know
that she trusts no man
Except for her right hand,
Grigori Babishkova.
Their base of operations
is a former Soviet prison.
It's a virtual fortress.
The locals call it
"the Citadel."
Frontal assault is out.
This isn't bin Laden's
condo in Abbottabad.
She'd be dead
while we're still
Trying to kick in
the front door.
Well, that leaves us
With a long shot,
infiltration.
Now, the problem with that
is, other than Grigori,
She's completely paranoid
about all men.
I mean,
her psych evaluation says
That it's
almost pathological,
unresolved paternal...
Daddy issues. Got it.
So she'd be doubly on guard
If some strange men
started knocking at her door.
What does she feel
about women?
Oh, her hate is unisex.
She thinks women are weak
And underestimates them.
Then that's
who we go with.
Use her prejudice
against her.
We don't have anyone,
ma'am,
I mean,
at least not qualified.
The military
changed their position
on women in combat
Too soon for this one.
And our own people?
Anyone who could
is too imbedded,
And, I mean, even if
we could get them out
Without blowing their cover
or getting them killed,
We couldn't do it in time.
We just
need to think outside
the box in this case.
Or more accurately...
Inside the Box.
[Sighs] Is that
two weeks up already?
Pizza day.
[Cracking knucles]
I been waiting
for today, Clay.
Me, too.
You only got two weeks
in the hole,
But my girl's still
stuck in infirmary,
Breathing
through a goddamn tube.
I told her
what would happen
If she didn't stop
shaking me down.
You don't think
you gotta pay me tribute
Like everybody else
around here?
No.
And what was
with the lackey?
You should have
told me to my face.
Aw, Clay,
you know I prefer
Talking about people
behind they back.
[Grunts]
I just wanted
my goddamn pizza.
Thanks.
Cassandra Clay?
What?
Here, kitty, kitty.
Fuck off, Pignatelli.
I'm working.
Don't worry.
I'll pay you
every penny
you're worth.
[Grunts]
KENDALL:
Kat Morgan?
Yeah.
Little privacy,
please.
I'll be keeping
an eye out on you.
Hey, pig face!
Fuck!
You'll do.
[Grunts]
Mei-Lin Fong?
[Sighs] CIA?
Give me a moment.
[Sighs]
[Women yelling]
Eww! What the hell?!
Nice trick.
Thank you.
Mona.
Raven.
I knew it was
just a matter of time
Before you
came crawling back.
Cutie-pie.
Office perk?
Surprise.
Fucking bitch!
Ladies, I hope you excuse
the rough treatment,
But time is money.
Mae-Lin Fong,
explosive ordnance disposal,
Qualified
multiengine pilot.
I also play piano.
Then you turned
self-styled techno-anarchist,
Blew up what you
described at the trial
As a "crooked
Wall Street bank."
Sentenced to 15 years.
[Mouths words]
What does a Chinese girl
Know about
making bombs, anyway?
[Faking accent]
Oh, the Chinese
invented gunpowder.
[No accent]
Or did they not
teach you that
In the trailer park,
sugar tits?
Kathryn Morgan,
Marine-Corps-qualified
scout sniper.
10 years for shooting up
your boyfriend's truck
While he and
his mistress were in it.
Shocker.
Not that great of a job.
You missed.
If I wanted them dead,
I would have
only needed two rounds.
I was just teaching
that cheap bastard
a lesson.
Cassandra Clay,
part of the pilot program
To prove that women
can serve in combat.
Ranger school, then Delta.
You were even given command
of your own little unit.
A real old G.I. Jane...
Until you lost half
your team in Afghanistan,
Attacked your C.O.
25 years
for nearly killing him.
You broke his arm,
Broke his legs,
one in four places,
Broke three ribs,
which resulted
in puncturing his lung.
You squashed
his eye socket.
Look, I can't
take credit
for all of that.
He was also
hit by a truck.
When you threw him
into it.
And then
at your court-martial,
Not one peep of why.
I couldn't recall.
Saving the best
for last?
Raven.
I'm not gonna tell
your real name,
Agency courtesy and all.
That, and I'd crush
your fucking throat.
You've seen
everybody's dirty laundry.
I think it's time
they see yours.
You see,
Raven was one of us.
We taught her how
to seduce and kill,
And she did it well,
very well,
Until she started moonlighting
as a hit woman for hire.
Private sector
paid good.
We might have
turned our backs on that,
But then you
killed one of ours.
That paid even better.
You're all pieces of shit...
But today you're
lucky pieces of shit,
Because Uncle Sam
wants you.
Uncle Sam must be really
fucking desperate.
The President's daughter
Was kidnapped
by an Amazonian she-bitch,
And she has her hostage
in some castle
In the backwoods
of Shit-hole-istan,
And she wants us
to prop her up
as new head of state.
We're gonna tell her
go to hell.
First, we need
to get Elise back,
So this is the reason I'm
putting this team together.
Kat, long-range
interdictions,
communications.
Mei-Lin, explosives.
Raven,
close-quarters wetwork.
Clay, tactical training
and command.
You get in, grab the girl,
get out. Simple.
Just the four of us?
No backup?
Right.
Simple.
Sounds like
a suicide mission.
Well, that's why
we're sending in
you four.
Oh lovely.
What's the job pay?
We've been authorized
To give each of you
a full Presidential pardon.
And even you, Raven,
With potential to be
reinstated in your
previous positions.
Of course, that's gonna
depend on the success
of the mission.
How does that sound,
Captain?
What happens
if we say no?
Well, if you say no,
Then you go
back to your hole,
And you serve
the maximum sentence.
We might even put
a few more charges
on top of that,
Depending on how vindictive
the President feels
When his daughter
comes home in several
small packages.
So what's it gonna be,
ladies?
When do we start?
We already have.
[Crying]
[clang]
I brought you
some food, hon.
[Snaps fingers]
Did the cook
char your chicken?
May not be
a state dinner,
But it's more than
virtually every resident
here eats in a day.
You shouldn't waste it.
The United States
doesn't do any negotiations.
For the masses, no,
But for you,
The rules are different,
And there's
virtually no price
Your father wouldn't pay
to get you back.
What makes you think
that he won't bomb you
Even farther
to the Stone Age
if something happens to me?
[Chuckles]
So educated,
yet so naïve.
The bullying Americans
Invading
another poor nation
for revenge?
Not in an election year.
The exit!
Now!
Silly girl.
[Chuckles]
Step away,
or she's dead!
Try anything funny,
And I'll slit
your throat!
Go ahead! Slit my throat!
I give you permission!
I am not
fooling around here!
Neither am I.
Shut up!
I swear I'll do it!
Do it!
Shut up!
Killing me
is the only way
out of here! Do it!
Shut up!
How disappointing.
I promised not to harm you,
not yet,
But you do understand
that insolence cannot
go unpunished.
Someone else has to be
punished in your place.
No! Let me go!
Stop! No!
No. Please.
[Speaking
Slavic language]
Please. No.
[Sobbing]
[Kiss]
You remember this
Next time you try
anything foolish, bitch!
[Exhales]
[Sighs]
Feel free.
No, uh,
changing rooms?
Bashful, are we?
You want to unhook
the back?
[Sighs]
Ladies.
Better than
prison jumpsuits,
isn't it?
We put together
something special
for each of you
That suits
your individual tastes.
It's German-made,
Blaser R93 bolt action
sniper rifle.
Shoots a .338 Lapua Magnum
with a five-round load,
Comes customized
for you, Kat,
With a Harris
bipod attachment,
And a 4-by-32 tactical
milled out scope,
With a ballistics computer
built into the optics.
Hmm.
Twin Glock 19.
Can shoot
nine-millimeter parabellums
In a 14-round clip.
Just the way
I remember them.
Come to me, girls.
Triggers aren't
broken in.
These aren't mine.
Your originals
are in my office.
I had them made
into paperweights.
No problem.
I'm sure I'll find
a way to break these in.
I'm sure you will.
ISA issue, Mark Four...
Mark Four
demolitions package...
C-PAT microdetonators,
Proximity
and radio frequency
switches
And next-generation
Semtex,
Moldable, concealable
and undetectable
To all current
bomb-sniffing tests.
Anything else?
What?
No toys for me?
Ah, well, anyone can tell
you're a purist,
So we figured
the best thing with you
was to keep things simple.
M-1911A1 .45 Colt.
Old-school gun
for an old-school girl.
Woman. I meant woman.
Would you pull
your shirt up for me?
What is that?
It's a universal
access number.
You get into trouble,
you dial this number.
Any phone in the world,
it will ring back here.
This chip is undetectable
to any metal detector.
This may sting.
[Thunk]
Ahh!
Fuck.
What happened
to old-school
memorization?
[Thunk]
Shit!
Unh!
Ladies,
your carriage arrives.
[Engine bangs]
That piece of shit?
Hey, you be kind
to Lula, huh?
"Tajikistan
Motoring Press"
Named her
car of decade.
Heh. What decade?
The eighties?
[Shushes]
I am Vez,
number one in import,
export to Ganzar.
You're a smuggler.
So was Han Solo.
The important thing
is that he says
He can get you
into the Citadel.
How?
I have man on inside
Who will vouch for you.
He's second cousin
to third sister's
husband,
But I know him
like first cousin
To second sister's
husband,
And for right price,
he looks other way.
Any more questions?
Yeah.
What's to stop us
from splitting the moment
we hit the road?
You mean, like
the micro-explosive
that's implanted
Subdermally
in your carotid
When you were
all knocked out?
Are you serious?
No.
We don't
need insurance.
Look at you.
This is what you
were built for.
Road to Citadel
is swarming with patrols.
Is best to go local.
Ohh! Oh, my God!
What is that?
It smells like yak piss.
No, no, no,
is not yak.
Is goat.
Do you really
trust this guy?
As much as I trust you.
So what do we do
with Ulrika?
Leave her. The brass
wants to ask her
a few choice questions
Before they shove her
into a dark, deep hole.
Sorry to ruin your fun.
Elise is the objective.
Rescue her,
and you're free.
The clock's ticking.
Hey, I driver.
I no porter.
VEZ: You have
song in America.
Is a Christmas song.
Is very stupid song.
Is, uh, Adolf reindeer
with red nose.
You know
this song, huh?
Is about
mutant, uh, reindeer
With
a bioluminescent nose.
He's outcast.
He's freak.
All of the reindeer,
they make fun of him...
So let's pretend we're
real military again,
Chain of command
and everything.
Let's rescue
Princess Peach,
Let's get our pardons,
And let's just never
see each other again.
Fine by me.
Kat, run the crypto check,
pretty please.
Charlie 2-3,
this is Foxtrot 1-2.
Crypto check. Over.
Why are we slowing down?
It's Ulrika's patrols, eh?
VEZ: Don't worry.
I handle it.
No, no, no, no.
We keep it cool,
all right?
We can't risk them...
We can't risk them
calling us in.
Guns away.
Hide your face.
[Speaking
Slavic language]
Merchandise.
Merchandise?
Mm.
Open it.
Hey. Heh heh.
See? Merchandise.
Oh.
I'm going to need
to sample your merchandise.
[Chuckles]
No, no, no, no, no.
You... You don't
want this, eh?
These women,
they're good for
housework only, eh?
They have,
eh, disease.
Make your dick
fall off.
Just a blow job, then.
[Chuckles]
I like this one.
Do you wanna
give me a blow job?
I asked you
a question!
RAVEN: Here's
your fucking answer.
Oh, shit!
Americans.
Runner at 11 o'clock!
KAT: I got this.
Good shot.
Yeah.
It's Clay.
What's going on?
Encountered hostiles.
Our transpo is
out of commission.
We lost Vez
and the contact.
Recommend
we abort mission.
That's a negative.
I repeat...
Our ride is shit-canned,
And we have no leads.
The mission is fucked.
Strongly recommend
we abort.
In less than 24 hours,
Care packages with bits
of the First Daughter
Is gonna
start showing up
at Pennsylvania Avenue.
You're smart.
Just find another way
to get in.
Use your
feminine charms.
Charlie 2-3 out.
[Sighs]
Looks like
we're walking, ladies.
Talk about
your shit-holes.
They haven't
had a functioning
government
Since
the Soviet Union.
One can
hardly expect them
To maintain
infrastructure.
Cool guns.
Thanks.
American, yeah?
Come to save us?
Not exactly.
I love America.
You guys all have
The best stuff,
the best movies,
even have same gun.
Hey, we got it, kid.
You don't look
like Army.
We're not.
You're mercs, aren't you?
I knew it.
I'm Lexi. You should
let me join up with you.
I'll help you,
and then you bring me
Back to America
with you. Deal?
Look, kid,
we're not nice women.
We're not gonna have
some fun adventure.
We gotta
do some very bad things
to some very bad people,
And it's no place
for a teenager.
I can take it.
I got skills to pay bills.
Hah! Hah!
Be gone, kid!
[Hisses]
[Chuckles]
Was that
really necessary?
Unless you
want to be responsible
For that girl's life,
yeah, it was.
Contact HQ.
Let Mona know that we
made our way into town.
I would have
shot her ass.
Yeah, I know you would.
Oh, shit!
My sat-phone.
Lexi!
Ready or not,
here I come!
Shit.
You take the doors. We meet
around back.
Shit.
Oh, come on!
You guys are
making this boring!
That cheeky little bitch.
You almost had me.
Too bad I'm just
too good for you.
I could have eaten
for a month
With what I would
have made from that.
We'd like to help,
but, uh, we need this.
That was
some nice work, though.
So can I join up?
Go back to being a kid.
Okay, but you'll never
get into the Citadel,
Not without me.
That is why
you're here, right?
Ulrika?
What do you know about it?
I know that
ever since yesterday,
Security has been
tighter than ever.
Something big
is going on.
Ulrika's going to be
very cautious.
Fortunately,
I have an idea.
All right, kid.
What do you got?
Every week, Ulrika sends
a truck to the port,
And, every week,
that truck comes back,
Always on
the same day, today.
What's inside?
Don't know.
Sometimes guns,
Sometimes medicine,
But always valuable,
And I know
exactly what route
they take.
Lexi...
You want to be
on the team?
I still think you guys
should have let me
use a bigger charge.
All right, Annie Oakley,
you're up.
Target has
been diverted.
[Beep]
Were you gonna
use that piece
of shit on me?
Keeping body count
to a minimum.
You're no fun, Clay.
What are
you gonna do?
[Groans]
You know what?
Pull that trigger,
I open a vein.
"Thank you for saving
my ass, Mei-Lin."
My pleasure, Raven.
Domo.
That's Japanese, bitch.
Same shit.
[Whistles]
Wow.
What kind
of missiles
are these?
ICBM.
Which is?
Intercontinental
Ballistic Missile
With a minimum range
of more than
5,500 kilometers.
Primarily designed for
nuclear weapons delivery.
Well, I guess I
know what to get you
for your birthday.
We could put this
On my Christmas list.
We're not
taking that, Raven.
And we're not keeping
those either, Mei-Lin.
Where you gonna put em?
Well, looks like we found
our calling card.
So let's
get into character
And start calling.
[Honking]
Ulrika.
What?
They've found us.
Lose something?
Thank you for returning
my shipment.
You've earned
30 seconds of my time.
I suggest you use it
to persuade me
not to shoot you.
Absolutely.
We could have kept
this bad boy
And sold
what was inside,
But that would
be peanuts
Compared to what
we have to offer.
Which is?
If you will...
Fannie Pong...
Daughter of Pong Fan Shui,
the industrialist.
Third-richest man
in China.
You broker the deal.
We split the ransom.
GRIGORI:
Checking identity online.
See how easy it is
To change Wikipedia?
[snorts]
Shut up!
Fannie Pong,
confirmed.
Your offer is enticing.
Now explain why it
makes sense to me to not
just kill you now
And keep all the ransom
for myself?
Well, that's an option,
But you'd be missing out
on a very lucrative
partnership.
Pong is just
the introductory offer.
See, we're good
at acquiring high-value
packages like this.
We just hate the paperwork.
Well, you've come
at a very inopportune
time for me.
I'm not sure
I want to take on
new distractions.
If you don't want
the easy payday,
I'm sure one of your rivals
will be interested.
[Speaking Slavic language]
You knew coming in here
That I would never
let you give such
a prize to any of them.
[Speaking Slavic language]
Now, y-you don't
want to shoot us.
Well, at least not me,
Not if you want to know
what I changed
The missile's
arm-disarm codes to.
'Cause, see,
without those...
Hi...
These are about
as effective as
a couple of sparklers.
What makes you think
that I won't torture
them out of you?
Oh, I know you would.
I just... I don't know
if you've got the time.
[Chuckles]
Good.
That's a difference
between men and women,
Brains,
not thick-headed muscle.
But I could keep pushing,
Because I know
you'll flinch first.
But it's so rare to meet
such industrious women...
So for right now,
I think it's
more exciting if I, um,
Say, "Deal."
Deal.
Grigori, have the ICBM
taken to the airfield
And loaded on the plane.
I want it
ready to ship
As soon as the funds
are wired.
[whistles]
Why don't you
and your associates
come with me,
And let's
hammer out the details
of our arrangement.
Whoa! No.
Not you, kid.
Sorry. You stay here.
What?
That's fucking bullshit!
Excuse me?
I told you
about this truck!
This was all my idea!
Stealing my truck
was your idea?
What's your name,
girl?
Lexi.
Grigori, show Lexi
our gratitude.
Finder's fee.
Cool.
Don't do it again.
Oh, I almost forgot.
For being incompetent
enough to be foiled
by a little girl's plans...
[snaps fingers]
Why don't we go to
the new VIP suites.
Come on.
Why don't you make sure
Lexi gets home safe.
I was never big
on sightseeing, anyway.
Good.
Go find something to do.
[Hisses]
So, what y'all do
for fun around here?
As you can see,
your country's war on terror
has been excellent for us.
Suicide vests.
Ah-ah. Can't give away
trade secrets
to a stranger.
Oh, just as well.
We're
business partners.
We use a sealed
gelatin explosive pack
With ceramic
ball bearings
Designed to pass
right through
Metal detectors
and bomb sniffers.
For our brothers
in the Middle East fighting
the imperialistic and...
Ha ha!
Whatever those crazies say.
But they pay in cash,
So if the fools want
72 virgins that bad,
none of my concern.
If I were you,
I would avoid
Your shopping malls
for the next few weeks.
[Beep]
Ladies...
I spared no expense.
Only I know
the code to these.
Call me paranoid.
[Beeping]
Okay.
Ow!
[Beeps]
What is this?
Business,
in a sense,
The oldest
business.
Prostitution.
Every woman
under my care
Are required
to perform so.
Money can only
buy a man's loyalty
for so long,
So if you really
want to control them,
Control
the choice pussy
in the region,
And the rest
is easy.
Well, you better hope
the choice pussy
Keeps getting
themselves locked up.
[laughs]
Well, of course.
Sooner or later,
Every woman winds up
in my prison.
[Footsteps scuffling]
Ah.
Here we are.
A new resident.
Uhp-uhp-uhp-uhp.
[Speaking
Slavic language]
Round up villagers
for revolt.
Says you killed
her sister.
Ah, yes,
The chambermaid
from yesterday.
Oh, Grigori did
make a mess of her.
And then to just
dump the body
On the side
of the river, ooh.
When Grigori
is done with her,
She'll be
as obedient
as a poodle.
[Chuckles]
[Woman gasping]
You like to watch,
Katrushka?
[Spits]
Next time.
Stick to the plan,
soldier.
We can't save her.
Elise is
the mission.
I don't know
who the bigger bitch is,
You or her.
I want to be up front
with you, Ms. Clay.
I don't trust you.
So why did you
let us in?
Well, never let it
be said that I put
paranoia before profit.
Well, look.
Listen,
if you're too busy,
Why don't you just
email me your schedule,
And we can do this
another time.
We haven't even gotten
to know each other yet.
Your accent, American.
Your posture, your poise,
military. [Chuckles]
Forgive me
for being curious.
My Army days
are long gone.
Dishonorable
discharge.
Go on.
I had 20 good men
underneath me
And a prick
of a C.O.
He said that women
in combat were a joke...
So he would
give us missions
That were more
and more complicated,
Hoping that
I would fail,
And every time
I succeeded,
It just really
pissed him off.
One day, he tasked us
with clearing
A cave complex
in Waziristan.
Well, we walked in,
And we were looking
at a hundred fighters.
That was the beginning
of 14 hours of hell,
At the end
of which I was one
of the lucky ones.
I only caught
two bullets.
Come to find out
My C.O.
was intentionally
withholding intel.
11 good men died
Because he
couldn't stand to see
a woman in charge.
So when I got
out of the hospital,
I put him in one.
Heh.
I knew there was something
I liked about you, Clay.
Your boss lady
says we should make
ourselves at home.
At home, I...
I never liked
to drink alone.
We are part
of an elite sorority,
Women that have earned
the command of men.
So tell me, how did
you earn yours?
My father.
He was a great
military leader,
But he would never
have given me the power
like he would a son,
So I shot him in the eyes,
and I took it.
But then I realized
Staying on top,
that's a challenge.
Very true.
Everyone wants
to steal your power,
So I've learned
to distrust everyone.
So forgive me
for asking, Clay.
Why, of all days,
did you come today?
Well, we didn't have
the bomb yesterday.
Perhaps.
Perhaps there's
more to it than that.
I don't know
what to tell you.
[Chuckles]
Well, I can easily have
my men make you tell me,
But for a kindred spirit,
I prefer
a different approach.
Hey, there, fellas.
Poker.
My favorite.
Deal me in.
Here's to the hole
that never heals
The more you lick it.
Ah. Na zdraví.
[Both laugh]
I have
a high-profile prisoner,
One that I'm sure
will attract at least
one rescue attempt,
And here you are
right on schedule.
Be truthful with me,
And I'll be lenient,
Even generous.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Heh.
That's a bit of a lie.
Your background,
that wasn't.
Your country
may have faith in you,
But I think you've
lost faith in them.
Isn't there something
you would like
To get off your chest?
Bap!
Boom.
[laughs]
I win again.
[laughs] Your ass
was really hoping
For that nine
from the river, huh?
And, you, I'm gonna
give you a free tip.
Stop with
that blinking shit.
Everybody knows that mean
you ain't got nothing. Damn.
[laughs]
Versace, Versace,
Versace.
You're gonna
have to wait
till next hand
To be dealt in,
new booty.
Enh.
[Chuckles]
I don't gamble.
Even if the stakes
are high
And the game
is rigged?
Hmm?
Ha! [Laughs]
[Chuckles]
[laughs]
[Speaking
Slavic language]
Do it, Mommy.
Shoot me.
So tempting, baby.
But first, I need you
to call your boss.
[Steady beeping]
They know I'm not
to be disturbed
When I'm
discussing business.
[Beep-beep]
Now, where were we?
Thanks for the drink.
Cheers.
To nipples,
Because without them,
Titties
would be pointless.
[laughs]
[Speaking
Slavic language]
[laughs]
Come on.
Shit.
Son of a bitch.
That's better.
[Exhales]
Okay, girls, let's go.
About fucking time!
[Groans]
In position.
Go to the end
of the hall. Turn left.
Go down two doors.
Make a right.
Clay, hang back.
Clear. Go.
Thanks, Kat.
Mei-Lin, it's me.
And just try
and keep it quiet.
It's about time.
"Keep it quiet,"
she says.
You keep it quiet.
I'm gonna show you.
[Man gasps]
[Kat grunts]
Whoo! Hot damn!
Silent-mite.
No boom,
no bang, no fun.
Oh. What'd I miss?
You look like shit.
Come on, Princess.
Elise.
Elise Prescott.
Yes?
Step back from the door.
CLAY: Clear!
[Boom]
Okay, come on.
Who are you?
Jehovah's Witness.
Can we talk about
Jesus Christ? Come on.
[laughs]
You guys better
get moving.
Okay. Raven,
how are we
at the motor pool?
RAVEN: I got you
covered, Clay.
Okay, just keep
on that track.
You got a clear path.
Anybody on your tail?
Negative.
Good.
Ohh!
Hit the lights!
[Speaking
Slavic language]
Clay, you owe me
a bottle of single-malt.
What the fuck
am I gonna do
With a pardon, Clay?
Get a job?
Find Mr. Right?
You and I
both know damn well
I'll be back in the Box
within a year.
So I made a change
to the plan,
Mm-hmm, made
a last-minute deal
with Grigori,
Not that he was
in any position
to argue.
[Chuckles]
Ulrika agreed.
Here's my new
Minister of Tourism.
Yep.
I'm gonna wine and dine
all the Americans,
Mm-hmm,
Get them to make
their movies here.
Hell, I might even
fuck George Clooney,
With a strap-on.
We're gonna run for it.
Are you serious?
Clay!
[Music playing]
[No audible dialogue]
[Whispers]
Okay. Come on.
We're gonna
have to jump, okay?
Are you fucking crazy?
Elise, trust me. You can do
this.
[Screams]
ELISE: No!
Let's go. Come on!
Move!
[sobbing]
Come on.
Take her
to her cell.
The other two,
do as you please.
Where's
the other American?
Shot the fucking bitch.
Hey, Grigori...
Eh?
The girl
that helped them,
What was her name?
Lexi.
Ah, Lexi. Okay.
[Gasping]
Fuck.
[Wincing]
God! Fuck!
May I...
Okay?
Thanks.
KENDALL: This was always
a long shot, Clay.
Pack it up. Head back here.
I'm really surprised that
you got as far as you did.
There's nothing more
you can do for them.
[Vehicle approaching]
[Gasping]
Lexi.
Lexi, baby, are you awake?
Oh, hi.
Okay, don't go to sleep,
okay, sweetheart?
I'm gonna take you
to America, okay?
You can go
to the mall. Heh.
We're gonna watch
crappy movies on cable TV.
You can go to the prom.
You'll do all those things
That teenagers are
supposed to do, okay?
Just don't go to sleep.
[Coughs]
Oh, my God.
Didn't anyone
ever tell you
It's not nice
to lie to kids?
[Crying]
[Whispers]
I'm sorry.
[Bottle shatters]
[Bottles shatters]
Ohh!
What? You just
gonna pick on her?
Don't tell me
you've gone PC.
You know what
the problem is with
Chinese cuisine?
Too much MSG.
Never enough salt!
[Screams]
[Groans]
Ah shit!
[Bone cracks]
[screams]
Ohh! Aah!
You're fucking kidding me.
[Gunfire]
The bidding
has started.
Excellent.
I'd stay
and watch,
But I've got
Iran, North Korea
And Al Qaeda
very interested
In paying
for the honor
Of killing
the First Daughter.
Grigori,
they're all yours.
Enjoy.
Heh.
You can have
the Oriental.
The white woman is mine.
[Radio]
Boss, we have
a situation
You should see up here.
[Speaking
Slavic language]
Not a finger on this one
until I return.
This one,
Do as you please.
[Spits]
[Speaking Slavic language]
Hmm?
Next time, do it yourself,
Or I blow your
little fucking dick off.
[Gunshot]
[Gasps]
[Bone cracks]
She's out
of your league, pal.
Are you here for us,
Or do you just
need us for Elise?
I'm here for everyone...
Everyone.
So what's the plan?
We do a PMS from hell
on this place.
[Speaking Slavic language]
[Alarm sounding]
Hey! Arm yourself!
Here!
Okay. Mei-Lin, hit it.
[Explosion]
Clay.
Ulrika, they have armed
all the prisoners.
Well, then,
you better unarm them.
With pleasure.
Get the brat.
So, what,
I'm your bitch now?
You are whatever
I'm paying you to be.
[Yelling]
[Yelling
Slavic language]
[Gagging]
You know,
My mommy
had blonde hair, too.
Time to die, Mommy!
Mommy! Aah!
Oh, you want to play?
Ah, you want to play?
Come here.
[Yelling]
[Speaking
Slavic language]
[Gasping]
[Speaking
Slavic language]
[Chuckles]
I know the perfect woman
for this job.
Be right back.
[Yelling]
Take your time.
[Speaking
Slavic language]
[Yells]
Like a poodle, huh?
[Shears snip]
[Grigori screams]
Oh, hi, Raven.
Hey, Clay.
Hah!
Now what, huh?
Yeah.
Now what?
Now...
Stop!
Don't you move.
I'll kill her.
Come in,
And keep moving.
The bitch is
right behind me!
Fuck.
I said move!
RAVEN: Move!
Go, go, go,
go, go!
Bye-bye!
[Boom]
Clay! Clay!
I'm here! I'm here!
Jesus, how many lives
do you have?
I was right on their...
I had them,
And then there
was a tunnel.
It imploded. I don't even...
I fucking lost them.
You'd been any closer,
we'd be scooping you out
with a spatula.
I can't lose her.
I have to go back.
Listen, even if you
could get through,
You'd never catch up.
Fuck!
Wait. The Soviets
were really boring.
They used the same
blueprints for all
of their prisons.
Okay.
Am I really
the only one
Who reads "Cold War
Architectural Digest"?
Okay, what is...
What is the point here?
No, no.
Okay, the tunnel,
Uh, it leads
to a structure...
A church, I think,
in the village
right below us.
This tunnel?
Yep.
Okay, great.
I'll get us
some wheels.
Okay. Go, go, go!
Come on.
Ulrika!
I wouldn't shoot
if I were you.
She's bluffing.
Hand her over,
Or we all die.
You wouldn't harm her.
She's the mission,
The whole reason
you came!
And you don't want
to die, do you, girl?
Come on, sweetie!
Tell the nice lady
how scared you are,
How you just
want to go home.
[Crying]
Elise,
how much would you give
To stop Ulrika
from ever hurting
another woman?
Anything.
Everything.
Me, too.
Wait!
It's okay.
This isn't over!
Oh, you can
count on it!
Get in!
Get in.
Shit!
You all right?
I'm okay,
but my rifle's not.
What the hell are
you waiting for?
Punch that shit!
Hey, Kitty-Kat,
you gonna sit there
and admire the view,
Or you gonna shoot back?
My rifle's broken!
Maybe you should try
some evasive driving for once!
Stop your bickering,
you two!
You want
evasive driving?
Hang on, bitches!
KAT: They got
a rocket launcher.
Okay, I've got
two rounds left.
It's all on you.
No pressure.
Two rounds?
Yeah.
I thought
you never miss.
Well, with a 1911
from a moving vehicle
at a rocket launcher?
I believe in you.
Hold it steady!
[Tires skidding]
[laughs]
[Blows lips]
Nice work.
I like that.
Don't tell Mei-Lin,
but I was aiming
for the driver.
I don't care.
Okay, we're stealing
her plane.
Let's go home, ladies.
Clear.
Big plane.
Small girl.
You good?
Like an Asian chick
gives happy endings.
I like 'em big.
Why am I
not surprised?
Get comfy.
Okay. Yeah, Daddy.
Okay.
Ladies and bitches,
This is
your captain speaking.
Please buckle up.
There is an Asian woman
behind the wheel.
We've been cleared
to taxi by me.
Pull up near
the cockpit!
Keep
your panties on!
Oh, hell, no.
Aah!
[Explosion]
See you next Tuesday,
Bitch.
MEI-LIN: We had
a little problem,
But don't worry.
I took care of it.
It's okay.
[Gunshot]
Fuck, no!
Fucking America!
God damn you!
Motherfucking
get you!
Ohh!
Shit!
Who the fuck shot me?
Fuck you!
Bullet in my shoulder!
Shit!
Aah!
You Americans
are so soft!
This is over!
You've stopped
being fun!
And you couldn't even
save your team!
Not yet I haven't!
Uncle Sam wants her.
[Yells]
[Explosion]
Fuck this!
Send me back
to prison. Fine.
Satellite tracking
isn't good enough!
I need eyes
on that plane!
I don't care
if you need
F22s from
the fucking moon!
Just do it!
Ma'am!
We have a visual!
They're
coming in hot!
[Panting]
You know that hole
you were saving for Ulrika?
'Cause all you'll need
is a shoe box.
[Chuckles]
And Raven?
That bitch's wings
have been clipped.
Heh heh heh.
Heh.
She's dead as a dodo.
[laughing]
She... She...
I... I got shot.
I have...
I have a bullet
in my shoulder.
Ma'am, the jet is
fueled and ready to go.
Ms. Prescott,
let's get you
out of here.
Your dad's
waiting for you.
Thank you.
I'm gonna make sure
that my father
Does something to help
all the women here,
Really help them,
Not just
some P.R. stunt.
Miss.
Hey, Elise,
You sure you don't want
to be part of the team?
You'd be a great addition.
Somebody's gotta
make sure you guys
get your pardons.
We have to go. Come on.
Hell of a job, Clay,
you and your team.
Got another
assignment for you,
If you're interested.
Heh.
[laughs]
Maybe tomorrow.
I owe these ladies
a drink.
Damn straight.
Gotta be ladies night
somewhere in this place.
Adios.