(classical music)
(camera reeling)
(suspenseful classical music)
(horn honks)
(classical music)
(water ripples)
(thuds)
(bag crinkles)
(can pops open)
(door thuds)
(keys jangle)
("Careful What You Wish For"
by Michael Rohatyn & DK Dyson)
# Tell me what you wishin' for #
(cars rev)
(horn honks)
(doorbell dings)
[Nick] Why, it's Pinocchio.
I asked for Cyrano,
and they gave me this.
They saw right through you.
Place looks great.
Kudos to Rae.
Hey, Sam.
[Sam] Rae.
[Rae] Already wasted?
Brought you a little somethin'.
Thank you.
What are you, an ostrich?
"One thing without stain unspotted
"from this world in spite of my own doom
"and that is my white plume."
[Lenny] Hey, Sam.
Hey, hi, how's it going, Lenny?
Hey, sorry about your dad.
Aw, yeah.
I'm good, listen man, how did it happen?
I don't know, a weird accident.
Hey, remember the time that he went
windsurfing across the lake?
I'll never forget him.
(chatting)
(slow indie music)
I could gotta give
this acceptance speech.
You should definitely wear the nose.
In my father's name, I accept
this seven dollar walrus.
(pot clanks)
[Nick] Terrible drunk, anyway,
it's a shame that I loot the rum.
[Sam] Watch my technique, this
is all I learned in prep school.
I was always on probation,
they made me mop the hall.
# You had your chance
# With me
(people talking)
# Now just let me be
("Just Let Me Be" by Michael
Rohatyn and Lindy Robbins)
# I used to pray all night
# You'd make everything
- You want one?
# All right
My own private stash.
No.
# But now my plans have changed
[Sam] So, what brings you
to this gathering?
[Anna] It's Halloween.
[Sam] This is true.
[Anna] What brings you?
One thing you can say about Nick
and Rae, they're always well stocked.
[Anna] Yeah, you got to
think on the upper hand.
[Sam] So, you know Rae?
[Anna] Uh, I know Nick.
(TV chatter)
[Sam] Oh, yeah, how do you know Nick?
[Anna] How do you know Nick?
I'm old friends with these guys.
Watch it, this is a crucial moment!
(slow blues music)
So, what's your name?
[Anna] Anna.
Yeah?
I'm Sam.
Great party. (kisses)
Thanks, I had a good time.
Say goodbye to Nick for me.
Yeah.
Goodnight.
So you know, I hadn't smoked for years
but I'm gonna quit in the spring.
You know, the whole country's against
it, so I feel it's my duty.
You're very compulsive, Sam.
Oh, yeah, you can tell that already?
The moment I set eyes on you.
They say I'm committing
suicide on the installment plan.
Shit.
(people talking)
What is it?
I had these photos.
Photos?
(chuckling) Anna,
this isn't, (chuckles) this isn't my coat.
Oh shit, this is someone else's coat.
We gotta go back, we gotta go back.
Oh come on, I'm sorry.
Can we just, I won't take a second.
Can we just go back?
(horn honks)
[Anna] You gonna go back?
Um...
Yeah.
I'll wait here.
I just gotta get this guy's coat back.
- [Anna] Uh-huh.
- [Sam] All right.
[Anna] OK.
Just in case you get stuck up
there, call me sometime.
No, no, no, no, I'll be right back.
I'll be right back, please,
will you please wait?
I'll wait.
Promise?
I promise.
(party chatter)
[Man] Three is better than two.
Well you can just come get me.
I'm not about to walk to the subway,
I'm wearing two inch heels.
Hey.
Hi, Sam.
(bottles clatter)
How's it goin'?
Anyway, I was leavin', Happy Halloween.
Have you been up to your father's place?
Yeah, yeah, I was up there tonight.
Yeah, there's a lot of shit to go through.
So, what about you, did you find a place?
Yeah, I think I found
a sublet on St. Marks.
Oh yeah? Cool, dude.
[Liza] I'll know for sure
in the next couple of days.
Well, you know if you need any
help with the move,
you know where I'll be.
(people talking and laughing)
So, are you leaving?
[Sam] Yeah, I gotta go.
It's so early.
Hey, it's the new me.
(upbeat rock music)
I gotta go. (chuckles)
Gimme a call about that move.
[Liza] Yeah.
(clapping and cheering)
(growls and giggles)
[Rae] Hi, Liza.
- How are you?
- [Liza] Hey.
Sam's leaving when he could
still see straight, did you notice?
(cars rev)
[Sam] Hey Mike, look at this man,
I got robbed on the subway.
They took the money out of
my pants when I was sleeping.
- [Mike] That's wrong.
- [Sam] Listen man,
can I get two coffees and The Post?
I'll pay tomorrow.
[Mike] Yeah, sure.
All right, cool.
(slow classical music)
(people talking)
(door creaks)
(door thuds)
Mutt?
(whistles)
(phone ringing)
(cat purring)
(pee splashing)
(distant siren)
(coffee pours)
(door creaks)
(keys jangle)
(dog barking)
(speaks foreign language)
Hair of the dog that bit me.
[Carrot Man] Yo, Segundo.
[Segundo] Hey, Senor Carrot Man.
How's your wife and my kids?
(chuckles) You can have 'em.
Take to the back, huh?
To the back?
[Segundo] To the back.
To the back.
[Sam] So you had a good
time at the Halloween party?
Oh, I had a great time
at the Halloween party.
Yo Lenny, we've got nothin' on the mics.
Let me tell you,
I meet this girl, right?
She comes straight up to
me, none of that messin'
around, makes it very
clear what she's after.
Uh-huh.
You know what I mean?
Uh-huh, mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
Anyhow, she takes me to a fuckin' boat.
A boat?
[Guitarist] Lenny, could
we get some sound up here?
She like, resides on a boat that's
docked in Tribeca somewhere.
I never heard of such a
thing, I'm tellin' you.
Lenny, could we get some sound up here?
(feedback resonates)
Yeah, you got some sound now?
Thank you.
And before I know it, she's taking
me up to the poop deck and
having her way with me.
On the fuckin' poop deck, man.
In front of all these Halloween freaks
that are trudging about, and shit.
Can I get some sound on the acoustic?
Hey Lenny, take care of these guys
man, I gotta make a phone call.
Nicky, hey listen, man.
I'm trying to get in touch with
this girl I met at your party,
she said you invited her.
No, never seen her before.
I was leavin' and she disappeared.
Anna.
Yeah, what's her name?
All right, well listen, I'm
at the restaurant, I gotta go.
All right, see ya.
(singer vocalizing)
Slimma.
Hey buddy, how are you doin'?
Doin', man.
All right.
You want this?
No, you keep it.
(whistles)
(cat meows)
Oh, goodbye Mutt.
I'll miss you.
(engine revs)
(boxes thud)
(brakes squeak)
(door thuds)
I can't believe I'm getting the hairy
eyeball from those two, what the
hell did you tell them about me?
[Liza] Don't be so paranoid.
No, they're treating me like
the schmucky boyfriend
who walked out on you.
Hmm.
You're the one who's moving out, Liza.
Well, I mean somebody
had to do something.
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, you got what
you wanted, you know?
Your freedom. (chuckles)
Oh Susan, that's great, would you just
put that lamp down over
here by the window?
Watch that cord so you don't trip.
(door thuds)
Need some help?
Nah, just move.
(door thunks)
That's it.
Well, you wanna come up?
I got a couple of beers in the fridge
and we're gonna order out for pizza.
I'll pass.
All right, well thanks for the help.
Sure.
So, did you have a
good time at the party?
What?
Nick and Rae's party?
Yeah, did you?
Go home with someone?
No, I got stood up to tell the truth.
(car horn honks)
Ah, speak of the devil.
How are you doin', Nick?
You're only an hour and a half late.
Sorry, I lost the address.
That was convenient.
Hey, Liza.
Hi, Nick.
So, how'd it go?
It's fine, we're done.
I need a sip of that.
So, you sure you don't wanna come up?
I gotta go, you wanna go?
Sure.
So long.
Sam, come here for a minute.
Nick, do you mind?
No.
I want you to be careful, OK?
Fine.
I mean, I think I'm doing the right
thing Sam, but I'm not
giving up on us, you know.
I understand.
I don't want you to go
crazy now just because
there's no one around to
call you on it, all right?
I gotta go.
Fuckin' nightmare.
I have a feeling I'm
gonna go through that next.
What, with Rae?
Do you want to grab a drink at Gold Bar?
[Sam] Where are we?
(cars rev)
First Avenue.
Let's just go to the Holiday, come on.
(phone ringing)
(classical music)
(pee splashing)
And what did she look like?
[Sam] I can't even remember, man.
Can't even remember.
(silverware clattering)
Is she short, is she tall?
Big hooters?
What she got?
Short-ish, nice figure,
you know, enough to reel me in.
Well, hate to one-up you Sammy boy, but
you should see the chick I bang with.
What, the one with the boat?
Uh-huh.
She's quite a little number.
Been seein' her ever since the party.
Oh yeah?
What does Allison think of that?
Oh, fuck Allison.
(thuds)
[Sam] Are you all right?
Yeah, actually considering
how much I'm getting laid,
it's amazing how shitty I feel.
You look like shit, dude.
(coughing)
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You goin' to the festival tonight
with Nick and those guys?
Yeah, I'm thinkin' about goin'.
Bring some (mumbles).
[Sam] Are you OK?
[Lenny] Seven o'clock, I'm fine.
[Sam] Man, you need to lay off
the hooch, you look sick as a dog.
(people chatting)
(slow blues music)
[Voiceover] Hey now,
wanna go racin', anybody
else out there wanna get in?
(fire sizzles)
(bell dings)
Hey.
Jesus guys, what's goin' on?
Hey listen, Rae's grandmother died.
Oh, shit.
We got a call this morning.
Rae, are you all right?
Yeah, she's been sick a long time.
I knew it was coming.
(people talking nearby)
Listen, do you guys not want to do this?
She'll be OK.
Yeah, I'm fine.
God.
So, did you find your mystery girl
from the party the other night?
No, it's been driving me crazy.
I can't even remember what she looks like.
She's been the perfect date in my mind.
Where the fuck is Lenny,
is he coming or what?
I don't know man, I saw him this
afternoon, he's looking pretty sick today,
I wouldn't be surprised if he passes.
Fuckin' Lenny, I probably spent a month
of my lifetime over the
years waiting for him.
Listen, I'm gonna get
a beer, anybody else?
(upbeat techno music)
(people talking)
[Man] We have a winner!
(bell rings)
Anna?
Hi, Sam.
It's really you,
what are you doing here?
You never called me.
You never left your number.
Oh, you never found it.
I left it in your pocket.
Really?
I wish you'd waited, I wasn't that long.
I've been trying to find you,
I've been thinking about you.
-I've been thinking about you, Sam.
Listen, I'm with Nick and Rae,
they had that party that night.
We could check out the festival.
I thought I found you alone.
It's so amazing to see you again.
- [Anna] You're blushing.
- [Sam] Oh, yeah?
(kisses)
Well listen, I should get this beer
back to Nick and maybe we can go
off and have a festival on our own.
I'd like that.
Yeah?
Are you gonna wait this time?
Yeah.
I came back the last time,
you weren't there.
I'll be here.
All right.
I'm sorry you guys,
I've just been so possessed.
I gotta check her out.
So, what should we do?
Lenny's not coming, I can tell you that.
I don't know Nick, why don't
we check out the festival?
Maybe we should just head back uptown.
Go on Sam, you are released.
(people talking)
(man on loud speaker)
Want to ride the ferris wheel?
I thought you dooped me.
Two tickets for the ride of your life.
(ride operator on speaker)
I'm kind of afraid of heights.
(clunks)
Ah, this fucker keeps coming.
(slow blues music)
So, what's the truth,
did you crash that party?
[Anna] I heard about it
through someone or other.
I haven't crashed a party in years.
There's no parties to crash, everybody
I know has gone their separate ways.
So, you've known Rae a long time?
Yeah, we went to school
together when we were kids.
We were gonna get married
when we were nine.
Good that's it, please
don't move, don't move.
Five seconds left, please
don't move, don't breathe.
And relax.
Rose, come on, Maria, Maria?
OK girls, OK and relax.
(slow blues music)
(siren chirping)
Yeah, this is a project that I've
been working on for a little while.
[Sam] That's a lot of work,
hope it gets published.
[Anna] His ticket to immortality.
[Sam] So tell me, Anna, that blowout
back there on the wheel, it's just
a, I got a thing about heights.
God, you're so beautiful.
(breathes heavily)
(grunting)
(horn blares)
(bird cawing)
(people talking)
(bell chimes)
(smoke alarm blaring)
Oh, shit! Ow, shit!
Hey, listen, I need you
to stand-in for Lenny.
No, tonight.
He fucking disappeared, I don't know,
he didn't show up last night either.
Look, fuck.
All right, um, OK thanks.
I'll see you Tuesday, bye.
("Home To You" by Flamin'
Amy and Sweet Potata)
# I want to go where I
got someplace to hide
# I want to go home
# To you
# Well life is tough #
(people murmuring)
You need a little change?
Yeah.
All right, I'll be right back with that.
How are you guys doin'?
[Man] This salad has no dressing.
Well, it does, if you want a
little more, I can get it for you.
I paid for the dressing,
I'd like to taste it.
Can you bring me a little
container, or something?
Yes, I'll be right back with that.
[Patron] What is with that guy?
[Sam] This really sucks, Lenny,
I hope you're hearing
this wherever you are.
(fire sizzles)
(distant siren echoes)
Tough night, huh Segundo?
All right, I'll see you man.
(speaking Spanish)
Anna!
Hi, Sam.
You found me, incredible.
God, I was wondering what
happened to you last night.
Oh, I tried to wake you,
you were passed out.
Really?
[Anna] Mmm-hmm.
Well you know I've been
workin' late hours.
You like hamburgers?
I may like a good hamburger.
I'm feeling a little light-headed today,
thought I might need some red meat.
You're not a vegetarian are you?
'Cause that wouldn't last too long.
No, not at all.
No?
I could be vegetarian but
there's just too much stuff I couldn't
give up, like lobsters, clams...
I don't think I could do it.
(soft rock music)
[Anna] What do you do at
the restaurant with the dishes?
(scoffs) Excuse me.
I'm the manager four nights a week.
What about you, do you work?
I work.
[Sam] Yeah?
Yeah.
What kind of work?
I don't like to talk about it.
It doesn't really have
anything to do with who I am.
You know what I mean?
Sort of.
Well, how much do you need to
know about someone to
be attracted to them?
Attracted? Nothing.
To stay interested, you
need to fall in love.
Well, I suspect that
the less you know about me,
the longer you'll stay interested.
Why, you have somethin' to hide?
No.
Just that men like to fall in love
don't like to stay in love.
(sighs)
All love ends in sadness,
that's my experience.
People expect too much from love.
# The mystery #
(keys jangle)
(door creaks)
Aren't you gonna invite me in?
I wouldn't leave you out there.
[Anna] Thank you.
(distant chatter)
(bags rustle)
You want a glass of water or something?
I feel kinda out of sorts if
I can't offer you a drink.
No, I'm fine.
- This is a nice place.
- [Sam] Yeah.
[Anna] You live alone?
(bottle thuds)
Yeah.
[Anna] Someone used to live here.
Liza, my ex.
Oh, you look happy in this picture.
[Sam] You think so?
Yeah.
God, I'm beat.
Oh, it's your father.
Yeah, does he look like me?
[Anna] Yeah.
You travel a lot, huh?
[Sam] This is true.
Your lip, it's cut.
Oh, yeah.
Or is that herpes?
[Sam] (scoffs) No.
What is it then?
Didn't you bite my lip in Battery Park?
[Anna] I didn't think you'd remember.
Sometimes, I can have a good memory.
A little...
Just a little bit at a
time, because I like you.
Sicko.
(people chatting in the distance)
(panting)
Wait, wait.
(moaning)
Wait, do you got protection?
Protection from what?
Seriously. Oh, fuck.
(moaning)
Fuck.
(kisses)
(Anna moans)
(exclaims)
(wind chimes chiming)
Ow.
That's protection.
Fair enough, fair enough.
It's not just pregnancy anymore.
I'm not contagious.
All right.
(sighs) You gotta ask, you gotta ask.
(water rippling)
I used to cut my arms at parties.
[Anna] (scoffs) Oh, you're a cutter.
[Sam] See? That's my favorite.
It's got the, it's kind of a map.
[Anna] (chuckles) A cross.
And then I have this one.
You can't see that as well, it's all over.
It's a weird thing to puncture your skin.
Skin is all there is between
you and the rest of the world.
Blood is so eager to get out.
You know it's blue and green?
The oxygen turns it red.
And what about this?
You pull out your teeth at parties, too?
No, I was mugged.
They kicked me in the face,
I lost my tooth.
They got six bucks off me.
I like it.
(Sam chuckles)
(keys clacking)
Well you know, Sam, you might want
to consider that you were
pretty seriously on the rebound.
Yeah, well, I don't know man,
she's got a real ease about her,
kind of a timeless quality.
Uh-huh, Uh-huh.
And you know, she jerked me off
on our first date.
(scoffs) That might have
something to do with it.
We are late for that funeral.
Oh, shit.
Come on, Rae's waiting for us.
All right, let's go, let's go.
Come on Nick.
You should come, I know Rae'd want
you there, and what else are you gonna do?
I don't know, something
with Anna I'm hoping.
Well, Anna's invited.
It's gotta be weird for you too, I mean,
the first year without your dad.
Yeah.
What'd you guys used to do?
After my mom died?
I don't know, I'd make a
turkey and creamed onions,
he'd have some of his cronies over but
last year, he was getting
kind of despondent.
Just wanted to be away so
we ate in this place uptown,
just the two of us, it was pretty dismal.
(bell chimes)
[Nick] Well, come out to the house.
The spirit of grandma will be there.
All right.
(slow classical music)
(bird caws)
[Anna] Sam?
Sam?
[Sam] Anna, hey, hold on.
This is the key to the front door.
(knocking)
- [Sam] Hi.
- [Anna] Hi.
What's that smell?
What?
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
What is it? (sniffs)
You can't smell it, you're
standing in it, I think.
- [Sam] Maybe it's the catbox,
- [Anna] Come here.
- Come here.
- [Sam] Catbox is right there.
[Anna] Look.
Hey, what do you got?
A good BBQ set.
(both chuckle)
We have to use it,
can we get on the roof?
Um, yeah.
So, we'll have a BBQ.
Where did this you get this?
It's really high tech.
14th Street.
You can shop anywhere when
you buy on 14th Street, right?
All right, OK, cool, so we'll
move this operation upstairs.
Great, I'll stay here.
(chuckles) It's not that bad, it's just--
[Sam] All right.
[Anna] Have you ever been naked
on a New York rooftop?
[Sam] Not in this life.
[Anna] What would that be like?
[Sam] You're sort of
an exhibitionist, huh?
(slow romantic classical music)
(horn honks)
(moaning)
(bottles clatter)
(horn honks)
(bottle clatter)
(distant siren)
(Sam moaning)
(people talking in the distance)
(phone ringing)
(wind chimes chiming)
[Liza] Hey, are you there?
It's me, um, well, it's been awhile
and I was just wondering how you
were doing and gimme a call someday.
(machine beeps)
It's good to see you.
How you been?
OK, what's been goin' on with you?
You look strung out.
I'm running a free life.
[Waitress] Hi.
Yeah, can I have a coffee please?
So, what's been goin' on with you?
Hey did you hear about Lenny?
No, what?
[Sam] He's gone missing.
Oh, well what does that mean?
He stopped coming to the restaurant,
he never called, nothin'.
Well, isn't he always
threatening to just up and go?
Yeah, well I think it's weird.
(phone rings)
(people laugh)
So what else is new?
How's Nick and Rae?
They're fine, oh, look at this.
I gotta give this speech
tonight about my dad.
[Liza] Hmm, what are you gonna say?
That he liked to travel
and he was never around.
[Liza] (chuckles) Mmm-hmm.
It's a reservation.
The reservation is the two-all,
we can't put them on the air.
I've got this young kid,
he's very telegenic.
So, how's your apartment and stuff?
It's OK, staying at Mark's place
is kind of funny, I guess,
It's sort of a circus.
[Man on Phone] No, listen,
you're calling me.
Well, I'd like to come by and see it.
[Liza] You should, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[Liza] What happened to your lip?
I get that every year, you know,
it's herpes or somethin', right?
You seem nervous.
Too much coffee.
I've been feelin' a little weird.
Yeah, like what?
(phone rings)
Liza, I've started seeing somebody.
I'm not saying it's serious or anything
but I just feel like we should
start to say our things over.
We don't have to have
this conversation right now.
I know, I know, it's just so you know.
Oh, well that didn't take long,
how long have you known her?
[Sam] Not that long.
Are you fucking her?
What do you think?
Well, I hope you're being careful.
Liza, come on.
You met her at that
Halloween party, right?
I knew it when I saw you there.
Liza, this isn't a separation if you're
gonna keep quizzing me on everything.
I mean, how is this any
different from living together?
You got me under a fuckin' microscope.
That's not me Sam, that's you
doing that to yourself.
(table thuds)
Ah, shit.
What's the matter?
(Sam breathing heavily)
Are you OK?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Just a little hung over.
Listen, this was a
bad idea, I'm gonna go.
No, just wait for a minute.
(door creaks)
[Voiceover] (chuckles) Look at you, how
much longer can you keep this up?
[Voiceover] Is she moving out?
[Sam] I'm all packed.
[Voiceover] What's up with you two?
[Sam] Just stuck enjoying
each other, I guess.
(people murmuring)
[Mr. Lyons] That's enough
out of me for this evening.
Now what we all came here for,
to here from his son, Sam.
Let's bring him on.
(crowd claps)
Thank you.
I'm not very helpful in these situations,
(paper rustles)
but I did try to put down a
few thoughts about my father.
I'm thinking about him and I believe
that he never stopped searching,
traveling around,
especially later in life.
I think that he took great comfort in
history and in the past,
he seemed to identify
with the ruins of great civilizations
as monuments to some sort of idealism
which he felt was lacking in the, "Culture
of narcissism," as he liked to call it.
That was Christopher Lasch,
my father liked that phrase.
He had a lot of ambivalence about popular
culture and the media
and I think he felt that
the education system discouraged real
self discovery.
I'm sure you've all discussed
these issues with him.
Anyway, I think that made him
bitter, but he was not
a pessimist or a cynic,
as some of his detractors would have it.
I think...
I think he was an optimist who'd
come up against a lot of disappointments.
But here in this
institution, I think he felt
idealism was still possible and I think
that meant a lot to him.
It meant everything to him.
So, in his honor,
I accept
this memorial.
What I'm sayin' is...
(distant laugh echoes)
Thank you, and now maybe we
should all get a drink or something.
Thank you.
(crowd claps)
[Mr. Lyons] Sam.
[Sam] Mr. Lyons.
Are you OK?
Oh, yeah I'm just,
been a little run down.
Well I'm sure all of this
has been pretty hard on you.
[Sam] Yeah.
That was very fine what you said.
It would've meant a lot to your dad.
Thank you, thanks.
How is that girlfriend
of yours, the painter?
Oh, Liza, she's fine, yeah.
Your father was fond of her.
She was studying archaeology, I think.
That's right, very good, yeah.
She's trying to decide
which way to go now,
painting or archeology.
Your father was tickled pink about that.
Oh yeah, they got along very well.
- [Anna] Who's this?
- [Sam] Anna?
Hi, sorry I missed
your speech, how'd it go?
[Sam] It was fine.
Mr. Lyons, this is Anna.
Hi, Jerry Lyons, nice to know you.
[Anna] I'm not interrupting
anything, am I?
Here Sam, I got you something,
in honor of the occasion.
[Mr. Lyons] Oh, nice.
What is it?
How extraordinary!
Peter, come take a look at this.
Come here, take a look at this.
Don't touch, it's for Sam.
What was that all about?
You're not mad that I showed up?
That was just so fuckin' weird.
[Anna] Come on.
(distant siren blares)
Listen.
What are you hearing? I don't...
[Anna] They're out tonight.
What are those, dogs?
Central Park used to be full of wolves.
(horn honks)
(thuds)
Oh, shit!
(growling)
(whooshes)
Anna, come on!
(howling)
(men arguing)
[Man] Don't move him, don't move him.
(water splashing)
Wait, don't move him, put him back in.
Anybody getting the ambulance, or what?
[Sam] Don't touch it, Anna.
[Anna] His little life is slipping away.
[Man] Don't move him, don't move him.
(brakes squeak)
Wait, don't move him, put you back in.
(water splashing)
Anybody getting the ambulance, or what?
[Sam] Jesus, that's a baby?
[Anna] It's the child
we'll never have, Sam.
(hospital chatter)
(slow ominous classical music)
[Sam] Seriously, Anna,
let's get the fuck out of here.
You're being perverse.
[Anna] Take me, Sam,
rub your hard cock against me.
You got a very morbid streak, Anna.
What, and you don't?
I don't know, maybe.
With your scars, Sam?
Drinking yourself into
a stupor every night.
[Sam] I got the gloom gene in my family.
(winces) Goddamnit.
(moaning)
(panting)
(slow classical violin music)
Look, I'm fine, all right?
I just need to get home, it's been
a fuckin' intense night, I've had it.
(sighs)
I'll see you tomorrow, we have
the whole weekend, all right?
I'll see you tomorrow?
All right.
All right, I'm sorry, I'm tired.
Be well.
(door thuds)
(horn beeps)
Sam?
Yeah?
[Anna] You like me?
(scoffs) After that?
[Anna] Really?
[Sam] Yeah.
[Anna] Why?
[Sam] I guess...
I guess you seem lonely.
You put up a tough front.
That appeals to me.
[Anna] Why?
Are you lonely?
[Sam] Well, maybe I am.
We live as we dream alone.
Who said that?
[Anna] You did.
[Sam] No, no, it was someone.
[Segundo] Mister Sam, are you OK?
I don't know man.
You don't look so good,
what is the deal?
Mister Sam?
Hi.
(speaks Spanish)
I'm fine man, I'm fine.
Here you go.
(distant horn honks)
She left a message on my machine, she's
going to meet us up there tomorrow.
I'm sorry, I should've checked sooner.
Think nothing of it.
Let's go then before we
get slammed by the traffic.
(soft rock music)
Cut someone off Nick.
I'm trying to get us out there
before Christmas time.
I would not take
the breakdown lane, Nick.
There are cops all over the place.
Now, isn't this nice?
Sheep, you're all sheep.
(horn honks)
Yoo-hoo, Mister Kingfuck?
Hey, Mister Teenage Entrepreneur?
[Rae] Hey asshole,
move over or I'm gonna
come over and kick your balls in.
(laughing)
Kick your balls in?
She means it, too.
# I just wanna be like you #
(light clicks)
Grandma's kitchen.
(clock ticking)
I'm gonna go to bed.
You know where it is?
Yep. (clears throat)
Night.
[Sam] Goodnight.
(distant horn blares)
[Anna] Sam.
Sam.
(bell chimes)
(gasps)
(clock ticks)
(birds chirping)
These were made by Grandma.
Really? That's weird, right?
Very sacred.
Wow, yeah.
Oh, to be cherished.
I wonder what she put in there?
Love.
(distant lawn mower buzzes)
So, Sam?
How's this thing with Anna turning out?
Oh, uh...
it's a...
I don't know, there's
something about her, you know?
Yeah, I can't get a handle on it.
But it's you know...
I'm not really saying anything. (chuckles)
Well, if you're happy.
Yeah, so what about you Rae,
how are things going?
Things are pretty hard right now.
[Sam] Yeah?
I'm trying to make
a major life decision.
Both options are pretty disappointing.
Like, what's goin' on?
Sam, swim in the ocean.
You're kidding.
We must be manly and
go for a dip in the sea.
No, that's impossible man, I'm sick.
Nonsense, good for the circulation.
Anyway, I need the company,
walk me to the beach.
What about you Rae,
you need some help here?
Entertain Nick, that's help enough.
All right, but I may not go in.
We'll finish this later.
Yes.
Bye. Jesus, man.
[Nick] To the sea!
[Sam] What am I supposed
to do with this?
[Nick] You put it on, that's a start.
Then we walk to the ocean, we put
our bodies into it, and we swim.
[Sam] So, I told her
it was over, pissed her off.
Come on, we can't return
to the house in defeat.
Look, I'm keeping you company, Nick.
I don't feel well, go in the fucking
water, I'll be your witness.
What is this new frailty
image you're cultivating?
Always the martyr, always the victim.
Don't be unkind, dude.
All right. I'm going in.
(zip unzips)
(waves crashing)
(Nick yelling)
(birds cawing)
(Nick groaning)
[Sam] Fucker! Fucker!
(Nick yells)
(both yell)
(heartbeat thumps)
(birds tweeting)
(plane engine whirs)
[Woman] Oh, sorry.
[Nick] Don't worry, I'm all right.
- [Rae] So, Nick?
- [Nick] Mmm-hmm?
No listen, I'm thinking that maybe
our little process (audio trails off).
[Nick] What's the matter?
[Rae] It's Sam, he's looking weird.
I don't think you should
encourage him drinking.
This woman Anna is obviously
doing nothing good.
[Nick] He spends so much time with her.
It's not about Sam.
(Nick and Rae argue)
Everything's about money.
(phone rings)
Happy Thanksgiving, Nick.
Yep.
[Man] Whoa, are you all right?
(bird caws)
(chatter and chuckling)
(slow dramatic classical music)
[Man] The Hunter's Moon, now that's
the name given the full moon in October.
Hunter, but it's mostly (mumbles).
(laughs)
[Man] Sam, the gravy.
No, every full moon has a name.
The Harvest Moon, that's
a full moon in September
and then of course the Blue Moon
and that's when there's two
full moons in the same month.
That happens well...
Once every blue moon.
[Man] Ah precisely, thank you.
Rae, you're looking like quite
the little temptress tonight
in your antique gown.
It really is beautiful.
Where'd you get it?
It was in my grandmother's closet.
I just put it on and it fit.
You know, I've never really
been attracted to antiques,
I always like what's happening now.
Well, it belonged to my grandmother,
that's why I like it.
You've got sort of an Emma Peel
thing going there,
Anna, that's very retro.
Yeah, well, I pick up a
few things along the way.
Rae, I'd like a toast, a toast
to the chef, Rae, thank you so much.
[Nick] Thank you, Rae.
Thanks, thanks very much.
[Nick] And to the glorious hypocrisy
of the Thanksgiving feast.
(all whooping)
And in the principles first embodied
in The Constitution, the rest we'll
just leave to that time-honored
commodity, historical amnesia.
Anna, you haven't eaten anything,
aren't you hungry?
[Sam] Anna's never hungry.
[Rae] Oh really, doesn't that put
a damper on your courtship, Sam?
Don't you always cook for your dates?
[Sam] Now Rae, you're giving away
all of my techniques.
Now he's cultivating
the ill-health routine.
[Rae] Oh yes, it's very sexy.
[Anna] It's OK, Sam,
you already won me over.
Thank you, and you all...
(all laugh)
With my manliness!
(all chuckle)
[Nick] Sam and I went swimming today.
It wasn't so bad.
[Man] That's very sporty of you.
[Rae] Is he all right?
Is he all right?
Oh, yeah, he just hasn't been
feeling well, lately.
[Man] Just a change in the weather.
That's weird that he just walked away.
(coughing)
(clock ticking)
[Voiceover] How is that
girlfriend of yours, the painter?
Your father was fond of her.
[Voiceover] Two tickets
for the ride of your life.
(thunder crashes)
Oh my God, there you are.
We thought we lost you.
(horse chomping)
(neighs)
[Rae] Did you see that?
Yeah, you frightened it.
What happened to you at dinner, anyway?
You disappeared.
Cramps.
[Rae] Oh really, I got some pills
for that if you need.
No, I'm feeling better.
So, what's going on with you and Nick?
What?
[Anna] You seem distracted.
It's a lot of things.
[Anna] Oh, right. Your grandmother?
What is your deal, Anna?
[Anna] Excuse me?
What do you do?
I don't believe Sam's ever told me.
I never told Sam.
Really? (scoffs)
You and Sam is absurd, I'm sorry.
Are you still carrying a torch for him?
I mean, hasn't it been quite some time
since he used to get drunk
and knock you around?
I mean, I don't know when you started
this thing about Rae, but I'll
tell you, I wouldn't
get too flip about it.
I mean, she's pretty together.
Yeah, I know.
Where is our little cast
of characters, anyway?
Our little starlets.
(chuckles) Rae went for a walk,
isn't that what you said?
Right, right, right.
It's a good thing too, I would hate
to think of them upstairs together.
They seem to dislike each other.
Yeah, what is that, anyway?
Have you ever noticed that Rae
is jealous of every girl you go out with?
That's in your head, man.
Open your eyes, man.
[Anna] Jesus.
(rain pours)
Ah, your dress is ruined.
You didn't like it, anyway.
I like you in it.
What is this, a come on?
Well, (scoffs) the setting's so right.
I've never gotten into that.
Oh?
Anyway, there's Nick.
Oh, is that all it is?
No, I don't trust you either.
(glass thunks)
(Sam scoffs)
(bottle thuds)
Ah.
(stammers)
I don't, no, man...
This is all I need.
So, if it wasn't me,
and I wasn't
with Sam?
But, I am with Sam you know,
and he's with me.
(kisses)
(thunder crashes)
(rain pouring)
We don't want to get into this.
[Sam] Whoo.
(Nick exclaims)
I hope Rae is all right in this rain.
She should be back.
(slow classical violin music)
(birds chirping)
(water drips)
Look at this piece of shit note.
We're getting sticked
for the whole weekend,
they've gone back to New
York, they took the train!
[Sam] What?
Nobody even woke me up.
Well, I can't wait, a whole
weekend being pissed off!
Exactly.
We close up the house and get out of here.
Hey.
We gotta do all the fuckin' dishes, man.
(Nick scoffs)
(Sam mimics gun shot)
("Save You From Yourself" by Tom Laverack)
# So it all comes together
# Just like a big band
# Even that school boy candor
# Make yourself into that grade
# Nobody seems to shutup
# And the parts draw scared
# You hate yourself
# I'm think I might kill
# Tell me who's goin' save you
# Who's gonna save you from yourself
# Tell me who's gonna save you
(cars revving)
# Who's gonna ask to get rid of
# His face won't tell
# Looking for somebody special
# Just on a road to hell
# Little pieces of gossip
# Might take you for a spell
(door thuds)
# Thought it cut my swing
# And I don't think it'll help
# Tell me who's gonna save you #
(machine beeps)
[Mr. Lyons] Sam, Jerry Lyons here.
I want to thank you again for the
other night and listen, I'd like
to have a word with you
about the young woman
you brought to the reception if you've
got a minute or two, give
me a call, we should talk.
(distant soft rock music)
(phone ringing)
Liza.
[Sam] It's Sam.
Yeah, Sam?
[Sam] Happy Holidays.
What's going on?
We didn't really get a chance to
talk, you kind of split on me.
Well, I mean I don't really need to
watch you stumble around with a hangover
Sam, you know I've done
that routine already.
I wasn't hungover, I'm sick.
What's the matter with you?
[Sam] So Liza, do you want to
get together, just to hang out?
Um, I don't think so, Sam.
[Sam] I haven't even seen
your place set up.
You know, I thought that if I just left
you alone for awhile, you'd try to
do something about your drinking Sam,
you know, decide what you
wanted to do with yourself.
I didn't think that you'd
be dating in 10 minutes.
I'm not dating someone,
I just met someone.
Well, I'm not mad at you if that's
what you're worried about,
you're off the hook.
Come on let me come by,
I'll bring a bottle of wine.
Whatever, I'll bring a bottle of seltzer.
Oh fuck, no, we'll
make it a bottle of wine.
[Sam] Is that a yes?
(clinks)
Oh, Jesus! You scared me.
Sorry, I'm late Sam.
You weren't making other plans, were you?
What the fuck, Anna?
Don't be mad.
(Sam panting)
See.
What happened to you two last night?
We went for a walk, when we got
back, you were both passed out.
Oh.
Sam, did you not? Please don't.
Just be with me tonight, OK?
We didn't have our weekend together.
I gotta apologize.
Liza, are you there?
Just pick up.
I'm sorry, I'll call you later.
(phone receiver clanks)
No one home?
I don't get you.
So, this is what you do, you pine
away over Liza when I'm not around.
I was giving her a call,
if you don't mind.
Sam, I don't want to have to compete
for your interest, it doesn't feel good.
Anna, I need some time
to work some stuff out.
I'm feeling really out of sorts.
I just, I don't think we should...
I just need some time.
I can give you time.
Anna, wait.
Did you say something?
I'm not saying anything.
Sam, don't worry about it, don't
lose any sleep over it, I'll get mine.
Anna...
(slow dramatic piano music)
I really...
I had a thing for you, I just
need some time, all right?
Right.
Here's your key, sorry.
Force of habit.
(door creaks)
(door thuds)
(sobs)
(growling)
(cat screeches)
(eerie music)
(water dripping)
(hissing)
(voices echo)
[Rae] He can't see he's in
total denial about his father.
[Lenny] Sammy, boy.
Oh, on the fuckin' poop deck, man.
[Rae] Already wasted?
[Anna] So, you've known Rae a long time?
[Nick] Like all conviction,
the worst are
full of passion and intensity.
That should appeal to you
a little bit, right Sam?
[Man] That's the name given
the full moon in October.
Hunter, but it's mostly (mumbles).
(men laughing)
(Anna hisses)
(skin rips)
[Anna] A little bit at a time,
because I like you.
(cat hisses)
[Voiceover] Sam?
(horn honks)
(Sam gasps)
Sam?
("Needle Men" by Rebecca Moore)
# No I've
# Justified and the shadow's
# Over me
# I wonder why
Sam?
[Sam] Hey.
Hey, Nick.
# Don't just sit there sadly
# Fingering the rip in your skin
# Go to the needle man
# They can sew it on #
Hey Sam, I was downtown, thought
I'd swing by, offer you a beer.
No thanks man, I'll pass.
Yeah? What's the matter?
Are you sick?
You were pretty crazy
out there on the road.
I don't know, man,
I just feel like I'm fallin'
apart, like my fuckin'
health is failing me.
What's going on?
I mean, how do you feel?
I know what it is, man, it's
just so fuckin' weird,
I been afraid to tell you.
[Nick] Yeah, what is it?
You're a mess.
It's about Anna.
Oh, God.
What?
Nothing, go on, what about Anna?
So, you know I broke up
with her last night.
That was quick, what's that been?
Two, three weeks?
Yeah, things went fast like that
fuckin' chick, she really messed with me
you know like an animal,
like a fuckin' parasite.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
No, you don't have any idea
what I mean, Nick.
Well, look Sam,
you broke it up with Liza
so you could be with
Anna, the mystery girl,
and now things are so fucked up, it's made
me realize what a turd you are and
it's made you ill, a sick person.
That's not what's going on.
Well, what is it?
You're being so mysterious.
What has transpired between you and
Anna that's making you so crazy?
Let me tell you this, man.
I'm all ears, Sam.
So listen man, like
that first night, right?
After the festival, so we're gettin' it on
in Battery Park and she bites into my lip.
I was wondering what that was,
I was afraid to ask.
No, I'm serious man, she's biting
into my lip to draw blood, so I said,
"What the fuck Anna, what are you doing?"
And she says, "Oh, just a
little bit at a time, Sam."
Sticks a finger in the cut
and like, licks the blood off.
So?
You don't understand man,
she does it like every time.
We'll be screwing or something
and she bites me and then
starts sucking the blood.
And what are you doing man?
Are you getting off?
I don't know man,
it's like totally amazing,
it's like nothing I've ever felt before.
It's like when we're screwing it's like
having warm milk running
through your veins or something.
What are you saying,
because she's biting you?
Yeah, I'll wake up and
I'll have this puncture mark
on my arm or my chest or something.
I don't get it, I mean,
if she's biting you
in these different places and then she's
sucking your blood, actively sucking it?
Yeah, and then I started
feeling sick like this
and I started to wonder 'cause
of what happened to Lenny.
Wait a minute, what does
Lenny have to do with this?
I'm tellin' you man, before he
disappeared, he was sick the same way.
Hold on now, Sam.
No, I'm serious man, I mean, at first
I was goin' with it 'cause
it was kind of cool.
I mean, it's not...
I don't know, it's just
like our little thing.
Like me and Anna, right?
And then I started feeling sick like
this and out of it and I started
to realize this fucking chick is like
drinking my blood in a way
that's affecting my health.
Sam, you should've stayed in the arts.
You have such a fertile imagination,
such a propensity for gothic melodrama.
I mean, seeing you work in a restaurant
is like, well, to use your beloved guy
is like Cyrano without his plume.
Fuck you, Nick.
No, fuck you.
I mean, what is this
concoction you've come up with?
That Anna is drinking your blood
and that she's drinking Lenny's blood?
You haven't gave a fuck
about Lenny disappearing.
[Nick] Lenny is always disappearing,
he's an irresponsible fuck.
No, man, it was Anna.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Anna what?
What are you really trying to say, Sam?
That Anna is sucking your blood
and that she's sucking Lenny's blood?
Are you trying to tell
me that Anna's a vampire?
Get a fucking grip, man.
Listen, I know it's absurd, but I swear
to God man, I've never seen her eat,
I've never seen her drink, I've never
seen her smoke, I've never seen
her once, not once, in the daylight.
I've never seen her take a shit
or piss, for Christ's sake.
And for that, she's a fucking vampire?
Because she won't shit in front of you?
I'm not telling you
she's a vampire, man.
I'm not asking you to
believe she's a vampire,
I mean, vampire.
Well, maybe she thinks she's a vampire,
maybe she thinks that you think that she's
a vampire and that's getting you two off.
Listen man, I'm just telling you what
I know that this chick does, right?
She drinks blood! (shudders)
[Nick] Vampires do not exist,
Sam, and it is unfortunate.
They would provide much diversion from
the miseries of life, many
in which you have effectively
avoided since your mother passed away
and left you that little nest egg.
You reveal yourself, Nick.
Nevermind that then.
I would prefer to make this point.
Vampirism is everywhere.
It is hiding in our hearts, Sam.
It is at the bottom of
a bottle or a needle
in the arm, it is 500 channels
of insipid cultural dribble.
The advertising and gluttony, draining
us of our ability to think.
It is the insidious Faustian bargains
we make every day.
The little compromises
that eat at our soul
but believe me, it is not to
be found embodied in Anna.
She's not that deep.
Hey, maybe she does drink
blood, I don't know.
She probaby belongs to one of those
blood-sucking cults or whatever they are,
but believe me, she is not a vampire.
And you, Sam, had better pull yourself
out of this rut you're going through.
God forbid, maybe lay
off the booze for awhile
or whatever it takes to
pull yourself together.
And if she's been biting you,
I'd get a fucking AIDS test.
Sounds like very unsafe
sex you've been having.
You disappoint me, Nick, man.
I can't even talk to
you, you're so fuckin'...
It's like you got the shade down.
Sam, what do you want me to say?
I mean, really.
I just want to tell you
the shit that's been goin' on.
Sure.
[Sam] Have you say,
you know, "It's all right."
Yeah, Sam.
And, "It's over."
It's over, Sam, you're gonna be fine.
I'm scared man, I feel
like I'm cracking up.
Listen, come have a
drink with us, Rae and me.
[Sam] I told you man, I'm not drinking.
You should be drinking, it's probably
the best thing for a man in your shoes.
(Sam chuckles)
[Sam] Why don't you
just get out of here?
Sure, you take care of yourself.
Maybe you are really sick.
Like, maybe you should talk to someone.
I will Nick, you can come
visit me at The Creedmoor.
Look, Sam, your father
died two months ago,
he'd been away, he stopped calling.
It looks like he died
on a binge or something,
you're feeling unresolved,
you've got a right to.
Look, all I'm trying
to say is I don't think
Anna is your problem, OK?
I hear you, dude.
[Nick] All right.
Look, take care, OK?
Call me, and tell me
what Freud has to say.
(door creaks)
(door thuds)
(horn honks)
(clanks)
Mutt?
Mutt.
Yo, mutt.
(distant cello music)
(gasps)
Oh, crap.
(exclaims)
Liza, Liza, it's Sam.
Listen, I'm in trouble,
you gotta come over.
OK, please?
OK, I think I'm cracking up.
(echoey cat screech)
(ominous classical music)
(distant horn honks)
(bell rings)
(knocking)
Liza.
Liza?
I remember you.
Have you seen Liza,
the woman that lives here?
I don't want no trouble here.
(door creaks)
Liza?
(gasps)
Liza, Liza, Liza.
[Voiceover] There's trouble
at the neighbor's apartment.
That's right, picking the lock.
That's right, I heard a lot of voices.
He's still in there, that's right.
You're gonna catch him if you hurry.
(dramatic classical music)
(turnstile clunks)
(men speaking foreign language)
[Voiceover] Anna's sucking your
blood, she's sucking Lenny's blood?
[Voiceover] I'll never forget her.
[Nick] Are you trying to tell me
that Anna's a vampire?
Get a fucking grip.
[Nick] What are you
really trying to say, Sam?
That Anna's sucking your blood
and sucking Lenny's blood?
[Mr. Lyons] How is that
girlfriend of yours, the painter?
Your father was fond of her.
[Nick] Are you trying to tell me
that Anna's a vampire?
Get a fucking grip.
[Anna] I don't want to have to compete
for your interest, it doesn't feel good.
[Mr. Lyons] How is that
girlfriend of yours, the painter?
(slow suspenseful classical music)
[Voicemail Message]
This is a crucial moment.
Leave a message for Nick
or Rae after the beep.
(beep)
Nick, it's Sam.
Listen man, give me a call at my
father's house, all right?
I'm serious man, I'm in deep shit.
(suspenseful chiming)
(knocking)
[Nick] Sam?
[Sam] Nick?
Nick?
(thud)
(knife clatters)
(phone ringing)
(panting)
[Anna] Hello, this is Anna.
Oh hi Liza, Sam told me about you.
So, you want to talk to him?
Sam, Liza's on the phone for you.
It's not possible!
[Anna] Sam?
He's in the bathroom, he won't come
out, can he call you back?
(clunks)
How'd you find us?
Well,
Liza, listen I'm really worried about
him, he's locked himself in the bathroom,
he's not coming out, I don't know,
he said he's sick so
maybe you can come by.
(Anna growls)
(Sam grunts)
(thuds)
Ow, no more, no.
Ow!
No more. (gasps)
(zipper unzips)
(Sam groans)
(Anna moans)
(thuds)
(Anna gasps)
(door thuds)
(breathes heavily)
(heartbeat thumps)
(groans)
(light clicks)
(slow mysterious classical music)
(horn honks)
(buzzes)
[Nick] Just wait out here.
(breathing heavily)
(heartbeat thumping)
(Anna growls)
(Sam grunts)
Just a little bit curious.
Have a taste.
How it feels.
- [Anna] Drink, Sam.
- [Sam] No.
(Anna hissing)
Sam?
(door rattles)
(Sam grunting)
(pounding)
Sam!
Sam?
[Rae] Sam?
(thuds)
[Rae] Sam.
Sam?
(door clunks)
[Rae] Sam.
[Sam] Ow.
(mysterious knocking)
Sam.
Sam!
(door thunks)
[Voiceover] No!
[Man] Somebody call an ambulance.
Call an ambulance.
("Mystery" by Tom Laverack)
# Turn your eyes
# Turn your eyes the other way
# Say a prayer
# Say a prayer and a lullaby
# Just a taste that keeps
# It different days
# A new way
# Listening
(truck brakes squeak)
# Hold your hand
(water ripples)
# Hold your hand so
# Take a breath
# Take a breath and abandon it
# Just a tear in your eye
# That left to remind
# There might be
# A little mystery
# Not a soul
# Not a soul can see
# Inside here
# Inside here there's a reckoning
# I was gently stuck
# Havin' place you once were
# Could it be
# A mystery
# All these tears
# Tears v
# Take out my soul take my
# Teeth pull out right out
# Feel
# Who am I
# Pull out teeth
# Oooh #
(distant siren blares)