Life can be so unpredictable.
One minute, you meet
the girl of your dreams.
The next,
you gotta ask yourself,
"How the hell did I
get in this position
in the first place?
I was always the guy
on the other side.
ASSASSIN X
Subrip: Pix
You know what to do.
I don't want to
see his ugly face.
I got to go. Sweetheart,
don't mess with that dirty dog.
You okay?
Hey, what do you want?
Sorry, guys, that's my dog.
Boss?
It is okay.
You should take better
control of your dog.
I know, I just got her last
week, so I'm sorry about that.
C'mon, get out of here, man.
You need to get off the phone.
It's family time.
It's business.
Do you want a dog?
Thank you, sir!
Are you okay?
Al! Al!
-Are you okay, Al?
-Boss, are you okay?
-Boss, what's going on?
-Dad, Dad.
-Are you okay, boss?
-Are you okay?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
You come here a lot,
don't you?
How would you know that?
I notice everything
and everyone.
Gabriela.
Nice to meet you, Gabriela.
I haven't seen you here before.
That's because you never look.
College student?
Yeah, language major, you?
Sales. Internet sales.
Pretty interesting?
It's kind of late
for you, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
My bus is late again.
It's usually here around
nine, but it'll be here soon.
Well, nice to meet you.
Wait, hey, you never
told me your name.
I know.
Samuel's on the right.
He's on China's terrorist list.
And that's his brother Eric.
He's also an exile from China.
They're both powerful war lords.
-Is this shit real?
-Every bit.
I mean, what we're up against
here is a trip by itself.
Well, screw that,
just walk up there
and blast their asses away.
That is exactly
what we don't want.
There are factions
outside our world
that would lose if they found
these two guys murdered.
This case requires
a lot of finesse.
I'm gonna have to
bring in Steele.
Screw Steele,
we don't need him.
This type of case
is his specialty.
Look, Frank,
this is gonna be my case.
All I need's a few mercs.
We go in,
and I'll smoke 'em all out.
That's not how
we do things at Blackstone.
Look, we go in,
make 'em all disappear.
No trace, nothing.
And I'll make it look like
they were deep underground.
You watch.
What if something goes wrong?
Nothing will go wrong. Trust me.
Frank, over here.
I love this guy,
punctual as always.
No, no, I'm okay.
Sit.
I really don't
need this, Claxton.
Nonsense, nothing like
a clean shave.
Make you feel like a new man.
Jose, let me do
this one, will ya?
Don't you love the
sound of a clean swipe?
It's almost like you
can feel each follicle
cutting at the base.
That was a bad,
big deal back there, Frank.
Damn bloodbath.
-I thought...
-You thought?
You rushed him, Claxton.
I told you it was too soon.
Yeah, the man was your
responsibility. Plain and simple.
You're getting old, Frank.
Maybe just a little bit too old.
I can fix this.
I'm sorry. I guess I pushed
this a little too hard.
Here you go.
What do you think?
Don't disappoint me, Frank.
We need Blaine.
Find him an appropriate mentor.
And don't mess up again.
Ronus!
Time to it let go, old friend.
There's nothing
to let go, Frank.
Come on, Ronus,
it's me you're talking to.
Everything's fine, Frank.
Just a little bit tired,
that's all.
-Just a little bit tired?
-Yeah.
Put up your fists. C'mon.
C'mon, get your fists up.
Up, up, up!
Back in the day,
you would've parried,
you would've lay three
punches in my gut
before I even could breathe.
Did you come here to give me
a boxing lesson, Frank?
No.
I need you to work
with a protege.
I work alone, Frank.
Hear me out. I brought Blaine
into the organization.
Blaine?
Are you kidding me?
The guy's a loose cannon.
I heard about what
happened in Chinatown,
and we still don't know the
repercussion of that case, Frank.
It was my fault
that I never should...
So now you're
cleaning up his mess?
He's good.
But maybe he's not
as good as he thinks.
I see.
So they want me to train a
psychopath to kill, right?
They want you to train a
psychopath to control the kill.
Why didn't Claxton
come to see me directly, Frank?
Because he knew you'd say no.
So?
I need this.
Do this for an old friend.
I know I promised
never to mention Juarez.
This means
that much to you, Frank?
Consider us even.
-I'm so sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry about that.
-What are you doing?
Get her! Get her!
Don't let her get away!
What are you doing, stop!
Stop!
-Look at me!
-Don't! Stop!
She's mine!
-Please stop, please!
-You guys go watch, man.
You guys can watch.
Shut up!
Shut up, please, shut up!
You're gonna like this,
you're gonna like this a lot.
Please!
Please stop!
Please stop! Please!
-Why did you kill her?
-I didn't kill anyone, I swear!
Yeah, you did!
Why did you do it?
I didn't kill anybody!
I didn't kill anybody.
We just wanted to have
some fun, I'm sorry!
My God,
please don't hurt me!
I didn't kill anybody, I swear!
We thought it was fun.
Don't hurt me!
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
The police will be here soon.
Remember what
I'm going to tell you.
You didn't see
what happened, okay?
You cannot tell them about me.
You'll be alright.
You gotta trust me.
Of course Claxton
would send you.
How long did we know each other?
Fifteen, 20 years?
I forget.
I chose that team.
If it was anybody else
who had do this...
I wouldn't want it.
Time.
Thanks for making it easy.
See you on the other side.
Hey, stranger.
I missed you last night.
I didn't know you
were waiting for me.
Internet sales, right?
Do you wanna take a seat?
I'm gonna go back
to my usual table.
So, you know my name,
and I still don't know yours.
Ronus, Ronus Steele,
that's my name.
That's a name.
Okay, Ronus Steele,
spill it out.
You come here every
night with your iPad,
you sit on the same table.
You sit there for hours,
you drink black straight coffee,
and then you leave.
So you can't be married
or even have a girlfriend,
so I'm guessing a dog?
A wife.
She died.
I am so sorry,
I didn't know...
That's okay,
I'm dealing with it.
Sometimes good to
talk out loud, you know?
I recently lost my dad.
So it's getting really late,
and I should go.
But I'll see you around?
Do you need a ride?
Yeah, but how do I know
that you're not a weirdo
or something like
that?
You don't.
But I'm not.
Okay.
Sure, let's go,
but I gotta warn you,
I'm really good in self-defense.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I do cardio kickboxing
at the gym.
I'm not gonna
mess with you then.
Close the door! Shit!
Get up.
Dude.
Get up!
You move, I empty your
fuckin' brains on the floor.
What the hell you doin' here?
He's a friend of yours?
Ouch!
You didn't tell me
he's so rough.
If I got to babysit,
it's gonna start today.
You got five minutes.
Yeah...
Give me the gun.
Give me that gun.
Give me...
-I like that.
-Not so funny anymore?
Do you wanna play?
Alright, 007
let's do this quick.
Frank told me I was gonna
go with you on a hit.
This is not a game, pal.
Feels like one to me.
Frank is dead.
We all gotta go sometime.
Never take your eyes
off of the target.
Lesson number one,
never take your
eyes off the target.
Lesson number two,
you don't kill anybody
that doesn't deserve to die.
Lesson number three,
stay focused on the target.
Never take your
eyes off the target.
Lesson number four,
always let them see you coming.
It drops their guard,
you get closer to the target.
Lesson number five,
immobilize your target.
Tomorrow you'll have
the chance to see my magic.
You don't look too good.
Need to get some rest.
Dumb-ass.
Good morning, sir,
what can I get for you?
Large coffee, black.
Would you like a shot of
cinnamon or vanilla sprinkles?
Just black, are you deaf?
Okay, okay,
that'll be $2, please.
Maria, large black coffee for
the cranky man that smells bad.
This is for you.
A man brought it
over last night.
He said you would be
in here this morning.
He also said you were
very, very smelly.
How'd you know me?
He said you were the man
sleeping on the park bench
across the street.
He also said you also
had a lovely personality.
One large coffee.
What a cutie.
Get in.
Well, if it ain't the sandman.
You thought that shit was funny?
Fuck you!
Just get in.
So you can put
me to sleep again? No way.
Just get in.
Where's your friend?
I don't know,
and I don't care.
Just a beer?
Just a beer and nothing to eat?
Yeah. I'm fine.
What time do you get off?
Hey, everyone, last call!
Last call, everyone.
-So...
-Excuse me, okay?
Easy, easy.
It's okay, he's just...
just rude.
always...
I got it, I got it.
-Jess?
-Yeah.
You okay, baby?
Meet me at the bathroom real
quick.
I'm gonna clean up, okay?
Hey...
it's none of your business.
Who's the big dog?
Donovan.
He owns this place
and everyone in it.
He own you?
Nobody owns me, you know that.
What if I told you,
five minutes from now,
I'm gonna beat
the shit out of him?
I'd say,
"Cool! Can I watch?"
Hi!
-You made it.
-Yeah.
I didn't think you were gonna
come by, I'm glad you did.
Do you want coffee?
-Not tonight.
-Okay.
So I know you're a student,
do you have a job beside study?
No, I've got a generous dad.
And your mom?
She died 10 years ago
in a boating accident.
Sorry about that.
She was mean,
and she never loved my dad.
That sounded wrong.
I was always closer to my dad.
So it hit me more when he died.
It sounds like
he was a good man.
He was... the best.
Are you a good man?
I'm trying to be.
Hey.
You handled yourself
pretty good back there.
You never told me what
you do for a living.
Kill people.
You kill people?
Like a hitman?
Assassin.
Sexy.
When were you gonna tell me?
I don't know.
You gonna kill me?
Are you gonna tell on me?
On the contrary,
what you did to them,
the way you did it.
You're a little messed up,
you know that?
You didn't seem to
mind it last night.
Can't lie about that.
Okay, gotta go.
Let me tag along on your hits.
No way.
You and I could work
really well together.
Yeah, right.
I won't get in the way,
I won't. I won't.
Okay, be ready when I call.
Okay?
Riskin, Chuy.
Please, Mr. Steele,
I want to live.
The last time I see this man,
I almost not survive.
He's like a ghost who come to my
bedroom and drop me to pieces.
Buenas noches, amigo.
Inside, you will find my
son's friend named Mickey.
He'll know how to find
the man you are looking for.
Adios.
Adios, amigos.
Get off me!
-Shut up!
-Not cool, man!
-Shut up! Shut up!
-God!
Shut up! Hey, you don't
have a lot of time.
What the fuck did you give me?
Shut up, shut up,
listen, wake up!
Hey, hey, hey.
I forgot to mention
the nasty side effect.
You're gonna lose
all motor control.
Your heart is gonna
start to race.
Eventually, your blood
is gonna boil.
So you get the picture?
I need to know...
Hey, hey, wake up!
You got information I need.
Do you know a man named Raskin?
I didn't do anything!
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up! Shut up!
You know you don't have
a lot of time before
you bleed out of your ass
and you swallow your tongue,
so you understand that?
You understand? I need to know where
he hangs out, can you tell me?
-Yes.
-You can tell me? Okay.
You see this?
Now this is gonna
save your life.
Not yet...
But remember... if you lie...
you're gonna see me again.
Hey.
-Talk.
-Are you ready?
Jeez.
I'll text you
when I review the area
-and I ID the target.
-Dude, just get to the point.
C'mon, just tell me,
I'm not a freakin' kid.
-Jeez.
-The Roxy.
When you get there,
don't do anything stupid.
Yeah, alright,
I'll see you there, bye.
C'mon, babe, gotta go
out for a kill, let's go.
Why in the hell
did you bring her?
-She's good.
-She's no good.
I know what I'm doing, okay?
Looking good in your two
dollar shirt.
Yeah. That's real good.
Look, everybody's laughin'.
Listen...
can I ask a favor?
Please, no shit tonight.
Goldy's good.
So what's the plan here?
Son of a bitch has
got enough protection.
What the hell is this?
I don't know. Probably a
crime boss or something.
Shit always sticks to shit.
That explains a lot.
No one shot.
For real, just play it cool.
Goldy, why wouldn't I?
Why would I do
anything to hurt you?
You know the last time you
didn't do anything to hurt me,
it took me a month to re-open.
Listen, it behooves you.
-Alright?
-I got it.
I mean it,
you're like a brother to me.
I'd do anything for you.
We're pals.
This shit is
getting interesting.
Where you goin'?
We had a deal...
One of your boys
crossed the line
and raided my business.
Calm down with that,
it was a mistake, that's all.
You know, boys will be boys.
Screw that.
You and I both know we don't
make mistakes like that.
Listen to me,
the east side is mine,
and the west side
is yours for now.
For now.
That is great.
Just statin' the facts.
The Valley Cartel are not
too happy with you right now.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I know you're not
moving enough merchandise.
Hell, you should be
moving twice as much.
That's my business,
and I'm warning you.
Stay on your side of the
line or I swear to God
you'll have more trouble
than you've ever had.
Maybe.
And just maybe one day,
that trouble's gonna
come back and bite you
-in the asshole, man.
-Son of a bitch!
Sit down!
Not here, not now.
Sit down. Sit.
This is gonna blow.
Can you shut up?
Okay, I'm just fuckin' waiting.
Don't do it,
don't do it.
Looks like
your shit worked, man.
On the wrong fucking person!
We're fucking done.
You know what,
watch how I do it now.
Christina!
Giordano!
Hey! Riskin!
Listen, man,
we can make a deal.
I can give you a lot of money.
Just name me a price.
I'm sorry, Riskin,
you can't afford me.
-What is that?
-You mean this?
Don't worry about it.
It won't hurt a bit,
it's a matter of seconds.
You'll be fine.
I got a lot of money,
I'll pay you,
I'll make you a rich man.
I don't need your money.
What the hell
did you do that for?
I had him!
From my vantage point,
looks like he had you.
I had him!
Have the money
and everything, you know?
You're such an asshole.
Don't ever do that again.
I had him.
Hi!
Are you stalking me?
This is where
you go to college?
Yep, you're probably
not very good at it.
At what?
You're funny.
You really don't
strike me as a salesman.
They're usually very outgoing
and talkative and you're not.
Thank you.
I'll see you tonight?
I can't tonight,
I have lab, but tomorrow?
Sure.
Why her?
Nice, but you know I don't
mix business with pleasure.
Everything's in the dossier.
There's nothing there.
This one is special.
You know I don't
work that way.
Ronus, you're a
goddamn executioner.
This one doesn't feel right.
It's not your call.
Ronus, I know you're
getting cozy with her.
If that's tainting
your abilities...
-It hasn't.
-Then what's the big deal?
Look, if you feel
so strongly about it, walk away.
I'll assign someone
else to the case.
No one goes on this case.
Ronus, I'm gonna forget we
had this conversation today.
I'm also gonna forget that you
interfered with my work flow.
But I'm not gonna forget
that you have a job to do.
And I expect you to
follow through with it.
Turn that shit down!
How am I supposed to work?
Much better.
Man, I love this
Mission Impossible shit.
What's that?
Next case.
What a shame,
she's kinda cute.
No, she's not.
Well, we all
gotta go sometime.
-Holy shit.
-What?
Now that's what
I'm talking about.
Alright, get dressed.
We got some work to do.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Nah, you don't look good.
Let's go for a ride.
Sure.
That's cool,
we don't need to talk.
I have something
I have to tell you.
I never like a
conversation that begins with,
"There's something
I have to tell you."
Why don't we go get a drink?
There's a nice place
here on Albany Road. I'm buying.
Ronus, you're making this
too easy for me, buddy.
Can you handle the girl?
Are you serious?
What do you want to talk
about that's so important?
Actually, I'm not a salesman.
See? I knew it.
Ronus, what's wrong?
Hey, you're really
stressed out these days.
I think you need a
vacation, a few days off.
Just to clear your head,
you know?
I could go with you if you want.
You know what, yeah,
that sounds like a great idea.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Let's go to Tahoe.
It's so beautiful.
You know, I remember
when I was a little girl,
my dad, he used to take
us there all the time.
Best time of my life.
Do you like camping?
Hey, Ronus.
Who's that?
A friend of mine.
Just give me five minutes.
So ain't you gonna introduce
me to your lady friend?
Dude, holding out on me.
What are you doing here?
Just want to spend some time
with a good buddy, that's all.
After all,
I'm your apprentice, right?
You're just an asshole.
I also kind of figured
that you won't be able to
get the job done, so here I am.
This is my case.
I can take care of
my own business.
Dude...
She's a little young
for you, you know that?
Tell me...
Does she know what
you do for a living?
I mean, would it ruin things?
Would she like it?
We both know why I'm here.
Hey, thank you
for helping me back there.
-What?
-Yeah.
I really did, didn't I?
What's this.
Hey, don't touch that.
-Why not?
-Give it here.
What?
Why is there a
picture of me here?
Give it here, it's nothing.
They were there to kill me?
Ronus, what the hell?
You're a hitman, too,
aren't you?
You've killed people!
I'm in a car with a killer.
I'm going to
take you somewhere safe.
I must be out of my mind.
Where are we?
This is a safe place.
We cannot go back
to the same place,
they'll be looking for us.
Why do I have a hit on me?
There's enough ammo
here to hold off an army.
Why are you giving me a gun?
I thought this was a safe house.
It is a safe house,
we cannot be too safe. Take it.
Geez, put it down...
Don't touch anything, okay?
This asshole likes to put chemicals
on shit around that put you to sleep.
Don't touch anything, I said!
C'mon, move, just stay here.
Stay here and don't move.
Shit.
All locked.
Look at this!
Don't touch anything,
I said, what are you, deaf?
Let me see that.
-No!
-Give it back.
Talk.
-Take it off, now!
-No.
Nice things.
Whose were they?
Someone I knew a long time ago.
It's a little weird
wearing her stuff.
I'm sure she's okay.
Who are you, Ronus,
if that's even your real name?
It is.
I worked for a
security company with a
friend of mine long time ago.
He showed me how to rid of
some scums from this earth
and get paid for it.
At the time, it sounded pretty
good, so I took the job.
First time, it was scary.
I thought a lot about
the guy I eliminated.
Killed?
He murdered five innocent people
in a supermarket while robbing it.
Later on that night,
he raped a woman.
And beat her unconscious.
It was a politician's mistress.
And you don't mess with
politician's mistress.
So how do you do it,
you know, kill them?
I don't like guns.
I don't like knives,
it's too personal.
I was a chemist.
I used a combination
of agents to kill.
So you mean poison?
In the end, yes,
you're right, it's poison.
Can be fast...
Or painfully slow.
Depends on the case.
So you're God,
you pass judgement?
No, I'm not God.
God works too slow for me.
So am I one of your cases?
Hi, I have an appointment
with Dr. Camacho.
Your appointment is here.
Thank you.
Hi, Dr. Camacho?
Gabriela Dresden.
Ms. Dresden, nice to meet you.
The report came in,
and at first,
I thought cardiac arrest
might be the initial C.O.D.
I looked closer and found
discoloration on his skin,
consistent of Botulinum.
Yeah, but what does that mean?
Botulinum is a
very deadly poison.
I almost missed it
in the tox report.
Very fast, lethal and effective.
Thank you.
Hey, beautiful.
Alright, come on,
let's go say hi to Ronus.
Excuse me!
Hi, could you please show
me to the records window?
Certainly, yeah, straight
down this corner on the left.
You can't miss it.
On the left, okay, thank you.
This way? Thanks.
-Where is she?
-Just give a minute.
Fucking cops inside.
What a waste of time.
When she comes out,
we're gonna follow her.
She'll lead us to Ronus.
That place is freakin'
crawling with cops today.
Shouldn't their fat asses be
eating some donuts or something?
-Freakin' pigs.
-Hey.
You know, I never liked donuts.
-This your car?
-Yeah.
You probably
know you're illegally parked
in an emergency vehicle zone.
No, I don't know, I don't
see any signs or anything here.
And your tags are expired.
Shit, that's great.
Let me get
your driver's license,
registration
and proof of insurance.
Where's the registration?
I don't know what that is.
Well, Mr. Beasley.
Your luck just
keeps getting worse.
-These are both expired.
-No, they're not.
I'm afraid we're gonna
have to tow your vehicle.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, Mr. Officer, I just
hitched a ride with Mr. Beasley.
I don't really know him.
Okay, you can go.
-Really?
-Mr. Beasley here
has to sign a citation.
Step out of the car, sir.
You bailed on me?
While you were busy making
friends with the police,
this bitch followed her.
And how the hell
did you follow her?
You're the only one with skills.
I'm parked on the
side of the road.
I'll text you directions.
You still have
your phone, right?
Well, you're talking to me.
But you don't have a car.
The buses are still running.
Just shut up, I'll get there.
Jesus,
where the hell did you go?
Where were you?
Next time you leave,
please do me a favor
and let me know.
That'd be great, thank you.
I went to the
coroner's office, okay?
My dad died a month ago.
I just wanted to see
what happened to him.
Hey.
I was just worried
about you, okay?
Do you think he's dead?
What the fuck,
there's only two of them inside.
You wanna go in, go!
Stay back, look,
I'm the assassin here,
you're just along for the
ride, don't forget that!
-Did you see that?
-Shit!
I'm standing right here.
He just took
out all your guys.
Well, why the hell do you
think I send them first?
Ronus!
Do you think
this case is over?
Not yet.
They will send more.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I just want this to be over.
I know we won't be
safe here anymore.
I got some passports for us,
we can head to Mexico.
I don't think we're
gonna need those passports.
I recently
lost my dad... my dad.
I was hoping I was wrong.
So that was you
right from the beginning.
Not that it matters anymore,
but why did you go
through all this?
How come you didn't kill me
right from the beginning?
Claxton knew it would take
an elaborate set up like this,
for someone to get
close enough to kill you.
Blaine, and the others?
Well, you did an amazing job
cleaning up their messes.
And you made
Claxton's job easier.
You don't know how many
times I wanted to kill you.
But I had to wait
till you finished the others
and my father.
He never talked about you.
Would it have
made any difference?
No emotional ties.
Remember?
I loved my father,
and he trusted you.
Frank was my friend.
You know,
there was a small part of me
that wanted to be
wrong about you.
Claxton has been
playing you and me
right from the beginning.
When you killed him,
you took a piece of me.
He knew I was going to
kill him before I did.
My dad was a good man.
You don't know how glad I am
that I figured out
all of your tricks.
Not all of them.
No!
Please!
Ronus...
-I thought you'd be...
-Dead?
In another country by now,
enjoying the fruits
of your labor.
Listen, whatever
you came here to do
or think you're about to do.
Make sure you know the outcome.
It ends here
one way or another.
I'm a dead man either way.
Ronus, it was never personal.
You became expendable,
and you know the rules.
Hell, you made
the rules yourself.
It was just a matter of time.
Who knows, but my time with
the agency may be over soon.
Maybe you're here on a case...
yourself.
Gabriela?
Too bad.
You know, I think she
genuinely liked you.
I considered
taking her off the case.
Where do we go from here?
I'm giving you a pass.
Something you never give anyone.
Well, that's so
gracious of you.
I expected more from you.
I thought you'd be
made of sterner stuff.
Just go ahead.
We've got a little
standoff here.
Let's figure this out.
I already figured it out.
Just take me off the list.
Well, I take you off the list,
what's to stop you
from killing me?
Nothing.
There you go, now what?
Consider this my
retirement bonus.
You son of a bitch.
Great job, Michael.
You didn't really
think you could just
walk away like that, did you?
Need me to off him?
No, not here in the open.
Get the hell
out of here, Ronus.
Run as far as you can,
but know this,
I'll be right behind you.
There's no place on God's
earth where you'll be safe.
Somehow, I knew you'd
say something like that.
It's survival of the fittest.
Consider the time you have
left of your retirement bonus.
I'm off.
Let's get the hell out of here!
No!
Doing okay?
Anything else you need?
Excuse me.
I thought you were someone else.
It's okay, wish I were.
Is everything alright?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
-Peak-a-boo.
-Screw yourself.