Advertise your product or brand here
Contact www .OpenSubtitles .org today
I N T E R T E L L R
My father was a farmer.
Like all that time.
Of course not started in this business.
The computer says it's too tight.
- I'm almost there.
- A cross the Strait.
- Try to get off, Cooper.
- All right!
- The proceed to foreclosure.
- No, do not do it!
Father?
Sorry, Murph. Come back to bed.
I thought you were the ghost.
- The ghosts do not exist, love.
- The grandfather says can you catch them.
No, this is because the grandfather is
close to becoming one.
Come back to bed.
I was dreaming about the accident?
Go back to bed, Murph.
We ran out of wheat.
We came the plague and had to burn.
But still remained in the corn.
We hectares of corn.
But what there was more dust.
I can not describe -la,
It was simply continued.
Was just that,
a constant dust.
We used sheet pieces
to cover the nose and mouth.
So as not to inhale too -la.
When we put the table,
the dishes were turned upside down.
Glasses, cups,
everything was upside down.
- Dispatch -t. Murph, touches the floor!
- Today at 13h, meet me at the barn.
- Herbicide Resistance 101, understand?
- Yes, sir.
At the table no, Murph.
Father, you can arrange -la?
- What the hell did you do to my rig?
- It was not me.
- Let Me guess. Was your ghost?
- He dropped -a of my shelf.
- Just like the books.
- The ghosts do not exist, idiot!
- Watch your language!
- Have I researched and calls If poltergeist.
- Tell HIM, Dad.
- That's not very scientific, Murph.
Said that science was admitted
our ignorance.
Now shut -t.
Anyway, try to have more
esteem for our stuff.
Coop.
All right.
Murph, if you want to talk about science,
do not just say you're afraid of a
ghost. You have to go further.
One must acknowledge the facts, analyze them,
get to the how, why and after
present your findings. Okay?
- Okay.
- Very well.
- Have a good day of school.
- Wait.
Parents meeting
It is with his father, not his grandfather.
Calm, Turbo!
It is a dust storm.
- The Nelson is burning the crops.
- Because of the plague?
They say there will never be
Another okra harvest.
Never again.
- I should have planted corn as all of us.
- Be nice to the Hanley Professor.
- It is single.
- And that means what?
Repopulate the Earth.
Start doing your part, young.
And if not metesses nose
which are not called? Old man.
All right, Murph,
gets the second.
Third!
- Looking for change, idiot.
- Cala -t, Tom!
- What did you do, Murph?
- Not done anything more.
- He blew a tire, that's all.
- Murphy's Law.
Cala -t!
- Go get the spare, Tom.
- Already we are using.
Brings kit for holes.
How do fix it out here?
You'll have to find out. I will not go
always be here to help you.
What's wrong, Murph?
Why did you and Mom
They gave me the name of something bad?
I did not give anything.
Murphy's Law?
Murphy's Law does not want to
say something bad...
.. .irá Happen. Says -In only
that what has to happen,
It happens.
And it seemed correct -In.
Enter.
Come in, come on!
What about the flat tire?
It is a drone of the Indian Air Force.
The solar batteries could
feed a whole farm.
Takes the wheel, Tom.
Come on, accelerates!
He points to it.
- Faster, Tom, we are losing it.
- Right.
Points out well for him.
Wait...
Here we go...
Good driving, Tom.
Father?
I am about to catch it.
Do not stop now!
- Father!
- Tom!
What? Said to
continue driving.
I think this answers the old question:
"If I throw a well, would you go back?"
- I lost it.
- No, we have not lost!
Would you like a ride?
Repairs.
Come here.
We will land it does there,
the dam margins.
Very well.
How long do you think
have you been up there?
The Mission Control in Delhi
closed 10 years ago, such as ours.
10 years ago?
- Why was flying so low?
- I do not know.
Perhaps the sun has fried the processor
or walked looking for something.
What?
Pass Me the screwdriver.
Perhaps some kind of sign.
I do not know.
What will you do with it?
I will give HIM something socially
responsible for making...
- How to drive a combine -debulhadora.
- We can not let it does go?
It does not hurt anyone.
Listen, Murph, this thing has to learn
adapting If, like us all.
- So how do we do? Come with me?
- I have classes.
But this girl,
You will have to wait.
- What have you done?
- They say when you come after -t.
- I'll have to annoy me?
- Not with me.
But please, controls -t.
Do not worry.
I got this!
- You're late, Coop.
- Yes, I had a puncture.
And I assume that you have stopped at a store
Chinese fighter jets.
In fact, it -If
a surveillance drone.
With a solar batteries
exceptional. It is Indian.
Sits -t.
Well, we already have the results of Tom.
- It'll be a great farmer.
- Yes, you are falling for it.
What about college?
Well, just enter the university.
There are not enough resources.
I continue to pay taxes. Where
the money goes? There are no more armies.
For universities
will certainly not.
Look, Coop, you have to be realistic.
Now you close the doors of
University to my child? He is 15 years old.
The result of Tom is not
loud enough.
As medes waist?
- About 80, 84 of crotch?
- I do not see where you want to reach.
Are you telling me that are accurate
2 numbers to measure your ass,
but only one for
measure the future of my child?
Come on, you are a learned man, Coop...
and a trained pilot.
- And an engineer.
Okay, but now we do not need
more engineers.
We were not without television or
aircraft; we ran out of food.
The world needs farmers.
Good farmers like you and Tom.
- Uneducated farmers.
- We are a provisional generation, Coop.
And things are improving.
Perhaps your grandchildren will eventually be...
Already we finished, sir?
No. Ms. Hanley is
here to talk about Murph.
The Murph is a flawless girl,
very clever.
But it has had some
problems lately.
I brought it to an oral presentation.
The chapter on lunar landings.
Yes, it's one of my old books.
Always liked the pictures.
It is an old federal book.
Substituímo it does the corrected versions.
- Fixed?
- Explain that the Apollo missions
They were simulated to take
the Soviet Union into bankruptcy.
We do not believe that we went to the moon?
I believe it was an advertisement
bright it took the Soviets
the esturrarem resources
rockets and other useless machines.
Useless machines?
And if you do not want to repeat the excesses
and waste of the 20th century,
then we have to elucidate the
our children on this planet.
No stories of how abandon it.
I know one of these machines
useless they used. If called MRI.
And if we still had any,
doctors could have detected
cyst in the brain of my
woman before she died not after.
In that case, she would be sitting here
to hear it instead of me,
which would be great, for it
always had more patience.
I'm sorry for his wife, Mr. Cooper.
But Murph became aggressive
with some of his colleagues
because of this nonsense
Mission Apollo.
As such we thought fit to call it does
to discuss how best
to deal with this behavior
hereinafter.
Because, it turns out tomorrow
at night there game.
She is now a baseball,
and will play her favorite team.
There will be candy, soft drinks...
I think I'll take her.
- How did it go?
- I got -te a suspension.
- What?!
- Cooper.
Speaks Cooper says.
Coop, the harvesters that -debulhadoras
If reconstruíste passed through.
- Reset the controls.
- I've done it, but you should come take a look.
Abandoned fields
and returned here one after another.
Something is interfering with the compass.
Magnetism.
Or something.
There is nothing special about the books. I have
been working on it, like you said.
- I counted the spaces.
- What for?
For the Ghost case try
communicate. I'm trying to Morse.
- Morse?
- Yes, dots and dashes...
I know what it is Morse code, Murph.
But I do not think your bookshelf
is trying to talk to you.
I had to reset every clock
compass and GPS to correct the anomaly.
- What was?
- I do not know.
If the house had been built
on magnetic ore,
we would have repaired the
first time we called the tractor.
I heard that the meeting at school
I did not go too well.
Oh yes? It is as if we had
forgotten who we are, Donald.
Explorers, pioneers,
not only caregivers.
When I was young, I felt as if Me
invent something new every day.
Whether it was a device or idea.
As if it were Christmas every day,
but in a world of 6 billion people.
Tries to imagine.
And each of them trying to
monopolize everything.
This world is not so bad.
And Tom will adapt up well.
I do not encaixas you.
Born 40 years more
late or 40 years earlier.
My daughter well knew.
God bless her.
And your children will know,
especially Murph.
Before we looked at
the sky and wondered
which was our place in the stars.
Now look down
and -In are concerned with
our place in the dust.
Cooper, thou good eras
in something,
but never had the
exploring opportunity.
Sorry.
Nobody expected the
land that gave us food,
turned against
us and destroy them.
April, if I remember correctly.
I believe it was April 15.
It was around 13: 30h than that
thing collapsed Gorge top.
In my time it is that there was real
players. Who are these stray?
Yes, but in my time, people
they were too busy
to fight for food,
instead of playing baseball.
Popcorn in a baseball game even looks
evil. I want a hot dog.
They say you're going to school
follow my footsteps.
- It seems Me quite well.
- It seems -t well?
I hate the fifth, Dad.
Words grandfather.
That's what grandfather said? Listen, what matters
It is how you feel about it.
I like what I do.
And taste of our farm.
And it'll be very good at it.
Let pisgar -In here.
Okay, this is the brave.
Malta, plays to put the masks.
- Tom, Murph ready?
- Yes.
Murph, Tom, closed the windows?
Murph.
The ghost.
Grab your pad.
You're gonna sleep with Tom.
Not a ghost.
It gravity.
I take the tone, then follow the city.
You're gonna clean the room?
When they are done for the honor.
Not Morse, Murph, is binary.
The thick lines
equals 1, the fine 0.
They are coordinated.
That's right.
I can not lose pinch.
The grandfather returns here
a few hours, Murph.
But you not know what you will find.
It is therefore,
that I can not take you.
Murph.
Grandfather comes soon,
HIM says that after I turn on the radio.
Jesus!
What are you doing here?
You think that's funny?
I would not be here if it was not me.
Do something useful.
Murph.
I think the road stops here.
Brought a cutting pliers?
Beautiful girl!
- Move If the fence.
- Do not shoot, I'm unarmed.
My daughter is in the car.
Do not be afraid.
- How did you find this place?
- Where is my daughter?
I had the coordinates of these
facilities marked on the map.
- How is that achieved?
- Where is my daughter?
Do not make me knock it does
Again, feel -If!
You think yet
you are a Marine, comrade?
The Marines do not exist.
And you know what?
I have soldiers like you
Me cut the grass.
Where did you find these coordinates?
Unless you wanna end
as a cut -relvas...
- I think I'd give a fabulous cleaner.
- Do not think so.
TARS, retreats, please.
It is to take risks to
use security ex-military.
They are antiquated and units
control are unpredictable.
That's what the government could arrange.
- Who are you?
- I'm Dr. Brand.
I met once a Dr. Brand,
but was a teacher.
What makes you think I'm not?
It was not so handy.
Please Dra. Brand,
I have no idea where I'm stuck.
But I am worried about
my daughter, and I want -a beside me.
Bring -a and tell HIM -ei
everything you want to know.
Takes the director and the girl
to the meeting room.
Your daughter's fine.
It is quite insightful.
- You must have a very intelligent mother.
- Made it clear they do not want visits.
Why not let us go back for
where we came from and follow path?
- It's not that simple.
- Of course it is.
I know nothing about you,
nor about this place.
You know yes.
Father!
Hello, Cooper.
Professor Brand.
Explain how you found Me
these facilities.
It was as if tropessássemos them.
We were on a rescue mission...
He is sitting in secret
best kept in the world.
Nobody stumbles in
entry or exit.
Cooper, please
cooperates with these people.
Well, it's hard to explain.
We found these coordinates
- Through an anomaly.
- What kind of anomaly?
Hesitate to qualify her from
supernatural, but it is not scientific...
You will have to start being more
Specifically, Mr. Cooper, and quickly.
It gravity.
What kind of anomaly
gravitational and where?
I really like your
enthusiasm for gravity, but...
We will not say anything
until we have guarantees.
- Guarantees?
- Exactly.
As we leave here safely
and not in the boot of a car.
- Do not you know who we are, Coop?
- No, Teacher, I do not know.
You know my father, Professor Brand.
We NASA.
- NASA?
- Exactly.
The same NASA to whom pilotavas.
I heard they were extinct by
refuse to drop bombs
the stratosphere over
hungry people.
When they realized that killing people
It was not a long term solution,
again they need us. Secret.
Why keep it secret?
Because public opinion would not
approve spending on space exploration.
Not when we fight for
put food on the table.
Pests.
They decimated the wheat,
seven years ago.
Okra this year.
Only left the corn.
But we have the production
highest ever.
Yes, but like potatoes in Ireland
and wheat during the dust storm,
corn will have its end.
Soon.
We'll find a way,
Teacher, always did.
Guided by the firm belief
that the earth is ours.
No, not just ours.
But it is our home.
The Earth's atmosphere
It is composed of 80% nitrogen.
But we do not even breathe the.
Pests yes, and as they proliferate,
our air gets less and less oxygen.
The last to starve
They are the first to suffocate.
And the generation of thy daughter
It will be the last on Earth.
The Murph is getting tired. I let -la
get some rest in my office?
Sure, thanks.
Very well.
Now tell Me what is the
his plan to save the world?
The idea is not to save the world.
It leaves it.
Rangers.
The latest components
our versatile ship in orbit.
The Endurance. Our ultimate expedition.
You sent people into space
looking for a new home?
- The Lazarus missions.
- Sounds exciting.
- Lazarus back from the dead.
- Sure, but first he had to die.
There is no planet in our
solar system that can sustain life
and the nearest star
It is a thousand years away.
It is no attainable goal.
Where you sent them?
Cooper, I can not advance any more,
unless accepted steer this ship.
- You are the best pilot we've ever had.
- I barely got out of the stratosphere.
This team never left the simulator.
We need a pilot, and this is the
mission to which they were trained.
Even without knowledge?
An hour ago, they did not even know I was
alive but would anyway.
We had no choice.
But something brought you here.
- They chose -t.
- They who?
- How long I will be out?
- Hard to say.
- Years?
- I have children, Professor.
Go there and saves -the.
Who are they?
We began to detect anomalies
gravitational, nearly 50 years ago.
Basically, small distortions in
our equipment into the upper atmosphere.
In fact, I believe that
Also you find one.
Yes, in the Strait.
During despenhamento, something
disabled the electronic controls.
Exactly.
But of all the anomalies,
This is the most significant.
Close to Saturn.
A change in the space -time.
- It is a wormhole?
- She appeared 48 years ago.
- And you will be where?
- The other galaxy.
A wormhole is not a phenomenon
what happens naturally.
- Somebody put him there.
- They?
And whoever they are,
it seems they are in to help.
Wormhole that allows -In
travel to other stars.
It appeared exactly
when needed.
They put potentially worlds
habitable within reach.
- Twelve, based on the first probes.
- Probes sent there?
We sent people there,
ten years ago.
The Lazarus missions.
Twelve possible worlds,
Rangers twelve launches.
Transporting humans more
Bold history.
Led by
Dr extraordinary. Mann.
Each personal landing capsule
He secured survive two years.
But it could resort to hibernation
to prolong this time,
extending the analysis environments
Organic for decades.
The mission consisted of
evaluate this new world
and proved potential would send one
sign before entering a long sleep
- Waiting to be rescued.
- And if the world did not show potential?
Hence bravery.
- Do not have the resources to visit the twelve.
- Certainly.
The data transmission through the
wormhole is rudimentary.
Simple binary packages
received annually
-In give clues
Worlds with potential.
One of the systems
If shown promise.
Just one. More like
a long shot, right?
A system with
three potential planets.
There's nothing remote.
Wait there.
So if we find a good place,
what happens?
- This is the remote possibility.
There is a plan A and a plan B.
Did you notice anything strange
the launch camera?
The whole installation is centrifugal.
It's some kind of vehicle?
A space station?
Both. That's the plan A.
How to raise the ground?
The first abnormalities
gravitational changed everything.
Suddenly, we knew the
use of gravity was real.
As such, I started working
a theory and we started
- The construction of this station.
- But still not resolved.
That is why there is a backup plan.
The problem is gravity.
Taking a quantity
viable of people on the planet?
Here is a way, the B plan.
A demographic bomb.
We'll get 5, 000 fertilized ova
weighing up to 900Kg.
How do they would develop?
With the equipment on board
We incubate the first ten.
Thereafter, with surrogate mothers
If this growth is exponential.
In thirty years, we
generate a colony of hundreds.
The real difficulty of
Colonization is the genetic diversity.
With this, the matter is resolved.
What about the people of Earth?
Just drop them?
What about my children?
That's why Plan A
It is much more attractive.
- What progress?
- I'm almost there.
Asks Me to quit...
- The name of a "quasi".
- I'm asking you to trust me -t.
-In Find a new home.
And when you return, I will have
solved the problem of gravity.
-t Give you my word.
Will -te though!
- Murph.
- Go. If you must go, go!
This world has always been small
for you, it was not, Cooper?
Why? Because feel
I was born to travel through space?
Because it makes me excited?
- It does not make it wrong.
- Maybe do.
Do not trust the correct,
when the subject is wrong.
- The "why" is the great foundation.
- And the foundation is solid.
We farmers, we'd sit -In
here every year
when the rains came and we said:
"for next year."
Well, next year we do not
will save, nor to come.
This world is a treasure, Donald, but there
some time telling us to leave.
Humanity was born on Earth, but not
mean you have to die here.
Tom is right, but you must
work things out with Murph.
I will.
Without making promises
you know you can not keep.
You have to talk to me, Murph.
We have to make peace
before you left.
Then continue angry
just for you to stay.
When you were born, your mother told Me
something that never got to understand.
Me said: "Now we are here...
to be the memories
of our children. "
I think I now understand
what she meant.
When are the Father, the -t recompensest
Future ghost of your children.
Said that ghosts do not exist.
True, Murph.
Look at me.
I can not be your ghost now.
I need to exist.
They chose Me.
Murp, they chose Me. You saw.
You're the one you took me to them.
That's why even if you can not go.
I deciphered the message.
It's a word. You know what?
- Murph.
- FICA.
- He says to become the father.
- Murph.
Do not believe me!
Look for books. He said FICA.
Why not give me ears?
He said IT IS!
I'll return.
When?
One for you.
One for me.
Once you're up there
in hyper -sono,
or travel at the speed of light,
or near a black hole,
the time will be different for me.
Will walk slower.
Therefore, when
we meet again,
- We will compare.
- Time will pass differently to us?
Yes.
Maybe when I get back,
we have the same age.
You and me. It is absurd!
Can you imagine?
- Murph...
- You have no idea when you will return.
- The idea!
- Murph.
Do not make me leave like this.
Come on, Murph!
Do not leave me like that, Murph!
I love you're in for ever.
Did you hear Me good?
And I'll return.
I will return.
- How did it go?
- Well.
He went well.
- -t Love, Tom.
- Travel with care, okay?
Takes account of this
place for me, okay?
- All right?
- All right.
- Can I use the van while you are away?
- The one that now belongs to you?