♪♪
All right, I'm in. I just
have to locate the intel
and I'll be out
in less than five.
You know, as long as
no one stops...
Uh-oh.
How y'all doin'?
( nervous laugh )
I was just here to, you know,
pay my electric bill.
Can you guys, um, direct me
to Accounts Payable?
Okay, chill.
Chill, all right?
I was only a few days late.
MEN: ( groan )
Oh, look at that.
Now your lights are out.
Oh, man, did the DVR cut out?
I hate when that happens.
All right, fine.
Okay, I'm sorry.
They were on to me,
I had no choice but to bolt.
How could you completely
fail your mission?
Uh, wait. I'm still alive.
So, technically,
I didn't completely fail.
I only half-failed.
Which means I also
half-succeeded.
So, if you round up,
one could argue that
I completely succeeded.
I want answers, KC.
This was a simple mission.
Says the guy who hasn't
been on a field mission in,
what, 50 years?
Forty years?
( mouthing )
All I'm saying is
it wasn't my fault.
- They knew I was coming.
- How could they have known?
This was a top secret mission.
It was off the books!
Off the books?!
I swear they were
reading a book called:
KC Will Be Here At 6:15.
Are you saying someone
leaked information?
Everyone out.
Glad that's over.
Not you. You stay.
So you can apologize in private
for yelling at me
in front of everybody?
Guess not.
♪ Oh, when danger
comes for you ♪
♪ You know
I'll stand beside you ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't nobody
keep things hustle cool ♪
♪ I'll always find a way,
a way out of the fire ♪
♪ Don't tell nobody,
tell nobody ♪
♪ I'm not perfect ♪
♪ So many things
I wanna tell you ♪
♪ But I, I, I,
I keep it undercover ♪
♪ Livin' my life,
no way to learn ♪
♪ Doin' my thing,
gonna make it work ♪
♪ Know I'm the realest,
baby, I'm fearless ♪
♪ But I always
got your back ♪
♪ Nobody can do it
like I can ♪
♪ I gotta find out
who I am ♪
♪ Ain't got to worry
about me ♪
♪ It's all
part of the plan ♪
I keep it undercover.
I keep it
undercover.
Are you suggesting there's
a mole inside the Organization
leaking classified information?
No, you're suggesting
there's a mole.
My suggestion is next time
you do an interrogation,
you might wanna floss,
'cause you got enough
spinach in your teeth
to bake a quiche,
my friend.
Yeah.
Noted.
I'm putting you in charge
of finding the mole.
Wait, me?
Yep, you better
get on it right away.
Okay, you got it, sir.
But remember,
trust no one.
All right, but if
I can't trust anyone,
then how do I know
I can trust you?
- You can trust me!
- Oh, really?
'Cause that sounds
like something a mole would say.
KC, do I look like a mole?
I don't know.
I've never seen one before.
Or have I?
Get out.
Yes, sir.
Or, yes, mole.
( groans ) Agent Johnson
just assigned me
another top secret case.
Guess I'll be doing
all the work around here.
I'm kidding. We all play
an equally important role.
All right?
What would we do without Ray
ruining our coffee
every morning?
Give it up for Ray,
everybody!
Yeah! Ray!
Whoo!
All right, well,
I'm gonna head down to
the Olive Pit all by myself
and look over these
highly-classified
sought-after files.
All right.
Oh, um, Ray, that's actually
a soil sample from
the Fresno mission.
It's not ground coffee,
just... ground.
Hey, Ernie.
Not that you asked,
but I'm working at the school's
pop-up clothing sale.
We are selling
gently used clothes
to raise money for charity.
Hmm. It's cool you
decided to volunteer.
Volunteer?
More like volun-told.
Vice Principal Wysocki
is making me do it.
- Why?
- I don't know, something about
not paying attention in class.
Honestly,
I wasn't listening.
Anyway, we need more
guys' clothes
and I don't wanna ask
anyone I'm dating,
have dated
or might date,
so that leaves... you.
Um... what do you got?
Well, since it's for charity,
help yourself.
Oh.
Attention, everyone.
Don't bother bringing anymore
clothes to the pop-up sale,
we now have Ernie's
sweaty gym shorts!
No need to get any closer,
I'm sure you can smell them
from where you are.
Point taken!
I'll check my dad's closet.
He's got a couple coats
he never wears.
Okay, good. Oh, and since
we need more menswear,
you might wanna check
KC's closet, too.
( glasses beep )
Well, well, well.
Look who we have here.
Agents McKenzie and Garcia.
- Oh, hey, girl.
- Hey.
I'm on to you.
Do us a favor, KC,
don't tell anyone you saw
us here, we could get fired.
Oh, no, no, no, you guys are
gonna get more than fired.
You two are going to prison,
you lowlifes.
Prison? Sure, agents aren't
supposed to date each other,
but what Johnson doesn't know
won't hurt him.
It's not like what
we're doing is illegal.
No, no, no.
You two are here
because I planted a seed that
I had sensitive information
and you two moles
took the bait.
The only crime
committed here
was when Agent McKenzie
stole my heart.
- Uh-uh-uh! Uh!
- Oh!
I don't believe
any of that for a second!
Now...
can you explain to me
why $20,000
would be wired to your account
and then withdrawn the next day?
Yeah, that's right. I got
information, my friend.
Are you laundering money?
Maybe funding a terrorist
organization?
Or perhaps you guys are lighting
the cash on fire
because you two
are a couple of maniacs!
Maniacs!
( sarcastic ) Yeah,
we're the maniacs.
Not that it's any
of your business,
but my grandmother
loaned me the money.
And why would your grandmother
loan you $20,000?
( sighs ) To buy this.
Was gonna wait
till after dinner, but...
Lori... will you marry me?
No!
You had to borrow money from
your grandmother to buy a ring?
Get back to me when you
open a savings account.
Hey, look, man, um...
just for future reference,
pizza place?
Not really the best place
to pop the question.
CRAIG: Kira!
KIRA: What?!
CRAIG: Have you seen
my brown coat?
( mouthing )
KIRA: What brown coat?
CRAIG: My brown spy coat.
The one with the built-in
laser doohickey.
KIRA: It's in with
your spy gear.
CRAIG: I'm looking
in my spy gear!
I don't see it!
KIRA: Well, did you look
on your stationary bike,
or as I like to call it,
"the pants tree"?
CRAIG: ( laughs sarcastically )
It's not there.
KIRA: That coat better not
be lost, Craig.
It's a two-million-dollar
gadget.
Two-million-dollars?!
Hey, son!
Where you going?
Uh... school.
It's 6:00.
Never too late to learn.
Kira!
KIRA: What?
I love you, baby.
Yeah, I'm still not helping
you find that coat, Craig.
Oh!
I cannot sell you these jeans,
Mrs. Crowmise.
They are a crime
against fashion
and I will not be
your accomplice!
You shouldn't talk to your
math teacher like that!
Oh, it's okay, we're close.
I've had her
two years in a row.
So far.
Anyway, remember the brown coat
I donated?
I need it back. That coat is a
two-million-dollar spy gadget.
Seriously? Your dad owns
a two-million-dollar coat?
And he keeps a drawer full
of old soy sauce packets?
- Where is it?
- I'm so sorry.
I sold it
to some guy this morning.
Okay, I'm gonna need
your security tapes.
Entrances, exits, any
surveillance you might have.
Ernie, this is a pop-up sale.
The only surveillance we have
is Mrs. Eaton,
who keeps browsing
and never buys!
Well, at least tell me
what the guy looked like.
( scoffs ) I don't know.
He was-- He was round,
he was wearing a red shirt.
And, like, eating
something sweet.
You just described
Winnie the Pooh.
No... I don't think
that was him.
KC: I'm telling you, it's
the only way to find the mole.
If you wanna know how evil
thinks, you gotta talk to evil.
Fine, I guess
we have no choice.
To get inside, you're gonna need
the access code.
( clears throat )
11B4J27QR9TT.
( stammers )
Dang, if you were that hungry
I would've given you
some peanut butter crackers
from my backpack.
KC, it's too important
to have a paper trail.
You need to memorize it.
11B4J27QR9TT.
Okay. Yeah, no.
I got it.
Good, because it's far too
sensitive to keep repeating it.
You need me to say it again,
don't you?
( scoffs ) No.
I am a professional
international spy.
All right. I think
I can handle a code.
Okay, then what's the code?
- I know it starts with a one.
- ( groans )
No, no, I'm kidding.
Kidding, all right?
I got this.
( keypad beeps )
-9TS?
-GT! 9GT!
Hello, Zane.
Long time, no see.
Bernice, I'm glad
they let you visit me.
How's life?
Must not be easy
being stuck with KC's face.
I am KC.
Oh, yes. I see that now.
Still, must not be easy
being stuck with your face.
What brings you
all the way down here?
Let me guess.
You came to ask my permission
for Brett's hand in marriage?
( chuckles ) You're so
old-fashioned.
( sarcastic chuckle )
You're so delusional.
Look, I came here
'cause I need information.
And I need a bathroom
with a door.
I guess we're both
out of luck.
No, what you need
is a better attitude,
Mr. Stuck-in-the-poke-and-
never-seen-the-light-of-day-
the-rest-of-your-life.
Fine. I would be happy to give
you the information you require,
Miss Disappointingly-average-
teenage-spy-gotta-ask-her-
family-nemesis-for-help.
- Provided you
give me something.
- Sure. What is it?
Paint supplies, so I can paint
myself something to look at.
( scoffs ) Really?
I would have given you anything
and that's what you choose?
- And my freedom.
- No, no, no. Too late.
You already chose paints.
Now, look. Someone
is stealing information
from the Organization,
and I need to know
how you would do it.
Perhaps...
it's not being stolen.
Perhaps you shared it
with the wrong person.
What are you talking about?
No one even knows that
I'm a spy.
What about your blonde friend?
The one who talks faster
than she can think.
Marissa? No. No.
All of my secrets
are safe with her.
I mean, she never
told anyone that I practiced
kissing on my pillow.
You didn't hear that.
Think about it, KC.
It's always the people
that we trust the most.
Husbands betray wives.
Children lie to their parents.
Friends spread rumors
behind each other's backs.
Maybe Marissa is selling
your secrets for profit.
( inaudible dialogue )
Hey. Hey, hey, hey,
how are you?
( chuckles ) Marissa, can I talk
to you in private for a second?
KC, what are you
doing here?
Zane was right,
I can't trust you.
Who is that guy and are you
selling him my secrets?
- He is my date.
- Your date?
Oh, so all of a sudden you
have a boyfriend that you
never even told me about?
I didn't tell you because
he's a freshman in college
and I knew you'd give me
a hard time 'cause
I'm still in high school.
No, Sean, Sean, Sean.
Don't leave.
I'm only technically
in high school
and I'm barely ever there!
Thanks a lot, KC.
Why are you spying on me?
There's a mole
in the Organization
and sometimes I tell you
highly classified information.
You actually thought that
I was selling your secrets?
For your information, when
you're telling me spy stuff,
most of the time I'm just
standing there quietly
waiting for you to stop talking
so I can start talking
about myself again.
I can't believe you.
You're right, you're right.
I'm sorry, okay?
It was wrong, I should've
never suspected you.
But I am not sorry
for ruining your date,
because that guy's too old
for you. I do not approve.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna have a little chitchat
with a criminal.
Oh, so I can't date someone
a tiny bit older than me,
but you can go hang out
with criminals?
That is a double standard,
missy.
Hey, at least
I have standards.
Well, she got me there.
Ah, KC, what do you
think of my painting?
Well, it's a pretty good alien.
It's a kitten.
In that case, it stinks.
You lied to me.
Marissa isn't the mole.
I'm taking the paints back.
I didn't lie to you. I was
simply illustrating a point.
Well, you illustrate points
about as well as you
illustrate kittens.
Now I need information.
How do I find the mole?
( clicks tongue )
Poor KC.
She's not asking
the right question.
I meant what I said.
It's always the ones closest
to us that hurt us the most.
So ask yourself, KC,
who's closest to you?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
Think, KC.
Who do you see every day?
I don't know.
Who knows your every move?
I don't know!
Who knows you better
than you know yourself?
Who knows you so well
that you'd never suspect them?
Even though they're
right under your nose.
My family! Okay? My family!
I said it, but why
would someone in my family
want to sell me out?
Well now...
you're finally starting
to ask the right questions.
KC, you okay, honey?
You've hardly said a word
since you got home.
Yeah. I'm sure you'd
love it if I just spilled
all my secrets to you.
Yes, I would. I mean, I like our
mother-daughter talks.
In fact, I like talking
to everyone in this family.
CRAIG: Kira!
What do you want
from me now?!
I searched this house
from top to bottom,
somebody took my coat!
Coat? Is there
a coat missing?
( nervous chuckle )
That's weird.
Craig, nobody took your coat.
Obviously, you lost it.
I didn't lose it.
The only thing I've ever lost
was my place in line for those
New Edition reunion tour
concert ticket.
'Cause somebody didn't
feel like standing anymore.
My water broke, Craig.
You know, if you didn't
lose the coat, where is it?
I mean, it's not like it
just up and disappeared.
Maybe it did!
It is a spy jacket!
You're right, Craig.
And maybe it went
on vacation.
Maybe it booked a flight
to Aruba for some R&R!
Ohh! And we were fourth in line
when your water broke.
If you could've waited
ten more minutes,
I'd have had my tickets!
Why are you staring at me?
Because you're sweating.
- What do you have to hide?
- I didn't do anything!
Oh, really? Then why do you
look so guilty?
All right, I admit it!
I knew it!
My own brother, the mole.
Mole?!
I'm no mole.
I took Dad's coat.
I gave it to Marissa for
a stupid charity pop-up sale.
Wait, so you're
not the mole?
No. I'm a two-million-dollar
coat stealer.
And I have no idea
where it is.
You do know that coat has
a tracking device, right?
What? I had no idea.
Yeah, good luck with that,
computer guy.
( door slams )
CRAIG: Kira, I got my hand stuck
in the toilet.
KIRA: What the heck was your
hand doing in the toilet?
CRAIG: I already looked
everywhere else.
What was I thinking?
Of course none of these
chuckleheads could be the mole.
( gasps ) Winnie the Pooh!
Thanks, tracking device.
Those cannolis,
best in the city.
Thank you, thank you.
And for my next trick,
I will make this jacket
disappear.
CRAIG: I'm telling you
the coat wasn't there before.
KIRA: Oh, so it just magically
appeared in your closet?
CRAIG: No, I bet you put it
there to make me look stupid.
KIRA: Craig, you do not need
my help to look stupid.
You do that all on your own,
baby.
KC: Hey, Brett. A kiss?
I don't see why not.
11B4J27QR9TT.
You're a liar, Zane!
You'll never get out of here!
- 11B4Q...
- KC. KC.
You're talking in your sleep.
What was I saying?
You kept talking about Zane
and then saying a bunch
of nonsense numbers.
What numbers was I saying?
I don't know.
11B4-something.
The code!
It's in here!
It's gotta be in here.
Uh, hate to break it to you,
but you made more sense
when you were sleep talking.
( groans ) They're bugging me.
They're bugging me!
Yes, and you're
starting to bug me.
Ah! I got it.
Ooh!
Ow! Whoo!
Ow.
Well, I found the mole.
Excellent, I can't wait to get
a hold of that slimeball.
I'll make him wish
he'd never been born.
Or, we could
forgive and forget.
What are you
talking about?
Well, technically,
the mole is me.
You?
Yeah, um, I've been
talking in my sleep.
Remember that code
that you ate for lunch?
Oh, yeah.
( grunts )
Well, let's just say I've
been practically singing
that code in my sleep.
So whoever bugged my room,
will have that tune stuck in
their head for quite a while.
Wait, if the code
has been leaked,
that means...
Oh, move!
No, no, no!
How could this
have happened?
Hey, look at this.
"Hello, KC.
If you're reading this,
then I have successfully
escaped.
That, or I tried to escape
and you caught me
and now you're reading this back
to me just to tease me.
I'd like to thank you, KC.
Without your help,
I never would have been able
to leave this place.
Thanks to your stay
in my barn,
I learned that when you're
stressed you sleep talk."
ZANE: "Thanks to the bug
I planted,
it was only a matter of time
before you let
the access code slip
and one of my people
came to bust me out.
Oh, and thanks
for the paint supplies.
It's amazing
what you can accomplish
with a nice, sharp brush
and a dull guard.
I guess this is farewell.
But don't be sad, I'm sure
we'll see each other soon."
Zane's out there.
He hates my family
more than ever,
and it's all my fault.
Rob, your name's on TV.