NARRATOR: It was
nearly 100 years ago.
I was but a lone
trapper then and would
Spend my winters on
Manitou Island, where
Small game were plentiful.
I'd heard the legend
of the Wendigo,
But a man's ignorance of things
unseen is never questioned.
Legend became life when
I came face to face
With the monstrous snow beast.
It was a fierce battle
that rocked the world.
But through some grace
of God, I was victorious,
And my life would never
again be the same.
The moment I
defeated the beast, I
Realized I must
protect the world
From this evil
monstrosity's resurrection.
Knowing the legend, I marked
this spot, this sacred ground
With the skulls of all
the previous victims
Of the Wendigo, creating
a spiritual shield
To protect the world.
However, if the circle
was ever broken,
The Wendigo would be reborn once
again, more powerful than ever.
And now it is here, in this
circle, that I've remained.
For, be it a blessing, be it
a curse, I am the chosen one.
I am the Guardian.
[Gun shot]
I'll drink to that.
Here's to the three-breasted
women of good old Tibitan.
And now, my good
old friend, let's
Make a toast to ourselves.
Another round, please.
Thank you.
This one's mine.
To my good friend, Larry.
Who's dad's name was Barry.
It's so damn scary.
His mom was so hairy.
But I got to thank him
for bringing me out early.
Shooting them signs.
Little squirrelies and I figure
if we keep drinkin', we're
Going to end up...
Drunk!
[Laughing]
I'm itchin' to blast something.
I was hopin' I'd
run out of booze.
What?
Keep out?
Private?
There isn't any private
property on this island
While we're here.
Ready?
Aim.
Fire.
[Gun shot]
Woo, oo, oo.
Oh, look, a fence.
I guess we're gonna
have to turn back.
Private property?
[Laughing]
There's your private property.
Let's see if anyone's home.
What?
Something illegal's
going on here.
Holy cow!
It's murder, mass murder.
Look at all them skulls.
Where you going?
I'm going inside.
Man, let's just get
the hell outta here.
[Door creaks]
You leave my land.
I'm not about to let some old
bum tell me where I can't hunt.
Respect is an attribute, my
friend, one you should learn.
Respect?
I think you need
to learn to respect
The man with the high
powered weapon in his hand.
Hey, man, let's
just leave him alone.
Leave me alone.
I shall ask you once
again to leave my land.
You've never seen one of these
babies in action, old man.
You think you might
want a demonstration?
You have no idea what
you may be the cause of.
Let's just get out of here, OK?
[Gun shot]
Shut up, or I'll
blow your head off.
Please go.
[Gun shot]
No!
The circle has been broken.
The wind it whispers.
Tell me.
The wind whispers.
Wendigo.
Now what are we going to do?
Gotta get rid of him.
[Hoarsely gasping]
What do you mean?
[Crash]
Ah!
What the hell?
[Crashing and shattering glass]
Ah!
What's going on?
What the...
[Smash]
[Buzzing]
[Screaming]
[Evil laughter]
Whoa!
[Clattering]
[Dying scream]
Dave!
[Screaming]
The circle has been broken.
You are the chosen one.
You must complete the circle.
[Laughter]
I'm out.
You're out.
Pay up, you saps.
What do you mean, you're out?
Pete, talk to our man here
about your low interest loans.
What's the matter, pard?
You got a bad set of cards?
Are you outta cash?
Well, I-
Pete's Pawns can do you a deal.
Yeah, ride 'em, Hoss.
You got something to trade?
You got something to sell?
Or do you just need a loan?
Well, come on down
to Pete's Pawns.
Our interest rates are
famously low city-wide.
And we ain't just city wide.
Hell, county wide,
and we ain't never,
Never turned down a deal.
Now how much you need?
Uh, five bucks.
Five bucks.
Five.
Very good, son.
Always glad to do business
with a fine, upstanding
Citizen like yourself.
[Laughing]
What did I do?
I didn't mean it.
I swear to God I didn't mean it.
I'll tell them it
was an accident.
That's it.
No, wait a minute.
I'll tell them Dave
shot the old dude.
No, no.
Dave's in enough
trouble already.
First things first.
Big monster.
Giant monster.
Got to get off the island.
Got to round everybody up
and get off the island.
That's it.
Get off the island.
[Wolves howl and grown]
[Laughing]
I warned you suckers,
let a dead man die.
I got to get out.
God.
Oh, holy smoke.
What a flight.
I felt like I was in a bag
and they put me in a bag...
Here, here.
Chug it.
Oh!
You know, if you've ever
been to Albany, New York.
If you've ever flown in there...
Hey, where's this new guy?
Oh, I forgot.
Oh, God.
[Laughing]
[Interposing voices]
What?
Is there a problem?
Black man can't hunt?
We didn't mean nothing.
I know, us brother's don't
like the cold, right?
Well, I got some news for you,
don't ask to see my frostbite.
[Laughing]
Hey, I get it.
I get it.
I know where I'm not wanted.
Oh, come on.
[interposing voices]
No, I ain't staying.
Come on.
And
Come on Leo, they
didn't mean anything.
Come on.
Leo.
We didn't mean anything.
No offense.
We didn't even know Tony
was bringing anybody, right?
No.
See, this has kind of been like
our own secret little circle
For the last five years.
No offense meant.
My name's Pete.
Leo Phillips.
You can call me Leo.
Jerry.
Lee.
It
TELVISION ANNOUNCER:
This is Brick
Branding in downtown Tecumseh.
And at the top of our news,
there's a winter storm,
Which has still not let up.
All throughout the state, the
rampages of the storm are being
Felt. Over 100 schools have
been forced to close down
But the hardest hit is
the Upper Peninsula.
Not like the ones in '66.
Well.
What have we got here?
I need to get to the island.
First in the morning.
No.
I need to get to
the island tonight.
Lady, if we go out in
that storm tonight...
Is there anyone
else who can take me?
Lady, I'm the only pilot here.
If it's that important, you
can walk across the ice.
OK.
Well, I've done more stupid
things for a lot less money.
Let's go.
Finally Tony gets to my
house, about two hours late.
Now, this is when
the fight starts.
I'm driving out
of my neighborhood
When this black cat
darts across the street,
I mean right in front of us.
No way on God's green earth
could we have missed it.
Boom.
I mean, you could hear it
hit the bottom of the car.
And by now, I'm
wondering if I was
Ever meant to go on this trip.
So Tony pulls the car
over and we get out.
Oh, come on, man, they do not
want to hear the rest of this.
No, we want to hear.
Anyway, but anyway,
we're out of the car
And we're looking for this cat
everywhere, and can't find it.
All of a sudden, I hear
this, boom, boom, boom.
And I look around and there's
Tony kicking at the tire.
I said, what the hell
are you doing, man?
He said, I found it.
I caught it in the wheel well.
So by the time I get around
there, he's got it out.
And this cat's laying
there, all mangled and dead.
Is this a joke?
No, it's no joke.
I mean, look we got
out, and I didn't
Even want to touch the things.
Old Daniel Boone here, he has
to put it in the first year.
That's where we
should have left it.
But Mr. Humanitarian here, he
can't leave well enough alone.
Well, you can't just
leave somebody's dead cat,
I mean, mangled, lying
on their front lawn.
I mean, that's disgusting.
No, no, Your dinner
was disgusting.
So I picked up
this cat and we're
Going to take it to the house.
The weird thing was when
we get to the porch,
The front door flies
open and this half
Naked woman comes running out.
I mean, she's screaming,
she was barefoot
And bawling her eyes out.
Yeah I mean, this was
sad, it was really sad.
I mean, she grabs this
bloody pile out of my hands
And she starts hugging.
And I'm going, oh, great, what
are we supposed to do now?
I mean, this cat's
more important to her
Than her husband.
You know, but I said, look,
I explained to her, lady,
We didn't mean any harm
by running over your cat.
And besides, I thought I'd offer
her a couple of bucks for it.
I didn't even think
she'd take it.
But she says OK.
So what do you
think a cat's worth?
$5, $10?
She told us it's worth $2,000.
- Right.
- What?
That's what I said.
No way.
I don't have $2,000.
For a cat?
So listen, I offer her $100.
Yeah, then I offer her
$100 on top of that.
$200.
$200 for a cat?
You're kidding me.
Oh, but that's not all.
Finally, we get out of there.
And we're driving
away and we're driving
And this cop car
comes barrelling
Down the street, light
flashing, the siren's wailing.
And they pull into her driveway.
And I say, turn around,
let's go see what's going on.
So we turn around
and when get back,
The cops are with this lady,
handcuffing her and putting her
In their car.
So I get out of the car and
the cops walk right over to me
And he goes, this yours?
And he hands me the $200.
I go, yes, officer.
I go, what's going on?
What did she do?
And he looks me
right in the face.
I mean dead in the face,
like I did something wrong.
And he goes, listen, son,
everyone in this state
Knows it's illegal
to sell pussy.
[Laughing]
On you.
That's real funny.
That's really bad.
[Laughing]
Does rough flying bother you?
I'm OK.
Well, I'd say this is
the worst series of storms
We've had in the last
decade, but nothing
Like the ones in '66.
Do you know the
island very well?
Lady, I grew up here.
I know everything
about this place.
Is there anything strange,
like maybe some strange landmark
In a weird shape or anything?
The only time anyone ever pays
any attention to this island
Is during deer season, which
happens to start tomorrow.
Few drunk hunters, fooling
and shooting themselves.
Ah, nothing ever happens
out of the ordinary here.
You can't think of anything
or even anyone strange?
There is an old guy.
He don't bother nobody.
And nobody don't bother him.
Sandy.
You are the new guardian.
And my powers have
been passed on to you.
As a guardian, it was
my death that caused
The release of the Wendigo.
And it is your strength
that will defeat it.
Beware the Wendigo's
sentinels, warriors
That will try to destroy you.
You must find the circle and
complete it before the sun
Rises on two days.
During this time, the
Wendigo's strength will grow.
And you will become weak.
If the circle is not completed,
you and many others will die.
What was that?
Jesus!
Something's jumping on the tail.
The first sentinel.
What?
What the hell is
jumping on my plane?
You've got to get down!
I can't even see.
How in the hell can I land?
It's on the plane.
It's tearing up the plane.
You've got to land.
I told you I can't see
two feet in front of me.
How in the hell can I land?
It's still out there.
You've got to get
this plane down.
[Screaming]
[Snoring]
[Heavy breathing]
Hey, get up!
That thing out there.
It's coming!
What the hell are
you doing, man?
That damn Wendigo.
It's out there!
Wait, wait.
The Hoodigo is what?
No, the Wendigo.
It's big, man, real big.
What the hell's
going on in here?
This guy just broke in and he's
messing up all your furniture.
You guys got to listen.
I know I sound like
an old '50s B movie,
But there's a gigantic
blue monster out there
That's called the Wendigo.
And it's already
killed my buddy.
Yeah, right.
I got the munchies.
Anybody else hungry?
I am.
Me too.
What do you got?
What did you call that thing?
The Wendigo.
Me and my buddy, Dave,
accidentally shot this old man
And everything went nuts.
The old guy melted
down into a skeleton.
Then it came alive.
It grabbed Dave,
smashed me in the face.
I got up.
I got hit.
The Wendigo grabbed
Dave and ripped
His head clean off
and put it on a pole
Next to all these skeletons.
The only reason I got
away, is that thing
Was still busy eating Dave.
It was eating him raw.
[Snoring]
When did all this happen?
Oh, come on, Pete.
The guy is nuts.
I want some of my
bodacious chili.
Well, we can't do
anything until morning.
But I don't understand all this
business about the Wendigo.
Yeah, it's an old
Algonquin Indian legend.
In the middle of winter, when
the winter storms have killed
All the game, and there
was no food anywhere,
You know, the Indians would
come in the middle of the night.
And they'd get one of their
own people, and kill him.
Then they'd eat him.
I'm hungry.
It's just their
word for cannibalism.
There's no such
thing as a Wendigo.
I mean, the Indians would say,
in the middle of the night,
The Wendigo ate Geronimo.
It was just another
excuse for their hunger.
Tell that to Dave.
How do you know all this?
As my great grandmother
used to say, lift your feet,
The shit's getting thick.
And the chili's good and ready.
No, you guys don't understand.
We've got to round up everyone
that's left on this island
And get out of here!
Hot chili.
Listen, man, why don't
you get off of this?
Do you need a place
to stay until you
Come off your drunk, well
fine, you can stay with us.
As far as that monster
stuff, nobody here
Believes it, especially me.
I wouldn't say that.
Why?
Is it gonna get me?
Ah!
[Screaming]
I told you it was real.
I told you!
[Screaming]
Look out.
Put him out!
[Screaming]
Help me!
Put him over there, on the cot.
Be careful with him.
Oh my god, what
are we going to do?
I don't know.
We don't have many choices.
The hell we don't!
We gotta get out of here!
How?
The only way on
or off this island
Is Duke's Charter Service.
And we have no way of getting
a hold of him until the morning
When he flies in.
I guess we're stuck
here until then.
[Screaming]
I'm going to get
rid of this stuff.
Not that it matters.
That thing is
everywhere anyways.
Hey, Leo, Leo.
Where you going?
Hey!
Come back here.
You can't go out there.
We can't let him go
out in those woods.
Let him go.
What?
I said, let him go.
Peter's right.
Leo is a hothead, but,
I mean, after all,
The guy did just lose a hand.
Storm out there
will cool him off.
He'll be in soon enough.
OK, but it's all your
shoulders this time now.
I'm not going to take
the rap for this one too.
Listen, we don't have
time for Leo's crying.
If he wants to try and get
out of here tonight, let him.
Well, what's your plan?
Three of us will head
out in the morning
And meet Duke when he flies in.
The other two will stay here.
When you find Duke, get back
here, and we'll take Jerry out.
When I find Duke?
What do you mean
when I find Duke?
I'm not going to go out there.
Hey, don't worry.
I'll go along with you.
Oh, great.
That makes me feel real good.
Two stooges against King Kong.
I'm no stooge, pal,
I'll have you know.
I had an encounter
with a Big Foot once.
Come on.
No, really.
It was in a restroom
in the Smoky Mountains.
I think you're talking
about big ass, not foot.
Actually, his whole
body is quite large.
And the phrase
referring to his foot
Actually denotes a small
piece of his anatomy
Which selectively
refers to the...
Wait a minute,
Tony, I thought you
Didn't believe me in any of
that hokey pokey legend stuff.
Yeah, Tony.
I thought it was just an
old Algonquin Indian legend.
I was skeptical
myself, until I actually
Encountered the Big Foot.
Yeah.
I'll never forget the
relief of finally getting
To use a flush toilet and the
sheer terror of coming face
To face with the Sasquatch.
Oh, sure.
Big ass gotta poop too?
Hey, fellas, I don't think
Jerry's doing too well here.
He's breathing's real weird
like there isn't any sometimes.
[Scream from outside]
What was that?
[Door creaks open]
Be careful!
God.
Help me, Please.
Are you OK?
What happened?
What did you see?
Was it big?
What the hell's going on?
What happened to
Jerry over here?
Hold it, hold it!
Are you all right?
We were sleeping my
boyfriend woke up.
He thought he heard
something rummaging outside.
He went out to check.
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Then there were the footsteps
in the snow coming closer
And closer then they stopped.
Why don't you go lay down
on the cot for a minute
And take a rest.
Except the wind.
The wind seemed to whisper.
See, I told you, it whispers.
It said, Wendigo, Wendigo.
Great.
Lay down over here and
try and get some rest.
No.
Too hot.
Hot.
It's too hot.
Too hot.
Hot.
Hot Too hot.
[Growling]
Holy Toledo.
Open the door!
What the Sam Hill's
going on here?
Open the door!
[Screaming]
Come and get me, boys.
Get it out of here.
Who's first for
my tasty treats?
Grab her.
[Screaming]
Let's get it.
Get it off me.
Please get it off me.
Want to dance?
I don't know.
It's been awhile.
Grab her.
Throw the witch into the wall.
One, two, three.
Ah!
You're all gonna die, whether
you perish in this cabin
Or out in the freezing cold.
Shut up, bitch.
You may be friends
now, but you'll
Become cannibals and feast
on the flesh of the others.
Not even the chosen
one can save you.
[Unearthly scream]
[Explosion]
Leo, I don't know how
you dealt with being
Out alone last night because I
got a bad feeling about this.
Yeah, unless it's got US
grade A prime ribs stamped
On the side, and
done medium well,
You've got a bad
feeling about it.
Look, I just don't like
being out here, that's all.
I mean we don't know
where that thing is.
Yeah, well, it's my guess
that it's just as safe out here
As it is in that cabin.
That's right.
You're right.
It's everywhere.
And it's everything.
That's right.
He's right.
You're right.
What's the matter
with you, man?
Me?
Nothing.
We just can't let that
thing get the edge on us.
I think you've been taking
these painkillers too long.
Here, hold this.
Where'd you get these?
I'm a doctor.
No fooling.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, we're never going to get
out of here now, never, never.
Hey, look over there.
Duke's still alive.
These tracks are fresh.
Come on.
Let's go get Duke.
Wait.
Look, there might be a radio
in that plane that still works.
It's worth a look.
Go check.
Leo and I will go and
see if we can spot Duke.
OK, but now don't go too fast.
I'll catch up with you.
RADIO: This is the
Leelanau air tower
To Duke's charter flight 401.
Over.
Again, this is
Leelanau air tower
To Duke's charter flight 401.
Do you copy?
Come to Poppa, baby.
Come to Poppa, radio.
It works.
Please report back, flight 401.
Come on.
What are you doing?
This way.
[Radio crackle]
Please respond.
Over.
[Radio crackle]
No.
Oh my god.
God, get away.
Leave me alone.
Yo, doc.
What am I going to do when I
run out of these painkillers?
It's not the painkillers
I'm worried about.
It's the whiskey.
Wonder where Tony is?
Hey!
Come on, it's Duke!
Holy smokes, it's a dame.
What do you mean, dame?
That's a woman.
That's what I said.
Now, come on and help
me get her outta here.
Come on.
Set those down.
Say what?
What are you going to carry?
You gotta take the girl.
I gotta go look for Tony.
He should have been back by now.
Come on!
Wait a minute.
Come on.
First it's the Hoodigo Wendigo,
then it's the possessed chili
Eats off my hand.
Now this hypothermic teenager,
what should I expect next?
What the Sam Hill you
yelling for George?
George.
[Static crackle]
BDFD TV three.
You're on the air, Jerry.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Jerry Harrison here
in our BDFD news room.
We have received word
that contact has been lost
With Duke's charter flight 401.
The plane was piloted by Duke
Davis, owner and operator
Of the charter service.
Some of you may remember
Duke from the winter of 1966,
When he single-handedly
saved a group of hunters
From Manitou Island during
the severe blizzards
Of that same year.
We will now switch
over live to Harve
Lindquist, who is reporting to
us from the Leelanau air tower.
Harve.
Yes, thank you, Jerry.
This is Harve Lindquist live
at the Leelanau air tower.
And with us is Mr. Matt
Hell... oh, excuse me.
Mr. Hell is the air traffic
controller here at the tower.
And I understand, Mr.
Hell, that you were
In contact with Duke Davis.
Yes, I was in contact
with Duke on his flight
Over to the island.
And I've continually tried...
Yes, bring it right in here,
Pal.
Nice job.
Hey, easy on the touch
down, there, guy.
Easy.
Sorry about that.
That's quite all right.
You were saying.
As I was saying, we've
had no contact with flight
401 today whatsoever.
But you will indeed, continue
to try and make contact?
Sure, all day.
In fact we've been in touch
with people in Bedford Falls who
Are indeed, putting together
a search team to see
If they can indeed find Duke.
See if he's gone down.
And what about passengers?
No, unfortunately Duke wasn't
very good with passenger
Flight records and things.
I see.
Well that seems to be the story
here at Leelanau air tower.
So for BDFD TV 3, Action
News, this is Have Lindquist.
Back to you, Jerry.
Thank you, Harve.
Terrible situation.
We hear at BDFD will
keep you up to date
With any further developments
in this possible tragedy.
He's dead.
Hey, Peter, He's dead.
What?
What happened?
I was just watching him and
he just stopped breathing.
I mean, what are we going
to do with him, Pete?
I don't know.
I wish those guys were
back with some answers.
We aren't going to
bury him, are we?
I mean, I can't
bury my best friend.
He was my friend too.
We can't just leave him here.
He'll start to smell.
Maybe we could put him in
a box and set it outside.
Cold air will freeze him
until we get back to town.
Hey, no way, man.
There's no way I'm putting my
best friend in some pine box.
Well, what do you want to do?
Let him sit here and
lose all his body
Fluids all over the floor and
stink up the entire cabin?
Making us all sick
until we're outta here?
Well I don't.
But you do what you want to do.
[Crying sounds]
Come on.
Let's nail this thing shut.
We got to get it out of here.
It gives me the creeps.
[Music playing]
I can't do this.
I know I gotta but I just can't.
Nick, it's OK.
Nick.
I know you guys were close.
Listen, I'll finish up.
Why don't you go outside
and get some fresh air.
[Music playing]
[Growling]
You let a dead man die?
What do you mean,
the plane's crashed?
It's simple.
The plane crashed.
Well, where's Tony and Gary?
Tony went to look
for the plane's radio.
When he didn't come back,
Gary went to look for Tony.
We gotta get out of here.
What are you going to do?
Walk across the ice?
Somebody's going to have to.
Are you crazy, man?
That's at least
a couple of miles.
Peter.
You all right, man?
Who is this?
Look out.
[Yelling and screaming]
Help me!
[Gun shot]
What's going on?
Look at my chili.
God, there's another one!
By your feet.
There's another one!
[Monster squealing]
Get up!
[MONSTER SQUEAKING AND
SQUEALING]
Get it!
Get it now!
Shoot it, man!
Get him!
[Gun shot]
Holy shit!
Come on, guys.
We gotta figure out
what's going on.
What do you mean, Pete?
It was her those
things are after.
She's probably the
one with the answers.
Well, we can play
20 questions later.
Right now we got
important stuff to do.
You're not going
across the ice?
Well how do you propose
we get off the island?
Wait until the spring
thaw, and swim?
Send her across the ice.
And let her take those damn
little monster with her.
She's the one that brought them.
Listen, we got...
He's right.
They are after me.
There will be a whole world full
of demons if they can stop me.
Two worlds have opened
into one another.
And I've got to stop the
Wendigo before it can stop me.
Oh, not the Hoodigo again.
Somewhere on the
island is the gate
That connects the two worlds.
The gate has been
opened and I've
Got to find it and close it.
She's serious.
Dead serious.
I need your help.
You guys know the
island better than I do.
Well, maybe you two
guys can help her.
But right now I gotta get
going before it gets too dark.
No.
Please don't.
It's no use.
Help me get this thing.
Help me find the circle.
I'm sorry.
But I can't count on
what you're saying.
It just doesn't make sense.
Nothing makes sense.
I've gotta go with
the only logical means
That I can think of
getting off this island
And that's getting
across that lake.
And getting some help.
He's right.
He's wrong.
You don't stand a chance.
Well, its the only
chance I've got.
No, it's not.
Sorry.
I can't believe it.
Tony's dead.
And better yet, somebody
on this island killed him.
Choked him to death.
If I catch that
deranged lunatic that
Did this, as if it's not bad
enough around here, all ready.
Hey!
Hey, you.
Hello, friend.
Look, pal, don't friend me.
What do you know about that
plane crash over there?
And what do you know about
that guy next to the plane
With a major ring
around his collar?
I don't know about
no plane crash
And I don't know about the
guy with the dirty shirt.
Wise guy, hey?
I bet you're the
one that axed him.
I ought to finish
you right here.
Wait a minute.
Axed him?
I don't what you're
talking about.
I get it.
Playing innocent, huh?
Let me see your hands.
Come on, let me see your hands.
OK.
They're pretty clean, but
that don't mean nothing.
You're coming with me.
Come on, pal.
You look too suspicious.
Look here, pal, I'm getting
a little bit suspicious of you
Too, and I'm tired
of this, all right?
Me?
No look, I haven't
done anything.
I mean, sure I
offed the old guy.
But it was an
accident, an accident.
Ain't you ever done
anything by mistake?
Anyways, how am I supposed
to know the old coot's
A keeper for some
giant dog from hell?
How am I supposed to know?
You know what I mean?
Sure, monsters in
the chili, people
Catching on fire, some God damn
giant monster in the woods.
Sure, blame me. That's it.
Blame me.
See, I'm a scapegoat.
I'm nothing but a scapegoat.
And now...
[Crack]
Snap out of it, man.
What's the matter with you?
What are you talking about?
Monsters in the chili,
people catching on fire,
Monsters in the woods.
You ought to see a doctor.
I am a doctor.
Listen to me.
You better take my advice
and get out of here.
Before it's too late.
[]whistling]
[Crack]
[Whistling]
[Growling]
[Screaming]
Please, God.
Let me live again.
[Static]
BDFD TV 3.
Good evening, ladies
and gentlemen.
We here at BDFD
TV 3 have received
More information on the
situation in Manitou Island.
Rescue efforts
have been thwarted
By a mysterious blizzard,
which seems too have
Centered over the island..
Local meteorologists cannot
explain this rare phenomena.
Our roaming reporter,
Harve Lindquist
Is at this moment in
downtown Bedford Falls,
And comes to us now
with this live report.
Harve, are you there?
BDFD TV.
Yes, Jerry, I am.
Thank you.
Standing outside
of Sites's Tavern
In downtown Bedford
Falls, which is
Located on the western
shoreline of our state.
And standing with me is
Jake Davis, the son of Mr.
Duke Davis, the missing pilot.
Jake, still no radio
contact with your father,
Are you at all concerned
for his well-being.
Nah, does some weird things,
but probably just lost
His head.
I see.
Well, I understand your father's
a very well-liked and respected
Man in the community.
But the police still
haven't ruled out foul play.
Is there anyone you can
think of who would have
Wished harm on your father?
He don't bother nobody and
nobody don't bother him.
That's right.
He's right.
Sir, you are?
Zeke Thatcher.
Tell me, Mr.
Thatcher, I understand
That the Manitou Island is
visible from the shoreline
Ordinarily.
Have you seen anything unusual,
anything out the ordinary
On the island recently?
Well, the other night,
saw a bird big as a truck.
Ah, have another beer, Zeke.
Ah, come on.
No, you can't even see
the island from the shore.
Ma'am, ma'am, could
you step up please?
Ma'am, what is your name?
My name is Kay Dunnit.
My husband, Ray
Dunnit, he works over
At the fire station over there.
Uh, well, he was part
of the rescue team
That went to the island.
But they can't even see the
island from the shore anymore.
Harve, can you
get any information
On the rescue mission?
About this rescue mission,
I understand it was canceled
Due to the inclement weather.
Is there anything you
can tell me about that?
Yeah, well Ray and the others,
they started to walk on the ice
Over to the island,
but the storm got
Really bad about halfway there.
So they had to turn
around and come back.
Oh, you know, they
did tell me something
That was really strange.
They heard thunder over
the island in the blizzard.
Thunder in a
blizzard, a snowstorm.
I though that was kinda...
Thunder in a snowstorm.
Yeah, yeah, you know
something really weird
Going on over at that island.
Well, folks, there you have it.
Panic is beginning to spread in
the tiny town of Bedford Falls.
And I guess all we can
do is pray for the safety
Of Duke Davis and the hunters
trapped on Manitou island.
So live outside
of Sites's Tavern,
I'm Harve Lindquist for
BDFD TV 3 Action News.
Back to you, Jerry.
Thank you, Harve.
We will continue to
keep you informed
Of the situation
on Manitou Island
As the information comes to us.
Jerry Harris, BDFD TV 3.
It's nearly dark.
We've got to get out
and find the circle.
What are you talking about?
None of us are going
out there tonight.
Not until someone comes
back with some answers.
Gary and Tony aren't
even back yet.
They've been gone all day.
The longer it has, the
more powerful it gets.
If you're so important, why
don't you just go by yourself?
You don't need us.
I can't do this alone.
Well, you're just going to
have to wait until morning.
We're not going anywhere.
I think Leo's right.
We have to wait.
The only thing you'll be
waiting for is your own death.
That's him.
Who?
It's either Gary or Tony.
Three shots in a row
is the distress signal.
You going out there?
We've got to.
I'm coming along.
No, you're not.
You wait here in
case they come back.
We'll be gone half an hour.
And if we're not back,
you can write us off.
Then you're on your own.
Just grab what you like.
When we get back, we'll
help you all right.
Just a half an hour, man.
I don't want to be out there in
the dark with all those things.
Half an hour.
Gary!
Tony!
Shut up.
You want the pigs to hear us?
You gotta be quiet, man.
The pigs are every place.
This is definitely
not what I planned when
I told Tony I'd come hunting.
I swear.
You don't have to
worry about it anyway.
Because out here, we're
the ones being hunted.
[Crying]
Hey, Leo.
Over here.
What's it going to do?
Escape?
Sandy!
Mother?
He sent you.
The Guardian sent you.
Shh.
I'm here now.
That's all that matters.
Let's go inside.
I need to talk to you.
I'm here to help you.
Hey, buddy, you all right?
Say, mister.
Hey, buddy.
You all right?
Hey, fella.
Say something.
[Retching]
Oh, my god.
They tore him in half.
And they ate the
skin off his face.
They're cannibals.
They ate the skin off his face.
It's not Gary.
It's not him.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Wait, wait.
I gotta stop.
Come on, man.
We got to make it back
before she locks us out
Here all night.
Come on, Nick.
You are the Chosen One.
It can't be me.
I'm not strong enough, Mother.
But dear, you do
have much strength.
No, I don't.
Some of which
you've shown already.
I don't even understand it.
How can I stop it?
Shh.
It's OK.
No.
(MONSTER VOICE) It's OK.
(HIGH MONSTER VOICE) It's OK.
[Crying]
It's OK.
[Roaring]
No!
Mother!
(SCREAMING)No!
No!
[Roaring]
Love you too, daughter.
I'm not your daughter!
We will defeat you.
[Gun shot] I'm melting!
I'm melting.
[Wolf howl]
Listen, listen.
The thing doesn't howl, does it?
I don't know.
The Hoodigo Wendigo gets
nothing out from me.
Come on, Nick.
Nick, come on.
Come on.
[Screaming]
What happened out there?
I went back to the crash.
Tony was dead.
Somebody had crushed his neck.
Where you going?
I've gotta find the circle.
What?
The only way to
stop the Wendigo
Is to close the sacred circle.
I know what it is
and where it is too.
So you mean you're the one
those things are after.
You gotta take me there.
And we gotta go now.
It's all making sense.
You're the one.
[Crash]
Where's the circle?
On the other side
of the island.
[Growling]
It's a couple miles.
It's a circle.
Let's go.
[Growling]
Gary, Wake up.
What is it?
What kind of circle?
It's a circle of skulls.
But I broke it.
[Crash]
[Growling]
[Gun shot]
Sandy!
What are you doing?
Falling.
Gary, help me!
[Screaming]
Help me!
Help!
[Screaming]
Put me down!
I can't get warm.
You've lost control of
your body temperature.
It's way below normal.
Don't exert any energy.
It only makes it
harder to bring up.
You're suffering
from hypothermia.
I'm cold.
Relax
No.
Slow your breathing.
Shh.
No.
Warm up.
Please.
[Gasping]
[Screaming]
No!
Sandy.
It broke my arms.
[Screaming]
My arms of ice.
Now look.
Look into my eyes.
[Screaming]
Eyes of the Wendigo.
[Gun shot]
[Growling]
[Screaming]
You OK?
We've got to leave.
Every minute we wait,
the Wendigo grows.
We've got to hurry.
We might be too late already.
What the hell is
going on out there?
Those are my friends.
They're not anymore.
They're just as much the
Wendigo as the Wendigo itself.
It controls their bodies.
They crave human flesh.
They're cannibals.
[Crash]
Gary!
Burn!
Let's go.
You gotta help me.
I tried to get away.
It didn't help.
No, not away.
To the other side
of the island.
We've got to find
the circle of skulls.
And I'm afraid we have
to do it before morning.
Before morning?
It's almost morning now.
I can feel the
Wendigo's power growing.
By morning, he'll be free of the
circle, free to move and grow.
Well, what's that
supposed to mean?
Armageddon.
Wendigo will start small.
Then death will rise.
Then demons will emerge from
the bowels of the earth.
Don't shoot us, Peter.
We can't help what happened.
We can't help what we crave.
We're victims.
Just like you.
Don't shoot me.
Don't shoot.
We're your friends.
We're your God damn friends.
[Gun shot]
Let's go.
[Thundering]
[Hissing]
[Explosion]
What is it?
It happened.
The gate has been opened.
The Wendigo is at full strength.
I seem to be losing mine.
That's it.
That's the circle.
There's the break.
There's got to be
another source somewhere.
I've got to find it.
Where?
In there.
[Growling]
[Roaring]
We can't go in there.
What about that thing?
[Roaring]
He can't touch me.
No!
Sandy!
Don't go in there!
Come back!
Don't!
[Explosion]
[Growling]
Hey, you ugly son of a bitch!
Over here!
Whoa!
[Static crackling]
[Roaring]
She defeated you.
No.
[Screaming]
OTHER WORLDLY VOICE: No,
She has defeated you.
The gate to your
world is closing.
Go with it.
The battle is over.
Then you will die.
Sandy.
You must join me.
I cannot stop it.
Stand up.
Sandy.
You have the power.
Join me.
We must stop the Wendigo.
[Static crackling]
[Explosion]
Don't be afraid.
Never be afraid.
You have defeated the evil and
you are free to go for now.
But remember, the Wendigo's
spirit only rests.
And there may come a day when
you area called upon again.
[Roaring]
[Music playing]