Welcome to the strange and
wonderful world of illusions.
Baa. Baa. Baa.
Illusions to deceive your eyes.
So I do take cheques.
Trick your tongue.
And fool your sense of touch.
Oh!
But don't worry, it's all in the
name of a noble scientific quest.
These illusions hold the key
to how our senses work.
When you open your eyes
in the morning,
most people think,
"I'm seeing the world as it is".
The beautiful thing about illusions
is they tell us that that's not true.
They show us that our perceptions
of the world are something different
from seeing it as it really is.
Illusions are providing a
unique window into the
inner workings of our minds.
Helping to reveal what our sensory
brains are really capable of.
So this is a golden age
in perceptual psychology.
The things we've learned over
the last ten years have been
absolutely phenomenal.
These new discoveries are opening
up a whole new world of possibility.
Even enabling us to move beyond
our sensory evolution altogether.
So watch, play along,
and prepare to be amazed at
what your senses can do.
Can you trust
anything you see with your eyes?
Do you think seeing is
really believing?
The beautiful thing about illusions
is that they make us realise
things are not
always quite as they seem.
So the question for you is,
you see the surface here
and the surface there?
Right? Do they look
the same in terms of their colour.
That's what you see,
they look different.
What if I told you that they're
actually the same.
Will you put money on it?
Would you bet your life on it?
You wouldn't be standing here,
would you?!
Do they look the same now?
That's mad, ain't it? It looks it.
Are they the same physically?
To our amazement and delight,
illusions are so powerful
that even when we know how
they work we can still be fooled.
But for scientists like
Dr Beau Lotto, they are far
more than fun and games.
Now, how many people see
four blue tiles on the left?
Yes? I see four blue.
How many people see
seven yellow tiles on the right?
I see seven yellow.
What if I told you they're all grey?
So if I take, for instance,
this tile, what colour is it now?
Grey.
If I move it over here,
what colour is it now?
Yellowish grey.
So those tiles
are all physically the same.
Illusions are crucial tools that
reveal how the world out there
can be very different
to the one in our heads.
And it's this gap between reality
and what we perceive that holds
the key to how our senses work.
So if you're unsure if seeing
is really believing,
you're not the only one.
Is seeing believing?
What do you mean by that?
No.
Yes.
I think it depends who you ask.
Seeing is literally believing.
We see what we believe.
So, yes.
So it's this question of whether
seeing really is believing that's
helping scientists to open up the
fascinating world inside our heads.
And one of the places they are
turning to for inspiration
is an ancient and untapped source.
Magic Singh is a master of illusion.
His livelihood depends
on his ability to confuse,
trick and deceive.
It's something magicians like him
have been doing for millennia.
But now scientists
want in on the act.
Magicians have developed
really powerful ways of
manipulating what we see.
And many of these techniques
have been tried and tested
in front of live audiences.
So by doing so, magicians have
sort of developed
a very solid understanding
of how we see the world.
Psychologist Gustav Kuhn is well
versed in the language of illusion.
In a former life,
he was a professional magician.
Today he's swapped the
magic circuit for the science lab,
but he's convinced
there are some important lessons
to be learnt from plundering
the magician's book of tricks.
So actually take the card out.
We're really interested
in the magic tricks per se,
but what we focus on is
the techniques that magicians
use to manipulate your perception.
OK, I'm not going to put the
eye-tracker on you, so if you could
just wear these glasses.
In order to find out how
these illusions work,
Gustav Kuhn has developed
an eye-tracking experiment
to enable him to find out
what's happening
when we watch certain tricks.
Now in the vanishing ball illusion,
the magician tosses the ball up
a couple of times and then on the
final throw, he just pretends to
toss the ball up in the air.
Yet most people actually
experience an imaginary ball
leave the hand and then sort of
disappear somewhere up there.
But when Gustav analysed his data,
he discovered the eyes
and the brain
told a very different story.
Now, the eye-tracking data
showed us that whilst most people
were fooled by the illusion,
the eyes weren't tricked.
So the eyes, rather than actually
looking at the imaginary ball,
just stayed on the face.
And what this showed us is that
the illusion really happened
in people's minds.
What this trick really demonstrates
is that, rather than
seeing what's physically present,
the way we see the world is
based on our prediction of the world.
So we see things that we expect to
see, so in this case,
we expect the ball to
leave the hand, and that's why
we actually see the ball,
even though physically
it's not actually present.
When it comes to what we see,
the brain often overrules the eyes,
even constructing events that
may not have actually happened.
It's an important insight into how
our visual system operates
in the real world.
In the real world things happen
incredibly quickly and we have to
respond at great speed and accuracy
to visual information.
This information processing may take
up to 150 milliseconds,
and that kind of delay would just
be far too great for us to miss,
for example,
catching a ball or so.
So rather than just relying
on this information,
what the visual system does,
is it predicts what's
going to be happening in the future.
So in many ways, what we see
is what's going to happen in the
future rather than in the present.
So seeing may not
always be believing.
But is our sense of
hearing any more reliable?
At any one moment, we are being
bombarded by sensory information.
Our brains do a remarkable
job of making sense of it all.
It seems easy enough to
separate the sounds we hear
from the sights we see.
But there is one illusion that
reveals this isn't always the case.
Baa, baa, baa.
Have a look at this.
What do you hear?
Baa, baa, baa.
But look what happens
when we change the picture.
Faa, faa, faa.
Faa, faa...
And yet the sound hasn't changed.
In every clip, you are
only ever hearing "Baa", with a B.
Baa, baa, baa.
Baa...
It's an illusion known
as the McGurk effect.
Take another look.
Baa, baa... Concentrate first
on the right of the screen.
Now to the left of the screen.
Baa, baa... The illusions occurs
because what you are seeing clashes
with what you are hearing.
In the illusion,
what we see overrides what we hear,
so the mouth movements we see
as we look at a face
can actually influence
what we believe we're hearing.
If we close our eyes,
we actually hear the sound as it is.
If we open our eyes, we actually see
how the mouth movements can
influence what we're hearing.
Baa, baa, baa.
It's a bizarre effect.
Remember, the only sound
you're hearing is "Baa", with a B.
Faa, faa, faa.
Baa, baa, baa.
What's remarkable about
this illusions is
even knowing how it's done doesn't
seem to make a difference.
The effect works no matter how
much you know about the effect.
I've been studying the
McGurk effect for 25 years,
and I've been the face
in the stimuli,
I've seen stimuli thousands
and thousands of times,
but the effect still works on me.
I can't help it, the speech brain
takes in that information
and doesn't care about what outside
knowledge you bring to bear.
Baa, baa, baa.
The McGurk effect shows us
that what we hear
may not always be the truth.
It also helps us to understand what
happens when our senses conflict.
Baa, baa, baa.
When the brain
has the conflicting information,
it tries to make sense
of that conflict,
and depending on what type of
modality is providing more, I guess,
salient information,
that information
might override or at least combine
with the other information.
So we can't always trust what
we hear because sometimes
our sense of vision takes over,
enabling us to maintain
a coherent view of the world.
But why do illusions
have such power?
Scientist are finding answers
in the most surprising of places.
For bees, colour
is a matter of life and death.
They need to
distinguish between colours
to find the source of their food.
And the way bees learn this
important lesson can offer us
insights into how we perceive.
One of the great things about
studying bees is that bees see
colour much the way that we see it.
They see the same illusions
that we see, yet they do it with
only a million brain cells.
Which means that we can actually
study how bumble bees see
and in doing so
we can understand how we see.
Dr Beau Lotto has devised a unique
experiment known as the bee matrix,
where he uses 64 coloured lights
to represent flowers.
The aim of the game
is to find the sugar reward.
We are training the bees
to go to blue flowers,
as opposed to purple flowers,
and the way we do that is we reward
only the blue flowers,
reward being sugar water,
and we don't put any reward
into the purple flowers.
So if they land on a blue flower,
they get a reward.
And then they associate
that with the colour.
In the top part of the array we have
blue flowers surrounded by white
flowers, in the bottom part of
the array we have purple flowers
also surrounded by white flowers.
Only the blue flowers
have a sugar reward.
At first, the bees quickly find
their reward by learning the
difference between the colours.
But then things
are made more difficult.
Using filters, Beau changes the
colours, so now the blue and purple
flowers look exactly the same.
But remarkably, the bees still
fly straight to to the reward.
So as far as the bee's
eye is concerned,
those are exactly the same.
If the bees only remembered
the colour of the stimulus,
they should go to both,
because they're physically the same.
If, however, they've remembered
the blue flowers in a context
and used that context, they
should now go only go to the top.
What we've shown is that that's
exactly what happens, which means
they are using the context.
They have remembered and learned
the relationships between
the colours to solve the puzzle.
So, to solve the puzzle,
the bees don't just look at
the colours in the middle
they also look at
the colours that surround them.
And it's by comparing the central
colours to those on the outside
that they are able to detect
the true colour.
It shows that, for bees, colour
isn't just seen in isolation,
it's entirely dependent
on the environment in which
it's perceived.
And what applies to bees
also applies to us,
every day of our lives.
Here we have two cubes,
except in this case
it looks as if the cube on the left
is under yellow light,
and the cube on the right
is under blue light.
On the left we have four
blue tiles, and on the right
we have seven yellow tiles.
What's amazing about this illusion
is that the blue tiles on the left
are exactly the same, physically,
as the yellow tiles on the right.
They're all in fact grey.
So in this instance
the brain has created colours
that simply aren't there.
When the other colours are stripped
away, we can see the blue and
yellow tiles are just grey.
Put the scene back, and the colours
change back to yellow and blue.
It shows that, in spite of our
strongest instincts, colour
is a purely subjective experience,
governed by the context
in which we see it.
Redness is not a
product of the world.
It doesn't exist unless
we're there to make it.
Blueness is not a part of the world,
wavelengths are not colour.
All they are is little packets
of energy called photons,
they are not colour.
We take that and we make
perceptions of them, and those
perceptions guide our behaviour.
Illusions fool us
because, try as we might,
we cannot overcome our experience
of how we think the world works.
It's these experiences we
store in our heads that really
determines what we see.
What's amazing is that that
information, coming from the eyes
through the thalamus
to the back part of the brain,
actually only makes up 10% of the
overall information we use to see.
The rest of the information comes
from other parts of the brain.
Only 10% of the information we
use to see comes from the eyes.
But are these experiences
only built up in the course
of our own lives,
or are some illusions so powerful
their roots lie
far in our distant past?
Janine Spencer and husband Justin
O'Brien are hoping to find out
if seeing certain illusions is
learnt in the course of our lives
or hard-wired from birth.
It requires several babies,
and a great deal of patience.
Anybody who studies with babies
will know they're
notoriously difficult,
not because they're hard
in themselves, they're lovely,
I love having babies in the lab,
but we can't ask them anything.
There is a number of reasons
why it takes such a
long time to get baby data,
pretty normal reasons.
They cry, they get hungry, they
don't like what they're looking at,
they want to move, they don't
want to sit in their car seat,
so there are a number of reasons
and because of that,
we have to test lots of
babies to get enough data.
BABIES CRY
In order to find out they are using
a famous piece of visual trickery
called the hollow mask illusion.
One side of the mask is hollow,
but it doesn't necessarily
look that way.
Even when we know it's an illusion,
we see it as the convex face.
Even when we know it's hollow
our visual system sees it,
we interpret it, as being convex.
Essentially, our knowledge
of faces is overriding what our
visual system can see,
so our depth perception
can see that it's hollow,
but our visual system is
overriding that and saying, "no".
Not in those words,
it's unconscious
of course, but that's a face,
so it must be sticking out.
They've been testing the hollow
mask illusion on babies at
just four and a half months of age.
I think it's important to study
babies to look at visual illusions
and any phenomenon where you want
to find out if it's innate or not,
because they don't
have that kind of experience
we would get as adults.
The younger you can test them,
the better it is.
It's known babies
are good at recognising
faces, but the question is,
do they still see a face
when they look at the hollow side
of the mask?
By carefully monitoring their eye
movements, it's possible to detect
if the babies see the illusion
by the way the mask
captures their attention.
We measure the amount of interest
the baby has in the experiment
by looking at their eyes.
We monitor their eye movements
and we time how long they look,
and when we get to a certain level
where they're not looking
very much at all,
we know they're
bored of the experiment.
It's still early days,
but 50 babies later
a pattern is beginning to emerge.
From the data we have so far,
it would suggest that
babies can see the illusion,
giving an indication that face
perception is an innate ability.
If this pattern continues,
it will be the first significant
evidence to suggest that seeing
certain illusions is so powerful
it's an ability we've
inherited from our parents.
What's exciting for us about the
results we're finding at the moment
is that it doesn't just tell us
about the way babies see, it tells
us about our evolutionary past.
The experience of our ancestors
of seeing faces and them
being so necessary for survival
is now written into our DNA,
so when a baby's born,
the first thing they'll look at
and show interest in is a face.
The hollow mask illusion helps
explain why seeing illusions may
have come about in the first place.
We've learnt to see what best
aids our chances of survival.
In our evolutionary past,
it's important to see faces
because they could be our enemy.
It's also not just human faces,
it's animal faces as well,
so we're very good
at seeing animal faces.
So something staring at you
through the trees could be a tiger,
so it's important you interpret
something as being a face.
If it turns out to be a pattern
of leaves in the sunlight,
you haven't lost anything.
If you ignore it and it really
was a face, then you're in trouble.
For Janine and Justin,
over five years of infinite
patience is finally paying off.
Yes, very pleased, we need more
babies but we're very pleased
with the results we have so far.
It's only taken five and a half
years but we're nearly there.
Illusions show us that we
literally see the world through
the lens of the past,
learning to see in
the way that's most useful to us.
It's an ability that's so important
it's been handed down through the
generations for thousands of years.
So if you thought being tricked
by illusions was a weakness,
then think again.
They may seem to be just a
bit of fun, but it turns out
they may be the key to our success.
So what if I told you
they're exactly the same?
Oh, my God.
So, I do take cheques.
You just lost so much money!
Many people think that illusions
in fact demonstrate the fragility
of the human senses, which is
in fact completely rubbish.
Illusions don't tell us
that our senses are fragile.
If they were, we wouldn't be here.
Illusions tell us that actually,
our brains are incredibly
capable of constructing meaning
from the meaningless.
We're really good at doing that.
If we were to
process all of the information
that we feel that we're aware of,
we would have to grow huge brains
and have massive heads that our
bodies would just fail to support.
Rather than using this approach,
we've evolved to, I think,
a very clever attentional system
that only processes the information
that is actually needed.
So, far from being a disadvantage,
illusions are a necessary
and powerful shortcut
that lie at the heart of our most
sophisticated human abilities.
And yet the insights we can get
from illusions don't end there.
Scientists are now realising that
illusions get even more fascinating
when the senses start
to work together.
One of the things most of us
can hold on to is that our
five senses work separately.
We see with our eyes,
hear with our ears,
taste with our tongue
and touch with our skin.
But scientists have been studying
a group of people
for whom this just isn't the case.
So when I hear the sea,
the big clunkiness,
as it were of the wave,
has a kind of dark, dark blue.
And the pebbley bit has
kind of oranges and yellows
and little bits of white.
I heard the wind earlier and
it had these kind of long shapes,
a bit like,
you know, mackerel fillets.
You know those shapes, but a bit...
The little thin ones.
Like that, but blue, and
quite a lot of them going across.
I have synaesthesia,
which means when
I experience taste, smell, sound,
I get visual images.
Shape, colour and texture
to accompany the sense.
Synaesthesia is a
mixing of the senses.
A sensory experience in one sense
can trigger an entirely
different reaction in another.
Whenever Philippa hears,
smells, or tastes something,
she also sees colours and shapes.
If I was to have fish and chips,
the fish -
the crispiness, that's angular
and then the actually taste
of the fish is kind of
speckeldy brown.
Nice brown, but yeah,
kind of coffee-coloured brown.
While this experience
isn't always pleasurable,
it's helped drive
Philippa's artistic creativity.
This is a painting of
the taste of English mustard.
It has such a distinctive
colour as it is as a product,
it's bright yellow,
but when you taste it, to me,
it has this massive red hit,
which then just
disappears into something else
that ends up, by the time
the kind of fumes of it
are going up through your nose,
it's actually quite...pretty.
So it starts off as a big,
massive red hit of taste, which then
disperses into something else.
For years, synaesthesia
wasn't taken seriously...
but now scientists are
realising that people like Philippa
provide important clues
as to the way all our senses work.
We're going to present you with
letters and numbers.
They're, um, going to be
coloured either red or green.
Dr Noam Sagiv has spent his
career studying synaesthetes
in an attempt to understand
how their brains are connected.
So scientists have suspected
for a long time that what causes
synaesthesia is extra connections
between different parts of the
brain, particularly between the
sensory areas that are involved.
For example, if someone has
auditory-visual synaesthesia,
we expect that the auditory part
of the brain and the visual part
of the brain would be cross-wired.
And this understanding of how
their brains are wired has led to
an exciting new idea about the way
all our senses develop from birth.
OK?
That's it. I got one wrong.
What we do know is that the brains
of newborns are actually a lot more
connected than the brains of adults.
We start our lives with a
lot of connections in our brains
and we lose some of them.
One of the ideas that
is trying explain the difference
between synaesthetes'
and non-synaesthetes' development
is that essentially,
synaesthetes were able to keep
a little bit more of those
many connections that we
all started our lives with.
So this condition might have been
something we've all had at one
time in our lives, but since lost.
But the similarities between
synaesthetes and the rest of us
may not end there.
Scientists are now beginning
to suspect that even as adults,
we may have far more in common
with synaesthetes than we realise.
I can't imagine what it
would be like to be alive
without it...
because it
doesn't impose itself,
it's just part of my being.
So I...
kind of don't believe that
people don't have it.
I think they're just
not looking hard enough.
And this question of the
way our senses are connected
is being answered with the help
of another set of bizarre illusions.
Neuroscientist Charles Spence has
recruited some willing volunteers
for an unusual multi-sensory feast.
He's taken his science out of the
lab and is going to attempt to trick
a group of trainee chefs,
who rely on their senses
more than most of us.
OK. You've got four coloured drinks
in front of you and what I want
you to do is to taste each one
and try and figure out
what the flavour is.
The colours and flavours of
the drinks have been mismatched,
resulting
in a certain degree of confusion.
Just looking at some of the
expressions on their faces, you
can see confusion and puzzlement.
One of the people thinks that
the yellow drink is apple.
It was actually strawberry.
And the red one, they smell like
berries, but in fact was lemon.
I think the green one tasted
more of lime.
Like lime cordial or something
like that, rather than mint.
OK. Excellent.
Green lime, so it's completely
lost the peppermint flavour
and it's being completely driven by
the eyes. The light green actually
reminded me of green washing-up
liquid rather than mint.
Lady's convinced it's
washing-up liquid smell.
And that expectation and knowledge
that comes
from names, from labels, from
colours, from textures,
from ways of presentation,
our brains use that all the time
to tell us what the flavour is.
People will talk about you eat
with your eyes, which is probably
much more true than we realise.
So it's impossible to separate
what we see from what we taste.
But what may be even more surprising
is that when it comes
to what you eat,
your ears may be just as important.
CRUNCHING
This time the chefs
are eating crisps,
but they are also hearing the sound
of their own crunch via headphones.
But what they don't realise is the
noises they hear have been changed.
When they hear low frequencies, they
are tricked into thinking the crisps
are significantly less crunchy than
when they hear higher frequencies.
When anyone thinks about
flavour, the first sense they
think about is taste.
To think about it a bit more,
some people say, "Well I
suppose smell's involved, too."
Then they start, possibly if pushed
they'll say, "Well maybe colour's
got something to do with it."
And finally a bit of texture.
Is it soft and slimy
or crispy or crunchy?
But virtually no-one
ever thinks about sound.
The results show hearing can have
a significant effect on taste.
Just playing higher frequencies
makes people believe crisps
to be over 15% crispier.
But all this culinary trickery
has even more insights to offer.
The reason these tricks work
is because it's impossible to
separate one sense from another.
It's experiments like these
that have enabled scientists
to piece together a revolutionary
new understanding of the brain.
The traditional view was that
you had five senses on the outside,
and the eyes are connected to one bit
of the brain, your ears are connected
to a different part,
your skin to somewhere else.
Each sense had its own bit of brain.
What we find now is in fact, the eye
is talking to the ear almost as soon
as those signals get from the
eye and the ear into the brain.
From very early on, there are
multisensory interactions at work.
Scientists are saying there is
no such thing as a visual brain,
no such part of the brain
that is just doing hearing.
All of the brain is multisensory,
all of the brain is combining all
the different senses, all the time.
So it turns out we are all far
more similar to synaesthetes
than we've realised.
It's clear we should no longer
think of our senses
as working independently
but as working together as one.
It's a discovery that has truly
revolutionary possibilities.
Hi. I'm Larry. Hi, Edie.
Very nice to meet you. We're going
to do little demonstration here
called the rubber hand illusion.
This illusion may look like
fairground fun, but it reveals
one of the most important
new ideas in brain science.
Right there.
Good. Can you put this hand down
right over here, and curl it up
like the rubber hand is curled up
a little bit. I'm going to try
to position the rubber hand
so it looks like it's your own.
Could you imagine that
being your own hand? Yeah.
We're going to stroke your finger
simultaneously, the rubber
finger and your real finger.
Hopefully this will convince you
that the rubber hand is your own.
Your brain will adopt this hand.
In the illusion, simply watching the
rubber hand being stroked at the
same time as the real hand is enough
to trick the brain into adopting it
as its own. We like weird!
And slowly but surely, you should
feel that the hand you're looking at
is actually part of your body.
It feels like you're
touching my hand with that one.
Right, so it feels like this is
your hand I'm touching, right?
Are you OK? Yeah. Good.
Try that at home with your kids!
The rubber hand illusion
is a wonderful example of how
multisensory perception can influence
how we perceive our own body.
That's how deep
multisensory perception runs.
When you hold your hand out, it's
generally thought that you know
it's there because of the information
you're getting from your muscles and
tendons and that sort of thing.
The rubber hand illusion shows
how that can be overridden
by visual information.
The rubber hand illusion shows
the powerful connection between
what we see and what we feel.
But it reveals even more than simply
the way our senses are connected.
It hints that a fundamental
change in the brain is taking place.
Oh!
Isn't that strange?!
Yeah, that's creepy.
What might be going on in
this illusion is that
the brain is actually changing to
accommodate the new rubber hand.
Going through some sort of structural
change that we call neuroplasticity.
Neuroplasticity is an exciting new
idea that suggests the brain can
change in response to experience.
And this is what's taking place
in the rubber hand illusion.
The brain may be temporarily
re-wiring itself to adopt
the plastic hand as its own.
It really feeling like it's
your hand now, huh? Yes.
Is that a little weird?
Yes. We like weird
in perceptual psychology!
Here we go.
Was that scary? Yes.
Good, we like that!
'Brain plasticity
is a terrifically exciting'
sort of phenomenon
for perceptual psychology.
I think the rubber hand illusion
shows that.
That the brain can change,
based on a new experience.
This is important for somebody,
say, who doesn't have vision,
to know that they can compensate
through plasticity with another sense
and use that to navigate the world.
This idea of a plastic,
flexible brain is so exciting
because of the phenomenal
possibilities it contains.
Not only do our senses work
together, but it suggests one
could be used to replace another.
CLICKING
I lost my first eye at the age
of seven months, and my second
at the age of 13 months,
to retinoblastoma,
which is a retinal tumour.
I have no visual memories at all.
CLICKING
Although Daniel is completely blind,
he's developed a remarkable ability
to see,
using his sense of hearing alone.
CLICKS HIS TONGUE
People do express surprise
at a blind person cycling.
I think different people
are good at different things.
I was good at cycling
but I wasn't much for ball sports.
Using the sound of his tongue
clicks, Daniel has learned to
echolocate, just like a bat.
Echolocation
is just another way of seeing.
It's a way of seeing with sound
instead of light.
You extract images
from the patterns of sound
as they reflect off the environment.
When Daniel clicks,
the sound waves he produces
bounce off nearby objects.
From the returning echoes,
Daniel creates an image in his mind,
which he uses to navigate the world.
It's an ability that's enabled him
to overcome the impossible.
I could cycle without echolocating
for a brief while, and then it would
end uncomfortably.
It's kind of like they say,
"Falling is really quite a blast,
it's the striking the ground that's
the real bummer." So, yeah...
But Daniel can show us
far more than what one
extraordinary man can achieve.
His remarkable bat-like abilities
are helping scientists reveal the
hidden potential of the brain.
Professor Lutz Wiegrebe
is an expert in bat echolocation,
but now in Daniel,
he's been given the unique
opportunity to study
his first human subject.
Wow. That is very cool.
There's another one!
Today, Lutz is conducting
a series of MRI scans,
to find out what happens inside
Daniel's brain when he echolocates.
For me personally, this has been a
really great experience, because
I've been working on the
echolocation of bats and
we've only recently started working
on echolocation with humans.
Having Daniel around is like
almost being able to talk to a bat,
and Daniel is not only exceptionally
good at echolocation, he's also
exceptionally good at verbalising
how he does it.
Inside the scanner,
Daniel is hearing virtual echoes.
This should enable the team to see
which parts of his brain
are activated when he echolocates
in the real world.
Lutz suspects that when Daniel
clicks, something remarkable may
be happening inside his brain.
Even though he can't see, the sounds
he hears may still be activating
parts of his visual brain.
What we are interested in is
so-called cross-modal plasticity,
which means that these parts
of the principal visual cortex are
taken over by auditory information.
Lutz is looking for evidence to show
just how malleable the human brain
really is.
Not only can experience
temporarily change the brain,
but as Daniel seems to suggest,
these changes can also be permanent.
It means that at the extreme
extent of...
the cross-modal plasticity on
a perceptual level that Daniel
has demonstrated, he can
really see with his ears.
That it's not only that he can
process spatial information acquired
with his auditory system, but that
he can also recruit parts of
his visual cortex to do this task.
It's just a demonstration how
plastic the system is,
and how intelligently it's designed.
If one part of the brain
has really no input any more because
of a sensory deprivation,
then this part can be taken
over by other modalities.
As unique individuals
like Daniel seem to show,
the human brain can change and adapt
in the most phenomenal way.
This has implications not only for
people whose senses are impaired,
it has the potential
to affect us all.
For Dr Angus Rupert, finding a way
of replacing one sense with another
has been a lifelong ambition.
It's `, rdlmthat for
his colleagues at Fort Rucker
Aviation Centre in Alabama
could mean the difference
between life and death.
Since 1990 alone, we've lost between
ten and 30 pilots and air crew
per year,
just due to spatial disorientation.
These are the figures across
our army, navy and air force.
We define spatial disorientation as
occurs whenever a pilot misperceives
the position, motion or attitude
of his aircraft, relative to the
Earth or other significant objects.
In other words it's,
"Which way is up?"
In normal circumstances, pilots
can correct the problem of spatial
disorientation by using their eyes.
But there are instances when they
can't always rely on what they see.
When you are flying, there is no way
for you to know where down is
unless you are actually
looking at the horizon
or looking at an indicator
to give you the information
in the aircraft.
But Angus Rupert
thinks he has found the solution.
It comes in the form of the Tactile Situation Awareness System, or TSAS,
which uses touch to support
or replace the sense of vision.
Together with research pilot
John Ramiccio,
they've found a way of giving pilots
spatial awareness by using a series
of vibrating pads called tactors.
So, in this situation we have
John wearing tactors incorporated
into the shoulder harness.
These are the ones telling him
if he is too high.
In the seat we have tactors letting
him know if he's getting too low
as well as tactors
around his waist here.
And you can see these tactors
giving information as to which way
he is drifting in space.
So confident are they in how the
system works, it's being
put to the test
on a pilot who will attempt to fly
with his eyes completely closed.
So it's at some risk that we are
not successful
but that's the essence of science,
is to experiment
and so this is raw...
and un-attempted-before footage.
We will have Captain Wingate
close his eyes, and use
the tactile cues to land
the helicopter so he
is going to be fully reliant
on feel for spatial orientation.
I would like you to take off
down the runway.
Do you feel the upper tactor fire?
It's your shoulder harness
telling you that you're
above 100 feet, which is perfect.
Eyes closed.
Zero the tactor out on the belly
button so you know you need
a little bit of...
There is your belly button tactor.
Keep your eyes closed.
Feel that increase,
it means velocity is getting fast.
Slow it down a little bit. Very nice.
Don't dump power.
You are on a nice descent right now.
I am not going to give you
any warnings.
Your seat pad will tell you 10 ft.
That's not going around.
That is me preparing cushion.
Right? You are on the ground.
LAUGHTER
Nice job! Nice job!
That was a first
for TSAS right there.
Eyes closed approach from over 100ft.
Straight to the ground
like crazy men. OK.
For pilots on the front lines,
this ability to make more of their
other senses could make all
the difference in the world.
I've done numerous dust landings
sat roadsides where you have
zero reference with the ground
because of the dust outside.
It's talcum powder -
very thick and it envelops you.
So to be able to use your body
and adjust appropriately,
not only are you saving
the guy's life on the ground
but you also have the guys on
board you are trying to protect.
It gives you another ability to...
adjust appropriately
so that's amazing.
I am very excited and pleased to be
able to say it is a wonderful feeling
in your heart to know you have an
answer for a problem that will save
many lives under many different types
of conditions, not just in aviation
but in many other situations.
This new technology
has profound implications,
helping to reveal what our senses
are really capable of.
As we use touch,
we will find there are more
and more applications in the future
and they will be almost limitless,
only limited by our imagination.
And it is up to us to come up with
new and better ways to use this.
And I am sure there are people out
there that will take this technology
and carry it well into the future.
And that future may be
just around the corner.
In the small German town
of Osnabruck, a group of scientists
have been pioneering
a groundbreaking new experiment.
They've been pushing the boundary of
our sensory capability, attempting
to give a man an entirely new sense.
They've been trying to see if
humans can make use of the earth's
magnetic field, just like birds.
So in the beginning
we came up with the idea you
could use the magnetic field of the
earth to augment the sensory system
and extend the sensory experience
you usually have.
For the past six years, they've been
developing the feelSpace belt -
a vibrating sensory device
that enables the wearer to feel
the position of magnetic north.
So actually that's the prototype
of the belt, so we did the first...
exploratory study with that belt
and it exists, basically
of a row of vibrators
like in cell phones
so these green things are vibrating.
And at the other side
is the most important part.
The compass
feeds information to the control box
and the control box then controls
all these vibrators.
So if you put it around your waist,
like this, there is always one
of the vibrators vibrating.
This one is vibrating because there's
north and if I turn like this,
the next one is vibrating
and if I turn like this,
the next one is vibrating.
So a signal's going around my waist.
I think it's not so important how
it looks but it really works so...!
Udo Wachter was one
of the volunteers
who took part in the study.
For six weird weeks, he wore the
belt every moment of his waking day.
In the beginning it was a little
bit strange because one isn't very
used to having a constant buzzing
on the body,
and I'm also a little
bit ticklish in certain places!
But it didn't take very long
to get used to it,
after a day or so, I didn't really
realise it was there any more.
The first clue the team were on to
something came when they noticed an
important and unexpected phenomenon.
Strangely, wearers found it
difficult to articulate
what they were experiencing.
It was a sign something really
significant was taking place.
It's a characteristic of senses
that it's so specific and so special
that it's hard to communicate
to someone who does not have it.
You can't communicate
how it is to see red to someone
who has never seen red.
It hints at the possibility that
there is really integration of
new sensory information going on.
In the modern world,
there's no shortage of technology
to find our way around.
But the feelSpace system
was unlike any other kind of device.
For the first time
it suggested new sensory
information could be absorbed
without having to think about it.
You might say, you can just have a
compass, and look at it and then you
can find your way anyways but this
is what we do not want to find.
We want to help subjects
integrate this kind of
information in a way which makes it
available to them just intuitively.
Usually senses do not work
or they do not need attention so you
open your eyes and see,
you take out earplugs and you hear,
and you just put your hand down here
and you feel that it's sand here.
After six weeks
of intensive training,
Udo and the other volunteers
faced the ultimate challenge.
Using only his new magnetic sense,
Udo had to navigate blindfold
around a previously unseen shape.
And even when
deliberately disorientated,
he still managed to find his way
back to his starting position
with remarkable accuracy...
an otherwise impossible task.
While wearing the belt, it felt like
having a new sense and after a
very short time it just felt like it
should always be there,
and it felt like it always was there.
After its initial trial,
the feelSpace belt offers us
a glimpse of the future,
suggesting we may not be limited
by the senses we are born with.
The team are already working
on a more extensive trial,
where they will probe the system's
impact on the brain
in even greater detail
but it's clear that when it
comes to creating new senses,
this is just the beginning.
Just the idea that
there are more ways
to experience the world
is just fascinating.
I wouldn't say it's going beyond...
er...
evolution, it's more like...
I would say it's more like
a part of evolution.
Because I would say evolution is
nothing which stopped ten years ago,
or 100 years ago,
or stopped just now,
but it's going on. And if it's going
to work out and if we are successful
with this study and we find out it is
working then it's an important step
for science, but also for everyone
who is a human being, in a way.
Over the past ten years,
our understanding of the senses
has undergone a revolution.
It's enabling us to finally unlock
the extraordinary potential
of our minds...
and promising to transform
all our lives in the most
weird and wonderful ways.
So next time you're not sure
whether to believe what you see...
enjoy it,
because these tricks of the mind are
how you make sense of your world.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk