♪
Girl:
"So when times are tough."
Man: Ooh, that sounds good.
Breakfast of champions
coming your way.
"When times are tough
and the money is down"...
Ooh, how about,
"And the chips are down"?
"Then vote Natalie Parish
for treasurer. I'll gamble
with your money."
- Ha ha. You're right.
That does not sound good.
- Okay.
- I gotta go.
No time for breakfast.
- No, no, look.
Take that in the truck with you.
You need the energy.
Okay, okay, okay.
I won't. Okay. Mmm.
Aw, my gosh, I know.
My dad's terrible.
He takes me to the mall.
He makes my breakfast.
He does my laundry.
And you're just never...
Why are you drinking my coffee?
I gotta go.
( engine turns over )
Dad?
- Yeah, honey?
- I really appreciate
everything you've done
with this whole thing,
- but if I lose, I just...
- No, no, no.
Don't even talk like that.
Okay, but there's
a chance that I will.
A really good chance.
Kalie Ryan is just more popular.
Sweetheart, just the fact
that you're running
is enough to make me
proud, okay?
I'm being dead serious.
I would have never
had the courage to do that
when I was your age.
In fact, that's something
that your mother would've done.
- Really?
- Really.
So just go in there
and give it your all,
and, you know,
swing for the fences
and do your best and all those
other uplifting sayings.
- ( laughs ) Okay.
- You're gonna do great.
- Thanks, Dad.
- You're welcome.
( school bell rings )
So remember,
you have your cue cards.
If you get nervous,
just look down.
You're gonna do great.
I have full faith in you.
Thanks, Dad.
You're gonna knock 'em dead.
Say hi to Uncle Nicky for me.
I will.
Call me as soon as you find out.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay?
Hello, Family Parish.
Hey, Tess.
Hey, Nat!
Give it your all.
Hey, how you doing?
Are you ready?
( chattering )
( horn honks )
I hope you got coffee.
Uh, yeah, I do.
I made a fresh pot at the house,
where you were supposed to meet
me about ten minutes ago.
Mrs. Rollins needed
her shower fixed.
- It was an emergency.
- Right.
And that's not something
her husband could've done?
Right, you know, Nicky,
one of these days,
you're going to get
your rear kicked,
and this guy isn't gonna do
a dang thing about it.
That's because you don't
know how to fight, old man.
Dude, I'm like 4 years
older than you.
Quit hitting me.
All right, listen,
Bruce pulled a lot of strings
to get us a shot at this job,
so just easy on the
trademark humor, okay?
Man: You know
I can't control it.
It's a gift.
Okay.
Girl:
I don't know
if you guys remember
last year's junior prom,
but in my opinion,
it was lacking.
And that's because you
didn't have me as treasurer.
I promise, if
you vote Kalie as treasurer,
senior prom will be bomb.
And my dad is
an investment banker.
So vote Kalie Ryan,
because handling money
is a family business.
Thank you.
Natalie, you're up.
♪
( knock on door )
I apologize again
for the tardiness, Mr. Woodrow.
Well, Bruce Cahill tells me
you're a reliable man.
And if there's one person
I trust in this life,
it's my lawyer.
As you can see,
the architect didn't even
break ground on the pool.
And the pergola design...
was a disgusting eyesore.
And the IRS got a hold of him
before he could even
build the thing.
Now this house is just
incomplete without a pergola.
Am I right?
Oh, yeah,
just awful without a pergola.
You boys can build, right?
We certainly can, Mr. Woodrow.
Whatever you need, we got you.
Well, naturally, I'm going
to want to clear
whoever you bring
onto my property.
Naturally, sir.
But it's just us.
Mr. Woodrow,
why don't we go inside
and discuss what look
you're going for?
I'm gonna treat
you guys to the best
iced tea you've ever had.
Peaches! Peaches?
Let's get some iced tea
for these boys.
Sick speech, girl.
I loved the bit about
"protecting our future."
You sounded like a superhero.
That was my dad's idea.
I felt like an idiot up there.
Well, the brain-dead slut's
probably going to win,
because that's life, but still.
Huh, speak of the devil.
Good job on her speech...
You think they're breaking up?
For the millionth time
this month?
Probably.
Who cares?
Idiot!
I actually like the guy.
I mean, so he owns a Bugatti.
Two Bugattis,
he made a point of saying.
( sighs )
That's about the 50th time today
that you've checked your phone.
What's going on?
You finally got a hot squeeze?
Come on.
You can tell me.
No, Natalie's said that
she's going to call me
as soon as she finds out
about the election.
I haven't heard from her.
I'm just worried she lost,
you know?
If she lost, she lost.
She's a tough girl.
I know, but a student office
looks really good
on a college application.
So do straight As.
She needs that scholarship,
Nicky,
just like we need to get
a job like this, okay?
We can't keep fixing
Agnes Mason's sink
every other week
for a slice of pie.
You watch your mouth
about that pie.
That is good pie.
And stop worrying about
Natalie so much.
Lucky for you, she takes after
the Barnes side of the family.
That's exactly what worries me,
by the way.
- What?
- Nothing.
Natalie.
I think they're just
a little blinded right now.
But the more they attack
each other, the closer they get.
Looks like someone's
been reading ahead again.
- ( intercom beeps )
- Man: Good afternoon, students.
Principal Henries here
with the results
of today's very close elections.
Our new school president,
Samuel Cahill.
Vice president,
Katherine Morelli.
Treasurer, Natalie Parish.
Secretary, Leslie...
Congratulations.
Get up, guys, get up, come on.
Hey.
Considering she's
so far ahead in the reading,
maybe the new treasurer
has time in her schedule
to cheer on the hockey team
tonight?
I'm not really a big hockey fan.
Want to know a secret?
Okay.
Neither am I.
( laughs )
And there's a party
at my house afterwards.
Sounds fun.
It's just I kind of
already have plans, so.
You can bring your friends.
The more the merrier.
Who you hanging with?
Oh, um...
well, it's just that
it's my dad, so...
( chuckles )
All right, uh, well,
congratulations as
treasurer.
Thanks.
Um, maybe I'll see you later.
What a sleazeball,
asking you out like five minutes
- after he broke up with Kalie.
- ( sighs )
Honestly, Nat, I don't know
how you two used to be a couple.
Tess, he kissed me on the cheek
once when we were five.
Besides, he didn't ask me out.
He asked me to the hockey game
and to the party after.
What'd you tell him?
That I had plans with my dad.
Right.
Hey, did you tell him
about the big news yet?
Oh, shoot,
I was supposed to call.
Or...
Oh, boy.
I'm so sorry.
You know,
these things, they're...
They're just popularity
contests.
You don't think I'm popular?
No, no, no, no,
what I mean is...
I mean that they never pick
the smartest,
or the most over...
You know.
They never...
What?
No! No! No!
- Yes? Really?
- Yes.
You swear?
Oh, my gosh!
That's so great!
I'm so proud of you.
Good job.
Oh, man.
- You deserve an Oscar.
- Thank you very much.
You want to join us
for celebration tonight?
Nah, you two enjoy.
All right, let's do it.
I cannot believe it.
That's so cool!
And the winner reaps her reward,
the world-famous...
Martin Parish...
( laughs )
Monster sundae, sundae, sundae.
( sighs )
You were a winner today.
But now you lose.
Dad...
Something's wrong? What, I put...
Too much syrup on it?
No, no, it's great.
It is, mm, it is great.
Great.
- But...
- What?
I kind of want
to do something fun tonight.
Oh, wait a minute, you want
a different game, right?
Well, there's a hockey game
this afternoon, and I thought
maybe it would be good thing
to go and say thank you
to everyone because
of the election and... right?
I get it.
Do some glad-handing,
kiss some babies.
That sounds fine.
Okay.
Well, I'll go change.
( crowd shouting )
( buzzer buzzes )
I'll see you after the game.
Hey, Marty!
Should've told me
you were coming.
I would've brought
another seat warmer.
Oh, that's all right, Bruce.
Nice to see you, Julie.
We heard Natalie's
a big winner today, too.
Yes, yes, I guess she is.
Guess she's gonna be working
for Sam now, huh?
Maybe.
You know,
we never see you
at these things.
Yeah, well,
Natalie wanted to come,
so it was either here or,
you know,
stay home
and draw up blueprints.
I can't believe
you made me come here.
It's one game.
Hey, Natalie.
Maybe you should dip
into the school treasury
and buy yourself
a shirt that fits.
Maybe you should dip
into your trust fund
and buy yourself a brain.
( cell phone rings )
Crap. My mom's
shift ends in ten.
I have to go pick her up.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
- Yay!
- Yeah!
( crowd cheering )
Martin, hockey
was never this big
when we were in high school,
was it?
It's hard to say.
We weren't the kind
to care too much.
I'm freezing.
I'm gonna go get us
some hot chocolates.
No whipped cream, right?
That's right.
Let's talk shop.
Jimmy Woodrow said everything
went really well today.
- Oh, that's great.
- He really likes your style.
He's not so keen
on your brother-in-law, though.
I had to vouch for him.
I'm really grateful
for what you're doing, Bruce.
I'm not doing anything,
all right?
Just introducing
a hardworking friend
to a client who needs
some hard work done.
A lot more's gonna
come from this.
Once the neighbors see this
beautiful pergola being built,
they're all gonna want one.
That's what it's like
in Deer Hills.
I hope so.
( crowd cheers )
( laughs )
There's the guy.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
- Great game.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Great game, Sam.
- Thank you, Mr. Parish.
Okay.
Dad, I invited some people over.
That okay?
It's a school night.
I don't think so.
Aw, let him have some fun.
He's earned it.
Homework's done?
Yeah.
You coming, Nat?
Uh, is that okay, Dad?
Sure, if Mr. and Mrs. Cahill
are okay with it,
I guess it's fine.
- You can ride in my car.
- Okay.
Don't worry, Mr. Parish.
I'm a good driver.
( chattering )
I'm gonna pick you up
at 11:00, okay?
♪
Natalie, what are you doing?
I just needed some fresh air.
Natalie, are you drunk?
Okay, come on.
Come on, no,
you're coming with me.
Come on, I gotta
get you in the truck.
- ( retching )
- Okay, okay.
Here look, you're getting
it in your hair.
Are you okay?
Are you done?
Dad, please, get off.
Dad, get off.
I'm trying to get home,
get off me.
- I know we're try...
- Get off...
- Honey? Come here.
- ( grunting )
( shouts )
( groans )
Excuse me, hi.
My daughter's been drinking.
She's getting sick.
She fell and hit her head.
Okay, sir, I just need you
to fill out that form,
and I'm gonna need
your insurance card.
- Okay, can I please just...
- We need a doctor up front.
Natalie, come here, baby.
( grunts )
( beeping )
Marty.
Hey.
Hey, I was just
finishing up my shift
- when I saw Natalie.
- Is she okay?
She's unconscious, but stable.
Alcohol poisoning.
But we'll keep
the oxygen flowing
and flush her system out
with vitamins,
and she'll bounce right back.
Listen, Marty,
does Natalie have a boyfriend?
A boyfriend?
No, why?
Just the admitting nurse,
when she examined her,
found some blood.
- Did somebody hurt her?
- Don't jump to conclusions.
We have a detective
on his way down just in case
any accusations arise,
but at this point,
it's strictly precautionary.
Whatever you need.
When can I see my daughter?
Soon. Soon.
In the meantime,
I am required to give you this.
Just... take it easy.
I'll be back, okay?
Take it easy.
Dad.
Dad?
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You had me so worried.
Martin.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm Detective Will Schaffer.
Martin Parish.
Natalie, do you mind
if I ask you a few questions?
Yeah, you can ask her
a few questions.
Martin, why don't you come
to my office for a couple
minutes, huh?
Come on.
I'll be right outside, okay?
Will: Mr. Parish,
Natalie's gonna be fine.
Her story is that nobody
did anything wrong.
The body examination
corroborates.
There was no sign of a struggle.
There's no indication that this
was non-consensual sex.
You said there was blood.
There was.
It was her first time, Martin.
Sometimes kids don't
really know their limit,
especially when alcohol's
involved.
- Who did this to her?
- Mr. Parish.
To be clear...
no one did anything
to Natalie, do you understand?
Do you know a boy
named Sam Cahill?
Yeah.
Natalie says that the sex
was consensual.
- Oh, man.
- Here.
If she changes her story,
gimme a call.
Take her home, Marty.
So you know him personally?
Yeah, I treated his wife, Sarah.
Bone cancer.
She died when Natalie
was four years old.
The girl's all he's got.
Um... honey,
can I make you some food?
'Cause you gotta be hungry.
And then we can talk?
I'm just really tired.
Okay, but, I mean...
we can talk, right?
I'm just really tired.
Okay.
Nat.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
- Why, what have you heard?
- What everyone else has,
that you spent the night
in the hospital?
What? How?
They said that the cops
came to Sam's house
and broke up the party,
after you ended up unconscious.
Do you want to talk about it?
- I have nothing to say.
- Natalie.
Careful, guys,
or Ms. Lightweight here
- might vomit on your shoes.
- ( laughter )
Gotta get to class.
Knock yourself out.
She didn't even touch it?
She's okay now?
She seems to be, yeah.
Well... great,
Great, Martin.
I mean, what a relief.
We had a real scare up here
with the cops knocking
down the door
in the middle of the night
and all that.
You have to know I had no idea.
When Sam said he had friends
coming over, I had no idea.
No, of course not, I know,
but still, you could've...
I just feel so bad
about the whole thing.
You let them hang
in the basement.
You trust that they're not
up to no good.
And then the cops show up,
and it's just a whole big mess?
I'm just so glad
that she's okay.
She just wants things
to get back to normal.
Yeah, yeah.
These things happen.
We all just have to move on,
right?
Speaking of which,
I just got off the phone
with James Woodrow.
He doesn't want
to wait any longer.
He asked if you and Nick
can start tomorrow.
That's great,
but we don't even have
- the plans laid out yet.
- It doesn't matter.
You just head on up
and start mapping out
your plans on the clock,
and listen,
if there's anything else
Julie and I can do,
you let us know.
There is actually
just one more thing.
Um...
Maybe Detective Schaffer
told you
that they had to test Natalie
with a, uh...
a rape kit?
Gee, Martin.
No, no,
he failed to mention that.
Probably because it didn't
amount to anything, it's just...
Is Natalie saying that Sam...
No, no, not at all.
It's...
It's just a precaution.
All right.
Anyway, I just, um...
I thought you should know.
Of course.
Teacher:
Okay, everybody.
Mr. President, why don't
you tell us what you think?
Sam.
Uh, yeah.
Sounds good.
Natalie.
We need to talk.
Please, leave me alone.
So how was school today? Hey.
Did you know that the police
went to the Cahills
after I went to the hospital?
Yeah, yeah, I, uh...
I knew that.
Did you tell them to?
No, I didn't tell them to.
But you told them
where the party was.
Honey, I... I told them
everything that I knew.
What?
Everyone's talking.
They're just concerned.
Why? Why can't everyone
just mind their own business?
- ( door slams ) - ( Sighs )
( whirring )
Hey.
So there's a B-movie marathon
at the Prestige.
Thought maybe we could go,
do our own voiceovers.
I have a lot of homework.
Okay.
Well, maybe some other time.
- Ready?
- ( engine turns over )
You should try the chicken.
It's good.
Just not really hungry.
Okay.
Tess!
Don't see you
around much anymore.
Yeah, sorry.
Tess, you know
you can talk to me, right?
I know.
Natalie hasn't really been
acting like herself lately, huh?
Look, I'm just trying
to understand what's going on,
and she's not talking to me.
Has she said anything to you
about that night at all?
She's been pretty much
avoiding me
and everyone else ever since.
What about Sam?
What?
Look, I don't want to get anyone
into any trouble.
You won't get anybody into
any trouble, I promise you.
( sighs )
So the day after the party,
I saw Natalie
and Sam in the hall.
He was chasing after her.
He was trying to talk to her.
He grabbed her.
How did he grab her?
Her arm.
Look, she was trying
to get away from him.
He grabbed her arm,
but then she pulled away
and ran off.
I don't know.
It was probably nothing.
Yeah, probably.
♪
( telephone rings )
Detective Schaffer.
Hi, Detective,
this is Martin Parish.
I'm Natalie's father.
I brought her
into the hospital for...
I remember you, Mr. Parish.
What can I do for you?
Well, you said to give you
a call if anything changed,
and, um... well,
I've been seeing symptoms,
and Sam Cahill,
he grabbed Natalie in school,
and it sounded pretty rough,
and I just thought that
it might be relevant.
Natalie told you this?
No, no, her...
Her best friend, um...
Tess Gerty,
she saw the whole thing.
Okay, well, um...
I'm afraid it's only relevant
if Natalie's changed her story
about what happened that night.
Otherwise it's just it's just
a couple of kids...
No, n... she has.
I'm sorry?
Yeah, Natalie,
she has changed her story.
Uh, okay.
Okay, well, then we're going to
need to get her on the record
giving her side...
Okay, well, see, the thing is,
is that I don't... I don't think
that she's ready for
that quite yet.
She...
It's a bit overwhelming,
and I'm the only person
that she's talking to about it.
Um... so I just
don't want to rush her.
But I also read it's important
to start these investigations
as soon as possible,
so I just thought
that if I called you that
we could start the...
I understand.
Listen, I'll bring Sam Cahill
in tomorrow.
I'll get his side of the story
in full detail.
Once we have that,
then maybe Natalie
will feel a little more
comfortable telling her side.
I'll be in touch.
Okay, thank you.
Tell us in your own words
what happened the night
of the party.
We're saying he's not
here to actually testify.
He's here of his own volition.
I'm just trying
to get to the bottom
of what happened that night.
Now neither you
or I were in that room
to give any sort of response
about what it was.
So I need to hear from Sam
exactly what happened.
Hey, sweetie.
I was going to wake you,
but you looked so peaceful.
Fish won't bite all day, though.
You're going fishing?
Nope, we're going fishing.
- Dad, I don't...
- Lake Hopatcong.
It's where your mom and I used
to go when we were
a little bit overwhelmed
or stressed.
It's a relaxing kind of place,
and you're gonna love it.
So get dressed.
Okay.
( sighs )
- So I have it unlocked.
- Wait, is this locked?
Yeah, you're good.
So I'm gonna cast first.
Ready?
Mm-hmm.
There you go.
Okay, then lock it.
Okay.
Watch the...
There you go.
Nice.
Done, there you go.
- Okay.
- All right.
Now what?
Now we wait.
Kind of boring, isn't it?
If by boring,
you mean relaxing, then, yes.
It is incredibly boring.
How's student council going?
It's fine.
Have you started planning
the Winter Formal yet?
Unfortunately, yes.
Do sophomores
get to go to that dance?
If they're asked
by a junior or a senior.
Ah, that's right.
That's how I first went,
you know.
I thought you and mom met
at graduation
with the famous
flying cap story.
We did.
I went with Julie.
Julie...
Cahill now.
Rogers then.
You never told me
that you dated Mrs. Cahill.
That was a long time ago.
Besides, your mother
was my first real girlfriend.
Julie and I were just...
casual.
Dad, ew.
I'm just saying,
I know how it is at that age.
Sometimes things don't feel
so black and white.
Can get confusing.
There's a lot of peer pressure...
Okay, Dad.
Okay.
I'm just saying, if you want
to talk to me about it.
Whoa, whoa, what do I do?
What do I do?
Okay, all right, all right,
all right.
We got a fish on.
That's good.
So what I want you to do
is we're gonna tire him out.
Okay, this just a matter
of waiting the fish out.
We're gonna exhaust him,
so when I say, go,
I want you to set the hook.
That just means give
a little tug.
Se the hook.
Just pull that. Good.
Now you got him.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Now just, uh...
Come here, buddy.
All right, come here.
I'm gonna reach out.
Oh, look at that.
Huh? So pretty.
Here. Pet him.
Just pet him.
( both laugh )
- Just pet it.
- ( laughs )
What should we name him?
Um, Food.
( chattering )
( reel whirs )
Oh!
( laughs )
We caught a pier.
If we're talking about poundage,
then this guy won.
But it's all about the catch,
and I caught more.
Well...
I can't argue with that.
What's the matter?
I think I just...
spent too much time in the sun.
Okay, why don't you
just go take a shower,
and I'll prep the feast?
Okay, don't do too much
without me, though.
I want to learn
the whole process.
You got it.
( beeps ) Martin,
this is Detective Schaffer.
Look, I spoke
with Sam Cahill today.
His story is that Natalie
asked to go up to his room
and it was consensual
the whole way through.
So if Natalie has a different
story like you said,
I'm really going to need
to hear it myself.
Otherwise there's nothing else
I can do.
- ( beeps )
- What'd you do?
Natalie,
you're not talking to me,
and I just figured I'd...
So you lied to the police?
No, I... look...
I just feel like you're maybe
a little confused.
I am not confused.
You are, you... okay,
You're not acting like yourself.
You're moping around.
You're acting down.
You're not...
That's because you couldn't
take care of me that night
without getting
the whole world involved.
Now I'm the girl
who partied too hard,
who went to the hospital
then broke up the party...
Let me ask you a question.
No, no, no, listen.
How do you think it feels
to be driving down
the middle of the road
and see your daughter
swaying all over the place
and then slurring her words?
- You're vomiting...
- I was drunk, Dad!
- That's what happens!
- Not to people like you!
I acted my age for once
in my life,
and I end up with you,
the police,
doctors interrogating me while
my head is still spinning!
Here's what I'm asking you,
okay?
If you're ready to talk
about it, I'm ready to listen.
- You're not listening to me!
- I am listening to you!
You're not listening to me!
I had sex with Sam Cahill!
Okay.
He didn't force me to drink.
He didn't force me
to do anything.
I asked him to take me upstairs.
I had sex with him
because I wanted to.
And, yeah.
I've been down.
Because losing your virginity
is supposed to be
a special memory,
not some big public circus
that you are only making worse!
Baby, I'm trying to fix.
No. No! No!
Don't "baby" me.
I am not your baby girl anymore,
so stop treating me like one.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if it's hard
for you to hear.
I really am.
But maybe if mom was here...
No, no, no, no.
No, you don't...
You don't get to say that, okay?
You didn't even know
your mother.
You need to stop putting her
on a pedestal.
Because she
wouldn't do anything.
Do you understand?
You can stop that right now.
( cell phone ringing )
Hello.
Uh... hi.
Julie?
Martin?
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry
to call you this late.
I was just...
I was hoping that maybe we could
get together and talk?
Martin, I don't think
that's a really good idea.
Bruce had to take Sam
down to the station.
I know, I just, um...
I don't have anybody
to talk to right now.
And I, um...
I just need somebody to talk to.
Please.
Okay.
I guess I can get away
for an hour or so.
Where should we meet?
( engine turns over )
( vehicle departs )
( ringing )
Hi, Tess.
Natalie, what's up?
I'm sorry that I've
been acting so weird.
I just don't have anyone else
that I can talk to now.
And...
I'm really scared.
I need your help.
Okay, what do you need?
You had a nicer car
in high school.
( laughs )
I was worried we were gonna run
into some kids out here.
I don't think these kids use it
the same way we used to.
( chuckles )
Not when they have
a basement and a comfy couch.
Martin...
I'm sorry...
No, I'm sorry, it was my house.
Julie, I didn't ask you here
to talk about that.
I... I promise.
So... is everything okay?
Is Natalie okay?
Yeah, yeah, Natalie's...
No.
Everything's not okay.
When Natalie
just started walking...
Sarah decided that she wanted
to do something... different.
She said that being a mom
was harder than she thought.
So she just wanted
to try something new.
So she started taking these
pottery classes up in Walden
every Thursday
from 5:00 to 6:00.
And every few weeks
she'd bring home a new vase
or a bowl or something, and...
I'd say, "Wow, honey, this looks
really great," you know?
"You're doing so good.
We should look into getting
a kiln
put in the house for you,"
you know?
I just wanted her
to feel good about something.
I wanted to feel proud
about something.
So this one week, she came home
with this really
pretty yellow vase.
And she said she thought
it would look beautiful
in the window
with some sunflowers in it.
So the next morning, I did that.
I went and got some sunflowers,
and I put them in the vase,
and I put it on the window.
And she was right.
I mean, it looked beautiful.
( chuckles )
Later that day when Natalie
got home from school,
she had a friend over
and they were rough-housing,
and they knocked the vase,
and it fell off the window
and it hit the kitchen floor
and shattered into 1,000 pieces.
So... I was mad.
Kept thinking,
"What am I going to tell Sarah?"
She's going to be so upset.
She worked so hard
on this thing.
Started cleaning it up,
and when I was done.
I saw this
one little shard left.
I picked it up,
and I turn it over,
and it had this sticker on it.
The sticker said "$9.99."
( sighs )
At least she got
a good deal on it.
It was a really pretty vase.
You know that place
the Pink Motel up on Route 14?
Real flashy one with the,
yeah, the big neon sign?
When I first saw the guy...
I was actually disappointed.
I guess I just expected him
to be this young,
slick kid, you know, but...
Maybe I thought it'd help
make sense of everything?
But he was just this guy.
He was like this...
normal guy,
this average guy.
Did you confront Sarah?
Yeah, she said
that he made her happy.
And that she was ready
to run off with him.
But then, uh...
She got sick.
Does Natalie know
about any of this?
No. I, uh...
I figured it was hard enough
being raised without a mother,
so I didn't wanna give her
any... bad memories, but...
The point is...
I wasn't enough for Sarah.
She needed more.
And what if Natalie
needs her mother now
and there's nothing I can do?
I mean, what if I can't do
anything about it?
What if I'm not enough?
You're the strongest man
I've ever known.
The strongest.
And you have all this love
that you share.
I just want to take care of her,
you know?
It's all I've ever known
how to do.
And if I can't do that, then...
I mean, who am I?
Natalie's gonna be okay.
Are you gonna tell your dad?
No.
He's been acting
like a crazy person.
I can't talk to him.
I gotta do this by myself.
What about Sam?
I don't even know
if he likes me.
Especially
with how I've been acting
with everything
going on right now.
Don't you think you ought
to figure that out first?
Go talk to him, Natalie.
And...
if you don't think
it'll work out
between you two...
there is another option.
Natalie?
Where you going?
I'm getting a ride to school.
What?! Wh...
So you're finally ready to talk?
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry
that I've been avoiding you.
I was... I was just
really embarrassed
about breaking up the party
and I kind of figured
that you were mad at me anyway.
No, I don't care
about the party.
I spent all of yesterday
at the police station
being questioned for rape.
- What did you tell them?
- I didn't tell them anything.
- You should.
- What do you want me to say?
The truth?
I mean, we were both
really tanked, right?
Right.
Look, I'm not like you.
I'm not going to get
into college on my grades.
I need this hockey scholarship.
If the coach at Boulder hears
even one word about it...
it's gone.
Look...
we will make sure
that everyone knows
this isn't true, okay?
What's going on
with you this morning?
Nothing.
What the hell is that?
- You don't think, uh...
- Yeah, I don't know.
I left you a message
this morning.
Well, we didn't get your message
because we were driving here
to work.
So would you please just tell us
what's going on right now?
I've decided to take the project
in a different direction.
You decided to change the plans
that you approved of,
that we started working on
because you weren't happy
with what we were doing?
- Is that it?
- Martin. Martin.
We've got the contract.
We'll lose him.
We'll sue these guys.
I wouldn't recommend that.
That's right,
you wouldn't advise it
because you have such great
representation,
- isn't that right?
- It's not worth it.
Come on, come on.
Hey, good luck working
for this pig.
Holy smokes.
For a moment there,
I thought you were actually
gonna take him out.
( engine turns over )
( engine stops )
Did you know?
What, we were gonna
get fired today?
- How could I possibly...
- About Sarah.
- What about her?
- She was your sister.
She must have told
you something.
She must have confided in you.
Did she...
Did she tell you anything?
Did you know?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
I'm gonna drive you home.
( engine turns over )
Sam: Yeah, the problem
with that is Coach Cran
needs the gymnasium every day
from 3:00 to 6:00 PM
for basketball practice.
So...
I guess we'll look
into other venue options.
That's a good meeting
today, guys.
Natalie, they'll talk.
Yeah.
They'll talk about how Natalie
and Sam are all over each other.
That's the idea.
I mean, we need to show them
that nothing's wrong, right?
So...
I'm your girlfriend now.
Okay?
My dad would kill me if he knew
I was even talking to you.
This isn't about them.
It's about us.
I really need you to be with me
on this one.
Okay, Sam?
Are you with me?
( laughs ) Uh-oh.
Looks like the student council's
here to bust us.
No one cares about you, Kalie.
Didn't you figure that out when
the president dumped your ass?
I heard you spent a night
in the hospital, Parish.
Yeah?
What was that like?
The food sucked.
( telephone rings )
Mr. Cahill will see you now.
Martin, what's on your mind?
James Woodrow fired me today.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I don't believe that's the first
time that you're hearing of it.
What are you insinuating?
I think you're punishing me.
I'm the one
who got you that job.
Which means it would be just
as easy to take it from me.
Bruce, I understand
you might be upset with me...
I-I might be upset
about what?
I had my concerns
about Natalie and Sam.
I... I called the police.
I just wanted them
to look into it, that's all.
And so you think this is what?
You accuse my son of rape,
and then I take away your job?
Bruce, I need the money.
I need it.
I'm sure.
You'll find other work.
But it seems like you're
no longer welcome in Deer Hills.
Can I just ask you
one more question?
Did you buy them the liquor?
Or are you just such
a generous parent
that you let them have some
out of your own personal stash?
We're back to this again?
Your daughter
can't hold her alcohol,
and that makes me a bad guy
because I'm not
overbearing like you,
because I don't keep tabs
on my kid's every single move?
Maybe if you did,
then my daughter...
Your daughter what?
Natalie is fine! She's fine!
You're the one losing it!
You want to know why
you lost your job?
Woodrow says that ever
since your daughter got sick,
you've been screwing up,
making mistakes,
working half-pace.
( laughs )
He says your half-wit
brother-in-law
is the only one holding
the thing together.
And still I stood up for you.
Until yesterday.
I'm sorry
if I was no longer so forgiving
after I spent an entire day
listening to my son
defend himself to the police.
Yeah, I'm sure you were plenty
helpful in his defense...
Don't you point
your fingers at me
because your daughter's a slut!
Hey! Hey!
You stay away from her,
you hear me?!
What are you doing?
- Natalie, get in the truck.
- No.
Get in the truck!
Go!
I just don't want you
hanging out with Sam Cahill!
- Why?
- Because he's no good,
just like his father.
- You don't even know him.
- I know enough.
- You don't know anything!
- What did you just say?
I said you don't know anything!
And you are a horrible father!
I wish that you would die!
I wish you died,
and I still had my mom!
- You never had a mom!
- What is that supposed to mean?
It means your mom was
at the Pink Motel
busy with her boyfriend!
So busy she couldn't
raise her own daughter!
What?
She was going to leave us,
Natalie.
Why wouldn't you tell me?
Natalie, you didn't need to know
about all that stuff, okay?
I wanted you to feel loved,
like you had a good mother.
Well, I needed a father,
and you lied.
I didn't... I was...
Look, I was just scared, okay?
- Of what?
- Of what?!
What? Say it.
Say it!
Say it, Dad.
Say what?
You were scared
that if I found out,
I would turn out just like her.
Don't you say that!
That's not true!
Guess what, Daddy.
Your whore daughter already
got herself knocked up!
( panting )
What?
Okay.
Why didn't you say something?
- Why didn't you...
- Tell you?
Yeah, why didn't you tell me?
That is a great question
coming from you right now.
All right, here's what
we're going to do.
We're going to talk about this.
We're going to figure this out...
I think that you have
made it very clear
that we have needed
to talk about a lot of things
for a long time.
But it is too late.
Hi, Sam. Um...
I think I need a place to stay.
Um... Yeah, sure.
( winces )
I'm sorry that my dad
attacked you.
It's okay.
Are you?
- Hmm?
- Okay?
I need to ask you something.
Do you regret it?
No.
I mean, I wish it had worked out
differently afterwards.
But I really like you, Natalie.
I need to...
I need to tell you something.
I'm pregnant.
Sam:
What do we do?
I don't know.
Thank you.
For what?
Saying "we."
Hey, sweetie.
What's up?
Natalie Parish is here.
No, so she can't
be here, Julie.
She needs to leave.
Bruce... she's pregnant.
( exclaims )
These kids,
they're both so confused.
They need help.
We should call Martin
so that we can all sit down
and discuss this.
No, we let them cool
off for a minute.
I'll handle Martin.
First, I want to talk to my son.
Sammy.
Have a seat.
So Natalie's
spending the night, huh?
Yeah.
I know you don't want me
talking to her dad.
It's just... complicated.
Because she's pregnant.
Your mom overheard.
You're a good guy.
You care about this girl?
Yeah.
Good.
Because you and Natalie both
have bright futures ahead of you
if you make
the right decision now,
if you nip this thing in the bud
before it's too late.
What do you mean?
Well, there's a clinic
in Milltown.
You're going to take Natalie
first thing in the morning,
and they'll take care of it.
It's early enough.
Quick and easy,
like it never even happened.
Dad... I don't know
if that's what she wants.
Sam!
That girl doesn't know
what she wants.
It's up to you to convince her
to do what's right.
What about Mr. Parish?
Doesn't he have to give
permission or something?
Legally, he's gotta be notified.
But there's something called
a judicial bypass.
You don't have
to worry about that.
I'll take care of that.
Do you understand?
Natalie, I know that you're
really angry with me right now,
but if you would please just...
let me in,
I know we can get
through this together.
Natalie, please?
Natalie?
- Come on!
- ( engine turns over )
( tires squeal )
Natalie!
Martin, are you out
of your mind?
- Where is she?!
- Get off my property.
- Bruce!
- Go back inside.
You didn't tell him?
You said you talked it over.
Talked what over?
Bruce, what did you do?
I gave our kids a solution.
Julie, please.
Where are they?
Julie, don't!
The clinic in Milltown.
Marty...
There's no operation involved.
What I am gonna do
is prescribe you
two oral medications.
The first is called
mifepristone.
That one you take immediately.
And what that does is break down
the walls of your uterus
so that the pregnancy
can't effectively continue.
After that, you're gonna take
something called misoprostol.
Now, that one's gonna cause
some pain and some bleeding,
but that's totally normal.
( crying )
( engine turns over )
I'm looking for my daughter.
Mr. Parish?
Sam, where is she?
Natalie Parish?
She left about 20 minutes ago.
She took my car.
Is there anywhere
that she would've gone
that you can think of?
No.
Call your mother, Sam.
I'm coming with you.
- ( door slams )
- No, you're not.
Natalie!
Nat!
She's left for good, maybe.
Maybe this is what I deserve.
Mr. Parish, maybe she's just
off thinking somewhere.
Don't... don't...
Don't presume to know her, Sam,
or know where she is, okay?
You're just a kid.
Now move.
It's why you're going home.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry this is happening!
But I'm here!
I'm not running!
We were just trying
to do the right thing!
And Natalie was scared.
She said she didn't want
to end up like her mother.
This seat taken?
I remember this place.
You used to take me here
when you'd follow mom,
didn't you?
Natalie, my feelings about
your mother are...
complicated.
So you knew she was gonna
leave us.
But you stayed with her
the whole time in the hospital
whole time anyway.
( sighs )
When her boyfriend found out
that she was dying...
he left.
She didn't have anybody.
You've got a stupid big heart.
You know that, right?
But I shouldn't
have lied to you.
I just don't want you
to hate her.
Well, I don't hate her.
But I don't love her either.
I mean, how can you really
have any feelings
about someone that you
never really knew?
All I ever really knew was you.
( chuckles )
Bum luck.
At least you make good sundaes.
I think you might have
a date to the Winter Formal.
Do you think I'm throwing
my life away?
Nah, it's just a dance.
Dad.
Your future is just gonna be
as good or as bad
as you want it to be.
But what if I'm a bad mom?
You won't be.
That I'm certain of.
I have to take my car.
I'm sorry, I just...
It's fine.
I'm happy you're okay.
Thank you, Mr. Parish.
Daddy...
Just be careful.
( sighs )