(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
EMILY: This is the story
of our friendship.
This is the way it began.
- Hey.
EMILY: A lot of things had
been said about Jackson.
What he is, what he did.
But this is who
he always was to me,
- before the bad years...
- MAN: Lights out!
(SCREAMING)
And what happened.
Jackson was a good kid.
He was an altar boy,
for Christ sakes.
If this were any kind of world
except the shithole that it is,
things might've been different.
Tragedy today in the city of
South Greenwich, Rhode Island.
EMILY: But I'm getting
ahead of myself.
First, you need to understand
some things about us.
Who we were.
Most of all, you have to
understand where we come from.
This is South Greenwich,
Rhode Island.
The shittiest fucking
place on earth.
This town was built
around a couple factories.
The biggest one, Smith brothers,
used to make gas masks
and other stuff.
You know, safety equipment.
That's all gone, though.
Jackson grew up
on the poor half of town.
I grew up on the better side
where everyone lived off credit.
Champagne lifestyles
and ginger ale budgets,
my mom used to say.
No matter which side
you were on, though,
the bastards were always
right at the edge
of the clearing.
I'd already
learned that early on.
I need to get by.
This our path, gotta pay.
Who says it's your path?
This does.
Tony, go long.
BOY: I'm open!
Aw, aw, oh!
(LAUGHING)
I just wanna go.
Then you have to give me a kiss.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(BEEPING)
KATHY: Hey, baby.
Did your father call?
No.
You want dinner?
Oh, no, honey, that's all right.
Mommy's so tired.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(CHUCKLES)
EMILY: I remember the day
Jackson came to our school.
His mother transferred
from a job in Jersey
to be closer to family
after his father's accident.
Not that they knew any of that.
All they knew
was that he looked dirty.
His clothes were wrong.
That was enough.
He was at the bottom
of the food chain,
which took some
of the pressure off me.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
For a while, I guess
that was good enough.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I wanna see some
freakin' bodies hit the floor.
Jimmy, good hustle buddy.
Come on, let's go!
Emily!
This is the fourth time
this quarter
you have failed to bring
your gym clothes.
You are now officially
flunking this class.
Are you aware of that?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Everybody stop.
Jackson Marshall.
Get your skid mark shorts
to center court, now!
Let me ask you
something, Jackson,
do you need to go
to the bathroom?
Are you sure you don't need
to take a dump or something?
No, sir.
Well, then,
maybe you can tell me
why you're running
like you have
a load in your shorts!
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Get out of here.
EMILY: I'm told that some
people cherish their childhood.
My mom always
talks about being young
and beautiful and the world
being full of possibility.
But for some of us,
we were ugly.
There was no possibility.
Some of us were told,
right off the bat,
there's no room for you here.
Nobody wants you.
There is nowhere to run.
And we are going
to eat you alive.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
EMILY: It's a jungle in here.
Predictable and cruel.
But then, one day,
Tony Brown and his whole
fucking family died.
Tony Brown was a rotten
little fucking asshole.
Used to hang out with Jimmy
Falco and the rest of them.
- (WOMAN MOANING)
- (BED CREAKING)
(MOANING CONTINUES)
- (RATTLING)
- (MAN MOANS)
EMILY: Apparently, Tony's
father worked a whole lot
and his mom was left
feeling somewhat...
- (MOANING CONTINUES)
- (CREAKING CONTINUES)
Unfulfilled.
(MOANING CONTINUES)
So she'd started
getting fulfilled
by one of her co-workers
on their lunch break.
(MOANING)
Somehow or another,
Tony's dad found out.
So one day, Tony's father
took his lunch break early,
and chopped his wife
and her boss
- up in the bedroom.
- (WOMAN COUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
They said he kept
chopping them up
even after they were dead.
Like wood.
- That part I remember particularly well.
- (GRUNTS)
Tony's father waited patiently
for two hours
until he got home from school.
Then he shot Tony
at close range with a rifle,
and hung himself
in the back yard.
(ORGAN PLAYING)
Honestly, so what?
There's one less asshole
in the world.
Four less,
if you count the adults.
And when it comes to assholes,
you can count
these people twice.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
Emily, sit down.
Everybody can see you.
- Hey.
- (LOUDLY) Ow!
PASTOR JOHNSON: Good morning.
On this somber occasion,
I have chosen
as the subject of this
homily a passage from
Paul's letter to the Ephesians,
chapter 5, verse 22.
"Let wives be subject to their
husbands as to the Lord.
"Because a husband
is head of the wife
"just as Christ is
head of the church.
"Being himself
savior of the body."
Wives, submit to your husbands.
How simple is that?
What we have here,
is the failure of a woman.
Who sinned against God
and against her husband.
And what is the result of that?
Her son is lying in that
cold gray casket right there.
A boy.
A dead boy.
And where is his mother
right now?
In a fiery lake in hell!
With an entire eternity
to answer the question,
was it worth it?
Inequity,
infidelity,
infidelity, fidelis, faith,
infidelity, unfaithful.
Wives, submit to your husbands.
Should we help it?
Yeah.
EMILY: From then on,
we were friends.
We grew up as friends
in this pretty little town
that was rotten to its core.
Surrounded on all sides,
wondering which of them
would be the next
to explode like
Tony Brown's did.
Or produce some new breed
of homicidal monster.
Maybe it would be that one.
Maybe it would be our own.
And years later,
when Jackson started
crossing the street
to avoid walking
in front of that
old fucking church,
I never even needed
to question why.
I already knew the answer.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- Let's go, let's go.
I better not see any of my
football players doggin' it.
Come on, go.
Attaboy. Come on, ladies.
Oh, Pakula. Jesus, come on.
Your ass is draggin'
in the dirt.
Move it.
Emily!
I'm a broken goddamn
record for six years.
Once again, no gym clothes,
and once again,
you're failing gym class.
Unbelievable.
What're you reading?
- Sylvia Plath.
- Sylvia who?
Exactly.
I want to see you in my office
before the end of the day.
- What about?
- Just do it.
Before the end of the day,
just be there.
(INDISTINCT TALKING ON PA)
You wanted to see me?
Yeah. Come on in, Emily,
sit down.
Have a seat.
I want to talk to you
about your little performance
in class today.
(SIGHS)
Emily, you ever wondered why
you can't seem to focus,
why you just don't fit in?
I mean, have you ever
wondered like,
where's the fucking beef?
(STAMMERS) Um...
I want to show you
a book, Emily.
It's the book that saved
my goddamn life.
I'm sorry, I don't mean
to curse in front of students,
but it's just you and me here,
so fuck it.
Anyway.
I was at the absolute
worst part of my life,
going nowhere.
No direction.
I was a weird little loser,
like yourself.
And this book...
(GULPS)
This book brought me
out of that nosedive.
And I want you to have
a free copy of it.
I want you to read this, Emily.
And I want you to look
at yourself in the mirror.
And I want you to ask yourself,
"Where does my power live?"
Where does your
power live, Emily?
- Where does my power live?
- Yeah.
Hmm.
Anyway, good talk.
Oh. And, hey,
please do me a favor,
I'm asking nicely.
Wear your motherfucking gym
clothes tomorrow, will you?
Oh, and, hey,
stay away from that
Jackson Marshall kid, too.
He is the weaker twin
that you're in the womb with.
EMILY: About that last bit,
- he may've been right.
- (EXHALES)
I always knew that
Jackson was different.
He felt things differently
from the other kids.
Some things he felt more,
some things he felt less.
(INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV)
(AIR HORN BLOWING)
Jackson!
EMILY: I guess I should tell
you about Jackson's parents.
That's something people
always want to know about.
What were the parents like?
Well, ours were pretty average.
...this fucking mess!
(COUGHING)
Now get over here. Get over here
and fucking clean it.
(COUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
EMILY: By the time I knew Carl,
he just sat
in his chair all day,
drinking and staring at the TV.
He was paralyzed,
had awful spasms that would come
in the middle
of the night sometimes.
MAN ON TV: ...ask you again.
Why do we...
EMILY: Sometimes the muscles
in his chest seized
- and he'd have to be
injected -(SCREAMING)
with a muscle relaxer
so they didn't squeeze him
to death
like a boa constrictor.
(PANTING)
Most days,
he just shit his pants.
Jackson's mother hung around
for the disability
and what was left
of his savings.
- But she was out of the house a lot.
- (AIR HORN BLOWING)
CARL ON BABY MONITOR: Jackson!
EMILY: Jackson didn't feel
things like the other kids.
But I believe that it was Carl
who taught him how to hate.
(DISTORTED TALKING ON TV)
(GULPING)
(GUN FIRING)
Fuck, I need some fuckin' ammo.
Yeah, 'cause I'm gonna win.
(LAUGHS)
- Bitch.
- (LAUGHING)
You know the Beach Boys
recorded a song that
Charles Manson wrote?
- That's weird.
- (CHUCKLES)
Did you know that the
Manson family killed
- one of the guys with a bayonet?
- Really?
Stabbed him in the throat
with a fucking bayonet.
Fuck, any civil war reenactors?
No, they were hippies.
Fuck, where'd you go?
I'm right... here!
Fuck!
God, I hate this fucking game!
Cool the fuck out.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Goddamn.
EMILY: And then, one day,
he broke.
One day, Henry Pakula
decided to piss
into his shampoo bottle.
As Henry later told it,
it was a long, healthy piss.
Jackson!
(SPUTTERING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT TAUNTS)
- (YELLS)
- (WHIMPERS)
Get the fuck off!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Fucking... I've got you.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
You little fuck!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
(SCREAMING)
MAN: You wanna be talked
to like you're here, Jackson?
Well, you're not gonna
be here for very long,
let me tell you that.
But you know what I think?
I think that
you're a little weasel.
A degenerate.
A grade "D" piece of shit!
What you did to that boy
is inexcusable.
Cheap shot. Rotten.
He's at the hospital right now
tryin' to get his thumb
sewed back on for Christ's sake.
They doubt he'll ever be able
to use it properly again.
If you were my kid, (LAUGHS)
I would get you home
as soon as possible
so I could mete out
the most severe punishment
of your life!
EMILY: And that was
the end of Jackson,
as far as most
people were concerned.
He was one of those
"What ever happened to's?"
Although, later they all pretended
they were real close with him.
When they had microphones
in their faces,
everyone had a story to tell.
The truth is, he disappeared.
Most people forgot about him,
and he even stopped calling me.
He said he had
a lot of appointments
and he couldn't go out anymore.
I had my own shit to deal with
and forgot about him
for a while.
♪ All my friends have
all grown up
♪ Alas, how did I get here?
(PHONE LINE RINGING)
(ON ANSWERING MACHINE) Hi, this is
Peter Kelly. Please leave a message.
(BEEPING)
♪ When my money has
♪ All dried up to dust
♪ How did I get here?
♪ When my family has
♪ Packed their things and left
♪ How did I get here?
EMILY: God.
Such a fucking cliche.
♪ Wait your turn
♪ Follow soon
♪ Wear a tie
(BEEPING)
♪ When I get the pictures
♪ All set out
♪ Now I belong here
(DIAL TONE)
(EMILY SCREAMING)
♪ My mother's gone away
- ♪ I live alone
- (MONITOR BEEPING)
(MALE REPORTER TALKING ON TV)
♪ Now I belong here ♪
REPORTER ON TV: ...one senior
insurgent leader was killed.
What you're about to see
is actual footage
from the air strike...
(EXPLOSION)
EMILY: There he was,
Prince Charming.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Always there
in the nick of time.
♪ Wait your turn
(INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV)
♪ Follow soon
(WOMAN TALKING ON PA)
♪ Wear a tie ♪
EMILY: After my mom's incident,
he started coming around
a bit more,
which is what Mom
always wanted, ironically.
I guess she found
where her power lived.
I think that was around the time
that Jackson met Mr. James,
who was supposed to be
like a mentor
slash social worker,
or some shit like that.
He was appointed by the district
to check in with Jackson
for the curriculum.
But then, sometimes he would
do stuff with him, too.
Mostly, he took him hunting.
They met at his house once,
Jackson saw his gun
collection, and that was it.
Sure, in retrospect
this all probably seems
very obvious
and clearly a bad idea.
But you know men
and their bonding bullshit.
Jackson's father
probably said...
- It's good for the boy
- to learn how to shoot.
Or some stupid
bullshit like that.
Dude thought he was
Robin Williams
starring in a movie
about himself,
not arming the next
white boy terrorist.
(GASPS)
- Finally...
- Whoo-hoo!
Some positive reinforcement.
(BOTH CHEERING)
He got fired two months later.
A cop pulled him over with a
bag of coke and a 17-year-old.
But thanks for
the weapons training,
Jiminy-fuckin'-Cricket.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
That summer, we were 18.
- Jackson played with guns...
- (GUNSHOT)
- I played with drugs.
- (SNORTING)
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
They didn't really
do much for me.
- Lost my virginity.
- (GRUNTING)
Read On the Road.
Injected a speedball.
Unfortunately,
I may have overdid it.
Went to rehab.
(EXHALES)
Came back.
She's here.
I'd like to report...
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
EMILY: What the fuck is this?
Well, hello there, Emily.
Now, Emily,
you and I have had
run-ins in the past.
You're always pretty tough
to get through to.
But I tried. I really did.
Precisely, because I didn't
want us to find ourselves
in a situation like this.
Mmm. And what kind of
a situation are we in,
Principal Ellwood?
Well, Emily,
we're in a situation
where we're gonna have to
make some tough calls.
We have a he-said, she-said...
It's a misunderstanding.
Now, I understand that, uh,
you were out partying last night
with Jimmy Falco
and some of the boys
and something
might have happened.
Which is delicate.
I don't know if you're aware,
but some of the boys you named
are very important members
of our football team.
Jesus fucking Christ.
These are the good kids, Emily.
Now, listen to me, the fact is,
is that you are one girl
with a history of drug use.
Intoxicated at yesterday
evening's party,
where we have witnesses
who say that you were
attempting to score drugs.
Now we can't...
(SIGHS)
We can't with any certainty
believe that your version
of the events is truthful.
Well, I certainly
don't mean to fuck
with anyone's version
of the events, sir.
But does their
version happen to have
any explanation for this?
Now, Emily...
Emily, I want you to believe me.
I'm gonna have a good
long talk with those boys.
- (SPITTING)
- Ow!
Fuck you!
All right, okay.
This fucking town
can suck my dick!
MAN: Nice.
Little cunt.
WOMAN: How are you
feeling today, Jackson?
What?
I asked how you were
feeling today.
All right.
You seem to be off
somewhere just now.
What were you thinking about when
you were looking out the window?
I was thinking
about Mercy Brown.
Is that a friend of yours?
Jackson, do you ever
think about hurting people?
In what way?
I don't know.
When you attacked
that boy in the shower,
did you think about doing it?
Sure.
Those kids are assholes.
Do you think they deserved
what you did to them?
I'm supposed to say no, right?
EMILY: She was a lazy shrink,
and she never followed up
until the police
were questioning her.
So let me fill you in about
what Jackson was talking about.
Mercy Brown.
That's where we got the name
everyone made such a big deal of.
That was our club of two.
The friends of Mercy.
When we were 13,
Jackson's mom bought him
a book of haunted places
in Rhode Island.
The only one we could
ride to on our bikes
was the one in town.
The gravesite of Mercy Brown.
We hung out there sometimes.
Once, I did a school
project on her.
She died in 1892,
just a little over
a hundred years ago.
Mercy Brown was the daughter
of a providence store clerk.
Two months earlier,
her mother and older sister
had died of consumption.
It was decided by her doctors,
due to her pale skin,
bloodshot eyes
and rapidly failing heath,
along with a sensitivity
to sunlight...
(SCREAMING)
...that the family were being
attacked by vampires.
She was whipped.
She was prayed over.
She was stripped
and bathed in ice.
She was made to drink
the blood of her dead mother,
which her family kept
at the advice of their doctors.
(SCREAMING)
Of course, it wasn't
vampires killing Mercy.
It was tuberculosis,
so she died.
(COUGHING)
Then, in January, her
brother Edwin got sick.
He was the only boy
in the Brown family
and the heir to their name.
The Brown women were all dug up.
Their coffins were pried open,
and the men of the village
gathered around.
Even the local paper was there.
Mercy's body had only been
in the ground for two months.
The others had been
buried longer.
Because her body
was in better condition
than the others,
it was decided that
- Mercy was the vampire
- (SCREAMING)
who had been feeding
on the Brown family.
And so, her heart
was ripped out of her body,
staked in front of the camera,
and burned at the graveside.
I knew what he meant
when he asked me about it.
Which means I also knew
better than to say so.
Mercy wasn't a vampire.
Just a sick kid.
But that didn't mean there was
no such thing as vampires.
(INAUDIBLE)
(YELPS)
The so-called friends of Mercy
killings in Rhode Island...
Police are learning more today
about the friends of Mercy,
two local teens accused...
And, Commissioner,
what do we know about these,
uh, friends of Mercy?
Jackson, I think we're having
trouble controlling your anger.
And I'd like to talk to you
some more in the coming months.
In the meantime,
what I'd like to do
is start you on a regimen
of a pill called vestitrol,
which will help
to regulate your moods
and keep these kinds
of outbursts under control.
There will be some things
you need to know, however.
You may experience
suicidal thoughts
while on this drug, Jackson.
You may also experience
some nausea
and a kind of
dissociated feeling,
as if you're viewing your life
through a pane of glass
or in a movie.
If that happens, you need
to talk to me about it.
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
(LAUGHTER)
EMILY: They fed him pills
until his tears dried up.
(BABY CRYING)
(INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV)
(MAN GRUNTS)
Oh, tons of fun.
We got another fuckin' jerker.
Let's go!
Thirty-seven years old.
Get up. Get up!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Lights out!
(WOMAN MOANING)
WOMAN: Oh, yeah!
(MOANING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMS)
(WOMAN GROANING)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
EMILY: Three months later he passed
an evaluation and they let him out.
For a while there it was cool.
Like old times.
Like we found something
good about ourselves
that we lost touch with.
We were older, weirder,
but it was cool.
We even opened up
the old fort for business.
(GIGGLING)
(GRUNTS)
♪ Please don't explode,
the glass will hurt my hand ♪
EMILY: Hmm.
Hmm.
Anything?
- No.
- Hmm.
I think you have
a saliva problem.
Me?
Dickhead.
- I hate this church.
- Yeah.
- Somebody should burn it down.
- (CHUCKLING)
You wanna see somethin'?
- Keep it in your pants, will ya?
- (CHUCKLING)
Whoa! (LAUGHS)
- Holy shit!
- Check it out.
Hey! Shit!
My mom tried to kill herself.
- (CHUCKLING)
- You're an asshole.
Well, relax. The safety's on.
Here.
It's lighter than I thought.
Where'd you fucking get a Glock?
For my birthday.
I've got six guns
at my house now.
I've been stashing
a few extras in the woods.
Jesus, kid.
Preppin' for the zombie
apocalypse?
See that light?
- (GUN SHOT)
- (CAR ALARM BLARING)
(DOG BARKING)
Whoa! (LAUGHING)
- Come on!
- (ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
- (DOG BARKING)
- Dude!
EMILY: This was the last
of the good times.
The rest of this shit I've been
over a hundred times in my head.
I can recite it from memory like
the Pledge of fuckin' Allegiance.
Once the news media gets a hold
of things, they're ridiculous.
So I felt it was important to keep
the facts together for myself.
On October 3rd or October 4th,
- (CAMERA CLICKING) -I was smoking
weed in Jackson's garage
and he was telling me about
this drill press he'd got.
He was all pumped up
about some tool.
I didn't understand, I was
fucked up and Instagramming,
so I was half listening
to begin with.
But he said he was learning
how to convert his gun, and I
didn't know what that meant.
He was nervous he was
gonna fuck it up,
because the gun was
expensive, I remember that.
But I mostly figured,
whatever, more gun bullshit.
♪ What's the hold-up?
♪ Time is money
♪ Bet you'll never
♪ Get much from me ♪
(GAGGING)
Jesus!
(CARL GAGGING ON BABY MONITOR)
♪ Well, there
♪ Come on
♪ Wasted, oh... ♪
(GRUNTS)
Jesus! Jesus!
(GROANING)
WOMAN ON TV: Hi, this is Tanya.
We should expect
to see a few showers of...
Blue skies for the next
few days...
Expect temperatures to be...
for the rest of the...
(GROANING)
(THUD)
MAN ON TV:
Well, thank you, Tanya,
that's good news for all
of us here in Providence.
And that's a wrap
for tonight's edition
of Rhode Island Channel 13 news.
EMILY: On October 27th,
he called me to help
move his father's shit
out of the living room.
(SIGHING)
It was two days after the funeral.
Jackson was off his meds.
His mom and everyone seemed super
pumped about how well he was doing.
And his therapist was talking
about him finishing school.
He was really comin' along!
Then, while I was there,
he took me in his room and showed me
a blueprint he made of the school,
using real blueprint paper.
It was pretty accurate too.
He said he'd scoped
the whole thing out himself.
He seemed very impressed
with his ability to do that.
I asked him...
Why?
Because I want to put
this rotten,
fucking town on the map.
(SCOFFS)
So, um, I guess
that makes you the, uh,
publicity agent, right?
What makes you think
this place is shittier
than anywhere else? Huh?
Give me a fuckin' break!
You know, okay, don't give me that
because you of all people should know!
I get it, okay! I understand.
But this, this is just
some fuckin'
rock star, cowboy bullshit,
okay? That's what that is.
Fuckin' grow up!
If he had listened then,
all of this might never
have happened.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Jackson, your goddamn
alarm is goin' off!
Jesus, with this kid!
(ALARM BEEPING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Jackson Marshall, do not move,
or I will shoot!
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
EMILY: And then he was gone again.
And this time it would be for good.
It wasn't even
on the national news.
Something like this happens
literally every week,
somewhere in America.
You need a body count of 10 now
to even stand a chance.
But it gave the locals something
to talk about for a day or two.
♪ There's broken pieces
in our path
♪ But even broken bones
ain't all bad ♪
MAN ON TV: Jackson Marshall was
arrested today on charges of conspiracy
to commit a mass shooting.
Police are interviewing him
as we speak after Mr.
Marshall was found
to be in possession
of a large arsenal of weapons
outside an area high school,
which police
have now confiscated.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
EMILY: Jackson was
never cut out for it.
What was it Coach Griffin had called him?
The weaker twin?
I guess that makes me
the stronger twin.
The one who survives.
Who doesn't get caught.
Who blends in.
Shh, be quiet.
Let's see what you're made of.
This is the story
of our friendship.
This is the way it began.
Jackson had it all wrong.
Who could blame him?
Motherfuckers were
runnin' the whole world!
Not just at school,
that was only the beginning.
They were winning everywhere.
(KEY WINDING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SNOW GLOBE)
(LOCKER CLOSING)
EMILY: Everywhere is too much
to think about though.
So kids attack
the world they know.
But stupid, pointless,
short attention span, look-at-me
bullshit, that's where I get off.
Some people think it's the guns,
but I know better.
It's not the guns.
It's deeper than that.
Since Mercy Brown.
Since all the way
at the beginning.
America is a dead
kid powered engine.
But when a thing needs doing,
you put your shoulder
to the wheel,
by gosh,
you get it done yourself.
(LAUGHING) Yes, John, yes.
I absolutely think it's gonna
work out this weekend.
Oh, yeah. Yep, yes.
I'll be sending over some
volunteers from our youth program.
Uh, yeah, yeah, I think you're gonna find that
there's some really, really fine young men.
(LAUGHING) You bet ya.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And, uh, you know I want to thank you
so much for the uh... The donations.
Very much appreciated.
And I wanted to tell ya
that we, uh...
We are very grateful for the work
you're doing over at the high school.
And that, uh, the faculty and
student body are in our prayers.
Yes, indeed.
Well, you know what, our mutual friend
will be in touch with you about, uh,
this weekend and, uh...
Yeah, I hope you enjoy
the boys. (LAUGHING)
Oh, yeah. Yes, indeed.
And, uh, I can't wait
to hear all about it.
Yeah. Okay. Yep.
Okay. Yes, you bet. Good night.
EMILY: The problem
with today's kids,
they want to do everything
the easy way.
(CLATTERING)
I have money.
- (GRUNTING)
- (GASPING)
(GROANING)
(THUD)
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
Say cheese, Father.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
Fine young men is right.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
EMILY: Knock, knock, knock.
Don't move.
Don't move in any way.
- Remember me?
- No.
Emily! Fuck!
Emily.
Wow.
What the fuck?
Let's make a deal, hmm?
You stay quiet
while we do this.
(SOBS)
I'll clear your browser history.
- You promise?
- Yep.
Nope.
Now, I'm willing to, uh,
look the other way here.
But if you scream,
we have to do it the sloppy way.
(SOBS) No.
And I just won't have time
to clean up any messes.
Thatta boy.
Thatta fuckin' boy.
Now, what we have here
is a he-said, she-said,
um, misunderstanding.
Remember how you and your pals
were never quite sure
if you could trust
a drugged-out bitch.
- Well, guess what, you fucking
shit bird... -Please.
I hope you can fucking
trust me now!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
(CLASSICAL MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
(GIGGLING)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
(LAUGHTER)
Welcome to the love shack.
- (GIGGLING)
- Whoo!
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
(SQUISHES)
(GUNSHOT)
Mary Stevenson,
nice tits, big ass.
B.
Chad. Ew. Chad.
- D minus.
- (PHONE RINGING)
- Yeah. Coach here.
- Hey, Coach Griffin?
Hey! This is Emily Kelly.
(GIGGLES) You're never
gonna fucking guess
whose phone
I'm calling you from.
- You're with Jimmy Falco tonight?
- Yeah!
We're all fuckin' partyin'
and shit.
They said you
were fun to party with.
Why don't you come on out
and party with us, huh?
We're all just chillin' at Jimmy's trailer.
You ever been?
Yeah, I was out there
just last week.
- So you're partyin' out there, huh?
- EMILY: Hell, yeah!
Come on out here,
I wanna see you.
I bet you can teach
me some things.
Well, I don't really know if I should.
I mean I'm pretty busy, you know,
but...
I guess maybe I can swing out there
for a little bit. I don't know.
Excellent.
I'll see you when
you get here, stud.
(GRUNTING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(HUMMING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Pakula, you old piece of shit.
What are you doing?
Yeah, I'm out here at, uh,
Jimmy Falco's place.
Yeah, you can come out here,
just give me some time
'cause I am closing in on some sweet
pussy that I've been workin' on
since she was
in sixth grade. Yeah.
(LAUGHING) Know what I mean?
Oh, yeah. Yep. All right.
Check you later, Masterbater.
(HUMMING)
Yeah!
Fuck.
Aw. Coach is here!
Let's all fuck some more.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
- (GROWLING)
- (GROANING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMING)
(CHOKING)
Coach, I figured out
where my power lives.
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SQUISHES)
HENRY: Oh, yeah!
Whoo!
We are the bravest!
Ha! Hey!
EMILY: If it isn't Henry
Pakula, of piss bottle fame.
What the fuck? Coach?
Oh, my God!
- (CAR ENGINE STARTING)
- Oh, boy.
- (ENGINE REVVING)
- (SCREAMING)
(THUD)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
EMILY: There must've been
something in the air that night,
or maybe it was just some
fucked up mutant strain
of mother-daughter DNA
that we shared.
She knew it was over before she saw me.
Before I said anything.
And she seemed relieved.
Like I had freed us both.
This is where your father stays
with his bitch.
That teacher of yours...
Hopper.
Emily...
You always were such
a good girl.
(SOBS)
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ I know a girl
with long black hair
♪ I wish she could see me
if she stared
♪ At the corner of the room
♪ I never seen a girl like her
♪ She'll make you shiver
when she purrs
♪ When you look into her eyes
♪ That's right she dance
♪ Fox, dance, fox
♪ Dance, fox, dance, fox ♪
You've had a hard day, pussy.
Are you stressed today,
my little pussy?
That's okay.
Momma's got a big, big dick
that's gonna make you feel
all better.
(CLATTERING)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
HOPPER: Come on, growl for me, pussy.
Come on.
Get it, get it.
You know you want it.
Get it.
Come on.
(LAUGHS) What the fuck?
Well, goddamn!
I was not expecting this.
- (HOPPER SCREAMS) -Emily, wh...
Emily, what are you doing?
Wow!
That is a mighty big dick
you have, Mrs. Hopper.
- Would you like to see mine?
- Emily!
- (SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
(SOBBING)
Listen...
I think I'm a pretty
open-minded person.
So I don't want you to think
that I'm judging this
in any kind of like,
- objective way.
- (CHOKING)
But, you know,
in a more personal way...
I am really, very
disappointed in you
right now, Dad.
(CHOKING)
I have a message for you,
from Mom.
(CHOKING)
Yeah, well, next time,
you're getting the coffee.
(BULLET CLINKING)
Quiet.
(BULLETS CLINKING)
EMILY: This is the story
of our friendship.
Well, are you gonna try
to kiss me again?
Go on.
Go on, head start's
all you're gonna get.
EMILY: A lot of things have
been said about Jackson.
What he is. What he did.
What he didn't do.
But this is who he was, to me.
He deserved a chance
to run away.
Grow up.
Figure out what his life could
be like somewhere else.
In a place where
no one knew him.
As for me, I found a place too.
Where people are simpler,
easier to understand,
more honest.
I feel quiet here. Better.
Besides...
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA)
They know better than to try me.