I ran the scan
three times.
Recalibrated
the equipment.
I keep getting a shadow
under number 11.
Let me see it.
You have a copy
of the old aerial scan?
Put it under it.
Give me de Vaux's plot.
De Vaux went over
this whole site
With a fine tooth comb.
He's dead, but he was here
50 years ago.
You can say he had
a technological disadvantage.
Son of a bitch!
What?
This isn't a shadow.
It's isn't?
No.
Archaeologists have been
coming here since 1947.
Sukenik, Harding, de Vaux.
They found
the dead sea scrolls
In 13 of these caves.
De Vaux explored another 40.
And all of them missed this.
There's another chamber.
It's hidden
under cave 11.
There is?
There is.
I want you to get me
five men with shovels.
Meet me at cave 11.
Got it.
Here's those fragments
you wanted me to catalogue.
Oh, great.
Whew.
What's going on?
We may have just turned
the last 50 years
Of biblical archeology
on its ears.
You want to go open
an undiscovered cave?
You're kidding, right?
We found it.
Under cave 11.
Let's go get
our hands dirty, shall we?
Absolutely!
There!
It's a cover stone.
Find the edges!
It's in cuneiform.
Sumerian, maybe?
Yeah, maybe.
It isn't a cave.
No, it's a vault.
Wait, what... hey,
what are you saying?
Must not open.
Death waits below.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
No, no, no, no!
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
Death waits below.
Take it easy.
Nobody needs
to get hurt.
We're on a search
for truth, not treasure.
You're foolish
to ignore the word of god.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Maybe he's right.
What?
That god would strike me
down If I opened the vault?
Please!
No, no, no.
Not god... Mold.
What?
Well, the seal on this vault
is airtight.
It could contain airborne
pathogens, Bacteria, fungi, spores,
That could very well
kill you.
Remember what happened
to lord Carnarvon
After he opened
Tutankhamen's tomb?
She's exactly right.
I got carried away.
We gotta be careful
about this and do this right. Russell,
go back up and get me some breathers,
and also get my air tester.
You all right?
Yeah.
Good catch.
That's it, Russell.
Okay, lift it on three.
Just a little bit.
One, two, three.
Good.
All clear. No methane. No
toxins beyond normal levels.
All right, let's get
down there!
That's it!
good, come on!
A little bit more!
Good!
Russell, get on
the other side.
On three, push.
One, two, three.
Good!
All right, ladder.
Look at these.
What are they for?
I don't know.
Never seen anything like it.
Could they be air vents?
Maybe, but why?
Uh, doc?
Yeah, I see.
Wow.
Oh, my god.
Run!
What?
Russell!
Unh!
Go, go!
Run!
Russell, come on!
Russell!
Professor!
Nicholas!
Doc!
Professor!
Nicholas!
Doc!
You think it could be it?
We need to get this back
to the university
So we open the jar there.
Let's just take one little
peek inside.
Just a little look, doc.
Not until we're in
An environmentally
controlled... Room.
Not until then.
You need to book us
on a flight out of here.
All right, but why do I
always have to do
All the booking
of the flights,
The lugging of equipment?
All the grunt work,
and you Joanna don't?
Seniority.
Tenure.
All right, I'm on it.
All right,
I'll help him out.
Russell, entire
academic careers
Have been made
out of discoveries like this.
Still, doc, I don't know
if this is a good idea.
You should
face the facts.
The fact is she's the best
archaeolinguist on the planet.
You could get Hoffmann
at Braxton University
Or Dr. Lillis
at Whittendale.
They could help us out.
Yes, but she is the best.
She's also your ex-wife.
So?
Doc, this is you
we're talking about.
You know, you and her,
oil and water?
Alcohol and public nudity?
Some things just don't mix!
Look, doc, I don't know
what happened between you two,
And it's none
of my business,
But every time
someone mentions her name
you get all dark
and irritable.
Then you usually find Two days'
worth of paperwork to dump on me.
It'd be two hours
if you could type.
There you go!
You haven't even seen her yet and you're
already attacking my academic credentials.
Give me that.
I wasn't attacking
your academic credentials.
I was just pondering
your lack of posable thumbs.
Right there!
You did it again.
Not nice, doc!
Not nice.
I bet that's a page-turner.
Nicholas.
Hello, Ava.
What do you want?
Your help.
I never thought
I'd hear you say that again.
It's important.
I don't know who else
to trust with this.
I don't know.
It's been a long time.
Yes, it has.
Doesn't make it
any easier, does it?
No, it certainly doesn't.
I'm glad to see you, Nicholas.
Really.
You look good.
I hope you're happy.
But I don't want
to do this anymore,
So please leave.
Ava, I think I just found
the last dead sea scroll.
You what? How?
Qumran.
I found an undiscovered
man made vault under cave 11.
Was there
a clay jar in it?
Yes!
Did you open it?
No.
The lid is sealed.
All right, but we do it
my way, no debates.
Fine, but I have to have
my graduate students with me.
They helped me find it.
Agreed.
Great.
So see you in an hour?
All right, fine.
Thank you.
All right,
I'll meet you inside.
Dr. Greenaway is
waiting on us.
So what's the deal between
him and Greenaway anyhow?
I'm surprised
he's even talking to her.
What happened?
I'm not really sure
of all the details, but...
about five years ago
One of Nicholas'
grad students
accused him
of sexual harassment.
Yeah.
It got ugly. She said
that they had an affair,
and after she broke it off,
he harassed her.
Dr. Greenaway found out about
the affair and dumped him?
Well, that's just the thing.
There never was an affair.
Turned out that
she had some mental problems
and was just
obsessed with him.
I mean, he was eventually
cleared of any wrongdoing, but...
it was after a pretty
lengthy investigation.
So why did they break up?
I don't know. I guess Dr.
Greenaway didn't believe in him
and that's when things
got broken between them.
Come on, I don't want to miss
the opening of the jar.
Dr. Greenaway,
these are my assistants,
Joanna and Russell.
Nice to meet you.
Joanna.
It's extraordinary.
The seal is cracked,
but it's intact.
We had a little trouble
getting it out of the chamber.
Yeah, like nearly dying.
Oh, he exaggerates.
Do you want to open it
or shall I?
you always had
the steadier hands.
I thought you forgot.
Okay.
Gentle.
Aidan, take this
to Caitlin for dating.
Thank you.
Let's see
what we have here.
Dear god,
they are amazing.
The most well-preserved
papyrus I've ever seen.
Are they decipherable?
This is different than anything
I've ever encountered before.
Look, the structure,
the syntax, it's unlike the other
scrolls discovered at Qumran.
But you can translate them,
though, right?
It's going to take time.
There's a lot
of information here.
There are a battery of tests
I want to run.
I'll put
my entire team on it.
Give me three weeks.
But...
Nicholas, let me
do my work.
All right.
All right, fine.
I'll see you then.
Caitlin, come here.
Come see.
Aidan, come here.
So what'd you find?
Nicholas.
I only managed to decipher
half the documents,
And that wasn't easy.
There's more to this than you
can see on the surface.
A palimpsest.
Yes.
What?
A palimpsest is parchment,
sometimes vellum.
It's written on, then the ink
is washed away and it's reused.
Only the surface text is visible To
the naked eye,
but there are secrets hat lie beneath.
So what is it?
It's the book of Genesis.
My god.
Carbon dating says it was
written around 380 B. C.
While the exodus scrolls are somewhere
between 98 BC. and 13 AD.
Yes.
And you just said this is
the book of Genesis.
As in the Book.
The unabridged edition.
There are things in here
that are not in any translation
of the old testament.
This is the oldest biblical
document ever discovered.
Cool!
There is still work
to be done,
but if it bears out,
this could be one of
the most significant discoveries
in the history of mankind.
Well, the dead sea scroll
was pretty significant.
Why is this one
so special?
According
to these scrolls,
Noah was sent on more
than one mission from god.
It says early
in the time of man,
giants, creatures,
and demons roamed the earth.
They were called
the Nephilim.
God banished all
these evil beings,
for he thought their wickedness
was corrupting mankind.
All of them were gone
except one.
It was created by the darkness
to do its bidding.
Tormented and tortured,
the darkness took pleasure
in the creature's pain.
The darkness?
It's a reference
to an evil being.
The devil, perhaps.
It's metaphorical.
The devil didn't exist.
Some religions don't
recognize the devil.
And some do. It's not metaphorical.
It's a matter of faith.
Right, fine.
Faith it is.
Go on.
The creature was to roam the
earth killing the faithful,
until god summoned
a righteous man, Noah.
God to spoke to Noah and ordered
him to build a mighty ship
to banish the darkness.
So you're saying there was
more than one ark?
Yes.
The first ark was
Noah's test by god.
Well, I guess
he passed.
Actually, he didn't.
Noah captured the creature and set
sail for the far ends of the earth,
to banish it.
For if left unchecked, it was determined
to annihilate all of mankind.
Get out of town!
So Noah built
a monster ark?
I suppose
you could call it that.
It says the powers of evil were
fighting with god over the ship.
They did not want the last
of their breed banished.
Lightning struck the ship
and it began to burn.
And as it burned,
a spear rose from the depths
and cleaved the ark in two.
I managed to decode the next
part of the palimpsest.
It appears to be
coordinates of a map.
It's in the middle
of Iraq.
It'd be impossible
to explore that right now.
Not necessarily.
Doc, you don't plan
on going into Iraq, do you?
Don't worry. I wouldn't
expect you to come with me.
I'll go.
I appreciate that,
but I don't know If
anyone is going just yet.
I'll have to talk
to someone.
Oh, I'm sure she'd love to
follow you there, professor.
Yeah, um,
I gotta go.
Me too.
You can't just leave things
alone, can you?
Me?
I'm fine.
I'm just amazed that
you continue to play games
with your career
and your reputation.
She's my student, Ava.
That's all.
I've heard that before.
That's right.
You heard the truth.
And you were the one
who chose to ignore it.
What did you
want me to think?
No, really, what did
you want me to do?
Just walk around campus
and be the oblivious wife?
Not me, nick!
Not anymore!
I loved you.
I was faithful to you.
I trusted you.
I am sorry that you were
too blind to see that.
I'm sorry.
I have faith
in something else now.
Oh, your faith... your faith,
your righteousness.
You're always right,
aren't you?
Don't go there.
Please, don't go there.
Hell, you have more faith
in a biblical fairytale
than you ever did
in your own husband
who was right
in front of you.
Don't you mock my beliefs...
No, you're a scientist, Ava!
You should act like one!
That's right!
You just love to push
the buttons, don't you?
But if you can't
touch it, or see it,
or have some rational
explanation for it
then you don't want
to hear about it.
I think I made a mistake
by coming here.
So do I.
Damn it.
And that's
really the basis
behind the classification
scheme.
Excuse me.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I want to talk to you.
Uh, I'm a little
busy right now.
It's important.
Oh, okay, yeah,
join the meeting.
This is Dr. Ava Greenaway.
Dr. Greenaway,
this is Mr. Fasanella
from Federal Tactical
Intelligence.
What is it
that you do?
We do satellite mapping
and imagery,
among other things.
I see.
I made an inquiry
to the defense department
about the coordinates that
we found on the palimpsest.
Apparently,
it raised some flags.
Earlier this month
we launched a satellite
that was tasked
with monitoring
The Sunni triangle
for insurgent activity.
Almost as soon
as the bird went up,
it began
sending us readings
That indicated
an energy anomaly.
In the area we want
to have an expedition...
Is within the quadrant
registering the anomaly.
What do you think it is?
We don't know for sure.
Communication in the area
is spotty at best.
The troops have a very difficult
time Operating there,
and the insurgents know that
and take full advantage of it.
It could be a weapons cache,
or a secret bomb making
facility, or worse.
Weapons of
mass destruction.
Possibly.
We'll be sending a small strike team
to the area to investigate, but
we thought with your particular
expertise in archeology,
it might be mutually
beneficial to bring you along.
You might spot something
our boys don't.
I'm going with him.
No, you're not.
It's gonna be
very dangerous at best.
I'm the only one who can
decipher the documents.
I haven't even finished
with them yet.
I'll provide more information
for you when we go.
I said no,
and that's final.
I don't remember asking
for your permission, Nicholas.
Who should you start now?
Why don't you stop
with the sarcasm?
Sarcasm? Me?
Oh, that is rich.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Put your team together.
You'll be meeting up with the
transport in the morning.
I don't want
to be responsible
if anything were
to happen to you.
You don't have to be
responsible for me.
I can take care
of myself.
Look...
I have to do this.
I believe in it.
Just trust me.
Please.
This is crazy.
You know that.
We should wait
until the war is over,
When it's safe.
No, anything that is out there can
be looted or destroyed by then.
No, we are gonna do this now,
not in five years' time.
Nicholas.
All right.
Joanna, right?
Yeah.
I just want to apologize
for my comment
the other day in the lab.
That was uncalled for.
Yeah, it was.
Okay, well, I just
want to apologize.
Apology noted.
You don't like me
very much, do you?
No, that's not true.
I just really care
about this expedition, and...
well, I'm concerned
about you coming along.
You think
that I'm a problem?
Well, where we're going is not
exactly a walk in the park, and...
I just think that everyone
should be in top form.
No distractions.
You think
I'm a distraction.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it's not
my place.
Joanna, I am going,
and you and I are going
to have to work together.
Okay.
If anyone wants
to back out now,
I wouldn't think
any less of you.
We're going to the most
dangerous place on the planet.
And there's a real possibility
Of getting hurt or worse.
Forget it, Doc.
It's Noah's Ark
we're talking about here.
As they say
in Texas hold 'em,
we're all in.
All right, then.
First stop is Dover, then we
catch a transit plane to Iraq.
I'm driving.
What? H-how come
you always drive?
Because you can't.
Yes, I can.
What he does cannot
be considered driving.
Oh, he knows you well.
I...
Oh, great, now you're
all ganging up on me.
What...
So if we find this ark,
are you still gonna think
the bible is fiction?
Whatever we find will be
an archaeological artifact.
I'm interested in proving
historical realities,
not perpetuating
biblical stories.
I'm not going
on a crusade here,
And I don't know
the frequent flyer miles.
You're amazing.
What?
We're about to discover The
first ark that Noah built,
And yet you refuse
to believe.
In what religion?
What about God,
Jesus Christ,
Mohammad,
Buddha, Vishnu?
No, there are
plenty of people
who believe
in those things
And have done horrible things
to their fellow man
in the name
of their religion.
Yes, but you cannot
let what men do
affect your belief
in a higher power.
I've never felt the need
to have something
in the universe
to intercede
in my life.
I am in control
of my life.
And if people
took responsibility
for their actions,
The world would be
a better place.
But I would hate
to live like you do.
You know, just living like
there's nothing out there.
That we die and we get
buried in the earth
for a future archaeologist
to dig up.
I sometimes envy you.
I...
I think it would be easier to
live life with those blinders on,
But I can't do it.
I can't.
This scroll you found,
the fact that it was buried
In a vault beneath a cave...
You think that somebody
didn't want them found.
Yes.
Yeah, that's
a pretty safe bet.
You know the legend
surrounding the scrolls.
The secret brotherhood
sworn to protect them.
That possibility
doesn't concern you?
That doesn't worry me.
It's all fiction
for the faithful.
That is definitely one
of the reasons why we broke up.
You have no faith in anything
unless you can see it.
The reason we broke up
Is because you
had no faith in me.
This is Cain.
Hello?
Hello!
It has been found.
We must alert the brotherhood
before it's too late.
Nicholas Zavatterro.
Major gentry.
Welcome to the sandbox.
Thanks.
We'll talk in my command center.
Come on!
The search area is
ten kilometers square.
We're using a low-profile
tack team.
I don't know
about this, major.
Aren't there an awful lot
of insurgents out there?
We're gonna look
just like any other patrol.
Not something for them
to target with their forces.
The only thing we need
to worry about
Is the roadside bombs.
Oh, that makes me
feel better.
We're going
to a communication dead zone.
The sat phone will be
spotty at best.
Excuse me.
May I state
the obvious here.
I think we need
a full unit to go in there.
Ma'am, with all
due respect,
I don't tell you
what rock to dig up.
I appreciate you not telling me
How to run no damn operation.
Get your gear together.
We leave in one hour.
All right, listen up,
you guys.
I didn't expect it
to be this hairy.
Maybe I should be
the only one to go out there
For safety reasons.
We're all here now.
Might as well go.
We all knew the risks
when we signed up.
Besides, I don't know
about you,
but I'm not gonna
sit around here
while you go out there
and discover
the most important
archaeological find
in the history
of mankind.
All right, let's go.
You getting out?
I got out the last six times.
I think I'll sit
this one out.
I don't know.
You think we got
the coordinates wrong?
One more hour, then we set up
camp for the night.
We need more time, Major.
You don't have more time.
I'm trying to do my job,
And you're making this
more and more difficult.
I suggest you find this damn
thing in the next hour.
Nicholas,
it says "a great spear
rose up from the sea
and cleaved the ark in two. "
There.
And there.
That could be it.
A bump?
After 5,000 years,
you'd be worn down too.
Number seven.
Lucky seven.
This is where it is.
Where?
I don't
see anything.
Look closer.
Look at the shape
of the rocks.
Look at the upper sections.
How they could be
the hull of a ship.
Yes, yes!
In Noah’s time, this entire
plain was under water.
See how the bottom
of the hull
must be embedded in what
was once the sea floor.
We did it.
We found it.
Whatever it is,
It has one hell
of an energy footprint.
But I'm gonna send my men
down there first just in case.
Stand back!
Over here!
This must the section
that leads to underground.
I said stand back!
All right, but don't
touch anything.
Relax, doc.
It's petrified.
I'm not gonna break it.
Come on,
let's go, y'all.
Get down there.
All clear!
Men, stand down.
yes, sir!
It looks
just as it's written.
So you gonna
open it up, doc?
No, I'm not gonna
open it up. This...
is a priceless
archaeological relic
found on what could be
Noah's Ark.
I'm not touching anything
until this site
is properly secured,
and then we get it back to the
states and open it up there.
Doc, I'm not
debating with you.
This box is pumping
an energy signal
the D. I. A. sent me after.
So either you open it up
or I will.
with some C-4.
C-4, check!
No, no, all right,
all right, all right.
We'll set up a port-a-lab
in base camp
and get it up there.
Thought you'd
see it my way.
Men, get to it!
Carefully!
Carefully.
All right,
put it over there.
This is the gopher-wood cage
they put the demon in.
Are you sure
we want to open it?
Whatever was in this crate
is long dead.
But then where's
the energy coming from?
We're about to find
that out.
Goggles, everybody.
All right, lasing.
Okay.
Did you see that?
It moved.
It's not possible.
Yeah, maybe someone
should tell it that.
Run!
What the hell
was that?
Where the hell is it?
It went that way, major!
What was that thing?
Damned if I know.
Get Martinez!
We got two men down
in there!
Martinez, we have a medical
emergency in the lab tent.
Do you copy? Over.
No! Aah!
Argh!
No, no! Aah!
No! Aah!
Get that sucker!
Watson!
Go! Go after it!
If you get it in your sights,
send it back to hell!
Soldier, you stay with me!
Major...
Solider!
No can do.
Don't you die on me! Martinez!
Zeke!
No.
You guys get to the APC. Lock yourselves
in. You guys should be safe there.
Let's go.
Just leave him?
No, let's go, let's go,
let's go, come on!
Here it comes!
Everybody run!
If you guys are gonna do
something,
now would be a good time!
Get out of the way!
if we shoot, we're gonna
take out the generator.
To hell with it!
Aah!
Come on.
Is it dead?
Lost it when it
took out the generator.
Show me a body!
Not dead, sir.
You mean that thing
survived the explosion?
No body, no blood.
Just tracks into the desert.
Mount up!
We're gonna hunt it down
and kill it.
Hutch!
Russell,
it's Jo.
You okay?
Take the APC and get those
civilians back to camp liberty.
Is it over?
Yeah, it's over.
Did we get it?
No.
We have a problem, sir.
I don't like problems,
corporal.
Well, that creature
took out most of our fuel
with that generator.
What we've got left is not
enough for all the vehicles.
And this was
my favorite shirt.
Well, you stay here
an protect the civilians,
and I'll be back for you.
Yes, sir.
What?!
No, no, no, no.
You are not gonna
leave us here.
You do as I say, professor.
Get in that damn APC
and don't come out
till I get back!
You listen to me.
I want my people
out of here now!
I don't care how many stripes
you have on your sleeve.
Your job
is to protect us!
If you shut up and listen to me,
that's what I'm gonna do.
If one of my people
gets hurt,
I'm coming after you.
These people's lives
are in my hands.
Welcome to my world.
That thing just killed
two of my men.
I'm sure as hell
not gonna let it get away.
Here!
Nothing gets through
the APC armor, nothing!
Can't we just call
for help?
Ma'am, all our communications
been trashed.
That thing is
getting away as we speak.
It's almost dawn.
I will be back
before noon.
Now it's on you.
It's kind of creepy that they carry
their own body bags with them.
It's Iraq.
The sad reality
is they're standard.
I didn't sign up
for this.
None of us did.
We have to set this right.
Look, I can deal
with being in a war zone.
Hell, it's scary.
But to be a part of
an archaeological discovery,
this important to find.
I'm in. but this thing,
this creature...
I don't do
razor-sharp teeth.
Radio's toast.
We should bed down
in the APC, get some rest.
Nicholas, we made
a huge mistake.
Yeah, well, you can't put
the genie back in the bottle.
That is just it.
I have been studying
these scrolls.
It says that
if this creature is released,
an age of darkness will
descend upon all mankind.
The beginning
will mark the end.
Are you saying that by
releasing this demon
we've triggered
the apocalypse?
I'm saying that
we put this creature
right back in its prison.
Oh, Ava, I don't know.
Nicholas, you just saw
this creature
that's from the time of Noah
come back to life.
Now if you do not believe
in this prophecy,
You never will.
She's right, doc.
I'm not a religious guy, but...
I'm starting to give this whole
bible thing another look.
There has to be a logical
explanation for this.
It could be some prehistoric
creature from the past.
A leftover from the age
of the dinosaurs.
Come on!
No.
We've known certain
species of fish
that have been extinct
for 70,000 years
until someone pulls one up
in a fishing boat in 1938.
Coelacanth.
That's right.
Yeah, well,
I'll tell you what.
The only thing I believe in
is staying alive.
And right now,
the best place to be
is between two inches
of plate armor out in the APC.
Just in case
your little friend decides
He wants to come back
and have some more fun time.
I'm with him.
Me too.
All right, he's right.
Let's go, come on.
You see anything?
Negative.
You summoned me.
This is a very
important day, Belus.
Whether it beckons
our salvation
or our destruction is
completely in your hands.
I don't understand.
The genesis scroll
has been found.
But it has eluded
our own people for centuries.
Who?
Who's made the discovery?
An American professor,
Nicholas Zavatterro.
Our spies tells us he already
mounted an expedition.
The secret is
in grave danger.
The knowledge must not
be allowed to pass
into the wrong hands.
If it does
and they release it,
We are lost.
I will have it back in our
possession within 48 hours.
You must do
whatever is necessary.
I will not fail you.
If you do,
you will fail a great
deal more than just me.
Hold it, hold it!
What is it?
Tracks.
They go up that way.
What's in that direction?
There's nothing
on the map, sir.
It's heading that way
for a reason.
Come on, let's go!
Well?
That's where they stop.
So it could be
anywhere.
You guys hear that?
Where's it coming from?
Out there.
Lock and load.
Let's go!
Fire it up!
Coles, left flank.
Wilson, right flank.
I'm on point.
Good hunting.
It's gone!
Double back!
Come and get me...
You stinking bag of bones.
Yaah!
Don't shoot!
I almost killed you.
I thought you were
that thing.
How could you possibly
mistake me
for whatever
the hell that is?
You're right.
Now that you mention it,
you are a lot uglier.
Aah! Aah!
Eat this! And this!
Y'all all right?
Oh, you want to play
hard to get.
Okay.
I'll play with you.
get out of the way!
Are you okay?
she probably doesn't
speak English, smart guy.
Wilson, you okay?
Yes, sir!
Coles?
Just a scratch, sir.
Let's keep moving.
Major?
It's gone.
Let's head back.
We got some civilians
to babysit.
Light it up!
We lost it.
Any contact?
Hit us hard last night
in the APC,
but it's been quiet
since then, sir.
Come on, follow me.
Yes, sir.
Professor!
We need to have
a little talk.
Now I don't know
what that thing was,
But two of my men are dead
because of it,
And I want some answers.
I don't have
any answers yet.
What does the scroll say
the ark was carrying?
The ark was used
to banish the darkness.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
It's some sort
of animal.
Listen, guys,
no damn animal
Can do that kind of damage
or take the kind of
firepower I shot at it.
This creature is a
holdover from the time
before god created man.
This is not something that's
supposed to coexist with mankind.
It was not supposed
to survive.
Well, I got news
for y'all.
It survived
and it's out there.
If it gets
in the wrong hands,
it's gonna be one hell
of a weapon.
We shot everything
we could at it,
and we couldn't kill it.
We've seen what it can do,
and we've got to stop it.
Screw that.
I say we get the hell out of here.
Yeah, I need to get
my team back to safety.
I don't want them running
around after some animal.
I will go with you,
but not them.
If we split up,
we'd be twice as vulnerable.
I can send your people
back with hutch.
It could attack them,
and they won't have enough
firepower to protect themselves.
The major's right.
We are going to do this.
God ordered Noah
to banish this thing.
Oh, his bad.
What's that got
to do with us?
The scroll is a code.
It talks of this creature
Destroying entire lands.
Of sending the world
into a time of darkness.
We're responsible for
letting this creature out,
Which means
we're responsible
for bringing about
the prophecy.
You really believe that.
It was right
in front of you.
You saw it
with your own two eyes.
How can you deny that?
I say we do it.
Great, fine.
How?
Okay, I managed
to decipher this code
a little farther
last night.
Right here it talks about
how god gave Noah a staff.
It has a golden tip and it's
imbued with special powers.
It will allow the faithful
to pierce
the heart of darkness.
And only by doing this
will the creature be stopped.
What does that mean?
It means we have to find
the staff.
Let me see that
for a minute.
well, where would
we even begin to look?
All right, these glyphs.
Have you been able
to figure them out yet?
No, it's unlike anything
I've seen before.
I think they're numbers,
not letters.
All right, this area
right here.
Is that the section that's
talking about Noah's staff?
Yes, yes.
But it goes on to say
that Noah lived
to be 700 years old
and then he died.
That's it!
They're coordinates.
For what?
If I'm right,
Noah's tomb.
And his staff
is buried with him?
Major!
Can you get us here?
I'll get you there.
I've hacked into American
military satellites.
According to the imagery,
there has been some very recent
activity where the legend says
the Ark may have
gone down.
It's possible
they have found it.
You must get there
before they do.
If they find the Ark,
the world is in grave danger.
I understand.
# take back your energy #
# take back your new way #
# her lipstick smeared
all over #
# me not know a thing #
# #
# he says his mind can't
hold that weight again #
# you know you've got #
# the way to show me
how you feel #
# this time will come... #
Wait, what are they
called again?
The noachidae.
They're descendants
of Noah.
They're a secret brotherhood.
The first masons.
Some say the most powerful
secret society in the world.
They're the ones who would
have built Noah's tomb.
And guarded it.
Kept it secret
for thousands of years.
You actually believe
in that?
I don't know
what to believe anymore.
It's a start.
# #
Unh!
Aah!
aah!
They found it.
It is here.
I always knew
within my heart...
that the legend was true,
but to see it with my eyes...
Over here!
Yes.
We were too late.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes, we will find them.
See that you do.
Don't!
Might be a booby trap.
Stand down!
All clear!
What did this?
I'll give you one guess.
No military operation
done this.
No impact craters.
No burns.
No bombs or artillery
done this.
Men getting torn apart.
It had to be your monster
did this, professor.
It got here
before we did.
It's trying to outflank us,
cut us off.
But how?
I mean, that would imply some
level of organized thinking.
A higher intelligence.
Don't look at me.
Y'all two the genius.
You let the damn thing out.
Why would it do this?
Maybe he knows
we're trying to kill it.
Unh!
Don't get any ideas.
Furthest thing
from my mind.
You see him?
Over there!
One of the survivors!
I ain't got time for this.
Aah! Unh!
Welcome to paradise.
Come on, let's move out!
We should be
coming up on it.
There!
Right there!
Right to the right!
Men, secure the area!
Corporal, watch out back.
Yes, sir!
Noah's tomb should be
subterranean.
Someone excavated the site.
Yeah, from the looks
of it maybe...
40 years ago or so...
There!
Found it!
Looks like a map room.
Russell, hand me a light.
Nicholas?
Down here.
Oh, my god.
He really lived here.
How do we know what
we're looking for?
I'm not sure.
Wait a minute.
There was this part
in the scroll
that I couldn't identify,
looks like measurements.
It's on this third
palimpsest.
Let me see.
Yeah, yeah,
this is a measurement,
But this is the...
alignment of the sun.
At its apex.
Ava, what time is it?
It's almost noon.
Okay, hurry.
I'm looking for a portal
or a hole in the ground somewhere.
Whoa, what about this?
That's it, good work.
Uh,
we need a staff.
A staff.
Ava, how long?
Um, almost four cubit.
Russell, these shovels
right here.
Pull on that.
Pull.
One more, come on.
Got it.
Well done.
That's it.
Looks like it's right underneath
that central chamber.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
Yeah, this is it.
This is it.
Okay, we're going in.
Not without me.
Russell,
let there be light.
It's been raided.
Maybe we read
the scroll incorrectly.
It is in here.
Or maybe this is
a wild goose chase.
Maybe we aren't meant
to stop it.
No, no, no, no.
Ava, look at
this structure.
There's something
behind this wall.
See how it stops right here.
Yes.
This may be
what we're looking for.
Oh, I wish I could do
this the right way, but...
We're gonna
have to improvise.
There.
Yep, everybody give me
a hand with this.
Doc, you're not gonna do
what I think you, are you?
Yes.
But after all those lectures
on respecting the artifacts?
Would you rather
sit here and wait
for that thing to come
back and kill us?
You're right.
I'm all over it.
Come on, everybody.
Major.
All right, everybody.
One, two, three!
Hey, doc.
Yeah?
Here you go.
That's good, Major.
They are here.
Put it down, put it down!
Oh, man,
this can't be good.
Keep an eye on them.
You come with me.
Put your weapons down now!
Drop the weapon now!
Drop the weapon!
Put the weapon down, man!
Put it down, man!
Put the weapon down.
Where you going?
Get away from the door, man.
Never gonna happen.
Drop it.
Put the weapon down!
Get away from the door!
Never gonna happen, man!
It's never gonna happen.
I'm not playing with you.
Hold it.
Everybody watch your step.
Ava, there's
another cylinder.
It should have
a scroll in it.
It could lead us
to the staff.
Okay.
Aah!
Everybody run!
Unh!
Come on!
Come on! Run!
What's happening?
I don't know!
But I don't like it.
Joanna, look out!
Nicholas!
Come on, hurry!
I'm right behind you! Go!
Get out of here!
Let's go, come on!
Oh! Aah!
Unh!
Aah!
Nicholas!
Help me!
Help... whoa!
Where's Nicholas?
Just sit still.
He's still in here.
He's... no...
No, no, it's too late.
It's too late.
I'm sorry.
You can't make it.
Don't you tell me that!
Oh, my god, no!
I have a medical kit
in the back.
Aah!
Please!
Oh, no, no, no!
God, don't let me
die in here.
Not like this.
Aah!
Major, we got a situation!
Hostiles!
Get to cover,
get to cover!
Don't you move!
I'll put this bullet
right through your head.
Now get out of there!
Hurry up!
Turn around.
Now everybody come out,
Or I'm gonna put
a bullet in his head.
Corporal, get their guns!
Hands behind the head.
Who the hell are you?
Hey, honey.
Oh, thank god.
Oh!
Oh, my...
what happened?
I'm not sure
you'd believe it.
How's Russell?
He's not good.
How's he doing?
Get up!
Now I ain't gonna
ask you again.
Be right back.
Who the hell are you?
Unh!
You answer him!
Who are you?
Where are you from?
I think the lady
asked you a question.
You're gonna giver her
an answer,
or I'm gonna kill you.
You're interested in this.
Careful.
Will you tell me
who you are?
The same people who have
worked for 5,000 years
to protect the secret.
The secret
you've unleashed.
You're Noachidae?
So the legend is true?
Where did you get that?
From my grandmother.
Why?
At ease.
Oh, my god.
What is that?
The symbol,
what does it mean?
It is a symbol of the order
to be passed down
from one generation
to the next.
No, this was special
because it was my mother's
and it was in my family
for generations.
My parents died
in a crash.
My grandmother raised me.
The... she...
You mean that my grandmother
is Noachidae?
Yes, as are you.
I don't... why wouldn't
she tell me that?
The knowledge is
only to be passed
when the child is 19,
not before.
She died when I was 16.
Wait, what does she
have to do with this?
Are you saying
she's a part of this?
The scroll's the first link
in the chain.
The scroll's location
and the secret it protected
Have been safely in our
possession for 5,000 years.
Christianity was not
even a religion.
A member of the order
renounced his vow
and threatened to reveal
the secret to the world.
He took the scroll.
He hid it.
Neither he nor the scroll
were ever found.
Fearing discovery, the order
scattered itself around the world
And never giving up
on its true mission,
And searched the far corners
of the earth For that scroll.
But what about
the other scroll?
The scroll that was
inside Noah's tomb?
The order put it there
when we moved Noah’s body
to another
secret location.
It gives that location,
But it's too late now.
The secret
has been revealed.
And if we don't stop it now,
the world is doomed.
Stop it?
The desert
swallowed it whole.
It's over.
It lives.
If you have read the scroll,
you know there's only
one way
to stop that creature.
Noah's staff.
And you know where it is.
Yes.
Look, you said it
yourself.
If we don't
capture this creature,
then the world
is doomed.
Now I understand that you
were sent here to stop us,
To protect your secret.
But it's too late
for that.
If we're gonna do
this thing,
then we're gonna
have to work together.
It would violate the vow.
Your vow versus
the future of mankind.
I don't think there's much
of a choice in that.
The staff lies with Noah.
He was buried with it.
And where did the order
move Noah's body?
Tell me!
I am a member of the order.
You have to tell me, right?
You must swear to me.
If I help you,
you must promise to keep
and protect the secret
as if the original vow
was yours and yours alone.
No. You must not allow the world
to know what you have learned.
No, I'm a scientist.
The knowledge of...
You must promise!
Some things are more
valuable than knowledge.
Such as?
Faith.
To reveal what you have discovered would be
to rob those who believe of their faith.
And that's not for any man.
You swear to me this vow,
I will help you.
I will take you
to the staff.
He's fading... we need to do
something for him!
If I make this promise to you,
will you make one to me?
What do you ask?
One of our men
is badly injured.
He needs a doctor.
I will keep
this secret for you
If you inform your pilot
to get my man
to medical attention.
You'll risk the future
of the world for one man?
Two minutes ago you weren't even
willing to give us the truth.
I think it's fair.
His life for your secret.
Very well.
My pilot will take
your man to the hospital.
And your secret
will be safe.
Unh!
Hang in there, Russell,
okay, you're gonna make it.
I'm gonna die,
aren't I?
No, no, you'd
annoy god too much.
Joanna, I want you
to go with him.
Make sure he gets
the best medical attention.
All right, we will be
okay without you.
No, no, I want to see
this thing through.
Russell needs you more
than we do right now,
and I do not want another one
of my students getting hurt.
Please do as I say
and go with him.
Okay, okay,
but be careful.
I will.
Now go, go!
Doc!
Yeah, buddy?
Kill that son of a bitch.
Will do.
Go!
Some biblical historians
believe that Noah
was buried in the graveyard
of the kings
on the island of Bahrain.
Which is exactly
what the order
wants you to think.
I told you, the order
spent 5,000 years
hiding the truth
about Noah.
Even the church?
The church has become somewhat
reluctant conspirators,
And even they don't know
the entire truth.
We've got to great lengths,
Dr. Zavatterro.
Nothing's left for chance
and nothing's an accident.
Why did you move
Noah's body?
The ancient city was built
by the Noachidae.
The order moved Noah's body
to protect it.
The creature was
once banished by Noah.
It will seek out the staff
and will destroy it.
We're coming up
on Al Bajib.
There was an Iraqi army
platoon stationed there,
but if they bugged out and the
insurgents have taken control,
I expect everyone here
to keep their heads up.
Captain Bahar.
We've been having insurgent
problems for the last three days.
Hutch, take the APC
and block off
the end of the road.
Yes, sir.
I'll be with you
in a minute.
Keep your eyes open.
Corporal,
get my flank.
Corporal, stand guard.
You won't be
needing that in here.
You're not getting
my gun.
This is
a house of god.
You got them fooled,
but not me.
Very well.
We must hurry.
The crypt is beneath the altar.
Sister, please, please.
Give me a hand.
No, this is...
this is all wrong.
The markings,
the frescoes.
This is a crusader's tomb.
A little farther east
than I would've expected,
but the tomb of a knight
of the crusades nonetheless.
Things are not
what they seem.
Are you saying that Noah
is buried here?
And the staff
is buried with him.
You better be right
about this.
Come on, move over.
Come on, put some
weight into it!
a little more.
This can't be.
It's dirt?
We wasted our time looking
for your magic stick, professor
and this guy led us To
a box full of dirt?!
No, it's here,
I know it's here.
How would you know that?
I know, I believe it.
Nicholas, how...
Ava, I believe.
I believe it!
aah!
You hold him off.
I'll warn the Major.
Good!
Aah!
You had faith
when I did not.
Major, I just saw it.
Let's go get it.
What was that thing?
Long story.
We'll destroy it, but we're
gonna need your help.
We're with you.
But the monster is gone.
No, no, it'll come back.
It'll come back and kill
everyone here.
We gotta figure out a way to destroy
this thing once and for all.
Now how does this work?
What do we have to do?
The staff has to be
in the hands of a man
With faith and righteousness
for it to work.
All right,
so you'll hold it.
No, I doubted my faith.
You did not.
You must be the one.
He's right... you're
the only one who believed.
All right, then we've
gotta figure out a way
to flush this thing
towards me.
I got an idea.
How many grenades
do you got left?
What are you thinking,
Major?
We'll rig explosions
all around the village.
We'll be the bait
to lure it out.
We'll draw it to the
intersection towards doc.
There's just one problem.
What's that?
We don't have enough explosives.
But we do.
We've got explosives
and grenades in our barracks.
Good.
I need your men to get
the people out of the village.
Get them to a safe distance.
Doc, we'll be back
when we're ready for you.
Let's go!
Nicholas...
When we were at the ruins,
I asked you
what happened to you.
You said that
I wouldn't understand.
What happened to you?
The chamber was collapsing
all around me.
And I knew
I wasn't gonna
make it out alive.
So I closed my eyes...
And I asked god
to let me live.
And he did.
I should've been crushed,
but I wasn't.
And I can't find
another way to explain it.
There is only one way.
There is.
All right,
let's get to work.
We're gonna need
that cage.
It will be taken
care of.
It is ready.
Very good.
You okay?
I'm scared.
What if this
doesn't work?
It'll work.
You're telling me
to have faith?
Yeah, I guess I am.
Be careful.
I will.
All right, let's do this.
Come on out,
kitty, kitty!
Kitty?
Kitty, kitty.
Come to big daddy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just want to rub you.
My gun's jammed!
Major, I've got him!
Aah!
Come on and get me!
It isn't working.
It's gonna kill 'em!
Do it!
Nicholas!
Unh!
Oh, my god.
It's not... it's not working.
What haven't we done?
Pierce its heart!
I don't know if I can.
You can, Nicholas,
you can, just believe it!
I need that crate!
Hurry! Hurry!
I can't hold on
much longer!
I can't hold on!
Now!
Lock it!
There are still many
secrets to protect.
Things that if revealed would shake
The very foundation of belief.
You have done well.
You all
have done well.
And I trust that this
will remain between us.
I'm sure you may
want this back.
You've earned the right
to carry it.
Come.
We have much to discuss.
So...
What other little treasures
are you guys hiding?
All in good time.
Where will it go?
Someplace safe.
It's time.
We must go.
I'll be right with you.
Well, doc,
it was nice knowing you.
You too, major.
You gonna hop a ride
with them guys?
Yeah, I think so.
Thank you, Major.
You saved
my ass out there.
I ought a be
thanking you.
And do me a favor.
Take care of that
ex-wife of yours, man.
She's still into you.
I will.
You ready?
Yes.
Yeah.
Captioning by captionmax
www. Captionmax. Com
Sync by Caradecuica