Tell the people to go home.
Quickly now.
Go home! There is nothing to see,
there's nothing to take.
Put him over there.
Taking names to your father?
My name is Luc Carlens.
- I know.
- Tell your father to arrest me.
Son of a collaborator!
- Any survivors?
- No.
Hello. I am Belgian. This is Belgium.
Belgium. Delahaut.
I am Jean. You have to hide.
- I can return for you. Return.
- Return?
Yes! I'll return.
It's Jean.
Please!
- It's late.
- Madame Daussois.
I need to see Monsieur Daussois.
- Why?
- An American from the plane.
He's outside. I found him
in the woods. He's dying.
- Why did you come here?
- You're in the Maquis.
No, you're mistaken. What's that?
The wheelbarrow.
He's dying.
Madame Daussois, I promised.
Go to Madame Dinant.
- Is the pilot conscious?
- No.
- You should get dressed.
- It's too early.
You came to bed late.
I couldn't sleep.
I was afraid he would die.
It happens. The others died.
Claire, you can't save everyone.
I don't understand you.
I told you not to take any more,
but you did it anyway.
This is the last one.
There's a meeting at Jauquet's.
I'll be back after dinner.
If I find out that you've lied to me,
I'll beat your brains out.
I was playing with Luc Carlens.
You can ask his father.
Goddamn Maquis!
I don't talk to such people.
They are destroying Belgium.
- Don't go near them. Understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you, Mother.
- My hand hurts.
- This is the place.
- Pardon?
- Where am I?
- Delahaut. Belgium.
- How do I get out?
- No, not today.
- I have to contact my squadron.
- It's done.
It's done.
Who are you?
- I am Claire.
- I am Ted.
- Ted.
- And the others?
No.
Thank you.
Thank you for taking care of me,
reading.
You listen?
It's poetry. Gerard Manley Hopkins.
An English airman we had
gave it to me.
Maybe later you can read more.
Your voice... is soothing.
It makes me feel...
I hear talking. It's my turn.
Don't worry. He is with the Maquis.
He is here to help you.
The Resistance. We will get you home.
Feeling better?
- I don't...
- He asks if you feel well.
Tell him not well, but not dead.
Not well, but not dead.
I have to get some water.
- Where are you going? Stay.
- Tell me, then, of you.
- This was not a bomber.
- No.
The pilot told me that
reconnaissance flights have begun.
It's not a rumour. It's a fact.
A fact that crashed in our backyard.
- It was a reconnaissance flight.
- What sort of reconnaissance?
For an invasion.
He said that a Flimsy radio
containing navigational codes
was still on the plane.
Nazi specialists have left Berlin,
while German soldiers stand guard.
We have to get into the plane.
We'd have to kill the soldiers.
There'd be reprisals.
If the Germans get the Flimsy,
there might not be an invasion.
We'd be stuck in this prison for life.
- We can't take that chance.
- It was destroyed.
- Yes.
- We can't say yes.
We've waited for this so long...
I can't remember how it was before.
Jauquet, it's like you said.
It's like waiting for Christmas Eve.
We can't risk everything
for a Christmas dream.
We have to be of one mind.
Say it! Spit it out!
Lucette... please.
Yes.
All right, we agree. It was destroyed.
We leave the plane alone.
You're so warm.
What time is it?
We decided... and then we drank.
The pilot is getting better.
You're drunk!
Only a little. And we have a plan.
Three days.
Then he'll be gone...
as if he was already gone.
- Kiss me. Too many clothes!
- It's cold.
Help me.
You don't love me.
- Go to sleep. You're really drunk.
- That's not true.
Isn't it natural for a man
to want a child with his wife?
- You'll wake the pilot.
- Fuck your American pilot!
You humiliate me. You don't love me.
I am here.
MacGreedy, Harpring,
Ellison, Dwyer, Blaise.
Davidowitz. Balzacs. Smalls. Wellman.
Mac. John.
- I apologise.
- No. Come on in.
You were talking.
Names.
My crew. My boys from the LIB.
I don't want to forget their names.
Sorry.
They were good men. The best.
Of course.
Except for Wellman.
He was a son of a bitch.
Tell me.
Ted, remember me their names.
Matt MacGreedy, John Harpring...
2Hey, lazybones. I thought
you were going to sleep all day.
You should go slow. You are not ready.
It's only three days
since your fever passed.
Three days. Boy!
It feels like I've been here since...
I heard Henri leave
about an hour ago, I think.
You hear everything in that room.
He didn't leave alone.
They meet almost every day
to prepare the route.
Good. I need to go.
They will move you tomorrow,
now that you can walk.
I will miss you.
I memorised the way you smell.
I can tell you're coming
before I hear your footsteps.
I should ride into town.
Tell Henri it is time.
"Glory be to God for dappled things -
"For skies of corporal-colour...
couple-colour as a brinded cow,
"For rose-moles all in stipple
upon trout that swim;
"Fresh-firecoal chestnut-falls;
finches' wings... "
Then there's some other
very poetic lines that I forget.
It's easier doing this
not having to look at your face.
- That is a favourite.
- I'm sorry I mangled it.
I knew it was your favourite.
That page was all wrinkled.
You leave your mark behind.
- You should not be down here.
- I just want to thank you.
I will tell Henri.
- Stay out of sight.
- You saved my life, you know.
- Yes. Well, no.
- Yes.
The hero!
Jean, I've been wanting to thank you.
- He does not understand you.
- I think he does.
He is already playing football?
I wanted to thank you.
Tell him he's lucky he's better.
You must hide.
- The Americans claim everything.
- He's a hero.
I want him hidden. Now!
- Thank you. Merci. You understand?
- Yes! Thank you.
- Take him upstairs.
- Go home, kid. Now!
- Please...
- I said now!
It would be good
to be rid of the American.
I'm sick of house guests.
Another month like that...
- It's what we do.
- Yes.
- A month is a long time.
- We'll manage.
It's all we can do.
He likes your wife.
Maybe she likes him.
Stop it. I've got enough enemies as it is.
What's happening?
- You should not be downstairs.
- I need to know!
The Nazis found one of the tunnels
out of Bruly-de-Pesche.
The tunnels are blocked. You cannot
move. Maybe soon. I don't know.
Not soon? I need to talk
to your husband or Anthoine.
- In the morning.
- Now.
- Now is not the time.
- I'm sick of being in the dark.
I am sorry. We have our ways also.
I've flown 31 combat missions.
I've been a target for 14 months.
I'm ignored by the people I'm trying
to save! You know where to find me.
You only think of yourself.
We could all die!
I won't sit here while you decide
what happens to me!
We do not ignore you. We save you!
The less you know,
the safer it is for everyone.
We're doing everything we can!
And it's our way. Goodnight, Major.
Let me go!
- What are you doing here?
- The village is empty.
They took half the village
and locked them in the barn.
- What?
- Someone killed the German guards.
What will they do? Where is Henri?
Go home. I'll catch up with you.
I'll move you as soon as possible.
- Move me where?
- Into the tunnel with the others.
I'll bring food for everyone.
Pack only what you need.
You were gone a long time.
I was beginning to get worried.
- What is it? You're flushed.
- I had a bad tyre.
- Bring it in. I'll fix it.
- No.
- You need your bike.
- What's going on?
- Please, go back upstairs.
Please!
- Have you seen Jean?
- You're scaring me.
What is it?
- Reprisals.
- For what?
Someone killed the Germans
at your plane.
Now it's the Belgians' turn to die.
- Where is your husband?
- I do not know.
Philippe Jauquet.
Emilie Boccart.
Emilie Boccart!
Jean-Luc Verdun.
Adrien van der Elst.
Elise van der Elst.
Sylvain Jacquemart.
Leon Balle. Roger Doumont.
Pascal Guillaume.
Klaas de Borgher.
Therese Dinant.
Long live Belgium!
- What will the others say?
- I have to stay.
He'll turn himself in to protect us.
He doesn't understand
that we'll lose everything.
What do I tell your husband?
There is a little boy.
This is where I belong.
Should I really tell him that?
- What if the American did it?
- I know him.
Then keep an eye on him.
I'll contact you as soon as I can.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Now hide.
- Goodbye.
Pretty girl.
Shame she's not at home.
Perhaps we could wait
for her to come back.
Let's go. There are other houses.
- We should have stayed with the others.
- This is important.
I needed to speak to you alone.
We should have stayed and fought.
It's not like us to run away.
- Sit down.
- There's no water.
Not even a chance of some cold tea.
Will you listen to me?
Bellefroid told me, but no one else.
I think you should know.
The Germans said they suspected
an American had survived the crash
and killed the guards to get the codes.
He had no idea what would happen.
He didn't think.
- And Claire stayed with him.
- Yes.
Maybe you should have stayed, too.
Yes, she's your wife.
- Of course.
- I'm talking rubbish. You know me.
What about the Flimsy and the codes?
Did he get them?
Nobody knows.
I can't go back.
It's not that bad,
if you like broken stuff.
- You think everything is funny?
- No. Just the depressing things.
Are you hungry?
Why did you come so close?
A reconnaissance flight.
The Allies are gathering
intelligence for an invasion.
Mother?
It's Jean.
He's gone.
- Will he come back?
- I don't know.
I have a list of the people
who were killed.
- I can't.
- They killed Emilie Boccart.
She was your friend.
I'm sorry.
You let him do it.
You let them all do it.
I have a new family.
It's me, Jean.
Thank you. That's kind.
Goodbye.
- Where are you going?
- I don't know.
I need you here.
Are you coming?
It's healing up quickly.
It always fades away in the end.
I made a list, to remember everyone.
- What is this?
- They are dead.
They were hanged.
Not a word to the American, you hear?
- He wouldn't have let them do it!
- Jean, listen to me. Not a word.
- All the Germans!
- Do you hear me? It's too much.
Did you ever see a person hanged,
Madame Daussois?
They look like they're dancing,
but their feet don't touch the floor.
I've told you now.
I won't tell anyone else.
- Hey, partner.
- He brought food. He's a good boy.
If he could speak French,
he'd be all right. I'll be right down.
- Not a word.
Care to dance?
Do you want to dance with him?
- Do you want kids?
- The war.
Ever?
Do me the honour. You're making me
look bad in front of the kid.
- No dancing.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
No dancing.
I feel like my dad.
He used to carry me in from his truck
when I'd pretend to be asleep.
- You are so good with him.
- It's easy. He's a great kid.
Where does he live?
Here, I think.
- Jean considers this home.
- Did he tell you?
No, but it's obvious. I noticed
Jean wasn't wearing my dog tags.
But he's a smart boy.
He knows he cannot wear them.
I am sure he hides them somewhere.
I should get them back.
Let him sleep.
He can get them for you later.
There goes my identity.
I'm beginning to forget who I am.
I promised myself I wouldn't
say it out loud, but there it is.
Message from London about the plane.
The codes are safe.
They were destroyed.
- By the pilot?
- Nobody knows.
But whoever it was
kept the codes out of German hands,
although it was at terrible cost.
Our next objective is Hanzinelle,
one of the Nazis' key supply lines.
The time has come. I'm sorry.
- Eleven dead.
- I need a team to blow up the bridges.
And we must do it soon.
- It takes two days to get to Hanzinelle.
- Claire...
Let's pull ourselves together.
I will go to Hanzinelle.
I'll teach the Nazis
what reprisals mean to us.
Filip is right.
I need focus.
I'm going to Hanzinelle.
I have not been given a bath
since I was a girl.
Claire, do you love your husband?
This war, it... changes people.
I waited a long time for him.
I know since very small
that I am marrying Henri.
- Henri is my cousin.
- Cousin?
Is that allowed?
Not close. Far cousin.
But the same last name.
- I don't even know your last name.
- Daussois.
Daussois.
You are not tired of me?
I'm not funny, not brave,
and my hands are ugly.
No.
I adore this face.
- You used to have cows.
- I do not remember. Come inside.
I bet you were good with them.
It must have been a nice place.
You want that they catch you?
Screw the Nazis. I'd like to kill
every goddamn one of them.
- Come inside.
- Belgium will be free soon.
Next time I fly here,
it's going to be with you by my side,
come back to see your parents.
- My parents are dead. Come inside.
- No.
Come here.
I'm not afraid.
You should be.
I'm going to marry you, Claire.
I'm going to marry Claire Daussois.
Give me some light.
- Ready over there?
- Yes, go ahead.
Let's go.
That's it, boys, I'm ready!
Cover your ears!
I can't close my eyes.
I see Claire at the end of a rope.
She's Okay.
She doesn't love me.
Try and sleep.
Maybe there's light
at the end of these goddamn tunnels.
Sometimes I'm afraid of her.
Henri, let's get this done
and then maybe we can go home.
What if we set the table
and nobody comes?
I'm not a soldier.
Leave me be.
- My boy, are you Okay?
- I have a new house.
What can I get for you?
We have apples today.
- I have a new mother.
- That's nice.
She's called Claire Daussois.
Quick! Some bread, cheese and beer.
What's the little runt saying?
You have to wait your turn.
I was talking to Madame Oomlop!
Where is she, then?
We don't need to wait.
Wait your turn!
It's my village. It's our store.
The bread is fresh.
Jean, get out of here.
You have to wait,
like everybody else!
- Enough.
- I want apples for my mother and me,
and for my father too.
What's he doing? I should kill him!
- Take your food and go!
- The kid's crazy.
Go!
- What got into you?
- Three apples for my mother, please.
- This is nonsense.
- And some beer.
- I will be back as soon as I can.
- Get some more bandages.
Jean's cut could be getting infected.
- You are the nurse now?
- I had a very good teacher.
Good. I'm tired of fixing men's faces.
- She loves you.
- Jean!
- What did he say?
- Nothing.
- Love, love, love you.
- Love you!
The cat... le chat... is away.
The mice will play.
Don't worry if you don't catch on
right away. It takes practice.
It's a little different than soccer.
- Baseball.
- Here we go!
A little Allie Reynolds chin music.
Don't just stand there. Run!
Run the bases!
- Home run!
- All right.
This is it,
you little Belgian Ted Williams.
- Home run!
- Don't get cocky.
I'm about to unleash the dreaded
Teddy Brice knuckle-curve, screwball,
slider-sinker-spinner,
high and tight, low and away,
say your prayers,
beg-for-mamma drop-ball.
- Home run.
- That's it. No mercy.
He checks the runner at first.
He shakes off the signal,
puts a little spin on the ball,
gets his feet ready.
Oh, yeah.
Goodbye, Mr Spalding.
I've won!
I'm calling the Indians.
They're signing you up.
You're a natural, kid.
Oh, man, you wore me out.
I have to tell it twice, for Jean.
No, American, English.
Okay, in American.
There was a boy,
and he grew up far away.
All he could see,
wherever he looked, was open.
When he ran, he made no sound,
because he ran in rhythm
with the earth.
And he was loved.
I'm awake. Go on.
This little boy became a man.
He made a house with his own hands.
He built a family, also,
and they were never alone.
They were never afraid.
When it rained, the sun got brighter.
When it snowed, the crops grew.
When they were sad, it was only
because it seemed too much
for one family to have all to themselves.
They were protected from the dark.
And night never came, because...
...because at midnight...
...at midnight,
all God's angels lit candles
to help them see that this was their gift.
Someone had to be happy, in love,
safe.
Somewhere there had to be peace.
A pear.
It's very rare, from Madame Oomlop.
Claire, what is it?
This Friday they are taking you.
Three days.
It's simple. I won't go.
They will come in the evening,
after dinner.
- You will go with me.
- It's not possible.
You have to go with me,
you and Jean.
- We have not the papers.
- Get the papers.
They cannot make them for us.
I am waiting here for my husband.
What are you talking about?
If I leave Henri, it is to denounce him.
Ted, it's not honourable.
The hell with what's honourable.
I make you happy.
- No talk.
- I make you happy.
I make you happy.
You do love him.
You could have told me.
I never lied to you. Never.
You have a husband.
Put it on.
I left a note for Jean in French.
Come soon, I wrote. I hope it's right.
I need directions. I want a village
where we won't be recognised.
- You know some back roads.
- What are you doing?
Taking you on a date.
I want to go to a cafe.
I want people to see us together,
out in the open, no hiding.
I won't touch you.
I just want to be with you
to make it...
You are totally foolish!
Tell him thank you, and good luck.
She wished us luck, called us foolish,
and she thanked you.
This was stupid. We should go.
I didn't realise there'd be
an arrow pointed over my head.
- I am sorry.
- No. I'm the fool.
I pretended it was real.
I fell in love with another man's wife.
My punishment is that
I'll never be able to forget her.
We have the same punishment.
- Don't touch me. I'm covered in mud.
- It doesn't matter. You're alive!
- It wasn't wise to leave Delahaut.
- How are the others? Anthoine?
He was captured.
We should go.
Tell him to get in the back.
His name is Ted.
Please ride in the back of the truck.
My clothes don't suit him.
You must tell me the news.
We've heard so little.
We blew up all the old tunnels.
We blew up the bridges.
We did our job.
I've been to see Oomlop. I know
the American is leaving on Friday.
She's mistaken.
He leaves tonight.
You should have missed me
as much as you'll miss him.
You leave tonight.
- Hey, buddy.
- Home run.
No, run home.
I'm ready.
Tell him to eat.
We have to leave in 20 minutes.
You have to eat, quickly.
- Jean, help me prepare the truck.
- No.
Let the boy eat. You go ahead.
Tell me, Jean, what happened
while I was away?
- You can tell me. Don't be scared.
- Nothing.
All right, we'll swap stories.
I'll tell you about the Maquis,
the tunnels, the explosions.
You'll tell me what happened
during my absence.
You say nothing.
Henri, thank you for getting me out.
Why is he talking to me
whilst I'm talking to you?
What's this soldier got to hide from us?
I'll have to ask my wife.
That's what happened.
What does this mean?
Go ahead, tell him.
Henri will hide you in the back of
the truck until the exchange point.
You will take 15 steps into the dark
and say, "Courage".
- Courage.
- In French. Courage.
Courage.
Henri has your papers.
The couriers will explain the rest.
The chocolate?
You say "Courage"
and hand over the chocolate bar.
- My ticket.
- Your ticket home.
Have you told him everything?
- We will always be here, won't we?
- Yes, we will always be here.
Jean...
- Return.
- Sure, kid.
You bet. Retourner.
Come on.
Look at that! Cousins, friends.
Friends, my friends, all dead.
Dead for you!
And Dinant, the nurse... saved you!
And Philippe Jauquet. My friend.
The best.
All dead for you.
Dead.
For you!
Now hide!
Come on. Let's go.
- Courage.
I love you, Claire.
Courage.
Perhaps you don't understand.
We'll try again.
- Claire Daussois.
- How long have you been a Maquis?
Tell me your husband's name.
Tell me Henri's name.
He gave us the American.
He thought it was enough.
But we need to know
who killed the guards,
and what the codes were
that were on the plane.
Now it's your turn to talk.
Or would you rather see
what happens if you don't?
War makes cowards of us all.
What's wrong with you?
Was it worth it, Henri,
keeping your mouth shut?
I want names, addresses,
times when they will be at home,
their favourite recipes.
I know there is someone
sending messages,
someone we somehow overlooked.
Delahaut belongs to the Fuhrer.
We need to get the Belgian virus
out of its veins.
You can help, madame.
You can be Germany's nurse.
Be careful. She must not die... yet.
Let's go home, Major.
Let's see the wife, kids, girlfriend.
Let's go home.
One more time. Who are you?
Major Theodore Brice.
Who hid you in the town of Delahaut?
7216892...
What members of the Resistance
did you meet?
Major... Theodore... Brice...
You're starting to get to me, Major.
I'm wanting to end our sessions
permanently.
Why don't you come clean?
It will make you feel so much better.
37216892...
Okay, you'd rather dance.
Lean your head back. Lean back.
Take him to the infirmary
and stop him bleeding.
37216892...
Tell the captain I'm ready.
How do you feel?
You do realise that you're free?
You are free!
Thank you.
- Anthoine, I thought you were dead.
- Almost.
They did their best.
I got some groceries for the shop.
I'll come with you. I'm not ready
to see what's left of my house.
I heard... about Henri.
Yes.
How is Claire?
She has the boy, the farm is recovering.
She'll get by.
- The pilot?
- Killed by the Germans.
- But he was an officer.
- He gave them a false code.
And he lied about killing
the guards at the plane.
1lt wasn't him?
No.
- It's good to be home.
- Yes.
Yes.
Mother! I'm going flying.
- We will always be here, won't we?
- Yes, we will always be here.