* guide me, oh, oh
* thou great jeho-o-o-o-o-vah
[Crowd screaming]
* feed me till
Time to be
Whitney Houston.
You ready?
* I want no more
mm-hmm.
[Luther vandross'
"never too much" playing]
Man: It's one of music's
biggest nights.
Woman:
One of the more anticipated
arrivals this evening
Is that of Whitney Houston.
I'm here in downtown Los Angeles
at the shrine auditorium...
Woman: She's nominated tonight
for best R&B solo performance.
Man #2: In four short years,
She has sold
over 30 million albums,
Had seven number-one singles
in a row...
Now that's topping the Beatles,
the rolling stones,
And anyone else on the planet.
As you can hear
from the screams of the crowd,
She's stepping out now.
* I don't want nobody else
to ever love me *
* you are my shinin' star
* my guiding light,
my love fantasy *
* there's not a minute, hour,
day or night *
* that I don't love you
* you're at the top of my list
* 'cause I'm always
thinkin' of you *
* I still remember in the days
* when I scared to touch you
* how I spent my day dreamin'
* plannin' how to say
I love you *
* you must have known
that I had feelings *
* deep enough to swim in
* that's when you opened up
your heart *
* and you told me to come in
* oh, my lo-o-o-ve
[Crowd shouting]
* a thousand kisses from you
is never too mu-u-u-ch *
[Man chanting "Whitney!"]
* I just don't wanna stop
* too much,
never too much *
* never too much,
[Both laugh]
Hey!
Who you looking for
with your big-head self?
I'm looking for you
with your big-head self.
[Giggles] Oh, Cece!
So good to see you.
You look fabulous.
No, you do.
Now, hold on now.
Hold on now.
Now, I know I get
some of that love, right?
You know I save
the best for last, bebe.
Oh, whatever, girl.
Get over here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please take your seats.
The third annual
soul train awards
Will begin in two minutes.
You keep bumping that man,
he's gonna get mad.
Who, him? Oh.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Don't let it happen
again.
[Up-tempo music playing]
Three 1989
soul train nominations,
One a.M.A. Nomination,
Sold-out concert engagements
everywhere...
It's not hard to figure out
Who the hottest
young male solo artist is.
His name is Bobby brown!
["Every little step" plays]
Whoo! Unh!
Oh, yes.
It's me again, the crazy one.
* I can't sleep at night,
I toss and turn *
* listenin' for the telephone
* but when I get your call,
I'm all choked up *
* can't believe
you called my home *
* and as a matter of fact,
it blows my mind *
* you would even talk to me
* because a girl like you
is like a dream come true *
* a real-life fantasy
* no matter what your friends
try to tell ya *
* we were made to fall in love
* and we will be together,
any kind of weather *
* it's like that,
it's like that *
* every little step I take
* you will be there
* every little step I make
* we'll be together
* every little step I take
* you will be there
* every little step I make
* we'll be together
* I can't sleep at night,
I toss and turn *
* listenin' for the telephone
* but when I get your call,
I'm all choked up *
* can't believe
you called my home *
* and as a matter of fact,
it blows my mind *
* you would even talk to me
* because a girl like you
is like a dream come true *
* a real-life fantasy
* no matter what your friends
try to tell ya *
* we were made to fall in love
* we'll always be together,
any kind of weather *
* it's like that,
it's like that *
* gi-i-i-rl
* every little step I take
* yea-a-h
* you will be there
* every little step I make
* we'll be together
* togethe-e-r
* every little step I take
* every step
* you will be there
* every little step I make
* we will be togethe-e-e-e-e-r
* we'll be together
* every little step I make
* every little ste-e-p
* every little step I take
* ooh, no
* every little step I make
* every little step
* we'll be together, girl
[Cheers and applause]
Yeah.
I knew you was going right now.
I told you.
You knew? I knew.
Hello.
[Indistinct conversations]
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me.
I just wanted to say sorry
for being so rude earlier.
Nah, forget it.
I was just messin' with you.
All right.
Oh, I liked your moves
out there.
Yeah, well, if you ain't
got the voice, you
better have somethin'.
What? No, you've got
a great voice, too.
You're playin' me, right?
Why would you say that?
You're Whitney Houston.
Well... You don't see me
With a trophy in my hand
tonight, do you?
You deserved it.
No, come on.
I'm happy for my girl
Anita.
Anyway, people are tired
of seeing me get prizes.
I don't blame 'em.
Sometimes, even I get sick
of hearing about myself.
Wow, humble, too.
Well, listen, I don't give
a damn about award shows,
But I can't stand to lose.
Can I let you in
on a secret?
Sure.
Me either.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
that sounds more right.
Yeah. [Laughs]
Listen, I'm not sick
of hearing about you.
Are you a fan, then?
Oh, hell, yeah.
Someone'd have to be
deaf and blind not to be.
Whitney.
You're on in five.
All right.
Well, as of tonight,
I'm a Bobby brown fan.
Hey, hey, hold on.
Hold on a second.
If I was to ask you out,
you'd say yeah?
I don't know.
Why don't you
give it a shot?
Okay.
How about tomorrow?
Figured I'd hit rodeo drive
while I was in town.
Nippy,
you need us.
I'm at the Hilton.
Pick you up at noon.
[Camera shutters clicking]
* everybody's searching
for a hero *
* people need someone
to look up to *
* I never found anyone
who fulfilled my nee-e-e-ds *
* a lonely place to be
* and so I learned
to depend on me *
* I decided long ago
* never to walk
in anyone's shadows *
* if I fail, if I succeed
* at least I'll live
as I believe *
* no matter
what they take from me *
* they can't take away
my dignity *
* because the greatest
love of all *
* is happening to me-e-e-e-e-e
* I found the greatest
love of all *
* inside of me
* the greatest love of all-l-l
[Cheers and applause]
* is easy to achie-e-e-ve
* learning to love yourself
* it is the greatest
love of all *
* and if, by chance,
that special place *
* that you've been
dreaming o-o-o-o-of *
* leads you to a lonely place
* find your strength
* in lo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-ve
[Cheers and applause]
* here we go, here we go,
here we go, hey *
* I'll be right here with you,
make you wait *
* here we go, here we go,
here we go, hey *
* I'll be right here
[Bobby and Whitney laughing]
Bobby: Man,
I-i-it's amazing.
What is?
How much they love you.
It's great.
[Groans]
Sometimes I wish they'd love me
just a little bit less.
Please.
No, you don't.
Come on, seriously,
you got to be digging this.
What I don't dig
is people thinking
They know everything about me
when they don't.
Sure, but you don't want them
to forget about you, either.
Hey!
Eh, I guess not.
See? So it's worth it.
Come on.
Look around. Look where we are.
We are in
Beverly hills, baby!
Rodeo drive!
Hey, hey, hey, who...
Which one of y'all want a
picture with Bobby brown, huh?
Come on.
Come take your picture, girl.
Get your picture.
[Camera shutters clicking]
[Laughs]
Oh, thank you!
Thank you so much!
I can't believe this!
Yeah, thank you.
Oh!
How about one with Whitney, too?
What you say?
Show 'em maybe they don't know
you after all? Hmm?
[Chuckles]
* hey, I'll be right here
with you, make you wait *
You are amazing.
I love you so much.
Bye!
Bye! Bye! Bye!
Bobby:
Go buy that album!
Hi!
I didn't think
you'd make it.
I know.
Wheels up at 7:00.
Don't worry. I'm here.
[Sighs]
You didn't
have to do that.
I wanted to.
So, how was Bobby?
[Sighs] Nice.
He's funny.
Come on.
Open your present.
Oh, fine.
[Laughs]
Shut up.
Wow!
[Chuckles]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mm.
[Sighs]
I'm glad
to be going home.
[Chuckles]
[Upbeat music
playing through headphones]
Thank you.
[Music stops]
[Chuckles]
Yes.
* oooooh
* my heart sing
* all night long
* oooooh
* it ain't nothing
to me, baby *
* I'll give you what you want
because you *
* you got that love,
you got that lo-o-ve, baby *
* you got it
* you got that love,
you got that lo-o-ve, baby *
* can't get enough,
I need your to-o-uch, baby *
* you got that love, and you
give it to me all night *
* the way you do
that thing you do *
Hold on. Hold on.
Tell mama what Michael got you
for your birthday. Ohh!
Yeah. Mommy, a monkey.
[Laughter]
I'm like,
"what am I gonna do with that?!"
* but I know that this is more
than just a feeling, baby *
* they don't understand
this love *
* oooooh
* you make my heart sing
Bobby brown!
You made it!
Hi! I'm so glad.
Yeah, well, I was
in the neighborhood, you know.
[Both laugh]
Nah, truth is, I flew up
from Atlanta to be here.
Happy Birthday.
That's so sweet.
This place is huge.
Please tell me you don't
live here by yourself.
No, robyn lives with me.
Robyn?
Robyn. Rob...
Robyn!
He made it!
[Chuckles]
She's my best friend
since I was 16.
She runs my businesses.
Hey, how you doing?
Great party, darling.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, hey. Good to see you.
Happy Birthday, baby.
Anyway, we just moved in.
Been building it
for a while, and...
I bet you don't know
half of what's here.
I know I have a movie theater
and a recording studio and...
Woman: Now, you know I'm coming
to get a hug, girl!
Hey!
How you doing, girl?
Thanks for coming.
Happy Birthday.
You want a tour?
Man:
Happy Birthday, Whitney!
* you have just what I need
Hey.
Keep the party going.
* you... you...
* ohhhh
* you got that
* he-e-e-y
Wow!
I may have taken home the award
the night we met.
Looks like you robbed
the whole damn store.
Yeah, kind of an embarrassment
of riches, I guess.
Great setup.
[Sniffs] Yeah. Here.
Nah, I don't do that.
Really? Bobby brown?
[Chuckles] Look,
I'm not sayin' I don't party,
But I'd seen
too many bad outcomes,
And I worked too hard
to get where I am.
[Sniffs]
It's just for fun.
Come on.
Thanks.
I'll stick with this.
This is giving me a lot of ideas
for the studio I'm building.
[Gasps] That's right.
I heard you write
your own stuff.
Oh, I'd like
to do that someday.
Girl, why not?
You should never get
so big,
You can't mess around
with what you love.
Maybe we'll
write something together.
[Both chuckle]
Oh, you probably get people
saying that to you all the time.
No.
What I mostly get is songwriters
saying "sing my song."
Well, the way you belt it out,
yeah, "sing my song!"
Well, I get that
from this lady right here.
Mommy taught me pretty much
everything I know.
She was my choir director.
Oh, yeah, I been there.
What, you sang choir?
Since I was 3.
[Laughing] What?
Saw James brown singing gospel,
and after that, I was hooked.
But, you know,
teaching only goes so far.
It's you that won all this,
not your mama.
Hey, I bet
I must be the 100th guy
That's told you
how nice you look tonight.
Am I right?
Maybe a few more.
Well, they lied.
Yeah,
nice doesn't do it.
Up close, you're
so freakin' beautiful,
I can't stop
looking at you.
[Chuckles softly]
Most guys don't usually
follow up like that.
Truth is, sometimes I think
I scare men off.
Maybe they don't like
strong women.
Or maybe they just don't know
how to handle you...
Not like
Bobby brown would.
Oh, you sound
pretty sure of yourself.
[Chuckles]
I have to be.
I got no margin
for error.
Where I come from,
there's only two ways out...
Either dead or in jail.
I saw my best friend killed
in front of me when I was 11.
First thing I did
when I got some bank,
I bought my mama a house
in a real nice neighborhood.
I got a big family to take care
of, and I mean to do it.
Tell me about it.
Hold on.
[Chuckles]
"Sparkle"?
W-w-what?
You know it?
Hell, yeah, I know it.
It's a classic.
When that movie came out,
I must have seen it 20 times.
I mean, all the other
black movies
Were "super fly,"
"shaft," "the mack,"
And there was Irene Cara
just... Belting it out.
Yeah, Irene Cara.
She was somethin'.
Wasn't she?
[Chuckles]
What?
You're just
not what I expected.
You're not
what I expected, either.
Really?
Yeah.
I used to think that you were
some kind of goddess.
But now I can see
that you're way more than that.
I can see
that you're real.
Guess we should probably
head back out.
Your guests gonna start
to wonder where you went.
[Horn honks]
Bye-bye.
Hello!
[Chuckles]
How's my favorite star?
Doing good.
Should I get your usual
for lunch today, miss Houston?
Hamburger and fries.
Thank you, ruthie.
You got it.
[Chuckles]
Unh, unh, unh.
Not in my office.
Whitney, you need
to protect the voice.
And, uh...
Stay away from yellow.
What?
Yeah.
Seriously?
Makes you look like
a canary.
[Chuckles]
Now white...
Now, that's good for you.
Oh, and, by the way,
What's this I'm reading
about you and Eddie Murphy?
[Sighs]
We are just friends.
We went on
a couple of dates is all.
Anyway, there's someone else
I'm interested in now.
Mm?
Mm-hmm.
Just stay out
of my business, okay?
Fine. Fine.
So [Chuckles]
what's on your mind?
I want to talk about
the new album.
I was thinking
I'd like to give 'em
A little different
kind of flavor.
Whitney.
You are the greatest voice
of your generation
And the biggest star
on the planet.
I don't want to change
a winning formula.
Clive, you know I've always done
everything you've asked.
Now I'd like
to express myself
A little more
in the music.
I think my audience
can handle it,
And I know some of 'em
are looking for something new.
I tell you what.
I just brought a new team
into the arista family...
L.A. reid and babyface.
Maybe they can work
on the new album.
Those are the guys
that did Bobby brown's, right?
Exactly.
Yes! All right.
That's... that's
the flavor, right?
All right, yes, the flavor.
[Laughs]
You're a very sharp
young lady.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
In my canary yellow?
Eh, I forgive the yellow
for the face.
Oh, oh, okay.
[Both laugh]
Oh, my God.
When I was a kid,
all I wanted to do was sing.
You know, I used to hide out
in the basement
And dressed up
in my mommy's gowns
And sing along to a record
Pretending I was
my cousin dionne or aretha
Or Gladys
or something like that.
And daddy would be
pounding on the floor
Screaming at mommy,
"can't you stop that noise?!"
And that's when she made me
go sing in church.
She said,
"if you can do it for Gladys,
You can do it for the lord."
[Laughs]
I used to dance
to Michael.
I used to put glitter
all over my sneakers.
I put so much on,
You couldn't even tell
what brand they were.
[Both laugh]
My mom
used to get so mad.
She'd say,
"Robert barisford brown, boy,
Now I know them ain't the shoes
I bought you last week."
Okay. [Laughs]
But I thought
I was pretty fly.
You're still pretty fly.
It's easy
to talk to you.
You too.
All right.
Break it to me gently.
I heard you have kids.
[Chuckles] Two.
I love 'em.
And I take care of
my responsibilities for 'em.
But back then,
I had no idea what I wanted.
A case of the big head being led
by the little one, I guess.
Where are they now?
Boston.
With their moms.
I go see 'em,
spend time with 'em.
I never want 'em
not to be in my life.
They mean everything to me.
And I need
to do right by 'em.
That scare you off?
You see me running?
[Lennox buppy brown's
"she's hot" playing]
She's on fire!
Yeah! And oba simba and buppy
come to call around.
Unh!
* ra-pa-pa
* ah-ah
[Scatting]
* so, from the very first time
* I saw your face, girl
* I thought
you were a shy girl *
* quiet and easy
* so, when I saw you
last night *
* mashing up the place, girl
* I could not believe
* what I have seen
* I like the way you bubble
and a wine down low *
* a wiggle and a tease
like you a dance gogo *
* little bit short a knee
and when me turn let's go *
* baby, I like your flow
* because you're hot
* girl
* with the body you've got
* you out Fe give me
heart attack *
* you make it stop, go bup bup
* and start go bu dup dup
* hey, yeah, baby, you're hot
* girl
* with the body you've got
Man:
But behind the voice of soul
Lies a heart of gold.
Whitney's many humanitarian
efforts and contributions
Have helped countless people
in need.
We realize that we're
in the presence
Of someone truly special.
You can say that again.
Hi, I'm Eddie Murphy.
I'm here on the set of my
new picture, "another 48 hrs.,"
And I had to take time to
congratulate you, Whitney,
For being the recipient of the
Frederick d. Patterson award,
And for all
the beautiful things
You've done for
the united negro college fund.
Also some personal things, too,
I've wanted to say
And a lot of things
I wanted to do
But never got the chance.
So, on a night like tonight,
I wanted to do them
in the presence of everyone.
So if you could just walk
up to the screen?
I'll wait.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Come on.
I just want to kiss you, baby.
[Laughs]
[Laughter]
[Chuckles]
I swear I didn't know
he was gonna do that.
Nah, it's no problem.
Oh, my God.
You're jealous.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
Why the hell
would I be jealous?
Oh, don't be like that.
I think it's cute.
Be serious. I got girls, okay...
Any girl I want.
Eddie Murphy
wishes he was me.
[Mockingly] Oh, I got girls.
Any girl I want. [Laughs]
You better watch out.
I'm serious.
Oh, yeah? Or what?
What you gonna do?
I'll do whatever.
Oh, yeah?
I'd like to see you try.
I'm really
gonna get you, then!
Not if I get you first!
You're not gonna get nobody.
I'm gonna get you first.
[Laughs]
I'm not even ticklish.
Yeah, you are, right here.
And right here.
What about... ohh!
Ohh!
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
Damn.
Oh, God.
I can't keep up with you.
Mm, baby, you don't have to.
Just let me do all the work.
[Both laugh]
Mm.
Bobby...
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
Oh, come on.
I got to get my rest.
I got to be up early.
I just can't help myself
around you.
You're just
so damn beautiful.
And thinking of all them guys
who would kill to be who I am,
Baby, I just get so damn horny,
I just [Chuckles]
Is that
what this is about?
Oh, hell, no.
Before I met you, I didn't
even know I could feel this way.
Mm.
What do you say, hmm?
Hmm?
You and me?
Let's move and make this
more permanent.
Didn't you hear
what I said?
I-I can't, Bobby.
I'm sorry.
I thought
we were getting serious.
Yeah, we are.
Then I don't get it.
It's just...
It's just happening so fast.
This is
all new to me.
So what are you saying,
you want to see other guys?
No. I just...
I-I don't know
how to be sure this is real.
You don't think
my feelings for you are real?
Bobby, no,
it's not about you.
It's me.
[Sighs]
When I was 15,
mommy put me in this...
This catholic girls' school,
And I was so shy and those girls
were so cruel to me.
In all those years,
I only made one friend... robyn.
It just... it takes me
a long time to,
You know, to give
that kind of trust.
I just thought we could keep
this casual, you know,
For a while longer.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, I got
a problem with that.
Hmm?
I love you too much.
[Sighs]
Bobby...
Wha... Bobby?
[Chuckling] Come back to bed.
Bobby, come on.
I'm not playing games
with you.
I love you. Straight up.
If you don't feel the same,
this ain't gonna work.
[Keys jingling]
Bobby, wh...
[Door opens]
[Sighs]
[Engine turns over, revs]
[Sniffing]
["I'm your baby tonight"
playing]
* unh, unh
* mm-mm-mm
* yeah-eee
* yeah-eeeee
* from the moment I saw you,
I went outta my mind *
* though I never believed
in love at first sight *
* but you got a magic, boy,
that I just can't explain *
* well, you got a, you got a way
that you're makin' me feel *
* I can do, I can do anything
for you, baby *
* I'll be down for you, baby
* lay all my cards out tonight
* just call on me, baby
* I'll be there in a hurry
* it's your move, so, baby
* baby, decide
* whatever you want from me
* I'm givin' you everything
* I'm your baby tonight
* you've given me ecstasy
* you are my fantasy
* I'm your baby tonight
* from the second you
touched me, I was ready to die *
* I've never been fatal,
you're my first time *
* I feel like an ange-e-l,
who just started to fly *
* well, you got a, you got a way
that you're makin' me feel *
* I can do, I can do anything
for you, baby *
* I will fly for you, baby
* hold on and enjoy the ride
* I'm not in no hurry
* we can fly all night, baby
* it's your move, now, baby
* baby, let's fly
* whatever you want from me
* I'm givin' you everything
* everything
* I'm your baby tonight
* I'm your baby
* you've given me ecstasy
* ecstasy
* you are my fantasy
* fantasy
* I'm your baby tonight
* I'll be your baby,
I'll be yo-o-o-ur, yeah *
* whatever you want from me
* I'm givin' you everything
* everything
* I'm your baby tonight
* said I'm your baby
* you've given me ecstasy
* ecstasy
* you are my fantasy
* fantasy
* I'm your baby tonight
* I'll be your baby
I'll be yo-o-o-ur, yeah *
* you know, boy
* eh, ooh
[Laughing]
Babyface: Yeah!
All right!
Wow! Wow!
I never thought our stuff
could sound that good.
You really do have
the magic voice.
Thank you.
[Giggles]
I like to
come out kickin'!
Yeah. Yeah.
[Laughs]
So, clive says you're
the writer of the team.
Yeah, yeah.
I-I write
a lot of the stuff.
You are lucky.
Why's that?
Just to be able
to express yourself this way.
I owe it to love.
Really?
Yeah.
Growing up,
I was always in love.
But I was just too shy
to ever tell anyone.
And when I tried to,
I'd just... Freeze up.
So, somehow, writing it
in a song opened me up.
Yeah, that...
That's exactly how I feel.
It's only onstage I can really
let go and be myself.
Yeah.
[Chuckles] Yeah.
It's a crazy business.
And we're all crazy in it.
Mm-hmm.
[Both laugh]
So, uh, what do you say?
Take another shot at it?
Let's do it.
All right.
Hey.
You know Bobby brown
pretty well, don't you?
Yeah.
What was he like
when you first met him?
Wild. Ambitious.
Um... Talented as hell.
But underneath,
you could see
That there was
another side to him.
He was smart, warm.
He just needed to find
a way to express himself.
I mean,
don't get me wrong.
He's crazy
like the rest of us,
But fundamentally,
he's a good person.
[Door slides closed]
I'm ready.
[Laughs] Let's do it.
Sister: Theatrical makeup
is terrible for my face, mama.
Effie: Sister...
Baby...
He's just gonna drag you...
To the gutter with him.
Gutter?
Mm-hmm.
How can you say that?
He's as big-time
as you can get!
As you can get!
I've lived in Harlem
I my life.
[Inhales sharply]
I do know a rat
when I see one.
You don't understand, mama.
You don't understand.
Well...
I said my piece.
I'm going home.
[Door opens]
[Inhales sharply,
sobs]
[Cellphone ringing]
Yeah?
Whitney: Bobby?
Whitney,
it's been a while.
What's up?
I miss you.
I miss you, too, baby.
[Exhales softly]
Where are you?
Down in Atlanta?
No. No. Boston.
Why, you want me
to come over?
[Laughs]
What, from Boston?
I could be down
in four hours.
Don't be crazy.
Too late.
Where you going?
Something came up.
Mm-hmm, I bet it did.
Oh, don't be that way.
I'll catch you later.
You're going to her,
aren't you?
And what about
laprincia?
You know I always
take care of my own.
Hey.
[Smooches]
It's never
gonna work, Bobby.
You know that.
[Door opens, closes]
[Sighs, smooches]
[Laughs]
["Tracks and lines"
by Eric Clapton plays]
Ohh!
I can't believe you came!
Come on! Come on!
[Giggling]
Here you go, baby.
I make love and make eggs.
[Chuckles]
What's wrong, baby?
What's the matter?
You weren't alone
last night, were you?
Bobby, come on.
Don't lie to me.
[Silverware clatters]
You're right.
[Sighs]
I was with Kim.
Oh, see, you said
you were done with that.
Look, I am done with that, okay?
Totally done with that.
Baby, listen,
it's just...
[Sighs]
Look, baby.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay?
It's just I thought
you didn't want me no more.
And I get lonely
without you.
You are the one I love.
You know that.
You're the one I want.
The only one.
You're my baby. You're my woman.
You are my heart, hmm?
Give it to me.
Mm.
So, what are you
gonna do?
[Sighs] I think
he's planning to propose.
Is that a good thing?
He makes me laugh.
You know,
he's a family man.
He loves me.
I know that.
And I love him.
I don't want
to lose this chance.
But?
[Sighs]
I don't know.
"I don't know."
Nippy, you always know.
I'm afraid
of making a mistake.
You know, the worst day of my
life was when daddy left mommy.
I don't want
that to happen to me.
And I know it's gonna upset
a lot of people.
What's in your heart?
That's what
you should follow.
Follow your heart.
What do you say?
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah. [Laughs]
I mean, really?
Yes! Yes!
Well, in that case...
Bobby!
[Laughs]
No, no, no, come on back.
Come on.
[Gasps]
[Both laugh]
What, you thought
I was gonna marry you
With that cheap
piece of crap?
I can't believe
you punked me like that!
I had to make sure you weren't
marrying me for my money.
[Both laugh]
Oh.
[Gasps, laughs]
I love me some you.
Mm.
Me too.
Girl, let me
hear you say it.
Why?
You already know I do.
I ain't gonna believe it
till I hear it.
I love you, Bobby.
Say it some more.
I love you, I love you, I love
you, I love you, I love you!
I love you.
I love you,
and I want to have kids
And have
a happy, normal life.
Me too, baby,
more than anything.
Mwah!
[Singsong voice]
I'm gonna be Mrs. Bobby brown!
[Squeals]
We're getting married.
We getting married.
[Laughs]
Michael:
And then there was Miami...
[Laughter]
No!
Okay! Okay!
I won't say anything!
I can't tell y'all
anything!
So,
what's the big mystery?
Nope.
We have to wait on daddy.
He's coming, too?
Yes.
Is everything all right?
Couldn't be better.
[Door opens]
Michael: Hey. Hey pops.
John.
Daddy!
Nippy! [Laughs]
Ah, don't you
look beautiful.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Mommy's here.
Ah. Oh.
How you doing?
Uh, uh, Monique.
Hey, how are ya?
Whose heart are you breaking?
Mine. [Laughs]
Oh, of course.
I knew that.
Okay, everybody,
before we have lunch,
I have
an announcement to make.
Oh, here she goes.
[Laughter]
[Singsong voice]
I'm getting married.
[All shouting]
Who gonna marry you,
nippy?!
Hush up, son.
Let me see! Let me see!
[Gasps]
I just hope
it's not Bobby brown.
[Shouting stops]
It is.
I spent my life trying to keep
you and your brothers
Out of the projects.
Now you marrying
into them?
He's not in them anymore.
Don't believe it.
You can take the boy
out the ghetto,
But not the ghetto
out the boy.
Nippy, he's got kids.
Yeah, by
two different women.
And he's a good father
to them.
And the point is,
we love each other very much.
And I don't want anything
To stand in the way
of our happiness.
I thought y'all
would be happy for me.
Whitney, this is not right,
and I think you know that.
You've always been
stubborn,
But now you're
only hurting yourself.
You already had Gary
when daddy married you.
That was different,
and you know it was.
Why is it always different
when it comes to me?
Whitney!
Nippy!
Where were you?
Are you happy now?
Oh, am I happy now?
You do this all the time.
Where were you?
You're head of security.
All right, all right,
all right.
Just take it easy.
We'll figure this out.
She's still our baby.
Michael:
Nice, mom. Real nice.
[Door unlocks]
[Gasps] Hey, baby.
Why you sittin'
in the dark?
What's wrong, Bobby?
Hmm?
What is it?
She pregnant.
Who is?
Kim.
Kim?
Baby, I can explain this.
No! I don't want
to hear this.
Whitney! Wait.
Baby, wait!
No! No!
Whitney!
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
Please!
No, you tell me this after
I tell my family!
I just found out,
I swear!
No, you don't need that, okay?
You have me. I'm here!
I don't have you.
She has you.
You're gonna have two kids
with her now?!
Look, this happened before
we got back together!
I trusted you.
But you have
nothing to worry about.
I'm not going back to her.
Well, you should!
No, listen,
I'm not going back to her.
That'd be unfair
to all of us.
Okay? I love you.
This changes nothing.
How can you say that?
Because it's true.
You've been with her
since you were 11.
You obviously
still love her.
She has no hold
on me anymore.
She's pregnant!
I'd say that's a hold.
I'll take care
of my baby, okay?
I always take care of my kids.
You know that!
[Sniffing]
But I ain't got to be with her
to do that.
Please! Listen to me!
I cannot stand the thought
of losing you!
Mnh-mnh,
Whitney, please!
Please!
Why? Come on. Why?
Bobby, don't you get it?
[Voice breaking] I wanted
to be the one to have your baby.
Me!
You will.
As soon as you can,
whenever you are ready.
I promise you she will
never come between us.
No one will, ever.
Unless we let them.
Bobby, listen to me.
I'm putting everything
on the line...
My career, everything.
For the first time,
I'm putting myself first,
And I'm choosing you.
I need this to be real.
It is real.
Forever.
I swear.
[Breathing deeply]
[Sniffles]
How'd last night's show go?
Girl, you mean tonight's show.
It's 3:00 A.M. Here.
I love
these Japanese people.
They don't come
to criticize you, you know?
Just to have a good time
and get they money's worth.
Oh, and Carol opening for me,
too, she knocked 'em dead.
Aww, your little sister
did good, huh?
Yeah, she gonna be huge.
But how's my baby doin'?
Baby, I am beat.
We worked last night till
5:00 A.M.,
Still got more to get.
Had to shut down for two hours
'cause there was
Some kind of problem
with the power in the building.
And I'm going into
the studio tomorrow
To record some more
of the album.
Clive thinks
"the bodyguard" soundtrack's
Gonna be bigger
than the movie.
Listen, you just make sure you
get yourself some rest.
Yeah, and Kevin's
been real good to me,
Real supportive...
And not just of the acting.
[Chuckles]
I can't imagine how beautiful
this baby's gonna be
With you as her mother.
Hey, you're not
bad-looking yourself.
Nothin' like you, baby.
[Chuckles]
Hey, you make sure you
don't do anything you're
uncomfortable with, okay?
Don't strain yourself.
I won't.
[Knock on door]
Oh, they're calling for me now.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Oh, hey, you remind Kevin...
Hmm?
No tongue.
[Chuckles]
Well, you just stay away
From all those
little geishas out there.
I don't want to hear
any rumors.
Baby, you are
all the woman I need.
[Knocking continues]
[Sighs]
[Smooches] I love you.
Come in.
[Door opens]
Ready for you on set,
Ms. Houston.
All right.
[Gasping]
Whoa, are you...
Are you all right?
Aah.
Ms... Ms. Houston?
We need the medic.
We need the medic
to Ms. Houston's makeup
trailer right now.
It's all right. It's all right.
Medic, what's your 20?
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
Nippy?!
[Sobbing] Mommy!
Mommy, I'm in here.
Shh. Shhhh.
[Sobbing]
It's okay.
Baby. Hey.
Shh.
The lord has his plans.
When the time is right,
it will happen.
Shh! Shh!
Now, you drink that up.
It's chamomile.
That'll be good for you.
Thank you, mommy.
[Sighs]
You always
come through for me.
I should not have taken
this gig.
No, that had nothing
to do with it.
Maybe it was a sign.
A chance to rethink things
a little.
You mean
with the movie?
No, I mean with Bobby.
Mommy, you have to stop
judging him.
I know trouble
when I see it.
Mommy, you don't know Bobby,
not like he really is.
I know what I know.
I been around
a lot longer than you.
Yes, and you taught me
everything I know.
But I am a grown woman now,
and I'm going my own way.
[Voice breaking]
I need your support.
I love him.
He loves me.
I think
you're making a mistake.
Then you should go!
If you can't accept my man,
you can't accept me!
[Sighs deeply]
Where is she?
Bobby!
Bobby: Baby!
[Sobbing]
Baby, baby, I came
as soon as I could!
Oh, baby, I'm here.
I'm here.
Baby, are you okay?
[Crying] I'm so sorry.
Oh, shh, shh.
[Smooches] Shh. Come here.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
Ohh, baby.
Oh, Bobby, I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry about that.
Come here. Come here.
Everything's
gonna be okay.
gonna be okay, baby.
I promise.
I wanted this baby
so bad.
I know you did.
We both did.
But we'll get another chance.
Don't worry.
If we did it once,
we can again.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come here.
Bobby, take me home.
I don't feel good
being here.
No, you can't quit now.
Too many people
are depending on you.
I should just
stick to music.
That's...
That's how people know me.
That's what
they love me for.
Now, you listen to me.
That movie's gonna
go through the roof.
And it's perfect
for you.
There's not another part
like it out there...
A leading role opposite
the biggest star in America,
And it's for
a black woman?
Baby, you got
to stick with it.
And not just for you,
you understand?
And I'm gonna
stay with you.
W-what about
your record tour?
I'll cancel
the rest of it.
Bobby, no.
Hey, who's
king of stage?
You think you should?
You think I can't take
a little break from my fans
And still come back
stronger than ever?
Well, w-what about
your label?
Oh, forget about them.
I already made them
enough money.
I got my woman
to take care of.
I love you.
[Sighs]
Come here.
Come here. I got you.
[Mendelssohn's "wedding march"
plays]
Officiant:
You may all be seated.
Let us pray.
Our father, love has been
Your richest and greatest gift
to the world.
Love between a man and woman
which matures into marriage
Is one of your most beautiful
types of loves.
Today, we celebrate
that love.
Let everyone say amen.
All: Amen.
[D.J. Zeta's "final call for
endangered species" playing]
Officiant:
What God has brought together,
let no man tear asunder.
Now?
Not now.
[Laughter]
I now pronounce you husband
and wife, wife and husband.
[Laughs]
You may now salute your bride.
[Cheers and applause]
Whitney:
She's so beautiful!
And she looks like
her daddy.
Bobby:
She looks just like you.
[Sighs]
I want
so many more with you.
Me too, baby.
[Infant cries]
It's okay, honey.
It's okay,
Bobbi Kristina.
Yeah!
That's your name!
Mm-hmm.
We love you, baby.
And no touring,
like we promised.
I just want to stay home
and be a mom and wife.
Hmm. You've earned
that right, baby.
[Sighs]
Yeah.
[Crying]
Thank you. Thank you.
Shh.
Thank you.
And then
that's how we do it.
[Gasps] Aww.
Is this the room
of the proud mama?
[Laughs]
Oh, I-i hope I'm
not interrupting anything.
No, come in.
Oh, I didn't bring
any flowers.
I figured
you already had enough.
[Laughs]
But I brought you
something better.
Look at this.
"I will always love you"
16 weeks at the top
of the billboard charts.
Wow!
It's never
been done before.
We're gonna have to
start thinking about the tour.
I'm not thinking about touring
right now, clive.
Oh, of...
No, of course not.
You... you need
to rest up.
We won't even talk about it
for a few weeks.
Weeks?
Not weeks, clive.
At least two years.
[Chuckles]
Two years is
a long time, Whitney.
I'm not changing my mind.
Sure. Let's not
talk about it right now.
Oh, God.
That is one
beautiful kid, huh?
She sure is!
You've done good.
She's precious.
[Telephone ringing]
Whitney: That's my milk.
That's my milk.
Give it up. Give it up.
[Both laugh]
Uh, it's clive Davis.
Oh.
Uh, it's
for Mr. brown.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, this is Bobby.
Sure, that's fine.
See you then.
What'd he want?
For me to come by tomorrow.
When?
At 3:00.
Did he say why?
No... But...
You heard
the way he reacted
When he heard that song
we wrote for my album.
I bet he wants
to sign me.
W-w-what about
your mca contract?
You know, clive can take care
of all that, no problem.
What did I tell you, huh?
Babies bring good luck.
Hmm?
I got a little good luck.
I got a big good luck.
[Chuckles]
* get money
Unh!
Having a good day?
So far.
Good. Me too.
Mr. brown?
Mr. Davis is ready to see you.
Unh!
Get money *
* get money
thanks for coming in.
Not a problem, clive.
Hey. [Chuckles]
Uh, drink?
* get money
always.
Please, have a seat.
Unh!
Well, what about
that Whitney, huh?
[Chuckles]
I mean, who knew she'd become
a movie star, too, huh?
[Both chuckle]
I'm, uh [Clears throat]
sure you've heard
About the offers
that are coming her way.
She's the highest paid actress
in Hollywood.
Yeah, it's pretty amazing.
[Chuckles]
Indeed, it is.
Thank you.
I swear, I'm gonna lose her
to the movie business.
[Chuckles]
But you...
You must be thrilled.
You're a new dad.
You're a husband to a superstar.
I am.
Well, you should be.
You are a very lucky man.
Yes.
Listen, Bobby.
[Clears throat]
I can turn
"the bodyguard"
Into the biggest-selling
motion-picture soundtrack album
Of all time.
But... In order to do that,
Whitney needs to tour.
And I need an ally
to convince her of that.
I made a promise, clive.
Oh, sure, sure. Of course.
A promise is a promise.
Only... Things change.
I mean, you know
the ups and downs
This business
can deal you.
Make her see reason,
Bobby.
This is her time.
Don't let it pass her by.
Is this why
you wanted to see me?
Of course. What else?
[Chuckles]
Look, promise me
you'll think about what I said.
Yeah.
All right. That's fair enough.
[Chuckles]
Oh, by the way, I heard mca
is releasing a new album.
Yeah. Well,
a compilation disc.
Compilation disc, huh?
That's fantastic.
Yes.
Good for you.
Mr. Davis,
your 3:30 is here.
Oh, that's right.
And, also, these are the proofs
for the cover art
That Alan needs you to sign
right away.
Oh, okay.
One, two, or three.
Yeah.
I'm... Not sure.
Oh, Bobby,
thanks for stopping by
And think about
what we talked about, okay?
I think, uh... Two.
Two.
* mmmm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm
* mmmm-mm-mm-mmmm
* mmmm-mm-mm
man:
What can I get you?
Give me a vodka straight up.
Man: You got it.
Make it a double.
Sure.
* little ones, to him belong
* they are weak
Give me another.
Coming up.
* but he is strong
* mmmm-mm-mm-mm-mmmm
* yes, Jesus loves me
* oh, yes, Jesus loves me
* yes
Bobby.
Why are you so late?
Stopped off
to get a drink.
It's all good.
So, what did clive say?
Oh.
You know. [Sighs]
I'm locked in at mca.
What did he want, then?
For me to convince you
to go on tour,
Promote
"the bodyguard" album.
And he went to you.
He's not wrong.
It's your time,
and yo time is our time.
All of ours.
Who's... w-who's gonna
take care of her?
You'll be there for krissi,
I'll be there for you.
We'll travel with you,
both of us, everywhere you go.
What about
your next album?
It's just
a compilation disc.
It's no big deal.
[Sighs]
[Crowd shouting]
Man: Stand back.
[Cheers and applause]
Go on back. Stand back.
Man:
Whitney, I love you!
Whitney, Whitney!
Hey!
Please sign this!
I'd be happy to show you
to your room, Ms. Houston.
It's Mrs. brown,
and you can talk to me.
Yes, sir.
You got that?
I love you!
I'm your biggest fan ever!
Whitney! Whitney!
Wait! Wait!
What was it like
kissing Kevin costner?!
Whitney, what was it like
kissing him?!
Ahh! Whitney!
Bobby: Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
You need to get up.
[Babbling]
What time is it?
It's nearly 7:00.
Come on.
Okay.
* ooh, oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh
* mm-mmmm
[Squeals]
* he-e-e-e-e-e-e-y
I'm coming.
I'm coming!
* whatever you want
Whoo!
* whatever you nee-e-e-d
* anything you want done, baby
* I'll do it, naturally
* 'cause I'm every woman
* every woman
* it's all in me-e-e-e-e-e-e-e
* it's all in me-e-e-e-e-e-e
[Crowd chanting "Whitney!"]
* ye-e-ah
* I'm every woman
* it's all in me
* anything you want done, baby
* I do it naturally
* whoa, whoa, whoa-oa-oa
* I can cast a spell
* with secrets you can't tell
* mix a special brew
* put fire inside of you
* anytime you feel
danger or fear *
* then instantly I will appear
* 'cause I'm every woman
* it's all in me
* anything you want done, baby
* I do it, naturally
* whoa, whoa, whoa-oa-oa
* I can sense your needs
* like rain on to the seeds
* I can make a rhyme
of confusion in your mind *
* and when it comes down to
some good old-fashioned love *
* I got it, I got it
* I got it, got it,
got it, baby *
* I'm every woman
* it's all in me
* anything you want done, baby
* I do it naturally
* whoa, whoa, whoa-oa-oa
* I'm every woman
* it's all in me
* I can read your thoughts
right now *
* every one from "a" to "z"
* whoa, whoa, whoa-oa-oa
* I ain't braggi-i-i-n'
* 'cause I'm the one
* just ask me
* ooh, it shall be done
* don't bother
* to compare
* I've got it
* I-i-i-i-I've got it
* whoa, whoa, whoa-oa-oa
* ohh, yeah, yeah
* got it, got it, got it, yeah
* whoa, whoa, whoa-oa-oa
* ohhhhhhhhhhh
* ahhhh, ahhhh
* ohh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
* I'm every woman
* every woman, baby
* ooh
* I'm every woman
* every woman, baby
* ohh-oh-oh-oh
* I'm every woman
* every woman, baby
* ooh-ooh-ooh
* I'm every woman
* every woman, baby
* ohh-oh-oh-oh-oh
* I'm every woman
Chaka Khan.
Chaka Khan!
* I'm every woman
Whoo!
* ohh
Longer.
* I'm every woman
* whoo-ooh, whoo-ooh-ooh
* I'm every woman, woman, baby
* I'm every woman
* all right
* ooh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
[Cheers and applause]
[Chuckles]
Thank you.
Whew!
For my last song...
I'd like to bring out
a very special guest,
One who it is my honor
to have traveling with me,
The one, the only
original king of R&B,
My husband, Mr. Bobby brown!
[Cheers and applause]
[Laughs]
Y'all ready to party
or what?
Mwah!
Me and my baby
got something in common.
We got
something in common.
Let's show 'em
what we got, baby.
1, 2, 3.
[Dance music plays]
* get off my back,
get off my back *
[Indistinct conversations]
* get off my back,
get off my back *
Yo, what's happening?
* ain't no other way to live
my life, but like a superstar *
* I love it fast, ladies,
that's why I got this supercar *
* sunglasses in the night,
I come and run the city *
* my music so loud,
I brought my TV *
* I pay my dues right,
I guess it's only right *
baby, hold this for me.
* go buy the bar
and tip c-notes all night *
* so, here we are,
put your bottoms up *
come on, let's go on
the dance floor.
* I want a bad chick in a
t-shirt that say "models suck" *
Peace out, Bobby.
Yeah.
[R&B music playing]
Sheryl: Bobby?
Bobby!
Hey.
It's sheryl.
You don't remember me?
You pulled me onstage
at one of your concerts
A few years back,
and we danced together.
And then we sort of
hung out after.
[Chuckles]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, right. Mm-hmm.
I heard the new album.
I seriously don't know
why it's not bigger.
Eh. [Chuckles]
And I loved the song
you and Whitney wrote for it.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
That was such a nice way
to end her concert,
The two of you
singing it together.
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
Anyway, it's good to see
you onstage again.
Even if it is
with another woman.
[Chuckles]
Hey, so, um,
you busy right now?
That ain't me.
Oh, no?
So, who are you now?
Mr. Houston?
* and the party don't stop
until we leave the club *
* believe that
* party don't stop
until we leave the club *
until the sun come up *
* bodies everywhere,
hands in the air *
* we can feel the love
in the atmosphere *
* party don't stop
until the sun... *
* to all my neighbors,
you got much flavor *
* this is how we do it
* let's flip the track,
bring the old school back *
* this is how we do it
* this is how we do it,
all hands are in the air *
* and wave them
from here to there *
* if you're an o.G. Mack
or a wannabe player *
* you see the hood's
been good to me *
* every since I was
a lower-case "g" *
* but now I'm a big "g,"
the girls see I got the money *
* $100 bills, y'all
* if you were from where
I'm from, then you would know *
* that I gotta get mine
in a big black truck *
* you can get yours in a '64
* whatever it is,
the party's under way *
* so tip up your cup
and you throw your hands up *
* and let me
hear the party say *
* I'm kinda buzzed,
and it's all because *
* this is how we do it
* South central does it
like nobody does *
* this is how we...
Whitney: Mm.
Gimme, gimme,
gimme, gimme, gimme.
[Inhales deeply]
[Exhales deeply]
[Moaning]
Baby, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
What? What is it?
Hmm?
What?
I'm not going on
the rest of the tour with you.
What?
Are you mad at me?
No.
Hmm?
No. No. No. No.
It's all good.
It's just this is your thing.
You don't need me.
I need to get to work
on my new album.
No, you promised
you'd stay with us.
That's the whole reason
I agreed to do this tour.
Look, and it was
the right thing to do.
It's just it's a lot of time
for me not to work.
My fans are looking
for the next one.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, Bobby.
No, listen.
Listen. Listen.
You don't know.
You don't write.
You don't know
what it's like
Being away from the studio
all this time.
Well, you can write
on the road.
It's too distracting.
[Sighs]
It's gonna be fine.
Everything's
gonna be fine.
No, not really, Bobby.
I-I-i don't want
to be alone.
Look, you're not.
You got lots of people
looking out for you.
They're not you.
I need you
with me, Bobby.
I know you do, baby.
But what I need...
Is to go.
[Sighs]
Woman: Laface records.
Mr. reid's office.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, this is Bobby.
Checking to see
if L.A. got the message.
Yes, I'm sorry,
Mr. brown.
He's still in...
yeah, you said that
the last time I called.
Yes, I did.
Look, well, that's a hell
of a long session.
You just tell him Bobby brown's
got some brand-new licks
That's about blow his mind!
I would be...
[Cellphone slams]
[Lighter clicks]
[Cellphone rings]
Hell, yeah.
It's about time!
Steve: Sup, man?
You were expecting me to call?
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
Someone else.
When'd you get out?
A couple weeks ago.
Been trying to get ahold of you.
Guess you're too much
of a big shot now, huh?
Nah, man, it ain't like that.
I just been workin'.
Well, take a break
and come see your homey.
I'm at the palladium.
Got some fans here,
all hot and bothered
To meet
the real Bobby brown.
Give me an hour.
* nothing holds you back now
Get us another bottle of this
here and keep it flowin'.
That all right, Bobby?
Hell, yeah. I got this.
Mmm.
You want to dance?
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah.
We'll be there in a minute.
Okay.
Why don't you two ladies
go dance together,
Show us what you got, huh?
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
You a married man now, huh?
Yeah? What's that like?
[Sighs]
Not all it's cracked up to be.
That's for sure.
Come on. You got the hottest fox
on the planet.
She's a'ight.
She's a'ight?
Hey!
What?
[Indistinct conversation]
Hey!
Did they come with you?
Bobby.
You paying
for their drinks?
Bobby!
Nah, I didn't think so.
Now step off.
Look, I didn't mean
no disrespect.
Like hell
you didn't mean nothing!
Yo, Bobby!
Bobby! Bobby! Bobby!
Stay cool, bro!
Stay cool!
Don't tell me to stay cool!
Tell him to stay cool.
Come on, man.
You all wound up, bro.
You need to relax.
Come on.
Which one you like?
Take your pick.
Look, man, I don't mind
dreamin' about it,
But I don't do that
no more.
What happened
while I was in the joint, man?
You go soft on me?
Nah.
It's just
Whitney wouldn't like it.
[Laughs]
Do you see her anywhere?
I mean,
the opportunity is now.
You got to do
what's right for you.
You know,
I've hardly written anything
Since I been with her.
Oh?
It used to come easy.
Yeah, writer's block.
Writer's block, boy.
Yeah, easy. I got something
that make it come easy.
Here, got a little snow
for you.
I got just the cure.
Mm-hmm.
Me first.
Me first, bro.
[Sniffs]
[Laughs]
Go on. Get you some.
Yeah.
[Both sniff]
Matter of fact,
get you two.
And I'll take the fourth.
You got to stay
with your roots, boy.
Got to stay with your roots.
That's where the fire is.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Yeah, screw... screw reid!
Screw reid, huh?
I'mma get out there
and make him hear my sh...
There you go! There you go!
That's the Bobby I grew up with!
Yeah. Okay.
What's up?
[Laughs]
That's my boy.
You home now!
This is what
I needed tonight.
You home now.
Yeah.
Hey, you gonna save some
for me?
Slow down with it.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, me like.
[Laughs]
As a matter of fact,
as a matter of fact...
Come on up here
with that sweet Booty.
She doing Bobby.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
That's so great, Bobby.
I knew he would.
Yeah, okay, I love you.
Good news, honey?
Bobby's going
to meet with L.A. reid
To talk about a new album.
[Gasps]
Aunt bae,
I want to use the break
To go to Los Angeles
and surprise Bobby.
[Chuckles]
Please, can you keep krissi
for a few days?
Of course.
I'm happy for Bobby.
Oh, good, yay!
[Singsong voice]
Mommy's going to see daddy.
And she's gonna tell him
how much we love him
And how much we miss him,
okay?
Yay!
Woman: God ain't no plaything!
[Man and woman moaning]
Every knee shall bow
and every tongue confess.
You want to succeed in life?
He said the kingdom of God
suffers violence,
And the violent
take it by force!
When you gonna pick up
your weapon?
You need to
get your mind right!
The battlefield is the mind.
You and Satan play,
He'll get you doing
any old thing.
We all got issues,
But if you don't deal with them
privately...
[Gasping]
You will deal with them
publicly.
Get your mind right!
Whitney!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
You need Jesus!
Whitney, baby, wait!
You know you need Jesus!
Whitney!
Whitney! Whitney!
[Clapping]
Come on, get up.
Get up. Come on, girl.
Get yourself together.
I don't want to.
You can't hide in here
forever.
And you cannot cancel
any more shows.
Come on, nippy.
You need to end this.
You need to leave Bobby.
I don't want to
talk about this.
Look, I'm not saying
he's a bad guy,
But he's not right
for you.
End it
before it destroys you both.
Listen,
you get back on tour.
By the time
you get back here,
I will make sure
he's out of your house.
Bobby: Whitney! Whitney!
I can't see him!
Don't worry.
I'll take care of him.
Whitney! Whitney!
She don't want to see you,
Bobby.
Look, you handle her
business affairs, that's fine.
But you're not a part
of this marriage.
You ain't nothing
but a punk, Bobby.
You better move
out my face!
Whitney!
What the hell
is her problem?
She cares about me, Bobby.
Oh, and I don't?
What do you want?
Why are you even here?
You know why I'm here!
I love you!
What I saw didn't look like
any kind of love I know.
Look, look, I get depressed,
I drink too much,
And when I do,
I lose it.
You don't know what that's like!
You are Whitney Houston.
What?!
Biggest damn star
in the world!
And every time I'm with you,
I'm reminded of it!
Oh, so I'm the problem?!
I'm not... I'm not...
I'm not saying that...
Yes, you are!
Look, we can work this out!
How, Bobby? How? How?
Well, I said I'm sorry!
How?!
I just
don't want to lose you!
Oh, you should have
thought about that before!
Baby!
Go away!
Whitney, open this door!
[Banging on door]
Open the door, Whitney!
Whitney! Open the door!
[Banging continues]
Whitney!
Whitney, open this door!
Baby, open this door!
Open this door!
Baby, please!
I can't go nowhere
without her being on my case.
You don't need that, bro.
You damn straight I don't.
You need that.
* said, give it, give it,
give it to me *
* here it comes, here it comes,
here it comes *
* I'm a sweet thing
and I know you want some *
* the way my body moves
to the rhythm of the drums *
* got you realizin'
Yo! Yo, shot.
What you want, man?
My money, fool.
What's your problem?
You don't see us talking?!
Who this punk ass?
I'm Bobby brown.
Yeah, well, stay out of my face,
Bobby brown.
Where's my money, man?
I paid what I owed, man.
Nah, nah.
The price was a "g" a bag,
and we fronted you eight.
It was only six.
That's not
what my boy said.
Well, somebody lying.
And it ain't my boy,
so you need to step off!
Oh, yeah? You want to go?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
[Grunts]
Stay cool,
and you'll get your money!
Get up, looking all weak.
[Laughs]
Yeah, everybody lookin' at you.
Everybody lookin' at you.
Cheers.
Drink your drink, man.
[Laughs]
A little punk, man.
Yeah, he's a punk man.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What kind of money
you owe him, man?
It's nothin', man.
Next time, next time,
you come to me, okay?
Next time I come to you.
Yeah.
You solve everything,
right?
Man, don't worry about it.
I can handle my stuff, man.
[Gunshots]
[Screaming]
[Gun clicks]
[Spits]
Steve?!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Somebody
call an ambulance now!
[Screaming continues]
[Cheers and applause]
It's Bobby.
Bobby: They shot him!
They shot my boy!
They shot Steve!
Steve's been shot!
Whoa, slow down. Slow down.
What?
They shot my boy!
Wait a minute!
Who shot who?
[Voice breaking] Steve.
Steve got shot.
Wait, what?
Where are you?
He owed somebody
some money,
And... and I-i just...
I just lost it.
This ain't the way
I want to go, okay?
I want to go!
I-I got my kids,
I-I-i got krissi,
and I got you.
Baby, please.
I need you to help me.
Okay, I will, baby.
I'll get you help.
Okay, I w...
I got to go.
[Cheers and applause]
Bobby: I don't want to end up
dead or in prison
Like most of the people
that I knew growing up.
But now I'm afraid
that it's gonna happen anyway.
It happened to Steve.
He was my best friend,
and now he's dead.
All my life I've been drinking,
trying to deaden this pain.
And, lately,
this drinking ain't been enough.
And now I'm causing pain, too...
Causing pain to the one person
that I love more than anything.
And it's got to stop!
But how do you stop when
the one person that you love
Is just as bad as you are?!
[Crying] How do you stop?
There you go.
And keep the chan...
Man: Appreciate it.
Where's daddy's
good luck?
Shh.
Hey.
Look at you.
Look how beautiful
you are.
More beautiful
than the last time I saw you.
I love you.
[Chuckles]
Is my wife here?
She's in her bedroom.
It was supposed
to be confidential.
That was some
pretty intimate stuff you said.
I never meant
for it to get out.
Then you shouldn't have said it
in the first place.
What do you want,
to destroy me?
No. No, baby.
I want to see us
get better.
It's not just me
with a problem.
I don't have a problem,
Bobby.
I'm not the one
being shot at.
getting drunk
And messing around
on his wife.
[Scoffs]
I'm at the top of my game.
Look around you.
Who do you think is paying
for all this?
The only problems I've got
are the ones you've given me.
Baby, if you just...
No! Don't!
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Don't touch me!
Will you listen?
You listen!
Don't! No!
I can't take it anymore!
No! No!
So, that's it?
You love me.
You love me, baby.
You know you do!
No! No! No!
Go! Go, Bobby.
I don't want you here
anymore!
Baby, please.
Please, g-g-give me
one last chance
To prove
I can be the man for you,
To be a father to krissi.
No.
This was supposed to be
forever!
I love you!
[Crying]
One chance.
But I don't want to hear
any more talk about this...
This stuff ever again!
Understand?
[Shakily] Yeah.
It's gonna be good now,
baby.
You'll see.
It's all...
It's all gonna be good.
[Breathing shakily]
* if I should stay
* I would only be in
* your wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-y
* so I'll go, but I know
* I'll think of you
every step of *
[Door opens]
* the wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-y
Baby, you're on in 10.
* and I-i-i, I, I-i-i
* will always love you, ooh
* I will always
love yo-o-o-o-o-o-o-u *
* you, you
* you-ou-ou
* my darling, you
* mmm-mm-mm-mmm
* bittersweet memories
* that is all
I'm taking with me-e-e-e-e *
* so goodbye
* please don't cry
* we both know I'm not what you,
you nee-e-e-e-d *
* and I-i-i-i-i, I, I-i-i
* will always love you-ou-ou,
ohhh *
* I will always
love yo-o-o-o-o-o-u *
* you, you, you, ooh
* ohhh
[Saxophone solo plays]
* uh-huh
* oh, yes, I will
* I hope life treats you kind
* and I hope you have all
you've dreamed o-o-o-o-o-of *
* and I wish you joy
and happiness *
* but above all this
* I wish you lo-o-o-o-o-o-o-ve
* and I-i-i-i-i-i, I, I-i-i
* will always love yo-o-o-o-u
* I, I will always,
I'll always, I'll always *
* I'll always
love yo-o-o-o-o-o-u *
* I-i-i-i will always
love yo-o-o-o-o-o-o-u *
* I, I will alwa-a-a-a-a-ys
* mm-mm-mm-mm-mm,
mm-mm, mm-mm-mm *
Ooh!
* o-o-o-o-o-oh
* mm-mm-mm, mm-mm
mm-mm-mmm *
* I will Al... always
* I will always, always
* love
* yo-o-o-o-o-o-u
* yo-o-o-o-o-u
* yo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-u
[Cheers and applause]
[Slow-tempo music plays]