[engine rumbling distantly]
[engine rumbling loudly]
- [in French] Move.
Move over, man!
- [in French] Please, sir,
there's no more room.
- Move over!
- There's no room.
- Just move your bag!
[engine rumbling]
[metallic thudding]
[creaking]
[indistinct chatter]
Give me your bag.
What do you mean
there's no room here?
Put the bag here,
and now move over.
[sharp whistle]
How many did you get?
- [in French] All of them.
Three from last time.
Plus six more.
- How much?
- 600.
- 600'?
Hey, stop!
Stop!
I said only four.
You.
You. You.
And you.
The rest of you, over there.
[horn honks]
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
- [in English] Yeah.
- Let's go!
[shouting in French]
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaks French]
- [murmurs indistinctly]
[people murmur indistinctly]
[in English] That is 4,000.
I have some...
This is better.
- [in English] Okay,
I like this. I like this.
- Okay, that's why-
okay, bring 3,500.
Three and a half.
3,000 and a half.
- I will give you 2,000.
Please, don't talk much, okay?
- I'll bring change for you.
Good luck.
[in French] Hey!
Do you want this?
- [in French] Let me see.
How much are they?
- 4,000.
- 4,000?
I have 1,000.
[engine rumbling loudly]
[brakes squeak, engine rumbles]
[brakes hiss]
[engine rumbling loudly]
- [in French] Name?
- Ayiva Seihon.
- Where to?
- Burkina Faso.
Zabré.
2,000.
Take this for now.
It should help.
Try to spend it slowly.
Hopefully things will get better
the further along we get.
Yes, I know.
It's so you can manage, for now.
Right now, it's tough,
but it'll get better.
Do you understand?
Yes, everything is fine.
Yes.
We are here.
Abas?
He's here.
[laughs]
He wants to get with
those European girls.
You know what I'm saying.
[chuckles]
- Look what Mades
put on Facebook.
- [chuckles]
Hold on.
He's big now.
- Look at this.
[people speaking French]
- [vocalizes]
[in English] Okay.
[in French] There he is.
[Women laughing,
[people speaking French]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
- [in French] As my colleague
told you, I can find you work.
So you can gather money
and pay for your trip.
- [in French] Okay.
We will think about it.
- Ayiva.
Come here.
Here's your money.
Don't count it in front of me.
We don't count money here.
[indistinct chatter]
- [in French] Hey, man.
- [in French] Can we have
a word with you?
- No, I have things to do.
- We have contacts in Tripoli.
[indistinct chatter]
- We can't stay here and work.
It will take us
at least two months
to save enough money.
Our brothers in Tripoli
won't wait for us.
We will lose our places
on the boat.
And we cannot take that risk.
- Listen.
If you can help us get to Libya,
I promise to get you
a place on the boat.
- You know very well
I can get you there.
But if I get you to Tripoli,
I want two places.
I got this!
Starting now,
we're out of here!
- Really? We're out?
- I got this!
- [in English] Oh,
are you not sleeping?
Why are you disturbing?
Don't you know people
are sleeping?
Look at the idea of the time.
- [in English] We stop.
We stop. We promise.
[in French]
Are you stupid or what?
- Go to bed before
I will sleep, please.
- [in English] Okay, okay.
[boisterous techno music
ringtone playing]
[giggling]
[boisterous ringtone continues]
- Okay, you want
to receive call too.
Are you not sleeping?
Are you the owner of this place?
- [speaking French]
- Huh?
- Please, leave these premises.
- [in English] Sorry about it.
It won't happen again.
[wind whooshing]
[gravel crunching]
- [in French]
Move along, quickly.
This is Mano.
He's your guide.
He'll take you to Tinel.
It's the last town
between Algeria and Libya.
Do everything Mano says.
Do not ignore his instructions.
[wind whistling]
- [inhales deeply]
[wind whistling and whooshing]
[wind whooshing]
- [in French] How does
he know if we're going
in the right direction?
- [in French] It's easy.
[wind whooshing]
You pick a point.
Aim for it.
And once you get there,
you pick another one
further away
and you head for that one.
That's how he does it.
[wind whooshing]
[rocks clattering]
[wind whistling]
[gravel crunching]
[rocks scraping and clattering]
[indistinct chatter]
[wind sighing]
- Head over that hill.
[indistinct chatter]
[men shouting indistinctly]
- [man speaking in French]
[heavy smack]
- [grunting]
[all shouting in French]
- [speaking French]
- [groaning]
- [shouts in French]
[heavy smack]
[all speaking French]
[woman whimpering]
- [grunts]
- [shouting in French]
[both yelling in French]
[people whimpering]
- [speaking French]
- [shouting in French]
[gunshot]
[wind howling]
[no audible dialogue]
[cloth fluttering]
[engine rumbling]
[wind whooshing and howling]
[indistinct chatter]
[wind sighing
and cloth fluttering]
[faint indistinct chatter]
[dog barks]
[engines puttering]
- [in English] Hello.
[in French] It's Ayiva.
Everything's good.
We're in Libya.
In Sabha.
Yes. We're fine.
He's fine.
No.
Uncle Ousman,
I want to talk to you
about something.
Yes, sir.
When we arrived in Sabha,
we didn't have anything left.
If you could help us,
a little more will get us there.
I see.
[tapping and creaking]
- So?
- He'll send it.
[people chattering indistinctly]
[flames crackling]
- [in French] Listen up!
This boat doesn't
leave the beach
unless one of you drives it.
I need a driver,
even if you don't like the idea.
- He's joking, right?
[people speaking in French]
- [in French] Why can't we go?
- [in French]
You have to take us, sir.
We paid you.
[people speaking in French]
You!
You have to drive the boat!
[all shouting in French]
- [in English]
Hey, motherfucker!
I'll do it!
Oh, I'll do it.
If none of these motherfucker
want to do it,
I'll do it.
I'll drive the boat!
- [in French] If you're driving
the boat, I'm not going.
- What he said?
- [in English] He said
you can't drive the boat.
- Oh, fuck you.
If you're a man,
stand up and drive the boat.
- [in French] You'll never
take that boat anywhere.
So sit down.
She's not supposed
to drive it; You are!
We paid you!
[all clamoring]
- Calm down.
I can do it.
I believe I can drive the boat.
- Where are you from?
- Burkina.
- There's no sea there.
How are you going to drive us?
You don't know how to drive.
- I'm not going if he drives.
- Me neither.
[surf crashing]
[water splashing]
[crowd chattering]
[grunts]
- [in English] Hey, you okay?
[motor revving]
[waves splashing]
[motor slowing]
[mechanical rattling]
[motor sputtering]
[mechanical rattling
and grinding]
[motor sputtering]
- [in French] Hey!
Do you even know
what the fuck you're doing?
[motor sputtering]
[motor revving]
[motor droning]
[thunder crashing]
[rain pattering]
[motor revving]
[people shouting indistinctly]
[loud splash]
[thunder crashing]
[people shouting indistinctly]
[man yelling]
[water splashing]
[thunder crashing]
[loud smack]
[people shouting indistinctly]
[thunder crashing]
[people shouting in French]
[thunder rumbling and crashing]
[shouting fades]
[foghorn blaring]
[flare hissing]
[low ambient music]
♪♪
[no audible dialogue]
- [shouting in French]
[people speaking indistinctly]
[water splashing]
[water gurgling]
[water splashing and gurgling]
♪♪
[man sputtering]
[waves splashing]
♪♪
[waves lapping]
[in English] Oh! Hey!
[people shouting indistinctly]
Hey!
[all shouting frantically]
[all shouting indistinctly]
[shouting fades]
♪♪
[waves lapping]
- [sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[door rattles]
- [in French] Where were you?
What's wrong?
[indistinct chatter]
[plaintive instrumental music]
♪♪
[motorbike engines buzzing]
[knocks]
♪♪
- Ah.
- [in French] Welcome.
[all speaking French]
Let's eat.
[metallic scraping]
- [in French]
Do you want a beer?
- No.
- And you?
Do you want a beer?
- No. Mm.
- How was the journey?
- It was okay.
- Did you find papers?
- They gave us three months.
- You'll need to find
a job with a contract
to get real papers.
Three months isn't enough.
How are things back home?
- Same as before.
- Mm.
- Except they built solar panels
for the school in the village.
- Mm-hmm.
- Boukare did all of it.
- Ah, mm-hmm.
- He built it all.
He did great work.
- Mm.
- He built the school
and sent the solar panels.
- Mm.
It's normal. He has to.
He came here a long time ago.
And he has the money.
It's for our children.
By the way,
have you heard from your sister?
- Mm.
Not yet.
- Why not?
- Because we couldn't
call anyone.
- You had no way of calling her?
Call her right now.
Take the phone!
- I'll do it later.
- Call your sister now!
She's taking care
of your daughter,
and you can't even call her?
Is this normal?
- Listen to me.
It's more dangerous
than you think.
I'm telling you,
you can't do it.
it's too dangerous.
- [in Italian] Quiet!
People live here,
for fuck's sake!
- [in English] Sorry.
[in French] I'm sorry I yelled,
but you don't know what I saw.
It's too dangerous
for you and Zeina.
I just got here.
As soon as I make some money,
I will send it to you...
- Oh!
- Mades!
- [in French]
Welcome, my friend!
- Oh!
- [in English] Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[in French]
When did you get here?
Who's on the phone?
- Aseta.
- Okay. These are my friends.
[in English] Yeah, hello.
- [in French] How's it going?
- Good.
- What's your name?
- Ayiva.
- Hello, Ayiva.
[all speaking French]
- [in French]
They just got here,
and they're already calling you!
[grunts]
[grunting]
Yeah!
- No!
- [speaks French]
- [in Italian] This is the last
time I'm telling you!
- Excuse us.
- Hey, let's go!
Ayiva! Let's go!
- Mades is here.
He's going to take us
to our place.
- Okay. Say hello for me.
- Okay.
- Mm. [speaks French]
- Uh-huh.
[all speaking French]
- What's with all this walking?
We need a car!
We can't walk like this
in this fucking cold.
- Oh, really?
You're cold?
[all speaking French]
[engine revving]
[electronic music thumping]
- [laughs]
Hey! What's this?
That's how they drive here?
[tires squeal]
[chuckles]
[electronic music thumping]
♪♪
[engine revving]
[car whooshing]
[electronic music fading]
♪♪
[footsteps scraping]
[flames crackling]
[indistinct chatter]
[wood clattering]
[people speaking in French]
- [speaking French]
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaks French]
[lights buzzing]
[gravel crunching]
Go get them a heater.
[speaks French]
[flames crackling]
- Do you have a cigarette?
- So this is it.
I know it's not perfect,
but at least it's close to town.
To find a house without papers.
It's hard. For us.
- What about work?
- Right now, there is less.
But I'll try to figure
something out. For you.
And since you just got here...
[paper rustling]
Take this.
- No, please...
- I know.
- Thanks.
- Take it, for now.
Take it.
[metallic creaking]
[speaks French]
Okay.
[metallic thud]
[speaks French]
Okay.
I'll catch you tomorrow.
[man speaking French]
See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow, man.
[all speaking French]
[men chattering]
[crackling]
[metallic scraping]
[embers hissing]
[footsteps sloshing]
[wood clatters]
[rat squeaks]
[wood clattering]
[flames crackling]
[wind howling]
[light tinkling music]
♪♪
- [shivering]
[dreamy contemplative music]
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[train whooshing]
♪♪
[horn blares]
[train whooshing]
♪♪
[wheels squealing]
[thudding]
♪♪
[metallic jingling]
Abas!
Take this.
- [humming]
[indistinct chatter]
- Good morning.
- [in French] Hello.
How are you?
- Good.
- Great. What's up?
- I wanna sell this.
- Huh?
- You want to sell this?
- Yes.
- It's nice.
- Yeah.
- Does it work?
- Yes.
It works.
- It doesn't work?
- It works!
- The charger?
- No, I have the earphones.
- We need the charger,
my friend.
[humming]
Salah!
- Huh?
- Do we have a charger
for this mp3'?
- [speaks French]
- Uh-huh.
[indistinct chatter]
[man speaking French]
Sorry, my friend.
I couldn't find it.
[flames crackling]
[bird chirping]
[traffic whooshing]
[indistinct chatter]
- [in Italian] We work.
You work.
They work.
[in English] Okay?
Did you understand?
- [in Italian] Yeah.
- Good.
- [speaking Italian]
- Yes.
- What's the difference
between "we are" and "we is"?
- "We are" and...
[speaking in Italian]
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaking in Italian]
[people speaking in Italian]
- [speaks Italian]
- [in French]
Can I ask you a favor?
- [in French] Sure.
- Do you know someone
who can buy this?
[clicking]
- Yeah, I think so.
- Let's go.
Hey, Abas.
- I don't want to go.
- Let's do this,
and we'll come back.
It's very important.
Hmm?
- I know it's important,
but I don't want to go!
[kids chattering
and shouting indistinctly]
- [in Italian]
Hey! How are you?
- [in Italian] All right!
- Good?
- Yes.
- Where's your brother?
- I don't know. Talk to me.
- Go get him.
- Talk to me.
My brother isn't here.
Talk to me!
- I want to sell this.
- The charger?
- No, don't have it.
- Go check if there's one
inside, Patrizia.
- Leave me alone.
- Go inside and get it!
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah, and you?
- Yeah, me too.
- [murmurs indistinctly]
You need anything else?
- No, no.
- Why don't you buy
this motorino?
- Motorino?
- It's a good one.
- The motorino is good,
but I don't need it.
- You don't need it?
- No.
- I'll give you a good price.
- I don't need it.
- Okay.
Give me a cigarette.
- I don't smoke.
- You.
Give me a cigarette.
[indistinct chatter]
Gimme a light.
Thanks, friend.
- [in Italian] You're welcome.
- A charger?
- Yes.
- I want to sell this.
- I don't want it.
I don't need it.
- I don't need it either.
So what do we do?
- Come on, I'll give it to you
for 5 euros.
- 5 euros?
- Yeah. It's a good price.
[both speak Italian]
- I don't have any change.
- What can we do?
- Both for 20 euros.
- 20 euros?
- Yes.
- It works?
- Yes. It works good.
- Is it real?
- Yes.
- [in French] Good?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
- Okay!
- Bye.
- [speaks Italian]
[train rumbling]
- Good night.
[flames crackling]
[indistinct chatter]
- What's wrong?
Hmm? What is it?
- Look around...
- So?
What do you want to do?
You want us to go back?
The others made it here.
- [sighs]
Just give it some time.
[loud clattering]
[doors creak]
[engine rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaking French]
[clippers snipping]
[leaves rustling]
- [speaks French]
- Aseta Seihon.
- Burkina Faso?
- 50!
You see, I told you!
[chuckling]
It's 40,000 CFA.
[speaks French]
Mm.
I did well at work today.
[laughing]
This is just the beginning.
Twice as big... And only
five people sleep there!
[indistinct chatter]
[relaxed music]
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Oh!
- [in English] Oh, my nigga!
Ooh! Oh!
- [in English]
I'm cool, and you?
Long time.
[indistinct chatter]
- Ayiva, what's up?
- [in English] Doing good.
- [speaks indistinctly]
Oh, how's it going?
- [in English] How's it going?
[all speaking indistinctly]
- How's it going?
[speaks indistinctly]
[all speaking indistinctly]
- [in English]
Ayiva, you're welcome.
- [speaking indistinctly]
- Life's a jungle.
- [speaks French]
[hip-hop music]
- Oh, Rihanna is my sister!
No!
- ♪ Come on, come on,
come on ♪
- [in French]
I want to give you this.
- [in French] Forget it!
- [speaking French]
- Don't worry about it.
Don't be in such a rush.
- No, no. No.
- You know me!
- [speaks French]
[indistinct chatter
and laughter]
[in English] Look at her.
[laughs]
- ♪ There's no way
I'm turning back ♪
- I love Rihanna,
so, yeah, she's my sister. Huh?
- Did you say your sister?
- Yeah.
- But I don't think
she's your sister
the way Floby is my brother.
- I don't like Floby.
Floby is a motherfucker guy.
- Wait a minute.
Do you even know who is Floby?
- I don't care about him.
Mades, let me see.
Rihanna is-
- Mades!
- [in English] What?
- [in French]
She doesn't know Floby.
- ♪ The affliction
of the feeling ♪
♪ Leaves me wanting more ♪
- Oh, see, yeah, I want
to see the fucking guy.
- ♪ 'Cause I may be bad ♪
- Who is this motherfucker?
Oh.
- [in English]
He's from Burkina.
- [in English] Why are
Burkina men so sad, man?
♪ I love the smell of it ♪
- Stop.
You see?
There it goes again.
Oh, oh.
- ♪ But chains and whips
excite me ♪
- What do you want to do?
- [in French]
Can I have a Peroni?
- You need some Peroni?
- Yes!
- I don't have some Peroni.
I have some drink.
[squeals]
- Don't put your fucking mouth
on my beer!
- Look at my teeth.
Open yours!
Wha...
- [laughs]
- [in French] You stink!
[laughter]
Motherfucker guy.
- ♪ Come on,
na, na, na, na ♪
- [in French] It's going
to be all right.
[all speaking indistinctly]
- Fucking nigga!
You look like one of those
boys in the streets,
in the train station.
[laughter]
- [in French] I don't get it.
- Look at your hair.
Look at your hair.
Look at your dressing.
You look like one of them!
[laughter]
- [in French] Hold this.
[indistinct chatter]
- ♪ 'Cause I may be bad ♪
[grunts]
[applause]
I'll take her in there.
[laughter
and indistinct chatter]
- Motherfucker...
[speaking indistinctly]
♪ Excite me ♪
- [in English]
Go and sit down there.
- You sit.
[all speaking indistinctly]
- ♪ Come one, come on,
come on ♪
- [whistles]
- [in French]
Aisha. Quick.
- ♪ I like it, like it,
come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ I like if, like if ♪
- Regina.
Please come home soon.
♪ M, M, M ♪
♪ S, S, S ♪
♪ And ♪
♪ M, M, M ♪
♪ Oh, Oh ♪
- [in French] Let's go.
We're leaving.
♪ You bring to me ♪
♪ Oh, you turn me on ♪
♪ it's exactly what five
been yearning for ♪
- [in French] We're out of here.
- [in French]
We don't say good-bye?
- ♪ And meet me
in my boudoir ♪
♪ Make my body ♪
[faintly]
♪ Say, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I like it, like it ♪
♪ 'Cause I may be bad ♪
♪ But I'm perfectly good
at it ♪
♪ Sex in the air,
I don't care ♪
♪ I love the smell of it ♪
[rain pattering]
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaks French]
- [speaking French]
Abas! Gimme a drag.
- [in Italian] Guys, how many
times do I have to tell you?
If you leave the stems
this long,
look what happens!
You rush, and the oranges
get destroyed,
and I can't sell them!
Understood? Guys!
How many times
do I have to tell you!
Eh'?
You fucking Africans!
Because I hire you for a job,
and you can't even do it.
I'm not paying for these cases.
You understand?
- [in Italian] I understand,
but it's his first day.
- I don't care.
That's your problem, not mine.
Let me guess.
It's his first day too?
Eh? Go fuck yourself!
- Let's do this; I'll send them
both with you today,
because today, I don't go.
They go to unload,
both of them, you pay only one.
- Fine.
[metallic banging]
[heavy thudding and squeaking]
[oranges thudding heavily]
[metallic banging]
[grunts]
[oranges thudding heavily]
Hey, you.
Do some work.
Come!
[oranges thudding heavily]
Let's finish this and go home.
[metallic banging]
[oranges thudding heavily]
Let's finish, and then we go.
- I don't understand you.
This guy is a fucking asshole,
and you wanna work
twice as hard?
For this shit job'?
- You think you know
better than me?
You were there earlier.
You saw everything, right?
So what don't you understand?
- I already have my money.
- Stop acting like a child.
Man up.
Do this, and we leave.
It's a small job, and we're off.
- You don't look like a man.
You look like his bitch.
- [screaming]
[crates crashing]
[men shouting]
[all shouting indistinctly]
- [in Italian] The machine!
Turn off the machine!
[mechanical whirring]
[whirring stops]
- [groaning]
- [speaking indistinctly]
We got him. We got him.
We got him.
[in French] Relax. Relax.
Sit. Sit.
- [grunting]
- Are you okay?
[indistinct chatter]
- [in Italian] Excuse me.
You feel like doing
another little job
before you go home?
Okay, I'll meet you
out front in ten minutes.
Huh? Okay.
[oranges thudding heavily,
metallic creaking]
[dreamy contemplative music]
♪♪
[motorbike engine buzzing]
- [in French] What's your name?
Ayiva, right?
Load these last cases.
I'm gonna go do something
in the house, okay?
[crate thuds]
[grunts]
[crate thudding]
[grunts and chuckles]
[sighs]
Why did you do that to me?
- [in Italian]
What language is that?
Italian.
- Burkina.
Burkina Faso.
- French?
- Yes.
- [in French] Go fuck yourself.
- You made this mess,
and you tell me
to go fuck myself?
Why?
- Why not?
- That's all?
- Yes.
- You're going
to pick up everything
and put it in the truck.
- [in English] English?
- [in English] Yes.
- Do you like Italy?
[murmurs]
- [sighs]
[oranges thudding]
- Up your ass.
[in Italian] Good-bye!
- [chuckling]
[speaks French]
[indistinct chatter]
Hmm?
- [in French] Good evening.
What, nobody can answer?
Say, "Good evening, Mama."
[all speaking in French]
Speak up.
[in Italian]
Remove your hats, please.
In Italy, we remove our hats
when we eat.
Take off this hat.
Good job.
No, I'm not going to steal it.
Take off your hat too.
You've got nice hair.
Beautiful curly hair.
Oh, it fell.
Bye.
Eat.
Bon appétit.
- You want to work, right?
- I've always worked.
- Then tomorrow,
you'll go back to work.
The same way?
For the same money?
- [in French] Same thing.
Yes, you will do that.
- Don't play professional.
- You think you're
too good for this?
"Me, I don't work here..."
And how will you eat and sleep?
- Anyway, Momo is an asshole.
I'm done working for that guy.
- Why?
- [in Italian] Hello.
Attention, please.
First, we want
to thank Mama Africa
for allowing us
to have this meeting.
Thank you.
[applause]
- Thank you.
I'm happy to be here
with all of you
and to hear you call me Mama.
And because you left
your mothers at home,
I'm happy to welcome you.
Okay?
[all speaking at once]
Enjoy your meal. Eat.
- [in Italian] Thank you.
[laughter]
- [speaks Italian]
[indistinct chatter]
A song?
- [speaking Italian]
- [singing in Italian]
♪♪
[all clapping rhythmically]
[singing in Italian]
[all chanting "Mama Africa"]
- Bravo, Mama. Bravo.
- [speaking Italian]
- Bravo.
[applause]
- I won't talk for too long.
[speaking in Italian]
- So what's up?
- Everything's fine.
- Oh. You found some other work?
- Yes, for this guy, Rocco.
- Who?
- He has a beard.
He's kinda tall.
- Ah, Rocco, yes.
I don't know him,
but people speak about him.
This man can get you
a work contract, everything.
You get your pay slips,
all that.
And then, it's possible
to have your papers.
- [speaking Italian] [applause]
[indistinct chatter]
- Seriously,
what is she talking about?
She's talking about
immigration, right?
- Yes, about immigration.
Problems with the boys
from Rosarno.
[leaves rustling]
[clippers snipping]
[indistinct chatter]
- You had 10?
- Yes.
- 20 euros for you?
- Thanks.
Who's next?
- You had 30 cases?
- Yes.
- [in English] Okay.
- I had 20.
- [in French] 20?
[in English] Okay. Okay.
- [speaking in French]
- Okay.
[in Italian] Ayiva, bring
a case to the house.
[in French] Next?
- [murmurs indistinctly]
- [in English] Okay.
- ♪ I am so super
pupper drupper ♪
♪ I'm the front girl
in round ♪
♪ I am so cool with
my fashion pink lips ♪
♪ Stacking money
rolls down ♪
♪ All the boys
say wow, wow ♪
♪ Girls in the back,
same, wow, wow ♪
- ♪ Enter the party,
call me candy dandy ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm high, high ♪
♪ I am so super
pupper drupper ♪
♪ I'm the front girl
in round ♪
♪ I am so cool
with awesome tits ♪
[singing indistinctly]
♪ Mimimimimi ♪
♪ Mimi, mimimi,
only mimi ♪
♪ Mimimimimi ♪
♪ Mimi, mimimi,
only mimi ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[rhythmic tapping]
- [in English] I like it.
- [singing indistinctly]
- Hey, Medhi.
- Ayiva!
[in Italian] How are you?
- Can I speak with you?
- [in French] I'm coming.
What's up?
- I'm good and you?
- [speaking French]
- You still got that
mp3 player I sold you?
- Yes.
- Can I buy it back?
- How much?
- I'll give you 5 more.
- What?
- 5 more, so 30.
-30...
50'?
- Please, come on.
Do this for me.
I wanna give this
to a girl I wanna fuck.
Get it?
[grunts]
[men speaking
in foreign language]
- Medhi!
- [speaks French]
- Yeah, what?
[speaks French]
- [speaking French]
Are you selling the gloves?
- Yes, how many?
- Ten pairs.
[plaintive instrumental music]
♪♪
- [whistles]
- [in Italian] Hey, man!
What's up?
- [in Italian] Hey.
- Was the phone good?
- Yeah, it's good.
What are you doing here?
Dancing?
- Yes.
You know where my house is,
right?
If you need anything, come over.
- Okay.
- [speaks Italian]
[lively instrumental music]
Pio'?
- It's good.
It's got YouTube,
Facebook, everything.
- How much?
- 150.
- 150?
- Yeah.
It's a good one.
- Right now, I don't
have the money for this.
I'll come back.
Show me the other thing.
How much?
- 20 euros.
For you, 10.
- 10 euros?
- Yeah.
You like the color?
- It's perfect for my daughter.
- Can I ask you something?
- Tell me.
- Is your daughter black?
- Yes.
- Where is she?
- Africa.
- Africa?
- Yes.
- That's too far.
- Yeah.
- [in French] You're not eating?
You must eat.
So you were able
to find some work?
- [in French] Yeah.
I sent some money to Aseta.
- Oh, that's a good thing.
- She asked me...
if they could come here.
- Come here for what?
There's nothing
for women to do here.
You know how it is.
There's no work for women here.
You think you'll make
a home for them here'?
You know you'll go back.
- They want to come here.
And it's their choice.
I can't do anything.
- I'm the one who
brought you here.
You're here.
You know you're with family.
I talk...
but you don't listen.
- I'm trying to manage
this on my own.
[silverware clangs]
- Okay, do what you want.
- About that.
I went by the school
and spoke to the girl
that works there.
- You want to get with
every girl you see, don't you?
Even the teachers.
- Hey, hey, that's not it.
I didn't talk about that.
I asked her about
bringing Aseta over.
She said that
with a residence permit
and a work contract, you can
do a family reunification
and you can bring her easily.
- It's not that easy.
- I don't care.
I'm not gonna end up with
some ugly village woman.
Okay?
I'm too handsome for that.
- Hmm?
You're crazy.
- Look at her.
- [sighs]
[speaks French]
- She's pretty, no?
Is she pretty or not?
- What about the one
with the longer hair?
- [speaking French]
- ♪ Got to love you,
got to love you ♪
- [speaking French]
- Check it out.
Tonight is our night!
[both laughing]
[in English] Sister,
you got beers?
- [in English]
I don't have beers.
- Let's go!
- ♪ Off the ground ♪
♪ Enough a them, fake man,
a king, a clown ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaking indistinctly]
[all speaking indistinctly]
- ♪ We lose a brown,
me alone ♪
♪ I make you start,
feel moan and groan ♪
[all speaking in French]
- ♪ I, I'm gonna flip
the script on ya ♪
♪ You don't even know me ♪
- Medhi!
- ♪ 'Cause I ♪
♪ I ain't even gonna fight it ♪
♪ Got to love you,
got to love you ♪
- [speaks indistinctly]
- ♪ Got to love you,
got to love you ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- ♪ Girl an me alone,
and give you security ♪
[singing indistinctly]
♪ You alone, I give you
the remedy to set you free ♪
♪ Some boy just wanna
hide you ♪
♪ That's why ♪
[singing indistinctly]
♪ Girl ♪
- ♪ I, I'll do anything
I could for ya ♪
♪ Boy, you're my only ♪
♪ See that, girl ♪
- ♪ I, I'm gonna flip
the script on ya ♪
♪ You don't even know me ♪
♪ Aha ♪
- ♪ 'Cause ♪♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ I don't even want
to fight, fight, fight ♪
- ♪ Don't need to fight, girl ♪
♪ Said I ♪
- ♪ I ain't even
gonna fight it ♪
♪ Got to love you,
got to love you ♪
♪ Yeah, got to love you,
got to love you, ♪
♪ I got to love you, girl ♪
- ♪ Got to love you,
got to love you ♪
♪ Got to love you,
♪ I got to love you, girl ♪
got to love you ♪
♪ Got to love you,
- ♪ Don't Want to fight ♪
- ♪ Hard steppin' girl,
We're not stoppin' ♪
- ♪ Got me spinnin'
in your orbit ♪
[tense music]
♪ With nowhere to run ♪
- ♪ Good lovin',
give ya good lovin' ♪
- ♪ Boy, you got me,
I can't ignore it ♪
- ♪ it's me and you
forever, girl ♪
- ♪ I, I'll do anything
I could for ya ♪
♪ Boy, you're my only ♪
[tense music continues]
- ♪ Love that ♪
- ♪ I, I'm gonna flip
the script ♪
♪ On ya,
you don't even know me ♪
♪ You're ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I ♪
- ♪ I don't even want
to fight, fight, fight ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaking French]
[chortles]
Huh?
[overlapping conversations]
- [in English] Fuck.
[laughs]
Ah, you drunk.
[overlapping conversations]
[man singing indistinctly]
[person whistles]
[indistinct chatter]
- Oh, fuck you!
- Hey! Yo!
- Abas.
- Whoa.
- [in Italian] If you touch him,
I'll kill you!
- Just give 'em what we have.
- [in Italian] What?
- If you touch him,
I'll kill you.
- I'm not afraid of you.
I'll burn you alive!
Today in Rosarno,
tomorrow in Milan!
[all speaking Italian]
- [in Italian] Listen to your
friend and get out of here.
- Go to hell!
[all speaking at once]
- Fuck off!
- I'll burn you alive!
- [speaking indistinctly]
I'll burn you alive!
[men speaking indistinctly]
I'll burn you alive,
you fucking piece of trash!
[all yelling in Italian]
- [in Italian] You, Moroccan,
you're no good.
- [laughing]
- Always starting some shit.
- Yeah, go ahead and laugh!
- [smooches]
[wind sighing]
[birds twittering]
[birds chirping and trilling]
- [in French] You!
Come on. Not you!
- [in French] You two!
Come with us!
[all speaking at once]
- [in Italian] You want gloves?
- [in Italian] Yes.
- Do you have money?
- No.
I'll pay you later.
- I have some.
- Oh.
- Oh, no, no.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You want gloves?
- Yes. Yes.
- You have money?
- No. I'll pay you later.
- Sure?
- Yes, sure.
- [speaks Italian]
Hey.
- No.
- No. You?
- [in French] Oh, there you are!
- [singing indistinctly]
[both speaking Italian]
- Okay.
- [singing indistinctly]
[humming]
- Let's take a break
and eat something.
Then we'll go, okay?
- Okay.
- [in Italian] Come on, kids.
Let's eat.
- It's about time!
[indistinct TV chatter]
- Mama.
- [in Italian] Give him some.
Let's see if he likes it.
- Thank you.
- [in Italian] You want some?
- What else is he gonna eat?
- Marta, eat.
Don't start with the iPad.
. Okay"
- Not now.
- Leave her alone, if she...
- No, she has to eat.
All: Bon appétit.
- Give Ayiva some wine.
- Do you want wine?
[indistinct TV chatter
continues]
[all speaking Italian]
- I can't take the news anymore,
these days.
- I don't pay attention anymore.
- What else are you gonna watch
while you eat, a movie?
- Of course! I'm just saying
it's always the same thing.
- That's how the news is.
- But it's not...
- But what else
are you gonna put on?
What else are you gonna watch?
I don't know.
- Yeah, but if you wanna know
the news, it's not easy.
- Come on, let's just eat.
- Yes, please, let's eat.
[all speak Italian]
- Mama, can you
pour me some water?
- [speaks Italian]
- Look what I found.
- You always have
an excuse not to eat!
- Leave her alone.
She's a little girl.
- It's good that
she has interests.
At least they're
not stupid things.
[people speaking indistinctly]
- ls this what it's like
in your country?
- It's like that,
but it's not like that.
- Do you like where you're from?
- Yes.
- What do you like
most about it?
- My daughter.
- You have a daughter?
- Yes.
- What's her name?
- Zeina.
- How old is she?
- Seven.
- Seven. That's nice.
Are you married?
- No.
- No?
Then take your clothes off.
[laughter]
- Grandma.
Can I have some water, please?
- Yes.
- [speaks Italian]
- Remember to put your hair up
when you're at the table.
- Fine.
- You can't be at the table
with your hair down.
- [exhales sharply]
- You can't have
your hair in the plate.
- Don't worry about it, honey.
Eat.
- [speaks Italian]
- Who am I
supposed to listen to?
- Listen to what's right!
- [chuckles]
- Tonight we have these two
young boys with us at the table.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah, I'm chilling.
- And this one, "lima surda!"
These guys really
work hard, though!
- You like it?
You like it?
Marta, ask him if he likes it.
- He understands
if you don't speak dialect.
- Okay.
- They understand.
When they want, they understand.
- But how do they live?
- Let's stop talking
about problems.
Tonight, in my house,
we're gonna talk about
positive things, okay?
Come on, gimme five!
[laughter]
Please, let's not talk
about our problems, enough!
- No, no, no.
- Mama, be quiet or else...
- Okay, let's pretend
it's nothing.
[laughter]
- [speaking Italian]
[laughter
and indistinct chatter]
- [in French] So...
is she gonna show up?
[indistinct chatter on TV]
- [in French]
Aseta's not answering.
- Really?
Maybe she doesn't know
how to use the computer.
[tense ambient music]
[chuckles]
♪♪
- [in English]
Look, look! Rosarno!
- [in Italian]
This morning, police evicted
African immigrants from
the historic center of Rosarno.
All this because
the local residents
wanted the immigrants cleared
from their neighborhood.
♪♪
- [murmurs indistinctly]
[indistinct chatter]
- I will go. This is fucked up!
- Sit down!
- No, I will not sit down!
They took my stuff,
drove me out of the house,
for what'?
No, no, no!
We need to go, understand?
[all speaking at once]
No, no, no.
No.
Fuck that.
I'm going home!
[dramatic ambient music]
♪♪
[ripping]
[banging]
[door bangs]
♪♪
- [in Italian] Everybody, out!
Come on. Come on.
Let's go.
[tense music]
♪♪
- What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
[all speaking in Italian]
- Papers!
Where are your papers?
- Shut up!
[police shouting in Italian]
- Sit still!
- [in Italian] Let's go.
[keys jingling]
[lock clicking]
- Ayiva Seihon.
Mary Elizabeth Innocence.
[crowd chattering]
[water dripping]
[wood scraping]
[footsteps creaking]
[engine droning]
- [in Italian]
What the hell happened?
[all chattering in French]
- [in French] Shit!
- [in French]
Where are you going?
- I'm going to work.
- Ayiva!
[tense ambient music]
We have to do something.
♪♪
[conveyor belt whirring]
[dreamy contemplative music]
♪♪
[engine turns over]
[engine rumbling]
- [in Italian] And another
season winds down.
[clears throat]
[lighter sparks and hisses]
Where are you off to next?
- [in Italian] I don't know
where I'm going.
- I can get you another job
at Marta's birthday party.
- Can I ask you something?
- Go ahead, Ayiva.
- Can you help me
get a work contract
so that I can get
a residence permit?
- I understand you, Ayiva.
When my grandfather
went to America,
he was in New York City.
He worked hard, really hard.
But he earned almost nothing.
He and his family had
to take care of each other-
with his sisters,
with his brothers,
with his cousins.
That's how people should do it:
Help one another.
[paper rustling]
You're a good worker, Ayiva.
You handled yourself
really well.
[train traffic
thundering overhead]
[mouse squeaks]
[footsteps patting lightly]
[stomping]
[train traffic thundering]
- [gasping]
[panting heavily]
[upbeat ringtone playing]
[in English] Hello.
[crowd chattering in Italian]
[in French]
What happened?
- [in French] It's bad.
They killed two blacks.
- Have you seen Abas?
- I tried to call him,
but he's not picking up.
I don't even know where he is.
[people chattering in Italian]
[all speaking in Italian]
[dog barking distantly]
- Have you seen Abas?
- No, get in the car!
Come here, get in the car!
[crowd shouting and
chanting distantly]
[sirens blaring]
[crowd chattering indistinctly]
[glass shatters]
- Ayiva!
I called Arafat;
He's joining the protest
with the others.
- Is Abas with them?
- I don't know
if he's there or not.
I don't know.
[low suspenseful music]
♪♪
[distant metallic scraping]
- [in English] There.
[speaks indistinctly]
[loud metallic scraping]
[crowd chanting distantly]
[in French]
Let's get out of here.
- [in French]
Ayiva, we have to do this.
[heavy metallic scraping]
[distant shouting and chanting]
All: [in English]
Stop shooting blacks!
[loud clang]
[glass shattering
and items clattering]
[people yelling indistinctly]
Stop shooting blacks!
- [grunts] [smacking]
[motorbike engine buzzing]
all: Stop shooting blacks!
Stop shooting blacks!
- [grunting]
[item smacks]
- [screams]
All: Stop shooting blacks!
Stop shooting blacks!
[engine revs]
- [in English] Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
[shattering and clattering
continue]
[tense music]
[crowd shouting indistinctly]
- [in English]
Go, go, go. Go.
Run.
All: Stop shooting blacks!
Stop shooting blacks!
[dreamy contemplative music]
[heavy metallic scraping]
[smashing]
[explosion booms]
[flames roaring]
[smashing continues]
[crowd yelling]
[man yells indistinctly]
[smashing]
[explosion booms]
[flames roaring]
[men yelling]
[men shouting indistinctly]
[car bangs]
[smashing]
[men shouting indistinctly]
[metallic clang]
[smashing]
- [yelling indistinctly]
[distant shouting]
[smashing]
- Ayiva!
[men shouting and smashing]
[grunts]
[explosion booms]
[flames roaring]
[men shouting indistinctly]
[sirens blaring]
[flames roaring]
[men shouting indistinctly]
[van door scraping heavily]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
[men shouting indistinctly]
- [in French] We're not moving.
Mades, come!
[all shouting indistinctly]
We're ready.
[footsteps thumping
rhythmically]
[flames roaring]
All: Stop shooting blacks!
Stop shooting blacks!
[gun blasts]
[canister hisses]
Stop shooting blacks!
[clattering and smacking]
[all yelling indistinctly]
[all grunting]
[smacking and grunting]
[flames roaring]
- [panting]
[dog barking]
[motorbike engine buzzing]
[crowd yelling]
[all shouting in Italian]
[smacking]
[crowd continues shouting]
Abas!
[metallic clanging]
[crowd shouting and smacking]
- [gasps and gags]
[all smacking]
[all shouting in Italian]
[sirens blaring]
- [in Italian]
Let's go! Let's go!
[sirens blaring
and footsteps scraping]
- Abas.
- [gags]
Abas. Abas.
[engine revving]
[engine droning]
[footsteps scraping]
[grunting]
- [in Italian] Come.
- [in Italian] Slowly...
- [sighs]
[dogs barking faintly]
[sheep bleating faintly]
[dreamy contemplative music]
♪♪
[bells jingling]
[sheep bleating]
[seagulls squawking]
- If you're looking
for something positive,
at least there's this:
He can get a residence permit
on humanitarian grounds.
It would last at least a year.
- [in Italian] No. No.
We're going home.
It'll be better.
[Skype ringtone playing]
[in English] Hello.
- [in English] Hello.
- [in French] Put the video on.
- Hey, here you are.
- [in French] Are you okay?
- [sighs]
Yes. I'm okay.
- You don't look okay.
- This is what I always
look like here.
- Maybe, but you look tired.
- [speaks French]
- The computer Works Well,
and We installed
the solar panel.
For now, it's fine,
but what will we do
if it breaks?
- Take it to the shop;
Get it fixed.
- Okay.
- Mm.
- Where are you now'?
Show me where you are.
- These places
all look the same.
- Look Who's here.
- [in English] Hello, Zeina.
- [in French] Hi, Dad.
- Mm.
- How are you?
- [in French]
I'm good. You?
- I'm good too.
- Where is the present
I sent you?
- What?
- The present I sent you.
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Mm.
- Yes, I have it.
[speaks French]
- Do you still have the music?
- Yeah.
This is my favorite one.
[Upbeat pop music]
♪♪
- ♪ Yellow diamonds
in the light ♪
♪ Now we're standing
side by side ♪
♪ As your shadow crosses mine ♪
♪ What it takes to come alive ♪
♪ H's the way I'm feeling ♪
♪ {just can't deny ♪
♪ But I've gotta let it go ♪
♪ We found love
in a hopeless place ♪
♪♪
[mouse clicks]
[Skype beeps]
[Skype ringtone playing]
- [in English] Hello.
Hello?
- [sniffles]
- Hello.
[speaks French]
She loves your gift.
She never puts it down.
- [speaks indistinctly]
- And she tells everyone
that her father
spent 1,000 euros on it.
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
[people chattering in Italian]
[engines droning]
[all speaking Italian]
[dance music playing distantly]
[woman singing indistinctly]
[people chattering
and clapping rhythmically]
♪♪
- [in Italian] Hello.
- Hey, Ayiva.
What are you doing here?
- Me?
- Nothing.
♪♪
- Are those yours?
- They're mine now.
♪♪
- Okay.
Be careful, man.
- Ayiva.
Give me a cigarette.
♪♪
And a light.
- You are always
breaking my balls.
♪♪
- Thank you.
Good-bye, Ayiva.
- Good-bye.
♪♪
- [in Italian]
Now, Mrs. Fondacaro,
your moment has arrived.
A special song for little Marta.
Give her a round of applause.
[cheers and applause]
"Sara Perche Ti Amo. "
[bright dance music]
- Ayiva, let's go inside
and have a drink.
♪♪
[crowd clapping rhythmically]
[woman singing in Italian]
♪♪
[music fading]
[silence]
[plaintive music]
♪♪
[dreamy contemplative music]