MAN:
911, what's your emergency?
WOMAN:
911? Thank God!
My friend went swimming
in Sandy Beach!
Oh, ok ma'am.
And he, he's gone!
When did you last
see your friend?
I can't find him!
When did you last
see your friend?
I don't know, a half hour!
Ok, ok, ma'am, I need
you to calm down,
we have someone on the way.
Hurry please!
I need you to calm down,
stay put, stay where you're at.
MAN: ...moved spiritually
to his Kingdom,
where they will
become one with others.
And their soul may
grow for Eternity.
For the Lord himself shall
descend from Heaven
with a shout, with the voice
of the Arc Angel.
With the trump of God and the
dead of Christ will rise first,
then which we are alive
and shall remain the same,
be caught up together with
them in the clouds, to meet
the Lord in the air and so we
shall be ever with the Lord.
James has moved on in spirit,
but shall be remembered...
Glad you could make it.
Man, I was just
with him last week.
PRIEST...as we too await our
calling to the Holy Land, Amen.
Shit!
I warned you, dude,
Filipino pussy.
She wasn't
Filipino, man.
Filipino, Malaysian,
whatever, the point is,
you've got to double up
on the raincoats, bro.
Yeah?
Yeah, hey listen, there are
some nasty organisms out there,
alright, E coli, swine flu.
I hooked up with
a Thai chick from --
Highland Park?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How old was she
again, 12?
She looked it...
after she shaved.
That's cute, man,
that's real cute.
I know.
You, my friend, are
a sick fucking asshole.
You think?
Mm-hmm.
It's so hard out there,
you have no idea.
Guys will post their pictures
online and you're like,
oh hey, he's cute,
maybe I'll get past
the "let's grab
a mochaccino" stage.
Yeah right, you meet the guy
and he's a freaking caveman.
I don't know what happened,
I used to be so fuckable
in high school.
Jessie, really?
I just have this sick
feeling that something
awful is going to happen.
Come here,
don't say that.
It's going to be ok.
It's just, first,
my fiance cheats on me
and I have to call off
my wedding...
and now Jimmy.
I know, I know.
Come on.
So how's your love
life, Courtney?
Fantastic, Ryan,
how's yours?
No complaints here.
I'm surprised your dick
hasn't fallen off by now.
Um...it's great to
see everybody again.
I just wish the situation
was a little different.
I think it's important
that we remember Jimmy
and the good times that we had.
So with that, uh, I would
like to propose a toast.
What the fuck is a toast
gonna do, bring him back?
You know what,
shut the fuck up, Nathan!
Why do you have to be so
depressing all the time?
Don't you think it's depressing
romanticizing a guy
that was stupid enough
to get himself killed
because he was in deep
with some drug dealers?
Or whatever
happed to him.
Don't you have any
fucking feelings, Nathan?
Such an asshole.
Like I was about to say...
To Jimmy, he was a great friend,
and the funniest guy
I've ever met.
No matter how down you were,
or no matter how down he was,
he was always good for a laugh.
Here here.
Cheers.
Do you guys remember when
he rearranged the reindeer
on Mrs. Heller's lawn,
so on Christmas Day
they were all
humping each other?
Christmas morning,
right?
Classic, man.
Or the time that
he jelloed the pool?
Or the time that he faked
putting pot into all
the cafeteria cupcakes and the
entire school was dismissed
because everyone thought
they were high?
Oh my God.
Remember Donald Buckley?
Oh my God...
It's on, go!
Hi Donald!
Congratulations on
being Valedictorian.
Blow any football
players this weekend?
That's funny, Donald.
Actually, I am doing an
interview for the school paper
and I was wondering if
you wanted to answer
a couple questions for us.
No.
Hey, it's on!
It's On!
One shot dude,
one shot right here.
There he is,
there he is.
Yes!
Fuck you, Buckley!
There goes your
scholarship, buddy!
So what did Jimmy have
against Donald Buckley?
Hmm...He asked Beth
out on a date.
Buckley?
What?
Oh my God.
I mean, I don't understand,
why did everyone wanna
ask out Beth
in high school?
She's cute, ok.
She was more than cute.
She had that, uh,
that velvet tongue.
I'm getting tight in the pants
just thinking about her.
Beth was always
there for you.
You do anything?
You had a thing for
Beth, huh, Nathan?
Oh, you're
blushing, dude.
Beth was Jimmy's girlfriend.
Yeah, alright, guys.
Who's the asshole, huh?
What? No, not me.
Seriously guys,
come on, pizza?
I mean, that's really
fucking high school.
Maybe a little bit of
imagination next time?
There's five
boxes, Ryan.
One for each of us.
Yo, Pedro, where...where'd
the pizzas come from, huh?
No? You don't speak English?
Not a fucking thing, huh?
Fuck man!
Help!
Help! Help!
Hey Beth, it's Ron from
work, uh, where are ya?
Beth, it's Ron.
Two days in a row,
I hope everything's ok.
Call the office.
Hey Beth, I don't
know what to say...
sorry this isn't working out,
um, there's no need to come in,
we'll mail you a check.
Ok, good luck.
Beth, I, uh, I hope this
is you, it's me, Jessie,
Jessie Anderson
from Grace Arbor.
Beth, I, I have some
bad news about Jimmy.
Look, I'm sorry, ok?
I didn't want to
scare the girls.
Bullshit, you didn't
want to scare the girls!
Why didn't you tell me?
It's confidential,
Ryan, ok?
If word got out that Jimmy
was barbequed like a brisket,
the whole town would go crazy.
I mean, there is a sick fuck
out there, dude.
Somebody stole my phone.
What?
Look, I'm not sure
what happened, alright.
Maybe you misplaced it.
Did you check your car
or something?
No, that fucking thing
is tethered to me, man.
I called the pizza parlor.
Somebody called in those pizzas
under my name, using my phone.
Look, you gotta start telling
me everything, ok Blake?
Ok!
I mean it!
Alright!
No more of this
police bullshit.
Hey Blake?
Somebody's fucking
with our heads, man.
Talk to Nathan?
No, fuck Nathan!
Fucking faggot.
Who moved my fucking car?
You're fucking kidding me.
Someone racked up a thousand
dollars in porn sites
on my credit card.
Somebody moved my car
to another parking spot.
Someone ordered a guy
prostitute to my house.
I got this in the mail today.
Dipshit, why didn't you
tell me you had my phone?
I had to see if we
were involved, man!
We're being targeted, Ryan!
Shit.
Do you know what's
happening right now?
What do you mean
we're being targeted?
Jimmy wasn't killed because
of a bad gambling debt
and Blake knows it.
Jimmy was killed on
the same day as Brandon Booth.
You guys remember him?
Three years to the exact
same day, June 5th...
Someone knows what
happened at Sandy Beach.
Someone knows we were involved.
No, no, that's impossible,
nobody else was there.
It's Beth.
It wasn't Beth.
It's Beth,
she was there!
Beth was out of town,
she would've had to have
done everything herself.
Ok, maybe she
has someone.
Beth hated pranks,
it wasn't her!
Guys!
Blake, what's going on?
The police think that it was
somebody from high school
who killed Jimmy.
Who? Why?
I don't know...
Jimmy did a lot of messed up
things to a lot of people.
So the police don't know about
Sandy Beach then, do they, hmm?
No.
Lucky for us, America's finest
can't put two and two together.
Nice.
We didn't do anything,
Sandy Beach was Jimmy's fault.
No, we obstructed an
investigation, Courtney.
Do you remember that?
We lied.
That makes us all
accomplices to murder here.
Manslaughter.
Whoa, you guys, I think we're
jumping the gun here, ok listen,
there's nothing that links
Jimmy to Brandon at all.
Of course they were
related dumb fuck!
They were killed
on the same day.
Guys, guys,
what if he's watching us?
What if this person
is watching us?
I can't handle this.
What if whoever killed Jimmy is
going to try and kill us, too?
Stop it.
I'm going to be sick.
Just stop!
You ok?
So what about
you, Blake?
Big-shot Sheriff.
Who ordered
the fucking pizzas?
Fuck off, Ryan.
No, who ordered
the pizzas?
I said, fuck off,
get out of my face!
You didn't answer
my question!
I'm not gonna fucking
answer your question!
Who ordered
the fucking --
Y'all need to
chill out!
Fuck you, Nathan
get out of my way.
Guys, fighting isn't going
to help anything right now!
Fuck you, man, you have
no fucking clue
what you're
talking about, ok?
You're messing up
everything!
I'm not messing
shit up!
I don't know
what I'm doing!
I don't know who ordered
the fucking pizzas!
You're fucking it all up!
You're a fucking asshole, man.
Hi there.
I am looking for the
high school yearbooks.
Ah, they're in the
reference section,
back aisle
against the wall.
Thank you very much,
appreciate it.
Find 'em?
Um...2010,
it's not here.
Oh, uh, let me
check the front.
Liam Rivers?
Yeah.
Sorry about the mess, we go
to print in a couple hours.
You wrote an article
about my brother,
he died three years
ago on Sandy Beach.
Brandon Booth.
Brandon Booth?
I remember,
drowning accident.
What do you want to know?
Well, what can you
tell me about it?
Just that the town
was pretty shaken up.
Did you say you
were his brother?
MAN:
911, what's your emergency?
WOMAN:
911? Thank God!
My friend went swimming
in Sandy Beach!
A wave came and he's gone!
I can't find him!
I don't know, a half hour!
His name is Brandon Booth!
Brandon Booth!
Yes, hurry please!
That was great, Beth.
No one's ever gonna know.
Beth, there's nothing
we can do about it, ok?
It was an accident.
Geez...Brother goes
searching for his brother
after they were separated
in a foster home as kids,
only to find that he's dead
when he comes looking for him.
That is a hell of a story!
You want to do
a feature, kid?
Brandon was with someone the
night he died, is that right?
Let me see, it was
a long time ago, um...
Yes, he was with a girl.
Good kid.
She seemed pretty broken up
about the whole thing.
Ah, what was her name?
Rebecca.
Becky.
It was Beth.
Donald Buckley,
is that you?
It's me, Beth.
We were on yearbook
staff together.
Oh my God!
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to startle you.
No, no, it's just...
I know, I look
just like him.
I'm Liam,
Brandon's brother.
Brandon's...
Brandon never
mentioned he had...
He never knew I existed.
Can we talk?
It's Beth, right?
I saw your picture
in the yearbook.
Um, this is a really bad time.
Ok, yeah, I get it.
Of course.
Um, well, I'll be in
town for a few days.
Here, let me...
Here's my number.
I'd love to ask you a few
questions about Brandon...
What he was like,
things he liked to do.
I really have to go.
I didn't mean to scare you!
Beth?
I'm Kelly.
Jessie left her keys.
Hi, Helen.
What do you want?
Oh, I don't want anything.
I just wanted to tell
you that I'm sorry.
Helen?
I'm apologizing to you, ok?
I'm sorry.
My mother had to read the letter
you forged from the doctors...
Do you know what it's like
for your mother to think
you're HIV positive?
Enough with the drama, Helen.
It was all in good fun.
Are you fucking
kidding me?
Telling everybody I had
a tainted blood transfusion
when I was really sick is fun?
It was high school, Helen.
People do stupid things.
I apologize.
Really.
I hope you die.
I hope something really
horrible happens to you.
You're cruel and pathetic
and you don't even deserve
to say you're sorry.
Everything alright?
Hi there.
Hi.
Hey Jessie, it's Blake.
I got your text,
I'm on my way.
This is Lincoln One Mary.
I am 10-7, out of service.
Repeat.
10-7, out of service.
Copy Lincoln One Mary.
LOUDSPEAKER:
Starting Head Linebacker,
from Grace Arbor High School,
Number 58, Blake Holden.
Starting Head Linebacker,
from Grace Arbor High School,
Number 58, Blake Holden.
Starting Head Linebacker,
from Grace Arbor High School,
Number 58, Blake Holden.
Starting Head Linebacker,
from Grace Arbor High School,
Number 58, Blake Holden.
Starting Head Linebacker,
from Grace Arbor High School,
Number 58, Blake Holden.
Starting Head Linebacker,
from Grace Arbor High School,
Number 58, Blake Holden.
Oh God, what the fuck?
What the fuck is this?
God damn it!
What did you
give him anyway?
A couple roofies.
He's fine.
This is mean, Jimmy,
it's cruel.
He never did
anything to you.
Oh no?
He only follows you
all around on campus.
Oh, come on.
Your fairy little
lap dog.
Yeah, wait 'til he sees himself
online in the morning.
Start digging-
C'mon, Beth.
This is my last prank,
I swear.
Please?
That a girl!
Alright, so I think we should
put the hole here.
I'll throw him in.
Jessie?
So Jessie never even talked
to you this evening then?
No.
She just left you her
keys where she works?
That's right.
She never told you
where she was going,
what she was doing?
No.
Did she ever talk about going
to see an old classmate,
someone she might have
pulled a prank on?
What do you mean prank?
You think this has something
to do with high school?
Did Blake ever do anything
back in high school
that would make someone
want to hurt him?
What were you doing,
what were you doing?
Someone, whoever it is, didn't
appreciate their sense of humor.
Is it safe to stay here?
I don't think it's safe
anywhere in Grace Arbor, Beth.
Did you ever do anything
to anybody in high school?
No.
Good.
You might want to
lock your door.
Sheriff, can you
tell us anything?
Are the victims from
Grace Arbor High School?
We're still identifying
the bodies.
I have no new information
for you,
we need to notify the families,
that's all I have for you now.
Thank you.
Can you tell us what
year they graduated?
No Jack, I can't.
Well, does this have anything
to do with the Edwards case?
Don' push it, Jack!
Asshole.
And there you have it,
no word yet if the two victims
are from Grace Arbor
High School.
This is Mara Simone outside
the crime scene for Action News.
Alright, so who
do we have?
Ronald Wallace.
That pecker boy
from the bathroom?
Ok great.
What about
Helen Guimond?
Ah, she was working.
Nobody knows what
time she got off.
Put her on the list.
Ok, so who do we have?
C'mon.
Um, Debbie Simmons,
Rita Snavely.
I need guys, GUYS-
Timothy Thaler.
Bruce Butler.
Donald Buckley.
Jesus Christ!
Jessie and Blake were murdered!
What the fuck is
wrong with you two?
Courtney, we can't
go to the cops, okay?
And we can't tell them
what happened to Brandon.
The only way we get out of this
is if we find out
who is doing the killing.
It's Beth.
She was my best friend.
How are you, Beth?
Don't ask.
So what's going on?
The Sheriff came by
Jessie's house last night.
Sheriff Morello.
He thinks someone in Grace
Arbor is getting revenge.
So he was here yesterday
looking for the 2010 yearbook?
That's right.
And you say it
wasn't here then?
No, it wasn't.
Reference books aren't
supposed to be checked out.
Did he ask
about Brandon?
No.
He didn't say
anything about it?
No.
Just told him about Ronald
Wallace getting fire-crackered.
We made a list.
Yeah, only half
the friggin' school.
What about that teacher,
the one you put the gay porn
in his slide projector?
Richards?
Gay people aren't
serial killers.
No man, what about Dahmer?
Remember him?
Right.
Put him on the list.
Can you think
of anyone, Ryan?
Something you
might have done?
What about Coach Novotska?
What did you do?
He blackmailed him into signing
off on his football scholarship.
What?
You know, I don't think
this is really the time.
Hell yeah,
this is the time!
How do you know he didn't do it?
Because I just know.
Ryan?
What did you do?
Aw, fuck, man.
Look, I had Courtney
take a couple pictures
with Coach Novotska.
I put a camera in her car
while she was with him
and she took her top off.
I wish that was all I did.
No wonder I'm
so fucked up.
You know, you didn't
have to do it, Courtney.
Jesus, Ryan!
You were my boyfriend, ok,
I wanted you to go to college!
What about you?
Please, She doesn't have
anything to worry about.
Brandon's dead.
Not exactly...
Brandon has a twin brother.
He's in Grace Arbor and he
wants to know all about him.
Shit.
Hey Bobo?
I need an age on blue boy.
Jimmy Edwards, 22.
What year is his
graduating class?
2010.
Hey?
What about that kid that
drowned over at Sandy Beach?
Got a graduating year
on him?
This is sick, man.
Yeah, what do you
suggest we do, Nathan?
You want to call
the police?
Room 122, great,
be there in five minutes.
You don't have
to do this, Beth.
I'm fine, ok, I'm fine.
Ya see that?
She's fine.
Yeah well, you're
not the one going in --
Nathan, I'm fine!
I can handle it.
How did he sound?
I mean, he doesn't
expect anything.
He just wants to
talk about Brandon.
Ok.
What if I find something?
Like a murder weapon?
What do you think
she should do?
Ah, that's great.
Send her in some hotel room
with a fucking serial killer
and you don't know
what she should do.
Hey wait, wait, wait.
Alright, maybe Nathan's right.
Maybe you don't have to go in.
No, I have to...l want to.
What if he's the killer?
Well, then we'll find out it's
him when she shows up dead.
Relax, Nathan.
The dude isn't going to take
her out in broad daylight
in his own hotel room.
I didn't think you
were going to come.
Why do you say that?
Strange motel,
strange person.
So...
What do you want to
know about Brandon?
What was he like?
He was very generous.
Kind...smart, really smart.
He liked to read.
I always thought he was
going to be a writer one day.
Really?
Brandon had a way
of seeing things.
He liked to laugh.
He had a sense of humor, too.
Dark, but he was very hopeful.
I think that's why
I liked being around him.
You always felt hopeful
when you were around him.
Were you his
girlfriend?
Um, I was seeing
someone at the time.
I hope you don't
mind me asking...
what happened the night
he went swimming?
The night he went swimming?
God...
Uh...
I, uh, told him not to go.
The undertow was really strong.
He wanted to anyway.
It was night.
Oh God, it was so horrible.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm just
really jumpy lately.
I don't blame you.
She's been in there
forever, I'm going in.
Nathan, just wait.
Hey, hey!
Beth, you ok?
Ryan, I'm leaving town
for a couple days, I'm sorry.
You're what?
Look, I have some business
I have to take care of, alright?
I gotta get out.
You don't have any fucking
business somewhere else, ok?
We're supposed to
stick to the plan,
we're gonna stick
together, alright?
If you don't do that, this
all goes to shit and we die.
Ok, Ryan, I am really
freaked out about
everything that's
happening, ok?
You have my number.
Court.
Shit!
Fuck!
Two people were
killed last night.
Did you know them?
I think I should go.
Aren't you forgetting
something?
Hey!
You forgot
your cell phone.
Thank you.
Look, I know
this isn't easy,
but I feel like I know
Brandon a little better now.
He must have been a
really special person
to have you
as a friend.
Thank you.
So...what do you do to keep
yourself occupied around here?
Oh gosh...l don't know anymore,
it's been such a long time.
Well, do you want
to grab dinner?
Um...
On me.
There's a place
called Moore's Pub.
It's on Main.
8:00?
8:00 is great.
Cool.
Alright.
Um, take care.
I will.
Yeah, it's...
So?
It's not him.
He's not a murderer.
No, no, how do you know?
Because he's just like Brandon.
Liam, Jack Meyer from
the Grace Arbor Gazette .
I have some information
about your brother
that you may find
very interesting.
Give me a call.
Got 'em.
Yeah.
Nothing gets
by you, Jack.
Hello?
Yeah, he's here.
Yeah, just a second.
It's for you.
Mr. Richards?
This is Nathan Nesbitt
from Grace Arbor High.
Uh...
Listen, I just wanted to
apologize for putting that porn
in your slide projector.
It's, it's been really
bothering me lately.
Ronald?
You got a sec?
We'll get rid of this little
chubbiness right there.
She is practically gift wrapped.
Oh man, just the way
I like 'em.
Whoo, alright.
Hi.
You live here?
What are you doing?
Just striking up a
conversation with a hot chick.
Really?
A hot chick?
Yeah.
How sweet.
Look at me.
Oh, I'm looking at you.
No, I want you to look at me.
Why? See you for
who you are?
Something like that.
Are you looking?
I'm peering
into your soul.
Good.
Now start the
conversation from the top.
Whoa, I like this.
A little role playing.
Go!
Alright.
Two strangers in a bar.
From the top.
Alright, here we go.
Hi.
You live here?
Fantastic.
You're really looking
at me now, aren't you?
Oh, I'm virtually
undressing you as we speak.
Great.
Because I wouldn't
fuck you if you were
the last living
thing on earth.
Don't take it so hard.
I'm lousy in bed.
I see a therapist twice
a week, I'm on medication.
I wouldn't fuck me either.
Thanks for the warning.
Fuckin' bitch.
What was that?
What, man?
Is there a problem?
No problem at all.
She's all yours.
Let's get the
fuck out of here.
Well, well, if it isn't
Prince Charming to the rescue
after four hours.
I'm sorry.
I had some things
to take of.
Must have been important.
We need to talk
about Brandon.
I thought that's what
we were here to do.
Now.
Jesus Christ, Sheriff,
now I've seen it all.
That bad, huh?
This is the receptionist.
Holy shit!
Oh, it get's better.
Wait 'til you see
what's in the lipo room.
Her name's Courtney Brenan.
She's from Grace Arbor.
Hey Bro!
Chick's bad news, man.
Get in the car.
Yeah man,
she's a fucking cunt.
Hey! Get in the car now!
And if she's a fucking
cunt, what's that make you?
I'll tell you what,
that makes him a cunt fucker.
Yeah! Yeah!
What'd you just call me?
Yeah, that's what
I called you, c'mon!
Slice him up, bro.
Let's go, let's go,
I'm going to fuck you up.
Mother fucker!
Give me the keys.
Give me the keys!
What are you doing?
You haven't been
honest with me, Beth!
You ever hear
of Jack Meyer?
He's a reporter.
Slime, but he had some pretty
interesting things to say.
Why didn't you tell me
Brandon was taking drugs
the night he died?
What do you
want from me?
It was three years
ago, ok, I forgot!
Why did you let
him go swimming?
Because I didn't know
he was on medication.
I don't believe you.
Look, I don't
owe you anything.
You owe him, Beth!
You were his friend.
You see this?
I have a fucking
drugstore in my purse.
I don't tell every
person I know.
He never told me.
I didn't know he was
going to die, ok?
I didn't know he
was going to die!
Oh God! Brandon!
Brandon!
Where is he?
I don't know.
Find him!
Brandon!
He's got to be
here somewhere.
Brandon!
Listen, he probably
woke up and left.
He probably
already left!
Fuck you!
What did you do?
I don't know, we'll
keep looking for him.
Brandon, if you're out
here, it's not funny!
What did you do?
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Oh my God!
Courtney, no!
When did it happen?
Tonight.
It was on the news.
Are you sure
it's her?
Courtney said she
was leaving town
and someone was
killed in Sterling.
It's her.
So where were you two tonight?
Did you tell
him anything?
What do you
think, Nathan?
Fucking Brandon's brother isn't
going to bring him back, Beth.
You just
better not.
You're a regular killing
machine, aren't you, Liam?
Where were you tonight?
Where were you?
What is it with you people
in this town, huh?
What'd you do for
fun last night?
Well, you have to admit,
you make a great suspect.
It's from Brandon.
He and I never met, but we did
write each other in high school.
Then the letters stopped
and I never knew why.
Go ahead, read it, Beth.
He talks about you a lot.
You wanna know why
I came to Grace Arbor?
I just wanted to know that there
was some light somewhere.
That just maybe, Brandon had
a better life than I had.
It's all so clear to me now.
How do I know it's love?
I think I would die for her.
Liam! Liam!
Dude, I've been trying
to get a hold of you.
Where you've been?
Chill man, I went to Sterling.
I talked to Coach Novotska.
Coach Novotska?
Yeah, I thought
I should apologize.
He said he did a lot of asshole
things, too, but he was cool.
I saw them take
her body out.
Dude, it's Brandon's
brother.
Check this.
His real name is
Liam Bennett.
He was molested by
both his parents.
They kept him in the basement
for like three years.
Dude took his father's
shotgun, killed them both.
Then he shot himself
in the chest and lived.
He, he was exonerated by the
courts because he was a minor.
He underwent major
psychiatric counseling.
There's your killer.
He knows what
happened to Brandon.
He knows we're involved.
Beth.
She told him.
Fucking Beth told him!
"W: I'm here in Sterling where
police have cordoned off
the area of what I have been
told is a grisly murder scene.
At the present time,
it is unclear
how many people inside are dead.
I want insider access and
a cover story on his arrest.
We got a deal?
What's his name, Jack?
Ah, give me a second.
His name is Liam Bennett,
but he goes by Rivers.
He's staying at the Motel
down by the highway.
Son of a bitch!
Jack?
Jack are you there?
Jack is that you?
Liam, it's me Beth!
We have to talk!
Liam, open up!
We can't stay here!
Trust me, it's not safe!
C'mon.
This is 8 David 4.
Request a unit be sent
to 713 Whitney Ave.
To check the welfare
of Jack Meyer.
I'm in route to the motel
by the Highway.
Will advise when I'm 9/7.
Fucking Beth, man!
I never trusted
that bitch.
RSI-Ryan!
Fuck man!
Where did he come from?
Dude, dude, dude,
it's the Sheriff.
We almost hit
the fucking Sheriff.
Shit.
Oh, we gotta go,
we gotta go, we gotta go.
That's not mine.
I didn't put that there.
It wasn't me.
Let's go.
Let's, c'mon, let's just go,
let's go, let's go!
Someone put it
in my room.
Who, Beth?
You're the only one who
knows where I was staying.
I wasn't thinking.
I mean, I brought them because
I thought you might...
It's Nathan or Ryan...
Oh my God.
Why did you go
to Sterling?
I went to talk to
Coach Novotska, ok?
You don't believe me?
Call him!
Fuck man.
I don't know who
to believe anymore.
Nathan, if I wanted you dead,
you would have been
first on my list.
I know what happened to you.
It's Beth.
Get out of the car, Beth!
There was a game
we played in therapy.
Did you know that, Beth?
C'mon Beth,
you can do it.
Liam, I'm sorry for what
happened to you, ok.
We all have fucked up pasts!
I'm not finished, Beth.
The shrinks thought it was
important in my healing.
It's called
re-association.
You re-live the
moment of trauma
and go back to
where it all began.
Can you imagine?
Most kids are out playing
football, going to their proms.
I was having my dreams
analyzed by ten-dollar-an-hour
therapists who fondled me
in the name of mental health.
Where did it
happen, Beth?
Liam...I'm.
Where did it happen?
Right there.
You want to know
what the worst part
about killing
your parents is?
Think about it, Beth.
It's the guilt.
I actually felt guilty for
taking those monsters' lives.
Guilt is a motherfucker,
isn't it?
It eats away at your
aspirations, your dreams,
your fucking soul!
You having a hard time
sleeping at night, Beth?
What did you do to him?
It was just supposed
to be a prank.
Jimmy was jealous of Brandon,
he buried him in the sand
after giving him some pills
at a party.
He was only supposed to be
unconscious for an hour.
But we fell asleep
and the tide came in.
Well, Beth...
I guess there's only
one thing left to do.
I'm really sorry
about this.
I'm taking you
to the police.
Nobody's taking
anybody anywhere.
Hate to inform you, buddy,
but you've got a serious
credibility issue.
Yeah, unstable psychopath
who murdered his parents
seeking to cleanse
his demons away
by avenging his brother's death?
Do you really think the cops
are going to believe you?
They don't have to believe me.
They'll believe her.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't keep the secret.
Beth, you're being a little over
emotional, don't you think, hm?
They're going to
put us all away.
Especially you, Beth.
You were there.
We should have told the
truth from the beginning.
C'mon, Beth.
See ya later, fellas.
Have a nice life.
You fucking cowards.
You oughta think twice.
Jesus, Ryan.
What are you doing?
Stay out of this, Nathan!
Showing your
true colors, Ryan?
Shut the fuck up, asshole!
Why'd you take all
your friends out, Ryan?
Afraid someone
might crack?
Afraid someone might tell
the truth about Brandon?
Don't fuck with me, man!
Jimmy was the first
to crumble, wasn't he?
He couldn't take the guilt
over Brandon's death
so he was going to
turn himself in,
but you couldn't have that.
No, you had to killed Jimmy.
But then you had to kill,
Blake, Jessie, Courtney!
One more word and I swear,
I will fucking kill you!
Did you do it, Ryan?
Stay outta this, Nathan!
Ryan, did you do it?
What do you think, bro?
Oh my God!
Drop it!
Drop the weapon!
So this is how it's
done in Grace Arbor?
Last time!
Put your hands above your
head and drop the weapon!
NO! No!
Oh my God! Liam.
It's not fair...
It's not fair.
It wasn't him!
You son of a bitch!
Alright, calm down,
calm down, calm down!
It wasn't him!
Put the weapon down!
Shit, shit, shit.
Oh God...Oh God.
Help, help!
Help!
No, no...
Helen?
Oh, hi.
It's Beth, right?
You work here?
Part time.
Things have been really
slow lately at the diner.
Hope you feel better.
Did Blake ever do anything
back in high school
that would make someone
want to hurt him?
Can you think of anyone, Ryan,
something you might have done?
What about Coach Novotska?
What about that teacher?
Richards? Gay people
aren't serial killers.
Did she ever talk about going
to see an old classmate?
Someone she might have
pulled a prank on?
No, please!
Thanks for the ride,
I appreciate it.
I just wanted to make
sure you got here safely.
What are you going to do when
you get back to New York?
Probably find a job.
Good luck with that.
Listen, here's my card...
if you ever wanna talk.
I told you everything
I know, Sheriff.
I hope so, Beth...
I really hope so.
You know when I came out here,
I thought I'd get away
from the big city,
catch up on my fishing,
drive the wife wherever
the hell she wants.
Whoever did this,
I hope they never
step foot in
Grace Arbor again.
Good luck to you, Beth.
Thanks.