GOD'S NOT DEAD 2
Subrip: Pix
Brooke, we're all upset,
but we need to move on.
Honey, you're a junior now.
It's your make-or-break year.
So there's no room
for self pity.
Can you give Marlene and I
a ride to school today?
I'm sorry.
I don't have time.
I have an 8:30 with Marc
Shelley at White & Wolfe.
What? Richard, you didn't say anything!
How did you get the meeting?
It's just a meeting, so don't get
too excited. But it could be huge.
I know!
Who's going to
the meeting with you?
Hey, I got the meeting.
I just think maybe you should
take Melinda or Janice.
Janice? You want
me to take Janice?
-Yeah. Why not?
-I'm not taking Janice.
-Rough morning?
-You know my parents.
Maybe they just
need a little more time.
I don't know
about that.
I'd say they're
pretty over it.
My mom's making tacos tonight.
I'll let her know you're coming.
It's not like
they'll miss me.
Brooke, I'm serious, honey.
You need to get focused.
Or you can say, "Good-bye,
Stanford, hello, Somewhere State."
Got it.
Yikes.
Good morning!
Morning, Grace.
You don't have to
keep doing this.
Are you kidding? This is the
best part of my day, Gramps.
Well, pills first.
You're a good girl.
Honey, you know I'm not
gonna be around here forever,
and you might wanna start
thinking about some other guy
you wanna have breakfast with.
I'll work on that.
Okay.
You know, I love the way
you do the oatmeal,
but what do you say I take you out
for bacon and eggs this morning.
My treat.
Not after your
last cholesterol test.
Besides, I have some papers I have
to grade before the staff meeting.
I'm 81 years old, and bacon is
not gonna be what kills me.
Nice try. You're 82.
Yeah.
-Good morning.
-Have a nice day.
Morning, ladies.
Morning.
Good morning.
Hey, what do you call
a teacher with no students?
Unemployed.
I got it.
How about ecstatic?
You're both right.
Retired.
Only 36 days to go.
You're gonna miss the kids
when you're gone, Rizzo.
No, Grace, that's sweet,
but no, I won't.
The older I get, the more difficult
these kids are to deal with.
I totally agree. Yesterday, I just
about snapped at Tim Webster.
That boy had me
on my last nerve.
Well, I happen to think that difficult
students can be a blessing.
Grace, honey, when is this
optimism ever gonna wear off?
Bill.
Junk mail.
Man!
David, why are
you always so sad?
Hey! You're back.
Why are you back?
My pastor gave me permission to
finish my doctorate at Hadleigh,
so if that's okay with you,
I'm gonna be here for a while.
David, you are a mess.
What happened to you?
I woke up.
Okay, for 500 points, for all
the cheese, for the game.
This quote
is from what document?
"We hold these truths
to be self-evident,
that all men are created equal,
that they are endowed by their creator
with certain unalienable rights..."
Boom, baby!
Team 1,
what's your answer?
Our answer is the Declaration
of Independence.
That's...
correct!
Team 1 wins!
Okay, monday we will
examine the assertion
of individual rights through the
last century. Have a good weekend.
Brooke, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yeah, thanks.
Ms. Ryan?
I lied.
Are you sure
you're being fair?
Trust me. They're over it. And
they expect me to be over it too.
It's like to them
never even existed.
The only thing
that I know for sure
is that I'm never going
to see my brother again.
Everybody's asked if there's
anything that they can do.
The truth is,
no one can do anything
because the only thing I really
want is five more minutes
to tell my brother
how I really felt about him.
Did you brother believe
there was something more?
I don't know.
Do you?
Brooke, every person
reaches a point in their
life when they ask
themselves this question.
There's nothing wrong
with you asking it too.
You never let anything
get to you.
How do you do that?
Jesus.
Hello?
How'd it go, Amy?
Michael.
It's gone.
My cancer's... It's gone.
My goodness!
That's incredible!
I know. I just...
I can't believe it.
Isn't that
what you prayed for?
Yes, of course.
I just...
Prayer
is a powerful thing,
and it turns out God has
much bigger plans for you.
You okay, Grace?
Yeah, I just can't stop
thinking about Brooke.
You know, she's searching.
She's hurting.
Yeah, that's the thing
about atheism.
It doesn't take away the pain.
It just takes away the hope.
What'd you tell her?
The truth.
Now she's free to
make her own choice.
Unfortunately,
in this day and age,
people seem to forget that the
most basic human right of all
is the right
to know Jesus.
Let's put her
on the prayer list.
Prayer always seems to be
the last thing we do,
when it should be the first.
Now, how 'bout
some more popcorn?
With a glycemic index
of 100, not a chance.
I swear, Grace, if you
don't start feeding me better,
I'm gonna leave you
for a nursing home.
Well, that's it for me.
I'm going to bed.
Love ya.
I love you better.
Love you first.
That's unfair.
Gotcha!
Brooke,
the people from that charity place are
here to pick up your brother's things.
Can you make sure
they get everything?
And don't forget to
put the milk away!
Well,
that's the last of it.
Thank you.
And while I was loading one
of the boxes onto the truck,
I noticed this and I thought
you might want to keep it.
So sorry for your loss.
So peaceful nonviolence comes
first in India under Gandhi,
and then later, here in the United
States under Dr. King and others
as a means of
achieving civil rights.
But what makes
nonviolence so radical
is its unwavering commitment
to a nonviolent approach,
not just initially, but in the
face of escalating persecution
by the opposing force.
Yes?
Isn't that sort of
like what Jesus meant
when said that we
should love our enemies?
Yes.
The writer
of the gospel of Matthew
records Jesus as saying,
"You have heard it said,
love your neighbor
and hate your enemy,
but I tell you,
love your enemies
and pray for those
who persecute you,
that you will be children
of your father in heaven,"
which indicates
a commitment to nonviolence.
Dr. King confirmed the link, describing
his inspiration from Scripture,
saying Christ furnished
the spirit and motivation,
while Gandhi
furnished the method.
Except that that didn't work. Jesus got
himself killed. Everybody knows that.
Well, so did Dr. King.
So I guess it just depends
on how you measure success.
Both men created movements
that survive to this day,
even though both
paid the ultimate price
for their commitment
to their ideals.
I still wouldn't do it.
Well, not very many people
have that kind of courage.
But I, for one, am grateful
for those that do,
you know, those who stand up
for what they believe.
Have a good day.
Are you Pastor Dave?
I am.
I'm Martin Yip.
Nice to meet you.
My friend Josh Wheaton
said you might be able
to answer my questions
about God.
Well, that definitely falls
within my job description.
How many questions
have you got?
So far, 147.
Is something wrong?
No.
Josh encouraged me to write them down
and be as comprehensive as possible.
Of course did. I'll have to
thank him next time I see him.
Come on.
So, what's
your first question?
Grace, I just have
to hear it from you.
Did this happen?
If you're asking whether I responded
to a student's question, yes.
If you're asking whether
her question and my answer
both referenced Jesus
as it was relevant
to the history lesson we were
discussing, again, I'd have to say...
yes.
Good afternoon,
Ms. Wesley.
I've asked Bob Fessler to sit
in... he's the school's attorney...
To advise us on any legal issues
we might be brushing up against.
Should I have
a lawyer too?
I don't see
the need for that.
Ms. Rizzo is present
as your union representation.
Okay.
We are here to hear
your side of the story.
Now, I understand a student in
your second-period history class
asked a question
about the parallels
between
the teachings of Gandhi
and remarks
allegedly made by Jesus.
Yes, that's correct.
And your answer incorporated specific
detailed reference to those teachings
that included
Scripture itself,
the words of Jesus.
Yes.
What were you thinking,
Grace?
Do you believe your response was
in line with district policy?
Yes.
As well as in compliance with
state and federal guidelines?
Yes, sir.
Well, Ms. Wesley,
unfortunately for you,
I'm fairly certain the
school board will disagree.
No, Coach,
you're not hearing me.
No prayers.
No moments of silence.
Nothing.
It's tradition
on the field.
Not on the field,
not in the locker room,
not in the parking lot
for that matter, okay?
-Whatever you say.
-Okay, thanks, Coach.
Come on in.
-Hi, Brooke.
-You wanted to see me?
Ms. Wesley is currently
under disciplinary review.
All of her classes have been
reassigned until things are settled.
I don't want you to have
any contact with her.
None whatsoever, either
on or off school property.
Do I have any say in this?
No, I've already discussed things
with your father and agrees.
Since when
does my dad care?
Brooke, the important thing for you to
remember is you've done nothing wrong.
Neither did Ms. Wesley. All she
did was answer a question.
Ms. Wesley's answer was not in
line with school policy. -Really?
Aren't we allowed to say what we
believe? When did that change?
I'm not gonna argue with you,
and I don't want you discussing
the situation with anyone.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Grace?
-Are you...
-Tom Endler.
Your union-appointed
attorney.
You don't look
like a lawyer.
Thank you.
I'm not sure I meant
that as a compliment.
I'm determined to take
it as one. Shall we sit?
So, have you defended
many teachers
in disciplinary matters?
Nope, you're my first.
Just hired on from
the public defender's office.
Criminal law? No offense,
but I'm not a criminal.
Don't be so sure of that. Your kind of
case makes everybody uncomfortable.
School boards,
teachers, parents.
Makes them feel... yucky.
"Yucky"?
Is that a technical
legal term?
You got a better word for it?
Grace, I'm gonna
level with you.
Nobody wants your case.
I drew it because
I'm low man on the totem pole
in a place where
seniority means everything.
If, for whatever reason, you're not
happy with me, you're on your own.
You're free to hire your own
attorney out of your own pocket.
Educational law isn't
exactly a common speciality.
So what's the good news?
I don't like to lose. And I'm
willing to fight for you.
Are you a believer?
You mean a Christian?
No.
But I think
that's an advantage.
Why?
You're passionate
about what you believe.
Let's face it. It's why you're
in trouble in the first place.
But it blinds you to
the realities of procedure.
Okay.
Okay, what?
Okay, I agree to
let you represent me.
Good.
Okay.
David, are you okay?
I'm terrific.
There was a young man
in here, brilliant kid,
with no exposure to Scripture
until a few months ago.
Came in
with some questions.
147 of 'em, to be exact.
Feel like I've been hit by a
truck loaded with Bibles.
Big heavy ones
with those thick covers.
"Always be ready to
give answer as to why
you believe and the
reason for your hope."
1 Peter
chapter 3, verse 15.
Yes.
And where were you
four hours ago?
"Trust in the Lord with all your heart
and lean not on your own understanding.
In all your ways,
acknowledge him
and will make
your path straight."
Father, I need you.
I can't do this alone.
I know that you're in control.
Please, give me the courage.
In Jesus' name, amen.
Call to order.
I assume
Ms. Wesley understands
that this board has
the power to recommend
any number of
disciplinary actions,
up to and including
termination.
She does.
And this board should be aware that
in the event of such termination,
which we would view as
wrongful and without cause,
she reserves all
rights of redress.
I may have a solution.
There might be a way around
all of this unpleasantness
that would satisfy
all parties.
A disciplinary notice
in Ms. Wesley's file
stating the school board's
objections to her behavior,
a response from Ms. Wesley
confessing
the inappropriateness of
and apologizing
for her actions,
along with a pledge
not to engage
in similar discussion
of Jesus in the future.
I'm confident that we can
move forward on that basis.
No.
Grace.
I can't.
I'd like to request a brief recess
to have a word with my client.
Excuse me.
Grace, this is exactly
what we were hoping for.
This is the part where you say
you're sorry, thank your lawyer,
go back to your classroom,
pick up your life and move on.
I can't do that.
Why?
I gave an honest answer to a student's
legitimate question in history.
Grace. Grace, you
don't wanna do this.
It's the wrong decision.
Is it?
I mean, I would rather
stand with God
and be judged by the world
than stand with the world
and be judged by God.
I am not gonna be afraid
to say the name Jesus.
I know her.
She's not gonna go for it.
How do we make this go away
and not get blood on our hands?
That's the easy part.
We let the ACLU do it.
They'll file suit
against Ms. Wesley
and if she is found liable,
which she will be,
then we fire her
for cause.
But the school district will
certainly be named as a codefendant.
We don't have the financial
wherewithal to fight that.
They've already
been in touch.
They aren't interested
in punishing the school.
They want her.
Are you sure?
Trust me. They've been
dreaming of a case like this.
While Ms. Wesley apologizes
for any inconvenience
her actions may have caused,
Ms. Wesley stands by
her statements,
and she does not retract or recant
them, either in full or in part.
So noted.
Having little choice,
this board recommends continued
suspension, henceforth without pay,
pending review by a court
of competent jurisdiction
to determine whether or not
Ms. Wesley violated
local, state
or federal guidelines.
This proceeding
is adjourned.
The last thing we need
is a bunch of religious
fanatics protesting
outside of our house.
We'll work to keep it
out of the media for now.
But next year, when you're
applying to all the colleges,
you'll be able to tell
the story of how Brooke
was part of a landmark
constitutional case
concerning the separation
of church and state.
And believe me, there is not
an Ivy League admissions board
that could resist that.
And think of the other
children out there,
innocent children
who are subjected
to their repressive
belief system.
And not forgetting
the financial opportunities.
Yes.
Ms. Wesley is an employee
of the school board.
We win in court and we establish her
misconduct as said paid employee,
well, there's nothing
that changes policy faster
than a big,
expensive settlement.
We're going to prove
once and for all
that God is dead.
Brooke is a minor.
As far as the court is
concerned, she has no rights.
That simply means I won't be
asking her to be a witness.
I feel supremely
confident about this.
Okay.
Injunctive relief?
They're asking
that you be fired,
plus revocation of your
teaching certificate.
What?
How am I supposed to...
Plus attorney's fees.
Essentially, you'II...
You'll lose everything.
Why are they doing this?
They want to make
an example of you.
To them, your beliefs
are like a disease
whose time
has come and gone,
sort of like small pox,
or polio, or the plague.
So, what do we do?
We win.
Hey, what's going on?
Brooke is exercising
her right to protest.
Idiot.
Hey, shut up, loser. At least
she's standing for something.
Give me that.
Brooke, you need to
stop this immediately.
Brooke, this is the last
time I'm gonna tell you.
If you don't stop this right now,
they're are gonna be some consequences.
I don't think there will,
because this is a sidewalk,
which is public property.
My dad's a lawyer.
Well, actually, this sidewalk
is on school property.
I suggest you girls
aren't late for class.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just reading the paper
while my laptop
goes through my online
jury orientation.
Well, shouldn't you
be paying attention?
Please remember that consumption
of alcoholic beverages,
non-prescription drugs and weapons
are prohibited in the courtroom.
Still, isn't it
your civic duty?
Theoretically, yeah,
but Matthew 22:14.
"Many are called,
few are chosen."
Exactly.
Three hundred people show up,
they sit around for eight hours,
and at the end of the day they all
go home, having not been selected.
Statistically, I have a better
chance of being hit by lightning.
Gotta get some coffee.
All right.
It's called "voir dire."
It means that we get a
chance to eliminate any
potential jurors that may
have bias against you.
Sir.
Thank you, sir.
-So, how are you feeling?
-I'm good.
This is a bit of an arduous process.
They bring all these jurors in.
It's gonna take the whole day, but
this is where we can win the case.
All rise for the Honorable
Judge Robert Stennis.
On the order of the matter of Thawley
vs. Wesley, you may be seated.
So, it says here...
What does it say?
It says you're a psychic.
Yes.
Do you know who's gonna win
this case? Don't answer that.
We're going to challenge
this juror, Your Honor.
Ms. Bailey, what's
your favorite TV show?
Pretty Little Liars.
Peremptory challenge,
Your Honor.
What is your
favorite TV show?
Duck Dynasty.
Peremptory challenge,
Your Honor.
Duck Dynasty.
Mrs. Smith, are you involved in any
community or charitable organizations?
Yes, the Salvation Army.
We'll accept this juror,
Your Honor.
Juror number nine.
You're a teacher.
I'm a retired teacher.
Ever have any disciplinary
run-ins with the administration?
Never.
Acceptable to the plaintiff,
Your Honor.
Acceptable, Your Honor.
Peremptory challenge,
Your Honor.
We'll take her, Your Honor.
Thank you, Mr. Cherry. Peremptive
challenge, Your Honor.
Number two
just screams Marine.
I don't want him.
It'll mean
blowing our last challenge.
Well, we have no choice.
What part of "God, Country and Corps"
do you wanna put on that jury?
What was your
last paid position?
Artillery Forward Observer,
United States Marine Corps.
Peremptory challenge,
Your Honor.
Thank you.
Your Honor, we'd like
to challenge for cause.
Why is that?
Your Honor, the man's an ordained
minister. Need I say more?
The juror is excused.
Objection,
Your Honor.
Basis, Mr. Endler?
Discriminatory, Your Honor.
Peremptory challenges
cannot be used to discriminate
against a certain class
of juror based on race,
ethnic background,
religion or gender.
The fact that religious
belief is tangential
to this case doesn't
change that.
Upon further reflection, I find the
respondent's assertion is correct.
Sustained.
You're not her pastor,
are you?
No, Your Honor.
Your Honor,
I must protest here.
Mr. Kane, you had a set number
of peremptory challenges,
all of which you have used.
Therefore, it's up
to opposing counsel.
We accept him, Your Honor.
Welcome to the jury, sir.
Henceforth,
juror number 12.
I hope you enjoy
your service to the community.
Better chance of being
struck by lightning.
It amazes me how we,
as human beings, think.
When I was battling
for my life,
I was willing to hold on
to anything, including God,
even though I really didn't
believe in him until that moment.
I was convinced
that I felt him.
But now that
I'm officially in remission,
I find myself
questioning everything.
So, effective immediately,
this blog is the personal diary
of one woman's
exploration of faith
on her own terms,
cancer-free.
Hey, Martin.
How's it going?
Very good,
Pastor Dave.
Please.
You sure?
Well, it seems that for
every question you answered,
three or four more
questions spring up.
Yeah, but that's
a good thing, right?
It's like what Einstein
said about science.
Picture what you know
like the light of a candle.
As the circle
of knowledge expands,
so does the circumference
of darkness around it.
So, I'm actually learning,
even though
I might not feel like it.
Yes, exactly.
Well, I've been studying
the Beatitudes.
They're very hard, one might say
impossible, to follow completely.
Here in Luke's account,
Jesus says,
"Do unto others as you'd
have them do unto you."
But how is that possible?
How can I react to the needs of
everyone else the same as my own,
even for one day,
let alone my whole life?
And how can I reconcile my
inability to do so with scripture?
Yeah, those
are good questions.
Okay, scoot over.
-What is that, Luke?
-Yes, 6:20.
"And Jesus said
to his disciples,
'You who are poor
are blessed
because the kingdom of God
is yours.
You who are now hungry
are blessed
because you will be filled.
You who now weep are blessed
because you will laugh.
You are blessed when people hate
you, when they exclude you,
insult you and slander your name as
evil because of the Son of Man.'"
You can't win.
Thanks. I'll take that
under advisement.
Come on.
You know I'm right.
I mean, why do it? Why go
through this whole exercise?
Here, thanks.
You know, I looked up
your history.
You're better than this.
You were third in your class
at Stanford Law.
You clerked for a judge
on the Ninth Circuit.
Why are you
slumming like this?
I believe people that
don't do anything wrong
shouldn't suffer at
the hands of the law.
You know what hate is, Tom?
I'm not talking about
the fairy tale stuff.
I mean real hate.
I hate what people
like your client stand for
and what they're
doing to our society.
And Stennis does too,
even if doesn't admit it.
The jury doesn't hate her.
But that's the secret, Tommy.
They don't need to hate her.
They just need to see a tiny
flaw in her, a half truth,
a small inconsistency,
just a little bit of doubt,
and they'll find against her.
Nice shoes.
You ready?
Come on.
Congress shall make no law respecting
an establishment of religion
or prohibiting
the free exercise thereof.
The first half of this passage is
known as the establishment clause.
The second half is known as
the free exercise clause.
Now, there has been
an ongoing debate
about what the role
of government should be,
because in practice,
these two provisions
are often in conflict,
which is what brings us
here today.
In the matter of
Thawley vs. Wesley,
is the plaintiff prepared to
make its opening statement?
We are, Your Honor.
Then proceed.
Ladies and gentlemen,
in a jury of this size,
I'm imagining that there are
probably among your ranks
a few Christians.
Hopefully practicing ones.
And that's a good thing,
that's fine,
because Christianity
is not on trial here,
even though my opponent will
try to convince you that it is.
Nor is faith on trial.
Only Ms. Wesley
is on trial here today.
Now, ask any fourth-grader
and they're probably
familiar with the phrase,
"Separation
of church and state,"
and that is guaranteed
to us under our laws.
The plaintiffs are the parents of
a student in Ms. Wesley's class
who was subjected to hearing
the teachings of Jesus Christ
being favorably compared to the
teachings of Mahatma Gandhi.
We all know that Jesus is part of
a particular religious tradition.
These parents, who are trying to raise
their daughter to be a free thinker,
free of any religious dogma,
are wholly offended by what
went on in that classroom.
And she, reciting the words that
were allegedly attributed to Jesus,
who allegedly lived
2,000 years ago,
gave a clear
and compelling indication
of what she believes,
what she supports,
what she endorses.
Now, let me put it this way.
I don't mean to offend anyone
who may be a Muslim here,
and I do not want to slight
the prophet of Islam,
but if you were to ask me a
question concerning the Koran,
the sacred text of Islam,
and I could come up with the answer
with great speed and accuracy,
and I could quote
the proper sura, or chapter,
then it would be reasonable
for you to infer
that I was not only
a follower of Islam,
but that I considered it
to be superior
to all other forms
of religion.
If I did this in a house of
worship, that would be fine.
But if I did it in an 11th-grade
classroom in a public school,
that would be preaching,
not teaching.
So why in the world
are we here today?
Why? Because Ms. Wesley
refused to apologize.
And that means that her true motivation
in that moment in her classroom
was to take
an innocent question
and turn it into
an opportunity to preach,
not teach.
If we grant Ms. Wesley
the right to do that,
and by extension,
everyone else,
to violate the law based solely
on our own private beliefs,
then our society will crumble.
I believe that.
So I implore you, please
do not set this precedent.
Do not.
The future of our republic
depends on it.
What's going on?
Brooke is exercising
her right to protest.
Brooke, I need you
to stop this immediately.
Brooke, this is the last time
I'm gonna tell you.
If you don't stop right now,
there are gonna be consequences.
-Hey, Aunt Amy.
-Hey, Marlene.
Yeah, I just saw the video.
What's going on?
Remember my friend,
Brooke?
Yeah.
Well, she got a teacher in trouble
for asking her about Jesus.
What? -She's not even
supposed to talk about it.
And we can't even cover it
in our school paper.
Is there any way
I could meet with her?
-The teacher?
-No. Brooke.
Mr. Endler,
your opening statement.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
I have here a copy
of the Constitution
of the United States
of America
and its Bill of Rights,
arguably the two
most important documents
in the history
of our great nation.
But despite Mr. Kane's
impassioned rhetoric,
you know what you won't find in
there, no matter how hard you look?
The phrase "Separation
of church and state."
That's right.
It's not in there.
Never has been.
Because that phrase comes from a
letter written by Thomas Jefferson.
Now, ironically, Jefferson was
writing to a Baptist congregation,
ensuring them that
they would always
have the right to
believe as they wished,
free of government
interference.
But lately, that phrase has
been taken out of context
and twisted and contorted
to mean the exact opposite.
One morning early this year, my client,
Ms. Wesley, she woke up as usual,
she drove to work
at her job as a teacher
at Martin Luther King
High School,
a place where she was
Teacher of the Year.
Her lesson plan for second-period
AP History that morning,
it didn't include
any mention of God or Jesus.
She didn't have a Bible sitting
on her desk in plain view.
She didn't start her class
with a blessing.
She didn't lead
her students in prayer.
No, all she did was
answer a question.
Because that is what
she gets paid to do.
Now, Mr. Kane will insist
loudly and often
that faith isn't
on trial here.
But that is exactly
what is on trial...
The most basic human right of
all, the right to believe.
Mr. Kane's afraid.
He's afraid that you,
the jury,
the touchstone
of common sense,
might not agree with his tortured
interpretation of the Constitution,
that you might understand
that my client has rights,
rights
that trump his agenda,
and that
in realizing that
you will hold as I do
that my client is guilty
of no wrongdoing
and innocent of any
and all claims against her.
Thank you very much.
And now it's become
this huge deal,
and all she did was
answer my question.
Why do you think your
parents are doing this?
Because my mom thinks it'll help me
get into Stanford or one of the Ivys,
and my dad thinks
it'll help pay for it.
And nobody's asked you
what you think?
No.
So, are you
gonna help her?
I don't know.
I would at least
like to talk to her.
Maybe I could help
get her story out there.
Great, because everyone's
telling me to stay out of it.
Do you always do
what you're told?
What is your heart
telling you to do?
Mr. Thawley, how
did you feel when you
found out that your
daughter had been exposed
to faith-based teachings
in class?
It felt like
we had been violated.
This was supposed to be a history
class, not Sunday school.
My wife and I
are free thinkers.
We're rationalists. We believe
in a nontheistic worldview.
That's how we were trying
to raise our daughter.
And did you discuss this
incident with your daughter?
Well, I tried, but
it's hard discussing
anything with kids
that age... she's 16.
Some of you know
what that's like.
It's hard enough trying to
maintain credibility as a parent
without a teacher jumping in and
arguing against your position.
We trust the school
not to overstep its bounds
in terms of what is
and what isn't appropriate.
Is that too much to ask?
No. Thank you, Mr. Thawley.
That's all, Your Honor.
Your witness, Mr. Endler.
No questions,
Your Honor.
Next witness, Mr. Kane.
Mrs. Rizzo,
did Ms. Wesley
talk about faith issues
on the school campus?
All the time.
Everybody knows
she's a Christian.
I don't think she'd chew a stick
of gum without praying first.
It makes everyone
feel awkward.
Thank you.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Your witness,
Mr. Endler.
Mrs. Rizzo, you stated that Ms. Wesley
talks about her faith all the time.
I'm curious. Can you
give me a specific instance?
Well, not off
the top of my head.
Well, has she, as far as you're aware,
ever started her class with a prayer?
No.
Has she ever asked anyone in the
teacher's lounge to pray with her?
No.
Has she ever asked you personally
to pray with her? -Objection.
-No.
-Cumulative.
The question has effectively
been asked and answered.
Your Honor, Mrs. Rizzo's
sworn testimony states
that Ms. Wesley talked
about her faith all the time,
yet she's failed to cite
a single instance.
I'm merely trying to discover
some basis for her opinion.
Sustained. Mr. Endler, we're done
with this line of questioning.
Mrs. Rizzo, in the school's
initial inquiry into this matter,
you were Ms. Wesley's
representative
on behalf of the teacher's
union, were you not?
Yes.
And did you ever consider that
your disapproval of her faith
might taint your ability
to represent her properly?
-Objection, speculative.
-Sustained.
God bless you.
Careful, or you
might end up on trial.
Mr. Endler!
No further questions,
Your Honor.
So, when are these
religious zealots
going to realize it's
not only disrespectful
of them to push their
beliefs on others,
in this case
it's actually illegal?
This woman, this fundamentalist,
used her position
of influence as a teacher
to fill the minds of our
children with nonsense.
If you ask me, the religious
extremists we need to worry about
are the hard-core Christians.
How about we show up in force
and show Ms. Wesley
just exactly what we think
of her proselytizing?
Principal Kinney,
what was the school district's
final determination?
Well, Grace has been
suspended without pay
pending the results
of this trial.
Isn't it rather unusual,
leaving it up to a third party
to determine whether
Ms. Wesley is fired?
We've decided to
accept the court's
interpretation of
wrongdoing either way.
No questions, Your Honor.
Your witness, Mr. Endler.
Ms. Kinney,
can you tell me
the full name of the high school
over which you preside?
Dr. Martin Luther King Junior
Memorial High School.
I noticed that the name
fails to mention
Dr. King's title
as Reverend Doctor.
It's his work in the field of civil
rights that we prefer to highlight.
But that's the whole point.
You consider
his faith and politics
to be separate things.
But I don't,
and certainly wouldn't have.
Objection, Your Honor.
Counsel is testifying.
Sustained.
Jury's instructed to ignore
Mr. Endler's preceding remarks.
Ms. Kinney, are you familiar with Dr.
King's letter from the Birmingham jail?
Yes, it's a seminal piece
of civil rights history.
In that letter Dr. King makes numerous
faith-based references, does not?
Offhand,
I don't recall.
Allow me to refresh
your memory.
Cites the example of the three
youths from the book of Daniel
who were tossed into the fiery
furnace by King Nebuchadnezzar
because they refused
to worship him.
Elsewhere, urges
action with Jesus,
and here I quote,
"Extremist love."
And in his speech,
"I've Been to the Mountaintop,"
stated that just
wanted to do God's will.
Is this coming back
to you now?
Yes.
In your opinion, would Ms.
Wesley, had she chosen to do so,
have been allowed to
present the examples
that I just mentioned
in her class?
-Objection. Speculative.
-I'm going to allow it.
Overruled.
Witness may answer.
No. If it were up to me,
she would not have been allowed.
Why not?
Because those examples are too
closely associated with faith.
In other words,
they're facts,
but they're just facts that are
too dangerous for discussion?
The word I would use
would be "controversial."
But aren't facts just facts?
I mean, there's nothing controversial
about two plus two equaling four,
or E equals MC squared,
or the date
man landed on the moon.
So why the controversy
about these facts?
I think the fact that we're all
here today speaks for itself.
Thank you for your honesty.
One last question.
In your orientation at the
beginning of the semester,
your memo to the staff stressed
diversity and tolerance, did it not?
Yes.
Well, would it be fair to say
that except for Christianity,
all other forms of diversity
are welcome?
-Objection! Your Honor!
-I will withdraw the question.
Mr. Endler, you seem
to have a penchant
for injecting commentary
where it doesn't belong.
You would do well to avoid further
provocation of this court.
I apologize, Your Honor.
I'll look to curtail it
in the future.
Redirect, Your Honor?
Ms. Kinney,
I understand
that you attended a service at Ms.
Wesley's church a short while ago.
-Is that correct?
-Yes, that's correct.
It was an event honoring
several students who
attend that church for
their community service.
And who was it that
invited you to that service?
Grace Wesley.
I see.
And where were you when this
invitation was extended?
At my office.
On school grounds?
Yes.
During work hours?
Thank you.
One last question.
Is it true that Ms.
Wesley accepts donations
for a faith-based charity,
Convoy of Hope,
right there
in the classroom?
Yes, she does.
Thank you again.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
You may step down,
Mrs. Kinney.
Court's adjourned.
Grace, can I ask you
a question,
off the record?
Sure.
These people, they're
looking to destroy you,
and I don't just mean
financially.
Do you think
it's worth it?
I hope so.
So do I.
Fishy and cheesy at the same time.
This tuna melt is exquisite.
Yeah, exquisite.
It's the provolone.
That was my idea.
I love what it does
to the flavor of the fish.
Don't I know you?
You're from
Blaze's Car Rental, right?
-Yeah.
Yeah, that gig didn't
really work out for me.
I don't think customer
service is my forte.
So you decided
to become a waiter?
This is where
I do dinner theater.
In the mornings
I serve up croissants.
In the evenings
I serve up Chekhov.
Hey, listen, sorry about
the whole car-not-working thing.
It's okay.
I learned my lesson.
Bought a Prius.
Starts every time.
-Same guy.
Amazing.
Gentlemen, I don't want
to spoil your brunch,
but I'm hearing from a friend of
mine in the prosecutor's office
about a subpoena
that just came down
demanding that we submit copies of our
sermons for the last three months
for review.
Can they do that?
They tried it in Houston.
So now the government
can determine what
we can and can't
preach at our churches?
Let's not overreact. I'm sure
there's no ill intent here.
Unfortunately, I think
this is just the beginning.
We've been ignoring it, and now
we're paying the price for it.
Well, don't forget the silent
majority. They're out there.
They just need something
to stand for.
I'll admit
there's pressure,
but I think with time
this will correct itself.
Forgive me,
but I think you're wrong.
I'm serving on a jury in a case right
now that touches on these issues.
Of course, I'm not allowed
to talk about it,
but the one thing
that it's convinced me
of is that if we stand
by and do nothing,
pressure we're feeling today is
gonna mean persecution tomorrow.
What makes you so sure?
Speed of change,
viciousness of the opposition.
The message of the gospel
has us standing in the
way of a lot of things
powerful people want,
and our resistance
to change that message,
because it's not ours to change,
has made us a lot of enemies.
Whether we admit it or not,
we're at war,
the war of Ephesians 6,
not against flesh and blood,
but against the powers
of this world,
against the spiritual forces
in the heavenly realms.
And if we insist
on denying that,
then we've already lost.
Brought a giant bag
of Chinese food
and a briefcase
full of files.
I say we eat first.
I say
you're a genius.
-Does Walter want to join us?
-No. He's hiding in his room.
How come?
He's treating this
like it's a date,
which should give you some indication
of what my social life is like.
Don't worry.
I won't tell.
Falls under
attorney-client privilege.
So, is this what you always saw
yourself doing, the lawyer thing?
No...
I wanted to be Batman.
How 'bout you? Your parents have
you all set to go to the convent?
Actually, there were no bedtime
prayers in my childhood.
I was raised in a house
without much faith.
When did you decide
to become a Christian?
I was walking home
from class.
It was dark, and I was
struggling with a lot of things.
And I turned the corner,
and right there in front
of me was this church.
It had this old sign
out front,
but it just stopped me
in my tracks.
And the sign...
the sign said,
"Who do you say
that I am?"
And as I read it, I could
hear the Lord speak to me.
You know, I couldn't get that
question out of my head for days.
So that was the start of a
journey that didn't end
until I found
the answer.
That was beautiful.
Forgive me, but I did not
know anyone was here.
No.
Please don't apologize.
I didn't mean
to interrupt.
I just didn't know
where else to go.
-I'm Martin.
-I'm Brooke.
Do you think I could ask
you a few questions?
That would be fine.
Good,
'cause I have a lot.
Doesn't make mistakes.
But I thought you proved bias.
Principal Kinney and Mrs. Rizzo?
Those were just jabs.
We need a knockout punch.
Why did you feel compelled to
bring Jesus up in history class?
Why shouldn't I have?
Grace, I'm not here to debate with you
what you think your rights were...
No, Tom, listen.
This isn't about faith.
This is about history.
Okay, maybe I'm wrong here.
I'm not the law expert.
But I think they've
missed the point.
I'm not sure I follow.
Their whole attack, it's
about me preaching in class,
but I didn't do that.
They're saying you did.
You cited scripture.
You talked about
Jesus' teachings just
like they were any
other verifiable fact.
But what if
they're just that?
Just because certain facts happen
to be recorded in the Bible
doesn't mean
they stop being facts.
We can separate the history-based
elements of Jesus' life
from the faith-based
element.
I mean, in my classroom I didn't talk
about Jesus as my Lord and Savior.
All I did was comment on quotations
attributed to Jesus, the man,
and I did it
in AP History.
There was nothing wrong
with the context.
And any rule saying
that you can talk about
any historic figure that ever existed
except Jesus is discriminatory.
They can't institute that.
And every credible historian
admits that Jesus existed.
There's just
too much evidence.
Grace, I love it.
This is our defense.
Jesus as a historic
figure, just like everyone else.
And you know what?
Kane will never see it coming.
You got some reading to do.
Just had so many notes
written in the margins
that for the first time I felt like I
was truly getting to know my brother,
like God gave me
the extra five minutes
that I so desperately
needed with him.
I just don't understand why
never told me about his faith.
Sharing one's faith
with family,
especially not knowing
how they will react,
can be difficult.
Count our struggles
as blessings, right?
That is exactly right.
There are more than five minutes
awaiting you and your brother.
John chapter 11,
verse 25 to 26 says,
"I am the resurrection
and the life.
Who believes in me
will live even if dies.
And whoever lives and believes
in me will never die."
Do you believe this?
I do.
Then invite him
into your heart
and make him
the Lord of your life.
Dear Lord, I'm not quite
sure what to say, but...
thank you for dying
on the cross for me.
Please forgive me
of my sin.
Jesus, please come
into my life,
and I will follow you
as my Lord and Savior.
Amen.
Thank you.
Can you state your name
and occupation for the court?
My name is Lee Strobel.
I'm a professor of Christian thought
at Houston Baptist University
and the author of more than
20 books about Christianity,
including
The Case for Christ.
Can you help me prove
the existence of Jesus Christ?
Absolutely, beyond
any reasonable doubt.
How so?
Actually, this court already
affirmed it when the date was given.
Our calendar has been
split between BC and AD,
based on
the birth of Jesus,
which is quite a feat
if never existed.
Beyond that,
historian Gary Habermas
lists 39 ancient sources
for Jesus,
from which enumerates
more than 100 reported facts
about his life, teachings,
crucifixion and resurrection.
In fact,
the historical evidence
for Jesus' execution
is so strong
that one of the most famous New
Testament scholars in the world,
Gerd Ldemann of Germany,
said,
"Jesus' death as a
consequence of crucifixion
is indisputable."
Now, there are very few facts
in ancient history
that a critical historian like Gerd
Ldemann will say is indisputable.
One of them is the
execution of Jesus Christ.
Forgive me, but you're a
believer, are you not?
-A Bible-believing Christian?
-Guilty as charged.
So, wouldn't this tend
to inflate your estimate
of the probability
that Jesus existed.
No, because we
don't need to inflate it.
We can reconstruct the
basic facts about Jesus
just from non-Christian
sources outside the Bible.
And Gerd Ldemann
is an atheist.
In other words, we can prove
the existence of Jesus
solely by using
sources that have
absolutely no sympathy
toward Christianity.
As the agnostic historian,
Bart Ehrman, says,
"Jesus did exist,
whether we like it or not."
I put it this way.
Denying the existence of Jesus
doesn't make him go away.
It merely proves that no amount
of evidence will convince you.
Thank you. No further
questions, Your Honor.
Mr. Kane, your witness.
No questions, Your Honor.
That's lunch.
We'll recess until 2:00 p.m.
Can I help you
with something?
Hi.
I was looking
for Pastor Dave.
My friend, Mina, she said
I should come see him.
She said's real
easy to talk to.
Won't be back
until after next week.
Okay. Thanks.
Sweeping is something
I only do part-time.
I enjoy it because
it helps me think.
But if you need to talk,
I'm actually a pastor.
It's been three weeks since my
doctors told me I was in remission.
-Amy, that's wonderful.
-It is.
Yes.
But even though
I've been given this gift,
I've been questioning my faith.
I know Jesus existed, but...
I'm struggling to believe.
Actually, I think you
already do believe,
and the proof is you're not willing
to put God back on the shelf
now that
your cancer is gone.
Won't let you
dismiss the thought of him.
Part of you senses
Jesus' presence
and wishes that would just
go away and leave you alone.
Actually,
now that you mention it,
I had thought of that.
Look, delights in using us
in ways we never dreamed of
and giving us things that we
never even knew we wanted.
We just have to
give him a chance.
Will you?
Thank you.
Hi.
I'm Reverend David Hill.
Sermon transcripts,
right?
Yes.
Just put it right there.
They've been coming in
all morning.
I'm sure they did what
they thought was best.
That's it?
Those are your entire sermons
for the past 120 days?
No, that's a letter
that I wrote
explaining why I'm not
going to hand them in.
Excuse me?
I know it's unusual
for a Christian pastor
to willfully resist a subpoena issued
by a lawful government authority,
and it's even more unusual that
should feel compelled to do so.
Are you sure
you wanna do that?
It's something
that I have to do.
You know the old saying, "The squeaky
wheel gets the grease," don't you?
I have another saying.
"A nail that sticks up
gets hammered down."
I'm seeing a teacher
who answered a student's
question to the
best of her ability.
Amy, it sounds like you're taking
the side of Grace Wesley here.
Surely, you see that
she used the student's
question to promote
her Christian agenda.
Actually,
that's not how I see it.
I believe Ms. Wesley's entitled
to her own opinions,
and that includes
in the classroom.
She didn't try to convert
these students. In fact...
Amy, I must say,
I'm shocked at what seems to be
a complete 180 from the typical
stance of your blog.
Just look at the facts
of this case.
She clearly infringed on
the rights of her students.
Marlene?
I have an idea.
Come over as soon
as you can, okay?
You look terrible.
-You really ought to ask to be excused.
-No.
No, I'm fine.
I really need to be here.
All rise.
You may be seated.
Juror number 12, is there
something you'd like to say?
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
I gotta...
Bailiff, call paramedics.
Sir.
I guess that proves
there is no God,
'cause they just lost the only
juror they could count on.
Any dizziness?
Yeah.
Vomiting?
About a half hour ago.
Does this hurt?
How 'bout this?
I hope you're not
too attached to your appendix.
-Brooke!
-Marlene.
It's not looking good
in there.
Ms. Marshall, are you prepared to
fulfill your duties as an alternate?
Yes, I am, Your Honor.
Mr. Endler, next witness.
State your name
and experience for the record.
My name is
James Warner Wallace.
I'm a retired homicide detective
from Los Angeles County.
And are you the author of the
book Cold Case Christianity?
Yes, I am.
Can you share the subtitle of
the book with the court, please?
A Homicide Detective Investigates
the Claims of the Gospels.
Would I be correct in saying that
your duties as a homicide detective
include investigating
cold case homicides?
Yes, that is
and was my expertise.
Don't most of those cases
get solved with DNA evidence?
Objection. Leading.
And counsel is
testifying again, Your Honor.
I'll rephrase.
How many of your cold cases were solved
through the use of DNA evidence?
None. Not one.
That's often popular on TV, but our
departments never had the good fortune
of solving a cold case
with DNA.
How do most of these cases
get solved?
Often by examining
eyewitness claims,
witness claims that were
made many years earlier,
even though often our
witnesses are now deceased.
Forgive my ignorance, Mr. Wallace,
but how is that possible?
We have a number of
techniques we can use
to test the reliability
of an eyewitness,
including something called
forensic statement analysis.
That's a discipline where we scrutinize
the statements of eyewitnesses,
looking at what
they choose to minimize,
what they choose to emphasize,
what they omit altogether,
how they expand time
or contract time.
And when we examine these
kinds of eyewitness accounts,
we can usually tell who's
lying and who's telling
the truth, even who
the guilty party is.
And did you apply this skill set any
time outside of your official capacity?
Yes, I applied my
expertise to the death
of Jesus at the
hands of the Romans,
and I actually
looked at the gospels
as I would any other set
of forensic statements.
Within a matter of months I
determined that the four gospels,
written from different
perspectives,
contained
the eyewitness accounts
about the life, ministry, death
and resurrection of Jesus.
Did you consider
that the four accounts
might be part of a conspiracy designed
to promote belief in a fledgling faith?
Yeah, you have to consider conspiracies
when assessing eyewitness accounts,
but successful conspiracies typically
involve the fewest number of people.
It's easier for two people to lie and
keep a secret than it is for 20.
And that's the problem
with conspiracy theories
related to the apostles
in the 1st century.
There are far too many
of them trying to hold
this conspiracy for too
long a period of time.
And far worse, they're experiencing
pressure like no other...
Unimaginable pressure.
Every one of these folks was tortured
and died for what they claimed to see,
and none of them
ever recanted their story.
So the idea that this is a
conspiracy in the first century
is just really unreasonable.
Instead,
what I see in the gospels
is something I call unintended
eyewitness support statements.
What's an unintended
eyewitness support statement?
If I can borrow
your Bible.
Let me go to the Gospel of
Matthew for an example of this.
I'll start with a
passage in which Jesus
is in front of
Caiaphas at a hearing.
It says here, "Then they spit in his
face and struck him with their fists.
Others slapped him and said, 'Prophesy
to us, Christ. Who hit you?'"
That seems like
a very simple request.
The people who hit him are
standing right in front of him.
This makes no sense.
Why would it be
prophecy to be able to
tell you who hit you?
But it's not until you read Luke
that you get an answer to this.
Says, "The men who were guarding
Jesus began mocking and beating him.
They blindfolded him and demanded,
'Prophesy! Who hit you?'"
Now we know why this
was a challenge...
Luke tells us the
thing Matthew left out,
that was actually blindfolded
at the time this took place.
This is very common, this kind of
unintentional eyewitness support
that fills in a detail that
the first witness left out.
After years of
scrutinizing these gospels
using the template that I use to
determine if an eyewitness is reliable,
I concluded that the
four gospels in this book
contained the reliable accounts
of the actual words of Jesus.
And that's to include the statements
quoted by Ms. Wesley in her class?
Absolutely.
Thank you, Detective.
Your witness.
Detective Wallace,
I'm not gonna try to match
biblical knowledge with you.
But isn't it true that these gospel
accounts vary widely in what they say,
that there are numerous discrepancies
between these accounts?
Absolutely. But that's exactly
what we should expect.
I don't quite
understand that.
Reliable eyewitness
accounts always differ
slightly in the way
they recall the story.
They're coming to it from different
geographic perspectives, their history,
even where they are
located in the room.
When I examined
the gospels,
I was trying to determine if these
were accurate, reliable accounts,
in spite of any differences there
might be between the accounts.
And as a devout Christian,
you feel you succeeded?
Mr. Kane, I think
you misunderstand me.
When I began this study,
I was a devout atheist.
I began examining the gospels
as a committed skeptic,
not as a believer.
You see, I wasn't raised
in a Christian environment,
although I do think I have an unusually
high regard for the value of evidence.
I'm not a Christian because
I was raised that way
or because I hoped it would satisfy
some need or accomplish some goal.
I'm simply a Christian
because it's evidentially true.
-Motion to strike, Your Honor.
-Granted.
Jury's instructed to ignore
Detective Wallace's last remarks.
No further questions.
Witness is excused.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Mr. Endler,
your next witness.
We don't have one,
Your Honor.
She didn't do anything wrong!
She was just trying to help me!
-Brooke!
-Order! I'll have order!
Young lady,
your youth is no excuse
for disturbing
the sanctity of this court.
But this case is
supposed to be about me.
I'm almost 17 years old. It's not
like I can't think for myself.
-I just don't have the right to speak.
-Brooke, what are you doing?
Not unless you are called
as a witness, young lady.
If I put her on the stand,
what am I gonna hear?
That she asked a question
and I answered it.
Your Honor, we'd like to call Ms.
Brooke Thawley to the stand.
Objection, Your Honor.
Ms. Thawley is a minor.
Her parents do not want her
subjected to the emotional pressure
of testifying against
her own teacher.
Ms. Thawley, are you willing
to testify on your own behalf?
Yes, Your Honor.
And do you understand that
you will have to answer
all the questions truthfully,
regardless of your feelings,
and that failure to do so
is punishable by law?
Yes, Your Honor. I'm not
afraid of telling the truth.
I'm only afraid
of not being able to tell it.
I will allow
this witness.
Objection overruled.
Brooke, in class,
who first brought up the name
Jesus, you or Ms. Wesley?
I did.
As part of a question?
Yes.
And at that time, did you feel like you
were asking a faith-based question?
No, not really.
It just seemed like Martin Luther King
and Jesus were saying similar things,
so I brought it up.
Did you consider Ms.
Wesley's response to
be a reasonable answer
to your question?
Yes.
So, if I'm hearing you
correctly,
you asked a question
in history class
about a historical figure,
and your history teacher answered
it in a sensible manner?
Yes.
Thank you.
Your witness.
Ms. Thawley,
do you like Ms. Wesley?
Yes.
Would you say
she's your favorite teacher?
Yes, absolutely.
Do you think
Ms. Wesley likes you?
Objection. Speculative.
Your Honor, it speaks to the
state of mind of the witness,
if not Ms. Wesley herself.
I'm gonna allow it. Overruled.
You may answer the question.
Yes, I think
she likes me.
Do you think there's any possibility
that in answering your question,
she may have tried to share
some of the ideas of her faith,
a faith that she holds
most dear?
N... No.
Not at that moment.
Not at that moment?
You mean to say that
there were other moments
in which she talked to you
about her faith?
Ms. Thawley, please?
You must answer the question,
Ms. Thawley.
Yes, but it was outside of school,
and it was only one time.
Move to strike.
Your Honor, this is irrelevant.
No actions off the school
campus are at issue here.
Denied. Mr. Kane seems to
have found a loose thread.
I'm inclined to let him pull it,
see what unravels.
Thank you, Your Honor.
-Why didn't you tell me about this?
-You didn't ask.
And I didn't think
it mattered.
Brooke, you realize that you
have to tell the truth here.
-You understand that, correct?
-Yes.
So, what did you mean
when you said
that you had talks about faith
outside of school?
My brother died in an
accident six months ago.
Ms. Wesley noticed that
I wasn't doing so well,
so she asked me if everything
was all right after class.
I told her I was fine.
But I went and found her
later on at the coffee shop.
And did Ms. Wesley refer you to any
kind of psychological counseling?
No.
Did she suggest
that perhaps
she wasn't the right person
to be discussing this with you?
No.
Well, then what
did Ms. Wesley do?
She was really nice.
We talked for a long time, and I
could tell that she really cared.
I asked her how she kept it
all together so well,
and she said,
"Jesus."
So, she's the one
who brought up Jesus?
Did her endorsement of Jesus move
you to explore Christianity?
Yes, at first.
But when the Salvation Army came
to pick up my brother's things,
one of the ladies found his
Bible and she gave it to me.
I didn't even know
that had one.
So I started reading it,
and once I started
I realized that...
I didn't wanna stop.
That's why.
That's why I came up with the
question that I asked in class.
Now, if I understand
you correctly,
without Ms. Wesley's
direct involvement,
you never would have asked that
question in the first place, would you?
I don't know.
After all of your
Bible readings,
do you feel now
that you're a believer?
Yes.
Maybe even a... Christian?
At the risk
of seeming redundant,
do you think any of this...
The Bible readings, the
question about Jesus in class,
the newfound commitment
to Christianity,
is it likely that any of that
would've occurred
without Ms. Wesley's
direct involvement?
No, it wouldn't.
I thank you
for your honesty.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Mr. Endler,
do you wish to redirect?
No, Your Honor.
You may step down,
Ms. Thawley.
Why do they look
so angry?
Because they think
we lied to them.
But we didn't.
It doesn't matter.
This court is adjourned.
I have to
prepare you, Grace.
We're gonna lose
this case.
I know.
You were right.
I'm gonna lose everything.
We saw a very large crowd
at the courthouse yesterday,
both in protest and support
of teacher Grace Wesley,
who is on trial for allegedly
proselytizing at the classroom.
In an unexpected
move yesterday,
we saw some of Wesley's
former students
come out to silently demonstrate
their support for their teacher.
O Father, please
take this from me.
I...
I don't know what to do.
Please don't forsake me.
Please.
Hey, Brooke.
I ruined everything,
didn't I?
It's okay.
You don't have to answer.
I know that I did.
I'm not even allowed
to talk to her.
How do I let her know that I'm
sorry without making things worse?
I can't tell you
what to do, but...
whatever you do,
just let her know you care.
Recently when I've
been praying, it's like
Jesus isn't letting
me feel his presence.
Usually I can almost
reach out and touch him, but...
But right now it's like...
It's like
He's a million miles away.
Honey, you of all people
should realize
when you're going through
something really hard,
the teacher is always quiet
during the test.
First of all, this trial
took an unexpected turn
when Wesley's counsel decided they'd
try to prove the existence of Jesus.
Gary, this is kind of
your area of expertise.
How do you convince
the skeptics?
Well, Governor, I employ what
I call the minimal facts method,
which uses only the historical
events that are so well evidenced
that they're accepted
across the board,
even by skeptical
and non-Christian scholars.
Now I understand what it is you
weren't allowed to talk about.
I wish I still wasn't
allowed to talk about it.
She needs me on that jury.
Have faith, David.
God's plan is at work.
How'd you get here anyway?
I borrowed your Prius.
It's very nice.
Don't get too comfortable.
I'm planning a full recovery.
Do you believe that she was
proselytizing to her students?
Governor, not at all.
Jesus Christ was the most
influential person who ever lived.
How could you ignore
that fact and teach history?
Hey. Martin.
More questions? -I wanted to
make sure that you were okay.
Yeah, I'm fine. They're just holding
me over for a little observation.
I'll be released soon.
Something different
about you.
Are you okay?
I should say so, yes.
I believe God wants me
to be a minister,
to return to my country and
become a pastor, just like you.
That's great.
There'll be challenges in your
country. Are you prepared for them?
I am.
I'm proud of you.
Come here.
That's awesome.
It's a shocking reality that Christians
are soon gonna be forced to choose
between obeying the law of man
or following the Word of God.
I'm Mike Huckabee. We'll see you
next time on Points of View.
Hey, Brooke, go be with Ms. Wesley.
I think we can handle this.
Yeah, seriously. We've got
backup coming. You're covered.
Go get 'em.
God's got this.
Where's Tom?
All rise.
Be seated.
Are we missing someone?
Sorry, Your Honor.
My apologies to the court.
That's unexpected.
Almost looks
like a lawyer.
Your Honor, I have
one final witness to call.
Grace Wesley.
Ms. Wesley, please approach
the witness stand.
Do I have to?
I'm afraid so.
Your Honor, given the
witness's reluctance to testify,
can I have the court's permission
to treat her as a hostile witness?
You may.
Proceed at your own peril.
Do you swear to tell the truth, the
whole truth, and nothing but the truth?
-I do.
-Please be seated.
Grace, I want you
to do something for me,
something for everyone
in this courtroom.
I want you to apologize.
I want you to say you're sorry
and that you made a mistake.
-Your Honor, what's going on here?
-Do it, Grace.
I can't do that.
Why?
Why can't you do that, Grace?
Because I don't believe
I did anything wrong.
Well, as your attorney, I'm
advising you to do it anyway,
to at least pretend
you're sorry and throw
yourself on the
mercy of the court.
What?
That would be a lie.
So what?
Everyone lies.
Not everyone.
A-Are you looking
to become a martyr?
What in the world
is doing?
I have no idea.
No.
Tommy.
Then what is it that you
want, Grace? Tell me.
Tell us.
I want...
I want to be able
to tell the truth.
The truth?
Whose truth?
And what truth
are you referring to?
Grace, is there some truth that
you know that no one else knows?
That's right.
The other night, didn't you tell me
that Jesus spoke to you personally?
Why are you doing this? -I'm the one
asking the questions, Ms. Wesley.
Did you or did you not tell me that
Jesus spoke to you personally?
Yes.
And what did say?
I'll make it easier for you. Didn't
you say that asked you a question?
That was personal.
You weren't supposed to...
I don't care.
The other night, you
told me that Jesus asked
you something. What
did ask you, Grace?
Tell all of us.
I think we deserve to know.
-Why are you doing this to me?
-Answer the question.
They won't believe me.
Doesn't matter.
All that matters
is that you believe it.
Tell us, Grace,
under penalty of perjury,
what was the question
that God presented
to you personally
that night on campus?
Answer the question.
Answer the question!
Asked,
"Who do you say
that I am?"
And what did you answer?
You are the Christ,
the son of the living God.
Well, there you have it.
Your Honor, I think we've
all heard quite enough.
Mr. Endler, are you looking
to change your client's plea?
No, Your Honor.
I say she's innocent
of all wrongdoing.
But I'm asking the jury
to find against her anyway.
I mean, let's face it.
She has the audacity to believe
not only that there is a God,
but that she has a personal
relationship with him,
which colors everything
that she says and does.
I think it's time
we stop pretending
that we can trust a person like
this to serve in a public capacity.
In the name of tolerance and
diversity, I say we destroy her.
That's enough, Mr. Endler.
Then we can all go
to our graves content,
knowing we stomped out
the last spark of faith
that was ever exhibited
in the public square.
-That's enough.
-I say we make an example of her.
Mr. Endler,
that's enough.
Let's set a new precedent,
that employment by our
federal government mandates
that you must first denounce
any belief system you have.
Mr. Endler,
you are out of order!
And if someone slips through the
cracks and hides their beliefs,
then we arrest them
and fine them.
And if they don't pay, then we seize
their property. And if they resist?
Well, let's not kid ourselves.
Enforcement is always
at the end of a gun.
Mr. Endler, you are out of order!
I charge you with contempt!
I accept the charge,
because I have nothing
but contempt for
these proceedings.
If we're going to insist
that a Christian's right
to believe is subordinate
to all other rights,
then it's not a right.
Somebody is always
going to be offended.
Two thousand years
of human history proves that.
So I say we get on with it.
Cite the law, charge the jury,
and send them off to deliberate.
So be it!
Now, we are gonna bypass
the usual closing arguments,
unless Mr. Kane finds the need
to further address the jury.
No, Your Honor.
We can ask nothing more.
My instructions to you
are simple.
Uphold the law without unfairly
prejudicing your decision
or risking a mistrial
on appeal.
Now, I believe
I can safely say
that the respondent's counsel
has dared you...
to convict
his own client.
The jury will now be
dismissed for deliberation.
We are adjourned.
She hasn't got a prayer.
Let's go.
Remind me to send him
a thank-you note.
Thank you so much. Thank you,
guys. Thanks for coming out.
Hey, right now on the phone, a friend
of mine named Amy is on the line,
and she's calling about a woman
who's on trial for her faith.
This woman has risked
everything for Jesus.
Amy's asked me to pray for this
woman. Will you guys join me?
Lord, we know that
to risk anything for you
is a complete honor
with eternal rewards.
But if it's
within your will,
can you please restore
this woman's hope
and make her faith
an example to all of us?
Lord, show your power
to a fallen world.
We know you have the power
to do anything.
So we ask you right now, crying
out as the body of Christ,
move those hearts of those people,
Lord, the judge and the jury,
to let them know the beauty
of your majesty.
And we all said amen.
Amen.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
have you reached a decision?
We have, Your Honor.
And how do you find?
We, the jury,
find in favor of...
Grace Wesley.
-You're wrong!
We are adjourned.
Nice shoes.
Grace.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't tell you.
It had to come as a
surprise, otherwise the jury
wouldn't have been
swayed by your reactions.
So you did have a plan.
No. You did.
You stood up
for what you believed in
and you held on
to your faith.
I don't know anybody
that would have done that.
They were hoping to
make an example of you,
but instead you became
an inspiration.
We did it!
Hey, you've kept
quiet long enough.
Why don't you go
share the good news?
Hey.
Thank you.
Yeah.
God's not dead!
A case that was turning
for the worse was concluded
with a powerful happy ending
for Ms. Grace Wesley.
Live outside the courthouse
here in Hope Springs...
Father. You did it!
God is good!
Wait.
I want to hear this.
In the case of Thawley v. Wesley, they
have ruled in favor of Grace Wesley.
The crowd is in full celebration
here at Hope Springs.
So are you gonna say it,
or should I?
Say what?
God is good.
All the time.
-And all the time...
-God is good.
Amen, brother.
I'll get to work
on the appeal.
Don't bother.
If we appeal and lose, it'll set
a precedent. I don't want that.
I don't understand
how we lost this.
Outsmarted us.
Played our role
in attacking Wesley.
Made the jury
hate everyone but her.
Not to mention proved the
existence of Jesus Christ.
-God's not dead!
-He's surely alive!
God's not dead!
He's surely alive!
Come on!
God's not dead!
He's surely alive!
You know I'm gonna
need my keys back.
I know.
Two days of ice chips.
I'm starving.
I'm hungry as well,
David.
How about I take you
for a nice tuna melt?
David Hill?
Yes.
You're under arrest.
For what?
Contempt of court.
You failed to produce your
sermons upon court order.
Please put your hands
behind your back.
Please be gentle.
He's just been released
from the hospital.
I don't understand. What
is being accused of?
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have a right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be provided.
Do you understand the rights I
have just read to you? -Yes.
Sorry about this,
Pastor.
It's okay.
Looks like I'm gonna need you to fill
in for me a little while longer.
Of course, David.
Anything you need.
What do we do now?
Same as always,
Martin.
We pray, in faith.