[***]
I don't need to tell you
what's at stake here.
We just have to
run the clock out,
Let it go into overtime.
But coach, we never went
into overtime.
This is for the finals.
Bridgette, when you're coach,
you can call all the shots.
Now just do what I'm
telling you. Sticks up!
Laurels on three.
One, two, three.
[Together]
Laurels!
[***]
[Crowd noise]
Whoa!
[Crowd cheering]
Miss, Miss Cunningham.
You're back
from your sabbatical.
Where did you go,
if I may ask?
They said you'd gone to Asia,
is that correct?
Oh well.
Three years.
I bet you know
fluent Mandarin.
Who is that young lady,
the captain?
Oh.
You have been gone awhile.
That is Bridgette.
Whoa!
Hey, Sharkies...
Woo!
[Chuckles]
That was so fun!
Hey, clean yourself up.
Hi, Candace.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be shaking hands
and kissing babies?
Headmaster York
wants to see us.
Ah.
Thank you for coming in,
Miss Berwitt.
Of course, Headmaster York.
You must be very busy
with your campaign heating up.
Oh, it's heating up a bit,
but I feel confident.
- Thank you for asking.
- Is this about me?
Or my mother?
A flippant attitude
may serve you well
In some circles, Miss Berwitt,
But it's not
in your best interests here.
Look, I'm sorry
about the Sharks Suck thing.
Sharks suck?
Well, they do.
Yet another note
of disappointment.
Miss Berwitt, part of my job
here is protecting Edgington.
If we let someone slide by,
it devalues everyone's diploma.
[Bridgette]
And?
And...
I have your five-week
progress report.
You are failing
both English and calculus.
That's what this is about?
I'll just get a tutor, or
I'll do some extra credit.
Whatever.
I'm afraid it's not quite
that simple here at Edgington,
Especially with
core classes like these.
I have no choice but to
place you on academic probation.
Students on academic probation
May not participate
in extracurricular activities
Including sports,
Which I'm afraid
means no lacrosse.
What? But we just kicked
St. Paul's butt,
And we win the playoffs
next week
And we go to nationals!
I'm the captain,
And tryouts for Eurotour
are coming up.
I could get a scholarship.
You can't take me off the team!
All of that is a distant
second to your education.
Your studies come first.
Full stop.
We understand,
And we couldn't
agree with you more.
Headmaster York:
Good,
Because the alternative
is not very pleasant.
If you are not mastering
these classes by midterms,
You will not graduate
from Edgington.
We have a decades-long
track record of excellence.
We do not tolerate failure.
You will not be allowed
to repeat your senior year
At this institution.
I know it doesn't feel like it,
but this is all up to you.
[Bridgette] Mom, this is
ridiculous, and you know it.
You've got to do something.
I mean, you're chairman of
Edgington's board of directors.
There's absolutely nothing
I can do, Bridgette.
This is one mistake of yours
I cannot fix.
Well, the board won't like it
If we don't make it
to nationals.
What is wrong with you?
Thanks for understanding,
Candace.
York is giving you
the benefit of the doubt.
I know what's really going on.
- Yeah, and what is it?
- Bobby Berry.
Spying on me.
Classy move.
I wouldn't hear things
If you didn't keep giving me
things to hear.
Yeah. Well, I think you're
just jealous I have somebody.
I'm going to ignore that.
This is serious, Bridgette.
This is the most serious
it's ever been.
- You cannot fail out.
- I'm not going to!
I know you're not going to
Because you're going
break up with Bobby tonight
So you can focus on your studies
for the rest of the year.
You can't make me do that.
I can tell Coach Ravino
To never let you
on the team again...
And she will listen to me.
Why?
Because I recommended her
to York.
You just have to win
everything, don't you?
[Sighs] Some day
you'll understand
It's not about winning.
Yeah? Well, that's where
you're wrong, Mom.
It's all about winning.
[Door closes]
- [Danni] Oh, hey, roomie.
- Hey.
I was getting worried.
[Bridgette]
It's such a long day!
- What?
- I heard.
We've lost our
fearless leader.
You should know that
you don't have to lie to me.
You know?
Somebody's
on next week's roster.
You were listed as out
on academic probation.
It's okay. It's just...
It's senior year.
It's a ridiculously hard school.
It's tough for everyone.
And I already talked
to my study group.
You are totally cool to join.
Even though I made fun
of you guys for being nerds?
We made fun of you for being
too cool for study groups.
[Giggles]
You would have fit right in.
So, who's going to be captain
Now that I'm forced into
temporary retirement?
Well, you know they normally
choose a senior,
And someone who's really good
with the plays...
So...
That's awesome!
You'll do a great job.
Thank you!
Here to fix your laptop,
ma'am.
Oh my God, you're crazy!
How did you get past
the front desk?
Visiting hours do not apply
to the computer technicians.
- Hi, Danni.
- Hi, Bobby.
Could you give us a minute?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Wouldn't want to get in the way
Of getting your lap
or your top serviced.
Oh my God!
Have fun, you guys!
My mom dropped a huge bomb.
What is it?
She said
I can't see you anymore.
What? Why?
She thinks it's your fault.
This is ridiculous.
[sighs]
What does this mean?
Two months of calls and sexting
until you get your GPA up?
Not even.
My mom's like a detective.
She watches the phone bill.
So this is it?
Just like that.
Tonight is our last night?
Danni?
Miss Berwitt...
I heard you were having
some computer issues.
Well, um, yeah.
He was just finishing.
That should get your hard drive
up and running, ma'am.
Call me if you need
any more assistance.
I didn't know Mr. Berry
moonlights as a technician.
He seems to possess
an enviable list of skills.
Oh, is that guy
a student here, too?
I didn't know.
Is there something else?
You do know who I am,
don't you?
I'm your new
faculty resident.
Oh. Are you going to
report this?
I'm kind of in a lot of
hot water already.
I know.
[Door closes]
[Bell rings]
Oh my God!
Are you actually
reading a book?
Don't we have a quiz
on this today?
Which one is this?
No, no. It's not this one.
That's the old one.
I'm just kidding.
- [Giggles]
- Oh, my God. You're crazy!
Where's Miss Patterson?
I was called back early
from my sabbatical to take over,
While Mrs. Patterson
is on maternity leave.
My name is Jane Cunningham.
Miss Patterson is pregnant?
Yes... and suffering
extreme morning sickness.
She'll be on bed rest
for the remainder of her term.
Any more questions?
Good!
Point of view.
Was your reading assignment
last night
Written in the third person
or omniscient point of view?
Bridgette.
Um, I mean,
it's the same thing, right?
Bridgette's heart
began to race.
She wasn't used to
not knowing the answer...
Or rather
she did know the answer,
But she had too much pride
to risk getting it wrong,
And so remained silent.
That's actually
third person limited.
We know the thoughts
of one person,
And the story
is centered around them.
If you wanted
an omniscient point of view,
You can get into
someone else's thoughts, too.
For example,
Bridgette looked over at Danni
And mouthed "help me".
Danni, who's known for
being a smart ass
Came up with
a self-aware response
That only betrayed
her deep-rooted fear
Of taking things
far too seriously.
Aren't you clever?
You're correct,
But mind your language
in my classroom.
Understood?
All right, then.
Mrs. Paterson
wanted to make sure
You got last week's exams
returned to you.
Apparently you all have issues
distinguishing points of view.
Hey, it's okay.
I got you.
Don't worry about it.
[Bell rings]
Miss Berwitt.
May I see you a moment?
Look, I... I know
I'm not supposed to see Bobby.
It won't happen again.
I'd just really appreciate it
if you didn't tell my mom.
Tell her what exactly?
You had your computer
repaired.
How did you feel about
the questions on the test?
Well, clearly I missed
the boat on a lot of them.
Yes. The thing about
Mrs. Patterson, the dear,
Is that she's very ambiguous
When it comes
to asking questions.
May I?
Ah, yes. See?
This question is open
to interpretation,
The timeline is skewed here,
And this last one is strictly
subjective opinion.
Come by my office before
first period tomorrow morning...
7:45.
[Door opens]
You're late.
And so are you.
Miss Cunningham:
Sit down.
So, tell me about Bobby.
You work here.
Why don't you
look up his record?
Tell me about you and Bobby.
Did my mother
put you up to this?
Well, you can tell her
we broke up,
And I won't be
seeing him again.
Do you love him?
Seriously,
what's going on?
I'm just trying to get
to know my new residents.
I really should be
getting to class.
When I was your age,
I was head over heels
in love with my boyfriend.
My parents forbade me
from dating him.
They said he was
a bad influence on me.
Okay.
What happened?
I didn't see him anymore,
and I always regretted it.
You must have
gotten over it by now.
Never underestimate the power
of missed opportunity,
No matter how long ago it was.
Are you being responsible?
[Bridgette]
Miss Cunningham,
I don't understand
what you're asking me.
Is he pressuring you?
No, no.
Besides, my mom made it
so that we can't even text.
So, sex isn't exactly
on the table,
Or the bed,
for that matter.
The male libido
is a powerful force,
Second only to its
counterpart, the male ego.
Miss Cunningham,
I'd love to stay and chat,
But I really
should be getting to class.
Apparently,
I'm failing all of them.
You're afraid
he'll lose interest in you
If you don't sleep with him.
Why are you helping me?
That's what friends do
for one another.
[Bridgette][giggles]
All right. I love you, too.
Good night.
Wow, I've never
seen you so happy
Talking to your mom before.
Well, it wasn't my mom.
[giggles]
Well, I know it wasn't Bobby
Since you've been forbidden
to talk to him.
It was Bobby.
[Sighs] Bridgette,
what are you doing?
Nothing.
Do you want to
get in more trouble?
No! I'm not going to get
in trouble
Because my mom
can't trace this.
Why, because
it's from a time
Before call tracing
was invented?
Where did you get
this thing? I never...
Miss Cunningham
gave it to me.
Miss Cunningham?
Why?
So I could talk
to my boyfriend.
Why would Miss Cunningham
care about you and Bobby?
I don't know. Maybe
she has the hots for him.
You can't even
buy these anymore.
She must be like
three times your age!
Oh my gosh!
You know, well,
she does use adult diapers.
[Laugh]
- What is that?
- I don't know.
Miss Berwitt.
It's for you.
Wow!
Please save the date.
Future Elite Party.
- Hey!
- Wow! Okay, okay.
That's sounds
really pretentious.
You're just jealous,
yeah.
We clearly established
that I'm not jealous.
I didn't get one.
Well, clearly you're not
as special as I am.
- Oh, okay.
- I mean, gold envelope.
Okay, gold.
Yeah, here. Catch it.
Work on those reflexes, Elite.
- Oh, okay. Okay.
- Miss Elite.
Yes, Bridgette?
Do you have another copy
of my book?
I think I left mine
in my room.
No, I don't have another copy,
but I do have your copy.
How did you get this?
I found it on the floor
after class.
It must be yours, right?
Yeah. Thanks.
You didn't happen to find
a bookmark in here, did you?
No. I'm sorry
you lost your place.
[Bridgette]
Who... who is this?
That's me.
Really?
Yes. Quite the homely
little thing, wasn't I?
No, not at all.
Just not what I was expecting.
I'll take that
as a compliment.
So, you had something
on your mind?
Yeah.
You wrote notes
in my book.
Yes.
Not just notes...
the answers.
My dear, I think
you're old enough to hear this.
Life isn't fair.
Oh, I think I know that.
Oh, you don't know
the half of it.
This world is built
by the people on the inside.
A little advantage can mean
the difference between
Living a common,
unremarkable life
And a life that can
change the world.
I'm not trying to change
the world, Miss Cunningham.
I'm just trying to
get back on the team
And see my boyfriend.
Yes, that's all
well and good,
But there's a bigger picture
here, don't you see?
It's about claiming
what is yours, Bridgette.
You can't just wait for it
to come to you.
You've got to
reach out and grab it,
Grab what's rightfully yours,
yours by birth.
With a little help,
you can have everything...
And I'm that little help.
Really?
Don't imagine for a second
this doesn't happen everywhere,
Including Edgington Academy.
How do you think we have such
a flawless graduation record?
You'd be amazed to know
the names of others
Who have had help making it
Through the rigors
of this environment.
Like whom?
Do you really think
top college football stars
Are graduating unassisted?
Not a chance.
Their focus is elsewhere,
as should yours be.
Why me? I mean,
why are you doing this for me?
Because I see myself
in you, Bridgette,
And I don't want you
to end up like me.
We both deserve
better than that.
But you're a teacher
at one of the most prestigious
Private schools
in the world.
Yes, well, even then
I'm just teaching babies
to color
And toddlers to count.
So I'm just a toddler
to you?
Quite the opposite.
You're a young woman
full of great promise.
You are the exception
to every rule.
People like you are rare,
But I know greatness
when I see it.
We all have a purpose
in this life.
You were meant to lead others,
And I was meant to help
people like you
Become the leaders
you were born to be.
That's just the way it is.
[Snickers]
Huh.
Birth control pills?
I hope I'll be seeing you
for the Future Elite Party
In a couple of weeks.
Bobby will be there, too.
It's sure to be
a memorable evening.
[Door opens]
Oh! You scared me.
Sorry.
Working on your English essay?
Yeah.
Wow, you wrote
a lot of notes.
Yeah, yeah. I did.
Okay.
No, I'm just...
I'm glad to see you're, like,
Taking it seriously.
Don't sound so surprised.
[Laugh]
Ow!
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
You hurt your shoulder
at practice?
Not exactly.
You got your Laurels tattoos
without me?
It's tradition to get them
before the semifinals.
I tried to find you,
But you didn't even come
to watch us practice.
I was studying.
Studying or spending time
with your new BFF?
Studying.
Look, I tried.
I'm sorry.
But I'm the captain.
We can get them together
when you're back on the team.
Whatever.
So, late night dining hall?
[Bridgette]
I have work to do.
All right.
Good luck.
A-plus?
Yeah.
What did you get?
A-minus.
That's great.
We both worked
really, really hard.
[Horn blows]
[Candace]
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks.
You keep this up,
And you can have your choice
of any university.
Applications are due soon,
you know.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, Mom, do you know this
new teacher Jane Cunningham?
Who?
Jane Cunningham.
She's filling in
for Miss Patterson,
While she's on
maternity leave.
Miss Patterson is pregnant?
Apparently.
[***]
Yes, yes.
Look, Bradley,
I have to go.
Yes, really, because
my boss just walked in!
Okay.
[Sighs]
How do they expect you
to get good grades,
Have extracurricular activities,
and college applications?
It's barbaric!
I don't even know
how I'm going to write
This personal statement,
whatever it is.
Okay. Let me see.
Ah, sum up your entire
purpose in life,
One page, single spaced,
At a time you're struggling
to figure out
Who you are for yourself.
[Snigger]
Yeah.
Well, what are you
most proud of?
Lacrosse, I guess.
Hmmm.
Must be hard for you
not being on the team.
[Grunts] Yeah, well,
I've only been gone
A couple of weeks, and
it's like I never existed.
I mean, they got their
Laurels tattoos without me.
Those traitors!
Yeah.
Hey...
Let's you and I go together.
I've always wanted a tattoo.
Seriously?
What? Do you think
I'm too old for one?
No, no, no.
Of course not.
Then it's settled!
Right after we finish
your personal statement,
We're getting inked.
[Laugh] Great!
Well, how long will this take?
Not long
if we put our minds to it.
So, tell me more about
your proudest accomplishments.
I guess
I'd start with lacrosse.
Miss Cunningham: Athletics,
like war, is an art.
If you excel at one, who knows
what interests lie dormant?
When you're ready,
then we can add some leaves
Or add some petals.
[Applause]
Remember, thick to thin.
[Door opens and closes]
How was practice?
Good.
Are you handling
everything all right?
What do you mean?
Captain
is a stressful position.
You have to be a leader.
All the girls are looking to you
to set a healthy tone.
It's not easy.
Danni?
[Danni]
Just go to your party.
Oh, wow, that's awesome!
Miss Cunningham: The head
of admissions at Swarthmore
Is actually
a good friend of mine.
So let me speak to her
and see what I can do.
If they were any closer,
I'd have to write them up
For inappropriate
display of affection.
No, they're just friends.
A man's body, no matter
how faithful his heart,
Is powerless against
a pretty girl in a tight dress.
Have you been taking
the pills I gave you?
It's been two weeks now.
Oh, I don't know
if I'm ready for that.
Oh, if you're not,
Little Miss Buxom over there
most certainly is.
I have another engagement
later this evening.
It would be a shame to let
an empty apartment go to waste.
[Giggles]
Where's Miss Cunningham?
She's out of the night.
She... said we could use
her apartment.
And use it for what?
For whatever.
Don't you think
she's a little too into you?
Not as into me
as you're about to be.
[***]
Wait.
Are you sure you're ready?
Do you love me?
Of course, I do.
Then show me.
Oh!
Oh, Miss Cunningham.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know
anyone was in here.
I just finished whipping up
the calculus exam.
It's straightforward, but I...
It's subtle in its
competency... assessment.
I just came to get my lunch bag
out of the fridge
Before the drive home.
Oh!
I knew there was something
different about you
The other day.
What?
It's the beard.
You didn't have it
before, did you?
Um, no, I... I had it, actually.
I've always had it.
I think it gives me a certain,
you know, professorial thing.
[Grunts]
[Heavy breathing]
Oh God!
[Breathing heavily]
You are so sexy.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
You're so sexy.
- Do you love me?
- What?
Do you love me?
Yes, yes, I love you.
Then show me.
Oh!
[grunts] Oh!
[Door opens and closes]
You're still here!
Is he?
Oh, no.
He left a while ago.
I just thought
I'd clean up a bit.
So, how was it?
[Chuckle] Uh, thanks
for making it happen.
Here's your key back.
Keep it.
Mi casa es su casa.
Got a little something
else to give you.
What is that?
Your calculus midterm.
- Uh...
- What's wrong?
I'm not sure
this feels right.
I don't think you understand
just how far I had to go
To get that for you.
I never asked you
to do that.
I did what I had to do
so you can get your life back
And get on
with your larger purpose.
And I really appreciate
all your help,
But I've been studying.
I can do this.
You want me to
just delete that?
[Bridgette]
Maybe that would be best.
What have we been doing
all this for?
None of this matters,
unless we ace this test.
That's your chance
for Eurotour...
Your relationship with
your mother and with Bobby.
You won't be allowed
to see him ever again
If you fail, remember?
We've got everything we need
to ace this exam right here.
I guess I was wrong
about you.
Wait!
Yes, Bridgette?
Nothing.
[Cell phone notification]
[***]
Don't stress
if you didn't finish.
Quality over quantity.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Enjoy the rest
of your afternoon.
Did you lose something?
Yeah, my underwear.
The skimpy red ones?
Yes. You're not
wearing them, are you?
No.
[Giggles]
Hey, well, help me find them.
You know, if I didn't
know any better, I'd say
You and Miss Cunningham are a
little bit more than friends.
Yeah, you caught me.
I'm having an affair
with my English lit teacher.
I'm not going to tell anyone,
as long as I can join in.
Into older women, are you?
Hey, when it comes
to a threesome...
Ew! You're disgusting!
Hey, you'd better
get out of here.
I don't want you here
while she's here.
Well...
My parents are driving up
this weekend for my match,
And they'd love to meet you.
I was wondering if you would
like to go to dinner
With my family.
Yes, as long as we go
someplace far off campus,
So that Candace
won't find out.
Yeah, sure.
No, that's not
what I meant. I just...
I have to get my grades back up
and get her off my back,
And we can show her
what a great catch you are.
[Snigger] Okay.
I guess I'm okay with that.
[Danni]
Where have you been?
Why do you care?
Were you with
Miss Cunningham?
Not really.
What does that mean?
I slept at Jane's,
but she was not there.
Okay.
Bridgette...
Bridgette?
You need to listen to me.
That woman is no good.
What are you talking about?
I know she's been helping you.
So, aren't teachers
supposed to help you?
[***]
Not like this.
Don't tell me that this
is your handwriting
- in the margins.
- Give it!
And I saw you yesterday.
In calculus?
What did you see?
You had a test
that was already filled out.
And how would I have that?
You know what,
I don't know,
But I know it has
something to do with her.
She's going to ruin you.
And like I'm the only one
with secrets around here.
What is that
supposed to mean?
[Phone rings]
Hello.
I'll be right there.
Mom?
Hmmm, good afternoon,
Miss Berwitt.
I thought it best
we do this in person.
Congratulations, Bridgette.
You've made
tremendous strides.
Ah, I read your English essay.
It's masterful,
so on point.
And Mr. Jeter was thrilled
with your calculus midterm.
I don't remember the last time
I saw a student
Make such a remarkable
turnaround.
You've done Edgington proud.
Welcome back
to the lacrosse team!
Horace, I know
you're my campaign manager,
But I still call the shots,
And there's no way
I'm going to show my face
In support of that woman!
No!
Horace, I've got to go.
Bridgette's here.
I am so very proud of you.
Headmaster York is amazed,
but I am not. Cheers.
I didn't doubt for a second
that you could do this.
- You are, after all, a Berwitt.
- [laugh]
It's okay.
You've earned the right
to have Bobby back in your life.
Thanks.
So, why don't you go call him
and tell him the good news,
And I'll start your laundry.
Candace doing laundry?
Don't give me a hard time.
I'm still your mother.
[Candace]
What are these?
They're just to
regulate my period.
Don't lie to me!
Jane Cunningham
gave you these.
Yeah, but she's just
trying to help.
You are never
to see her again.
Well, that's not really
possible, Candace.
She's our faculty resident.
That woman is sick.
Do you understand?
She's a teacher.
She's trying to help me.
She cares about me.
Okay. Please, please.
Bridgette, listen to me.
Why do you have to
control everything?
This is not about control.
I am on your side.
Jane Cunningham
is on my side.
You just happen to be
my mother.
[Bridgette on computer]
Do you love me?
[Bobby on computer]
Of course, I do.
[Bridgette on computer]
Then show me.
Ahem.
Why are you doing this?
[Jane]
Nice to see you, too, Candy.
We agreed to stay out
of each other's lives.
Your daughter came
to me for help.
You call this help?
She took those
from my purse.
She's 17!
I had hoped that your leave
Would have given you
time to think.
Oh, I did nothing but think.
Have you ever read Kawabata?
There's a lyrical subtlety
in his native language
That is sadly lost
in translation.
You do know that Edgington
is still paying
For Hannah's therapy.
She had to put off college
for a year, at least.
Am I to be held accountable
for every student
With a weak constitution?
I'm getting Bridgette assigned
to another English class
And another dorm.
What if she's happy
where she is?
We had an agreement, Jane.
I'm certainly holding up
my end, Candy.
Stay away from my daughter.
She told you that she doesn't
want to stay away, didn't she?
She needs me, Candy,
More than
she's ever needed you,
And you can't stand it.
Good to see you, too,
Candace.
Maybe I'll drop
by the house sometime.
[Muted chatter]
You can go over five,
or you can...
[Jane] Miss Berwitt.
May I see you a moment?
[***]
[Jane] Miss Berwitt,
can I see you for a moment?
[Laugh] God, I can
so turn the teacher thing on
When I want to, can't I?
So hey, I can't believe
You never came to
tell me the good news.
Yeah. Thanks
for all your help.
That meant a lot.
It was nothing.
So, now that we've
crossed that hurdle,
It's time to get back
to those college admissions.
The first step is an engaging
personal statement.
We need to work on yours
post-haste,
So why don't you
grab your things...
I can't right now.
Well, why not?
I'm with my study group,
and it's really important
If I'm going to stay
on the team.
You got back on the team
without their help.
You can stay on the team
without their...
I just can't right now.
Fine! Tonight.
I had dinner plans,
but I can cancel them.
I don't need this anymore.
I have to go.
[***]
[Knock on door]
Jane.
Uh, did your bulb go out?
I could call maintenance.
I was just about to
head over to the cafeteria
To get some dinner,
if you'd like to join.
I mean,
if you're not too busy.
I just thought maybe
we should talk about our...
Well, about us.
I can't stop thinking
about the other night...
Which was so wonderful.
You asked me to express
certain feelings,
And I was just wondering
if that was because
You had similar feelings
towards me.
Okay.
Maybe we could
talk about this later.
But I have to go.
Uh, sure, sure.
Of course.
[Laugh]
Sorry to have interrupted...
Whatever you're doing...
In the dark.
[Bobby] So, my parents really
like you, if you can't tell.
[Laugh]
I like them, too.
Bridgette, what is it?
[Sigh] What if, what if
I don't get into college?
What if I can't make it
outside of Edgington?
Says the girl
who just kicked ass
In all of her midterms?
I don't deserve to be here.
I was just born
into the right family.
Well, Miss Cunningham
seems to think
That you're pretty special.
Right?
What's going on
between you two?
Whatever it is,
you can tell me.
Bridgette?
[Phone vibrates]
Miss Cunningham?
[Jane]
Bridgette, come in!
You said
there was an emergency?
Right. College admissions
deadlines are fast approaching,
And we need to work on
your personal statement.
- Miss Cunningham...
- Jane.
Miss Cunningham,
I really appreciate
Everything you've done for me,
But I should really just do
my own college applications.
That's a very mature thing
to say.
I think I should start taking
responsibility for myself.
Right.
So, tattoos?
[Bridgette] Thanks for getting
them all. I'll read them over
And let you know
if I have any questions.
Please have a cookie.
I'd love to, but I...
I have practice in the morning,
And I should just get to sleep.
I spent all night
decorating these.
At least take a few back to
the room for you and Danielle.
What is that?
You went without me?
We were supposed to
get those together.
It wasn't about you.
It was about my team.
My friends.
[Plate crashing]
[yelling] I am your friend!
When you got
kicked off the team,
They all just went on
with their lives.
I dropped everything for you!
You can't just
walk away from me!
My mother
was right about you.
Bridgette.
[Door closes]
Bridgette!
[Yelling]
[Yelling] Bridgette,
come back here!
Bridgette!
[Yelling]
Jane!
Um, uh, I was afraid I'd done
something to upset you.
Why would you think that?
I don't know.
You know that thing
you wanted to talk about?
That thing?
I told you
we could talk about it later?
Okay, I'm ready.
We can talk about it
right now.
Oh, uh, um, well that's...
Well that's...
Sort of a private matter,
don't you think?
No.
Okay. Okay.
Um, listen, Jane,
Don't you think
it would be better
If we did this privately?
I mean, maybe
we could have dinner.
- Dinner?
- Yeah.
Why would I have dinner
with you?
Uh, what?
Do you really think
someone like me
Would go out
with someone like you?
You can't dress yourself.
Your breath smells.
Your beard is disgusting,
and your hair is falling out.
Your penis is minuscule.
No one likes you.
You're only good at one subject,
the most boring subject,
And right now you've got
soup on your face,
And you don't even know it!
Well, doesn't he?
[***]
[Door opens]
What's going on?
They're putting me
in Pinehurst House.
But that's the dorm for...
Kids who try to
hurt themselves?
Yeah, it is.
I don't understand.
[Sighs] Well, apparently
there was a report
That my eating disorder
is back.
[Sighs]
Is it?
No!
Who would say that?
Who do you think?
We... we've got to do
something.
- We've got to tell somebody.
- Tell somebody?
You don't think
I've already tried?
You think they're
going to believe me?
My shuttle is waiting.
If you want to find me,
look for the short bus.
[Door opens and closes]
[Cell phone notification]
Bridgette.
Bridge?
Where are you?
Hah, you found them.
Bridgette.
Oh, man.
Bridgette, what are you doing?
You are crazy!
Jesus, Bridgette.
[Groans]
[scream]
Hey, come back!
Get away from me!
[sobs]
Get on the ground, now!
- [Sobs]
- Hands behind your back.
[Sobs]
Miss Cunningham?
Thank God you came!
He lured me
under the bleachers.
[Sobs]
[Phone dings]
Hello.
Bobby! Bobby, are you okay?
I've been arrested.
Miss Cunningham.
It was a setup.
She had them put me in jail.
No matter what they tell you,
she made it look like...
Like I...
Okay, I gotta go.
I'm so sorry, Bridgette.
I thought it was you. I swear.
Bobby!
Bridgette, come in.
I just opened
a bottle of wine.
Why are you doing this?
Doing what?
I know what you did
to Bobby and Danni.
Look, whatever happened
to your friends,
I'm sure they got
what they deserved.
They weren't good for you.
You're not good for me!
I'd bite your tongue,
if I were you.
You saw how easy it was
for your grades to get better.
How hard do you think
it would be
For them to get worse again?
Miss Cunningham...
Jane. You know
you can call me Jane.
[Door opens and closes]
[Bridgette]
Mom?
Are you okay?
I just got off the phone
with the headmaster.
He told me about Bobby.
Yeah.
His dad's on the way down
to post bail.
That woman is insane.
The board and York
believe Bobby is innocent,
And we think
the police will, too.
Of course he's innocent.
She should be the one in jail.
She almost was...
Once.
Her three-year sabbatical
was not voluntary.
It was prompted by an alleged
obsession with a student.
So she's done this before.
How could you
let her come back?
Why didn't you turn her in?
We had no solid proof,
Certainly nothing
that would stand up in court.
We decided our best option
was to send Jane
As far away as possible
until it all blew over,
And poor Hannah could get
the help she needed.
When you decided,
who was "we"?
The board, Headmaster York.
Something like this
can ruin a school, Bridgette,
Even an allegation.
But she's insane.
You have to do something!
We're going to meet on it
tomorrow morning.
She's dangerous, Mom.
We don't have
a choice, Bridgette.
Do you have any idea
how hard it is
To fire a tenured teacher,
And I can't afford
a scandal now.
You don't get it, Mom.
It's not just Danni
and Bobby she's after.
Jane's been helping me.
She changed my grades.
She wrote the lit essay
for me...
And she gave me the answers
to the calculus midterm.
I'm sorry.
I know it was wrong,
But, but I have the essay notes
in her handwriting,
And we can use it as proof
that she cheated.
Hopefully it's enough
to get her fired,
Maybe even sent away.
[Sobs]
I'm really sorry.
I know it was wrong.
I didn't mean
for it to happen.
It just did.
Please say something.
Don't just sit there.
The same thing
happened to me.
Here, at Edgington,
25 years ago.
Oh my God!
Jane always had
a brilliant mind.
Socially inept,
mildly delusional...
But completely brilliant.
It... it started out
as nothing.
I would come in late
from play rehearsal exhausted,
And she'd talk me
through the homework.
But it kept progressing.
I had no time to study.
I was class president.
I was captain
of the volleyball team.
I was lead in the fall play,
and the more I took on,
The more I needed her.
And I let her do it for me.
And before I knew it,
it just...
I know.
Jane...
She did my application.
She got me in.
But look what it got me.
This.
A career.
A standing in the community.
Respect.
Everything I always wanted.
You're not going to do
anything.
Are you?
You're afraid
she'll expose you.
Cornell?
Jane?
Yeah.
[Laugh]
You've gotta go.
What? Are you serious?
If you don't play
by her rules,
She will out you
as a cheater.
You'll be kicked
out of Edgington.
You'll be a pariah
at any Ivy League school.
This is your future,
Bridgette,
The rest of your life
we're talking about.
What, so I'm just
supposed to play along?
Yes.
And then you can go off
to Cornell and start over
And forget
any of this ever happened.
Have you forgotten it, Mom?
[***]
* How did you take me
this far *
* My, oh my
* I wasn't prepared
from the start *
* For life, oh I
* I should tell the truth
* But I lie to you
* But if you to
* I will die for you
* Because I lose
* Time after time,
so I use... *
I'm sorry.
I... I just had to see you.
I let myself in.
I fell asleep waiting for you.
I... I hope you don't mind.
Of course not.
Are you all right?
I don't like being alone.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry
for what Bobby did to you.
I should have
seen it coming.
He was always
talking about you.
I just can't believe
he did what he did.
I'll be fine.
Don't you worry about me.
And Danni.
She was just
so jealous of me...
Of you and me.
At times, we don't want
to see the signs of illness
In the people we love.
I realize now just what
you were trying to do for me.
I understand now the way
things work in the real world.
I didn't get that before,
but I get that now.
- I'm just here to help.
- I know.
Just like you helped
my mother.
She told you?
I saw something
in your mother.
I knew it
from the moment we met.
She had something.
Everyone was drawn to her.
She had the light.
And you were
such good friends.
We were.
We were, indeed.
And you did so much
To help her to get her
where she is today.
I'm sorry you drifted apart.
It was inevitable,
but I'm happy for your mother,
And I'm happy I could
help her in some small way.
You have the gift, Bridgette.
I saw it in you
The very same way
as I saw it in your mother.
Everyone is born
with a purpose.
I recognized at a very early age
that I don't have that light,
That spark that you
and your mother have.
But what I do have
Is the ability to recognize
those lights in others
And help those light bearers
achieve their destinies.
You really think I'm a light
bearer, Miss Cunningham?
Jane.
Oh, I know so.
It's my gift, remember?
Your light is bright, my dear.
I have so much to learn.
Teach me.
Help me.
[***]
Okay. Just make this
a little bit more clear.
Okay.
[Phone vibrates]
Sorry. I don't recognize
this number. I better get it.
Hello?
Yes, it is.
Are you serious?
Oh my God!
Yes, th... thank you.
Thank you so much!
I'm a finalist for Eurotour!
Bridgette, that's amazing!
Congratulations!
Tryouts are this weekend,
upstate.
Oh, it's so exciting!
I have a great idea.
How about you come up
with me?
- To the trials?
- Yes.
We'll have so much fun
on the trip,
And maybe on the way back,
we can stop in New York City,
Catch a show,
see a couple of museums.
I don't know.
Just the two of us?
Yeah! A weekender.
We'll have a blast!
Okay!
[Cheers]
All set?
Where's your stuff?
Bridgette, is something wrong?
You're one crazy bitch!
I beg your pardon?
Come on. Let's go!
You're not going anywhere.
But what about Eurotour?
Jane, stop!
I've had enough of you.
My mother
has had enough of you.
All those girls you've ruined
have had enough of you!
You're evil,
And you're going away
for a long, long time.
Bridgette...
Don't do this.
- You need me.
- I don't need you!
All that stuff about
you recognizing light
And helping others
is just your sick way
Of justifying your lonely
and obsessive existence.
I don't need you.
I have never needed you.
No one has ever needed you.
[Jane]
Bridgette!
Listen to what you're saying.
You could have everything,
and you're throwing it all away.
I want you to admit yourself
To St. Abigail's
psychiatric ward.
It's a lockdown
treatment facility.
I... will expose you...
For the cheat that you are.
You will never
graduate from here,
Much less go to Cornell
Or any other reputable
university for that matter.
Fine! So be it!
Headmaster York
is right outside these doors.
Now you come to your senses,
or I go straight out there
And I tell him
all about your cheating
And your mother's as well.
Jane,
I'm giving you a chance.
I won't go to the FBI
if you'll just comply.
FBI?
I'm afraid
giving prescription drugs
To a minor is a felony.
Oh, and those tapes
of Bobby and I having sex?
Hmm, I think the FBI frowns
upon child pornography.
[Fighting sounds]
[Screams]
[Cheers]
Say it!
Say you'll go!
Say you'll go,
or I'm going to the FBI.
- Okay. Let me up!
- You'll go?
- Yes.
- You'll go immediately.
Yes.
[Heavy breathing]
[Screams]
I dare you.
You think
you could blackmail me?
Huh?
[Scream]
[Heavy breathing]
Are you all right?
Oh, my baby! My baby!
Miss Berwitt,
are you all right?
Why would you do
all that alone?
That was reckless.
Indeed!
You could have been killed.
That woman is very dangerous.
Now you say so.
You should have never let
Jane Cunningham come back,
And you know it.
Yes, well, it's over now,
thanks to you.
Hold on, Headmaster.
I know what you did.
I know you played a part
In Jane Cunningham
coming back to Edgington,
And I know you were in cahoots
with Candace on the cover-up.
But we're going to put
all of that behind us right now.
Here's how it's gonna go.
Mom, effective immediately,
You're going to
turn in your resignation
As chairman
of the Edgington board.
Agreed?
Agreed.
[Bridgette]
And Headmaster York,
You are going to make
Edgington history
And grant me
a second chance...
A repeat of my senior year,
as well as reinstate
My position
as the lacrosse captain,
Once the very able
current captain
Completes the season.
In exchange, I will maintain
a 3.5 or above GPA
Throughout the year,
fairly and squarely.
No cheating.
Agreed?
Agreed.
[Swan honk]
[Candace] You're so brave.
If I had half your courage
when I was your age.
Hey, no more looking back,
Mom, only moving forward.
You did the right thing...
Giving up your position
on the board
And coming clean
with cheating in school.
I'm really proud of you,
And I'm really sorry it had
such an impact on your campaign.
I think you would have been
The best city councilman
probably ever.
[Laugh]
But I'm not sorry
it happened.
Things are better now.
Such a weight lifted.
I don't know
what I was so afraid of.
I haven't been this relaxed
in 25 years.
Well, a Berwitt
is never down for long.
What's next,
another campaign?
Another board?
President?
[laugh]
I know exactly what
I'm going to be doing.
I'm going to be enjoying you
For the last few weeks
that you're here
Before you go off to college
Because there's nothing
more important to me.
The rest will all
fall into place.
[***]
[Jane] Love her,
love her, love her.
If she favors you,
Love her.
If she wounds you,
If she tears your heart
to pieces
And as it gets older
and stronger,
It will tear deeper.
Love her, love her.
Love her.
Everybody needs
a little help sometimes.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
You have a bright future
ahead of you.
Trust me.
Your light is very bright,
my dear.
[***]