Life is about making decisions.
I suppose the ones taken from
me were the worst possible.
I wish I could take the time back.
No.
I want my life to be normal again
My name is Casey Benson...
and this year I graduated
from West Angus Gymnasium.
MONTH EARLY
- Hey, Case.
- Hey.
Can you look at me and tell me
if I have solved it properly?
y... x..4x... equals 5...
Yes, it looks right!
Thank you! I really need
another six on algebra.
Mother will kill me otherwise.
GIRL WITH PERSPECTIVE
(way of life)
Just tell you I hate them.
- Bye.
- Yes, until later.
- Jeremy!
- Oh, hello.
How many hours are we going
to the shore tonight?
Aahahm, see Casey, can
we talk for a moment?
What do you think of her?
- Too thick legs.
- It can happen.
Seriously?
Her hair is disgusting.
- It's true.
"We can always paint her hair.
Yes, but we can not paint her face.
What's left?
Look, Casey.
I do not know how to tell you.
That's why I'll say it straight away.
You are a very precise girl,
but it will not happen to me.
What?
Well, we did understand to
be honest with each other.
- Yes.
"Well, I'm honest at the moment."
One kind... I like another.
Which?
She studies in Ven Westerly.
"It does not matter, I'm sorry. Is everything alright?
- OK?
Yes, if you want to go out
with one of my friends...
- I will not mind.
- Coming out with your friends?
Yes. I just want to say
it will not bother me.
Hey, Jeremy?
I have to go.
If you do not want this plush
'kimono' dragon I won for you...
I can give it to my
sister for her birthday.
But if you want to keep it, there
are no problems. Whatever.
Hey, dumbass!
Do you want me to be honest?
Are we honest with each other?
It's not 'kimino', it's comodo.
And he did not win it.
The man you gave him out of pity...
because it spent 36 $...
and yet you could not
even get a bottle.
I can buy the same
for $ 2 in Chinese.
- It hurts me!
- Seriously? Casey Benson?
That dick?
Yes. Simple at first glance.
But there is a potential.
The previous owner has left.
pretty fast...
he left everything in the kitchen so
the equipment comes in the price.
Refrigerators are old.
We will have to change them.
But everything else is in good condition.
We can cover the deposit.
My Investor Confirmed
That Location Is Great...
The common room is exactly
what we wanted...
the kitchen is small.
Look, I'll take care of the bills...
but everything here depends on you.
"Holly, if you do not like the place..."
- It's great.
- Do you think?
- I adore him.
Great!
"That really means we're starting, is not it?"
- Let's start.
Thank you.
- Hi, Casey!
- Hi, Amber. What's up?
Very cute blouse!
"Well, what are you thinking about doing this Friday?"
- I do not have plans anymore.
Taylor, Kylie and I will go to a club.
Do you want to join?
Do you want me to come with you?
This is new.
Did not your cars get
damaged at the same time?
Wow! Problems with confidence I feel.
Lovely.
Have you ever been
to the Gold Bar?
Gold Bar? No.
You must be 21 to enter,
and we are only 18.
It is!
That's why I must have arranged
a fake ID card for you...
and these things do not happen right away.
Well? What would you say?
Are you with us?
- Come on, Casey, it'll be fun!
- I do not know.
All right.
See what.
This is the e-mail sent
me a picture of you.
I'll send you the card
and see what happens.
Say when you decide.
All right.
What did he want?
She asked if I wanted to go
with them to the Gold Bar.
They'll make me a fake ID.
You are kidding!
Can he do one for me?
I do not know if I'm going.
After Jeremy...
I'm not like guys.
Forget Jeremy.
Does not deserve you!
Come on.
Meggy talked to a
restaurant for a long time.
Should I call her to tell her
that you are not interested?
Meggy needs a business partner,
and I'll take the whole menu.
She needs an investor
this is all!
We should not be her kind of ATM.
Not true! She did not
even ask me a penny!
Yeah right. Still, just wait!
- I really want to participate.
- No way.
I will not let you
blow our savings...
for some idiotic
restaurant stupidity.
- Christopher!
- No!
I decided to apply at Wittendale in the fall.
If anyone is interested.
Dear, this is great!
When did you decide?
- In the last few days.
- I am very happy.
I was hoping you'd be there.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
My dear, I had the impression you
wanted to go to Cal State Northridge.
I think.
Wittendale have the best
department in geology...
I think this is a
great solution!
Do you really want to move to
the other end of the country?
Yes.
Can you excuse me?
I have a lot of work to do...
I have a lot of work on
this tattoo I will do.
Very funny!
Mila proud of you.
- Thanks.
- Me too.
"All right, what is it?"
- Nothing.
We told her he could
go to Wittendale...
do you know how much effort
he made to go there?
That's why I do not
want Maggie and I...
to dig us up with your
restaurant business.
This has nothing to do
with the restaurant!
And thanks to him, I can help.
"Do you really believe him?"
- Yes.
do you know how long
it will take before...
to start recovering
if it ever starts?
No! You will work for no money and I
will be distorted to support you.
This is not true.
We have already secured an investor.
We will not need money.
- I ended up with this conversation.
- All right, but I'm not.
I have to call. Excuse me.
Hold for a moment.
Hey, Amber is.
You know what to do.
Hey, Amber. Casey is.
Look at your e-mail. I sent you the picture.
I'll see you on Friday.
4 Long Beach Ice Tea.
- How much do they cost?
- Casey, get out.
I will pay the first,
and then take the boys.
- The boys?
- First rule.
If you do not buy a drink
for the first 3 minutes...
is not worth the attention.
Wait for you to meet Max and Roger.
They are well loaded.
Hey, Amber, my lovely one!
Max, that's Casey.
- Hi, Casey.
- Hello.
- Girls already have drinks!
- Well, buy us shots.
Awesome idea. six 'kamikaze',
please be cold as well.
"One more, please.
- No, it's enough for me.
No way!
I will not drink myself.
He was watching us.
That's right.
Did you like what you saw?
Drink. You'll like.
Patricia approves of it.
- Who is Patricia?
She is the alcoholic
living in me.
"I've never met a girl like you."
- Me too.
- I have a question about you.
- Is it rhetorical?
Perhaps.
Patricia likes to kiss
her before people...
from a person who
has just met...
and who, unbelievably, likes it?
I'm not sure about Patricia, but...
Casey would have liked it.
I told you it would
fit perfectly.
- At 18, is not it?
- Spock. I checked the ID card.
It's all over.
Kylie has a problem.
No, I was not kidding!
"I thought you were joking!"
"Do you seem to joke?"
No, but do you think I
can hear anything...
of that music?
Very well heard what I said!
You know what? I'm getting away.
Hey, calmly get my hands off me.
- What is the problem?
- He does not want to pay.
Did not I know he
was a prostitute?
Do not call it that.
500 bucks, fast.
Dude I do not have that much money.
He did not have that much money.
He does not have that much money.
If I see you around
my girls again...
I will tear you a throat.
- Have we got it?
- Yes.
Are you okay?
Kylie, I love you...
but you have to let
me record customers.
I'm sorry, Jack.
- Come on. Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Did he hurt you?
- No.
I am fine.
God, I adore this song!
- Me too.
- Yeah right. -No, seriously!
Do you want to get out?
- All right.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Oh, yeah, that's familiar to me.
It's good.
You can get used to it.
"What's your whole floor?"
- No, not exactly.
Nice and comfortable.
Oh, look.
There is a sushi restaurant...
and one more opposite.
"They're so close to each other.
- Allow me.
- Wait.
- What's wrong?
I do not...
Nothing.
Casey?
Do you know it's 1 at night?
I'm sorry.
I lost a sense of time.
Hold it.
Where have you gone tonight?
I told you. I went to a movie.
- Did you?
"God, do you really need to
to make this conversation now?
- I'm tired.
- Let's have it now!
If you are not too drunk
to have a conversation.
What's happening?
Casey just got back
half an hour ago...
and she's obviously got drunk.
I'm not drunk.
What would happen if the
police had stopped you?
Holly, calm down.
She did not stop her. She
said she was not drunk.
Thanks.
Okay, do you smell it?
She made a small mistake.
Do you remember when
we were her age?
Will not be repeated.
Casey, I do not want
to talk again about...
driving drunk, did we get it?
- We agreed.
- All right, go to sleep.
- Good night, Daddy.
- Good night.
Is this the message that
you want to get our girl?
That it is normal to lie to us...
to miss the evening hours?
Honey, you have to be more relaxed.
Little. Miss you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Holly really need to
relax as a whole.
- Who is she?
- What you mean?
You really need to check
your phone more often.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
She just said you missed her.
They must have confused the number.
And why are you
looking at my phone?
Do you have a mistress?
- Do you have?
- No! I do not.
Even if I had it,
would it matter?
It's not like we've had
something left lately.
I can not believe
that such men exist!
It's so cute and funny.
I was going to give up
the men after Jeremy.
Mother dear!
You can not compare idiots
from school with...
mature men.
This is the difference
between low and high class.
It was the best
night in my life.
Well, it's about to
become even better!
- What is this?
- Your share of Max - $ 600.
Very funny.
I will take them if you do not want to.
You mean Max has paid to...
Does that mean I'm a prostitute?
No, that makes you smart.
There is nothing wrong with what we do.
From which planet do you come from?
First, this is illegal.
And second I do not sleep
with men for money.
Neither do we. Let's talk
with them because we want to.
Money is just a bonus.
Casey, look around.
Look in the mirror.
We do it and we do not have
to apologize to anyone.
We decide for ourselves with
whom to spend our time...
and with no one.
But our attention is not free.
And they know it
It's no different if he
brought you to dinner...
and took you a bottle
of champagne for $ 600.
The one difference is that it
gives you the money directly.
Casey, do not think so much.
He's been doing great, you too.
All the above won a little money.
Look, how many times did you sleep with Jeremy?
And what do you get in return?
McDonoughs and Cinema?
Was that a kimono
dragon for two dollars?
Please!
Casey where did he go?
Will return.
I do not know what happened to us.
Before he was so funny,
loving and kind...
But in recent years it has changed.
He is constantly angry and distant.
She started to work late, to go
somewhere without telling me.
Well, what are you going to do?
What I had to do
a long time ago.
I'll ask for a divorce.
I have a meeting with a lawyer...
tomorrow morning.
I'm afraid to tell him.
You will tell me if you need something, do not you?
You can count on me.
Thank you, I can handle it.
Before you tell him anything...
look at your property, bank
accounts, such things.
Why?
When my sister divorced...
her husband emptied all their
savings and hid them from her.
It was a complete mess.
- Hey.
- I'm not a prostitute.
All right.
All the nonsense
that he told me...
that I am smart and
beautiful and unique?
Why did you ever bother,
you paid for everything?
I told them because I
really thought them.
Yeah right.
You are a false bastard! Walk on...
Hey, Casey. Stop, can you
at least listen to me?
It was incredible last night.
I really love you too.
I think you're
smart, sexy, fun...
I do not want to stop seeing.
If you feel bad
about the money...
do not take them.
I thought you defined
the conditions.
And I thought you were frank.
I guess we're wrong.
Please do not.
wait...
If you do not want to see
more, that's your right.
You can just leave and
never look at me again...
But I really hope you
make another decision...
because next week I come
back to town again...
and I'm glad to get out together...
in some nice place.
What would you say?
We will see.
So we will see.
I have something for you.
Do you remember the song
from the club you like?
I called a friend of
mine this morning.
He is a promoter...
- These are third-order!
- Yes.
I was thinking to give
it to you next week,
but when I was surprised
so pleasantly...
- Wow, thank you!
- You're welcome.
- Until next week?
- We will see.
I will help you.
AVAILABILITY PER ACCOUNT: 0.00 $
There is nothing wrong
with what we do.
If you feel bad
about the money...
do not take them.
Casey, do not think so much.
You both spent great.
All the above won a little
money during that time.
Really?
Hey, Max. Is everything alright?
Actually not.
Casey came to the hotel this morning...
and gave me the money back.
What has she done?
He told me he was
not a prostitute.
Jack, I'm not sure
what you're doing.
It was not very cool.
I'm sorry it happened, man.
Will not be repeated.
Look, I do not want to get her into trouble.
I really like it very much.
It's okay, I understand.
We have to be discreet.
Right?
Sometimes I come with
clients at this hotel.
Max, calm down, is not it?
We'll fix things.
There is nothing to worry about.
Well then.
A light path and I'll
see you next week.
Well then.
Max is one of my most
profound clients, Amber.
She was new, she did not know.
Yeah, maybe you had to
explain it to her...
before taking it with you.
Jack, wait! Do not.
Let me talk to her.
He's going to talk, Amber!
I promise. There is no.
I know her.
It would be best not to.
She's your girl.
If you do not take care
of that, I'll do it.
Hello.
Hi, I wanted to talk about something.
I was like a full-blown last
night and I'm very sorry.
How was your day?
Not very well.
What happened?
I checked our bank
account and found this.
And?
Our accounts are empty.
What happened to our money?
I moved them.
How did you move them?
I've been dealing with our
finances for 20 years.
You never asked me.
And suddenly this curious.
Because these are not just your money.
These are our money...
the money we saved...
for the University of Casey.
Exactly.
That's why I invested them.
What did you invest in?
Walter, he told me about a deal...
with which he killed the fish some time ago.
And I did the same.
Have you put our money
on a risky exchange?
Can we download them?
It's not risky.
For hedges it's...
and yes, we can pull them, but
there will be penalties...
we just have to wait a little while.
If we wait, however, we will
regain our input many times.
Do you mean that our
money is virtually gone?
Our money is not gone.
Look at one is cheating on me.
It is another thing to ruin
our daughter's future.
Holly, would you quit?
You do not know what you're talking about.
You know? I've been thinking
about it for some time...
I can not go any further.
I want a divorce.
You know our marriage has not
been going on for a long time.
- You serious?
- Yes.
Do you want to divorce?
And I think you have to go out.
Right?
Just by way of the case...
I think it's going to be
much easier for Casey.
Do you think I have to
get out of my house?
The house I've been
paying for 20 years...
to have a roof over
your head and Casey?
Do not you go mad?
At the end, lawyers will
decide who will get the house.
Just for the moment it will be best.
You are the most self-centered, self-interested...
And you'll take care of
University Cash for Casey.
19 years.
All he did was get you.
And now do you want me to move?
You are the one to move.
Not so!
You are the one who thinks
it's too good for me
Why do not you move, huh?
Just get out of here
- Christopher, stop.
- What? What to stop!
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
Holly, I'm sorry!
I did not want.
Dad?
- All right, sweetheart.
- What's happening?
Everything is fine.
I promise, just go home.
Where do you lead him?
I promise, everything is fine.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Why are you taking him?
Everything is fine. I promise.
Mom, what's up?
What the hell is going on here?
- Casey, your father hit me.
- What?
My God.
We scrambled and he lost
his own self-control.
How did you crack?
Is it for me?
Because I was late that night?
- No, no, no.
"What then?"
Come here.
I asked your father for a divorce.
I would wait until you finished...
I can not do it anymore.
I'm sure Dad is sorry
for what he's doing.
Did you try to fix
things between you?
Just...
It's too late now.
Right?
Is it too late...
for two people who
said they loved...
and have they muttered to each other,
to dare to quarrel constantly?
Mile is not that simple.
Trust me. I tried.
I tried as much as I could.
Is it true?
I do not think you want a divorce...
- It's like having tried enough.
- Your father has a mistress...
and I know I should not tell you, but...
he has withdrawn almost
all of our savings.
He has put them in
some bad investment.
You mean we have nothing left?
I'll take care of us.
I promise.
How, Mom?
How do you make sure...
sending dad to prison?
"I suppose you enjoyed it."
- Not so.
You know this is not true.
Okay, he hit you.
This is terrible.
Did you really have
to call the police?
No, but you wanted to humiliate him
in front of all our neighbors, right?
I'm getting out of here.
Vodka with soda.
Who is she? Is it from yours?
Yes. Excuse me.
Yes.
Why is she here?
- How would I know?
"Better have no trouble with her."
I do not want the Princess
to fuck our business.
Relax. He must be here to work.
I want to be sure in that case.
I have a client ready
so go and find out.
- All right, after a while.
- Immediately!
Cheers!
You want something to drink.
Bartender?
No no. That's enough for me.
Are you okay?
Great! My dad is in the dungeon.
My mother wants a divorce...
and I find that my
family is falling apart.
How was your day?
You are kidding.
I do not want to go
to university anyway.
The only reason I get
excellent grades...
was to go to study
geodesy and ecology.
Casey, I'm so sorry.
You will not do something
stupid now, will you?
No. I need a rest.
That is all.
Well, was there time to think
about our conversation?
And?
And, I really wish I had not
returned Max's money...
especially after all
that has happened today.
Listen, Casey.
I'm not a finance expert,
but I know this:
I can work from $ 500 to $ 2000
for one night.
On more busy weekends I can bring
them up to 6 grand! It's easy.
I will never have to
think of money anymore.
Neither do you.
How much do I owe you?
The girl in purple, do you like it?
How long is it all night?
2 grand.
1 and 500.
Okay, well two sounds decent.
Case?
Do you see that guy there?
Ready to pay 1200
overnight with you.
I think he explicitly wants you.
The decision is yours.
Up to you.
It looks like Jeremy
plus 10 years.
Two more vodka with soda, and
I'll look like Bradley Cooper.
Where were you?
Good morning to you too!
Do we have aspirin?
- I called you all night.
- I know. That's why I put out my phone.
I was scared of worry!
Just to call the police!
Right?
Why should they close me?
Okay, I do not deserve such an attitude.
Neither am I. I am 18.
I can stay out all
night if I want to.
Casey!
"Where did you get that money?"
- It is not your business.
Who gave you that?
Casey?
Father! He gave it to me.
Ask me not to tell you.
And how long has your father
been giving you so much money?
From a week ago he went to jail.
Take half.
They're actually yours.
What do you think of this?
I want her!
I adore her.
$ 900.
I love this dress.
In that case, it brings it...
I think he'll be right
with these shoes.
When was she last
shopping for her?
This is the cop, Jack.
Our work is broken.
Seriously!
It's coming.
- Good evening ladies.
- Hello.
- Hey.
You seem to have gone through
all the shops in the mall.
Hello dear. How are you?
I'm better now.
May I sit?
Casey, it's time
to meet the boss.
You know Officer Jack, are not you?
From school, yes, hi.
Hello. It's a little weird, huh?
It can be said.
Jack introduces us
to the men we meet.
When asked...
what are you going to do this Wednesday?
We have a school activity.
We have a client that I
think will interest you.
A Hollywood actor, by the
late 20's, is very sweet.
We call it Valentino.
No way!
Did he return?
God, Casey, you have to see it.
It's wonderful.
And let's say he gives
as much as you give him.
Hey, Taylor. Where have you been?
Put a nose on my nose. Why?
Give me your prowess.
Your prowl, right away!
Okay, here we are again.
I told you to leave this shit.
What are you going to do?
Will you arrest me?
No. I'm just not going to
write you for more work.
It looks like you do not
need that much money, huh?
I'm sorry. I'll get them out.
You know the rules.
Our scrambling is 'clean'.
Well well. God.
What are you going to order?
Amber, would you like
to divide a salad?
Why not.
Casey, I saw your father's file.
I'm sorry you need
to go through this.
Tomorrow they'll probably release him.
I think I'm going to get a taco.
How long have you been a pimp?
I prefer the word 'manager'.
- Manager, sorry.
- No problem.
What exactly does the manager do
in an industry like this one?
Well, Casey...
I carefully select
the people you meet.
And what do you win?
A fair question is, is not it?
- No?
- Yes, it is.
My profit varies.
Sometimes it is 20%, sometimes it is more.
Depends on customer.
Do not worry.
You do more than I do.
There is a logic, yet we do
more than you do, do not we?
Wow, look at yourself!
I just knew you.
Hey.
Where have you been?
I have not seen you forever!
You know...
Talk to Amber?
About the ID card?
Come on, Casey! You know I'm also
going to go to the Gold Bar.
You do not have to go there.
What? Why not?
And what does that mean?
I'll see you in class.
What does that mean, Casey?
It's getting bigger. That's disgusting!
What would Jack say?
Nothing. Just get out in a few days and...
take that, it should help.
For now.
This time it was at least number one.
Number two is
disgusting, believe me.
Taylor, shut up.
You will be OK.
One moment.
Excuse me. I have a quick question.
It `s urgent.
A girl just came in here.
Blonde, so high.
He wore a black coat and high heels.
Can you tell me where he went?
We do not provide such information,...
and I do not follow anyone
who goes through the lobby.
Hello.
Please, please, do this to me.
This girl is my daughter.
If you wanted to know where he was
going, he would probably tell you.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but
I can not help you.
Would you listen to me? Baxter!
My daughter just came here,
looking like a whore!
I'm afraid something really
bad can happen to her...
if I do not find it.
Madam, this is a first class hotel...
we have a duty to keep our
customers confidential.
If they want to spend their evening
in the company of a young lady...
this is their job.
Wait a minute.
What are you trying to say?
I say this is not her
first stay here.
It seems like the type of person
who can take care of himself.
I will now ask you to address
your personal problems elsewhere.
This is my only child!
She's in high school, damn it!
Madam, if you do not calm down,
I'll have to call the guards.
What are you doing here?
Are you following me?
What have you been doing
for the last 3 hours?
And no more lies!
Why did you come here?
I went to a party.
The receptionist hinted
that you had come before.
He's told the truth. I've come.
Many people are doing coupons here.
Casey, dear...
if you got involved in something
you can not get out of...
- I'm not!
- Who's Max?
I saw your calendar and
saw the $ 900 tickets.
Are you in my stuff?
I can not believe!
Please tell me the truth!
Max has given you that money.
OK! Fine. Yes. Max gave me the
money and tickets for the concert.
Are you happy? They are gifts.
- Max and I love each other.
- All right. How old is Max?
On 28.
"And where did you meet?"
- God!
Casey! Max should not
go out with someone...
who has not yet graduated from high school!
Do not you understand?
Mom, you have no idea what
you're talking about.
You can not tell
me what to do now.
Yes I can! I am still your mother,
and you still see me under my roof.
This is about to change.
Move out.
- What did you say?
- Goodbye. Stop watching me.
Casey, do not be ridiculous.
Where are you going to go?
- Hello.
- Hello I am.
Casey, what time is it?
I have no idea.
God, it's three and a half in the morning.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I will not stay
with Mommy anymore.
Welcome to the group.
Look, dear, I'm sorry I did not call.
I was trying to decide what I would do.
Look, Dad.
I need a favor.
19 years.
19 years I work for you child.
I gave her every
penny, everything.
And how does he thank me?
They call the police
to put me in jail.
Father?
He must have told you I hit her.
It's true.
I did it and I'm sorry.
It just happened, but did you
tell her she hit me first?
Did he say that to you?
Dad, I need a place to stay.
What?
Can I stay with you?
To me?
Where are you?
Do you think Mike, from my job?
There is a small apartment.
There is hardly room for me.
I got together on
a single couch.
Miley, believe me.
I would shelter you if you can.
But I can not.
But you know what?
I could send you some money.
You will be able to
find a temporary home.
Or do you know what?
You can stay at a hotel.
This may be fun.
Do you know any good hotels?
Case?
Hello? Casey?
Kay...
Thank you for allowing me
to stay here for the night.
Do not worry.
Are you sure mothers
do not mind?
Yes, completely.
You can use my room.
I'll be up, okay?
My mother has been ringing
me for about an hour.
Take it. Do not answer her.
I'll ever have to.
On the contrary, there is no.
Your mother must realize that
you are already great and...
you can make your own decisions.
You are not tied to her. And you
can stay here as much as you want.
Now go and take a relaxing
bath and go to sleep.
- All right.
- Going to bed.
Thank you, Amber.
She would do the same for me.
- Good night.
I know, I know, I know.
God, look at this junk.
How will I do?
It takes too much.
You should have
warned me earlier.
I pay him for every hour.
Do you know how much it costs me?
"It's mine.
- What?
- That.
- On the contrary. I bought it.
- Remember? It's mine.
- All right, keep it.
In fact, I've paid for everything here.
Virtually everything
is mine, feel lucky.
By the way, where is Casey?
She went to a girlfriend
for a few days.
Has she not exported?
No, she has not gone.
You've never been
good in lies, Holly.
You are right, this
is your specialty.
Call me at night.
He said he did not want
to live with you anymore.
Where did she go? You know,
first, then, and Casey.
You're fine, you kicked
everyone out of your life.
Take a new TV because I
will go back to the LCD.
Knock Knock?
I got a message from Jack.
How do you feel about
earning $ 5,000 today?
You're probably joking?
No! He said we had a rich client...
Who likes watching two girls in
action and is willing to pay.
- Luck of the lottery. What do you think?
- Troll?
I can not do it.
- Come on, Casey.
- No way!
Do not be so narrow-minded!
What is the problem?
Do not you find me attractive?
Very funny!
Anyway, I'm busy.
Max will return tonight.
Well, we're doing it by 4 o'clock in the afternoon...
and you can see Max afterwards.
That's 5 grand!
Only a few such a month and...
you can pay your money and
get your own apartment...
on the beach.
All right.
Only me and you.
Yes! All right. I'll call
Jack and tell him we agree.
We agree!
Great rich man?
Really?
You'll be here all the time, right?
I will not move from here.
Unlocked.
Wow.
Hey.
You are both so wonderful.
Thank you for coming.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'm coming in a minute.
He is...
He'll pay us pretty well.
Casey...
take one of these and you
will not know where you are.
Ok?
No!
I do not want to do it.
Did he see what it looks like?
He is ugly, and old and lousy!
Casey!
And so...
you find me ugly and disgusting.
Please drink.
I'm sorry, I did not
have to say it.
It's interesting to tell
someone in your industry.
Especially considering
the money I pay...
to get exactly the opposite.
Sit next to me.
All right.
I would like to...
I can do it.
And while she does,
I want you to...
You're not particularly convincing.
I am sorry. I can not.
Casey!
I need you.
Did you hear me? I need...
Hey, what happened?
I can not make it sorry.
What you mean?
I'm not going to do it
with this paraglider!
I do not care how
much money we offer.
How not!
She hired two girls.
Go back.
You go and do it after
it is so important.
Come here! Come here!
Listen to me! It has already
caused me enough problems.
So if you do not go back, do
not do what Amber says...
I will beat you in such a way...
that it will be months before you
can guess. Do you understand?
Now come back!
- Wait wait!
- Do not...
Casey!
What the hell is going on?
Come inside!
- You're fired.
- I'm leaving.
I know where you live.
I know where your dad is working.
If you tell someone...
I will kill both your parents...
and then you too.
And if you think these are empty
promises, think again. I'm a cop.
I know exactly how to
get away with murder.
Hey.
- Is everything alright?
- No.
I did not expect you.
Wow, hello Casey!
Will you join?
I thought I'd see you tonight.
- Casey?
- Mommy?
Dear, what happened?
What about you?
"Can you come get me?"
"Of course, where are you?"
And how many girls are
involved in this?
I am not really sure.
A few.
Are they also from your school?
Mom, I told you, I do not
have to talk about it.
Here.
This pimp, how did you meet?
Mom, stop. Everything
you need to know...
is that it's dangerous
if I tell someone...
Baby, we can not let
them get out of here.
They will do the same with another girl.
Someone has to stop them.
Mom, they'll kill me, you know!
So just quit.
Dear, if they threatened you,
then we have to go to the police.
God, no!
Certainly not the police.
Promise you will not get involved.
Why?
I do not want to explain
what I've done.
I do not want to tell them
that I have prostituted.
Dear, they lied to you.
They have drawn you into something
you did not want to take part in.
It is not.
I chose it myself.
I myself chose to take the
money, no one made me.
I'm not the one you think, Mom.
I'm not the one I thought I was.
On the contrary, you are.
You are still that little girl I
loved from the moment she was born.
We all are wrong.
I'm also wrong.
It does not define you as a person.
- I'm sorry.
- Do not...
- Dear...
I love you more than
anything in the world.
Let's just move.
Let's just get out of Los Angeles.
I do not want to live here anymore.
We'll make it, I promise you.
I would like to move my
daughter out of this school...
and they said I had
to demand a transfer.
I'm disappointed to hear it. Casey
is among our best students.
- I know.
"There's no problem?"
- Is our conversation confidential?
- Completely!
Casey is afraid to
come back here.
There seem to be some people...
students...
involved in something illegal.
Mrs. Benson, if this is the case...
I need to know what's going on.
I do not know if it's happening on...
the territory of the school but...
I have reasons to believe
that some of the students...
are involved in sexual circles.
Has Casey telling you that?
Did not tell me names...
or details, but it was very clear he
did not want to be part of it all.
But yes, she told me.
With your permission, I
would like to do something.
These are certainly
undesirable news.
Prostitution is becoming an
increasing problem in schools.
In Granada Hills have
caught a 16-year-old boy...
to pimp your 15-year-old
girlfriend.
We are talking about good schools!
These children are of decent families.
Girls do not think they're
doing anything wrong.
Or at least so.
This is a real tragedy.
We need to stop him before
he gets stuck in our school.
Certainly.
Do not worry, Mrs. Benson.
I appreciate your daughter's private life.
We will get to the
bottom of this story.
- Thank you.
- For nothing.
Thank you, Officer McKonley.
Director Jenkins will
not be myrrh while...
Casey gave no names!
- Do you understand?
- He will not, Jack.
"I know her, did you understand?"
- You do not know anything!
- Do you understand?
- Understood...
What are you going to do?
I took it from the black market...
last year.
The expertise will bring them to him.
"We can not just kill her, Jack!"
- Can not we?
No.
Do you know what happens
if he talks, Amber?
Kylie and Taylor will get away with them.
And we both?
We will go on warm for a long time.
- You want to go to jail?
- No.
- Do you want?
- NO!
You must be very strong now.
Can you do it?
You have to do exactly
what I tell you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
What do you think, transferring
you to Van Westerly?
God. Not this place, there's
Jeremy's girlfriend...
This is recommended by the district.
The regional?
Who did you talk to?
I spoke to Director Jenkins.
Dear God, Mom.
What did you tell her?
Please tell me you did not tell me.
Casey, dear, they asked
me a lot of questions...
I did not answer in great detail.
I told her you did not want to discuss...
you know, the details.
- Mom...
"My dear, I had to tell the reason.
- Did anyone see you?
- What do you mean?
Anybody else except
Director Jenkins?
- I'll open.
- No.
I will go.
Amber?
Casey, we need to talk.
- For what?
- I need help.
- Why?
- Because of Jack.
Something happened and
he was just crazy.
Come on, Casey. Open it.
I'm afraid, someone can see me!
- Casey, who is she?
- Hello.
A friend, Amber.
All right.
"Hello, is everything okay?"
- No it is not.
Run, honey!
Do it and your mother dies.
- You're both coming.
- Hadey.
Goodness!
This is crazy!
Shut up!
Amber, keep an eye on
them until I come back.
If they move or try something...
- shoot them.
- All right.
He will.
Dont watch me like that.
- Excuse me, sir?
- What's wrong?
- Get in the car.
- What are you doing.
- I'll give you whatever you want.
Amber, help us, please.
What's wrong?
I thought you were my friend.
You obviously did wrong.
If you do that, you will be
an accomplice to a murder.
Yes, and I will spend the
rest of my life in jail.
- Yes.
- Save your fairy tales.
Why would she ruin her
life for this crap?
Because I'm crazy about it?
As far as I know from Casey, you too.
I see what she meant.
Too mouth!
Now both shut up!
Who are you?
What is it all about?
Look does not look like a robber.
What do you want?
Is it money?
If so, I'll give you money.
I do not need your money.
Turn left.
You do not think he loves you?
I know she loves me.
He's a pimp!
Taking advantage of young girls!
Now take advantage of you too!
May I take advantage of it.
May I use it to get what I want.
Did that old man,
in his awful house?
No. You had to be drugged
to force yourself.
I did it for the money.
And what do the money bring to you?
Freedom.
Are you free?
You do not look like a free man.
You look, a frightened man.
I manage high-end services.
I have an idea.
Would you like to spend the
evening with one of my girls?
No thanks.
Why, there is one particular thing that
I think you will be interested in.
His name is Casey Benson.
I know I know. Are you surprised?
One of the best is.
Honestly, a lot of money brings me.
If you understand what I mean.
Or at least he did.
- You are sick.
- Right?
I know you do not want to hurt us.
We are on your side.
We want to help you.
Please!
Okay, what do you think will follow...
after Jack has finished with us?
- I do not know.
- Let me tell you what happens.
You will be the next.
Think about it.
He's ready to kill Casey because...
may testify against
him as a prostitute.
You will now become a murder witness.
If you betray him, he will
get a death sentence.
He can not afford such a witness.
She is right.
Amber, untie us.
I can not.
On the contrary, you can! You can!
Come on. Give me the weapon.
I promise you, we will
not let him hurt you.
Now we are the only
ones who can help!
Come on!
Come on, untie us.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Returned.
Do not stop.
- Here.
- Go on.
OK! Fine!
- Dad!
- No! She has not done anything...
Shut up.
Shut up and sit.
Take off the jacket.
Take it off.
OK! Relax.
Now sit down.
If he moves, kill him.
What is all this about?
What are you doing?
Why are you causing it to us?
I will not do it.
You will do it.
You see, you're an angry,
divorcing husband...
his impending expulsion
from his own house.
- So you're going to shoot wives.
- What?
And your daughter.
And then you will kill yourself.
America's killer-suicide
typical of America.
It happens every day.
You will never get away with it.
They will understand that you did it.
They will understand that it was you.
Who 's'? The police?
I'm the policeman, Mr Benson.
I know exactly how to
impersonate a crime scene.
Casey, I'm sorry.
I love you. It's all my fault.
- It is my fault...
"You'll shut up!"
I'm sorry.
I hate to look at you
how you pretend.
Do it and get out?
Please, I will give you
whatever you want.
I will sell the house.
I'll give you everything I have.
Please do not do it.
No.
I will not let you kill them.
Mila, do not bullshit.
Run the gun.
No, let yours go.
Did she really think I'd
give you a loaded weapon?
Run, Casey! Run!
Run!
Holly!
It was the first offense for Amber.
The judge agreed that she had
been manipulated by McConnell...
so he received 5
years of probation.
I heard her mother had to sell
the house to pay the lawyers...
eventually moved
to another state.
I do not know what happened
to Amber afterwards.
We never saw each other again.
Taylor's parents sent her
to a dependency setting.
He came back and finished, but...
it was no longer the same.
Kyle's family
actually denied it...
I think you blame me for this.
Are you proud of yourself?
Yes.
With Mom and Dad, we
attended the Amber trial.
In some strange way...
this brought us together
again as a family.
I think he helped Mom and Dad
think twice about divorce.
As for me...
that summer they accepted me in Wittendale,
and I never looked back.