JOE CAMPBELL
(VOICEOVER): Well, we're
Leaving that all behind, both
of us, just for a few days.
I'm just passing through.
He works back there in one of
those pin-striped buildings.
He sells stock now.
His name is Fletcher.
Fletcher Cain.
If he couldn't add it, subtract
it, multiply or divide it,
Fletcher wouldn't know what
the hell to do with it.
Don't get me wrong.
I love the guy.
It was great to see him again.
This was the hunting trip we'd
always promised ourselves,
Before we'd gone off
our separate ways,
College, the Army, time flies.
I hadn't seen him
in years, and it
Was to perfect day, the
sunshine, the birds,
Like, kind of like God
was looking down on us.
And the city didn't even exist.
I had spent a lot of
time back in these woods.
I loved it here.
To me, the trees were like home.
But to Fletcher,
like always, a tree
Was something that grew in
the front yard for a dog
To piss on.
He had a lot to learn.
Fletcher, where did
you get all this stuff?
What's a credit card
and a telephone for?
And a company runner.
You know what I like?
I like it because it means
you're getting into it
And that's good.
Oh, hey.
Oh, flowers for me?
Fletcher, I didn't
know you cared.
Camouflage.
Had to run home at
lunch for this thing.
These things aren't exactly
welcome at Son Sweeney.
Why?
Somebody might use it?
These days.
You know, Fletch,
I brought you one.
Bequeathed, my mother.
She was quite a shot.
Bullshit.
Mother used to be.
Never had the touch
for this stuff.
You know, they
only made about 700
Of these Winchester model 21s.
So what, I can't
get bullets for it?
Shells, Fletch,
not bullets, shells.
Check it out.
Look at that balance.
Want to sell this?
It was my mother's.
What's it worth?
About $30,000.
$30,000?
One could buy a Porsche
with this thing.
Try not to drop it.
JOE CAMPBELL (VOICEOVER): We
grew up together, same town.
Except see, his father
seemed to own most of it.
They lived in a big house,
four car garage, swimming pool.
They even had a
high diving board.
After school, we'd all be there,
all the neighborhood kids,
Making like he was their
best friend, because he
Had a pool with a high dive.
I remember those days.
Fletcher used to stand
on that damn board
Out at the edge,
seemed like hours,
Just waiting,
holding everybody up.
The other kids, stacked up
on that ladder, shivering,
Would start yelling at
him, jump, Meathead.
I used to tell him, Fletch,
once you're up there,
There's no way back.
No way.
Until one day, that day I got
tired of freezing behind him.
I walked out to the edge.
He looked at me.
I pushed him.
And that was the day we
became friends, that day I
Pushed him off, like a brother.
Come on, come on, boy.
[Bark]
What are you doing?
[Gunshot]
This used to be Campbell land.
New boots.
You got a lot to learn.
Suppose I die of pneumonia?
Yeah, well, serves you right.
It's cold.
Lesson number one,
you break in the boots
Before you go hunting.
Great, wet boots all day.
And by tonight, they'll be
dry and fit you like a glove.
Stop crying.
Here.
Sorry about your mom.
It's all right.
She hated hospitals.
It's kind of a
blessing actually.
And now she's up there
with your dad, huh?
That great duck
blind in the sky.
Drinking bourbon,
telling dirty jokes.
Man, she was always pretty
good with the dirty jokes.
I liked her.
How did you turn
out such a wimp?
Breeding, fuck you very much.
[Laughing]
Fletch, see, no, you point.
Don't aim, point.
Point, and squeeze.
Don't aim.
OK.
Ready?
Good.
Safety.
All right.
[Gunshot]
Sort of like that.
Let's just put them over on the
stump over there, all right?
I'll get the feel of it.
Oh, right.
And the quail, of course, are
just going to sit on the stump
While you get the feel of it.
Throw the can.
OK, Butch.
[Gunshot]
(WHISPERING) All right,
now wait til they flush.
Never shoot them on the ground.
You have to be neighborly
about your killing.
Sounds like the office.
Fletch?
Huh?
Why didn't you shoot?
Got something in my eye.
Nicely situated.
Needs a little renovating.
Somebody left in a hurry.
Yeah, a long time ago.
Yeah, the valley's
full of these old dumps.
Wonder why nobody's claimed it?
County forced them out.
Who knows?
Or no water.
Can't brew moonshine
without water.
Don't do that.
What?
Don't ever reach
for a gun like that.
The trigger, Fletcher.
It's not loaded, man.
You don't know that.
OK?
Same thing.
My uncle died that way.
Crossing a fence.
My father tripped.
It wasn't loaded.
Sorry, my god.
Fletcher, a gun is
never empty, all right?
OK.
Come on, Fred.
Come on, babe.
So where do we
sleep tonight, Bwana?
I saw a big oak tree back there.
Make a lovely campsite.
Are you kidding?
No, let's sleep
under the stars.
Roast these birds
under a camp fire.
I'll tell you what, Fletch.
You could play Campfire
Girls if you want,
But I booked us into a motel.
Motel?
Wait a minute.
That is a denial of the
whole hunting experience.
What about communing
with nature?
I'd rather commune
with a hot shower,
Color TV, and clean sheets.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Because it's the last game of
the World Series, that's why.
Oh.
Let's get back to the car.
Wait a minute.
What do you want
to do with these?
Put them in your
pouch back here.
All right.
I'm heading south.
So we need to go north.
That's north.
Hm.
Now, Fletch.
Let's think about this.
Now that's north.
How can that be north when
the sun is setting over there?
I don't know, but
the needle says.
Forget it, Fletcher, forget it.
We followed this path here,
we'll just take it back.
The needle's just
freaking out here.
Where did Fred go?
Over there.
Fred.
Freddie.
Come here.
Where's he going?
Freddy.
He's never done that before.
Fred.
[Barking]
Freddy.
Here, Fred.
Fred.
Here boy.
Freddy.
Come on boy.
Joe, Joseph.
I just saw a deer.
You're dreaming.
No, I swear to God.
It stared right at me.
It was beautiful.
Fletcher, there are
no deer in these woods.
There used to be, but
see, now there's no river.
No, no.
Fletcher there's no river,
because they built that dam.
And they built
that dam on a bond
Issue which you and your little
friends raised to make a buck.
So you didn't see a deer.
OK?
Hey, I trade paper,
for Christ sake.
I don't kill little
furry forest animals.
Not intentionally.
What the fuck's
happened to you?
What's happened to me?
What's happened to you?
Nothing's happened to me.
Exactly, Fletcher.
Nothing has happened to you.
Fuck!
Fletcher, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Jesus, Joe.
Now, come on.
Let's go and see what you can
do with that Porsche of yours.
Come on.
Freddy.
Come on, boy.
God damn dog.
Wait a minute.
Now it says that way's north.
This doesn't make any sense.
Christ, will you
stop trying to prove
How smart you are, Fletcher,
and put that fucking thing away?
I know where the trail is.
Yeah?
Where is it?
Listen, asshole, the
trail, the trail picks
Up again right near here, OK?
Let's split up.
You head down that way.
I'll go this way.
Wait a minute.
Are you crazy?
I'll never find you.
You find the path, you
fire a shot in the air,
And we find each other
on the sound, you got it?
That's a great plan.
Well hey, well, I'm sorry.
You want to stay out there
and commune with nature,
You be my guest, OK?
Fuck you.
Try not to stumble
through these trees
While these fucking rocks
break my fucking neck.
Hey, hey, hey.
You heard the lady.
She said, let her go.
OK?
It ain't your affair, boy.
Ain't you got no sense,
or you just plain deaf?
Look here, Billy.
We got us an revenuer.
Nah, too purty.
Look, I'm just looking
for a path out of here.
I don't know what you
do, and I don't care.
See that?
That's a path.
Now get out of here.
Let's get out of here.
Fletcher, Fletcher, come on.
Hey, Fletcher.
Hey, leave her alone.
Please, excuse me.
Christ, Fletcher.
Excuse me.
Fletcher.
She's obviously not
interested in you.
You can't just force
yourself on her?
You want her?
Fletcher.
No, no, I just...
No, you want her.
Fletcher.
No, I just think that...
Come on, get up.
Let's go.
Come on, fellas.
[Gunshot]
Fletch.
This is very attractive.
We come out here to
relax, kill a few birds,
Now we're being chased
through the wood
By the cast of Deliverance.
What?
Huh?
Shh/
[Gunshot]
Fletch.
Fletcher.
Jump.
What?
Jump off, Fletcher.
Fletcher, just
jump the fuck off.
[Gunshot]
I need to get to a phone.
Call the police.
Hold him there, Pop.
That the one, Pop?
It must be.
It was an accident.
We just wanted directions.
What do you mean, we?
Joe.
Who's Joe?
My friend.
Joe Campbell.
They chased after him.
Please, can you help me?
Campbell?
Who'd you kill?
I didn't kill anybody.
Eye for an eye, Pa.
They ain't never gonna...
Oh, hush up.
They were trying to kill us.
What are we going
to do with him Pa?
Better help me get him inside.
Can't bring in strangers.
[Scream]
We ain't animals.
We's people.
Now, help me get him in.
I never turned away
someone in need.
What are you doing?
Keep still.
Lord, that's need a poultice.
Shh.
You made them... Thank you.
I didn't do it for you.
Can you get a message... Oh!
Shh.
Keep still.
Papa wants to talk to you.
You brung trouble
on this house, Les.
No more than we already have.
Don't sass me.
What were you doing
out there, girl?
Don't matter.
I go where I please.
Not in this valley, you don't.
Well, he can't stay here.
He can't walk, Daddy.
He's on his way.
He's here now.
Girl, he can't stay.
He's on his way.
I'll mend him quick.
Promise.
Killing's going to start.
Not before the stew
gets cold, it ain't.
You wash your hands over there?
Yes.
Who's that for?
I dinna say, get up.
Bless this food dear Lord.
May it nourish our bodies as
they word nourishes our souls.
Amen.
I need to get to a phone.
My friend is out there.
Just keep still.
Hush.
Eat.
No.
What is that taste?
Possum.
Eat.
Come on.
Possum.
Great.
Please.
Shh.
Listen to me for a short moment.
I need to get to a phone.
Joe.
Joe!
Hey.
What's your name?
Fletcher Cain.
Oh, I ain't going to kill you.
You hear my dogs?
Sometimes I just
can't control them.
Call them off, Docker.
I don't think that
I can, Hallie, girl.
[Gunshot]
He ain't worth it.
I'll be coming for you, darlin'.
You know I will.
He's been buried proper.
What kind of people are you?
There's been trouble.
My daddy's worried.
What trouble can I cause?
Just came here to
hunt some quail.
All I want to do is get out of
here and back to civilization.
Not trouble from you.
From whom then?
My name's Hallie Campbell.
How do you do?
Them fellas you're
running from...
That killed Joe
and strung him up.
Them is McDonalds.
So?
Oh, I see.
This is some kind of
thing going on here?
Some sort of hillbilly thing?
Don't call us hillbillies.
They sold you a lame horse
and you blew up their still.
It's like out of
some stupid novel.
Jesus Christ.
Mind your mouth.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Ow.
It's all swolled up.
Jesus.
When did this happen?
Now shut up.
Look, miss, I think...
[Scream]
Mornin'.
How do, Mr. Campbell.
Horace, how come when my throat
gets dry, you know to turn up?
Why, it's a gift.
That pop skull stuff.
You give that to the McDonalds.
Their brains is already rotted.
Would I offer a valued
customer the same swill
As them heathens?
This is bonded.
Daddy.
You got some of them [inaudible]
Miss Hallie.
Mr. Carlin.
Wouldn't somebody be
ailing now, would they?
Sure hope it's not that
fine brother of yours.
Back in the house, girl.
Mind your chores.
Don't you be buying none of
that rot guy from him, Daddy.
I'll
Take uh, three jars.
And an extra for
somebody who's lame?
[Groaning]
Pain down?
How long have I been out?
Two days.
What?
Water?
Fixing my knee?
Can't walk on it
for a few days.
I made you this.
Thank you.
No need.
Hallie.
What?
Do you ever see
things in the woods?
Got eyes.
I mean things
that aren't there.
Ah.
It's only a bad dream.
When you wake, you'll be
all mended and on your way
Back home.
Tell me more about
where you live.
Wouldn't like it.
Besides, you promised
to read to me.
Help me with big words?
Therefore shall ye
keep all the... all the...
Commandments.
Commandments which I
command you this day, that ye
May be strong and go in and...
Possess.
I know it's odd.
But the first two Ss are like
a Z, and second two aren't.
Possess.
Possess the land,
which the Lord swear
Unto your fathers
to give unto them
And to their seed a land that...
Floweth.
Floweth with milk and honey.
For if you love the Lord your
God, and walk in all his ways,
Then, my Lord, drive out all
these nations before you.
And you shall possess
greater nations,
And mightier than yourselves.
So, you call me up and say
you want to buy some stock.
$0.03 cents worth.
No, you don't need
money to make money.
You put up your $0.03.
I give you three
shares at $0.10 each.
That's $0.30 altogether.
Now you owe me $0.27.
So now I owe you money
and all I got is this?
You wait... excuse me.
You wait for the price
of the stock to go up.
When it hits $0.20, you sell
them all, $0.60 altogether.
You pay me my $0.27,
you have a $0.33 profit.
So what if no one
wants to buy these?
Well, they will eventually.
Fletcher, these ain't no
good to me on the eventually.
I can't eat these.
In this valley, we
trade what we can use.
OK.
All right.
Wait a minute.
Oops.
Say it's potatoes.
So you sell me potatoes
and I can't pay the price.
Right.
It's called margin.
So I eat the potatoes.
Well...
And what are you going to eat?
Possum pizza.
Look, don't worry about
what I'm going to eat.
It ain't a fair trade.
Isn't.
In this valley,
you give me this,
And I trade you this right back.
That's fair.
It may be fair, but
it's not smart business.
It may be smart,
but it isn't nice.
If... I'll peel... If you
want, I'll peel the potatoes.
Hi.
Could I uh, need some help?
I've never done it
before, but uh...
I'd like to be of some help.
Whatcha doing?
Thinking.
I am good for something,
thank you very much.
Thinking about leaving?
No.
The Romans.
You know, they didn't have
anything you don't have.
Two thousand years ago,
they had central heating,
Indoor plumbing, highways.
Where did you learn all that?
Public television.
You like that?
It's yours.
No, it's yours.
Take it.
It's yours.
What did you do that for?
Huh?
What did you go and do that for?
Them McDonalds, they know
that we got him in here.
Cold day in Hades when I do
anything on the McDonald's
Say so.
You're part of this.
The code is broke.
They'll never rest on it.
An eye for an eye.
Why don't we finish it then?
Let me go...
Oh, now sit.
He's not our kind.
Your life is here.
Don't you ever forget it.
You see?
No.
Me and the Romans, baby.
No, that's good.
Thank you, Zebediah.
What it is.
[Japanese]
Hold it.
Reach for it,
neighbor, I'll carve
You a brand new pretty face.
Jesus, you're a regular
Norman Bates, aren't you?
You want my woman?
That what you're
after, city boy?
That'll do, Duncan McDonald.
Oh.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Zebediah Campbell.
Out back.
'Bout mended up.
He's got to go back, honey.
Now, I know that
as sure as I know
I got to kill Duncan McDonald.
And you do too.
Don't we never get
but one chance in life?
Meant like this.
Forever?
I never knew about these
feelings, Zebediah.
I never had a man.
I never had a chance.
No.
Sometimes in this valley,
you'd be better off if you
Didn't have no softness in you.
I don't even know how
this started, Zebediah.
Moon's almost full.
It's comin'.
These are Campbell
chickens, right?
Come here.
I got you.
Hey, you got her!
Good boy.
Bring her over here.
Put her on the block here.
Put the hen right on
the block right there.
Stay.
Stay down.
Now hold her steady
when I swing.
You gotta hold her tight, boy.
Sorry.
Oh.
God!
Hold her over the bucket.
Let the blood drop out.
Oh, don't be squeamish, boy.
You gotta kill it if
you're gonna eat it.
I just buy some thighs
at the supermarket.
It's the law of nature.
You kill the next one.
You need more?
Got a lot of mouths to feed.
Whole family's coming, aunts,
uncles, cousins, nephews.
What for?
First footin'.
What's that?
Well, I'll let Hallie
explain it to you.
It's a hell of a celebration.
Excuse the language.
Well, want to wring
it first or chop it?
You go ahead.
I'm getting pretty
good at holding.
A man gotta learn to kill.
No.
What are you made of, boy?
I'll just chop it if that's OK.
Fine.
Take a swig.
Take a big one.
[Cough]
Come on now.
Swing it like a man.
There you go.
There you go!
I did it.
Your first kill.
Which one's next?
I think that brown one.
Brown one.
US poultry, down
two and an eighth.
I got some chickens
for you to pluck.
I did that.
So what's all this
about first footing?
Everybody brings a lump
of coal, a crust of bread,
And a jug of whiskey.
That's an interesting menu.
What it means, is
for the year to come,
The larder and the coal
bin will never be empty.
The whiskey is to
drink to good fortune.
Excuse me.
That's a capital idea.
[Crack]
You... Wo!
I lost my first footing.
Help him back to bed, Zeb.
My good man, you are too kind.
I'm gettin' the
chores done, Daddy.
I know what's in
your head, child.
Not to be taken with that man.
He's just... he's
different, Daddy.
Different from who?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm your pa, Hallie.
[Gunshot]
That the best you can do?
Kill my chicken?
Come on, you want to kill?
Kill me.
Don't stand behind no tree.
Kill me like a man.
[Gunshot]
Don't waste no powder
on cowards, Zeb.
I'll see you in hell, McDonald.
Hi.
Who's that?
My great aunt.
Died young.
She never married.
Never had no chance for a man.
What'd she die of?
The feud.
Bullet in her back.
They all died in the same year.
Bad fight.
Jesus Christ.
Sorry.
Fighting never stops when
the harvest moon is full.
Has to stop sometime.
It can't.
Why?
Always someone left
to carry on the hate.
That's the way it is.
Hallie.
There's so much
I wanted to see.
Big out there like
you said, isn't it?
It's pretty big.
People are kinda
small sometimes.
It's still there.
It's not going anywhere.
Maybe I'll show you someday.
Tell me about where you live.
Do people carry guns
out where you come from?
Afraid they do.
Why?
Rob usually, or keep
from being robbed.
Do you want to go back there?
There must be something
good out there.
Oh, sure, there is, there is.
Movies.
Good restaurants.
Chocolate ice cream.
I had that once.
Designer ice cream?
What's that taste like?
Money.
Got a girl?
I um, no.
Guess you'll have
to come for a visit.
See for yourself.
Don't say that.
Hallie, there's no harm in...
Hallie, Hallie girl.
Hallie.
It's my cousin, cousin Ginny.
Come on.
[Background chatter]
I've left my spaceship
parked at the side.
[Groans] That's the first
time I've used one of those.
Um, just a sec.
I gotta go.
Just go have fun.
Going to dance later, Zeb?
Sir, would you do me the
honor of dancing with me?
You are very beautiful.
Come with me, Hallie.
Where?
Back to the city.
Ah, Fletcher.
Wherever you want.
I'll build a house
in the country.
With raining water?
Just like the Romans.
And a garden.
Not just a garden of
carrots and potatoes
And cabbages, a garden
full of flowers.
Whatever you want.
Sounds so perfect,
the way you tell it.
It will be.
Fletcher, it just
ain't going to happen.
At least Hallie, come with me.
I can't.
- Why not?
- Fletcher.
Why not?
Fletcher, no.
I'm not like you.
What is that?
I don't understand.
What does that mean.
Wait.
Hallie.
Get away from my sister.
Christ.
Zeb.
Zeb, she's coming with me.
She's staying here
and you're going.
Zeb, listen to me.
She can't.
Tell him, Hallie.
Hallie.
I told you.
What?
Fletcher.
Come on.
Hallie?
Don't say goodbye.
Will you just shut
up for a second?
I'll take him from here.
Like hell you will.
No, Zeb.
[Gunshot]
That's done it, Mr. Campbell.
Hellfire and brimstone
coming down on your house.
I have to go.
I really wish I could stay.
I just have... I have to go.
Uh, bye.
I'll be seeing you.
Um Take care, bye.
It wasn't my fault.
I know.
There are other ways
to settle all this.
No there ain't.
It's meant.
How can say that?
Nothing's meant.
You are a dead man if you
don't get down that holler.
All right, all
right, I'm going.
And don't you never
come back here, Mister.
This ain't your place.
Fucking Neanderthals.
You cross that crick,
you're out of our valley.
Which way to the road?
And don't never come back.
Well, goodbye.
No offense.
None taken.
Hey, wait a minute.
I don't need it.
Tell Hallie.
I know.
Git.
Well, go on.
Get inside.
[Gunshot]
[Gunshots]
All right!
Hallie.
Keep your head down!
[Multiple gunshots]
Daddy!
I've had enough of this shit.
I'm going outside.
Watch me on the right.
I'll be back.
[Gunfire stops]
Hallie.
Go.
Now.
Listen to me.
I told you, I can't.
Now.
Oh, honey, they're gone.
I can't.
Please come.
Now.
No.
[Gunshot]
Ah!
It's OK.
[Gunshot]
Fletcher.
This weren't your affair.
You were never part of this.
She stays here with me forever.
[Screaming]
Hallie?
Ha... Hallie?
Oh, my god.
It's finished.
You finished it, Fletcher Cain.
The last man to hate is gone.
He can rest now, it's over.
Morning, Mr. Cain.
Pleasant day, it seems.
Well, uh...
Courtin', I see.
JOE CAMPBELL
(VOICEOVER): As for me,
I always like that high dive.
I was part of something
bigger than myself.
I think Fletch understands
something about that now.
Once you've climbed
up there, there's
Really only one way to go.
And there's no way back.