Mr. Brown ought to be here any minute.
But why don't I walk you through
the aerial survey and site plan
until he arrives.
What do you think they're getting
per square foot over there?
Sorry?
What kind of money are they getting
for that space
in the business park?
I'm sure I don't...
I don't really know, Mr. Mayor.
- Guesstimate.
- I don't have a clue.
I bet a bundle.
I bet a bundle, Nate.
It's Saturday, for heaven's sake.
Can we please look at this thing
and get going?
Trish talked with him ten minutes ago.
He ought to be here, you know,
in a minute or so, but I can get started.
Let's get the show on the road.
This is the six block area.
We vacate the alleyways and create
a superblock site. You follow?
Superblock, yes, yes.
Let me orient you.
Neighborhood-serving retail here,
upmarket women's shoes and apparel,
fine dining, fountains, textured
hardscape, just like stone,
even an indoor children's playland.
It's a pedestrian-friendly,
relatable space.
And then... on that superblock site
I give you...
Cortona.
Cor-tona.
It really, I think, expresses
simplicity, beauty, and elegance.
If I do say so myself.
Actually, I think it creates
a sort of Aristotelean unity...
And the piece de resistance,
one hundred and seventy condominium units
for the discriminating consumer.
- It totally redefines the urban fabric.
- I like.
I think it's fantastic.
Pardon me, but I don't see
the low income units.
There are no low-income units at Cortona.
We'll build whatever the city requires...
... off-site.
Off-site?
Sure. We pay the in-lieu fees
and build them...
In East Orange.
Not exactly. My partners and I
have found the perfect parcel
out on Maple Avenue.
We can build our low-income units
out there.
You know what they say. Out of sight...
... out of mind.
That's all well and good, gentlemen,
but what about the current owners?
Hi, Jennifer.
Lizzie from the Paisley Set.
Yeah. Gimmie the L'Oreal lightener.
The one-pound tub.
Make three of 'em
and ten boxes of foils.
Oh. And a gallon of Barbicide.
Right.
Right. Cheers, darling.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- Hi.
- Hello, Samantha.
- Just coffee. In a to go cup.
- Large?
- Perfect.
- Got it.
- Is Leonard here?
- He's in the back.
I'm just going to hit the loo.
- Well, now! Good morning!
- Had to see you before work.
Anybody see you come in?
- Len. I can't wait until Monday.
- Monday?
Yes, yes, the city, remember?
Ozzello's on Mulberry Street.
- I don't know...
- What don't you know?
Well, you see, Monday night
is Deeanne's book club night.
I'm in charge of the kids Monday.
I'd have to get a sitter.
And Deeanne would be suspicious if
I got a sitter.
Well, why don't you think about it.
I've got to get to work.
- I want to...
- I know, I know.
- One more.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sam, dear, the loo.
You're out of paper towels.
Okie dokie.
Alright, you.
I'm turning on the lights.
Bollocks.
Up to your old tricks, dad?
God Mehar! You scared me to death.
What are you doing here?
I work here, Lizzie.
You could have killed me, you know.
I was putting a penny in the box.
And you. Flicking the switches.
I could have gone up... poof.
I've got to call an electrician.
That's more like it.
I heard you up here.
Talking to the ghost again?
Why do you believe in ghosts?
Unless I am mistaken, Christians
aren't supposed to believe in spirits.
That's alright, dearie. I'm Scottish.
Yes. We believe in ghosts and brownies
and selkies and howlers and griffins.
Why are you in so early?
- The wedding party!
- Oh, crikey, I forgot.
Oh my god. The florist isn't there yet.
Mom. Did you hear that?
The florist isn't there.
Jacks, a red velcro.
Cheers.
- This is a disaster.
- She'll be there.
The point is she's not there, mother.
Hold your head straight, dear.
- Why don't you call Daddy.
- What can Daddy do?!?
He can't even hire
a responsible florist!
- Hand me your phone.
- You didn't bring your phone?
I'm getting married today
and you didn't bring your phone?
They won't let me have a cell phone.
- Cell phones are overrated, dude.
- Thank you.
But I need one.
They are the bane of humanity.
- What's a bane?
- I need it for school.
Hey, you do not need a cell phone
distracting you in the classroom.
Don't stunt her growth, Mother.
I might as well just forget the wedding.
- Now what?
- Daddy's pants don't fit.
Oh, for heaven's sake,
they can let them out.
In one hour!?!? He's got to be
at the church hall in an hour
to pay the florist.
Who, by the way, is not there.
You need to relax, dear.
Today is your day to shine.
I cannot shine when everyone's
screwing up.
Listen.
You've got a good man and
a diamond ring on your finger, you know?
The wedding is pure gravy.
We should all be so lucky.
Everyone's in an up-do? Am I right?
- Except mine's the biggest.
- Oh, for God's sake.
Of course, dearie.
You're queen for a day, and
your beautiful hair will be your crown.
Come on.
Good morning, ladies.
I have a certified letter
for miss Lizzie.
And I need a signature.
Lizzie! You have to sign for something!
Good morning, beautiful.
How are you today?
Good morning, Craig.
A certified letter for you today.
You're still beautiful.
- You have a great day.
- You too, Craig.
Thank you.
Bloody hell!
- Mehar, can you cover?
- Yeah, of course.
Back in a sec.
- Mister Mayor.
- Lizzie Munro. Right?
I try to keep everybody's name
right at the tip of my fingertips.
- What in the hell is this?
- Hey, take it easy. Have a seat.
Would you like some coffee?
Maybe... What have we got?
- What about this...
- An explanation. That's what I want.
Well this is a notice from the Planning
Department that tells everybody
what's gonna happen around here.
- Eviction? From my own property?
- Eminent domain.
My domain.
Look. It's all legal.
C'mon, Lizzie.
It's how you give an old town
a nip and a tuck. Gets rid of the blight.
- Blight?
- Improves the tax base.
You do wanna improve the tax base,
don't you?
What are you talking about?
My father left that building to me
and I've worked my fingers to the bone
to pay it off.
Hey, is that Lizzie?
Where is she going now?
Leonard.
- Lizzie. What a surprise...
- Have you seen this?
I got a letter. Sure.
I just had a very interesting chat
with Tiny Provenzano.
Eminent domain they're calling it.
They're going to force us to take
a piddling sum for our buildings
whether we like it or not.
Then they'll scrape the whole business,
and put up some fantasyland
with Coldstone Creamery and Baby Gap.
Right here! In Old Town!
You're right.
That's what I understand.
- I just paid off that building, Leonard.
- Yeah. That's hard.
But, look on the bright side.
It could mean cash in our pockets.
I can swing a divorce
and can make alimony.
And you and I could...
Ok. Look.
We'll talk about it,
when we're able to. Ok?
Yeah. I know.
I'm sorry for barging in like this.
Anyway, I've got to get back
to my ladies.
I'll just... call you Monday.
Or something.
Yes. We'll talk Monday. Can I
get you something in the meantime?
We have a new burger on the menu...
Are you hungry? C.J.'s at a rally,
and I'm a loose ends.
I dunno.
- I'm knackered.
- Come on. My treat.
Don't make me eat alone.
It's awful good of you to sacrifice
your Saturday night for the old boss.
You know, you might just be in line
for a raise.
I'll make a note of that.
- Since when do you smoke?
- Since today, dear.
What's up, cuties?
Wanna keep us company tonight?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- In their dreams.
The whole thing sucks.
I'd hate to see the old block
turn into a pile of bricks.
Me, too.
It's just greed.
Hear, hear. And it's not just my
business
or you girls trying to put
food on the table.
- It's bigger than that.
- Yeah.
What about our ladies? Don't forget them
and their frosts and tips.
Oh, God. How can I?
You know, my father left my mum
and my brother and me in Stirling
when I was eight.
Broken hearted.
So, I did my beauty school stint
in Glasgow,
and as soon as I knew one end
of my shears from the other,
I tracked the bastard down.
All the way to Manningtree, New Jersey.
- Of all places.
- Yes.
But by the time I got here,
he'd already been dead a year.
And all he left was the building
and a failing little haberdashery.
And a monstrous mortgage.
You know,
in a weird way I'm thankful.
For him and his folly.
I met some nice people here.
I've learned to drive
in three foot of snow.
And eat hotdogs with yellow mustard.
There you go.
- What about a nightcap?
- Right you are.
Nice break.
I love Manningtree.
I love my customers.
I love cutting and flatironing
and perming the lot of 'em.
I really do.
It'll be sad to leave it.
So sad, Jacks.
Come on, you're not leaving.
Your friends are here.
What about bowling nights?
- What about Len?
- What about him?
You'll be together some day.
Men. Bah.
If I had any sense
I'd become a lesbian.
But then I think about the fights!
Females are fierce.
- See me. You can?
- I can.
Put two of 'em together.
Crikey, what a mess!
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes.
A word, Mr. Berry.
My name is Lizzie Munro.
I own the building at 150 Main Street.
And I need to talk with you
about a letter I received.
It's my lunch hour, Miss Munro.
It's my building and your town
is going to seize it.
We'll negotiate a fair price, Miss Munro.
You have nothing to worry about.
What if I refuse to negotiate?
With all due respect, Miss Munro,
you can't refuse.
Supreme Court. 2005.
Kelo v. New London Connecticut.
We have the authority to condemn
and clear private property
if we can't come to a reasonable
accommodation with you.
Are you saying, you can take my propriety
without my consent?
That can not be right.
In America, Miss Munro,
progress is always right.
Cortona is progress. Ipso facto.
Cortona is right.
That's all we have on Cortona.
Let's see. At a dollar a copy,
that'll be a hundred and ten dollars.
- A hundred and ten dollars?
- We take checks.
Holy cow!
- A hundred and ten.
- Thank you.
I'll be back in a minute
with your receipt.
Jesus.
Did you hear the expression
of fly in the ointment?
Yeah.
Just had a visit from a certain
Lizzie Munro.
That's what she's gonna be.
I think you'd better call our friend.
Ok. He'll deal with it.
Don't worry about it.
Warren. Tiny. How's it hanging?
Yeah. Well, we have a little problem.
A broad.
So.
What about us?
- What do you mean?
- Leonard.
What can I say to you that I
haven't already said, Lizzie?
Deeanne doesn't understand me.
We haven't had a physical relationship
in, well, in a long time.
We're separated.
What do you want from me?
Does Deeanne know you're separated?
You still live with the woman. For all
I know, you still sleep in the same bed.
Now, Lizzie.
Here's the thing about affairs,
Leonard.
You cannae help me.
If I'm in trouble, you cannae help me.
Or comfort me. Or fight for me.
At least not in public.
And I'm in trouble.
Big, bollocky trouble.
I will fight for you, Lizzie.
I promise.
Everything is gonna be alright.
No, Leonard, not tonight.
Good night.
And these lights come on
when they want to.
And every time we turn on more
than one dryer, zap.
Everything goes down.
It's no wonder.
With the electrical service
of this building
you'd be lucky to light up
a family of gnats.
Where did you say the fuse box was?
In the basement.
Down the hall to the right.
I'll show you.
- Hi. Can I help you?
- Oh. Well. I need a haircut.
- Shampoo and haircut?
- What do you think?
I think you look great,
but if you insist... follow me.
- Have a seat. Can I take your coat?
- Thank you.
- Right here?
- Yes.
So... Lizzie can help you.
Can you?
Of course.
I'll prep the patient for you.
Miss Munro, you need a subpanel.
Gotta get those circuits outta
the basement. Fire code.
Alright. Yes. You'll get me a bid asap?
- Tomorrow.
- Brilliant.
Have a good one.
- Hi. I'm Lizzie.
- I'm Warren.
- So... what do we want today?
- Haircut?
- Shampoo?
- Great.
Brilliant. Right this way.
Right here.
- Comfortable?
- This is great.
- Sorry, ma'am, we're closed!
- Bernie, let me in.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon. I want to show you
something. You're just in time!
Those bags I bought in Vicksburg
just arrived.
Beaded. Beautiful. Bendel's. Circa
1920. I'll let it go for ninety bucks.
- What would I do with a beaded bag?
- You never know.
Listen, Bernie. Do you know about this?
- What is it?
- A letter from the Township.
There's probably one just like it
in that pile of unopened mail.
I just got home last night,
for God's sake!
I've barely had enough time
to brush my teeth.
Open it.
I-95 was a freak show. Pileup.
Spotsylvania.
Ten cars and a tractor trailer.
I mean, what part of "slow down"
do people not understand?
- Oh my God.
- Read on.
- No way.
- Yes.
We're all going to be swept up
into a giant dustpan
and dumped God knows where.
- All of us?
- The whole neighborhood.
What can we do?
I haven't thought that far.
I wanted to talk to you first.
- There's not that many old timers left.
- Old timer. How kind.
- We could hire an attorney, I suppose.
- Attorney? Is it that serious?
If we don't sell, they'll take!
Liz, I just refinanced this place.
I can barely afford the mortgage,
much less pay a fortune to some lawyer.
Like, hello? What's your hourly?
Three hundred. Perfect!
Can you help us? Maybe yes, maybe no.
We lose. Broke again.
Bank takes the building. Precious
antiques out on the street.
Roll end credits. I mean, thank God
for Robert's Air Force pension.
What are you doing?
You can't sit there.
- Please, Bernie. Try to focus.
- I'm sorry.
It's just that it's mid-century.
Mint condition.
I have a buyer in mind.
Gorgeous man. About fifty.
- Tall. Graying. But... married.
- You're not exactly single.
True... but a man can dream,
can't he?
- Bernie. Tell me one thing.
- Anything.
- Will you sell out to these bastards?
- What do I look like? A wuss?
- Hello.
- Hey.
You're forty minutes late. I was
about to go give up and go to sleep.
I'm sorry. Something came up.
I'm sorry about the other night, Len.
I'm just...
I know.
- You know?
- Yes, darling. I know.
Sometimes you get impatient with me
and my circumstances.
But at the same time,
we gotta keep our eye on the ball.
We're a perfect match, Lizzie.
Physically, intellectually...
...spiritually.
You know it and I know it.
It's all about timing.
We've got to be patient.
We gonna be together.
Soon.
Len. I'm worried about Old Town.
Well, you know, we'll deal with that
when the time is right.
We've got to figure out
how to derail this thing straight away.
We need to make sure
everybody in Old Town knows about it
and is ready to fight.
You're with me on this, right, Len?
- The dog's getting a chill.
- Leonard.
Hey, come in for breakfast
and I'll make you a Denver omelette.
- Good night.
- Night.
I'm liking this color quite a bit.
It's good. Sempre giovane.
Makes me look young.
But you are young, Mrs. Provenzano.
You look a lot younger than your nephew.
The poor thing. It's the weight.
It wouldn't kill Tiny to miss a meal
every once in a while.
- I've got a bone to pick with that man.
- A bone.
Word on the street is
that the town council is hooked up
with some big-time developer.
Now they're telling us we all
have to sell up or be condemned.
- All of us. Macintosh's, Bernie's...
- Len's Coffee Shop...
Len's...
Damiano's Drugs.
Dear old man Sivney
and his hardware store.
Tiny's leading the charge.
From Bedford Falls to Downtown
Disney in one swell foop.
And they'll give you pennies
on the dollar. Right, Lizzie?
- I think that's how it works.
- Honey, that doesn't seem right.
Well, you might ask Tiny about it.
I tried to talk to him,
but he's dead keen on this project.
He gave me the brush off.
No, that can't be right.
Let me tell you.
I happen to know that Tiny's had his eye
on some of these old buildings
for a long time. He loves 'em.
He wants to fix'em up.
Between you and me,
Tiny's been biding his sweet time,
waiting for the older guys
to retire and sell up.
Is that so?
What do you got there about
"Sufficiency of Evidence"?
It says here... "a court confronted
with a plausible accusation
of impermissible favoritism
to private parties should conduct..."
Got that?
..."a careful and extensive inquiry
into whether, in fact,
the development plan chronology is
of primary benefit to the developer...
...and private businesses which
may eventually locate in the plan area,
and in that regard, only of incidental
benefit to the city ..."
- Exhausting!
- Crikey.
Incidental benefit? What does it mean?
We're screwed?
Let me look at that.
Hey, you know who built our library?
- No. Roosevelt?
- Andrew Carnegie.
- As in Judy?
- Judy Carnegie?
Judy at Carnegie. Hall, that is.
- Yeah, exactly.
- How fabulous.
He was the richest man in the world
back in the eighteen-hundreds.
Born in Scotland.
A stone's throw from my own hometown.
He came to America as a boy.
What in God's name was he doing
in Manningtree?
Oh, I don't think he ever set foot
in Manningtree.
Pittsburgh is where he ended up.
He made a fortune in steel and coal.
Billions. And when he got old,
he gave it all back.
- To who?
- To us, dear. To the people.
So Mr. Carnegie built
the Manningtree Library.
Manningtree and a few thousand others
in the States and all over the world.
He was a true Scotsman, Bernie. He had
faith in the power of everyday people.
That sounds like my Aunt Minnie.
She was a communist.
Before she died, she wrote
"Marxism for Dummies".
Died in her penthouse
on the upper east side.
I wish I could have a cigarette.
Ash?
- You're on your own.
- Suit yourself.
Tim and me. We've given it up. Big
tobacco's not gonna run our lives.
- A principled decision, eh?
- Tim's a political science major.
Of course.
- He's got a job at Town Hall.
- Does he?
Maintenance man.
Well, good.
So, is it serious between you two?
You mean birth control serious
or wedding serious?
- Well, I suppose I mean marriage.
- No. We're good. We're tight.
- We're just not in the box yet.
- I see.
I mean, it's not like
it's a hook-up or anything.
- Hook-ups suck. Especially for chicks.
- How d'you mean?
You know, right? There's like
what you want, okay?
"Love me, love me,
you're hot, pay attention to me."
You'll do anything to get nothing.
That's a hook-up.
Then there's, "Hey, I'm important,
I'm gonna pay attention to me,
and by the way dude, who said
you could drink my last beer?"
That's when you're ready for true love.
Nice!
We aim to please.
Holy toledo. Gettin' that fuse box
out of the basement was a slog.
Hey, C.J.'s here. Do you mind if I go?
I don't have any clients
until tomorrow at two.
No. Go ahead.
- A bientot!
- So long, Jacks.
- Hello, Leonard. How are things?
- Lizzie. Lizzie Munro. How's by you?
- Hope I'm not interrupting anything.
- No, no. Just talking.
Restaurant business talk.
Trying to... boost the bottom line.
Recession proofed the...
thing.
That's what it's all about
in a low-margin business.
Indeed. Well, I wondered if you
were free to... Macintosh's happy hour.
Thought you might want to join me
and a few friends... a quick drink.
Chat about... local commerce.
Why, sure. Tell you what.
I'll meet you there in... five?
- Five's good. Take ten if you need it.
- Ten it is!
- Save me a cocktail banger!
- Will do.
- You Scots are a morose bunch.
- Not ordinarily.
- Then what? Sentimental?
- Ordinarily? Defiant.
- Tonight? Disappointed.
- In me?
In me.
Please, Lizzie. This thing is bigger
than the both of us.
We... we got caught in the undertow.
Please, Leonard. Stop before you say
something you truly mean.
Look at me, Leonard. Look at where I am.
The Paisley Set?
Yes, Leonard. I parked in front
of my building.
And I cannot seem to get you interested
in helping me save this building.
Or Old Town. Or your own backside.
Len, I need you.
We can talk about all this
at the culinary trade show.
No, Leonard.
There will be no trade show.
But... I made reservations.
Orlando. The Radisson.
Pina Coladas by the pool.
It'll be like it used to be.
What's happened to you?
As you can see in this slide,
our timeline is aggressive...
but achievable.
Eighteen months from city
entitlements to vesting.
Cortona. Physically possible,
financially feasible,
maximally productive...
legally allowable.
The highest and best use.
Warren, can you talk to us about
our exposure?
Minimal.
Once our concrete is in the ground,
in other words, once we're vested,
we can't be touched.
What about the opposition?
It's simple. We can hit them
with a SLAPP suit.
Strategic Lawsuit Against
Public Participation.
It's best way to deal
with any insurgency.
Philip. These are mom and pop
operations.
They can't afford to lawyer up
in any meaningful fashion.
Besides, what we don't already own,
our friends do.
Holy shit! This place is a maze!
Ladies and gentlemen, allow me
to introduce Mayor Anthony Provenzano.
You must be the money guys.
How are you?
This ends the study session to consider
the pending development agreement
with North Sea Assets, S.A.
The next regular meeting is set
for July 25th.
I will circulate the agenda, Mister Mayor.
Right. We done.
Are we done?
- Are we adjourned, Mister Mayor?
- Yeah, sure.
Then gavel us out of here, please.
I have things to do.
I second that motion.
My sitter bails in 15 minutes.
I've got to go.
Adjourned.
So... is this your new hobby?
Well, Tiny, I've lived here for 20 years
and have never once dropped in
to see what all the excitement was about.
Town Council is really inspiring.
- Inspiring?
- Yes, indeed.
The back and forth.
The parliamentary procedure.
Fascinating. I've really missed out.
You know, I think it's so important
to have an understanding
of how things work
in these United States.
Things? What things?
The People's business.
Democracy in action. I'm enthralled.
As a matter of fact, I might bring
my chums the next time.
- What's that woman up to?
- No good, Nate. No damn good.
Tiny, my man.
I'm on my way to a meeting.
How may I be of service?
Lizzie Munro? A minor obstacle.
I'm already taken care of it.
Well, my people have a saying, Tony:
all cats are gray in the dark.
Mister Hottie has returned.
Back for more?
- Warren, is it?
- Good memory.
I'm good with faces.
What can we do for you?
- Just a trim. I like to keep it neat.
- I can fit you in.
Congratulations, Mr. French.
Back at ya! And your wonderful
company, too.
- What a winning bunch of folks.
- You're the real winner, Mr. French.
So...
You given any thought to what you
want to do with the old place?
Oh, I don't know. Hire a wrecking ball?
- Is it going to be cash or check?
- We're lucky. I have cash.
- We're lucky indeed. That'll be thirty.
- Perfect.
Tell me Warren... shall I make out
a file card for you?
How can I say no?
I'm sorry for being so bold.
Would you consider having dinner
with me tomorrow night?
Yes. I would give that
serious consideration.
That's my cell.
Great.
- Dude, that never happens!
- Not to me, it doesn't.
Thank you.
We'll have the Dutton Goldfield
Pinot, please.
So. You're looking for real estate
in Manningtree?
Yeah. But I'm taking my time.
My consulting practice gives me
that luxury.
What do you consult on?
A little of this and a little
of that. Urban planning, mostly.
Town planning?
Nowadays they call it urban planning.
Sort of a semantic thing. Towns are...
- ... disappearing.
- Evolving.
I've never really understood
what consultants do.
- It's sort of a broad term.
- A catch-all, is it?
Well, let's see. I help make things
happen for a variety of concerns
on a variety of fronts.
My consulting practice allows me
to set my own schedule,
vacation when and where I want.
I have a house on the Dalmatian Coast.
That is, when my Blackberry lets me
out of the cage.
But I'm more interested
in what you do.
What I do?
I cut, color, and style hair.
It's pretty simple.
- They say simplicity is happiness.
- Oh, well, happiness is another matter.
I go to work to forget
the complications in my life.
Please. Let the lady.
That's very nice.
So, tell me about these complications.
You know how... if you don't keep
your hair trimmed, you get split ends.
Wee things going this way and that.
It's a mess.
So, you get your shears,
you trim off the ends,
and your hair looks healthy again.
It takes on a new shape.
Well, that applies to life.
Life has little complications
going this way and that,
not leading anywhere.
You gotta get rid of 'em.
Then your life has a new shape.
That's my philosophy, anyway.
At this time in my life, Warren,
my shears are in my hand.
You and your scissors don't scare me.
You'll see in your packets that
we've arrived at purchase agreements
with a substantial number
of Old Town property owners.
Stan Singleton... Dennis Howe...
Andrew Macintosh, Leonard French.
- Len's Cafe is going away?
- Good riddance.
I assume he'll be relocating to Route 22.
- Where he belongs.
- What's wrong with Route 22?
Len French drove a hard bargain.
He's landed a 600 square foot space
in the new project.
An upscale little coffee place.
A real sweetheart lease.
Whattya know.
The guy's got some gonads.
North Sea is currently working with
Amuelson's Leather Goods,
and having a look
at the Paisley Set property...
- What 'bout Bernie Depper?
- And Bernie Depper.
Bernie's Antiques.
I don't need to tell you, these are
ongoing and sensitive negotiations.
All that remains is the certification
of the environmental impact report.
That's the bound document in your packet.
- So, we vote on this?
- Correct.
I think we have the votes now.
- I say go for it.
- Then let's get this show on the road.
Not so fast. It has to be approved
in a public meeting.
- With two weeks' notice.
- Come on, fellas.
- That's what the town charter says.
- He's right, Tiny. Two weeks' notice.
I'm having my gall bladder out
in two weeks.
No, you're not.
Bonnie! Post that notice!
Are we done yet? I've got lunch plans.
I move to adjourn.
Do I hear a second?
Hell. I'll second it myself.
All in favor?
Opposed?
Ayes have it. Adjourned.
Let's go eat.
- How did it go?
- I think you have a project.
Your usually scungigli salad,
mister Mayor.
Thank you.
No bread for me, please.
I'm on Atkins.
Atkins is dead. He fell down.
Smack. Right in the middle
of Manhattan. Some diet.
It's working for me. No more bat
wings under here.
I look better
than I did twenty years ago.
- I like the color.
- What?
The color of your hair.
It's a lot less...
Johnny Cash.
It's my hair stylist. Lizzie Munro.
In Manningtree. She does good.
- You know her?
- Yeah, I know her.
She said you gave her
the cold shoulder.
- Did you? Give her the cold shoulder?
- What is this, the third degree?
I promised your mother on the day
she died that I'd look after you.
Make sure you went to mass.
Make sure your hair was combed.
But you're a man now.
- I try to stay out of your business.
- Good idea.
So I was surprised when Lizzie
told me about this Disneyland thing.
And how you brushed her off.
Disneyland.
What are you talking about?
The big, crazy shopping mall.
Now wait a minute. If you're talking
about Cortona,
that's a beautiful plan.
- Beautiful condos, stores, restaurants.
- In Old Town?
Yeah. But I don't wanna discuss it.
I just wanna eat.
I don't get you, Anthony. Didn't
you tell me you were gonna pick up
some of those buildings
while the market was not so good?
Fix 'em up?
Isn't that you told me at Carla
Pezzimenti's daughter's confirmation?
- I do not recall.
- Gavone.
There's nothing quite like
the Manhattan skyline.
They say that architecture
is frozen music.
Some architecture.
It embodies every aspiration,
everything powerful about this country.
I don't know. Sometimes I think
it looks like a graveyard,
with the stones pointing up
out of the ground.
Am I bit dark?
Not at all. A bit poetic, maybe.
Do you know Sir Noel Paton?
He was a painter. Scottish.
I studied him at university.
He also wrote poetry. He had the most
fantastic sense of the visual.
The plaided ghosts of buried centuries
Were mustering in the glen
with bow and spear.
And shadowy hounds to hunt
the shadowy deer
Mix in phantasmal sword-play,
or, with eyes of wrath and pain
immortal, wander o'er
Loved scenes where human footstep
comes no more.
- You're the poetic one, Warren.
- You bring it out of me.
Hello, sir.
- Heading home?
- Oh, yeah. It's American Idol night.
Good night, Mr. Berry.
Tim. When you're done here,
you have to get to those floors.
Yeah. Okay.
- It's like a dry lake bed in there.
- Gotcha.
- I mean perceivable dirt.
- No problem, Mr. Berry.
Good. Good.
I would have loved to see this mill
when it was up and running.
It must've been grand.
The water turning the enormous wheel.
The yarns all coming together
on the loom. The warp and weft.
Dead marvelous.
Electricity reared its ugly head
and put this old beauty
out of business.
That's progress, Lizzie.
Did you know my grandparents
were Scottish?
- Liar.
- Dundee.
Now you're pulling my leg, Mr. Brown.
I learned about progress from them.
About Scotland.
How it was the birthplace
of modern physics and chemistry.
James Dewar. Charles Macintosh.
Thomas Graham.
Those were my heroes growing up.
Progress is a good thing, Lizzie.
You're nearly perfect, aren't ya?
- What've we got here?
- What does it look like?
- Uisge beatha.
- Right you are.
To better living through chemistry.
Scottish chemistry.
Slainte.
- Tell me, did someone die?
- The guy just sold up.
So what does this mean?
It means that the North Sea Assets
project will be a done deal.
I will not sell.
Then the bulldozers will come
roaring down the street.
Either way, you lose.
Why can't you face reality? Take
the money they offer you and go.
Surrender? Never!
Jesus. Whose side are you on, Mehar?
- I'm on the side of progress.
- Sometimes progress blows, dude.
Do you want to go work for ultra cuts?
Because I don't!
Do you think we need another strip mall
in town?
- I don't want to live in MacManningtree.
- So? Whose side are you on?
This one's nice, honey. Hon?
I don't know.
This one's pretty good, Lenny.
You can go really soft...
or pretty darn firm.
I don't know, Dee. Those are
expensive little units.
Oh, come on, now.
It'll last forever, honey.
It'll be the last mattress
we ever own.
Don't be penny-wise and pound foolish.
Besides, we have got some
extra cash in the bank now.
We can get the pillow tops
for the kids
and treat ourselves
to something really special.
Think about your bad back. And you know,
everything comes ready to go.
Fitted and flat sheets, two pillow
cases apiece. Are you listening?
Isn't that Lizzie Munro?
- I'm looking for the Mayor.
- Well, he's not here right now.
Thank you, Connie.
These look delicious.
You like 'em?
I have a little old man
up in Hoboken who makes 'em special.
He does all my baking
for events and stuff.
Altar society, bridge club.
I shouldn't.
For my sins.
I asked you to come here
for a reason, Lizzie.
My beloved nephew, Tiny Provenzano,
is no friend of yours.
Well, he's on the wrong side
of the Old Town fight.
- No, no, no. He is your enemy.
- My enemy? Now that's a bit dramatic.
He is in bed with the developer.
North Star.
North Sea.
North Sea. Tiny has been making offers
on buildings up and down Main Street.
He is throwing money around
like an intoxicated sailor.
But, Connie, how could Tiny afford
that? He has one mattress store.
Cheap money, Lizzie.
Cheap money and bribes from North Sea
in exchange for Tiny's influence.
Tiny is going to make millions
from ground leases and tax incentives
from his piece of the project.
You don't look well, honey.
Have a bite of your "canolli".
What do you say we double on this hole?
Make it 200?
That makes it 200, right?
- Nice shot.
- See what you've got, Tiny.
Warren, darling. It's Lizzie.
I need your consulting expertise.
Call me as soon as you get this.
Alright? Bye.
You think three?
We got all day.
Let's go.
Bollocks.
Hello, Mr. Brown.
- Dennis, how are you?
- Very well, thank you.
I'm dreamin'.
- How's your new baby?
- Very good, thanks.
That's great.
Holy shit.
- Bastard.
- Men are beasts. We should know.
What an idiot I am!
That's the trouble with this world.
No loyalty. No honesty.
And honor's out the window.
- What a fool I've been.
- We're behind you, whatever you do.
Don't worry, Lizzie.
I'm afraid we're beat before we've
even had a chance to get started, Dad.
I may have to give this place up.
But damn it, I know I should fight.
- Give 'em hell, girlie!
- Aye, I'll give 'em more than that!
Tell them I have something to say.
Hey, everybody, listen up!
Lizzie's got something to say!
Hello Manningtree!
I want to thank you for coming out
on a Monday night.
I hope the bartender has treated you well
and you've all had something to eat.
The drinks are on me tonight.
Tomorrow, the fate of our dear
little town will be decided.
Will we be buried by developers
and politicians, bought and paid for?
No!
Or will we let them know
what we think of their silly Cortona?
Are ye ready to fight?
Then I'll see you at Town Hall.
Bring everyone you know.
Bring your wee bairn and your granny
if you have to. Just show up.
Here's tae ye!
- Just a wee trim, Jacks.
- Trim it is.
This man has no shame.
Go away, Warren. As far as ye can get.
Just open the door.
I've welcomed my last walk-in,
Mister Brown.
My services are available
by appointment only.
Now you slither on home to Fifth Avenue
and leave us alone.
Listen. I was just trying to help you
come to terms with the inevitable.
The inevitable? Is that what they
call a roll in the hay?
I was fallin' in love with you,
Warren.
You and your Scottish grandparents.
And your Gaelic and your poetry.
But it's all just a lot of bollocks,
isn't it?
You're wrong.
Up your kilt with a banger!
Can I see one of those, please?
Excuse me.
- Good work, lassies.
- My God!
- Dude. We should run for President.
- We should.
Ladies and gentlemen, after you.
All right, all right. Council will
convene in five minutes.
Oh, my God!
All raise for the pledge of allegiance.
I pledge Allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, indivisible,
with Liberty and Justice for all.
Bonnie, first item please.
Item 1-A. Appreciation of Ruth McDuff
retiring president
of the Senior Citizens Forum.
Item 1-B. Proclamation recognition
of international mail carrier's day.
Item 2-A.
Approval of sanitation department
budget increase.
Item 3-A. Budget increase
for town council trip to Yokohama.
Item 6. Formation of study group
for arts funding.
Item 8-F. Certification
of the EIR Cortona mixed used project.
Order!
First speaker... Martha Ruth.
I want this town to be for my son
the way I grew up here.
Thumbs down on Cortona.
For the sake of our children
and our future just say "no" to Cortona.
Remember. We voted you in,
we can vote you out.
Mayor is a disgrace,
he ought to be ashamed...
My father owned a motorcycle shop
here for 10 years.
We want to keep it that way.
This is our town...
And we're not going to let you take it.
Worst thing that ever happend
to this town. We have to stop it.
All of us. We have to stop it.
A lot of projects are bad
for Manningtree, New Jersey and US.
And who is this town belong to anyway?
It belongs to us, all of us.
- We, the people, say "no" to Cortona.
-I don't want to live in MacManningtree.
Stop this...
I will fight so that Cortona
will never happen here.
This is for the people. All the people.
Besides, I need a place
to get my hair done.
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
You can't play with people's lives.
I think it should stay
just the way it is.
That's the kind of place
I want my kids to grow up.
The last speaker...
Lizzie Munro.
Mister Mayor.
Members of Town Council.
My name is Elizabeth Munro.
Most of you know that. I work
and live here in Manningtree.
You probably know that, too.
I guess you can tell I'm from Scotland,
if you don't know me already.
We Scots have a long and proud history
in America.
We signed
your Declaration of Independence,
we lived in your White House
more than a few times.
We invented your telephone.
We're Lucille Ball and Jimmy Stewart.
Ulysses S. Grant, Davy Crockett
and Neil Armstrong.
We're even Jackson Pollock,
for God's sake.
So it's important to me
to live to up to all that. Ya ken?
We're not here for a history lesson,
Ms. Munro.
Right.
In my home town in Scotland,
William Wallace, Braveheart,
stood his ground against the English
on Stirling Bridge.
Against the insurmountable odds
he and his people
routed English invaders that day.
That was September 11.
In the year 1297.
And like you,
we Scots have a long memory.
But I'm sad to say that some Scotsmen
have forgotten who they are
and where they come from.
And when you pledge allegiance
to the almighty dollar, or euro,
or whatever you have in your pocket,
you've lost your citizenship
in the human race.
- Get to the point, please.
- That is the point, Tiny.
For chrissake, Aunt Connie.
Can you let me do my thing here?
A town... this town... is a place
to live, and work,
and raise your family.
But a town is not an amusement park.
Not a chain store.
It's not a bloody ATM machine
for developers and city officials.
- Time's up.
- I'm not finished.
You are finished.
Could we get the police here
to clear the room?
Point of order, Mr. Mayor.
We don't have a police department.
Bonnie, call the roll.
Bonnie, are you deaf? Call the roll!
Item 8-F. Certification
of the environmental impact report.
You cannae vote until the people
have been heard!
For God's sake, Bonnie,
will you call the roll here?
Mayor Provenzano. Let me finish.
Ms. Munro. I am the chairman
of this Town Council.
And when I say your testimony is over,
your testimony is over.
Mister Mayor!
What about our bloody constitution?
- Excuse me?
- Well, what about it?
You have to let her speak. She has
waited for nearly six hours.
This is a public hearing.
Don't be a silly man.
Bonnie, cut to the chase here,
call the roll.
The question is before the Council.
All those in favor...
No.
No!
The applicant withdraws!
Excuse me!
You can't do that!
- You can't do that!
- I just did.
God bless America.
- Hey.
- Hey, Jacks.
Dude. Your ten o'clock cancelled.
Really? She told me she was eloping
tonight.
- It's off.
- Bummer.
Lizzie,
may I have a word with you please?
A small token of my esteem.
Take it.
Hang tough, Miss Braveheart.
Alba gu bra!
Scotland forever.