Are you ready?
I can't do it for you.
I had a dream about you.
- What happened?
- You took the bullets out of my gun.
- Alvey doesn't need this fight.
- Is that him?
- Should we come down on the number?
- Why would we do that?
Pony the fuck up.
It's a million fuckin' dollars.
Why are you being so mean?
Because I don't need your
unsatisfied, depressing shit.
Open the fuckin' door, Kayla.
She can hardly walk.
Let's do a third fight.
Just get back in, dude.
Make money with the
gift that God gave you.
I am Sid fuckin' Vicious.
Get the fuck off me.
I baptize thou for the Father...
and of the Son...
and of the Holy Spirit.
Thank you.
It's buzzing.
Shit.
Shh.
Sorry.
You answer that phone,
you're going straight to hell.
Come sit down...
for a sec.
When's the last time
you were in a church?
Besides a meeting?
When the boys were little
and we went on that church kick.
Yeah.
We were gonna show them the way.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Just banged up. I'm fighting again.
God damn it.
Hey, would you stop?
I got to go.
Are you going to Jay's
for dinner tonight?
Wasn't asked.
You better go, grandma.
What's wrong?
Well, use another room.
You girls are driving me crazy.
Too bad Mac wasn't there.
Yeah, he was on call.
I just got a text from Dan
and I got to go show a house.
Right now?
Yeah.
Even with your face like that?
Who punches a friend in the face?
I hit him first.
Crazy isn't cute.
It's not?
Not when you have a daughter.
She loves me crazy.
You were wasted and you drove.
- You can't do that.
- I'm never gonna do it again.
- You always say that.
I was kidding.
I fuckin' woke up this morning,
I felt like shit.
It's never gonna happen again.
What house are you showing?
Um...
It's a pocket listing
in Mar Vista, I think?
What time is your mom coming?
I told her six.
Can you pick this stuff
up from the store
on your way home for dinner?
You got it, boss.
I won't let you down.
You really want to impress me?
Go sell that fucking house.
So you just came in and he was gone?
No note? Nothing?
No.
He got a phone?
He left it in his room.
That's not good.
What do you mean?
A lot of times, suicides
leave important shit behind.
Phones, wallets...
They don't need'm anymore.
Yeah, I am... kinda worried.
He's been really depressed.
I bet he has.
Jesus Godamighty, can you imagine?
But, hey. Maybe he...
He just went off the grid.
I mean, a lot of times
I go to the pool,
I leave the phone in the car, you know?
It's good to unplug.
But on a positive note,
you're looking well.
You got a suit on.
Put on some good weight.
You fitting in okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Good. Good.
Me, I'm...
I'm actually retiring.
Good for you.
Well, I had to.
I got a whitehot case of shingles.
Felt like a goddamn harpoon
going through my chest.
Still got marks on my side.
Fucking wakeup call.
Gotta slow down.
Yeah.
You see, Keith,
you tell'm we're looking for him. Okay?
Yeah.
Nice to see you
picking up the pieces, Ryan.
You stay the course?
Come on, come on!
- Come on!
- Come on! Hustle!
- Let's go!
- Okay!
Good. Good.
You good?
Keep working.
Right there. That...
That was your mistake.
You gave up your back.
At some point, you... you got...
you gotta tap.
Dan, I am so sorry...
Jay...
You're fired.
I...
Dude, I gave you chances, okay.
I don't know hat world
you think you're living in,
but this is civilization
and you act like a fucking monkey.
You did more dumb shit in one night
than most people do in their career.
I've never seen anything like it.
All right, I have
a philosophy when I...
When I hire an agent, okay?
I don't give a shit about experience.
Any retard can learn real estate.
I want a dynamic personality,
and guess what?
You got that, man. You do.
But you also have
a fucking screw loose.
Seriously. It's like you
don't want to succeed.
You don't want to thrive, man.
What do I do?! Tell me, because...
I can't work with that.
Do you have anything
you want to say to me?
Thank you for the opportunity.
I really appreciate it.
And I'm sorry it didn't work out.
All right. The final check
is going to go to your house,
and I'm gonna need... I'm
gonna need your iPhone back.
Good luck out there, man. I...
Yeah?
You in the middle of something?
No, come in.
That was nice, this morning.
It was.
You okay?
Yeah, we should talk about Nate.
Yeah. What's up? What's going on?
Garo's dragging his feet about
putting him on his next card.
Why?
I don't know. It's weird.
He's just kind of not responding.
Fuck'm, put him on another promotion.
He needs a fight. He's got momentum.
I agree.
And Ryan? What about Ryan?
Garo wants to put him on your card.
Comain event.
Not gonna happen.
You'll be fighting last.
No. Not doing it.
Your name will be bigger.
What is the problem?
No. Geez, I don't know, Lisa.
What is the fucking problem?
I'm doing one fucking fight. One.
I mean, all the cards in the world...
He's got to be on my fucking card?
He can't wait four weeks?
It's not Ryan. It's Garo.
This is a big event.
He is paying you a million dollars.
Do you really want to make
a big deal out of this?
I'm not doing a comain event. Okay?
It's not what I signed up for.
He can be on the card,
but he can't be comain.
Okay. I'll relay the message.
Hey. I want you to try some of this.
What is it?
Whey. Grassfed.
Super fucking clean.
There's vanilla. I got chocolate, too.
Not bad.
Nice, right? Natural.
Hey. It's on me.
Thanks.
Watching you and Alvey today.
You guys have been working
together for a while, right?
Long time.
Yeah.
I kind of...
Kind of noticed something.
If I may.
By all means.
When you jab, you leave
that front leg wide open.
No, I'm angled away. It's safe.
Not if he steps over the left foot.
Right?
Hey, Alvey.
How you doing?
I got a class. Catch you guys later.
Hey, Lisa tell you I'm on the card?
Yeah, she did.
You're cool with that, right?
We'll figure out. This you?
Yeah.
You don't clean up after yourself?
I just used it.
Wash your fucking dishes, man.
All right?
There's other people here.
Can I get another one of these?
So, there's a crib, and a pack 'n play,
changing table.
Jay took some of it, but
a lot of it's boy stuff, so...
Thank you. This is really helpful.
No problem.
So, how's Mac?
Is he taking care of you?
He's trying to.
Are you guys getting married?
No.
It's more like just friends.
He really wants to be involved.
Good.
He's a good one.
Could've been worse.
Take whatever you want.
Just lock up before you go.
Okay.
I've been in a really...
I've been in a shitty mood lately, too.
Everything pisses me off.
That could be
withdrawal from the Lexapro.
I also got this pain
running down both my arms,
my hands are numb, my back.
Fucking with my sleep.
Were you injured?
No.
Not that kind of pain. It's...
It's like... It's like...
I feel something coming on.
Have you seen a doctor?
Mnhmnh. No.
I wanted to talk to you
about it, you know?
Since I'm coming off
the medication that, you know,
maybe it's causing some kind
of misfire, you know?
Nervewise.
Possible.
I mean, I've never seen it.
I would really like you
to go see a doctor
to rule out anything structural
or neurological.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
This is what I'm concerned about, doc.
I...
I have been hit in the head a lot.
You mean CTE?
Parkinson's,
CTE, all of it.
Is that common among MMA fighters?
You know, it's common
among fighters, period.
You get hit in the head.
Yeah, MMA fighters,
fighting... just... Whatever.
I mean, I don't know.
What does it even fucking matter?
First tremor, I'm putting
a bullet in my head.
When's the pain the worst?
The morning.
And at night.
Times when you're typically alone?
It's all I can fucking think about.
'Sup, brother?
You done for the day?
Alvey's got an appointment.
Shit, I can hold some pads for you.
Want to get some extra work in?
No, man, you're leaving. It's all good.
Bro, where the fuck
am I going? Come on.
You sure you don't mind?
Get your ass in there, come on.
Get some work in.
You know what the worst mistake
in hu... in human history was?
in human history was?
Anyone?
It's... It's a little controversial.
The worst mistake
in human history was...
Agricultural revolution.
Once we learned how to plant crops,
we effectively enslaved ourselves.
We used to be nomads.
We used to forage and hunt.
I'm hungry, I'm gonna grab
a fig out of the tree.
A turnip out of the ground.
Take a nap. Fuck a little.
Now you just... it's all work.
I mean, that's all you do
is work, you know?
You c... you c... you clear
the fields, you till the soil,
you plant the seed,
you water it, you harvest it,
you put it into a silo.
And even when you have enough,
it's like all you want is more.
And this has made us violent,
and... and bloodthirsty,
'cause we don't roam.
We just... We settle into one spot.
And we acquire possessions,
and we shit out babies,
and we get real territorial.
No, I'm not gonna walk away.
No, I'm gonna fight
to the fucking death!
That's what we do now.
Because...
You know, because
we don't roam anymore.
And we don't know there's
a big fucking fig tree,
a sweet, ripe, plump fig tree
right over the hill.
We're all just...
slaves to...
wheat, and corn, and potatoes,
and famine, and bloodshed...
We're not what we were meant to be.
Agricultural revolution.
Anyway, I'm gonna go to the...
The grocery store rright now.
So, I wish everybody here
a wonderful afternoon.
Don't work too hard.
Nice. Nice.
Nice! Oooh.
All right.
Loose, loose, loose.
When you come in, jab step,
right hand. All right?
You got it.
Hey.
Yeah?
First, you coming in
with the jab, right?
Yeah.
Fake the takedown,
come with that power.
I strike to the takedown.
It's... It works for me.
I understand, I understand.
It's a little predictable.
Won me a lot of fights.
Listen to me.
You got KO power in your hands, right?
I feel it. I feel it.
I see it when you're hitting
mitts with Alvey. All right?
He flinches every time you let one go.
You got dynamite in your fucking fist.
Fucking use it.
Let it go.
Dom?
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
Alvey doesn't want you to coach Ryan.
That's not why you're here.
He asked for my help. Alvey isn't here.
Dom! Let's fucking work.
Let's work!
I got to go.
Hey!
You fucking cunt.
Dom!
My office. Now.
There's Vaseline in the lounge.
I'll bite down on my pad.
Hey, coach.
Shut the door.
I thought I made myself
clear about Ryan.
You absolutely did.
The fuck you doing
in the cage with him?
He just wanted to
get work in, that's it.
He got his work in before I left, Dom.
I...
I was literally holding pads.
Hand to God...
I'm not gonna deal with this bullshit!
You understand?
I don't have fucking time.
You get a warning today.
Nate and Ryan need one
fucking voice in their head.
You understand? That's mine.
You start contradicting the shit I say,
you confuse my fighter.
You confuse my fighter,
we got a problem.
Are we clear?
Yes. Yes.
I apologize.
You do it again, you're out.
I understand, and I apologize.
I apologize.
You're just... You're just
figuring the place out still.
I'm enjoying myself.
I mean, you set up a great
culture here, you know?
All right. Dom, we're done.
Just get the fuck out of my office.
Ooh, he's cute.
And British, which is awesome.
He's a US citizen now.
Yeah, but he's got that accent.
I'm a sucker for a British accent.
Or Australian. It's very hot.
But you... you...
You have to watch that.
Everything they say will
sound like a royal decree.
It makes you feel too stupid to talk.
He's not like that.
He's from Manchester.
It's kind of, like, a rough area.
Well, good. I don't
want you to feel inferior.
I don't.
Are you sure you want to be
in a relationship?
Why wouldn't I?
Aww. You haven't done this before.
I mean, you might not even know
what kind of guy you like.
Maybe you need to go
through a couple of them
before you settle down.
I'm not settled down.
It sounds like you are.
Nate, he gave you a key.
Dad doesn't even know yet.
Is Will pushing you to come out?
No. No, he gets it.
Well then,
it's none of your dad's business
until you're ready.
It's your life.
You guys heard from Jay?
Not yet. Did you call him?
Yeah, it says his phone
is disconnected.
Will you try him?
Yeah.
Hey, Lisa.
How'd your little chat go?
Shh.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
So, your... your top fighter
asked me to train.
What am I supposed to do?
You're not supposed to train him.
He asked me.
And then he played you against Alvey
and got Alvey's attention.
I fucking hate politics.
I fucking hate it.
Then don't be fucking political.
How do I fix this?
Leave it alone.
He'll forget about you
in a couple of days.
How do I fix it with you?
We're good.
You want to have a drink with me?
My God. You can't be serious.
Are you kidding me?
I can't do that either?
I mean, I got to fucking write a list
of all the things I can't do.
Don't train Ryan,
don't drink with Lisa...
Don't be a smartass.
I feel like a dumb-ass.
I feel like a dumb-ass after today.
Have a drink with me.
Come on.
She go down okay?
Yeah. Finally.
You need a glass of wine.
Are your parents still together?
Sorry, what?
Are your parents still married?
- Yeah.
- How long?
Umm...
42 years I think.
That's amazing.
I bet your mom is beautiful.
Please just fucking sleep.
Do you want me to try?
No, it's ok. She'll... She'll stop.
Sorry.
Hi.
Where the fuck have you been?
At work.
You're three hours late.
Yeah. Dan insisted on cocktails.
Why is your phone disconnected?
My phone was stolen at the bar,
so Dan had to disconnect it.
For security reasons.
Because it's a company phone,
but fear not.
I took it upon myself
to upgrade dinner.
Steaks.
$30 a pop!
And...
A bottle of French wine...
highly rated in the low 90s
with hints of wet leather,
soil, and currants.
Look at me.
You're fucking high.
I can't fucking believe you!
It's... Dan insisted on a few drinks.
Why?
Drumroll, please.
Because I...
sold a house today.
That's great.
That is great.
Thank you.
It's just an offer,
but it is above asking,
which is exactly what
we were looking for.
So, I'm gonna get cleaned up,
make myself appropriate,
use the facilities,
and then we can get cooking.
What do you say? You hungry?
Starving.
Just a minute.
- Open the door.
- Just a second.
Open it.
You're blowing it.
What are you on?
You on coke?
Let me see your pockets.
Get out of my house.
You're scaring her.
This is not your home.
Please leave.
No.
I want you to leave.
Mnh.
Okay.
Yep, I'm here.
Yeah, it's in Venice.
Cash.
Enzo.
No, it's not a problem.
I don't have a preference.
That's fine.
Natural?
Sure.
Ten o'clock, latest.
Can't do any later.
Yeah?
That's great. Thank you, sweetheart.
How are the steaks?
How's your steak?
It's good.
Let me see.
Look. At. That.
Goddamn thing of beauty.
It's not too done, is it?
- Nope.
- No?
I take mine rare.
Knock off the horns and wipe the ass.
Is that a... baby crying?
Am I wrong? What the fuck? Am I wrong?
Is that a baby crying?
Are you... are you gonna pick her up?
When I'm finished.
Well, then, I'll pick her up.
No, you won't pick her up.
Rowr!
Tiger mom.
We could've used one
of those, Nathaniel?
If we're not gonna do anything,
then maybe we just kill
the fucking monitor.
You want me to turn
this baby monitor off?
Well, if it just doesn't matter
that she's crying,
then I don't know why we
have to fucking listen to it.
Do you have any idea how fucking
gross you are right now?!
Drunk and high like a fucking loser.
You have a daughter, Jay!
I know that because
of the fucking crying
that I hear for her mother.
I am disgusted by you.
I'm a monster, right?
Fuck you, Amy.
Yeah.
Do better.
Jay, shut the fuck up.
Nate, she's bringing up an issue,
but it's not the real issue.
The real issue, right, is class.
You can't let this go!
No, no, 'cause we
are white fucking trash,
and she can't believe
that she got stuck with us.
And a baby, no less.
You see this?
$30 steak.
Means shit to me.
Means shit to me 'cause I am who I am.
And I'll eat scraps
out of a fucking gutter.
I'll dig a fucking ditch.
I'm out. You want a ride?
Whoa, we're done?
Yeah. You want a ride?
It's early. Where you going?
Home.
To do what?
To do whatever
the fuck it is I want to.
- Hey.
- Thanks for the drinks.
Hey, hey, hey. Come on. Come on.
Before you go... Before you go...
Sir?
Sir, can we get two shots of añejo?
No, no, I'm good.
The good shit up top?
Come on.
Before you go, before you go...
You want to play a game of chance?
What's the game?
You sure you want to know my game?
You don't even have one.
No, I do.
Don't be scared.
But, I got to... I need
to know if I can trust you.
Now, see, are you gonna
be honest with me?
I don't know. That's really your call.
I can trust you.
You got an honest face.
Get on with the fucking game.
Okay, okay.
I have to guess three things
that you're gonna do
when you get home tonight.
Now, if I'm wrong... I'm never wrong...
I take both shots.
Now, if I'm right,
you take a shot with me
and we keep on drinking.
How many guesses?
Shit, I'm gonna go three for three.
Cocky.
I'm not cocky. I'm desperate.
You ready?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Okay.
In no particular order...
Number one...
When you get home,
you're gonna pour yourself
a glass of wine.
I'm also going to brush
my teeth and go to sleep.
Those are easy ones. They don't count.
I'm warming up.
I'm on my move... I'm gonna get there.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna get in there.
Number two. Number two...
Tchtchtchtchtch tchtchtchtch.
Don't slap me.
I can't promise anything.
You may get a little upset.
When you go home,
you're gonna get yourself off.
You have no fucking class at all.
Was I wrong?
What, that's...
- My bad. Am I wrong?
- Go to the next question.
Thank you.
Number three.
Number three...
When you go home,
you're gonna cry about some shit
that's not even your fault.
Who'd you talk to?
A few people told me.
They... they love you.
It wasn't gossip.
Can we have two more shots?
- Hey.
- Enzo?
Yeah. Come on in.
Drink?
I don't drink.
They told you everything?
They did, indeed.
Thanks.
Okay.
So...
Where do you want me?
The bed?
The bed.
You on the pill?
What?
Are you on the pill?
Yeah. Shut the fuck up.
My God. My God.
- Fuck.
- Shit.
Fuck.
Shit.
Where you going?
You're fucking wild, man.
Dom?
'Sup?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Wow. Just like that?
Are you serious?
I think you had a pretty
fucking good time tonight.
All right.
You drive safe, all right?
Yep.
I got fired today.
Why?
Numerous offenses.
You told Amy you sold a house.
Yeah, I did that so
that she wouldn't get mad at me
when I came home all fucked up.
You gotta combine a positive
with a negative.
Like, I'm wasted,
but I'm celebrating.
Sweet and sour.
Sugar and poison.
There are the
fundamental building blocks
of a healthy relationship.
You can try it on Will.
You can call me and say thank you.
She's trying with you.
I know, but, it...
It's, like, hard.
She's got...
one foot out the door.
I'm just giving her,
you know, a little push.
It's not a joke.
You gonna lose them.
Maybe it's better.
Yeah, I mean,
she can bring Maya to Wisconsin.
She's got a really good family.
Her dad is a, um...
He's an actuary
which is, like, a, um...
It's like the elite form of accounting
'cause they have money
put on their back
in order to predict the future.
It's... it's a better life.
That is so fucking weak.
I'm a very weak man.
I thought you wanted a family.
I want for nothing.
I just... I accept what comes my way.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
When you were getting
fucking shitfaced today,
and you got fired
from your fucking job...
acting like an asshole at dinner,
did you think for one second
about your fucking daughter?
I mean, do you want to be
a part of Maya's life or not?
I accept what comes my way.
Well...
I don't respect that.
Nathaniel,
you have so much to learn, man.
You have so much to fucking learn.
Yeah.
Again?
I must be on your mind.
How was dinner with the boys?
Disaster.
What happened?
Jay disappeared,
and then he came home high.
Fuck, really?
Fucking kid loves chaos.
Yeah, I wonder where he gets that from.
Mnh. You?
No, that would be you.
Me? I'm fucking stable.
You're... you're a gypsy.
Where do you even live?
I live in your dreams.
That's right.
You do.
There anything else about that
dream you want to tell me?
Like what?
Like... did we fuck?
Did we fuck?
You really wanna know?
Well, I'm curious.
No.
You gave me too much heroin.
I couldn't get a hardon.
You must be getting old.
What are you wearing?
Keith?
Hey, man, where have you been, dude?
I thought you fucking
killed yourself, dude.
Dude.
What the fuck happened to you?
Are the police looking for me?
Yeah. What the fuck happened, man?
I fell down the side of the highway.
We gotta get you to a hospital.
No.
Yeah, dude. Keith...
Keith.
Keith, you're fucking bleeding, man.
I am bleeding,
but can we go in the morning?
I'd just like to spend
one more night here.
Please?
Please, Ryan, and then... Then I'll go.
You can... can have
this whole place to yourself.
Keith.
I don't want this place.
Why not?
I don't know what
you're talking about, man.
What?
Come on, man.
Nobody wants...
What?
Nobody wants to live here.
Let's...
I don't want you to look at me.
Come on, man. Come on, buddy.
Hey.
Why you crying, man?
I don't want you to look at me.
Why you crying?
No, hey. Hey, I got you dude.
I got you.
Keith.
Buddy.
I got you, buddy. Come here.
It's all good, man. There no...
Come here. I got you. I got you.
- Shh.
- I got...
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, I got you, man.
I got you, buddy, okay?
Shh.
You wanna stop somewhere to eat?
Get a burger?
Keith, they're not gonna
put you to sleep, dude.
Probably just gonna
extend your probation
for cutting off the monitor.
I'm not coming back, Ryan.
Sure you are, dude.
We'll get you sorted out
with the police.
We'll get you under a doctor's care.
You'll be back before
you know it, okay?
Turn right up here.
What?
Ryan, just turn right.
- Why?
- Please, just turn right!
Okay, all right. Calm down.
Keep going.
Okay, you're gonna stop here.
Where?
Just stop here. Turn the car off.
- Up here.
- Over here?
Yeah.
Okay.
Right here?
What're we doing?
I have to show you something.
Okay. What?
- Follow me.
- Keith... Keith, wh...
Keith?
Keith, what are we doing, bud?
Keith.
Is this... Is this where you were?
Keith, come on, man.
What? What? What about it?
Lift it up.
Lift it up!
Fuck!
Ga...
Keith, what did you do, dude?
Whoa.
Fuck!
Synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com