(silence)
(wings flapping)
(thunder and pouring rain)
- Oh no.
Oh fuck.
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck,
fuck, fucking shit!
(screams in agony)
(classical music)
- [Thomas] Relax druggie Dougie.
- Don't fucking call me that.
My name is Doug, or Douglas.
I'm a fucking adult!
- I believe he's trying
to assert his authority.
- Are you trying to
assert your authority?
- Maybe he thinks
he's in charge here.
- Do you think you're in
charge here, druggie Dougie?
- Don't fuckin'--
(fist slamming)
- What did I say?
- He said to relax
druggie Dougie.
(sighs)
- I did.
I said to relax.
Right?
- What do you want from me?
- We want to see how much
you love your new God?
- Are you familiar
with yubitsume?
- Yeah, it's that brown chicken
dish at fucking Benihana.
- No Doug, it's a ritual
practiced by the Yakuza.
Yubitsume is a form of apology.
If a member of the Yakuza
were to dishonor himself
or one of his bosses he'd
be required to perform it.
- Perform what?
- He'd be asked to use this.
(eerie music)
- To cut the tip of
his pinky finger off.
(soft eerie music)
- Fuck, fuck you guys.
I'm not cutting the fucking
tip of my finger off!
- Oh that's up to
you druggie Dougie.
- Yes, we're not the low
life drug addicts here.
- This stuff, this
means nothing to us.
- We just as soon flush
it down the toilet.
- We would.
But we know you
wouldn't like that.
- You're what they
call a super addict.
And besides we're only
asking for a pinky
you big baby.
- It's gonna hurt
like fucking shit!
- Wow.
It really only tickles a little.
- And you'll have that
sweet, sweet crack
to take the edge off.
And then we'll drive
you to a hospital,
they'll patch you
up neat and tidy.
- This is, this
is fucking fucked.
- So is chemical
dependance, but here we are.
And you've certainly
dishonored yourself.
So I can't think of a
more apropos way to atone.
- Just the tip, right?
- That's all.
- So what do you
say druggie Dougie,
pinky or no pinky?
- And you fuckers
are going to take me
to the hospital right
afterwards, right?
- My golden word of honor.
- Let's up the ante a
little bit, shall we?
Odds are you've never seen
a kilo of cocaine before,
so feast your eyes.
- It's still yubitsume.
- But--
you do have to use this.
- Fuck.
Oh and how the fuck
am I supposed to
cut my finger off with a rock!?
- Figure it out.
That's your problem
druggie Dougie.
- Or you can go for the
small package instead
and just use the knife
like a little bitch.
Shall we count?
- Fuck it!
- You got this Doug!
(screams in agony)
(wild screaming)
- It hurts!
- Go, go, go!
- It fucking hurts!
It hurts!
- Just severe the bone
and you're all free!
Oh do it Doug!
One more!
(yelps in agony)
- Wow!
Oh my God!
Douglas, I am impressed.
Unbelievable.
You were right.
- See I told you, drug
addicts will do anything.
- Help!
- Well I am a man of my word,
you won fair and square.
- Thank you.
(heavy breathing)
- What the fuck is that about?
- Oh you see, I bet a dollar
that you would use the rock,
but Charles here, he
thought you'd puss out
and go for the knife.
- You bet on me you
yuppie assholes!
(amused chuckling)
What's so funny!?
- It's powdered
sugar druggie Dougie.
- And the packet was rock salt.
(condescending chuckling)
- You fucking dick holes.
Fuck you.
Just take me to the
hospital please.
- Now where are our
keys druggie Dougie?
- If they've been snakes--
- They would've
bitten me, I know.
- You can't walk away from me.
- Have to dash druggie
Dougie, it's been fun.
- Don't you fucking
leave me here!
Fucking help me!
(suspenseful electronic music)
(alarm ringing)
(knocking)
- Mother, are you decent?
- When am I ever not decent?
Are you trying to imply
I'm not a lady, Charlie?
- Of course not mother.
How did you sleep?
- Terribly.
Oh, if I could
move without pain,
I would've tossed
and turned all night.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
You are still beautiful though.
- Yeah?
- Mhm.
- Am I still your favorite girl?
- Forever and ever.
- You sure got that
look sweetheart.
- Thank you mother.
- What time is it?
Oh, would you get my
medicine for me baby.
- I'd be glad to sweets.
- Thank you.
I had the weirdest
dream last night.
- You don't say.
- Yeah, I was standing
in the middle of the road
watching this horribly
disfigured man
being pulled out of a car wreck.
(chuckles)
And guess what?
- What?
It started to rain rose petals.
Isn't that the damnedest thing?
And to top it off the
police and the paramedics
around the wreck stopped
pulling the guy out
and started dancing around
like it was a Broadway musical.
- Then what?
- Then my son called me
indecent and here we are.
- Oh hush.
Do you know what
Freud would say?
- Oh who gives two wooden
nickels what Freud would say.
That's all psychobabble anyway.
- Probably true.
It's all just a series
of dreamed up notions.
- Barely 11 am,
and Freud is the
topic of discussion.
I'm missing out.
- Good morning, Thomas.
- Good morning mumsie.
- You two were out
late last night.
I hope you weren't
getting into any trouble.
- Not in the least.
- Is that true?
- Yes, of course.
- Good.
- Charles.
(keys jingling)
Breakfast.
- Have a good day.
- You too mother.
- Hmm.
(eerie quiet rumble)
- Is there anything in there?
- About what?
- About last night.
- Oh I'm sure our friend
Dougie either bled to death
in a gutter somewhere or
he patched himself up.
Also, do me a favor.
Never bring up Doug again.
Better for all of us.
- Of course.
I'm sorry.
- No, never be sorry.
You know that.
Sorry is a sign of
weakness Charles,
and that is one thing
we cannot afford to be.
- More coffee guys?
- Please.
- [Charles] Please.
(coffee pouring)
- Genevieve, what a pretty name.
- Thank you.
I actually pronounce it
Genevieve, sounds fancier.
- You're new here.
- Yeah, just started
yesterday actually.
- Well we're a
couple of regulars,
so we'll be seeing
lots of each other.
- Oh, great.
- I'm Thomas, and this
less handsome devil
with the pancake in his
mouth is my brother Charles.
- Oh, I'm sorry, hello.
- Hi, I'm Genevieve, again.
- Mommy.
- And that's my
daughter, Maddie.
Well you guys need a fill
up just give a shout.
- Now that's a kind of
woman man was made to ruin.
Genevieve.
(exhales in shock)
You look like you
could use a fill up.
(yelps in pain)
You could.
(intense dramatic music)
(heavy breathing)
- Thomas.
Thomas.
Thomas!
You're creaming
all over the place.
Did you go away for a moment?
- She's got some big hips.
It's a good sign of
a healthy uterus.
- Can we please go
one day without you
using the word uterus?
- It's my very
favorite word, Charles,
can't help myself.
I'm in the mood
for a movie today.
You?
(laughing on screen)
We should get a hooker.
- [Charles] What?
- [Thomas] Did you
put salt in this?
- A little.
- Doesn't taste like a little.
- What about the hooker?
- Oh, we should get one.
- Why?
- Because it's time.
- So, so we're really
going to do it?
You think we're ready?
- You're not chickening
out on me, are you?
- No.
I just didn't think we
were ready, that's all.
- We're ready.
We've tested ourselves,
and we've tested others.
I say we just push forward.
- So what do we do, just
call up an escort service?
And then what?
- No, no you idiot, we don't
just call up an escort service.
That leaves a paper trail.
You're supposed to have
the higher IQ here, right?
- So what, we just pick up
a girl off of the street?
- Yes, we just pick up
a girl off the street,
take her to a motel.
- Oh, motel?
Isn't that leaving a trail?
- We pay cash, she
books the room,
no one sees us with her.
- All right.
Also we should rent a
car, so their hooker--
- No.
I don't leave paper.
We'll borrow our mother's car.
She won't be needing it anyway.
- What kind of girl
should we get then?
- Any kind, doesn't
matter to me.
It's all the same meat
in the end anyway.
- Would you two dick holes
please shut the fuck up!?
I'm trying to watch the film.
Just shut up!
- We're not animals, Charles.
Though he is on the list.
- It shouldn't just be
any kind of girl though.
She should be special.
- Okay.
So you pick.
It really doesn't matter to me.
(forcibly exhales)
- Your indifference
is suffocating.
- My indifference
is justifiable.
No one's gonna care one eye
about any of these girls.
Pretty or not.
(quiet eerie music)
- That one.
- That gaudy one?
She's decrepit Charles.
Why her?
- She's beautiful.
She looks like mother.
- All right.
Legs.
- Evening boys.
How can I help you?
- Well my brother and I
have carefully selected you
for tonight's indulgence.
- Selected me?
Both of ya?
You wouldn't happen
to be cops, would ya?
- Oh no ma'am, just regular
red blooded American horn dogs.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- I'm Drew, and this is Hank.
- Nice to meet
ya, Drew and Hank.
I'm Vanity.
- [Charles] Is that
your real name?
- No, of course it's not
my real fuckin' name.
- [Thomas] So are we
gonna party or what?
- I'll just get my purse.
(door creaking)
We could've gone some
place nice, you know?
- Dirty places for dirty
things, I always say.
- I'm gonna go freshen up.
- How should we do it?
- You wanna sleep
with her, don't you?
We can't rape her Charles,
it'll leave semen behind.
Even with a condom
it wouldn't be safe.
- Did you smell her?
Her scent, she stinks
off cooked meat.
- That's because it's
not meat brother,
that is the smell of impurity.
- So how should we do it then?
- Let's just roll with the
punches and see what develops.
- So what do you
two little pervs
wanna do with me tonight?
- A great many things.
- You don't have
to call me ma'am.
I'm your whore,
not your librarian.
Now I can be if you want to.
So we ridin' solo or tag team?
I don't do anal, usually.
Though I can be
financially coerced.
I don't swallow--
- This is a nonsmoking room.
- Seriously?
- Cigarettes are the
leading cause of death
in the United States.
- Okie doke.
Well you boys are in
charge, so let's--
- Oh no, no.
You're in charge tonight.
We want you to take the reigns.
- I like your style blondie.
You can come first.
(guitar music)
Do you like what you see?
I've always wanted to
be a ballet dancer.
- Yet you became a prostitute.
- Well life's what
happens when you're busy
making other plans.
Isn't that the bullshit saying.
Like God works in
mysterious ways, whatever.
- How many sexual partners
have you had Vanity?
- Many.
Too many.
- What would your mother
think about all this Vanity?
- She'd say I hope those two
sexy brothers tip well dear.
You know what's funny?
This is actually
my biggest fantasy.
Well not exactly,
but close enough.
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna suck your cock,
is that okay with you?
(eerie music)
(slurping)
(heavy breathing)
Gimme a chance to warm up!
- Get off me!
You disgust me.
- You fucker!
- Thomas what are you doing!?
- She's not the one!
- Not the one, what,
what do you mean!?
- She's so impure, she's rotten!
She can't be our first.
- I'm your first?
(laughing mockingly)
- Thomas wait up!
Thomas!
- Get away from me Charles.
- Thomas.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Hey, what happened!?
- She wasn't pure!
She wasn't pure, Charles.
She was a piece of
garbage nothing.
It was all wrong.
- All wrong?
How is it all wrong?
We knew what she was before
we ever walked into that room.
- No, no.
You see, it's the wrong tack.
We're going about it all wrong.
- Are we?
Or did you just lose your spine?
- What did you to say to me?
What the hell did you say to me?
Don't you ever!
- I'm sorry.
- Don't you ever say
that to me again!
I did not lose my
spine you idiot!
How could you not see
that she wasn't right?
Or you're too stupid
to understand?
- How wasn't she right?
We were supposed to kill her,
not put her on a pedestal.
- That's exactly
my point Charles.
We should put them
on a pedestal.
At least our first one.
It shouldn't be some thrown
away street trash tramp,
it should be someone who's
death would mean something.
Hookers get killed all the time.
Life goes on.
We need them to
remember what we do
and who we do it to.
(heavy breathing)
- Well, we could've
just strung her up
and made it look like
Jack the Ripper got to her
and that would've made ink.
- Nooo!
Keep in mind this
is an experiment,
a test of the superior
intellect versus
the weak minded cattle.
For it to lead to transcendence
it's got to mean something!
But for it to mean something
we must also make it art.
It must be a defiant act
of our above all else.
The victims are as much
part of it as we are.
They are the canvas Charles.
- Don't worry.
- And we--
- You will live.
- Are the goddamn paintbrushes.
(tense eerie music)
- I saw the light coming
out from underneath the door
and figured you were awake.
- Yeah, I'm having
trouble sleeping.
- Anything I can do?
- Tuck me in, sing me a song?
- Okay.
(ambient eerie music)
- You look worried.
Is everything all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Just got a lot on my mind.
- You know I can
read you like a book.
Something isn't right.
- There's nothing.
- We're supposed to tell
each other everything.
No secrets.
Is it Thomas?
He's weak and--
- No mother.
Everything is fine.
- Hmm, boy wasn't
that the look you got.
- Let's see, what song
would you like to hear?
- Well I could use
a little sunshine.
- You got it.
Sunshine baby
It's sunshine
Time to wake up baby
(chilling music)
Oh it's sunshine baby
All for you
(suspenseful music)
- [Genevieve] Good
evening stranger.
- Hey Genevieve.
- You remembered?
Sit wherever, it's
super dead tonight.
- I will if you join me.
- Um.
(soft piano music)
Cookie dough's my favorite,
but we don't carry it.
- I've never really been
a big fan of cookie dough.
- Most guys aren't.
Maybe it's a girl thing.
- So I guess your
husband doesn't mind you
working the graveyard shift.
- I'm not married.
- Oh, I figured since.
- Getting pregnant
and getting married
can be mutually exclusive.
It was just a
stupid time in my life.
I don't regret
having my daughter.
I love my little Maddie.
- You have a tattoo.
- Oh yeah.
Souvenir from the old days.
- It's beautiful.
- Thanks.
Maddie likes it.
So tell me about yourself.
What do you do?
What do you like?
You okay?
- Yeah, nervous twitch I guess.
- Are you nervous?
- Well yes.
After all I am all alone
with a very strange woman
and there's no telling
what you'll do to me.
- You're safe in my hands.
- Good to know.
(ambient relaxing music)
- So what about your
brother, what does he do?
- He's a writer.
He wants to write
true crime books,
he's fascinated by death.
- Oh, I couldn't do that.
There's enough
ugliness in the world
to go digging for more.
Back to work.
Grab a seat, I'll
be right with you.
- Are you seeing anyone?
(exhales nervously)
I am sorry.
I didn't mean to blurt
that out just then,
it's just I was
wondering if maybe
you'd like to go with me
to the movies sometime.
- Are you into chick flicks?
- Not particularly, no.
- Too bad, you'll learn.
(police sirens)
(laughter)
(crowd giggling)
That was funny.
(chilling music)
- You're glowing.
- I am?
- It's blinding.
- Thanks.
- May I?
- What?
- I want to hold your hand.
- Oh, sure.
- I can feel it.
- What did you say?
- Oh, nothing.
I'm sorry.
(cinema crowd laughing)
- You have any cocoa chocolates?
- We got movie shit.
- That was actually really good.
- I would go with the
definition of trite.
- You're kidding,
it was so sweet.
- Oh hey, you two!
- Hi!
- I didn't know you
were seeing this movie.
Wasn't it good?
- I know, and the ending.
- Who would've
thought he'd make it
to the altar after
all those mishaps?
Right?
- Right!
It was so good.
- What did you think Charles?
- Um, I thought it was okay.
- Okay.
This is the man who'd
argue the merits
of Bela Tarr's films
versus Bergman's work
and all he can say
is it was okay.
- Some films only
deserve an okay.
Can't like all art, it
would defeat the purpose
of personal intent
and free will.
- Well put sir.
Ugh, goddamn battery.
Charles do you mind if
I borrow your phone?
My mom's watching Maddie.
I didn't really tell
her I was gonna be.
- He doesn't have a
cell phone actually.
- It can lead to brain cancer.
- Though we do have
a phone at home
just right around
the corner from here.
- Oh, maybe I
should just go home.
I gotta work tonight.
- Don't be a silly goose,
come on over for lunch.
I'm an excellent cook.
Hey, you like pasta, huh?
- I love pasta.
- Fantastic!
Stay for an hour, Charles here,
he'll take you home.
You know what, call
Maddie, call your mom,
bring the whole clan over.
I'm part Italian, we
love big gatherings.
What do you say?
Huh?
- Okay!
(laughs enthusiastically)
(somber violin music)
- Welcome to our home.
Wow.
- Just make yourself at home.
Phone has been on the fritz.
I'm just gonna go
get my cell phone,
I don't really care
about brain cancer.
- Okay.
(soft gloomy music)
- What were you
doing at the theater?
Spying on us?
- She's perfect.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't play dumb Charles.
She's beautiful, she's kind,
she's loved by those around her
she even is a mother.
She's so bloody perfect.
- No.
No, I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
Then why were you going
out with her today
if you weren't
testing the waters?
I'll be a monkey's uncle,
you like this girl.
You honest to God
and the baby angels
actually like this girl!?
- She glows.
- What about me?
What about your big brother?
What am I supposed to
do when you kick me
to the curb for this,
for this woman!?
What do you even know about her?
- Okay.
- You know she's probably
as loose as Vanity?
All women are the same Charles.
You and I need to remain pure.
Have you forgotten that!?
- Okay, okay.
- What do you want me to do?
You're breaking my
heart here Charles.
Am I supposed to
just give up on you?
Because I won't.
You're my baby brother
and it's my job
to keep you safe.
- I said okay.
- Atta boy.
You know--
she is a pretty little
thing, isn't she?
Maybe it wouldn't
be a half bad idea
to marry a gal like that.
- Kill her Thomas.
- Who needs the headache?
If she glows like you
say, she's the one.
She's our canvas.
- Okay fine.
So how do we do--
- Follow my lead.
- Well as luck would have it,
I can't really seem to
find the damn thing.
- Oh, okay well
that's all right.
They can do without
me for an hour or so.
- Atta girl.
Now let me occupy your mind with
some fettuccine of the gods.
How does that sound?
- Great.
(giggles)
Shall we shrimp?
You allergic?
- Nuh-uh.
- Let's shrimp.
- [Mother] Charlie!
- Charles, mother beckons.
- Is your mom here?
- [Mother] Sweetheart!
- Yeah, she's, she's sick.
I'll be right back.
- Old lady problems.
- [Mother] You're not
being a bad boy are you?
- No, no mother.
- Thomas isn't doing things
he shouldn't be doing, is he?
Putting ideas in your head
that shouldn't be put there.
- No mother, I promise.
- He's like a canker
sore, that boy.
Always trying to be the big man.
Oh, I'm sure glad
you got that look.
Top me off, will
you honey bunch?
- Of course mother.
(mother breathing heavily)
I want to try and get some sleep
so you can have a
little peace and quiet
with your friend.
- So Charles tells me
you're into serial killers
and things like that.
- Mhm.
I like the obscure ones,
Earl Nelson, Henri Landru.
To a degree I consider
them artists, geniuses.
- Really?
I don't know.
I mean what would
possess someone
to want to kill
another human being?
I don't consider that genius,
I consider it insanity.
- There are Neanderthals
everywhere, Genevieve.
There are predators
and there are prey.
The trick is to eat
before you're eaten.
- Well maybe that's
true to a degree,
but I don't think killing
should be admired.
I certainly wouldn't
wanna live that way.
- Then you will be swallowed up.
Survival of the fittest.
- Wow, life's already
swallowed me up.
Best I can do now
is teach my daughter
to be bigger and
better than mommy.
- All parents want
that, most of them fail.
- Has anyone ever told you
you sound like an asshole?
- Not to my face, no.
Thank you.
- Oh my God.
You are radiant.
- Way to cover for your brother.
- I mean it.
You're glorious.
- Okay, okay.
Let's get this over with.
- What are you doing?
- We have been waiting for this
for a very long time.
- For what?
- You.
You, young lady,
are gonna be our masterpiece.
- Charles, tell him to back off.
This shit ain't funny.
- Funny?
You think I'm playing around,
Miss Genevieve?
What kind of hoity-toity
shitty name is that?
Stuck up bitches like you
are better off dead, I say.
Charles, it's here--
(shattering)
- Thomas!
(crashing and breaking)
(yelling)
Thomas, Thomas, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Thomas?
She's getting away.
She's getting away, Thomas.
Come on!
(trembling)
- Someone help me, please.
(crying)
- [Charles] She's suffering.
It's so beautiful.
- [Thomas] Charles?
- [Genevieve] Help me, help me.
(whimpering)
- Look at her, Thomas.
- Go away.
- Look at her.
- Stop.
(trembling)
Charles, please.
Why are you doing this to me?
- I'm not doing this to you.
I'm doing this for you,
because you're beautiful.
- I didn't do anything to you.
- You glowed.
Because you are glorious.
(hitting and crying)
(soft ethereal music)
(pounding)
(vomiting and pounding)
- Charles.
Stop.
(pounding)
God damn it, Charles, stop it.
Leave her alone.
She's dead.
(heavy breathing)
(eerie instrumental music)
We took her face off.
We took her God damn face off.
What should we do?
Oh Jesus.
(soft eerie music)
- It's beautiful.
Thomas.
It was a divine act.
It was divine.
The universe approves.
(laughing)
Did you see when I told her
it was because she was glorious?
She smiled.
Like she was giving
me permission.
- She didn't fucking smile.
Why did you keep
that damn thing?
- It's one of my souvenirs.
What's wrong with you?
You're shaking.
- Nothing.
Forget it.
- Thomas, I know you.
What's wrong?
I mean--
We pulled it off.
We did it, you know?
- Yeah.
We did it.
The problem is--
I didn't like it.
It shouldn't have
been like that.
- What should it have been like?
- I don't know.
I don't fucking know.
- You don't have
to curse, Thomas,
there's not need for that.
- I don't have to fucking curse?
Fuck you, Charles.
It shouldn't have
felt like that.
- Like what?
- Pity.
I felt,
sorry for her.
- Well.
I'm sorry to hear you say that.
(eerie haunting music)
(door opening)
- Swinberg, long time no see.
Hey!
How are the kids.
- I don't have children.
- I meant you're balls, pal.
You have testicle cancer, right?
- Yeah, how did you--
Right.
They're fine.
They're in remission.
- So, I'm coming in late here.
Fill me in.
- Female, age 26.
- Jesus, what is this, man?
- We found her off
the side of the road,
off Cold Water Canyon.
Someone took a rock to her face,
multiple times.
- Rock for sure?
- Well, we couldn't find it.
But, all the rock
debris in her wounds
is consistent with a rock
as the murder weapon.
- No prints on her?
- No, she was clean.
We're still waiting on fibers,
but the site wasn't
exactly pristine,
so it may take a while.
Also, we found a
patch of skin missing
behind her right ear.
It looks hastily removed.
Probably a trophy piece.
- Of course it was.
He probably framed it too.
Okay, darling.
Let's see if we can't find
out who did this to you.
(gasping)
- Up for a movie?
(pouring coffee)
I'm in the mood.
- I'm not.
- You can have it.
I wasn't going to eat it anyway.
- How did you know?
- I saw it.
I think I can see
everything now.
(chuckling)
- Sorry, boys.
Didn't mean to startle you.
May I cop a squat?
Pun intended.
- Of course, Officer.
- It's Detective.
Detective Homer Gaul.
As long as we've got that clear,
you can call me
Homer, we're pals.
- Well, how can we
help you, Homer?
- Not sure if you boys
have heard the bad news,
but one of the waitresses
that worked here
was found murdered
late last night.
- Oh no.
My goodness, who?
- Oh, pretty little thing.
Named Genevieve Du Bois.
You boys know her.
- We knew her somewhat, yes.
She would wait on us
whenever we came in here.
- Well, that's the reason
I'm bugging you folks.
You see, I asked
Angelo, the owner here,
to pick out for me a
few of the regulars,
and he fingered you two,
among a few others.
- Well, we are certainly
regulars, aren't we Thomas?
- Uh, yes.
- And, you two are what friends?
Lovers?
Nothing unsavory
or illegal going on
under this table is there?
(chuckling)
- No, Homer, we're brothers.
I'm Charles Brubaker, and
this is Thomas Lo Bianco.
- Different dads?
- You got it.
You must be really
good at what you do.
- You flatter me.
(chuckles)
It's a gift.
- Here you go, Detective.
- Ah, Homer, please,
we're pals, remember?
Now, lemme-- (sipping)
Mmm!
Oh!
Oh, Angelo, Angelo,
Angelo, Angelo.
This is the first
time I've actually
tasted coffee the way
it was meant to be made.
(chuckling and sipping)
Mmm!
Have you tried this coffee?
Astounding!
It's like cinnamon
and Jesus had a baby.
- Don't trust him, Charles.
Kill him.
- You boys ever
chat with Genevieve?
See her at all
outside this place?
- I can't say we have.
Wanted to though.
She sure was a pretty
young little thing,
like you said.
- Yeah.
Of course, I was
going off pictures.
Whoever killed her--
Man, those twisted bastards
really did a number on her.
- How was she killed?
- Charles!
- It really wouldn't
help the investigation
if I started running
my mouth about
the sensitive details of
the case, now would it?
Turn on the local news.
I imagine all the gory details
will be in the 6 o'clock.
Now, if I wanted to
reach you fellas again,
how would I do that?
- Well, this is our home number.
And that's in gold
leaf too, FYI.
- Pals, I wanna thank you.
- Ah, ah, ah, Thomas,
manners, please.
- Is it something I said?
My aunt always told me
to modulate my tone.
I hope I haven't been--
- No, it's just that we're sick.
Wouldn't want to spread it.
Besides, you have
work to do, Homer.
Taking a sick day now
would just slow you down.
- That's really very
thoughtful of you.
Talk soon, pals.
Hey, can I talk to you folks.
- Did you see his cup?
He had the glow.
- He came over to
shake our hands.
- How can you be sure?
- How 'bout a foreign film?
Something long.
- I'm not feeling well.
Take me home.
- Suit yourself, party pooper.
(kissing)
- Oh, let's take a picture.
(camera shutter)
- That one's good.
(kissing and moaning)
- Shh!
(kissing and giggling)
Excuse me, old timer.
(typing)
(suspenseful music)
(slurping and dramatic music)
- My God, you pervs.
Get out of here.
Out, out, out.
Hurry, move, move, move.
Have I seen you before?
Move, move, move.
(eerie suspenseful music)
- Psychic cop.
You've gotta be
fucking kidding me.
(pouring drink)
(squeaking wheels)
- Mrs. Du Bois?
- Oh, hello, Detective.
- How we doin'?
- Well, we're just--
trying to stay strong.
For her.
- Hey there, Maddie.
- Honey, this is the man
that I was telling you about.
- Can I shake your hand?
(eerie music)
- Well, if you guys
need a fill up,
just let me know.
- Thank you for that, Sweetie.
Oh, I'm so sorry, honey.
- You know, you're
kind of her hero.
- She's kind of mine.
I promise on my life
that I will find the bad people
who did this to your
wonderful beautiful mommy.
It's my job,
to make sure little
girls don't cry.
You can count on me.
Okay?
I'm the axe,
and they're the big bad wolves.
(creaking floorboards)
- Who is that?
Who the fuck is that?
(crashing)
(whistling)
- Here we go.
Ham and cheese.
- Mmm, extra mayo?
- Extra extra mayo, my dear.
Now, I have to dash,
but Thomas will be here if--
- No.
I'm turning in early tonight.
Hopefully.
- Oh, okay.
- [Charles] Down the hatch.
- Over the lips and
through the gums.
- Sleep well.
- Be a good boy.
- I'll be the very best, mother.
(humming)
- What are you gonna do tonight?
- Just drive.
We'll see what develops.
- [Thomas] You're not going to--
- If the spirit moves
me, I shall allow it to.
- You remember that
cop from this morning?
- Who, Homer?
- He's supposed to be psychic.
(laughing)
- I knew it!
Something told me to keep
you away from his hand.
That's why his
drink had the glow.
- He's got a 98%
conviction record, Charles.
- Well.
All we can do is hope.
- What?
- That we fall within
that golden 2%.
- He knows.
I'm sure he knows.
- Thomas, psychic
intuition is not evidence.
Even if he's really
really good at it.
He may know,
but he still has to prove it.
We are above this,
and we always have been.
(chuckling)
(door opening and closing)
(door opening)
Do you know where the keys are.
- Um, no.
How should I know?
- Thomas, are you lying to me?
- What do you say we
just stay home tonight,
get drunk,
and watch some reality TV crap?
- Oh, but that's boring, Thomas.
And if there's
one things I hate,
it's boredom.
Now-
That bulge in your right pocket
wouldn't happen to be
the keys, would it?
(keys jingling)
Thank you.
What would I do without
you, big brother?
(whistling)
(door closing)
Well, hello gorgeous.
- Well, well.
Where's Tweedledum?
- He's at home.
He's a little shy.
Doesn't know how
to treat a lady.
- But you do?
- Only one way to find out.
(door creaking open)
(screaming)
(crashing)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
- Same room, huh?
Maybe you should
rent it by the month.
- It's not going to be
very clean after tonight.
- Things gonna get
dirty, are they?
- You could say that.
- Yeah?
You look like a
nasty little boy.
- I have no intention
of kissing you
or the 1000 cocks you've sucked.
- Well, fuck.
Tell me how you
really feel about me.
I'm gonna go freshen up.
- Take a shower.
With soap and hot water.
I want you to be clean.
Put this on.
You see,
I'm going to eat you,
from head to toe.
- Sounds like a
Saturday night to me.
(eerie music)
(gun cocking)
- Okay, you no-faced bitch.
Come and get me.
(heavy breathing)
Come out,
Wherever you are.
(eerie suspenseful music
and heavy breathing)
Oh shit!
Oh fuck!
(crashing)
(heavy breathing and struggling)
(dramatic horror music)
Oh Jesus.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, Genevieve.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please, please, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
No, no.
Please, please, please.
No, fuck.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
No, no, no.
(whimpering and trembling)
(screaming in pain and crying)
- Thomas!
- You see, my brother
and I have a theory.
We once saw a cat get run
over by a car when we were 6.
A week later the carcass
hadn't been picked up yet,
but where it laid in the grass,
a patch of daisies
just sprung up.
That's where we first saw it.
- Saw what?
- The divine tragedies of life.
God's love in death.
Beauty amongst ugliness and rot.
- Are you a bible
thumper or something?
- No.
No, we haven't
written our bible.
Not yet.
But you.
You're very lucky.
- Oh yeah?
Why's that?
- You will be our second
step toward divinity.
You see, when I said that I was
going to eat you
from head to toe,
I meant that I was
going to eat all of you.
Your skin.
Your heart.
Your liver.
Your pancreas.
Your spleen.
Your ovaries.
Your everything.
- What the fuck do you--
(screaming and crashing)
(screaming)
(crying)
(laughing and radio music)
- This is one of my favorites.
(alternative music)
I can kill you
first if you like,
but you have to promise
to be quiet, my dear.
Vanity, come on.
- Fuck you.
(spraying and dramatic music)
(screaming and crying)
- What did you do, you bitch?
You fucking bitch.
What the fuck?
(crashing)
(alternative music)
- What the hell?
(trembling and ripping)
Oh Jesus.
(heavy breathing)
What the hell?
(splattering)
Oh, Jesus Christ.
(screaming)
What the fuck?
Oh, Jesus.
(heaving breathing)
(coughing)
- Oh my God.
- So how long does something
like this usually take?
- Depends on how
willing the spirit is.
Sometimes a day or two,
sometimes instantly.
- [Swinberg] And,
what do you see?
Is it like pictures, or what?
- Anything.
Sometimes the last images,
sometimes bits and
pieces, voices,
and it completely takes me in.
I see all of it.
- And with her?
- With her--
(eerie soft music)
I'm with you now.
I'm here.
Talk to me.
Did you know them.
Good.
That's good, sweetheart.
You have to tell me
their names, Genevieve.
Don't worry.
They can't hurt you anymore.
Talk to me, so I can make sure
they don't get away with it.
- They'll hurt Maddie.
- She's safe.
I sent her away
with your mother.
I won't let anything
happen to her.
I promise.
Now, talk to me, please.
(sharp dramatic music)
She's being stubborn
because she's scared.
But I know there
were two of them.
One did all the killing
and the other watched.
(eerie soft music)
(suspenseful music and moaning)
- [Voiceover] Almost.
Yes, that's it.
(humming)
- Hi, how's it goin'?
- Shut up, bro.
(talking on movie screen)
(suspenseful horror music)
(engine running and turning off)
(keys jingling)
(car door shutting)
- Hey, hey, I caught you.
I tried the door,
no one answered.
Figured you were out,
figured I would wait.
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph, my
boy, what happened to you?
- I fell down the
stairs, Detective.
- It's Homer,
we're pals, please.
Does it hurt much.
My wife always says onion--
- How can I help you, Homer?
- Well, I wanted to ask
a few followup questions
if you have a spare
second or three.
- Alright, okay,
yeah, okay, sure.
Is this about the
whole waitress thing?
- Yeah, pal.
I'm afraid it's about
the whole waitress thing.
- Alright.
Here's your water.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah.
- So, where's your brother?
- He's around somewhere.
I don't really keep tabs on him.
- That's curious.
I figured you two
for being very close.
- Well, we are.
Sort of.
- Sort of?
Well now.
Probably off with
his girlfriend.
- Charles doesn't
have a girlfriend.
- He doesn't?
Well, no dancing
car for him then.
You're the lady killer
in the family, huh?
- I don't know about that.
I'd say Charles has
more to account for
in that department.
- So, both your dad and
Charles' dad are dead?
- Yes, sir.
- [Homer] Heart attack for one,
drunk driving for
the other, tragic.
- It happens.
- [Homer] It does.
Doesn't make it any less tragic.
Right?
- Right.
Yeah.
- Nice place.
Good use of space.
- Thank you.
- What do you call this
style of architecture?
- Oh, I don't really know.
I guess it would be a--
I don't know.
(eerie suspenseful music)
- So, where were you the night
Genevieve Du Bois died, Thomas?
- Um.
What night was that again?
- Two nights ago.
- Oh, gee, let me think.
No, I can't remember.
- You know who I am.
- I looked you up.
- I figured you would.
So you know what
I can do, right?
You're not stupid, Mr. 160 IQ.
Best to be honest
with me, alright?
(eerie music)
- I know about the--
Charles took it, not me.
- I've got you, pal.
(eerie haunting music)
Let's make it easy.
(gun shot)
(groaning)
Shit!
I should've seen that coming.
- Mother?
- He talked too much.
- Mother, are you okay?
Come on.
You're okay.
Here's the bed.
Hop up.
Okay.
(moaning)
Here you are.
Can I get you anything.
- I'm fine.
- If there's anything,
I'd be happy to.
- No, I'm fine.
- I just, I feel like I should
probably explain a few--
- Just send Charles
in when he arrives.
- Why do you hate me?
With every word you say to me,
you spit poison.
You hate my fucking guts.
- Thomas, language!
- I try to be the
good son for you,
but you always want Charles.
Why is that?
- Alright.
Alright.
Could you get mumsie some
of her medicine, please?
- Of course, mother.
Mother--
Can I--
Can we talk about
what just happened?
- Best to forget it, I think.
- There's a police
officer bleeding to death
in our living room,
we can't just forget it.
The thing is, mother,
Charles and I,
We--
killed someone.
- I know.
- You what?
- It's called guilt,
you big pussy.
That's what you're feeling.
And you wonder why
I favor Charles.
- He told you.
Charles, he told you?
- Of course he told me.
He told me the
night it happened.
Especially how
you started acting
like a colicky
little baby about it.
You're just like
your mewling father.
Useless.
If I hadn't killed
him when I did,
he would've impregnated
that stupid secretary
of his for sure,
spreading more of his
garbage seed around.
- What are you saying, mother?
- Your father was a drunk.
It was easy to fake.
And Charles' father
was a genius, but--
He couldn't fuck
to save his life.
- Oh my God.
- Do you know how easy it is
to fake a heart attack, Thomas?
You could even pull it off.
- Mother?
Why?
- Because.
They weren't worthy, that's why.
I know the two of you
have been paying attention
to me over the years.
But somehow,
somehow I knew I'd
go wrong with you.
You had garbage genetics.
You've been my canker
sore ever since.
(crying)
- Jesus Christ.
- Oh, look at you.
Acting like one
of them even now.
You may have come
out of my cunt,
but you came out wrong.
- You killed my father?
- And I was happy to do it.
- But he loved me.
- Love isn't real.
Respect and fear, that's it.
Charles respects me
because he fears me.
But you--
You're different.
You're weak and powerless
and you yearn for
things that don't exist.
You may have acted
like Mr. Big and Bad,
but when the world opened up and
showed itself to you,
you shit your pants or ran
away like a little baby.
(sniffling)
You should just kill
yourself and be done with it.
Save us the trouble of
having to deal with you.
(eerie suspenseful music)
Oh good.
Shoot yourself in the head.
Pull a Hemingway.
Smartest thing
you could ever do.
I've been pushing Charles
for years to kill you,
but he wouldn't do it.
Damn idiot.
I should've aborted you
when I had the chance.
(laughing)
Really, Thomas?
You don't have the balls.
- You can't run away from
what you did, mother.
(talking on movie screen)
- Hey, fat guy.
(pounding)
Hold this.
Thank you.
(pounding and
dramatic horror music)
(eerie music)
(applause)
You like me.
You really like me.
(applause)
I want to thank my mother,
and Thomas,
and most of all,
I want to thank God.
Thank you.
(applause and cheering)
Goodnight!
(humming)
- Where were you?
- Where was I?
(dramatic horror music)
Oh, yeah.
I was turning water into wine.
- You're really the king of
the fucking idiots, aren't you?
(giggling)
- It's nice to see you too.
- You framed it?
- Yeah.
I had to go to three
separate craft stores
just to find the right size too.
- And you told mother.
What the hell were you thinking?
- What did you do?
Mother?
Mommy?
No.
No, no, no, no.
(sobbing)
What did you do?
(gunshots)
(crying)
You didn't have to kill her.
- Don't you see
what she did to us?
We're like this because of her.
- Like what?
- Delusional.
Crazy.
(suspenseful music)
- I'm
crazy.
(dramatic music and fighting)
She wasn't crazy.
You're crazy!
You're the crazy one!
- What happened to us?
What the hell happened to us?
- Everything!
Everything happened
to us, Thomas!
We were made for this!
Because we're smarter.
We're better.
All this other garbage
and conventional thinking,
we're beyond that.
We have the look.
- What look?
- I have the look!
Jeffrey Dahmer had it.
Ted Bundy had it.
And now, I do too.
The look of a confident
and untouchable being.
We've touched hands
with the divine, Thomas.
Our eyes
have been opened
by God.
- We were wrong.
We were so fucking wrong.
- There is no regret.
Not for us.
Not anymore.
Once you're born,
you can't go back.
- Stop talking, you're crazy.
You don't get to talk.
(dramatic horror music)
- Where are you going?
(fighting and suspenseful music)
- Get off, Charles.
(struggling and fighting)
- You're telling on us?
Huh?
You're gonna tell
on us like a little
snot-nosed tattle tale?
Huh?
You big mongoloid baby.
I swear to God, I could just
kill you right now, Thomas.
(screaming and dial tone)
Thomas!
- [Thomas] Let's
turn ourselves in.
- Stop this, Thomas.
We can bury mother and go back
to the way things were.
Nothing has to change.
- We can't run away
from what we did.
They're waiting for our call.
- Don't.
- We can ask for
a cell together.
They should be
able to grant that
if we cooperate.
- [Charles] Don't
call them, Thomas.
- It'll be okay, baby brother.
- Thomas, put the phone down.
- They said they'd go easy
on us if we confessed.
Everybody makes mistakes.
- Thomas, put down
the fucking phone.
- Language, Charles.
(gun shot)
- Tommy?
Oh shit.
Thomas?
Oh my God.
Tommy?
(crying and whimper)
Are you okay?
- I could use some
sunshine right about now.
- Okay.
Okay.
Sunshine, baby
It's sunshine
Time to wake up, baby
Open those
pretty little eyes
Oh, it's sunshine, baby
All for you, sunshine 떰
(crying)
- I love that song.
- What?
- It's okay, Charlie.
I can see her.
- See who?
- Genevieve.
She's there.
I can see her.
She says she forgives me.
(crying)
- Tommy?
Tommy?
Oh my God.
(crying)
Tommy!
(sobbing)
I'm so sorry.
(crying)
I don't know what the
fuck is wrong with me.
(sobbing)
I love you so much, Tommy.
Please don't go.
- Sorry, Charles.
(sobbing)
Goodbye.
(soft acoustic music)
(police sirens)
- Fuck!
(heavy breathing and sirens)
(heavy rain)
This ordeal will
seal your fate
(soft acoustic music)
- It's over, pal.
You can come back
to reality now.
After the storm
You'll transform
As the warm blood
coats your face
Just comply 떰
[music continues]