Subtitle created by - Aorion -
"The Accountant (2016)" ^ (Run time 02:07:54)
What the fuck?
Wait, let me call it in!
Move back!
Why are you doing this?
Take that, motherfucker!
Please.
Just fucking stop it!
Put your gun down!
Come on.
Please.
I'm fucking begging you.
I didn't touch him.
I didn't touch that old man.
I wasn't even...
the accountant
Buried on Sunday.
That was the end Of Solomon Grundy.
Solomon Grundy.
Justine, please.
It's called “stimming.”
It's self-stimulation
Where as, you and I might
tap our fingers, grind our teeth,
bite our nails.
Your son rocks back and forth.
It's more obvious,
but perfectly natural.
We came here, because we heard
you specialized in, in...
What is it?
What does he have?
Mm, not a fan of labels, ma'am.
Your son is a remarkable young man.
Who goes crazy when
you turn the vacuum on.
Wears one Tee-shirt.
Won't let you hug him.
Loud noises, bright lights
can be especially difficult
for someone like your son.
The shirt, most likely fabric sensitivity.
Hugging, closeness, touching,
that can be a challenge, yes.
When it's somebody else's child,
it's a challenge.
When it's yours,
it's a problem.
My practice focuses on education.
I like to work with your son
at his speed.
Help him develop the skills
he'll need to live a full life.
Communicating, eye contact,
understanding non-verbal cues;
making friends.
The only friend he has
is his little brother.
I'm sure moving from
base to base doesn't help.
My husband's in the Army,
which means we all are.
Would you be willing to let your son
stay with us for the summer.
Free of charge, working with me
in a sensory-friendly environment.
That's not going to happen.
If loud noises and bright lights
bother him, he needs more of it,
not less.
The world is not a
sensory-friendly place
and that's where he needs
to learn where to live.
Not in here.
Doctor, in your opinion.
Can our son lead a normal life?
Define normal.
I need to finish.
Solomon Grundy, born on a Monday,
Christened on Tuesday,
Married on Wednesday,
Took ill on Thursday,
Grew worse on Friday,
Died on Saturday,
Buried on Sunday.
I need to finish.
Solomon Grundy, born on a Monday,
Christened on Tuesday,
Married on Wednesday,
Took ill on Thursday,
Grew worse on Friday,
Died on Saturday...
Buried on Sunday.
I...
I never thought of
myself as a quitter.
I'm a...
4th generation farmer.
But, between...
the property taxes and
fertilizer cost,
insurance.
Ah, the hell with it.
What if...
just temporarily mind you,
we put this year's taxes
on our credit card?
Do you like it?
I made it myself.
No, not particularly.
You ever sell one?
At church fairs now and again.
Mrs Rice, you may have what the IRS
calls a “a home-based business.”
What room do you use in your house
when you made those?
I don't, really.
Just wherever I happen to be, I guess,
in front of the TV,
at the kitchen table...
I'll spread my beads out in the dining room
but Frank...
Yes, it would be better if
you could try to remember
the one specific space
that you use.
Your home is 29,13 square feet.
IRS code allows us to deduct
from your taxable income
a percentage of your work space
relative to your overall...
- What?
- Mr Rice.
How big is your dining room,
Mrs Rice's office?
I wouldn't so much
as call it an office...
It's...
approximately 200 uh...
- Make it 300 square feet.
- Excellent.
- Mrs Rice.
- Dolores.
Dolores, when you order supplies,
do you order online?
I don't, I just run over
to the beads store.
Example?
I drive, the truck.
The company truck.
Come in.
Mr. King, you've wandered so far
outside your legal purview.
As the president of Southern Trust Bank,
I intend to protect my customer's privacy...
Stop talking. You have a very
cavalier attitude for the president of a bank
with such a piss poor capital cushion.
Now, I want a record of every transaction
Abayed has had for the last two years;
deposits, withdrawals,
cashier checks, credit cards.
Birmingham or Bahrain,
it is now Treasury business.
Good bye.
Medina.
- Am I saying that correctly?
- Uh, Medina, yes sir.
I've read all your case files,
Director King.
It's impressive work.
Very.
Marybeth Ascension Medina.
Graduated University of Baltimore cum laude
with a degree in criminal justice.
2 years Baltimore PD as an analyst.
2 more at Homeland,
analyst again.
And the last 5 years
here at Treasury.
Analyst.
You did the heavy lifting on
Agent Lorenz's case last month.
I worked on it, yeah
but Agent Lorenz...
Why haven't you applied
for promotion to agent?
You've already doing the work.
Analyst is a good fit.
And I enjoy the work.
So...
Well, you're a liar, Medina.
Ward to the State of Maryland's foster care and
Juvenile Detention System from age 11 to 18.
Weapons chargers,  assault and battery.
Ouch, attempted murder.
Those records are sealed.
Is that a 9mm?
(Tattoo)
.45
You better sit your ass back down
in that chair, young lady.
This is a big moment for you.
Make a good choice.
Lying on a federal employment application
is a felony.
So, right now,
I'm the only thing standing between you
and significant prison time.
What do you want?
Do you like puzzles,
Marybeth Medina?
I meant what I said, son,
you're welcome out to the place anytime.
Do you fish? I got a two-acre pond
that is just thick with catfish and bass.
I don't fish.
I shoot.
Oh well, the farm's a perfect place
to do a little plinkin'. So...
Well, thank you.
You take care, son.
Thank you.
My daughter is meeting me for lunch.
I think you two just might hit it off.
Nice to see you.
Already enhanced.
It was taken 3 years ago in Antwerp
by an undercover Interpol agent.
Their target's on the far right.
Yeah, Zalmay Atta.
Go on.
Run the world's largest opium pipe line.
Ties to Karzai, Ghani,Taliban.
I mean he was considered untouchable.
Look at the rest.
Tell me what you see?
I remember most of these arrests...
they were huge.
Focus.
They're all not arrest.
It's the same man.
Lou Carrol.
For what it's worth.
It's an alias.
The Hong Kong photo
was backed about 5 years.
And that one, he's Carl Gauss.
Tokyo, Tel Aviv, Nepal,
there was a sighting in Tehran.
All describing the same man:
“an accountant,” “our accountant,”
“the accountant.”
“The Accountant”?
Like, “CPA accountant”?
Okay.
Say you're the head
of the Sinaloa Cartel.
Now, the cartel count their money
by weighing it in eighteen wheelers.
But one sunny Mexican day,
your in-house money-scrubber
comes to you and says
you're thirty million light.
Who can you trust to do the
forensic accounting, track your stolen cash?
Deloitte and Touche?
H&R Block?
You somehow, contact an individual capable
of coming in cold, un-cooking years of books...
and getting out alive.
I retire in seven months.
Before I do,
I need to know who he is.
How he does it.
I mean, who survives
this kind of clientele?
The secrets this guys has.
What exactly do you
want me to do?
Report directly to me.
No other case work.
No other Treasury personnel involve.
By the end of the month,
one of 2 things would have occurred.
Resolution of this case,
or we update your photo.
ZOLOFT 100 mg
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Where are you going?
Mom!
You just don't care.
You always control him!
Mom!
No!
Where are you going?
- We had help!
- Then stay.
- You threw it away!
- Stay here, don't go anywhere!
- Mom!
- Hey.
Hey.
That's it.
There we go.
Solomon Grundy,
- Born on Monday.
- Solomon Grundy.
- Alright?
- Born on a Monday,
Christened on Tuesday,
-There we go.
- Married on Wednesday,
Took ill on Thursday,
Worse on Friday,
Died on Saturday,
Buried on Sunday.
That was the end
Of Solomon Grundy.
Do it again.
Solomon Grundy, born on Monday,
Looks like somebody's seen
too many westerns.
Yeah, he must be what...
a mile out?
Not on my best day c...
Holy shit.
Okay, listen to me.
In... flec... tion, alright?
Listen, just listen to my tone.
I say,
"Oh, you look another year older."
"I don't know if I would ever
going to get out of this fucking place."
And you say.
You're probably right, Francis.
You're extremely most unlikely to survive your...
No, hold on.
That's not what you say.
2 years together every night,
you know.
I give you PhD in black money,
but you got to learn this.
- This is crucial.
- You're frustrated.
- What am I?
That's what I am.
I'm frustrated.
Good, good.
Excellent.
Finally.
Alright, let's do another one.
Lights out, ladies.
Lights out.
Names and addresses, go.
Cenyon Ivankov,
79 Primorsky Boulevard, Odessa.
The Meier brothers, Moushein and Tzak,
221 Sherwood Avenue, Jerusalem.
Dominick Rabito,
96 Court Street, Brooklyn.
Ask for Bobby.
You know, I'm old,
I may be remembering things
a little rosier than they were.
I mean if you want to fill out 1040s
and itemized deductions,
pulling 50 grand a year, I mean it's a living,
because if you go down this road, this road...
You can't go back, you understand?
It's dangerous, do you understand?
I understand.
You find one person
you can trust, just one.
And do not make my mistake,
you keep moving your ass around.
They gave me a new handler today.
I don't like this guy.
He's dull.
Worried.
Yeah, fuck it.
Good night, son.
Good night, Francis.
What about Zurich?
Or Saudi Arabia?
The Swiss are cheap.
Dubai is one thing but we're
too conspicuous in the Kingdom.
- I vote Chicago.
- Why?
There's an update in online chatter,
people looking for you.
- What people?
- The unfriendly kind.
Let try a legitimate client for once.
No cartels, arms brokers,
money launderers, assassins.
I like safe.
I like you safe.
Everyone's hiding something.
At least there's honor among thieves.
There is honor among
Illinois electronic manufacturers.
They're in your current backyard,
no risk of movement.
You'll meet?
Yeah, I'll meet.
One last piece of business.
Just the Renoir.
I don't have a buyer
for the Renoir.
The Pollock can move.
Will you ever let it go?
Hello?
Just the Renoir.
Drop the price.
Heavy sigh.
Go to work, Dreamboat.
Uh, Mr. Wolff, I half suspect
we're wasting your time.
I'm quite sure you're not.
And you know this how?
I'm on the clock.
Well, shit, I hope
we're not wasting ours then...
Look, kidding aside, I think if you saw
our books, you'd run for the hills.
We have an incredibly
complicated accounting system,
depreciation schedules on
hundreds of different items,
full time and contract employees,
Department of Defense classified accounts.
It's a numerical shitstorm.
I'll need to see all those books
for the past 10 years,
bank statements, a complete
list of clients and vendors,
hard copies printed out, my eyes only.
All the information is right here.
Okay, whoa, whoa.
Look.
This all came to my attention
only last week..
Now, a junior cost accountant stuck
her nose where it didn't belong
and obviously had no idea
what she was looking at.
Lamar's overreacting,
there is no missing money!
How long have you been
CFO of this company, sir?
15 years.
I need the books for the
past fifteen, please.
Well, you're goddamn blunt.
I'm Lamar Blackburn's oldest friend.
I've been by his side since he was turnin' out
RC robots that Radio Shack called crap.
I wouldn't take a dime
without his say so.
- You're angry.
- Oh, this is bullshit.
Unusual way of making contact
with you, Mr. Wolff.
You were recommended
by Mansoor Lakhani.
We custom made prosthetics for
this man's daughter.
You may know that she lost
both legs to a car bomb
outside his investment firm in Lahore.
He told my brother, Lamar,
that you were nothing short of supernatural.
Mr Lakhani holds advance degrees
in mathematics from Cambridge and Caltech.
Why does a man
like that need you?
I don't discuss client business.
Carl Gauss -
5 years ago Hong Kong
CARL FRIEDRICH GAUSS
The Prince of Mathematicians
Lou Carroll -
Colombia , Tehran,  Tel Aviv
Louis Carroll
What do you suppose that
young man is thinking right now?
Why do I still feel my arm?
How did everything
go so wrong so fast?
It's cold.
Turn up the heat.
Christian Wolff, I presume.
Mr. Blackburn.
Lamar.
Come with me.
Are you aware of
Living Robotics' three income streams?
Consumer electronics, next generation prosthetics,
unmanned military applications.
Prosthetics division showed
tremendous growth over the last 10 years,
it's seems to have matured.
Consumer product is your
highest source of revenue.
followed closely by Defense department
contracts, prosthetics sits on three.
You are well informed.
I never married.
Never had kids.
This company is my child.
That's it, money has never
been a motivation.
Balance sheets,
profit and loss statements.
My mind doesn't function
the way your's works.
I need you to be
my eyes and ears, Chris.
Whatever you need to do your job,
you let me know.
I'll start in the morning.
Zurich, Switzerland.
Son of a bitch.
Excuse me?
Who the fuck
do you think you are?
Do you know who
the fuck I am?
Simon Dewey.
The founder, CEO of Dewey Capital.
American.
Shocking.
I have kidnap insurance,
you obviously know that.
Sorry, but how would I
know that you have...
You people are fucking amazing...
You know, when you interrupt
somebody like that,
it makes them feel that you're just not
interested in what they have to say.
Or maybe you just think
what you have to say
is more important than
what I have to say.
Is that what you think?
That gun,
makes you a big man, does it?
This gun?
Come on.
I'm part of a potent department
of a private security force.
We have a client, it's called a...
European manufacturing concern.
You're shortening their stocks simultaneously,
spreading false rumors regarding
the harm of the company.
The result in declining stock price
has made you your millions, but...
It's been on my client's expense.
They have been forced to cut
hundreds of jobs, Simon.
These are third generation metal workers,
people with families.
Pensions are being rendered worthless
because of you.
But, you'll stop now, correct?
Which company?
Wrong answer, Simon.
Look..
Ow.
It's the same spot, Simon.
Why'd you let me hit you
in the same exact spot?
I only meant.
We all chose positions
on dozens of companies.
Shit, Simon.
I suppose, you spreading false information
about more than one company,
if that's what you're doing?
You just gonna have to stop
shortening them all.
That's ridiculous.
I can't be expected...
Alright, keep your chin up, son.
No pouting on my watch.
Yeah, you're a man,
You're just...
You're a man in your own way.
Alright, Simon.
I'm an avid reader
of the Journal.
So I expect cooperation
be reflected there.
Simon, are we good?
Yeah?
Good boy, Simon.
I'm proud of you.
Oh, hello.
Good morning.
Oh.
Hi.
- Um...
- Hi.
I'm Dana Cummings.
You're... the consultant, Mr. Wolff?
- Christian.
- Hi, Chris... tian. Um...
I'm Dana.
Cummings.
Yes.
Um...
These are all the files you wanted.
I cross-reference them
by year and alphabetical.
So...
It must have taken
you all night.
It sure did.
Right.
So...
So.
What do you want, Dana Cummings?
Oh, Mr. Blackburn,
um...
Sorry, he said I should...
I'm the person who first
noticed the missing...
- what I think was the missing money.
- Yes, I understand. I'll find it.
Yeah, I thought we could...
have lunch and...
I brought my lunch.
No, I bring my own lunch too.
I can answer any questions
that you have.
I have no questions.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, you want to...
- make your own assessment.
- Yes, thank you.
Okay.
Um...
I'm in accounting
if you need anything.
There is a...
some donuts there for you.
I don't eat donuts.
Okay.
Mr. Secretary.
Sir, there's been speculation that
your ability to link banks in South Florida
to money laundering efforts of terrorists
are actually the result of a whistle-blower?
Or the NSA?
You care to comment?
Let me turn this over to
the head of my task force
Financial Crimes Director, Raymond King.
Folks.
There's no great mystery here.
Nothing fancy.
Just team effort,
comprised of long hours of
good old-fashioned investigative work.
Question?
Please, Sorkis,
give me something.
I match the face of the man in the photo
to a surveillance video in the NYPD data base.
Wait wait wait...
NYPD?
What did you find?
2006, your guy takes out
2 mob enforcers with a steak knife
he lifted off from an Italian restaurant
down the street.
Then he strolls into a den of stone cold killers
and goes on a 7 mnn killing spree.
Using their own weapons.
Head shot, head shot,
head shot.
Sorkis, stop.
The den of stone cold
killers, where is this?
Ravenite, headquarters of the
Gambino crime family.
He killed Anthony,
"Little Tony" Bazzano.
Forensics list cause of death
as blunt force trauma.
Your boy kicked him in the head, once.
Again, play it again.
Hey, hey, hey.
I better call it in!
I also got an audio file here.
Inside of the Ravenite,
it was bugged.
Come on.
Please.
That's Little Tony.
I'm fucking begging.
I didn't touch him.
I didn't touch that old man!
Okay, give me the recording ASAP.
I wasn't even...
MB, you're an analyst for Treasury.
What the hell have you
got yourself into?
What do you have to hit
to dent a steel thermos?
It's just old.
How did you, um...
get into financial consulting?
Department of Labor statistics indicate it's
one of the fastest growing professions.
Actuarial sciences are experiencing
a tremendous growth as well.
Okay.
I like the balance of it.
You know, like finding things
that aren't obvious.
Plus my dad was an accountant.
He actually...
You know, he had
the whole schtick.
He..
You know, the little amortization book,
with the green eye-shade.
The, like dorky
pocket protector and...
I've got a pocket protector.
That's a nice one.
I mean, his was dorky, I guess.
Yours is nice.
Yeah, but he convinced me to go
into the field.
Because I wanted to study art.
At the Art Institute of Chicago. But...
Art doesn't pay the mortgage.
"Art doesn't pay the mortgage, young lady."
Dad's tastes ran more to
Dogs Playing Poker.
I like Dogs Playing Poker.
Because dogs would never bet on things.
So it's incongruous.
I like incongruity.
Yeah, Dogs Playing Poker is nice.
It's just sort of...
just different.
So I studied accounting at the University
of Chicago. “Where fun goes to die.”
Why?
Why what?
Why does fun go to die at
the University of Chicago?
Oh, no.
It's just an expression.
I'm joking.
Right.
- I'll leave you to it.
- Okay.
Let me know if you need
anything while you're here.
- Have a nice day!
- Yes, you too.
I'm fucking begging.
I didn't touch him.
I didn't touch that old man.
I wasn't even...
Okay..
Give me something.
I..
I'm fucking begging.
I didn't touch him.
I didn't touch that old man.
I wasn't even...
Subfloor Vocal Track Isolated
Solomon Grundy, born on Monday,
Christened on Tuesday,
Born on a Monday,
Married on Wednesday,
Come in. Come in. Come in.
You have to see this.
Look at this.
It's going to blow you away.
I mean, it'll just...
jump right out at you.
- There it is.
- Uh-huh.
Living Robotics, 10 years ago,
earnings before interest, tax, depreciation,
$14,495,719.
9 years ago. earning
before tax depreciation.
Revenues go up, profits go down.
No large capital expenditures
dragging profits down.
No spike in raw materials
or labor costs.
Year 8, profits and revenue
both go up,
but not at a comparable fashion.
X no longer equals Y.
6, 5, 4, 3.
You're making money
but there's a leak.
The leak is...
The leak.
Where's the leak?
SLEWITT manufacturing.
I signed these checks.
- Who authorized it?
- Ed... Mr. Chilton.
They make electronic assemblies for
the consumer division.
No, they don't.
Look at this.
You notice anything?
- Second number in each is a 3.
- Yeah.
Most people, when generating random numbers
tends to relies subconsciously on certain...
- ... patterns.
- Patterns. Yeah.
Yes.
- I was right.
- You were right.
- Yeah.
- Uh, I'm...
I went through these ledgers for months.
And I got through one fiscal year.
You went through 15.
Overnight.
It's not even the best part, look.
This part is...
They're routing money to a company
that doesn't exist.
And yet profits go up,
and they continue going up.
It absolutely makes no sense.
- Where's the money coming from?
- Where's the money coming from? Exactly!
- It's not inventory?
- Inventory checked out.
- Chargebacks to vendors?
- No, perfectly in order.
Internal offsets?
No, that's a terrible idea.
Um.
Cummings.
You're needed in whatever area
I'm paying you to be needed in.
Sorry.
And?
3 million, three hundred forty five...
6 million, three hundred ninety seven...
12 million...
Sixty one million, six hundred and seventy nine thousand...
$ 61,679,000 ...
and some change.
Who did it?
Best guess?
I don't guess.
You'll have a report for me?
When I'm finished,
yes.
Hey, Ed.
We're having lemon meringue pie.
And those two bottles of insulin.
I just thought that you'd appreciate
me treating you like an adult, right?
So here's what I got.
You administer your own accidental
insulin overdose, and just die
but do it with dignity.
Your wife whose sleeping upstairs,
she'll be the beneficiary of, what's got to be,
a very generous insurance policy,
am I right?
But the only way she's going
to collecting that policy, Ed,
is that we have the
appearance of an accident.
If we lay hands on you,
you're gonna fight, squeal,
she wakes up,
my hands are tied.
One accidental death is just that.
Two?
No, I'll have no choice but to
rock and roll a home invasion,
violate your wife
a dozen different ways,
kill you both, burn the
place to the ground.
I'm sorry for that.
Ed, Ed, Ed, hey.
Nobody's gonna violate your wife, okay?
Besides, what that would say
about me as a human being?
Physiologically, it's a non-starter.
Sometimes I think I just say shit,
say a poop comes out of my mouth.
I will however plug a .45
in your brainpan.
I don't mind commitments.
It's kind of sad you and your
sticky fingers probably find hard to grasp.
Make a decision, sir.
Where are you going?
Sir.
Stop that. Why're you doing that?
Stop that!
Sir.
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Mr. Chilton passed away.
I was told to
clean up the room.
What's happening?
Could you give us a minute, please?
This is the balance of your contract.
- I understand you're upset.
- Yes, I'm upset.
- But I haven't finished yet.
- Yes, you have.
Ed was a diabetic for 30 years.
You think he didn't know how
to check his blood sugar?
Whatever unresolved issues remain,
my friend was poisoned enough
by them to take his own life.
As far as I'm concerned
whatever he did is forgiven.
Please... I need to finish.
Please.
- Sorry, I'll come back.
- No, no. Come in, dear.
We're done.
You're very good, Mr. Wolff.
But, I hope our paths
never cross again.
I'm responsible for the
death of my best friend.
I'd prefer not to be
reminded of it.
Do you think that's true?
That Mr. Chilton killed himself?
That makes you think we're responsible?
It's very hard for me to interpret
what people do what they do.
This...
I'm not finished.
I mean look.
Look at this.
SIMOPS reports.
This is out of order.
They completely re-rearrange this.
I don't.
I...
I'm not finished.
Bye, Chris.
Again.
Enough.
They're not done.
Tomorrow is another day.
They have done their best.
If that were true, you would
be covered in blood and snort, not them.
Keep going.
Aggression correctly channel
overcomes a lot of flaws.
Tapping into that aggression requires
peeling back several layers of yourself.
It's my job to know
my son's limitations.
Get up.
It's your job to peel.
Do your job.
On your feet.
Again.
We could have went to his house.
Shot him in his home.
We would be on a plane by now.
Or on a security camera,
or some nosy neighbor's iPhone.
Call the bookkeeper in.
He's too far,
he won't hear...
- Now.
- ... me.
Let's go.
Get up.
Come on.
Move.
Come on, come on, come on.
Christian!
Chris!
Again.
Louder.
Chris...
- No! No! Please!
- What the fuck?
Dolores!
- She's coming with me.
- I say, stop it! Leave her be!
Shit!
We're all going together.
Just pull that truck around the back.
Let's go. Let's go!
Let's move.
Come on, drive!
Drive now!
What the fuck?
When I say the name of your employer,
you say ''Yes''.
Practice.
Yes.
Camorra... Juarez... Gambino...
Do you understand the rules?
My left pocket.
Kill you both,
that's all I know.
- Hello, Dreamboat.
- Dana's in danger.
Kill Christian Wolff.
Transfer all domestic accounts overseas.
- Current vehicle?
- F-150.
- Virus to triple Z?
- Wipe everything.
And... done.
In the D-O-T data base now...
reassigning the license and vin.
I have “George Boole” or
“Charles Babbage” in the queue.
Boole.
Obviously.
Silly of me.
What else?
She is not your problem.
Straight to the trailer,
hook it up and disappear.
There's no time,
only the trailer.
Address and phone number.
Get it.
She's not answering.
We could use a small box.
She looked bigger in the photo.
God!
God damn!
Bitch!
We should go.
Since when are accountants
difficult to ventilate?
Dead?
Are you crazy, what did he do?
Hit him over the head with an adding machine?
Oh God.
Alright, just...
Put me in touch with the client.
I'll handle this accountant myself.
Running isn't an option for me.
I can't just walk out on my life!
We've to go to the police!
That's what normal taxpaying people do!
The police can't protect you from someone
who could afford to return 61 million dollars.
Return?
What are you talking about, "Return".
The money was being put back.
Stay here.
What are you doing in here?
- Who are you?
- You can't... You should not be here.
Sit down.
Sit right there.
What is this place?
Panamerica Airstream.
34 feet 7 inches long.
8 feet 5 inches wide.
The dimensions which are perfectly
adequate for one person, preferable.
This is where you live?
No.
I don't live here.
This is a storage unit.
That would be weird.
That's what would be weird?
I just spend more time here.
However, I'm afraid some of
my clients have followed me.
Why would your clients follow you?
You're an accountant.
How do you know what to do here?
Why are you prepared for this?
Plus, this is on wheels.
Which means I could hook it and
be gone in 12 minutes, usually.
Sarcasm.
Is that sarcasm?
No, that's not sarcasm.
I don't use sarcasm material please.
Everything in the world that
is important to me, is in this trailer.
And right now, changing my routine
for you is jeopardizing that.
Tell me that's not
an original Pollock.
We should go.
Now.
- Medina.
- Ms. Medina.
This is Gordon Amundson
with the FBI Language Services.
Ah, yeah.
Anything luck?
It's an unusual audio file.
Solomon Grundy is a nursery rhyme,
circled in 1800s.
Your voice has four of the six intonation
patterns we use to define American English.
That's difficult to confirm with a rhyme.
Out of curiosity...
was your subject a trauma victim?
Um.
Why you ask that?
Well, you indicated on your submission,
that this event occurred
in a high-stress environment?
Yeah, exceptionally.
That's interesting.
The first was repeated
a total of four and a half times.
Zero variation in pitch, stem, tempo,
volume or articulatory precision.
So what does that mean exactly?
We often see this type of repetitive chanting
in children who have been exposed to trauma
or persons with neurodevelopmental disorders.
"Neurodevelopmental disorders?"
Fragile-X syndrome, autism.
Okay, so, let's say
I was looking at mug shots,
how would that present itself,
what exactly am I looking for?
Fragile-X, elongated face,
protruding ears, poor muscle tone.
Autism is nearly impossible
to identify visually.
The traits are behavioral.
Difficulty with social reaction and communication.
Lack of eye contact.
Okay.
- Good luck to you.
- Thanks.
Asperger's Syndrome
Mathematician
The Prince of Mathematicians
None of this makes sense.
Why go to the trouble of skimming
the money, if you're going to put it back?
Over the last 3 years, the number of invoices
submitted by Slewitt Manufacturing had declined.
Scared of getting caught?
Price hike?
The prices of consumer electronics
go down not up.
Right. Down, yeah.
Um...
I can't afford this.
I know.
My treat.
In the U.S, 104 men,
last name any standard derivation
if you were a mathematician
called Gauss.
Reported over $500,000
in any of the last 7 years.
Okay, go a million plus.
17.
Of the 17, how many
between the age of 25 to 45?
4.
Of those 4, only one
has an income stream
that's cash heavy or easily laundered.
And he...
died 3 years ago.
What's this?
Names of the 100
most famous mathematicians.
Look, we know what we're doing now.
So, just...
enter the names, narrow down
the search right off the map.
Male, Caucasian, 25 to 45.
Earning a million plus.
No investment income,
he'll concentrate on cash.
What's in it for me?
Look, if you help me find him,
I'll see what I can do
about getting you out of here.
Please.
Single avowal or filed jointly.
Hey, those paintings in your trailer,
- They're real, right?
- Yes.
You didn't buy them
at auction. Did they?
They were a form of payment.
Right.
Hey.
Thank you.
At my apartment.
Oh
Yeah.
Can we sit down for a second?
Okay.
Just...
have a sit.
How do you...?
You know...
How to...?
My father was an officer, in the Army.
Psychological operations.
He was concerned I might be
taken advantage of somehow,
so he arranged for me to train with...
under a specialist, during my childhood.
We live in 34 homes in 17 years.
- You moved 34 times?
- Mm.
God, that's extraordinary.
Now I'm sure it must
have been difficult.
I've never been anywhere.
Only Cancun,
not my proudest moment.
Um.
I just mean...
Your life is... unique.
It's not unique, I have...
high functioning form of autism
Which...
means I have an
extremely narrow focus,
and a hard time abandoning tasks
once I've taken them up.
I have difficulties socializing
with other people I don't know,
but I want to.
When I was a senior
in high school.
I wanted this
special dress for prom.
I told myself that spending
a hundred bucks on a trashy dress
that I was going to wear
one time to an event
that I thought was silly
in the first place,
- it's just...
- Wasteful.
Yes.
But Vera Wang made this
black strapless classic,
it was more expensive but you could
wear it to all kinds of future events.
- It's an investment.
- Yes!
Where were you when
I was in high school?
Oh, North Carolina.
Israel.
Right.
Um.
The problem is. They wanted
$1700 dollars for this dress,
and I didn't have that so...
- You asked your parents?
- No.
Hang on.
Black Jack.
I never played a hand but I...
went to the library and checked out
all these books on strategy.
And I turned the Naperville North
math club into a little Vegas!
- What's a "math club"?
- Math club.
You compete against other schools.
Theory and speed math.
Like what's 298,567 times 92.
27,468,164.
Right.
Um.
Black Jack.
I could tell you when to hit,
stand, split, re-split,
then moved on to card counting,
shuffle tracking, hole carding.
And I took everything I had,
which is $183 dollars,
and I drove down to
Harrahs in Joliet.
- Why was this dress so important to you?
- It wasn't about the dress.
I just wanted to walk into that gym
and have everybody say “Wow.”
I was trying to...
Hold on.
I was trying to connect.
I think no matter how different,
we're all trying to do the same thing.
But I... I lost all but 20 bucks
in the first 10 minutes.
Fed that into a nickel slot
on the way out and I won 2 grand.
I used the extra cash
to pay for a limo.
Only wore the dress
just the one time.
Chris, why are we here?
Um...
I thought this hotel
had good water pressure.
The Holiday Inn Express in Aurora
has good water pressure.
Yes, but these towels are very fancy.
Cheaper hotels have scratchy towels.
And...
I wanted you to like it.
Crazy Eddie and the Panama Pump.
Crazy Eddie Antar and the Panama Pump.
Have you ever heard of it?
What?
Crazy Eddie Antar!
He owned a...
a string of electronics stores
on New York City in the '80s.
Crazy Eddie Antar, he started stealing
almost as soon as he opened his business.
Okay, I'm not following.
He deposited money in Tel Aviv,
then he cycled them
through Panama and
bring back into his stores.
Okay, why? Why take
it out and put it back?
Well, initially he was just stealing and
garden-variety taxes evasion.
But he came up
with a better idea.
You see,
by taking his own money,
stealing it and putting it
back on his books.
It was raining cash.
He took the company public at
eight dollars a share.
A year later it was
trading at seventy-five.
Rita's taking Living Robotics public.
Yes.
But why would she hire you in the first
place if she thought you'd figure it out?
I don't know.
I'll have to ask her.
Whatever Rita's involve in,
it's not your concern.
You disappear,
I make a call.
Please.
I'm worried about you.
If I don't do something,
Dana will die.
Risking your life for a girl
you known a week.
Why?
Heavy sigh.
What's the plan?
Find the person who
wants to kill her.
And?
Shoot him in the head.
Last one.
Two "FF"s.
Christian.
245 men.
Four with incomes over a million.
All over the age of sixty.
Sorry.
But...
your guy's an accountant.
Two Christian Wolffs own CPA first .
The first Christian Wolff,
owns Wolff Accounting,
121 South Street,
Scottsdale, Arizona.
Income of 435 grand.
It's a good year.
So good, we audited
him 2 years ago.
He's clean.
The other Christian Wolff.
Nope.
Only 75 grand.
ZZZ Accounting.
Wabash Way, Plainfield, Illinois.
ZZZ, it's not exactly
a smart Yellow pages move.
Wait a second.
Who filed the returns for Kim's nails,
Wabash Way, Plainfield
ZZZ Accounting.
- Could just be the neighbor...
- Great Mandarin, Wabash.
ZZZ Accounting.
Paul's Laundromat.
- ZZZ Accounting.
Tell me they are all
registered as partnerships.
Everyone.
Managing partner: Christian Wolff.
- Christian Wolff.
- What?
Christian Wolff, last year ran
$75,543 through his accounting firm...
Whoa.
Who is Christian Wolff?
The accountant.
Well...
- 75 grand, that's chump change.
- Agreed, but...
He ran another $287,765
through Kim's Nails,
$445,112 trough Great Mandarin Chinese,
and you'll love this...
$505,909 through Paul's Laundromat.
Paul's Laundromat?!
Are you fucking kidding me?
He's playing with us.
He can't clean that kind of money
through an accounting firm.
The paper trail's too heavy.
So he's laundering it
through cash businesses.
All of those were in the
same strip mall south of Chicago.
ZZZ?
I mean, he doesn't care about the traffic,
it's a front,
All of it. “Christian Wolff,”
"Carl Gauss", “Lou ‘Lewis' Carroll.”
He's using the names of famous
mathematicians as a cover.
Charitable Contributions here to
Harbor Neuroscience last year alone,
- that's got to come to close to...
-  One million one hundred dollars.
That one's not a cover.
That's the real deal, I've checked.
So you're telling me this guy risks
his life doing forensic accounting
for some of the scariest people
on the planet,
collect his fee, goes to
all the trouble laundering it
and then gives
almost all of it away.
What if he's taking
other means of payment?
Yeah.
Possible, yeah.
I caught him, Ray.
Maybe.
Pack your bag.
We're going to Chicago.
90% probability they are
all right-handed.
It was an accident.
To me it's stand forth, right wrist.
Thought maybe you enjoy waiting
in the schoolyard sucker punch.
Life is a series of choices,
none of which are new.
The oldest is choosing
to be a victim
or choose not to.
Second oldest, loyalty.
Family first, good times or bad.
Bonjour, fellows.
- Yeah!
- Let's see what he's got, yeah.
They are new glasses.
You think if... you don't fight back,
then maybe they'll like you?
Stop picking on you,
calling you freak?
Here's what it is.
They don't like you,
they don't dislike you.
They are afraid of you.
You're different.
Sooner or later
different scares people.
Victim or not?
Make your decision.
Go.
You're different.
Sooner or later
different scares people.
In here.
.357 Colt Python.
Serial number's gone.
Hydra-Shok
Wireless security cam.
Infrared, weatherproof.
He's got a network of them.
The whole backyard he's got eyes.
This is our guy.
So why is a guy who's up to
his elbows in cash live here?
Given his clientele, he figures
blending in will extend his shelf life.
It's the smart move.
Well, maybe not smart enough.
I take security cameras back here.
Anybody can roll up
from the front.
How does he cover this?
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
Don't see that everyday.
Boys, let's have a situation report.
Are we good, Ike?
All clear.
Rock and roll.
And how about you, sport?
It's Bobby.
I got nothing.
Is all this really necessary?
You should be
watching his home.
Yeah. That what you think?
That your idea of a subject.
I love it when people tell me
how to do my job.
I believe I recommended you
to leave the country.
- You declined.
- He's an accountant!
I could see it in his eyes.
The freak wasn't
going to let it go.
- Give my best to Michelle.
- I will.
I was old 10 years ago.
So what's your story, Medina?
You know my story.
I know what the Court said.
I stuffed a handful of cocaine
up a drug dealer's nose.
Pistol-whipped him
in the trunk of his car.
I was seventeen.
It was August.
He coked for three days,
but lived.
Do you regret it?
The coke was half borax.
Same shit he kept
selling me sister.
She's a dental hygienist
in Annapolis now.
Married with 3 kids.
And, I don't regret it.
That's rough.
All due respect, Director King,
what the fuck do you
know about Wolff?
- Wait, let me call it in!
- Move back!
What don't you tell me, Medina?
Hey!
Men kill each other
for any number of reasons.
Money, power,
fear.
Right there, motherfucker!
9 men had died
that day at the Ravenite.
But for none of those reasons.
They had taken something from
the man who was killing them.
Something that couldn't be
made whole again.
Something very important to him.
And he was there
for his pound of flesh.
Please.
Just fucking stop, man!
Put the gun down!
"Little Tony" Bazzano.
I'd been wasting
in a van for 6 months
listening to that arrogant little prick
belch, fart, and brag.
I didn't recognize his voice
with all the fear in it.
I didn't touch him.
I didn't touch that old man.
I wasn't even...
Our man had come for revenge
and he got it.
Nine dead.
And I was tenth.
Your name?
Ray.
Raymond King.
Who employs you, Raymond King?
I'm a Treasury Agent.
Are you a good one?
No.
No. Not particularly.
Is that it?
Kids. I got...
I'm a dad.
I got 2 kids.
Grown?
Yeah.
Yes. Yes.
They're all... They're all grown up.
Were you a good dad, Rayond King?
Yeah.
I've been a good dad.
I'm a lousy agent
and I've been a weak man,
but that...
that I didn't screw up.
That I got right.
Imagine you were a Treasury agent
approaching the twilight of a
spectacularly dismal career...
And then one day...
that break you should've been
looking for...
Francis Silveberg, the black money legend,
who cleaned cash from
Monte Carlo to Havana to Vegas.
He kept the books for the
Gambino family for forty plus years.
Until one day, the boss,
"Big Tony" Bazzano,
thought maybe the old man's age
made him vulnerable to prosecution.
Ordered his son, "Little Tony",
to kill Francis.
Kid fucked it up.
Francis ran, became a was a federal informant
in return for protective custody.
It could've turned my career around
only If I had listened.
I didn't.
He was processed out.
And he lost the only
protection he had.
Please stand clear of the gate.
The protection that he was promised
when he testified against "Big Tony".
And this time,
"Little Tony" got it right.
He had Francis
in a couple of hours.
down in a filthy basement in the Bronx,
nailed to a chair,
tortured to death.
So I...
volunteered for a joint task force,
Sat outside the Ravenite
surveillance van for months
hoping to get a shred of evidence
to use against Francis's killers.
Wait, wait,
let me call it in!
Move back!
I went in there hoping
I could ease my guilt.
And I met our accountant.
Why he let me live,
I didn't know .
But he changed my life.
I gave my notice
to the department.
I started looking forward
to the day again.
You know,
feeling the sun on my face.
Quit drinking.
I was on my way out the door...
and then the phone rang.
Ray King.
I'll never forget that voice.
Do you like puzzles, Raymond King?
She tells me she works
for the accountant.
And that a shipping container
packed with Chinese nationals
is passing through
the Port of New York.
A few months later,
one ton of uncut Juarez Cartel product
is entering Miami.
All those cases you put together.
Smoke and mirrors.
So, who is he...
this “accountant”?
Prisoner 831,
Fort Leavenworth maximum security.
Military prison?
So he was in the army.
Army lent him to us to track
Al-Qaeda money launderers
He was transferred from Leavenworth
to our detention center in DC.
Did the work of five men.
Data Mining, Basket Analysis.
He roomed with Francis.
They kept to themselves.
Played chess. Ate together.
Sat in a TV room together.
They were inseparable.
And then one day, a guard
told Wolff why Francis
hadn't called or written
since he got out.
And his burned body had been found
on a Staten Island landfill.
Wolff snapped,
went after the guard.
He fractured the man's skull
with a thermos.
Escaped from a
third-floor window.
Took the thermos.
That's all you got?
- I mean, Leavenworth, they would have military...
- Records are all heavily redacted.
Well then, arrest records, something.
Spring of 2003, at a funeral home
in Kankakee, Illinois.
Our boy sent 6 locals to the hospital
with a variety of injuries.
No one knew Wolff.
The older man who came with him
was identified as a colonel, US Army.
Funeral home.
Whose wake?
One customer that day.
Mrs. Lauren Alton.
Mrs. Alton taught first grade
for 13 years in Kankakee.
Survived by a husband
and two boys, ages 12 and 10.
By all accounts,
an ordinary life, well-lived
but cut short.
Excuse me, sir.
This is family only.
Sir, please come over.
I'll have to ask you to step outside.
And then a fight breaks out.
A brawl really.
Over what, the authorities never...
get down.
Get your hands off me.
Deputies respond.
A barney fife type squares off
with our boy gets rattled, pulls his gun.
The colonel just stepped in front
of the 83 weapon.
Army collected both men.
Police report named
Wolff as "Soldier one".
The widower identified the colonel by name.
His late wife's former husband.
I've checked, it's an alias.
No more real than "Christian Wolff."
She was the dead colonel's ex-wife.
And you think
Wolff is what to him?
Were you a good dad?
Ray King?
I've given up trying to figure out
when I'll get a call.
The why though,
that I got.
Someone breaks his moral code.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm retiring in a few months.
When she calls...
somebody needs to be
there to answer.
No.
He's a criminal, Ray.
Yeah.
He aids and abets drug cartels,
money launderers.
He's a fucking killer.
Believe me, I've wrestled
with the same decision.
But when I got
that first call,
I realized something.
I spent my whole life only recognizing
my lucky breaks after they were gone.
The Brit, who is she?
Hello?
Miss. Medina,
tell Eliot Ness to get
his feet off the furniture.
He's not in a barn.
Living Robotics.
Write it down.
More than 6 feet, short hair,
athletic build, yes?
Correct.
When you say short hair,
you mean short hair like my hair?
- Or you mean short hair like short hair?
- You... What's the difference?
I was told you could fix this,
so fix it!
But you did speak to the man, am I right?
You spoke to him.
What did he sound like?
We made small talk,
what's it matter what he sounds like?
That's Ike, right?
Is it north side?
Yo Bobby, was that you?
Bob.
Bobby.
Ike, are you there?
Ike?
Guys, stop fucking around, someone answer me.
Course to the left.
You might consider using a round
with superior ballistic coefficient.
Give me the layout
of the home.
Points of entry,
corridors, rooms, cover.
Go.
Fuck!
Sit down.
- What's this all...?
- Shut up and sit down in the chair.
You ever see a magic green round
traveling 3000 feet per second
go through a window?
Nobody does.
Get down, now!
4 men, front entrance.
Go right at him, go now.
You,
I got the cameras.
Go join your friends.
Up!
Clear.
Smoke.
Move!
Go!
Man down!
I'm at the front entrance,
pinned down!
Are they dead?
I need situation info.
How many down?
Are they dead?
Answer me!
Okay, he's on the roof.
Now, follow me, let's move.
Check the skylight.
Check the window.
When that motherfucker comes in,
I want to hear gun shots,
and I want to hear
"Target eliminated".
That's enough.
He's in the god damn house!
Get out there and end this!
Brax, give me a situation report.
Have you got eyes on anything?
What's happening?
Say something!
Solomon Grundy,
Born on a Monday,
Christened on Tuesday,
Married on Wednesday,
Took ill on Thursday,
Grew worse on Friday,
Died on Saturday,
Buried on Sunday,
That was the end,
Of Solomon Grundy.
WHAT IS THIS?
Hey! Hey!
Stand down!
Fuck off!
Hello, Braxton.
Don't...
Don't do that.
I've been looking for you for 10 years,
and you're going to come at me like
we just saw each other yesterday.
That's what you got to do?
But...this.
Well, I think...
Well, I think that you're going to be
happy to see me, I guess.
I am happy.
I need to finish.
You should go.
I should go?
Okay, I...
Okay, I'll just go.
But first I'm gonna
ask you a question.
You're going to
give me an answer.
Why would you and Pop
go to that funeral?
She left us, did you not remember that?
Did you not remember that!
It's your fault that
Pop's dead, you hear me?
- It's your fault!
- I'm sorry, Braxton.
You're sorry?
Sorry doesn't cut it, you weird fuck!
Shit.
You don't give a shit about me.
How about now?
Are you going to fight?
Fight!
I'm sorry, Braxton.
You know, If you had to see her...
If that was something
that you had to do.
You call me.
I'm your brother.
I always have your back.
You don't call him,
you call me.
Did you even wonder
where I was?
I know where you were.
I just wanted you
to be safe.
Some of my clients are...
quite dangerous.
I kind of consider
fairly dangerous myself.
Well, you've made an improvement.
Shit, man.
You and me here,
- Yeah, it's...
- Well, statistically speaking...
Christ, man!
It's rhetorical.
I mean, really?
I was just saying.
Not happy.
Do you consider what you
do important, Mr. Wolff?
To someone other than yourself,
I mean.
What I do is.
Living Robotics public offering
would have been worth billions.
Money to be used for
neuroprosthetics, nanotechnology.
You?
Why in god's name
did I ever hire you?
To leak-proof your books.
Dana found a mistake, and you wanted
to be sure it's safe to go public.
And now you want to kill her.
I'm fond of Dana.
But I restore lives, not Dana!
ME!
Men, women, children.
I give them hope.
Make them whole.
Do you even know
what that's like?
Yes, I do.
Sorry.
I missed you.
I missed you too, Braxton.
I missed you too
because I love you.
You're my brother.
Maybe...
Would you want to...
Maybe I can see you
in a week?
Name the place,
I'll be there.
How will I find you?
You won't.
I'll find you.
Helen.
How do you responds to rumors
that some of the victims had wounds
consistent with anti-aircraft rounds?
I'd say the Chicago police department
has ample experience
solving all manner of homicides.
Sir, how are the conspiracy
and fraud charges related to
the deaths of Lamar Blackburn
and his sister, Rita?
This is a very fluid situation.
With a lot of surprising revelations
over the last 48 hours.
Let me introduce you to the person
leading the investigation.
Agent Medina.
Good afternoon.
As much as I
like to take credit for this,
I can't.
Because this was...
a team effort,
comprised of long hours of good
old-fashioned investigative work.
Questions?
Can we get more information...
Harbor Neuroscience
Hanover, New Hampshire
He was just like our other two,
he was a happy baby.
Now, he rarely speaks.
It's like, our child is missing.
He's not there.
He's lost and he needs our help.
We thought...
we hoped that he'd catch back up,
but he didn't.
1 in 68 children in this country are
diagnosed with a form of autism.
But if you can put aside for a moment
what your pediatrician
and all the other NT's
have said about your son...
“NT's”?
“Neuro-typicals.”
The rest of us.
What if we're wrong?
What if we've been using the wrong tests
to quantify intelligence in children with autism?
Your son's not less-than.
He's different.
Now, your expectations for your son
may change over time,
they might include marriage,
children, self-sufficiency.
They might not.
But I guarantee you.
If we let the world set
expectations for our children,
they'll start low
and they'll stay there.
Maybe your son is capable
of much more than you know.
And maybe...
Just maybe...
He doesn't understand
how to tell us.
Or...
we haven't yet
learned how to listen.
Hey, honey, for the hundredth time,
don't wonder off like that.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's alright. It's fine.
Can he visit with you
for a while, Justine?
Okay, good.
- C'mon, folks, I'll give you the nickel tour.
- You okay with that?
It's okay.
Come on.
Oh, he'll be fine.
Justine's one of our few
full-time residents.
She stopped talking 30 years ago,
communicates with a digital translator now.
Doctor, how is Harbor funded?
We are fortunate to have
very generous private donors.
- I'll say they're generous.
- Why is that?
- That woman, Justine.
- My daughter.
She's your daughter?
The reason I started the Institute.
Justine's computer, it's a BX-32.
Water-cool, 12 Core.
That's right, you're a software engineer.
Well, some of our donors are
more generous than others.
Why?
Is that a good computer?
Good?
Doc, she could backdoor
the Pentagon with that rig.
Hello, Dreamboat.
Shall we chat?
- Hi.
Sign here, please.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Subtitle created by - Aorion -