♫ See the ponies trottin' down the street ♫
♫ Equestria is where they wanna meet ♫
♫ They all know where they wanna go ♫
♫ And they're trottin' in time ♫
♫ And they're trottin', yeah ♫
♫ They got the beat ♫
♫ Yeah, they got the beat ♫
♫ Go-go music really makes us dance ♫
♫ Do the pony puts us in a trance ♫
♫ Do watusi just give us a chance ♫
♫ That's when we fall in line ♫
♫ 'Cause ♫
♫ We got the beat ♫
♫ Yeah, we got it! ♫
Excuse me! Dragon on the move!
Important Princess Documents coming through!
Wow! Everypony from Manehattan to Saddle Arabia is here!
I know, filly - we almost couldn't book a stable!
Princess Twilight must have her
hooves full with this giant festival!
Are you kidding?!
She's smart and organized and cool under pressure,
there's nothing she can't handle!
Ohm... my goodness
I can't handle this!
Ooo, nothing is working!!
I just have to get it together.
Just go in there. And ask.
This is YOUR Friendship Festival.
Everypony's happiness rests in your hooves!
Oohhh.
OK, Twilight.
Got all your charts and graphs!
Oh, thank goodness you're here, Spike!
I'm just so nervous about this meeting!
Wha'chu talkin' about?
I'm about to ask the three most royal princesses of Equestria for a
HUGE favor!
What if they reject me?!
It'll be fine!
Just remember the most important thing!
Smile??!!!
Uh. No!
You're a princess, too!
Right.
Good morning Princesses!
Thank you all for seeing me.
I have an idea that I think will
make our Friendship Festival the
most wonderful celebration Equestria has ever seen!
Yes, Twilight, we are very excited.
Ponies have been arriving from all
over all morning!
I'd like to think it's to see us,
but Songbird Serenade
might be the bigger attraction.
Yes, she is the “mane event”
...and to make it extra special,
I could use your help!
Spike?
Songbird Serenade's performance is
not scheduled to start until
after you begin the sunset
and based on my precise calculation,
to get the very best lighting for the stage...
Princess Celestia, I was hoping you
could make sure the sun stays about
28.1 degrees to the South.
And Princess Luna
if you could raise the moon 62 degrees to the
North at the same time,
it would reflect the sunlight on the other
side and really frame the entire stage perfectly!
I...
But wait... there's more!
Cadance, if you could use your
crystal magic to create an aurora above the stage,
the sun AND the moon will shine through it
and create a truly amazing light show!
Presenting: Songbird Serenade!
Yah, yah yah, Woo ho...
Whoooaaaaa!! Oof!
Ta-da...
So, you're saying you want us to
move the sun and the moon...
for the party?
Well, I'd do it myself except I
don't have your magic!
Twilight, each of us uses our powers
to serve Equestria in our own way.
You are the Princess of Friendship.
You already have all the magic you need.
So... that'd be a no?
YES!
Skies cleared and ready for the festival!
WHOA!!
Heads-up, Fluttershy!
OUT OF CONTROL BALLOON!!
Oh! I don't think it's the balloon
that's out of control, Pinkie Pie.
Hey y'all!
Anypony up for some free samples
of my family's applecider?
Thank you!
Loved it!
Wow, Rarity, that's a fine job you're doing there.
'Course it might not get done
'til AFTER the concert!
Applejack, darling, anypony can do
“fine.”
Twilight asked me, so
clearly, she's going for fabulous.
And fabulous takes time.
Fabulous takes FOREVER. But awesome...
...can get done in four seconds flat!
Faster if I do my Sonic Rainboom!
Ahh!
No
No!
Don't you DARE, Rainbow Dash!
It looks wretched enough already.
Oh, come on, it's fine.
IF you were raised in a barn.
No offense, Applejack.
None taken.
'Specially since I
wasn't raised in a barn.
My family
just happens to have a barn.
Where I was born.
And spent most of my formative years...
Raised in a barn!
Okay, just two hundred and eighteen
things left to do and we're ready!
Hey Twilight...
Hello Spike.
Uh, hi Rarity.
How'd it go with the other
princesses? They like your idea?
I bet they loved it!!
Not exactly. They think I can make
today perfect without their magic.
And they are absolutely right, darling!
This festival is your brilliant idea,
and we know you're up to the task.
But what if I'm not?
What if Songbird Serenade hates the stage?
Or nopony makes a new friend?!
And if I fail at the festival, then who am I?!?
Twilight... look at me.
This, will be the biggest celebration
Equestria has ever seen!
As the Princess of Friendship,
you CANNOT fail.
This day will DEFINE who you are!
The pressure is INTENSE!
It's almost too much for any single pony to handle!
AHHH!
But you have us!
So stop worrying!
♫ It's time to show 'em what you've got ♫
♫ It's time to go and get things done ♫
♫ But you don't have to do it on your own... ♫
♫ 'Cause you've got friends right here to make it fun ♫
♫ We got this, ♫
♫ You got this ♫
♫ We got this together ♫
♫ Sometime the pressure gets you down ♫
♫ And the clouds are dark and grey ♫
♫ Just kick 'em off and let the sun shine through ♫
♫ And scary as it seems ♫
♫ More help is on the way ♫
♫ Cuz friends have friends that
want to help out too ♫
♫ We got this ♫
♫ You got this ♫
♫ We got this together ♫
♫ It's the Festival of Friendship ♫
♫ And we can get it done ♫
♫ A Festival that they won't forget ♫
♫ A party to be proud of ♫
♫ A day of games and fun ♫
♫ Just you wait and see ♫
♫ A magic day in perfect harmony ♫
♫ You got this ♫
♫ We got this together! ♫
♫ With friends and family you are never alone ♫
♫ If you need help we've got your back ♫
♫ You can be honest let your problem be known ♫
♫ 'Cause you got us ♫
♫ To pick up the slack ♫
♫ We got this ♫
♫ Eyup! ♫
♫ We got this together ♫
♫ Pay attention to the details ♫
♫ Every gem even spaced ♫
♫ Make the colors perfect ♫
♫ Taking one or two to taste ♫
♫ Inside and out ♫
♫ Beautiful throughout ♫
♫ Generosity is what we're all about ♫
♫ We got this ♫
♫ You got this ♫
♫ We got this together ♫
♫ Today needs to be perfect ♫
♫ It all comes down to me ♫
♫ I don't know if I'm ready ♫
♫ For all the things they need me to be ♫
♫ I am the princess of friendship ♫
♫ But that is more than just a crown ♫
♫ It's a promise to bring ponies together ♫
♫ And never let any pony down ♫
♫ We've got an awful lot to bake ♫
♫ Each pony needs a piece of cake ♫
♫ Oh, wait! There's something better... ♫
♫ ... We can do ♫
♫ We're gonna need some more supplies ♫
♫ To make a really big surprise ♫
♫ She'll be so shocked... ♫
♫ She's sure to love it too ♫
♫ You got this ♫
♫ We got this together ♫
♫ It's the Festival of Friendship ♫
♫ Together we are one ♫
♫ A day we will never forget ♫
♫ And now everything is ready ♫
♫ So when the day is done ♫
♫ The weather ♫
♫ The banquet ♫
♫ The style ♫
♫ And music ♫
♫ All will be in perfect harmony! ♫
Pinkie!
Oopsie!
Guess my easy bake confetti cake cannon
needs a little bit more fine tuning.
Songbird Serenade!
Is it really her?
It is, it is!
Hiya!
I'm looking for the pony in charge?
I need to set up for my sound check.
Songbird Serenade?
Um, I was just going to check on you...
I'm Princess Twilight.
And sorry about the mess.
I'm usually not so...
(How embarrassing!)
Caked in... cake?
Heh heh.
You have visual on buttercream?
Visual confirmed, go for clean-up.
Storm clouds?!
I ordered perfect weather!
Rainbow Dash?!
Uh...
I... don't think those are storm clouds!
Ooh! I bet those are the clowns I ordered!
Or definitely NOT the clowns
I ordered.
Brian..
No!
Ponies of Equestria...
We come on behalf of the fearsome,
The powerful,
The almighty...
...Storm King!!
And now,
To deliver the evil, evil message:
Put your hooves together
for COMMANDER TEMPEST!!
Is that a... unicorn?
I think so, but what happened to
her horn?
Tempest, is it?
How may we help you?
Ah, I'm so glad you asked...
How about we start with your
complete and total surrender.
Hi there, Princess of Friendship.
Not exactly sure what's going on,
but I know we can talk things out.
Oh goodie.
All four princesses.
Here's the deal, ladies,
I need your magic.
Give it up nicely, please...
...or we make it difficult...
For everyone!
And why should we cower before you?
There's one of you, and hundreds of us.
I was hoping you'd choose...
...difficult.
AHH!!
Cadance!
I can't stop it!
Luna, quick!
Go south!
Beyond the badlands!
Seek help from the Queen
of the Hippo...
LUNA!
Twilight!
Easy as pie.
Oh I love pie.
Oh, you TOTALLY got the last princess!
That's not the Princess.
Grubber!
Get.
Her.
NOW!
GUYS, WE GOTTA GET THE PRINCESS!!
Over here y'all!
C'mon!
Which one of you guys are going down there?
I would, but I just had a hearty meal
and I will sink and
I WILL side cramp.
I'm very big boned
I sink quick.
Everypony OK?
I think my bottom's on backward.
We just got our cupcakes handed to
us by the worst party crasher ever!
We gotta go back there and fight!
You saw the size of those goons!
You seriously wanna go BACK?!
So now what?
We can't hide here forever,
and let's be honest,
We can't go back...
Look what they did to the princesses.
We've got to keep them from Twilight.
The queen...
Yeah, the Queen!
Uh, what queen?
Celestia told Luna to find the
Queen of the...
Hippos.
Luna can't, so I have to.
Uh, hippos?? Seriously?
I've heard they're surprisingly
graceful for their size!
But they're always hungry.
Hungry?
Hippos?
They're somewhere South... past the badlands.
That means we'll have to... leave Equestria!
I'm not even packed!
I understand you're scared.
And nopony else has to go.
But I have to find this Queen.
She might be our only hope.
Well, you're not getting ALL the glory.
We're in this together.
We got yer back!
Indeedy!
I am ready to save Equestria!
Yay!
We're all behind you, Twilight!
Let's go find this Hippo!
Uh... South?
Boingy boingy boingy boingy boingy!
Anypony up for a game of “I SPY?”
No really, come on!
I Spy, with my little eye,
something that is orange.
No takers?
It's you, Applejack!
All this power, wasted on parties.
When there are far greater uses.
Well, answer it!
Where am I supposed to be looking.
I never understand how this spell works!
TEMPEST!
Over here, Your Excellency.
Where?!
Over here.
Huh?!
No, no, right.
Look right.
My right?
Yep.
Oh, there you are.
Here's the deal.
I'm in the middle of a BIG re-brand here.
“The Storm King” is tracking well,
as “intensely intimidating”.
But you know what?
I need to back it up.
You know what I need to back it up with?
A STORM!
That would be great!
You promised me magic that could
control the elements,
and right now I'm holding a what - a branch, a twig.
Blehh!
That would be The Staff of Sacanas,
Your Excellency,
And it will channel the magic of
the four rulers of this land.
Mm Hmm.
Mm Hmmmm.
You'll soon have the power of
a hundred armies.
So that would be a YES on you
locking down the four
pegacornicuses or whatever you call them?
Give me three days.
I'll have everything ready for your arrival.
Remember Tempest,
only I have the power to make you whole.
Make this twig work,
and you'll get your reward.
Fail me, and your horn won't be
the only thing that's broken.
It won't be a problem.
Great! I'm r-ready to power up,
c-crash and b-bang,
be the b-biggest baddest bugaloooo...
Sorry. Bad spell service.
You want me to call him back?
Do you have the princess?
Well... uh... funny story.
It kinda seems like she...
she might
have, like, you know...
Got away...
A little bit.
I know you're disappointed,
But I got one word for you.
Spongecake.
I need all FOUR for the staff to work.
Hey... I know.
I want the Storm King to fix
that crazy horn as badly as you do!
It's looks like a crackly chipped
tooth, on the top of your head!
And you know you don't look
good in hats.
That princess is not going to keep
me from getting my horn back.
Prepare my ship.
Please. How far can one little
pony get on her own.
There's...
Sand in my...
Everything...
Saving...
Equestria!
Oh look!
Maybe this guy knows
which way to go!
What's that, friend?
We're lost?!
Ha ha ha ha... ha ha ha ha...
We could be going in circles!
Endless sand.
Nothing for miles...
But sand...
And this rock...
And this cactus...
And this road...
This road.
Hnh? A road?
Where there's a road...
There's a...
Whoa!
Cool!
What is that?
OOOOO!
A city!
We are DOING IT,
YOU GUYS!
You know what they say...
Where there's a city,
There's a SPA!
WHO says that?
In case you forgot, we're on a
mission to save Equestria.
I can multi-task.
Don't worry, little one,
we'll let you go!
To the highest bidder!
Nice!
Oooooh!
Hey, you with the horn!
You selling?
Hi there!
Oh, I'm sorry...
here, let me help you with that!
Hey, no magic around my merchandise!
Hmm, very interesting...
OK, we just gotta stick together.
Be careful who you talk to, and try
to blend in.
CAN I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION
PLEEEEAAAASE!
CAN ANYPONY TAKE US TO THE
QUEEN OF THE HIPPOS??
You want something - you gotta give
somethin'!
Well, how about a big warm hug from
a grateful pony friend?
How about this comb that I've never used?
A picture of my sister Maud?
This BREATH mint??!
Seriously buddy. Help me help you!
Pinkie... you can't just take off,
And you don't need to announce to
EVERY...
RELAX Twilight, I've totally got
this.
How much for the giant gecko?
Who you callin' a gecko?
Uh, Spike isn't for sale.
I WANT THAT fancy purple HAIR!
I'll give you TWO Storm Bucks for it!
TWO Storm Bucks?! It's worth more
than that.
GIMME THAT PINK ONE!
I'LL TAKE THAT BLUE ONE!
NO, I WANT THE BLUE ONE!
I NEED THAT LIZARD!
I'LL TAKE THE PICTURE OF YOUR SISTER!
I WANT ALL SEVEN FOR MY COLLECTION!
Back up everyone!
BACK. IT. UP!
Y'all in some serious danger!
Now you didn't touch any of them,
did you?
Just look at all those colors-
you think that's natural?
They're infected with pastelus coloritis!!
Now you listen here, fella, there ain't...
Don't worry, don't worry
As long as you're not
covered in purple splotches, you'll be fine.
Uh oh.
What do I do?!
Enjoy your last moments.
And don't touch anyone.
Because parts will fall off.
Me parts!!
Well, all right.
You.
Are.
Awesome!!!!
Mmm-hmm.
And quite charming.
Huh.
Capper's the name.
Charming's my game.
So, to the hippos then?
I don't know if we should trust him.
We could definitely use a friend out here.
You know what?
Little Cotton Candy Hair was right.
And if I do say so myself...
♫ This town is not a nice place ♫
♫ For little fillies all alone ♫
♫ There are lots of twists and corners ♫
♫ That could lead to the unknown ♫
♫ Let me guide your way ♫
♫ And I'll be sure to help you through ♫
♫ You could really use a friend out here ♫
♫ And luckily for you... ♫
♫ I'm the friend that you need ♫
♫ When you're lost and don't know what to do ♫
♫ I'm your pal, your amigo ♫
♫ Useful and resourceful too! ♫
♫ And my help, you'll concede ♫
♫ Is a plus, guaranteed ♫
♫ You can call and I'll come running ♫
♫ Just follow my lead ♫
♫ Cuz I'm the friend you need!! ♫
He's a friend
Quite a friend
He's a friend indeed
♫ You need a bud to
spot the danger ♫
♫ A pal to stop the creep ♫
♫ A chum and not a
stranger to assist ♫
♫ You need a bro who is cunning ♫
♫ That can help you take the leap ♫
♫ A friend who knows what's lying
in the mist ♫
♫ Don't fear these darkened alleys ♫
♫ They're scary, yes I know ♫
♫ Why you could use a friend ♫
♫ To protect you wherever you go ♫
♫ And such a dazzling beauty ♫
♫ Covered in dirt and muck ♫
♫ But now your fate is changing ♫
♫ Now you are in luck ♫
♫ Cuz I'm the friend that you need ♫
♫ When you're lost and don't know
What to do ♫
♫ I'm your pal, your amigo ♫
♫ Looking out for friends like you! ♫
♫ And my help, you'll concede ♫
♫ Is a plus, guaranteed ♫
♫ Just call and I'll come running ♫
♫ We'll say it's agreed... ♫
Here.
Tell Verko my place.
Twenty minutes.
I've got something that will...
..."magically" erase ALL my debt.
♫ Cuz I'm the friend you neeeed! ♫
♫ He's a friend ♫
♫ Quite a friend ♫
♫ He's a friend indeed ♫
Welcome, my little ponies
To my little Manor!
Ooh, sort of a...
Roco-hobo-Bohemian-hodgepodge.
Apologies for the state of my litterbox
I wasn't expecting guests!
Oooh, so many fun breakables!
Y'all sure y'all want the Hippos?
Yessiree! The QUEEN of the Hippos!
Not like the queen of lions, or the
tigers, or the bears...?
Oh my!
Huh...?
Please, PLEASE, I don't know
anything!!
You really think the ponies got
this far?
Oh, they're here.
Attention!
A little purple pony passed this way.
Tell me where she is...
Or somethin' real bad's gonna happen.
You think we're gonna fall for this again?
I don't know what kinda scam you're workin'
with Capper and the rest of your friends, but...
Friends?
Poison or no poison... you're gonna pay.
Oh, Fishman just got dropped!
Now, about this Capper...
Stop playin' me!
A Sonic Rainboom?
That's not a real thing!
Is that a real thing?
I'll show ya!
No no no - I don't need you sonic
rainbooming up in my place
Thank you very much.
Whoa, hey, hold up now.
Whoa.
Here you go! I do apologize.
If we were back home
I could have done something truly fabulous.
Okay. What's the catch?
Nothing!
After all that you've done for us?
Consider it a thank you.
Oh, uh, don't thank me. Really.
Guys!
We've been looking for the wrong Queen!
We don't need the Queen of the Hippos
We need the Queen of the hippoGRIFFS!
Part Pony, part Eagle.
Oh! Oh, the HippoGRIFFS?
Now the trouble with that is, no one knows...
Where they are.
Says here they're on the top of Mt. Aris.
You mean the mountain right outside
the window?
Objects in windows may be less
mountainous than they appear
Heh heh heh...
Let's go, everypony.
Wait! You can't, you can't make it
by yourselves!
You'd need an airship...
And lucky for you, I can get you a ride!
I think we can get there on our own.
Here's Verko!
These ponies better shoot rainbow
lasers outta their eyes...
...if they're gonna settle your debt!
Brought the big cage.
Let's load em up!
You were... you were going to SELL US?!
I KNEW IT!
We gotta get out of here!
Silly little ponies
Tempest!
Trusting strangers?
Big mistake.
Big.
Huge!
Hoo Hoo my goodness!
Well look at you!
With your scary broken horn
and scowly eyes...
What tricks do you know, my little pony wony?!
...not bad.
Go, go!
Get her - now!!!
You gonna be scared now, ponies!
I'M...
GONNA...
BE...
SICK!!
We have to get there, to the docks!
Hurry!
That's it - don't look down now!
YAY!!
Pinkie!!!
Best. Escape. Plan... EVER!!
WHAT?!
Shhh.
Did you hear something?
Yeah, probably just the rats.
If we find 'em, we'll eat 'em.
Rats?!
Now, where are they going?
Okay! No need for violence!
Uh, they're headed...
They're headed east.
Yeah to, to Black Skull Island.
So, uh, glad I could be of service
to His Majesty the Storm King.
I'll just be on my way...
...when I get my princess.
Until then, your fate is still...
up in the air.
Oh, you're gonna go in the skiff,
Which is a boat
Specifically, a air boat!
We make a great team.
I love it how you said his fate is up in the
air and then I said
“you're GONNA be in the air in the air boat...”
What do ya think, Twilight, should
we just... ask 'em to take us?
The last time we trusted somepony,
he tried to sell us!
Hey guys...
...come check this out!
Looks like a pack of stowaways.
What are we s'posed to do with 'em?
I think we tie 'em up!
Nah - we clip their wings!
Nah, we SCAR 'em...
...emotionally!
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
What say the book, Captain Celaeno?
Storm King's rulebook says...
Throw them overboard.
All right, that's lunch!!
What?!
Whoa whoa whoa...
So, you were
about to toss us overboard
And you stopped for a lunch break?!
Storm King only allows one break a
day for meals.
Then it's back to
hauling goods.
So you're delivery guys?
And gals. These uniforms aren't
exactly doing us any favors...
Then, can you DELIVER us to Mt. Aris?
Sorry. We do what The Storm King
orders, or we suffer his wrath.
Right, still going overboard.
Eh, it's nothing personal. Pudding?
There's pudding?!
You weren't ALWAYS delivery birds,
were you?
What about BEFORE the
Storm King??
Yeah, we used to be much more
adventurous.
Ooh! I met that guy in the desert!
Whoa... you used to be pirates?!
Uh, we prefer the term,
“Swashbuckling Treasure Hunters.”
So, pirates.
You birds have a choice to make.
You can let some cloven-hoofed
Storm King tell you
how to live your lives, or...
...you can be awesome again.
Rainbow Dash, this really isn't a
good time for a...
♫ I know the world can get you down ♫
...song.
♫ Things don't work out
quite the way that you thought ♫
♫ Feeling like all your best days are done ♫
♫ Your fears and doubts are all you've got ♫
♫ But there's a light ♫
♫ Shining deep inside ♫
♫ Beneath those fears and
doubt so just squash 'em ♫
♫ And let it shine
for all the world to see ♫
♫ That it is time, yeah,
time to be awesome ♫
♫ Ah, ah, ah, ah, awesome!
It's time to be so awesome! ♫
♫ You've no idea how hard it's been ♫
♫ This dull routine we've been forced to do ♫
♫ Don't let them rob you
of who you are ♫
♫ Be awesome it's all up to you ♫
♫ I feel the light ♫
♫ Stirring deep inside ♫
♫ It's like a tale
still yet to be told ♫
♫ And now it's time... ♫
♫ ...To break the shackles free ♫
♫ And start living like
the brave and the bold ♫
♫ It's time to be awesome! ♫
♫ Let loose, be true - so awesome! ♫
♫ Go big, be you - so awesome! ♫
♫ We used to soar through
the clouds in the skies ♫
♫ Elaborate schemes we
would love to devise ♫
♫ We rescued our treasure
and stored it away ♫
♫ Saving those gemstones
for a rainy day! ♫
♫ We see that light
filling up our skies ♫
♫ So take the Storm King's orders
and toss 'em ♫
♫ 'Cuz it's the time
to let our colors fly ♫
♫ Hey scallywags,
it's time to be awesome ♫
♫ Hey ♫
Come on, let's show these little
ponies how it's done!
Awesome!
I knew you had it in ya!
And now, for the finishing touch!
Rainboom
Oh
No
NOO!
Rainboom
Aw yeah! Ha ha ha, woo!!
Wow!!
Look at that rainbow!
Whoa, that's so cool.
Yeah - of them to alert us.
Funny though, they don't seem to be
headed to Black Skull Island.
Like, Hah Hah funny, or huh huh...
Yeah!! Ha ha
Nice!
Storm guards!
Looks like they found you!
Tempest!
Secure the rigging!
Lock down the cargo!
Everyone
prepare to be boarded!
Oh goodness!!!
You think
she saw my sonic rainboom?
Are you KIDDING me?!
Where is the pony princess?
Princess?
Princess... Princess...
Nope. All we're hauling is Storm
King merchandise.
You do realize that if you were to
shelter fugitives,
The Storm King
would be quite... explosive.
We have to get off this ship before
they tell Tempest we're here!
We helped them get their mojo back.
They're not going to give us up!
Whoa!
I've got this.
Now, I'm gonna to count to 3 and if
you don't tell me where they are...
...your ship is going down.
1...
Hold this.
What are you doing?
2...
Oh this is inteeeeeense...
3!!
What?!
OH
FOR
CELESTIA'S
SAKE!!!
WHEEEEE!!!!
I can't look!!
What in the hay is she up to?
Oh, thank goodness!
Heeyew! Quick thinkin' Twilight!
Yahoo! Haha!
That was fun! Can we do it again?!
Next stop, Mt. Aris!
We're home free!
There's no ponies.
But I found this.
It's a kind of a cupcake
with some sprinkles...
Oh yeah,
and I found this, too.
Ah.
Wow. This is a real artist.
Looks like they're heading to MOUNT ARIS.
Really? Mt., Mt. Aris??
I didn't,
well that's my mist...
I didn't know they...
Mt. Aris, that's my bad I didn't...
That my... I'm sorry, I'm
very very sorry...
Now, about your betrayal.
We had to crash the balloon at the
BOTTOM of the mountain?!
That's it!
I simply.
Can not.
Even!
I have nothing.
The bad guys have won!
I'm so sorry...
We're almost there!
Will you stop saying that!
No, really - we're actually here!
This is it!
Oooooooo!!
Well I'll be! Heh heh.
Hippogriffs, here we come!
Ah, time to rest my hooves.
Are we sure this is the right place?
Hello? Is anypony home?
No Hippogriffies here.
Or here.
Wait.
Nope. This place is em-pty.
But Celestia. The map...
They have to be here!
Something bad happened here.
Something that turned this whole
place into a ghost town.
A g-g-g-g-ghost town?
It's coming from over there.
What was that?
Hey! Wait up!
CANNONBALL!!!!!
PINKIE!!
She's gone!
Now what?
Huh?
Oh boy.
I HATE epic adventures.
Way to leave it 'til the last
minute, Twilight.
I didn't make these bubbles...
Then... who did?
Hello? We're looking for the
Hippogriffs.
How do I know I can trust you?
Please! The Storm King invaded our
land and we need their help.
The Storm King?!
I'm so glad I saved you guys!
I'm totally taking you to my mom!!
Does your mother know where they are?
She might have an idea...
Hoo hoo!
We're almost there!
Wow!
MOTHER!!!!
Look what I found!
Is it another shell?
Uh-uh
Because I am telling you, if it is another shell
I am...
Princess Skystar!
What have you done?!
You know surface dwellers
are forbidden here!!!
Guards!
No no no - Mom Mom Mom, please!
It is SO not like that!
The Storm King is trying to destroy their home, too!
We need to find the Hippogriffs.
Do you know what happened to them?
Well of course I know.
I'm the Queen.
I know everything.
Ooh, ooh - it's SUCH a good story!!!
Don't you DARE tell them!
Once Upon A Time, like...
A while ago,
the Hippogriffs DID live on Mt. Aris.
Did I not say don't tell them?
But hey - I'm just the queen,
don't mind me.
FINE. I CAN'T tell you
But if I COULD tell you,
I'd say that that horned beast DID show up
to steal their magic...
Seriously?
But to keep it out of his clutches,
their brave and majestic leader, Queen Novo
Hid them deep
underwater where he could never go.
We are,
Well, we were,
The Hippogriffs!
TAH DAH!
But... I totally did NOT tell you that.
Well. I guess the pearl is out the oyster now.
I am Queen Novo.
Hold on now, let me get this straight.
When the Storm King came,
you just abandoned your entire city and fled?
We didn't flee, we swam...
You know, in order to flee.
But... how?
Oh! Can we show them?
These are the first guests
we've had in like FOREVER!
Canwe
Well, I suppose I should make sure
it still works.
Canwe
Careful now.
Wow!
These fins are divine!
Hey, Applejack! I'll race ya to
that coral!
You're on!
Woo-hoo!
Try it, Fluttershy.
Yay.
Guys.
Guys!
What is
Happening?!?
Aww, so cute!
This is amazing!
With this, we could transform
everypony at home into...
...something POWERFUL enough
to face the Storm King's army!
Or, it could end up in his greedy claws.
But...
Honey, I'm sorry about your home.
I truly am.
But my responsibility is
to protect MY subjects.
The pearl...
...is not going anywhere.
But we've come all this way!
And you can't just hide down here,
trapped forever,
There's so much you're missing!
We are 100 percent
Okay. With. That
Yes, Jamal?
Ooh! Time for my seaweed wrap.
Yes, a massage, too! Mama needs
her deep tissue.
So that's it... we left home for nothin'?
Ohmigosh
Best idea
You can stay with us...
FOREVER!!!
There are so many things we can do!
We could make friendship bracelets
out of shells,
And picture frames
And decorative waste
baskets out of shells.
Oh, I have so many projects
that involve shells.
Now I have someone new to
share them with.
I mean, aside from
my friends Shelly and Sheldon.
Right, Shelly and Sheldon?
Get it?
Oh, oh - that sounds lovely,
darling,
But you must realize we
can't stay.
We've gotta get back to our
families.
Oh no.
Of course. Of course!
Of course you have
your own friends back home.
It's fine - it's fine!
Shelly and Sheldon get jealous anyways.
It's probably for the best.
Yeah,
I'll just, um
I'll get Mom to, uh,
Turn you back so you can go home.
I KNOW we have to go, but...
You guys saw how disappointed
Princess Skystar was.
Couldn't we stay for
just a LITTLE longer?
Pinkie, we just don't have time...
Oh no. No, no. Pinkie's right.
Say what now?
Well, we still need to come up with
a plan to get back.
A few minutes
won't make a huge difference.
And if there's anypony who can cram a
lifetime of fun into a blink of an eye,
It's Pinkie Pie.
So go ahead and show Skystar the
best time ever!
I won't let you down!
I'm counting on it.
It's probably for the best.
♫ Hey now don't be sad ♫
♫ I know we can not stay ♫
♫ But we've got a couple minutes ♫
♫ And a little time to play ♫
♫ I know you have important things ♫
♫ So it's okay, just go ♫
♫ But we can still pick one small
little thing ♫
♫ To do with you, y'know! ♫
♫ One small thing
doesn't seem like a lot ♫
work with time time you've got ♫
♫ Soon one small thing becomes two ♫
♫ After two perhaps another few ♫
♫ Then one small thing is not so small! ♫
♫ One small thing can be
the biggest thing of all! ♫
♫ All right now since you're here ♫
♫ Let's see what we can do ♫
♫ Swim with the flow until you go ♫
♫ Together me and you ♫
♫ I've got necklaces for everyfish! ♫
♫ So what else do ya got? ♫
♫ Well, we could play the bubblefish ♫
♫ You'll like this one a lot! ♫
♫ One small thing
It's a good place to start ♫
♫ Just one small thing ♫
♫ One small thing
and we don't seem so far apart ♫
♫ Don't seem apart ♫
♫ Soon one small thing leads to more ♫
♫ It's so much more than there
was before ♫
♫ Just one small thing and
you will see! ♫
♫ The start of something big
for you and me ♫
♫ One small thing ♫
♫ Just one small thing ♫
♫ Or a tall thing ♫
♫ Just one tall thing ♫
♫ Or a sing thing ♫
♫ Just one sing-y thing ♫
♫ Or a bling thing ♫
♫ Just one bling-y thing ♫
♫ A conga thing ♫
♫ Yeah a conga thing ♫
♫ Or a longah thing ♫
♫ Just a longah thing ♫
♫ A blue thing, true thing,
you thing ♫
♫ A whee thing, sea thing,
me thing ♫
♫ So many things and everything ♫
♫ Until our time is done ♫
♫ There's one small thing for each ♫
♫ And everyone!! ♫
♫ One small thing ♫
♫ So much we can create ♫
♫ You and me ♫
♫ We started something great ♫
♫ It's so amazing look around ♫
♫ At all the happy sights and sounds ♫
♫ One small thing,
is big it's true! ♫
♫ You did this all for us ♫
♫ I just wish there was
one small thing ♫
♫ An extra-special kind of thing ♫
♫ That we could do for you... ♫
♫ One small thing ♫
Well, I guess there is one small
thing we can do...
The pearl alarm!
Oh no, the pearl alarm!
NO!
Please!
All of this so you could sneak in
and take the pearl?
THIS is why we don't bring
strangers into our home!
You don't DESERVE to be one of us...
What were you thinking?! I mean,
STEALING their pearl??
It was the only way to save
Equestria!
Except it WASN'T!
The Queen was going to say “yes”!
We did what you told us and that's
what made her realize we were
ponies worth saving.
Unless... you didn't really want us
to show her the best time ever!
You just wanted us to distract her!
I never would have done it, but
this isn't Equestria!
We can't just dance around with con artists,
Make rainbooms in the sky and
expect everything to work out!
It's NOT enough, WE are NOT enough!
No, Twilight.
WE stuck together.
WE were gonna get the help we needed.
The only thing that stopped us, was YOU.
Well, I'm doing the best I can!
It's all on me.
I'm the one Tempest wants,
I'm the last Princess...
You're ALSO the only one who
doesn't trust her FRIENDS!
Well maybe I would have been better
off without FRIENDS LIKE YOU!!!
Pinkie... I...
I just can't talk to you right now.
Twilight...
It's okay
You'll figure it out.
No...
I can't...
I ruined everything.
There's no chance to save Equestria now.
It's all my fault...
Spike?
AHHH!!
No no no no no... no!
SPIKE!
Twilight!!!
Aw, the Princess of Friendship...
...with no friends.
And no way out.
Why are you doing this?
You're a pony!
Just like me.
I'm nothing like you.
And more than you'll ever be.
♫ It's time you learned a lesson ♫
♫ It's time that you understand ♫
♫ Don't ever count on anybody else ♫
♫ In this or any other land ♫
♫ I once hoped for friendship ♫
♫ To find a place among my kind ♫
♫ But those were the childish wishes ♫
♫ Of someone who was blind ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ And see the world from where I stand ♫
♫ Me among the mighty ♫
♫ You caged at my command ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ Give up your sweet fantasyland ♫
♫ It's time to grow up and get wise ♫
♫ Come now little one ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ We all start out the same
with simple naive trust ♫
♫ Shielded from the many ways
that life's not fair or just ♫
♫ But then there comes a moment ♫
♫ A simple truth that you must face ♫
♫ If you depend on others ♫
♫ You'll never find your place ♫
♫ And as you take that first step ♫
♫ Upon a path that's all your own ♫
♫ You see it all so clearly ♫
♫ The best way to survive is all alone ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ And see the world from where I stand ♫
♫ Me among the mighty ♫
♫ You caged at my command ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ And behold the fading light ♫
♫ It's time to grow up
and get wise ♫
♫ Come now little one ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
I'm so sorry you felt so alone.
I saw the truth.
My “friends” abandoned me
when times got tough.
Looks like I'm not the only one.
Face it, Princess.
Friendship has failed you, too.
Friendship didn't fail me.
I failed friendship.
This whole journey was such a
mistake!
All we wanted was
somepony to help us!
You think maybe it's time we talk
to Twilight?
She's been taken!!!
What?!
Twilight's been taken!
Tempest
she grabbed her and took her on her ship!
We gotta get her back!
How?! We'll never catch up!
And we got no way to defeat those
monsters...
Well, good thing I happen to know
of a group of...
...mighty heroes that
could handle this easily!
Well, look what the cat dragged
in...
Himself!
These heroes have faced the Storm
King's army and escaped!
I've seen them tackle the streets
of the roughest towns,
Break out of the tightest situations, and
inspire others to join their cause!
Now don't get too excited,
he's just talking about us.
They even escaped certain doom at
the hooves of Commander Tempest!
Yeah, that was pretty great.
Are you kidding me??
That was AWESOME!
Figured you could use a claw.
We're onboard to help you fight the
Storm King!
Just not on board our
actual ship...
That crazy unicorn sunk it... but
you got back our arrgghhh!
And we're ready to kick some booty!
Is that what I think that is?!?
Hellooooo! Me again!
I'm gonna get SO grounded but I
talked things over with Shelly and Sheldon and...
...they pointed out that you were just trying to help your
friends!
So I wanna help, too!
Because you know, one small thing
can make a really big difference!
That's it, right? We didn't make
friends with anypony else?
All right, y'all.
I think our course is clear.
Y'all ready to do this thing?
We're coming, Twilight!
Yee haw!!
Aw yeah! Ha ha!!
As soon as we bake up a plan!
♫ I am here and I see your pain ♫
♫ Through the storm ♫
♫ Through the clouds, the rain ♫
♫ I'm telling you, you cannot escape... ♫
Tempest, don't do this! Don't give
the Storm King...
Your magic? Did you think you'd
keep it all to yourself?
Time to share.
I'd love for everybody out there to
know what I can REALLY do.
Ooh, fascinating!
What CAN you really do?
Your bidding, of course, your
mighty one!
Bidding's good - I like bidding!
Um, what are you supposed to be?
I'm the Princess of Friendship.
Oh. That's nice.
Why is this one still moving?
She and her friends put up a bit of
a fight, but she's alone now.
She won't be a problem.
Yeah, so SPEAKING of problems.
This place. It seems... a little too,
Oh I don't know, CUTE!
I don't like CUTE, I never did like CUTE,
Doesn't really go with my
whole big bad powerful magic guy thing, does it?!
Deliver the punchline Tempest,
because this has gotta be a JOKE!
Ugh, no!!
Check out the light show!
WOW!!
Let's get this storm started!
Ooh, hey, that's good, I should
trademark that.
Not bad.
Actually, kind of first rate!
What else does it do?
Your Excellency, you promised to
restore my horn, and give it even...
Dehdehdeh det... Okay, hang on...
You gotta be kidding me!
I can move the SUN!?
AH HAH HAH! WHOA!
Now THIS is what I'm TALKIN' about!
HA HA!!
Time to play!
Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday!
Day night, day night day, night day
night day night sunrise sunset...
De de bup bup bup bah bah bah
bah...
Uh, yeah.
I got a delivery here
for a Mr. The Storm King.
I was given explicit instructions to
bring...
...THIS here cake to THIS here
Castle's throne room.
All right then.
Look here, could one of y'all go be a pal,
go tell your boss he's not getting his...
“Congratulations on subduing
defenseless pastel ponies” cake?
'Cause I don't want to be the one
responsible for the big guy missing...
His special dessert, you know what
I'm sayin'?
Thank you kindly fellas, I'mma be sure and put
a good word in for the both of y'all.
Pinkie, quit lookin' so happy!
Y'ain't foolin' nopony!
Oh, okay.
Mmm, pie!
Oh, hello cake.
Ooh, don't mind if I do.
Mmm. It's some like... gourmet
icing!
Who puts eyeballs in filling?
GUARDS!
Uh oh... Plan B?
The jig is up!
Come on!!
Gotcha!
Lovely!
Surprise!
Double surprise!
You seem tense. Do you wanna talk
about it?
Head for the castle!
We'll hold them off!
C'mon!
Let it all out.
FLUTTERSHY!!
Oh, sorry, our time is up, buh bye!!
Bye!
Keep going!
Shelly, Sheldon...
I can't see!!
Uh oh!
Hey, ain't you a FIRE-BREATHING dragon?
What?! How...?!
It's... it's the magic of...
Yeah yeah, friendship and flowers
and ponies and bleeeeh...
I'm so totally over the cute pony thing!
THIS ENDS NOW!
Uh oh.
YEAH!
Move them hooves, ponies!
You'd have to be traveling faster than
a speeding Pegasus to break through THAT wind!
Excellent idea, Rainbow Dash!
Now I truly am the Storm King!
And the entire world will bow to my
va va va VOOM, BABY!
Yes, yes, you are every bit as
powerful as I promised, sire.
Now, restore my horn and I swear to
use my magic to serve you.
Who cares about your dinky little
unicorn horn.
But, we... we had an agreement...
Get with the program.
I USED you.
It's kinda what I do
Hold on!
Why are you saving me?
Because this is what friends do.
Aww...
...Isn't that just so sweet!
Yeah.
See ya.
You sure about this?
JUST DO IT!!!
THANK YOU!!
I'm excited!
Who's excited?!
AHH,
I've never been so excited!!!!!
Bullseye!
Pinkie!
You all came back! I'm SO sorry! I
was wrong to...
I'm sorry, too!
Friends mess up sometimes but we never should...!
Uh, make up later!
This isn't over!
I've got to get control of it!
Go! You got this, Twilight!
No.
We've got this!
Together.
WHEEE!!
The staff belongs to ME!
NO! That's MY staff!
THE POWER IS MINE!!!
NO!!!
WHHOO
AAAAHHHHH!!!
WHHOOOOAAAA!!!
TWILIGHT!!
NOOOO!
YAY!!
Yee haw!
Alright!
Yay!
GROUP HUG!
NOOOOOOOOO!!!!
Whoa
I can't believe she did that!
I can.
Now what?
Now...
...we fix everything.
Twilight!
Princesses!
Fillies and Gentlecolts!
Get ready for a little...
SONGBIRD SERENADE!
And now to celebrate the fact that
we're all still here in one piece...
Give it up for Princess Twilight
and her friends!
All right! Way to go, guys!
YEAH!! HEH HEH HEH HEH!
♫ I know you, you're a special one ♫
♫ Some see crazy, where I see love ♫
♫ You fall so low,
but shoot so high ♫
♫ Big dreamers shoot for open sky ♫
♫ So much life in those
open eyes ♫
♫ So much depth,
you look for the light ♫
Ooooh!
And, perfection!
♫ But when your wounds open,
you will cry ♫
Mom!
♫ You'll cry out now
and you'll question why ♫
You are so grounded.
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as they fall on down ♫
♫ I can see your soul grow ♫
♫ Through the pain as they hit the ground ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as the sun comes out ♫
♫ As the sun comes out... ♫
That's one thing that never changes
around here.
The party.
Well...
I hope you'll stay.
More friends are definitely merrier.
But, um...
My horn?
You know,
Your horn is pretty powerful,
Just like the pony it
belongs to.
I did tell you I wanted to show
everypony in Equestria
What I could do, right?
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as they fall on down ♫
♫ I can see your soul grow ♫
♫ Through the pain as they hit the ground... ♫
Nice touch, Tempest.
Actually, that's not my real name...
Oooooooo!! What is it?!
It's Fizzlepop Berrytwist.
OKAY!
THAT IS
THE MOST AWESOME NAME...
EVER!!!
♫ I can see your rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as they fall on down ♫
♫ I can see your soul grow ♫
♫ Through the pain as they hit the ground ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as the sun comes out ♫
♫ As the sun comes out ♫
♫ I am here and I see your pain ♫
♫ Through the storms,
through the clouds, the rain ♫
♫ I'm telling you you can not escape ♫
♫ You can do it,
just feel baby ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as they fall on down ♫
♫ I can see your soul grow ♫
♫ Through the pain as they hit the ground ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as they fall on down ♫
♫ I can see your soul grow ♫
♫ Through the pain as they hit the ground ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as the sun comes out ♫
♫ As the sun comes out ♫
♫ Here comes the sun ♫
♫ Smiling down ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In your tears as they fall on down ♫
♫ I can see your soul grow ♫
♫ Through the pain as they hit the ground ♫
♫ I can see a rainbow ♫
♫ In yo... ♫
♫ As the sun comes out ♫
♫ As the sun... ♫
♫ So, we wanna stay ♫
♫ But can't find peace while sitting still ♫
♫ I guess we never will ♫
♫ We're on the way ♫
♫ We don't hurry back again ♫
♫ The journey is the end ♫
♫ I love this very moment ♫
♫ We're speeding up not slowing ♫
♫ We might know we can't win ♫
♫ But we're dumb enough to try ♫
♫ We're going, there's no maybe ♫
♫ That's why they call us crazy ♫
♫ And we'll say if anybody asks us ♫
♫ Hey, where you gonna go ♫
♫ We're off to see the world ♫
♫ We don't need to know ♫
♫ Hey, where you gonna go ♫
♫ We're off to see the world ♫
♫ We don't need to know ♫
♫ We never need to know ♫
♫ Seeking boundaries to break ♫
♫ Let's forget the ones we've made ♫
♫ So we carry on,
don't let good things pass us by ♫
♫ The time we're gone will be the
best time of our life ♫
♫ I love this very moment ♫
♫ We're speeding up not slowing ♫
♫ We might know we can't win ♫
♫ But we're dumb enough to try ♫
♫ We're going, there's no maybe ♫
♫ That's why they call us crazy ♫
♫ And we'll say if anybody asks us ♫
♫ Hey, where you gonna go ♫
♫ We're off to see the world ♫
♫ We don't need to know ♫
♫ Hey, where you gonna go ♫
♫ We're off to see the world ♫
♫ We don't need to know ♫
♫ So go tell 'em we won't stop ♫
♫ We know they can't change us ♫
♫ We're gonna go way off the map ♫
♫ To get ourselves back on the track ♫
♫ Go tell 'em we won't stop ♫
♫ We know they can't change us ♫
♫ No need to worry so much ♫
♫ We do whatever we want ♫
♫ Hey, where you gonna go ♫
♫ We're off to see the world ♫
♫ We don't need to know ♫
♫ Hey, where you gonna go ♫
♫ We're off to see the world ♫
♫ We don't need to know ♫
Subtitle made by SandPox
Thanks for watching.