Psagmeno.com | No1 Subs iNFO
It was the witching hour
when the bogey man comes out.
When people go missing.
Matron thinks the witching
hour arrives at midnight.
The girls say 1 or 2 o'clock
in the morning.
I think it comes at 3
in the morning,
when I'm the only one left awake
Like, always.
Like now.
Oy!
You're bladdered, the lot of you!
Would you clear off!
There are children trying to sleep.
Hello little missy.
Don't little missy me!
I'll call the coppers,
I will do it.
Never get out of bed.
Never go to the window.
And never look behind...
the curtain.
Never get out of bed,
never go to the window
and never look behind the curtains!
There aint no place to go
unless you has wings
I's hungry.
It's time for eats.
Where am I?
Giant country.
No such place..
Wish I was a long, long way.
Yeah, it'd be a distance.
What's that? What's that?
Giants.
There are more of you?
Yeah, well..
Flesh Lump Eater, Bone Cruncher.
Man Hugger, Child Chewer, Meat Dripper,
Gizzard Gulper, Maid Masher
Blood Bottler.
Blood Bottler?
Yeah. And the Butcher Boy.
The Butcher Boy?
Please don't eat me.
Me?
You think because I'm a giant,
that I'm a man gobbling cannibal.
Me? Gobbling up human beings?
Do you mind!
This I never.
Then, who are you?
What kind of a monster are you?
You has me wrong.
You snatched me.
Yeah, well, there
you has me right..
Anyway, I didn't steal
you very much.
After all, you's only
a little thing.
I can't help thinking about your poor
mother and father, they must be...
I don't have a mother or father.
You don't?
They both died when
I was a baby.
So you is an orphan?
Yes. You took me from
an orphanage.
You didn't know?
I.. I didn't know that.
Were you happy there?
No. I hate it.
The matron who runs it
is incompetent and
she has crazy rules and
you get punished a lot.
How is you punished?
She locks you in a dark cellar.
There are rats down there.
The filthy old fizzwiggler.
The other giants..
Are they nice,
like you're nice?
No, I's sorry to say the boys
would eat you up in one dollop.
My 24 foot,
puddin nuts in giant country.
And that's where you is.
In giant country now.
But why did you bring me here?
Why did you take me?
I had to take you.
Because the first thing you'd be doing, you'd
be scuddling around, yodelling the news
you were actually seeing a giant.
And then there would be a great
rumple dumpus, wouldn't there.
And all the human beans would be rummaging
and wiffling for the giant what you saw
and getting wildly excited, and then
they'd be locking me up in a cage
to be looked at with all the squiggling
you know, hypo-dumplings and
croco-down-dillies and gigi-raffes.
And then there would be a giganteous
look-see giant hunt for all of the boys.
I won't tell.
No-one would listen to me anyway.
I'm an untrustworthy child.
Yes you would.
No I wouldn't.
Yes you would. No I wouldn't.
Yes you would. No I wouldn't!
You would be telling the whole wonky world
most likely on the tele-tele bunkum box
and the radio squeaker.
I won't tell. I wouldn't ever.
Please, take me home.
I'm scared, I want to go home.
No.
Gah. It's horrible.
You're just going to have to
be staying here with me.
For the rest of our lives.
You mean, of my life.
For the rest of my life.
Hey, is you not all fridgedy cold?
Heh. In your little nightie.
I WILL run away.
Listen. Listen, you.
I is warning you.
Not to ever go wifflin' out of
this cave without I is with you.
Or you is coming to an
ucky mucky end.
You can't stop me.
I've run away a 1000 times.
I have instincts.
Instincts. I always thought
human beans was full of brains,
but you is not very clever.
I can stop you.
Those giants, they'd swallow you
up like a piece of frumpkin fry.
It's pumpkin pie, not frumpkin fry.
And gigi-raffes are giraffes.
Crocodile-dillys are crocodiles
and hippo-dumplings are
hippopotamuses.
I cannot be helpin it if I sayin'
things a little squiggly.
I cannot be right all the time.
Quite often I's left,
instead of right.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to be rude.
Yeah. Well, what I says and what I means,
sometimes two different things.
Ey, what is you reading?
Nicholas Nickleby
What's in those jars?
Dreams.
Dreams aren't things.
I don't dream, actually. I've got insomnia.
Is that right?
Dreams is actually very
mysterious things.
All the time they is searching
for sleeping.
People...
with throbbing veins and burning skin.
Eyes wild and heavy.
You can.. you can read!
Yeah!
Thoughts hurried 'n disordered.
He felt as though the light were
re proach, and shrunk
involuntarily from the day
As if you were some foul
and hideous thing...
Help me!
No, help!
Help!
You did that!
There you has me right.
I told you. I didn't dream,
so it was much scarier
than it needed to be.
Needs must.
Titchy little snapper whippers like you should not
be higgling around with old sage and onions like me.
Giants is all murdererful
and cannibals.
They's swallowpin' up human
beans like they's sugar lumps.
Beings, not beans.
Well, they'd eat you either way.
What is that green fizz?
Frobscottel.
All giant's is drinking frobscottel.
It's fizzing the wrong way.
All bubbles go up.
Up? Up?
Upward going bubbles gives
a filths of belchy burp.
What's wrong with a
little burp now and then?
Ooh, is loathesome.
But if the bubbles in your
tummy go down and come out...
someplace else,
that could have a far nastier result.
A whizzpopper.
A Whizzpopper?
Yeah, the sign of true happiness.
Oh no.
It's glummy!
Runt!
Is you at home, Runt?
No.
You.. is jabbling.
Who is you jabbling to, Runt?
Why is you such a chatbag
in the morning?
Why is you not sleeping today?
Because you keep me
awake with your jabbling.
I's have a booboo.
Possibly later.
Now, Runt!
Right. I'll just have to fetch some water
No, no, no.
No water.
Hide, hide behind there.
Gimmee it. Gimmee it. Give't here.
Does you have a new
little petty-poo.
No.
I smells bean, Runt.
I finds him, I eats him up.
You is barking up the wrong dog,
There ain't no bean here.
I's hungry.
Why don't you have that snascomber?
That is a scrumptious snascomber.
It's fresh.
You live on some rotten garbage, Runt.
Don't be like that.
Have you never tried that for a stump eater.
No, never.
I tell you I was guzzling that
wonder veg gleefully night and day.
Well, that's what's wrong with you.
The outside is horrigust.
But, the inside is smelly something
sweetly familiar.
Yeah, go on. Go on boy. Get your
lips around that, that is lovely.
Wait! Wait!
You hates vegetables,
you eats only beans.
I hates vegeterribles.
I eats only beans.
Yeah. Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
That's what I said
That's what I said.
I said it
I hates fruits and vegeterribles.
And water.
And water
I'm taking this.
You. You is an insult to giant people.
Cheers.
Too hot! Too hot!
And something to wear?
Where'd you get the jacket?
In your scraps. It's nice.
Is.. something the matter?
No, nevermind.
Where're you going?
To work.
What do you do for work?
Ah, now you is asking me to
tell you whuppsie big secrets.
I won't tell a soul. How could I, anyway?
I'm stuck here for the rest of my life.
I catch dreams.
I want to come.
Now.. you is stayin' here.
No, I'm not.
Yes you are. You is human
bean and human bean
is like strawbunkles and cream
to those giants out there
so you gonna stay in a nice
safe place right here.
Not possible.
I goes and catch dreams, same
as every day. I goes alone.
I's a feature of habit.
But you'll be leaving me here with them.
They WILL eat me.
They is soundin' asleep.
I is going dream catching.
I is going alone.
You be snug as a bug up there.
Oh my.
You can't have secrets from me.
It's too late for that.
You must take me.
No.
We can't have secrets. I'll tell you mine.
I sneak out at night too
and I steal sometimes, and I lie.
So I'm lonely most of the time.
I've never had a best friend,
Sounds like you are that.
We gets over it.
We gets on with it.
Flesh Head, he'll come and eat me,
my blood will be on your hands.
Everything about you goes against
all my better judgementals, gal.
Well I'm right about this one.
I promise I am.
See, they snooze-lents, so hold your
breath, cross your fingers.
Here we go. We have to go right
past all those sleeping giants.
Climb all those steps, to get
all the ways up theres.
Runt!
Where's you gallopping off
to in the daytime, Runt?
You know I's going off to my work.
You can be seen by snoopers
and bring a giant's hunts.
We is not wanting a
giant's hunts, is we?
Now let me down Flesh. Let the
boys sleep in the day.
We's all awake now, we might as well...
Frolic.
Yeah, we might as well frolic.
What's frolic?
Frolic, you know..
Oh yeah. Sorry.
Don't just take it. Do something.
Gizzard Gulper, go long.
Why you not hunt with us, Runt?
Look at the puffers!
Rain be comin'.
Bean.
You shouldn't let them treat you like that.
Nobody should.
I lives with nine bean-eating giants.
They takes, so I gives back.
I blows my dreams about.
Well, it's as good as I can do.
I do something, eh?
I do something.
We's here at last.
You's in dream country now, missy.
I shared you a secret.
Look at all the stars!
Often enough on a clear night
I's hearing far away music coming
from those stars in the sky.
You do? What else.
I's hearing the tiny little ants chittering to
each other as they skiddle about in the soil.
Cattlepiddlars though.
They is the worst chatbags.
All the time they is arguing about who
will be the most pretty buttery flies.
Go on. please.
I hear the footsteps of a ladybird
as she walks across a leaf.
But the funniest, the funniest
old stories I always..
I hear it from the plants and
the trees themselves.
Yeah, they is living and growing,
laughing and chittering
Just like you and me.
Come on, down you go.
I's hearing all the wondrous,
and all the terrible.
Terrible, terrible things.
All the secret whisperings of the world.
Really?
You think I's swiss-fingering you
don't you?
No.
It's just all rather hard to believe.
At one point someone..
someone called me
"the big, friendly giant."
What shall I call you, gal?
My name is Sophie.
Well, jump. Sophie.
This be where all my
dreams is beginning.
Oh my.
As a dream comes whiffling by,
is so silvery soft,
for is making a tiny little buzzing,
humming sound, like music
Boggswinkles!
It's a fizzwizard.
I don't be seein' many
of them anymore.
It's behind you on your elbow.
No! Not that elbow,
the other one!
Now it's on your foot.
The other foot.
It's on your bottom!
I's got it.
It seems to know you, gal.
Look, it is a golden fizzwizard.
I wish I could hear it.
Here.
It is very soft.
Do you actually hear
what these dreams say?
Yeah, I do.
This one sounds like you.
Hello, beautiful dream.
Look!
Go on, make yourself useful,
little frogglefrump.
I couldn't.
Yeah, you could. Use your hands,
your tetchy little finglers.
I got one!
Let it go, Sophie.
Give it here, give it me,
Give it me.
Mince my maggots!
I think this be a very, very bad dream.
There bad dreams here too?
It be a trogglehumper.
What're you going to do with it?
I locks them up, wicked beastie.
What does the bad dream say?
It says...
Look at what you is done.
And there be no forgiveness.
Where are you?
I can't see you!
Big Friendly Giant!
Big Friendly Giant.
I'm going to call you BFG.
You calls me what you likes.
Where are you going next?
Dream blowing.
It be as good as I can do.
Why here?
Because I hears his little heart.
What be your pleasure, missy?
Make them all happy.
BFG, did your mother or father
teach you about dreams?
Giants don't have mothers or fathers.
Never?
How old are you?
Well, I's.. as old as the earth, I suppose.
I get a little bit crumply...
Us giants is mostly just going on and on
and on. Like whiffsea time twiddlers.
BFG, did you hear my heart
at the orphanage?
Yeah, I hears it right now.
What does the dream say?
Well, the boy, he's dreaming that the
telephone is ringing in his house.
His da he answers it and he says..
Yes, this is Mr. Goulash speaking.
And then he's gasping like he
has a lobster stuck in his throat.
And he's saying, 'Who? What?
Yes sir. I understand. Surely, sir. "
It's me you wish to be speaking to,
not my little boy.
And then his face turns white
and his eyes pop out of his head.
And he says Yes sir. He is
here, sir. Yes sir. Yes sir.
And he hands the phone to the boy.
Is you knowing the President of
the United States, he asks.
No, says the boy, but I suspect
he's hearing about me.
And then he takes the phone,
the boy, and he, he's having
a long chittery-chat on the
phone with the President.
Well, let me take care of it,
Mr. President.
No, no, sir, you'll bungle it up
sir, if you do it all your way. "
And his da, his eyes is
googling out of his head.
And then his ma, she comes into the room
and his da, he tells her, and then,
and so on and so on and so on.
Dreams are so quick.
On the outside, they's long on the inside.
What?
I hears a lament.
Somebody's selky's is
cryin' for their darlin'.
Look!
Monsters.
We have to stop them.
You can't keep living like this, BFG.
BFG, what did you do with my blanket?
I thought you had it there. Where is it?
In my other... In the cape?
I think I dropped it in giant country.
You dropped it in giant country.
Giant country..
Did I fall asleep?
Why are you giving me a dream?
Why are you giving me a.. dream?
You dropped your blanket.
So they must know you was there.
You's not safe with me, gal.
So? You is not safe with me.
Never mind that now.
There was a boy.
He liked to read. He taught
me how to read.
You's wearing his little red jacket.
I hears his lonely heart,
just as I hears yours
Then, he seen me, like you did.
So I had to take him, ipswitch.
I could've brought him back home..
but then it be too late.
It won't be like that.
We'll stop the giants.
We'll make them go away forever.
Was the boy scared?
Yeah. In the end.
I'm not.
Brave Sophie.
I'm not! I'm not.
BFG, you say you can hear
ants talk and spiders spin.
And you can hear the stars.
Can you still hear me?
I feel you're here.
I know you're here.
Jump, Sophie.
I need a plan.
Are you thinking of a plan?
I's not having the foggiest
idea in the wonky world.
Well, keep at it.
Runt!
Sophie, hide.
Oh Runtie, is you at home.
I has a boo-boo.
Well, you's a big boy. You take care
of your boo-boos yourself now.
I will.
Oh, he will.
You has a bean.
Right, out!
Let's get on with it.
Time to hunt.
Time to hunt!
Skitter scatter boys.
Find me the chiddler.
This be my work.
This be my work, boys!
Look at me!
Once, we giants, we be gentries.
Those days are over.
Where is the delicious little chat-bay?
Right, out, all of you!
He find the last one.
I finds this one.
This be my home.
You don't come in here any more!
Go on, get out!
Curse you, be Runt.
Get out!
This be my home!
You. You is insult to giants.
Well, there be my dreams
disappeared into a thick ear.
Into thin air.
Words.
There's so such a twitch-tickling
problem to me all my life.
I knows exactly what
words I want to say
but somehow they all come
out squish squiddled round.
Don't worry. That happens to everyone.
Not like it happens to me,
I speaking the most terrible wigglish.
Well, I think you speak beautifully.
You do? You really do?
Uh hum.
Simply beautifully.
That is the nicest present that anybody
has ever given me in my entire life.
BFG?
Oh, woopsie splunkers!
How absolutely - what's the word - squiffling.
BFG!
I's all of a stutter!
Yeah, yeah.
I have a plan.
A plan?
We are going to the Queen.
We really really need her help.
We can be there by dawn.
Right, you be giving your queenie
a frightsome curd-bloodling
troggle-humper
Needs must.
Scary as you can make it.
The Queen will dream that giants, all
nine of them, are in England.
And they are eating little children.
Be sure to put some army in it.
Be sure you have a little of me.
Did you add yourself?
The Queen will dream,
that a little girl
is sitting on her window sill.
Then, she wakes up, and I am there.
We are there.
And then what happens?
Well. Then a
Big Friendly Giant steps forward
and bows and says..
Your Majesty.
I am your humble servant.
You mean she actually sees me?
No, not in a month of Mondays, gal.
BFG, stop.
You're going to knock me off.
I'm trying to listen to the different
breathing of manly bean and lady bean.
No. No no
No, horrible.
Make them stop.
Giants. Giants!
Horrible. Man-eating giants!
No, stop. No! No!
No no no.
Your Majesty?
What is it?
Mary.
I had the most horrible dream.
Well, only a dream, ma'am.
Let me get your tea.
I dreamed that girls and boys were snatched
out of their beds in boarding schools
and were being eaten by
the most ghastly giants.
There was so many of them.
There was the Flesh Lump Eater.
and the Gizzard Gulper
and the Meat Dripper
and the..
Butcher Boy.
I'm sorry
The giants put their hands
in through the windows,
and plucked the children
out with their fingers.
It was so bloody,
so vivid, so real.
So real, Mary.
The children just disappeared.
Oh my.
What the matter, dear?
You're white as a sheet.
Well sit down. Mary, sit.
You're trembling.
What is it?
It's just..
It's so odd, ma'am.
So very odd.
You haven't seen the papers?
No, I haven't seen them yet.
Here. Look.
It's the very dream you had.
Children have disappeared in the
night. Gone. Taken.
But not by giants.
Well, no, it couldn't be,
could it ma'am.
Draw the curtains.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh!
I don't believe it.
There's a small girl standing
on the window sill.
Is there not, Mr. Tibbs.
There is indeed, ma'am.
She is standing right there, ma'am.
You didn't dream it.
But I did dream it.
How in the world did you get there?
Well...
Let me handle this ma'am,
come down.
No, no, don't do that.
A giant put you there.
Yes, he did, ma'am.
He's waiting in the garden now.
Is he?
He's my best friend.
He made your dream.
Did he?
Queen's garden.
Rear window, please.
Why have you and your
giant come to see me?
I think you would remember that,
Your Majesty, if the mixing went well.
Yes. I remember.
You have a plan.
You need me.
Yes. We do.
Should we call for him now?
I suppose we should.
You promise you won't
hurt him, ma'am?
Rear garden, rear garden please.
I'm ready.
BFG.
BFG, the queen would
really like to meet you.
You won't put him in the bunkum house?
Come down from there, child.
Mary, take her downstairs and
get her some breakfast,
Mr. Tibbs, find out where she comes from.
No no. He's just afraid. He's never done
anything like this in his whole life before.
BFG.
Be brave.
You promised you wouldn't hurt him.
Mr. Tibbs.
Tell the guards to stand down.
Stand down, gentlemen, please.
Stand down.
Dear. Come here.
Your Majesty, I am your humble servant.
Youe Majester, I is your humbug servant.
I am so pleased to make
your acquaintance.
Oh Majester, oh monarcher, oh ruler..
of straight lines.
I's come with my little
friend Sophie to give you a...
To give me what?
Assistance.
Thank you, I'm sure you have,
but not in my dressing gown.
Giants, Boris. Man-eating giants.
Have people been disappearing?
We have verifiable intelligence.
We might need air clearance.
I'll get back to you.
Nancy, is Ronnie there?
Well, wake him.
Her Majesty the Queen.
This way, sir.
Just follow me
Follow me.
That's it, sir.
Slow ahead, careful.
And full stop.
The port side sir.
Careful of the antiques, sir.
And up. Up.
Careful, up, up.
That's it.
Hard to port.
And slow.. ahead.
Steady. Yes sir.
Boggswinkles! What was that?
That was Louis quatorze.
I'm so, so, so sorry, Your Majesty.
He's never really been
in a house before.
Your cape, sir.
What a whupsi spliffering room we is in.
Your valet, sir.
Your Majesty.
This room is so gigantous I's needed
bi-circulars and telescopes
to see what's going on at either end.
Does he always talk like that?
Yes, Your Majesty.
He's never had schooling.
Sir.
Please BFG, start.
There is only one word
for that, Majester.
Scrum-diddly-umptious!
Oh. That is glummy.
Good bye snascomber!
What's snascomber?
It's this horrible stinky vegetable and
I'm afraid it's all he has to eat.
Doesn't seem to have
stunted his growth at all.
Poor BFG his coffee please.
What's that?
What's that black stuff.
What's all that foam?
He's magnificent, your giant.
Sophie, dear, do start.
You must be famished.
It's delumptious.
Oggle-frunk.
Please, Majester. What is this horrible
swig-pill I was drinking, Majester?
Would he prefer tea?
Would prefer frobscuttel.
Frobscuttel?
A little gift for Your Majester.
Delumptious fizzy frobscuttel.
It be a personable for rent.
How kind.
Would Your Majester be so kind
as to honor me with...
a pour?
It's fizzing the wrong way.
Our bubbles go up.
Yeah. We would have some
galumptious whizzpopping music.
Does he like music?
We have bagpipes.
The generals have been briefed, ma'am.
This is a story that beggars belief,
but we don't have the time.
We're on our way to giant country.
BFG will chart a course for you.
Generals, BFG.
In 10 hours, the giants will
once again be on the hunt
and I intend to stop them.
And where exactly
is giant country, sir.
Where is it?
There.
What?
Gentlemen, your men
will follow the BFG.
I have promised him that you
will go only once to giant country.
You'll not be finding
it a second time.
Just look at those bubbles.
I believe in the BFG.
The BFG.
To the BFG
Marvellous bubbles.
To giant country.
We will hold here.
BFG. I'm asking if you have a plan.
BFG? Do you have a plan?
BFG. Do you have a plan?
The troggle-humper I caught.
You're giving it to the giants?
Yes, I's giving the boys the
most horridest dream of despair.
If the dream does its job, they wakes
trapped in flush-bunkun remorse.
And if those whuppsie belly poppers
out there does their job,
then I think we stands a chance.
Look at what you has done,
and there be no forgiveness.
Needs must.
Now, stand back, gal.
We has brought the hunt
to giant country.
What is Sophie's dream?
A golden fizzwizard.
I don't see much of them any more.
But what does it say?
It tells the story of a little girl.
A little chiddler, with her
whole life ahead of her.
With a family of her own.
Little chiddlers of her own, too, someday.
There'll be great successfuls
and funnies ahead for her.
Truth to tell, just a dribble of despair.
Times'd be hard, times'd be soft.
Adventures'd come and go.
But in the end,
she remembers the good deeds.
Now, Sophie, I know
that story be your hearts desire.
I knows it.
The dream, it came to you, didn't it?
It be Sophie's dream.
But then I wake up.
And you wakes up.
But not here.
No, you has more dreams to catch,
my little froggle-frump.
But not in giant country.
But will I still have you?
Will you still hear me when I call for you?
Are you forgetting something?
Are you forgetting these?
It be time, BFG.
Now, where did I put the...
I left me trumpet at Her Majesters.
I'm such a mixed up
boggled up giant sometimes.
Deliver us from weasels.
Sophie.
Oh no.
Oh no, Sophie.
And what does we have here?
You is a cannibal!
I is bad!
Have pity on a poor little giant!
You are a very bad giant.
I has no regrets.
Runt.
Run Sophie, run.
It's over, Flesh Lump Eater.
It's over, boy.
It's time to stop now.
I's always hungry.
Come on lads!
Take him away!
The giants were taken far, far away
to a place you've never heard of
and a place you'll never go.
The Queen sent them off with snascomber
seeds. It was all they would have to eat
and they were just going
to have to get used to it.
It's time to wake up, darling.
Morning, Sophie.
I had a dream last night.
In the dream I was awakened by a beautiful
buzzing humming noise floating above my bed.
I walk to the window and
against the horizon
I saw his long legs leaping,
suitcase and trumpet in hand.
I could see all the way
to giant country,
I could see the garden
BFG was growing.
He had fruits and berries,
cauliflower and tomatoes
He refused to have Brussels sprouts,
though,
but snascombers were still
growing beside his cottage
How else would he make frobscuttel?
I saw the stone door and
the crooked windows.
His cape was hanging by the door.
I saw the crow's nest,
and his sailor boat bed.
I saw his rocking chair and the
fire burning in the fireplace.
With a much nicer stew cooking.
I could see the scattered pages
of the book he was writing.
He was happy
and I was happy.
When I'm lonely, which is
not nearly as often as before
I talk to him and he actually hears me,
because BFG hears all the secret
whispering of the world.
Good morning, BFG.
Psagmeno.com | No1 Subs iNFO