Don't.
There's no place for
you in the human world.
I beg to differ, sister.
There is.
Gina,
darling, listen to me.
I'm not talk to you as an agent.
I'm talking to you as a friend.
SHE WOLF RISING
Subrip: Pix
It's not the right
project for you.
It's not what you do best.
And you have no idea
what I'm capable of.
Just give me the goddamn
scorsese audition
and I'll show you.
You don't
have to show me anything.
I know you're a good actress.
The best in your field.
Yeah well, maybe
I'm better to move on
to a bigger and
better field.
Darling, I believe you
and I believe in you,
but there's no way I can
get you into that audition.
Why? Because I'm a
fucking scream queen?
What do
you want me to say, Gina?
I want you to say
that you'll do your job
and get me the audition.
Excuse me.
Do you even have a
photo of yourself
that doesn't have you
dripping in blood?
I have a perfect shot.
God help me.
Okay, put your picture
in an envelope.
Shit.
Tape
it to your door.
If Pete doesn't see
it when he drives by,
you know he won't stop.
Shit.
Sorry darling,
you know he's a pain in the ass.
No, it's 'cause I
just cut my finger
'cause you got me aggravated!
B-blood alive.
Shut the hell up.
You know.
Just need a new goddamn agent.
Stupid bullshit.
New agent is what I have to do.
Then I'll get good parts.
Shit. Fuck. Fuck.
God damn it.
Fuck.
Say hello to your boss for me.
It's like I told ya,
you can run but you cannot hide.
Rufus gon' cut you
side to side.
No!
What the fuck'd you do that for?
Fuck!
Hahaha.
No!
Fuck you!
You dumb twat.
What the fuck'd you have
to go and do that for?
Anyway, it's okay.
It's okay.
No, it's alright,
everything gon' be,
everything gon' be just fine.
I can still carve you up.
Why Rufus, you are one
sick, mother fuckin' puppy,
you know that?
Thank you, Professor.
Hahahaha.
Shit!
What the fuck are you?
You're a fuckin' zombie!
You're a fuckin' cunt!
I know you! You're a
fuckin' zombie, right?
I'm part of
Amy, Professor.
Hahaha, fuck!
Shit!
Dude, that was so
totally fucking awesome.
I mean, that fucking rocks.
What'd you think of her?
Do you really need to
ask me that question?
If she was vomiting and
had explosive diarrhea,
I still wouldn't
kick her outta bed.
I would climb up into her ass.
I would build a summer home
and I would vacation
there on the weekends.
How the hell did you get
your hands on this DVD?
The movie's not even out yet.
I know, right?
Tell me, you fuck!
Trust me, I wish I could.
But...
Do you need me to
punch you in the dick?
Is that what you need?
Alright, you ever
had one of those things
where you're not really
sure if you're dreaming
or if it's real?
Mmhmm.
You're gonna think I'm nuts.
Dude, I've known you
since kindergarten.
There's no doubt in
my mind that you're
a big ol' fuckin' bag of crazy.
Tell me!
You know you want to.
Alright, I'll tell you
but you gotta promise
not to tell anybody.
Alright, so I was in the
magazine store, right?
And I was tryin'
to distract myself,
get my mind off Allison.
Then, I saw it.
Saw what?
The latest issue
of Dude On Dude?
You're a dick. No.
The latest issue
of Scream Sirens
with none other than
Gina Skylar on the cover.
Dude, I have that issue.
I love that issue.
Like, that issue could be
the ultimate homo test.
If you don't catch wood
lookin' at that picture,
bing, you're a frickin' homo.
Did you read the
article on the inside?
No. What for? I
looked at the picture.
The magazine was
just the overture.
Continue.
As I read the
article, I realized
that there was a lot more
to this princess of darkness
than meets the eye.
True, her curvacious
body was the cause
for the petrified
forest in my pants,
but her eyes?
Her eyes as beautiful
as they were
seemed to be crying
out for me to help.
I clung to every word as
I read her intimate story.
My heart's rhythm changed.
My breathing changed.
Suddenly, the world
seemed different.
I felt lighter and more
alive than ever before.
Something was happening to me.
It was frightening and
exhilarating at the same time.
I wanted and thirsted for more.
I eternally ached for
this euphoric sensation
my entire life.
And now the doors have opened
letting in a
fantasmagoric feeling
that I surrender to completely.
Thank you.
Do you want me to sign that?
That would be awesome.
Awesome.
Do you have a pen?
Hold on.
Hey, can I borrow a pen?
No.
What do you think this
is, a charity center?
If you want a pen,
you gotta buy it.
If you're gonna write
in that magazine,
you gotta buy that shit too.
This ain't a fuckin' library.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Jake.
Turn around, Jake.
What?
There you go.
Thank you.
Maybe I'll see
you around, Jake.
Hey asshole, this
isn't enough money.
You still owe me 30 cents.
Dipshit.
No fucking way.
Way.
I never went home that night
because I lost the magazine.
The magazine in which
Gina Skylar wrote,
"I'm sure we'll meet again."
Those words vibrated
up and down my spine.
I kept thinking about
her and wondering
would I ever see her again?
How are you, young man?
You're Jake, right?
This was unbelievable.
Robert Lonzo, the
biggest producer
of horror films in the world
was calling my name.
He's the man responsible
for discovering Gina Skylar.
Yeah, I am.
Come here!
I hear you're a
gentleman and a real fan.
I guess.
Don't guess, ya either
are or you're not.
No, I am, sir.
Good! Would ya like to get in?
It's been a long time since I've
spoken to a real fan.
Don't worry. I'm not queer.
Besides, Gina's in here too.
Sure!
I listened to Mr. Lonzo
as he told his war stories
of how he had to fight
to get the credibility
and recognition his
movies deserved.
Under ordinary circumstances,
I would have been riveted
in every syllable.
But just knowing that
Gina was a glance away
was more than I could handle.
She's even more
beautiful in person
than she is on the screen.
Hey kid, how would
you like to help me
cast my next movie?
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I want you to help me
cast my next movie.
I guess.
What would I have to do?
Just tell me if you
think the girls have
talent.
It's gonna be super fun.
Jake.
Never in my
wildest imagination
could I have anticipated what
was about to happen to me.
I can't take it anymore.
Why doesn't shit like
this happen to me?
Why?
Why don't you just go home?
I'll catch up with you tomorrow.
No! I'm stayin'!
You're telling me
the whole story!
Woah.
Look,
it's pathetic, I know.
I got no life.
I got no job.
I got no girlfriend.
I hadn't washed my underwear
in like three weeks.
I need to hear every
single detail of this story
and if you leave out one
mother fuckin' thing,
I'll kill you.
Lonzo told me
there were two things
he looks for in talent.
I think he meant three.
Looking back, I kinda
feel like a pervert.
I watched Lonzo as he
took detailed notes
of each girl that went by.
Some of them would dance close
and I could see him hide
his little note pad.
He was a consummate
professional.
I, on the other hand, was
his complete opposite.
I couldn't concentrate
on any of the strippers.
I had only one girl in my mind.
I just had to get outta there.
My brain was on
overload and I felt
I couldn't trust
any of my senses.
I found solitude
in the men's room.
Don't turn around.
Listen to me very carefully.
Okay?
Lonzo's in trouble.
But, I,
Don't talk, baby.
Just listen.
Lonzo's in trouble
and I need your help.
It's gonna be very dangerous,
but if my gut is telling me
the right thing about you,
I know that you're the
right one for the job.
Can you handle it, Jake?
Will you help me?
I desperately
searched for the words
to let her know that I
would do anything for her.
But all that came out
was, "Okie dokie."
Okie dokie.
Really, really love a
man that has no command
for the English language.
So,
here's my home address.
My personal number
is in your back pocket.
You call me later
and I'll tell you
what we're doing next.
Don't be nervous.
That's better.
See ya later?
Do you have any idea
how good that tongue felt?
No, I'd like to try.
Worked for George Michael.
Goddamn
bitch. Well, I warned her.
Shit.
I don't wanna do all this
fuckin' work for her.
Damn it.
Ya know what, this'll show her.
That's it. This is it.
This is the final place.
This is where she belongs.
Yeah, that's right, yeah.
Yeah, I told her.
I warned her.
God, I can't believe this.
I can't believe I'm doing
all this damn work for her.
Should just throw her body
down the fuckin' hill.
Yeah, well no, no, this
is a better place for her.
Yeah, I showed her.
You always were a cold bitch.
Shit!
Where the fuck is my wallet?
Shit.
This is not happening.
This is not fucking happening!
Where to?
Just up the road a bit.
I don't know.
I'd be grateful.
Alright, get in.
So, do you have any gum?
Can I have it?
Where the hell
did you get this?
You tell me where
you fuckin' got this
or you're fuckin' gonna die.
You gave it to me.
You're dead meat, missy.
And what's
wrong with dead meat?
Hello?
Gina?
Hey,
it's Jake.
Did you just call me or?
Were you just at my apartment?
Did you give
me your phone number?
I don't think so.
Did you tell
me where you live?
No.
I don't even
know your last name.
It's Bubar. Jake Bubar.
Well, Mr. Jake Bubar,
I'll see ya at 10:30.
Do you need my phone number?
I have caller ID.
Well, do you
need my address?
Hello?
That is truly fucking weird.
I thought so too.
My heart raced as I
walked down the hallway
to Gina's apartment.
I couldn't wait
to see her again.
Could I be bold enough to think
that we might have
a future together?
Stop it! I'm way
ahead of myself.
One step at a time.
Hi.
You must be Jake.
Yeah.
Gina's told us all about you.
Is she in there?
Don't be silly.
It's just me and Lace.
Okay.
Hey Jake.
Come sit down.
Holy snikies.
She said sit down.
Jake.
This is gonna take a while.
Baseball,
baseball, baseball,
baseball, baseball.
Baseball,
baseball, baseball, baseball,
baseball, baseball,
baseball, baseball.
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Do you want me to continue?
I'm so fucking deprived.
Couldn't possibly
get any worse for me.
Well.
Just finish the fucking story.
Having fun, Jake?
What's this all about?
They think
you're a hot shot
Hollywood producer
looking for talent.
Why do they think that?
'Cause I told them.
Hurry up, meet me at the
Chinese restaurant downtown.
Fine. Bye.
Girls, I have to go.
You were great.
I'll have my people get
in touch with your people
and then they can all
touch each other.
Okay.
Hey!
Hey.
How are ya? Are ya hungry?
No. Just coffee.
Hey Bets. Can I get
coffee for my friend here?
You know we
don't serve coffee.
Only green tea, hun.
That'd be fine.
Green tea ice cream?
The usual?
Absolutely.
Anything for you?
No, that's it. Thanks.
You okay?
What's up with your friends?
What friends?
Lace and Gwen?
Yeah, those aren't my friends.
Then why did
you send me there?
I needed to get
Lace outta the place
so I can deal with a little
detective work, ya know?
So, you used me.
No! No.
My head's just been crazy.
I've been all over the place.
I didn't meant to use you.
I'm sorry.
You said Lonzo is in
some kind of trouble.
What sort of trouble?
Somebody stole the footage to
Vampire Psychos Suck.
Your new movie?
His new movie.
I was just lucky
enough to be in it.
Unfortunately, it's gone
and it's my best work.
Better than Blood Poison?
I can't wait to see it.
Well, doesn't he
have some kind of
movie insurance?
This is a low-budget
world, Jake.
We're not a big
company. No money.
No insurance.
Well, why doesn't
he just reshoot?
Because he broke
the cardinal rule
of independent film making
and he used his own money.
Now he's flat broke.
Thanks.
Anything for you?
I'm okay. Thank you.
This is his best movie yet.
It's movie gold. It's his
ticket to the big league.
Well, Lonzo's lucky
to have a friend like you.
Me? I was workin' at
K-Mart when he discovered me.
He came in to buy an
axe for body choppers.
Your first movie?
Yeah.
I didn't believe him.
Anyway, 48 months
later, 33 films later,
eight box covers, four
chiller conventions,
I've got a gazillion
members to my website.
Number one scream queen
and I owe it all to him.
Will you help me
find the footage?
Gina, I don't know.
I'm sorry. I know it's
a lot to ask. Forget it.
I'm sorry. I just.
You're a sweet guy.
I shouldn't mix you up
in things like this.
Forget I said anything.
You have a little.
What?
-On your.
Shit.
I just got my nails done.
Would you?
Sure.
You can use your finger.
That way it doesn't set in.
I'll do it.
Whatever you want.
Whatever you need, just ask.
I knew I could count on you.
This is great.
I absolutely
love this place.
It looks really familiar.
Yeah? Maniac Warehouse
one, two, three,
and the prequel?
Of course!
This is where all the
dead bodies were stored.
You got it.
This is great.
All that shit,
there's still body
parts in all of those.
But, why are we here?
I got the keys, ya know,
so we could shoot stuff
here when we needed to,
and I thought you would like it.
You're a fan, right?
Yeah!
Yeah? Do you like it?
What was that for?
'Cause you're
cute and I like you.
Well, that's great to hear.
Woah.
We have work to do, Jake.
Can't always just be about play.
We're detectives
now and we're almost
on the verge of figuring
this whole thing out.
Of course.
Sure you're right.
Probably.
But once all this
detective work is finished,
then
Then?
You can have
anything you want.
Are you okay?
Wait,
I think I just came in my pants.
Get the hell of my
-cushion now!
Nah, come on, dude.
So.
Shit, nobody's supposed
to be here. Come here.
We're not supposed to be here.
It's Lonzo.
He doesn't look good.
Quiet on the set!
Roll sound and action!
What's he doing?
Shut up.
Cut!
Let's do it again.
Get more blood in there!
I want more blood in there!
Make it flow like the piss
at port authorities bathroom.
Shit.
Do it now!
That's a wrap.
The calla lilies
are in bloom again.
What's he doing?
Shut up.
As God as my witness,
if I have to lie,
cheat, beg, or steal,
I'll never be hungry again!
As God as my witness!
I think he's lost it.
No, he hasn't lost it.
A lot of people don't know
that he's a film historian.
His love for art,
film, boundless.
He once told me that he
gets all his strength
through great moments in cinema.
Then, when he hits rock bottom,
he recites lines
from classic movies.
Tonight, as the clouds
are dancing around the moon,
I'll be dancing around you!
You and the moon.
You wear a necktie
so I know it's you.
I wish I had some popcorn.
Shit's not funny.
He's in pain.
Yo, Mick! What about my prime?
You help me, Polack!
I don't believe you have
the nerve in your body.
Lonzo.
I knelt before
the bed of death.
No, no, no, no. No.
I knew that there
was but one thing
that could bring you back to me.
The scroll of Thor.
No, don't do that.
What is it?
I'm a scream queen, you idiot.
So?
And so I dare the God's anger
and stole it.
I'm a true scream queen.
I hear lines recited
from famous hor,
horror films.
They broke in on me
and found me doing
an unholy thing.
God.
Tie my hands up.
What?
Tie my hands up!
They're
coming for you, Barbara.
Look! There's one of them now!
Shit!
Take my pants off
and tie up my legs.
Shit.
Hurry!
The spider spinning the
web for the unworthy fly.
Tighter. Tie
it fuckin' tighter.
Now put something in my mouth.
I am gonna learn
every frickin' word
to Halloween two.
Put something in my mouth.
What?
Put your goddamn
shirt in my mouth!
Take it off and put it
in my fuckin' mouth.
Now! Hurry up!
The blood is the
life, Mr. Renfield.
Okay?
Even the man
who's pure at heart
and says his prayers at night
can become a wolf when
the woofbane blooms.
The Autumn moon is
pure and bright.
'Tis a lovely day
for an exorcism!
I'll be right back, okay?
Gina,
I'll be right back.
Mr. Lonzo.
Fuck!
This is gettin'
better every minute.
What the fuck happened next?
Mr. Lonzo, are you alright?
Auntie Em, there's
no place like home.
You're gonna be
alright, Mr. Lonzo.
Gina?
Mr. Lonzo?
Okay, okay.
This is one of
those reality shows.
I just need to figure out where
all the camera's are hidden.
Okay, I get it!
I get it. You can tell me
where the camera's are now.
Okay, this is a little creepy.
Just listen to your inner voice.
What would your inner
voice tell you to do?
Get the fuck out.
Gina?
And where are you from?
I resemble that remark.
But, never you mind, you swine.
I'd horsewhip you
if I had a horse.
Now, down to business.
Say the secret word and the
girl of your dreams will appear.
What?
Wrong word but,
don't worry, be happy.
We have a constellation
prize for you.
The girl of your nightmares!
And here she is
fresh from the crypt,
fully loaded with
chewed up maggots
and rotting flesh,
dadadadadadaaaa!
It's Lillian!
Lillian, Lillian.
Have you screwed Lillian?
Lillian, the creepy lady?
Well, I can see that the
two of you want to be alone.
No, don't!
I'll be on my way.
Let's get nasty.
Woah.
I need to watch a Disney movie.
Who is it?
Hey.
Are you okay?
What happened to you? I
was worried about you.
You know how happy I am
that you've been
helping me with this?
You're amazing.
But I have to do the
rest of this on my own.
Are you crazy?
Listen, I promised you
that I was gonna help you.
And I'm not backing down until
we recover that missing footage.
I appreciate that.
But
I'm a scream queen.
It doesn't matter
to me what you are.
I care about you.
You pussy whooped bastard.
What would you have done?
Well I,
alright, go on.
I'll be careful. I promise.
Now let's come up with a plan.
I just don't want
anything to happen to you.
If someone's following
you or trying to stop you,
then you're definitely
not the right person
to be handling
this investigation.
You sound so official.
Just give me a hit list
of all your potential
suspects, okay?
I'll do what I did with
Gwen and her friend.
I'll follow them and
then, at the right moment,
I'll question them.
Yeah, that
actually could work.
I mean, you could say that
you're doing an interview
for like Sirens of Cinema or
Fango or something like that.
And if I tell them that
I've already interviewed you,
that'll give me
instant credibility
and maybe they'll
loosen up a little bit.
My hero.
I think we should wait.
Til all this is done.
Ya know, til we,
go to the next level.
Whatever you say, boss.
Wait. Wait a minute.
I just realized something.
Gina Skylar was standing here
in this apartment.
Yeah. So?
So?
I think I can, I can,
she sat on this
couch, didn't she?
I think I can taste
her in my mouth.
I can, she's actually
in my mouth right now.
Dude.
It's delicious.
Dude, you really
gotta get a girlfriend.
Eat me.
Gina kept
referring to herself
as a true scream queen, which
would get her very distressed.
So, I searched the
libraries and internet
and the only item I found
that made any reference
was a screenplay titled,
"The True Scream Queen".
A script that was
optioned by Robert Lonzo,
but never made.
Now this was getting weird.
I was able to get some
info about the writer,
Kiara Lupanel.
She had a bestselling
novel published
when she was 16 and had
written seven movies for Lonzo.
This was way freaky, but
I knew I had to see her.
I called her using the
guise of being a writer
doing an article about her
and she agreed to see me.
But once I arrived at her home,
well let's just say I
wasn't exactly prepared
for what was waiting for me.
Kiara.
Mr. Bubar?
Yes.
It's a true pleasure to meet
another artist of the pen.
You flatter me.
I'm not even close to
being in your league.
I won't hold it against you
as long as you
don't disappoint me.
You're much younger
than I thought you'd be.
And more beautiful.
She sleeps.
Rem?
Leave us for now.
Nice dress.
I absolutely adore dressing up
as the characters I write about.
Should we move
away from the chair?
I don't wanna wake her.
She sleeps like the death.
Is she part vampire?
Don't make jokes
about my Mother.
She can get quite angry.
You may begin your
interview now.
Alright, why does
a writing prodigy
put her novels on hold to write,
forgive me, B horror
films for Robert Lonzo?
Is that really what
you want to ask me?
Then, I shall indulge you.
I live through the
characters I write about.
Their hopes, fears,
passions are all mine.
A few years ago, you
wrote a screenplay.
The True Scream Queen.
Robert Lonzo optioned it but
the movie was never made.
Someone's been
doing their homework.
He produced seven of your
scripts, but not that one.
And why is this of
such great importance to you?
I have a friend and she says
she's a true scream queen.
A young, aspiring
actress looking to
break into movies through
the horror corridor.
No, nothing like that.
Gina's a superstar.
Gina? Gina Skylar?
Yeah. Do you know her?
That movie will never be
made. Mother forbids it.
Please tell me more.
I have to know what is
a true scream queen?
Something you
need to be far away from.
Please.
I think I'm in love with her.
Are you familiar with the
story of Romulus and Remus?
Didn't they
nurse from some wolf?
Not some wolf, Mr. Bubar.
The she-wolf, Lupa.
The true mother of Rome.
She nursed the twins and
saved them from peril.
When the boys grew up, the
wolf would take human form
and protect and guide them.
Without her, there
would be no Rome,
no Caesar, no glory!
How does that relate
to a true scream queen?
Their lineage is connected.
They share similar
traits because they're
from the same source.
The she-wolf is
motivated to protect
and nurture the helpless.
When she rises up and
changes from wolf to human,
she has a rational side
and a kind, gentle heart
that cares and loves.
Contrary, the scream
queens transmutation
from human to wolf,
or better yet demon,
loses all reason, purpose,
and compassion.
Even if that is true,
she would never hurt me.
We have feelings
for one another.
She might have
feelings for you,
but the beast does not.
Why are you saying beast?
She's absolutely beautiful.
The belladonna
plant is beautiful.
It's also the deadliest plant
in the Northern hemisphere.
Say that it is true.
What could make her
change? A full moon?
This is not a horror
movie, Mr. Bubar.
It's reality.
I don't understand.
Every she-wolf
has their trigger.
It's ingrained at a young age
and when that trigger is
pulled, no one is safe.
So, you're telling me that,
Be cautious, Mr. Bubar.
Rem?
Show Mr. Bubar out.
I cannot believe he's in
love with her. It's not fair!
Bellisima.
Why does Gina get to walk
in the world of gardens
that I write about?
Do you think
I love her more than you?
Will Gina ever come home?
I don't know.
I must get back to work.
Say the secret
word and the girl
of your dreams will appear.
Let's get nasty.
The heart becomes
salvage, Mr. Bubar.
salvage.
I spent
the next two days
interviewing Lonzo's crew.
I was astonished at
how happy they all were
given the fact that most of them
lived just above
the poverty level.
Just a creepy old car,
Jake. No big deal. Right?
What a creepy old car.
Harry?
Yeah?
I'm Jake.
Have a seat, Jake.
Would you like some?
I'm good.
I've already eaten
lunch, but thank you.
Ya know, at first,
I didn't like sardines.
I didn't even like
the name sardines,
especially the way they smelled.
I'm sorry. Takes a
while to get used to.
But when you do,
they're like a woman.
You can't get enough.
And you always want more,
you know what I'm sayin'?
I actually just have
a couple questions.
On the last day
of Lonzo's shoot,
you were the one to put
away the equipment, right?
Yeah, I was there but,
Mr. Lonzo told me
to leave early.
So you weren't
the last one to leave?
No.
Ya know, after
one of our shoots,
Mr. Lonzo gave me
two whole cases.
He couldn't pay us
'cause the distributors
check bounced.
And he wanted to make sure
we got enough protein.
You know how much
protein there is
in one can of sardines?
No.
More than three
whole steaks. Yes sir.
I love that guy. He cares so
much about the little people.
You sure you don't want any?
I, I'm okay.
I'm okay, thanks.
Put hair on your chest.
Lead in your pencil.
Actually, I think
that's all I need but,
it was great meeting you.
Thank you so much
for meeting with me.
Take care.
You too.
Yeah.
Miss Bell?
Call me Flame.
Hi, I'm Jake.
I know. The guy
from the magazine?
That's right.
I hope you don't
mind if I continue
my workout while we talk.
Otherwise, I'll
never get it done.
No, of course.
I hope these questions
aren't gonna be too personal.
I got interviewed once by a guy
pretending to be
from a magazine.
He turned out to
be some pervert.
What happened?
I dropped a bar
bell on his crotch.
Last I heard, he
became a candidate
for a sex change operation.
Don't worry. You have
nothing to be afraid of.
Besides, you're kinda cute.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What?
Rawr.
It's okay. I can handle it.
Hey, can you do me a favor?
Sure, if I can.
I wanna make sure I'm
doing really good push ups.
So, can you just put your hand
on the floor and make sure my
chest touches it each time?
The floor?
No, silly, your hand.
What did I do in
my life to deserve
to be subjected to these
thoughts and images
that torture my young soul?
Even Buddha got to touch
more tit than this.
I just see these films
as a stepping stone
to my final career plateau.
Well, what
is that plateau?
Playboy magazine, of course.
Can you be completely
honest with me?
Sure.
Tell me what you
think of these.
I mean, do you think
they're Playboy material?
I can do this. I can do this.
I can do this.
I mean, they're
really n..., they look...
Do you want to feel them?
Actually, I just
had one question.
Don't bother. They're real.
That's not what
I was gonna ask but,
good for you.
Thank you.
Why weren't you at
Lonzo's last wrap party?
That's a weird question.
I'll tell you
but then I'm gonna
have to kill you.
What?
I'm only kidding.
It's okay.
So anyway.
I've had to make a wee wee
for like an hour and a half
and I'm not leaving this room
until I hear every single
detail of that story.
If I gotta piss in
my pants, so be it.
Okay.
I'll tell you everything.
But I swear to God, if
you pee on my floor,
I'm never talking to you again.
Okay.
You got any more chips?
I was down to the
last person on Gina's list.
An old timer named
Charlie Graves.
Mr. Graves?
Youngblood.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Here, take a look at that.
Is that you?
I was a handsome
devil, wasn't I?
Mr. Graves, is that Thomas
Edison in the picture with you?
Exactly how long have
you been in the business?
Not long enough.
I still have a few
purty movies left in me but,
I don't know if I'm gonna last.
Until I get some.
Unless what?
I get some young!
Yeah, funny.
I didn't scare you
too much, did I?
No. Not at all.
It's alright, kid. We're
all scared of something.
Fear.
It lets you know you're
alive and makes your
heart race and your blood pump.
It's the next best thing to sex.
Why do you think so many people
watch scary movies?
I guess I never
thought of it that way.
When you've been around
as long as I've been,
you see things a whole new way.
One's vision and take
on things become clear.
-Can I ask you one last question?
-Go right ahead, young blood.
Is there such a thing
as a true scream queen?
Where did you hear that?
Who told you about that?
I just heard some people.
Now, that's some bullshit.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll answer your question.
It's a myth.
But I thought.
But that's all I got to say.
It's a myth.
Well, thank you very
much for meeting with me.
I appreciate you
taking the time.
It was nice meeting you.
And remember one
thing, young blood.
Charlie Graves doesn't lie.
It's a myth.
My God.
That was the
best fun of my day.
It was awesome!
My God.
I have, I have the best
time when I'm with you.
Me too.
With yourself?
No, with you.
Dumb actress. Can't
do stuff like that.
It's Lonzo.
Hey.
No, please don't say
that. It's not over.
That's a wrap.
Lonzo, please, just trust me.
We'll get it figured out.
Yes, we will.
Hello?
I'm so sorry.
What?
I let you down.
You didn't let me down.
You're crazy.
You're the only person that
I've ever known in my life
that would risk their
own safety for me.
That's pretty awesome.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
Yeah, you shouldn't have.
I love this art work.
Yeah.
It's always about good box art.
Not when you're in them.
You really are a fan?
Hey.
Who's Tony Boca and why
haven't we checked him out?
Tony
produced a bunch
of Lonzo's movies
back in the day and
kinda got bored with
it all, I think.
He retired and he
owns car washes now.
Well, we have to follow
up with every suspect.
Not that guy.
No way. Forget about it.
He grew up with Lonzo.
They were best friends.
He would never hurt him.
Well, who else is left?
Doesn't hurt, right?
His place is like two
miles down the road.
Lonzo!
That was his car.
Lonzo! Lonzo.
Lonzo!
Lonzo.
Little late for a car
wash, don't ya think?
Why would you do this to
him? He was your friend.
He cut me off
for no good reason.
No. You retired.
No, no.
He got rid of me.
This business
is full of rejection.
You, of all people,
should know that.
I can't believe you're
talkin' to me like that.
Why don't
you just let him go,
you dumb fucking grease monkey?
That a nice thing to be saying
to a guy with a gun?
Watch it. Put that back.
Real tough guy now
when you have a gun?
I don't need a gun for
a two bit scream queen.
Two bit.
I'm number one scream
queen, ya fucking jerk off.
I'm gonna feel a
lot better knowing
I killed a number
one scream queen
rather than a number two.
Just do it, you dickless fuck.
Myth or no myth, please work.
Jake!
Now that you have become
what you have become,
it is best that you go
back to your country.
And leave Transylvania forever!
Who the fuck are
you supposed to be?
I am Dracula.
Ahaha.
Put your hands down.
Get down on the floor. I'm
gonna cut her heart out.
Listen to them, the
children of the night.
What the?
What music they make.
Are you kidding me?
As the spider spins the
web for the unworthy fly.
Gina? Gina? Is
that really you?
Gina. Gina, what
are you doing?
Now we can fuck!
Okay.
I can't.
I can't!
No.
You had me going there.
That was good. I
was with you there.
You're good.
I swear it's all true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
Hey listen, thanks
for the food, man.
You should write
that bullshit down.
I mean, I didn't believe
you but, pretty good story.
Might make a good
movie or something.
Call ya tomorrow.
We'll get some beers.
Keep it gay.
What'd you forget?
Gina?
It's over.
It's over!
Hey, that was a
damn good movie.
It's a crossover
film for sure!
I thought it sucked.
An overnight success
that took 15 years.
Am I right, Eddie?
I thought it sucked.
I really love the part
where the whipped cream
got cleaned off.
You would.
Hey, what are
you trying to say?
You got a problem with that?
Go eat a sardine.
Fabulous idea.
I smell like fish
'cause I love sardines.
What's your excuse?
Asshole.
Hey Ed, what's taking
Rufus and Lillian
so long to get back
with the champagne?
Probably having sex.
That's disgusting.
Not when I do it, baby.
Asshole.
Guys, take it easy. This is
supposed to be a celebration.
Fabulous idea.
Hey Ed.
Everybody!
Everybody, shut the fuck up!
Eddie, what are you
doing? Are you crazy?
No. I'm just a
psychopathic producer.
What's goin' on? Are
you feelin' alright?
I'm feeling fine.
Okay.
And by the way, Julia,
you sucked in the movie.
You couldn't act your
way out of a paper bag.
Alright.
Quit kidding, Eddie.
We're all friends here.
Friends.
Good point.
Leo,
please come here and
help out a friend.
Yeah, okay.
Anything else, Eddie?
You really like the
movie, didn't you?
Yeah! I loved it.
That's great.
That's really, really great!
I guess that's a cut.
That's not funny, Eddie.
This is all bullshit.
Now, wake up that jerk off
and let's have a party.
Fine.
You're right. He is a jerk off.
Why don't you wake him up?
I will.
Hey, moron!
Get the hell off the floor.
Hey. This'll wake him up.
He must be wearing a cup.
Having a little trouble?
You can never find a
PA when you need one.
My God, he really is dead!
Did I really
suck in the movie?
Are you kidding?
You're amazing.
Go, go, go.
Come on, come
on, come on! Hurry!
Here, hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hurry!
My God.
What the hell happened to Eddie?
Eddie's completely lost it.
No shit.
Listen, he's just got a knife.
There's a bunch of us. Why
don't we just jump him?
Yeah, okay.
We need a plan.
Eddie?
Julia? Julia?
Julia!
Shit.
Julia.
Tim. I thought you left me.
You alright?
Come on. I wouldn't leave you.
Are you okay?
Listen, Eddie's still out there.
So we have to wait it out here.
No.
Come on, I'm not gonna
let anything happen to you.
He's never
done this before.
Stop.
I love you.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you, alright?
Would you like a sardine?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Tired?
Yeah, a little bit.
Killing people is
harder than it looks.
How 'bout a snort of this?
Hahahahaha. The
hair of the dog.
Just what I needed.
Would you like a napkin?
Yeah, you got one?
I thought I did.
Julia.
Julia?
Julia! Julia!
Tim!
Julia!
Look!
Douchebag.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Can't go that fast.
Wait, wait.
Shit!
Tim!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Shit.
Ring around the rosie.
Pocket full of spinners!
Going so soon?
Why, my little party's
just beginning!
Come on. Come on!
Top of the world,
Ma! Top of the world!
You okay?
It's great to
have an audience.
I'm ready for my
closeup, Mr. DeMille.
Hey guys. You like it?
I got it at K-Mart.
Come out, come
out, wherever you.
They're coming for you, Barbara.
Look! There's one of them now!
Tim, get up! Tim!
Tim, get up.
Get up!
Fuck, he's coming.
Come on, get up!
Get up!
Go! Julia, go!
There comes a time
in every man's life
when he must take
the bull by the horns
and face the situation.
I can't. Just
go get the police.
Fuckin' sick bastard.
Fuckin' sick bastard!
Come on baby. Come on, baby!
Chainsaw, don't fail me now!
By placing my hands so,
I can crush your
head like a walnut.
Let him go, Eddie.
I said let him go!
He's gone, Julia.
He believes he's Lonzo, the
character from the movie.
His mind is just a bunch
of celluloid clips!
How is that even possible?
He believes it with
every fiber of his being.
Well, I can believe too.
You mean?
I said I can believe too.
Fools!
Do you think you can
kill me with your
crucifixes and your wolfs bane?
I have centuries behind me!
Yeah. Do it.
Your blood now flows
through our veins.
Kill the brain and
you kill the ghoul.
Yeah. Do it.
Keep going.
Ask me no questions,
I'll tell you no lies.
Keep going!
Crazy, am I? We'll
see who's crazy.
It's alive! It's
alive! It's alive!
Leave it alone,
Fritz. Leave it alone.
Do it.
And then was
acknowledged the presence
of the red death.
Mother of mercy.
Is this the end of Draco?
Holy shit.
You are a true scream queen.
God, I love you.
Julia?
Julia, it's me.
Julia? Snap out of it.
Julia? Julia!
Gina darling.
I'm truly sorry about
the Scorsese project but,
you do understand.
It's the nature of the business.
I do and it's alright.
Don't worry about it.
Gina, wait.
Forget that I'm your
agent for a moment.
I forgot that weeks ago.
Hahahaha, you say that now.
But, since your last
picture was released,
my phone rings off the hook
morning, noon, and night.
They're begging for you, Gina.
Not just these little
independent producers
from all these little
shitty pictures.
I mean Hollywood.
I mean big budget.
I mean major
producers, major stars,
and you in all the lead roles.
Money.
Don't you understand?
You can write your
ticket anywhere.
Don't you understand?
I don't wanna do
horror films anymore!
God damn it, Tess.
I don't believe
that for one second.
You don't believe it.
What was the line
in that one movie?
It suits you perfectly.
No, don't do it. Don't
even think about doing it.
No, I think I know what it is.
What was that line?
Tess, don't!
It was made for
you. I love that line.
Got it!
No, do not say it.
You are a true scream queen.