Out of there. We wanna swim.
We do the wash. sir.
There's soap in the water.
Don't bother me none.
I could use a bath.
You hear me? Out of there.
Get them out of there.
Mary. Jesse. Come on.
Need a little encouragement.
They're scaled. sir. They can't move.
Well, they better learn quick.
Come on, Negress! Swim for it!
Oh. Lord.
Mary. Jesse. come on.
- What's going on here?
- Just teaching your niggels some manners.
That's not your place.
You harm them and you'll pay lo! them.
Come on. Jesse.
For God's sake. Jackson.
it was only sport.
We don't make sport with our slaves.
No, you love your niggers.
Wesley, I will make you sorry
if you ever bother one of our slaves again.
- Nigger lover.
- Look out, master.
Get up.
Get up. Wes.
Now. come on.
Take ii. son.
That's how it is with nigger lovers.
That's light.
I wasn't ready for the others.
Suppose I should've been.
Why, you whipped them good
lots of times, master.
That boy just ain't never gonna learn.
that's all.
A wedding. she says.
Nothing but a charade and a fiasco.
Just so a couple of Negroes
can jump over the broom.
I feel faint just thinking about it.
To think that the president's
daughter-in-law could do such a thing.
Well, that's Yankees for you.
- Sarah's hardly a Yankee.
- Well, she might as well be.
Mixing slaves and white folk
at a social event.
Can you imagine?
Good afternoon, ladies.
Is that your son, James?
Yes.
Well. he's a fine young man.
Best keep him out of my Lizzie's sight.
She's got her eye out for a beau.
Your brother's so handsome.
Last time I saw him
he was all gangly and spotty.
- Why doesn't he come talk to us?
- Oh. he's probably been in a fight.
Happens a lot.
He likes to pretend we don't know...
...so Easter cleans him up
and mends his clothes.
- Easter?
- Slave girl. She does all the weaving.
Oh. is that all?
Whoa.
- See to the horses.
- Yes. sir.
Easter? My shirt needs mending.
- You hurt bad?
- Only my pride.
I couldn't win against all of them.
Thank you, master, for what you done.
- How's Jesse?
- She gonna be fine.
Shouldn't have even been on our land.
You tell them next time. Easter.
They ain't never gonna pay no never mind
to a slave.
Why? I have to
if I want to stop you chattering... Oh, ow!
- sake.
- They'd whoop me or worse.
They sell me llom here
like they did my mammy.
That won't ever happen.
You won't ever be sold.
This is your home. It always will be.
Besides. whatever would I do
without you?
That all very line. master.
but I still don't get to go to no wedding.
What wedding?
Master James is taking the family...
...to Nashville next month, Parson Dick,
for a wedding.
Yes. sir. I know. sir.
And you're not going.
- Now, how would you know that?
- Everybody knows it, sir.
The president's slave, Alfred,
is marrying Miss Gracie.
Now. why is it
when anything happens in this country...
...all the slaves know all about it
eons before we do?
Jungle drums. perhaps. master?
Well. that's exactly light. Voodoo.
That's what it is. Sheer voodoo.
Whites and Negroes at the same wedding.
Disglaceiul. ma'am. I agree.
You see? Even the Negroes are against it.
- Lizzie. you look lovely.
- Tush.
Just thinking about these Negro nuptials
makes me glow.
- Poor Mama's in a terrible pother.
- Aren't you going?
Of course we're going.
If only to see Miss Sarah
make a fool of herself.
Gill? My shawl.
going.
- I don't know if I am.
- Such a pity.
I would have saved you a place
on my dance card.
- Fool girl.
- Sorry, miss.
That's the best French chiffon.
- Please don't do that.
- Well. she's just a clumsy...
We don't treat our slaves that way.
Why. I declare.
Ale you a Negro lover?
It's a wonder you ain't going to Nashville.
Our old friend, Alfred,
is getting married at last, Captain Jack.
Yes. sir. So I heal. sir.
Well. you should be going to Nashville
as Master James' valet.
But there's more.
Oh. I can't lead. sir.
Now. you know it ain't legal.
He can damn sure lead
as well as you and I can.
Very well. then.
The president writes that Alfred
would like you to be his best man.
And of course, you have my permission.
That's wonderful news, sir.
- Will you write to tell him I accept?
- I already have.
Thank you. Captain Jack.
What is it?
It's my daughter. Easter. sir.
You know. Annie's gill.
She wants to go to that wedding
more than anything. sir.
- It would mean the world to her.
- Well, of course.
She can tend the ladies.
- Is that all?
- Yes. sir.
Thank you very much. sir.
James. will you wait a moment?
I remember my own father.
God lest his deal soul...
...when he colored me with such a talk
before I left for the New World.
It's never easy to! me to discuss
personal matters with you. James.
But now. I must be even and direct.
It is time you were married.
- Yes. sir.
- Good then.
VVe've... That is, I've prepared a list
of eligible heiresses for your consideration.
Daughters of planters, all of them.
The Perkins gill is my first choice.
He! family's quite agreeable to it all.
And you seem quite taken
with her self as well.
Liz is...
Liz is charming. but she's...
- I don't know it I love her.
- Whele do you get these wretched ideas?
Love has nothing to do with it.
It's for sons, Jamie.
Heirs to inherit all that I've created here.
Love can come later, if you're fortunate.
You know.
the first time I saw your mother...
...I thought she was the most
beautiful creature I'd ever seen.
And I wanted he! at that very moment.
But I didn't love he! then
at that very moment.
I didn't know her.
I'd not even spoken to her.
Love came later with knowledge.
The more I came to know her.
the more I loved her...
...until now I cannot bear
to be apart from her.
But we were married
for different reasons.
We married for mutual benefit.
We married for family.
And it's high time you did the same, Jamie.
Now then. this Perkins gill
would bring a fine dowry.
And he! bleeding is gland as well.
So if there's no one else on the list,
I suggest you put your mind to it.
- No. sir.
- What?
No. sir.
- There's no one else.
- There's a good lad.
- Come along. we'll have a drink on it, then.
- Yes. sir.
Now. I don't...
Don't heal any hesitation on that score.
4300!
“Ah!
It is gonna be a wonderful wedding.
The talk of the South.
I certainly am looking forward to it.
Well. I hope you have a nice time. then. sir.
with that Miss Lizzie.
Don't be mean. Easter.
just because she slapped you.
- I told her off.
- And couldn't take your eye off her.
Well. Miss Lizzie's very charming.
I sure am looking forward
to seeing he! again.
And who you gonna dance with?
At the wedding.
Yes. you can go.
You can go as my sister's maid.
We wouldn't have missed ii, Sarah.
You know my husband,
Andrew Jackson, Jr.
It's my pleasure. sir.
Will your father come?
No, sadly, no. The affairs of state
keep him in Washington.
Our daughter. Elizabeth.
I ain't never seen such dresses.
Now. you simmer down. missy.
And you mind your manners.
There's important people here.
Well. this is quite a fuss
you've stirred up.
- I'm so glad you're here.
- Well. o1 course.
You know. we weren't sure
i1 anyone would come.
Sarah, my father's the president.
Now, who would turn you down?
- James.
- Mrs. Jackson.
- MI. Jackson. how do you do?
- Alfred.
- Jack!
You old buzzard, you.
This here is Gracie. Jack.
Oh my, ain't you the prettiest thing.
I don't understand.
Now. how did this old grizzly bear...
...catch something as lovely as you.
Now, speaking of pretty things.
Oh. this here be Easter.
Me and Annie's gill.
Well. little sweetheart, you just make sure
you have the best time here.
- Yes. sir.
- Oh. you done fine. Jack. Just fine.
Well. the hell with it.
We can't let the niggers
have all the fun. Sarah.
- Oh. my God.
- She touched him.
Sony. master.
Does anyone own this gill?
Come along. Easter.
I expect you have work to do.
Somebody should flog that bitch.
Where's the music?
What am I paying you iellas 101?
Hush. Easter. It was an accident.
No one's gonna blame you.
They all do.
There you are. James.
I have found a place for you
on my dance card.
Look after her, Captain Jack.
Child.
No strenuous activity of any kind.
Leave it all to your son.
He's quite capable.
How long might I have?
That's impossible to predict.
I'm sorry. James.
Suddenly.
everything seems so very urgent.
Yes. master?
I want to thank you for the many years
you've been with me, Captain Jack.
No one could have served me better.
Thank you. master.
When you first came to me. you know.
I didn't hold with slavery in this land.
But it was the custom here.
So I promised you that IL you worked lo! me
willingly and well...
...I would give you your freedom one day.
Here is that freedom now.
- A little later than it should have been.
- No.
No, thank you, master.
Don't do this to me.
A long time ago.
when I wanted to many Annie...
...I asked you 1o! my freedom
and you told me no.
Wasn't time.
- But I needed you then.
- You bloke your promise to me.
And you let my Annie be sold away.
So, what good is freedom to me now?
I'm old. What would I do?
Where would I go?
What's left of my life is here with Easter.
- But you can stay here. Flee.
- Yes. sir. I'll stay.
And I'll work for you
until the end of my days.
But every time you see me.
every time you look at me...
...you'll remember
what you did to my Annie.
And the promise that you bloke to me.
When I was a young man in Ireland...
...I fought against the British.
That was a cause I believed in
because they had enslaved us.
And I would have given my life
for that cause.
When I was a young man.
I didn't believe in slavery.
Then I came here...
...and I got rich.
And I forgot what I believed in.
I bloke my promise to a man...
...who was my most loyal friend.
What are you doing here. Easter?
Ain't no law against it.
There is because I say so. Now, clear off.
- Because you buck-naked?
- Don't you talk that way. Easter.
Bet you gonna
let Miss Perkins watch you.
Don't you talk that way
about Miss Perkins.
It's Miss Perkins this and Miss Perkins that
all the time these days.
What's become oi plain old Lizzie?
- You wouldn't understand, Easter.
- Oh, I understand, all right.
- You got the fever for Miss Lizzie.
- You hush up. That's vile talk.
Well, you can just cool off that fever
in the cold water a little more longer.
Hey. Easter.
You come back here with my clothes.
I'll whip your hide. I swear I will.
Come on and whoop me then.
Oh. come on. Easter.
this is beyond a joke.
Promise me you gonna come and see me
more often.
I'm not going to promise you.
You're a slave.
Get your tail out of here.
Do what I tell you.
Get dressed. young master.
There is God.
Yes. Father.
We all believe in God.
There is God in everyone.
It was my pleasure
to serve your daddy as overseer. sir.
And it would be my pleasure
to serve you.
Thank you. Henderson.
Our sincere condolences. sir.
- We are all at your disposal.
- Thank you.
I so sorry.
You have to make a decision
about Lizzie.
I mean. it's been months.
We can't have he! dangling like this.
I know. I know.
Of course if there's someone else...
- No, Lizzie's the one. I just...
- Well, then what are you waiting for?
- James?
- Love. I suppose.
Love can come later.
Duty must come first.
Look at that.
See that?
Mercy.
Some people say
it means the end of the world.
And some folk say it the star...
...that guide the Wise Men to Bethlehem.
I with child.
And you got nothing to say?
Say?
It's another damn mouth to feed.
They say it hurts, you know?
And you...
...never could stand a lick of pain.
We've known each other so long.
You must think I'm an awful slow coach.
always said
that we make a splendid couple.
So why don't we prove them light?
Will you many me?
Oh. James. I thought you'd never ask.
I'll try to be a good wife.
Give you fine sons.
Oh. it's a gill. Easter.
Yeah, you got yourself a fine baby girl.
What a wedding it'll be.
The South in all its glory.
and not a Negro invited.
Are you still smarting about that?
But it was a disgrace.
Blacks in such proximity
to white women.
We must be constantly on guard.
Nliscegenation will be the downfall
of the South.
Why. I've seen plantation children
you could swear were white.
We all have.
And in that cesspool New Orleans.
We ladies should retire.
Excuse me. master.
Slave-child just been born.
That's good news. Captain Jack.
Give the mother our congratulations.
Yes. ma'am. I surely will. ma'am.
And Easter's doing just fine.
Easter?
She does the weaving.
Suddenly I... I don't feel well.
The wine, heat.
Excuse me.
She gets sick headaches.
Lizzie. deal.
I won't many him.
Yes. you will.
This is the richest union
that you could ever make.
You will have a long engagement.
And you will become used
to the idea and grateful for it.
Why, if it were not for the slave girls...
...we women would have to
submit to our husbands...
...whenever they feel healthy.
Papa too?
All men are the same. deal.
All lecherous brutes.
[SINGING “ALL THE PRETTY
LITTLE HOHSES"I
Little princess.
And white as cotton.
Her life will not be easy.
She looks as white as you or I.
Does she have a name?
Captain Jack calls he! Princess.
You men and the havoc you cause.
Princess.
Hello. Queen.
Was it bad?
Popped out easy.
Liar.
I could heal you
all the way at the big house.
While I was proposing to Lizzie.
It good you took a wife.
You need a son.
But I have the best of you.
Let me give you a flesh glass, ma'am.
Well. congratulations.
I thought you'd never get around to it.
Well. you know me. Sam.
I like to be sure.
This child is adorable. Who's is she?
Guess.
Oh. you rascal. you.
Did I tell you I'm gonna be lecturing
at Harvard next year?
I must say she is a lovely child.
She's a darling.
She'll make a splendid companion
to any daughters Lizzie might have.
Such a sensible arrangement.
Though it's taken Lizzie
a while to get used to the idea.
I don't know
what I'd do without our slave gills.
MI. Perkins is a regular demon.
you know?
Yes.
The place is looking splendid. James.
Your father would be proud.
I think we're doing well.
Salting some away
for a rainy day, I hope.
- There are some storm clouds out there.
- Hope nothing serious, surely.
These abolitionists are becoming
quite strident.
These new northern politicians
may take up their cause.
- The end of slavery wouldn't be the end.
- It'd be the end of the South.
- Without cheap labor...
- We'd divelsiiy.
I don't see you
getting out of cotton, James.
Well, here she is.
And looking so beautiful.
Thank you. Papa.
I need to steal my groom
for a minute, please.
Oh. James.
My. aren't you the pretty little thing.
Who's little gill are you?
Oh. I think you need a nap.
Come on. darling.
Come on. I know. I know.
- Why, she's just as white as cotton.
- Shh.
How was I supposed
to know she's Negro?
- This field nearly planted. Henderson?
- Yes. sir.
Niggers are working hard today.
We should be done by this evening.
Very good.
Master says y'all
working pretty good today.
But IL you like to eat.
you'll work a little harder.
You like them sweet potato things?
Move it!
You heal me?
- What's that one?
- Cat.
- Right.
- Stop that.
Anybody find out you learning
her to read, we all get whooped.
- Or worse.
- Well, she got to learn, ain't she?
E is for “ephalump.“
No, child. That's elephant. Elephant.
- Elephant.
- Right.
What's elephant?
Well. see. an elephant is
a great big old animal...
...with a long. long nose.
He live in Africa.
That's where my rnarnrny and pappy came
from and all your family.
My mammy Cherokee.
I ain't never been to Ahica.
Well, Africa is a beautiful country.
A long, long way from here, though.
Is that where my pappy is?
You heal that?
No, child.
But your daddy
is a very important man.
So you got to learn good, work hard.
You know, make him proud of you.
Stop that. Queen.
don't you ever think about your pappy.
He don't matter to you.
You stop to put fancy ideas in her head.
Heading and stuff.
She a slave and always gonna be one.
Slaves gonna be flee one day.
Everybody talking about it.
- I tell you the day is coming...
- Us ain't going to be around.
Well. maybe and maybe not.
But Queen sure will be.
And when that better day come,
we got to be ready for it.
Ain't no use in having freedom
if you can't use it.
If you ain't got learning, you know,
to better ourselves.
All I do is dream
of that better day for her.
Well. you go on and dream.
But you let that child be.
That day will come. You'll see.
That day will come.
- She ain't white.
- I am too. Look at me. Look at me. I am...
You're just {Ike us-
You're a nigger, just {Ike us.
- Look at me. Look at me.
- You ain't got no pappy.
I do too.
Go on! Go on! Get out of here.
Get out of here, you little brats.
There. there. there. don't cry.
- There's no need now.
- But they called me names.
Well.
People called me names too
when I was little.
Why do they do that?
Because I different.
Because I look white.
Because I can lead.
Queen.
Don't ever tell anyone that you can lead.
Some people wouldn't like it.
- They might try to hurt you.
- But my pappy would've stopped them.
Like you stopped those.
Captain Jack.
take this child to the kitchen.
- Get he! a sweet.
- She been trouble. master?
No.
No trouble at all.
Sarah Jane got some cookies
in that kitchen for you.
How about some ice-cold milk too?
What you look 101?
Nothing.
What are these?
What's that?
Nothing.
Mm. This soup is delicious.
Why is everyone so glum?
Politics.
Something women shouldn't bother
their pretty heads about.
- Don't be patronizing, dear.
- Of course it bothers us.
All that Yankee talk
about the abolition of slavery.
Whatever would we do?
And that dreadful business...
...with Nat Turner
killing white women and children.
We could all be murdered in our beds.
And my baby.
What baby?
My baby.
Congratulations.
That's wonderful, Lizzie.
Of course I'm hoping for a boy.
A boy. gill. I don't care.
Just the thought of a baby.
Thank you. Lizzie.
You did have something
to do with it. James.
We'll have to fix the nursery.
And find a good Nanny.
And of course the child will need a slave.
What? There's plenty of time for that.
Well. there's no harm in looking.
We'll need the best.
Unless. well.
Queen could come and live here...
...and be a companion for him.
Or her.
And they could grow up as friends.
- No.
- And she could...
...help out around the house.
Do you really think that's a wise idea?
I think it's an excellent idea, Mother.
Lizzie. I am so pleased.
When will it be?
No.
She'll be raised with my children.
She'll have all the advantages.
But she all I have.
She'll still be yours.
I want this, Easter. It's best for her.
Why does master come see you
every night? He my pappy?
You hush up about your pappy. Queen.
Before I take a switch to you.
He ain't here
and that's all there is about it.
You just know
that your mammy love you.
And your master will love you too.
just like he was your pappy.
You should have used the back door.
You ma'! 9°-
I still going to see he! again, missy?
Of course you will.
This is another house.
not another county.
But you should know...
...this is the master's decision.
I do not approve oi it.
But since it is to be.
the child will be given every advantage.
She will be trained as a lady's maid
with all the necessary etiquette.
So when you see her...
...keep your distance.
I don't want he! learning
your Negro ways.
I only want the best for her, rnissy.
What you want has nothing to do with it.
We own her.
Now. say goodbye and go.
You gonna be a fine lady. Queen.
You gonna live in a big old house
just like I always told you.
Now. you be good. You do as you told.
You heal me?
Just like...
Just like you have a new mammy.
I am he! mistress.
Not he! mammy.
Come along. Queen.
I don't want to.
Queen.
Queen?
Aren't you ever gonna be ready?
- Queen?
- I sorry, Miss Jane. I coming.
What kept you so long?
Couldn't make up my mind
which bonnet to weal.
Well. come on. Papa's going mad.
There you are at last.
Miss Jane. Miss Queen.
Young ladies do not run.
- Sony. Papa.
- You both look lovely.
Now, come on. The shops will be closed
before we get there.
All right, all you red-blooded,
God-fearing young men.
That's one opportunity for travel
and promotion.
Good pay.
You'll start at $11 per month.
You'll make great companions.
You'll have the best of arms. You'll have...
You know. Uncle Sam is planning
to wage slaves...
...like all those people in northern...
One. One. One. two. one.
- Is there gonna be a war, Papa?
- No. Of course not.
Why would Americans
want to fight Americans?
- Because of slavery?
- Speak when you're spoken to, Queen.
Looks like war. All those soldiers.
It's just a lot of
fuss and bother about nothing.
Jane, you can go window shopping,
but be careful.
- Don't talk to any strange men.
- Oh. everyone knows us here. Mama.
I know.
There are a lot of strangers in town.
Queen. keep he! company.
- You have money for a cool drink?
- Yes, Mama.
- How dale they.
- I don't mind it.
- Afternoon, ladies. Sure is a pretty day.
- All around the square.
We don't speak to strange men.
- Oh, we're not strange. Just strangers.
- And we just wanna be your friends.
Pay no attention to them.
Oh. now. then. don't be so heartless.
We've come to enlist to! the war...
...and you just might be
the last pretty ladies we talk to in years.
We might even die.
So how about it?
Come on. just one little bitty kiss
to! a soldier on his way to glory?
Leave me alone.
- That didn't hurt a bit. did it?
- How dale you kiss my slave?
I'm surprised at you.
I thought you were a gentleman.
Come on. let's go.
How the hell was I supposed
to know? The bitch looks white.
Keep her off the streets.
Put a sign on her or something.
- Ale you all light. Queen?
- I was scaled.
They're just pool white trash.
I don't want no war.
And I hate them soldiers.
I must say, he's quite a catch.
Never thought I'd nab me
a real live overseer.
Some more tea, Mrs. Henderson?
Why, thank you. No, Miss Jackson.
I have had an elegant sufficiency.
I am so sorry. The time just slipped away.
Is this your bride?
Miss Palmer. It was, sir. Of Charleston.
Aren't you the sly one,
keeping your pretty wife a secret.
Well, it happened so fast, sir.
On my leave.
I took one look at him
and I said to myself...
I said. "Leticia. that is the man to! you.“
Young ladies do not listen at doors.
Upstairs at once. The pail oi you.
And my dear
mother's heart is broken, of course...
...that I'm living so far away from home.
And my poor father.
All this talk of war, and me getting wed.
His only comfort these days is the gin.
Isn't she awful? Why did he marry her?
- Don't wanna end up an old maid, I guess.
- He can't keep his eyes off her.
That's enough.
Men are so funny when they're in love.
Hany Peters says he loves me
all the time.
And he gets all sweaty
every time he says it.
But he wants to be a preacher.
and I don't think that would be fun.
- I wanna many a prince on a white horse.
- Oh. Queen. don't be silly.
You're just a raggedy itty-bitty slave girl.
Who's gonna marry you?
Somebody will. One day.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
Play the Lord my soul to keep.
And please.
don't let Hany become a preacher.
- And send a nice slave 1o! Queen.
- Amen.
- Good night, Queen.
- Good night, Miss Jane.
I suppose it wouldn't be too bad
being a preacher's wife.
But I'd lather he was something dashing.
Another game?
I'm going to bed.
Ale you coming up?
In a little while.
I might get some ail.
- Don't be too long.
- No, of course.
Sleep well, my love.
Is there gonna be a war. James?
Oh. maybe. But I doubt it.
It's probably just hot ail.
You know how these things are.
The politicians will hull and pull
until the last moment...
...and then everyone will back down
and find a sensible solution.
Play God you're light.
It frightens me so.
Such a pretty night.
What's wrong?
Abraham Lincoln
has been declared president-elect.
Southern states are up in arms about it.
Mississippi's already talking about
seceding 110m the Union.
So is South Carolina.
There's gonna be a war. Easter.
Because of slavery?
Yes.
Oh, they'll say it's for the South.
States' lights.
Can't have a bunch of Yankees
in Washington...
...telling us how to run our affairs.
You gonna fight?
Yes.
For slavery?
- No.
- Well. what then?
For the land.
For honor.
For everything my father worked for.
To hold onto what's ours.
To keep us safe.
I promise you. I'll come home.
Bu! H anything does happen to me...
...know that I will have loved you
until the moment that I died.
Have we been good to you?
Yes. missus.
- You've been very good to me.
- I've tried.
- I hope you're happy.
- Yes. ma'am.
You'd say that even if you weren't.
You're such a pretty child.
You remind rne of those portraits
that I've seen of the Empress Josephine.
Ma'am?
She was this lovely French girl
from the island of Martinique.
She came to Paris and captured the heart
of the emperor, Napoleon.
And their court was the grandest
of all Europe.
And they had a vision of a great empire.
That was my husband's dream.
To conquer the wilderness.
To make a new society.
And here we are at war with one another.
Brothel pitched against brothel.
And all that work undone.
Mammy, he dressed up like a soldier
going for war.
I don't want him to die.
There, there now, Queen.
He come home safe.
You can't know that.
I ain't never tell you no lie.
Not even about my pappy?
You always told me that he left us
and went away.
But the other slaves laugh at me.
Talk about me behind my back.
They tell me that the master...
...m'{ PaPPY-
Is he?
Is that true?
Don't listen to them. Queen.
It don't matter.
It does matter.
It matters to me.
It like half of me missing.
I love you. Mammy. The black me.
But who the other side of me?
The white me?
Where she came from?
From love. child.
I swear before God, from love.
- Daddy. no.
- It's all light, Jane.
Jane. it's all light. I'll be home soon.
I hate to see you go.
I hate to have to go.
Be brave. Do your duty.
I can't bear it.
I love you.
Don't go, please.
I must.
No. please. God.
- Go. master. quick.
- Oh. God.
Take care of them, Queen.
Forward. ho.
Pray for him, Queen.
He YOU! PaPPY~
Some of you will have heard...
...that this war is being fought
for and against slavery.
That is not true.
The South is fighting...
...for the right to protect
its own way of life.
The alternative
is too dreadful to imagine.
Now, you've all heard the stories
of what happens to your people up north.
Hunger. sickness. poverty.
This is not our way.
When you are sick. we tend you.
When you are hungry, we feed you.
When you are old, we care for you.
And when you die. we bury you.
That is our Christian duty.
And now I ask that you all kneel
and play with me.
Oh. Heavenly Father.
our creator and provider.
We pray to you now in this,
our hour of need.
We beg for peace, oh, Lord,
and an end to this war.
File!
And we beg
that in your infinite wisdom...
...yuu spare lives
that would needlessly be lost in battle.
And we humbly ask that in your mercy...
...you bless and protect our beloved son,
James.
Keep him safe from harm...
...and bring him home again
to the bosom of his family.
But if his time on earth is done...
...we beseech you to receive him
in paradise...
...and attend him with angels.
Amen.
Get some hot water. Hurry.
Lieutenani. they're coming in.
it's more than we can handle.
We set up another tent there.
- Yes. sir.
- Get to it.
Yes. sir.
Hang on. son.
I need some...
He's gone.
Hold him down. Hold him down.
Gonna get you another man.
- I'm scaled.
- Don't be. son. It's easy.
Be mindful of God's mercy.
What“? What mercy?
Hold him down.
- All right, bring those three in.
- Hang on, son, hang on.
My buddy!
I need a table. I need a table.
Cover him up.
- All light, son.
- How is it, James?
Bloody dreadful.
- How is it?
- Same. It's gonna hurt, like it or not.
Tell me.
Tell me true. cousin.
Am I dying?
Well. James. you'll live.
We're working our guts out
to keep you with us.
Did we win?
Oh. yeah. we won.
Bull Run is ours. cousin.
Then God be thanked.
I wouldn't have wanted to die
for nothing.
We need a hand here.
She's slipping away. I know it.
Do something. Get the doctor.
Can't do nothing. Miss Lizzie.
It's the diphtheria.
You heal what he say?
Oh. Lord. Jane.
Let me do that. Let me help you.
You think I'd leave he! here with you?
You don't care about Jane.
All you care about is your brat. Queen.
Haven't you had enough from me?
You want my child dead too?
I'll have you whipped.
I'll have you sold away.
- Get the overseer.
- There ain't no overseer.
It's just us womens now.
We gotta help each other.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. Easter. I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean it.
There now. Miss Lizzie.
Ain't no harm done.
It's just your pain talking.
That look real good there.
Parson Dick. How your back doing?
It ain't doing so good.
Quit bothering me.
I know you ain't used to being
out here and ain't happy about it.
But we're gonna be all light.
I get you some water. all light?
- And what y'all laughing at?
- Queen?
If y'all was working,
Parson Dick wouldn't have to be out here.
Miss Sally, what you doing out here?
This ain't no place for you.
A letter from the master.
I can't read it. My eyes.
But Miss Lizzie can lead.
You think I want he! to know
my business? Here.
- I can't do it.
- I know you can.
It against the law.
What does it matter now?
Who's gonna whip you now?
- Here, read it. Head it.
- All right, Miss Sally.
“My dearest Mother...
...I hope this letter finds you well.“
The master's been wounded.
He's coming home.
He's been discharged.
Be a pool homecoming.
- What is wrong with you?
- I's fine.
Just making some broth for Miss Lizzie.
No, you're not fine.
I'm gonna help you.
What you gonna do?
Go out in the field like some Negro slave?
You're too old. Miss Sally.
You're just too plum old...
...to bleak your back picking cotton.
husking com.
None of us would be here
if it wasn't for you.
Now it's your time to lest.
I used to be pretty good
at picking cotton.
We used to put our hands
to all sorts of things.
Back in the early days.
Oh. Lord. my back.
Ain't fitting.
the mistress planting cotton.
I can't do it anymore.
- We have to.
- I can't.
We gotta get this field done by sunset.
Come on.
What is this?
Miss Jackson. what are you doing
out in the field planting cotton?
Queen needed me.
So Queen is in charge now?
Queen can order the mistress of the house
out into the field like some common nigger?
Somebody had to, Miss Henderson.
There ain't enough of us niggers left.
Don't you sass me. gill.
Don't you ever sass me.
Or you will regret it
till the end of your days.
I do need a rest, Queen.
You come with me. Miss Jackson.
Come on. There's some water over here.
Oh. play God. Let it be.
James.
Oh. God.
Miss Lizzie. we ain't done yet.
It's Master James.
Oh. my love. Oh. James.
My love.
I'm sorry. ma'am. I haven't seen him.
There was a horrible epidemic.
There was nothing we could do.
Nothing.
- Deal God.
- No.
Now. don't you argue with me.
You're going to bed.
I be fine. missy.
Hun and fetch Queen now.
Hun as fast as you can.
Mammy! Mammy!
Come now.
we have to find a winding-sheet.
Come. child.
My love.
Sony I ain't come yesterday. Mammy.
But I had a lot to do.
Hope you didn't miss me too bad.
Things ain't too good around here.
Mammy.
Half the slaves gone up north.
Some of them said they gonna fight.
I do the cooking now,
and the cleaning for Parson Dick.
And Miss Sally. she too old.
And Miss Lizzie. always sick.
Captain Jack. he ain't light in his head.
Keep saying freedom gonna come
for all of us.
Like he always knew it would.
Say we can all leave here.
Go soon.
But I don't know
where I gonna go. Mammy.
This here my home.
These are here my family.
I miss you.
I sorry. master.
It's all light, Queen.
I come see he! most every day
when I can.
I've been watching you, Queen.
You work hard.
I'm sorry we're not more help to you.
Ain't your place. master.
Sometimes I wonder where my place is.
Don't hate yourself so much, master. I...
We love you.
I'm going back.
I'm going to form a regiment of my own.
I'm going back to fight.
No, master.
Would you mind, Queen.
lo! a little while?
It's not light, James.
- You fought. You were wounded.
- That's enough.
- What it the Yankees come?
- They'll never get this far south.
They might.
And it's my job to try and stop them.
- Sergeant. lead them out.
- Forward. ho!
Yes.
Hallelujah.
- The Yankees.
- What?
The Yankees coming.
They done burned up Florence.
- Old Lincoln. and they killing everybody.
- Praise be!
Good morning. captain.
We are, as you can see,
a depleted family.
There are no men folk here,
apart from these few slaves.
I trust you mean no harm to us.
We mean no harm to anyone. ma'am.
who is loyal to the Union.
I cannot swear allegiance to your flag. sir.
I believe in a different cause.
Well. you believe in any cause you like.
As long as you do not try to fight us.
I don't think that you would win.
We are your prisoners
and we'll do as we are bid.
We're taking no prisoners.
You're free to go
about your peaceful business.
However. there are some other things.
My men are hungry.
We have very little.
You will be given a voucher
to the value of what we take.
And as your local militia destroyed
the bridge to delay our advance...
...we have orders to seize cotton
to pay for its repairs.
That is our only income.
It's of no value to you now.
This area's under federal jurisdiction.
Your local cotton mills will be destroyed.
You will not harm us.
but you will bankrupt us?
I have my orders. ma'am.
Sir, you will kindly arrange
an escort for me.
Ma'am?
If you are going to destroy
our only means of livelihood...
...I intend to be there to watch.
It would be an honor for me, rna'arrl,
to escort you myself.
Steady the horses.
Whoa. whoa!
Steady. Hold steady.
How would you have us live now?
I lost two brothels in this war.
Killed by Johnny Heb.
I don't care how you live.
Or if you live.
All right, gentlemen, let's hurry it up.
- Easy.
- Help me.
- Leave us something.
- The lady wants us...
...to leave he! something.
I'll leave he! something.
I always wanted a line Southern lady.
- Leave me.
- You going with the slaves. little gill?
- Leave me alone!
- Ever try a real man?
She wants to play.
I know a game she can play.
Don't tell them. Don't you ever tell them.
- Your black slave come to protect you?
- Come on, old man.
- Get inside!
- What are you gonna do about it?
Get down. sir.
- Stay down. old man.
- No! No!
No! No!
Ne!
Captain Jack. no!
Leave him alone!
Leave him be! Leave him be!
- Her turn now?
- No, she's just white trash.
Leave he! alone.
Captain Jack.
Come on. please.
As far as help hem me.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Can't you keep out of trouble, cousin?
I don't think I can save that arm.
I'll be discharged again.
Not this time. James.
Colonel's don't need two good arms.
But we do need every man we can get.
He say he dying.
I can't talk him out of it.
Captain Jack?
Captain Jack.
The Lord is calling me. Mrs. Sally.
I'm sure he would wait a while.
No, Lord, it's been my time.
But I wanna die flee.
But you are flee.
And you have been for a long time.
I have your paper here.
Yeah.
Master gave it to me years ago.
He said one day
that you'd be asking for it.
Now. you stop all this talk
about dying. you heal?
We've been together for a long time.
I mean. we have done some things.
Now. didn't we?
You knew old Master James before I did.
You remember how we set him up?
I told you where he went riding
and you was there...
...nursing your baby
by you first late husband.
Showed much more of myself
than I should.
One look at you and he was gone.
Oh. we've had some times“ Yes...
Oh. Oh.
Queen?
This here be Annie's grandchild.
Don't ever let her be sold
away from here.
Please.
Oh. I couldn't do that.
Soon she'll be flee.
All the slaves will be flee.
All the slaves be flee?
Very soon.
Oh. sweet Jesus.
Then this must be...
Then this must be that better day.
He gone.
Well. maybe now
he see the promised land.
What you doing?
I'm leaving. I'm going to Virginia to see
ii I can find my brothels and my sisters.
Then maybe on up north.
- But this here where you belong.
- No.
No, Queen.
Not anymore.
I am flee.
I don't belong to no man.
and neither do you.
If I was you, I'd get as far away
from this plantation as I could.
But these here my family.
Colonel Jackson. he my pappy.
What you expect your pappy to do?
Take you into the bosom
of his family...
...tell the whole world that
“this little Negro girl here is my daughter“?
No.
Queen, gonna be some hard times
coming for everybody.
White folks gonna stick together
like glue.
They ain't about to admit
that these mulattos...
...and quadloons. an octoloons running
around this plantation is their kin.
And as for you,
you don't mean nothing to them.
They won't even admit that you exist.
Ain't true.
They love me.
I'm glad he died flee.
Thank you.
You're flee too.
Flee to go where you will.
do what you will.
Thank you.
Where will you go?
I serve you.
Work for you.
We have no place for you here.
But this my home.
Listen to me very carefully.
The world as we knew it has gone.
And it can only get worse.
We cannot feed the family even now.
And after the war,
I don't know what we'll do.
Well. I'll help you.
I'll cook. I'll clean.
I'll tend the garden. I'll do everything.
We love you
and we have tried to do light by you.
But you are a Negro
and you are a slave.
And times will be hard and your best place
will be with your own people.
My pappy won't let you tum me away.
You rnust never think
of Colonel James as your father.
You're a child of the plantation.
Just like a thousand others.
That's all.
You my people.
This my family.
Miss Sally.
You're my family.
Mammy.
Help me. Mammy.
God. help me.
What I gonna do?
Where I gonna go?
Help me.
Any man who wants to sell his land...
...I'll give him a fair price for it.
Cash money. No questions asked.
Yankee dollars.
You could buy half the South
for a decent meal.
I'll have no work for you, you know,
when we get back.
With no slaves.
We got a bit put by.
The missus has always wanted a stole.
Some small thing.
Made you some coffee.
It ain't very good.
Just ground up acorns.
But it's hot.
What y'all want for dinner?
I was wondering what we might have
to! dinner tonight.
- Hmm?
- Chicken.
- Mm. Mm. Mm.
- I'd love some roasted chicken with gravy.
Well. Miss Lizzie. you go out
and catch me a chicken and I'll cook it.
I could make a vegetable stew.
I suppose we'll have to do
with vegetable stew again.
Mm.
Mm. We must count our blessings.
I'm sure it'll be delicious.
Blessed alt thou among women...
...and blessed is
the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God...
...pray for us sinners,
now and the hour of our death...
He coming! The master coming!
- Oh. no.
- Jesus.
No. Oh.
Isaac.
Davie. you still here?
Matter of fact, master,
we was just leaving now.
Well. I could use some help
around this place.
Won't be able to pay you much.
But something.
That's kind of you, master.
But Davie, here, wanna see the world.
He ain't never been off the plantation.
Well...
...if you change your mind...
Good luck to you.
Mama, I'm sorry.
I'm so very sorry.
My beloved son.
You're home. You're home.
Come on. Isaac. let's get.
You come along with us. Miss Queen.
Ain't nothing 1o! you here.
Well, you take care of yourself now,
you hear?
Come on. Isaac.
We moving so slow
we ain't never gonna get there.
We'd be happy to.
I got a poor price for it.
Needs must be met.
Before long, I'll have no land left to sell.
I can't go on like this.
You're very quiet.
But then I suppose I haven't said
a lot of things I should.
Like thank you,
for all you've done for us.
I should have
said something before. But...
Well. I...
I'm very grateful. We all are.
- Ain't nothing.
- Yes. it is.
You've been housekeeper, gardener.
cook and maid all rolled into one.
I don't think my family could have survived
without you.
I can't afford to pay you much.
A few dollars a week.
- But when things get better...
- I don't want your money.
I have to pay you something.
illegal now.
Doing lather better than we are.
aren't they?
Good day. Henderson.
If it's about more credit...
No, I've come to pay my bill.
Well now. that is good news.
The missus will take care of you.
Leticia. MI. Jackson's here. Financial.
Oh. MI. Jackson. come on in.
I've got some fine roasting hens.
That uppity little girl's
still with you. I see.
Nice day for it, lady.
Don't mess with her.
She's a high yellow.
Well. hell. it don't matter to me.
I don't mind a little midnight velvet.
How was your day. mother?
Well, I went to the Mitchell funeral.
It was quite a turnout considering
what a vile-tempered man he was in life.
You spend your life going to funerals.
Mm. getting used to it, I suppose.
Well. doesn't this look delicious?
You'd think it was a celebration.
I suppose it is in a way.
I don't know how pleased you'll be...
...given our circumstances,
we hardly need another mouth to feed.
A child?
That's wonderful, Lizzie.
I'm praying for a boy.
I hope it's a gill.
With Jane gone.
the house seems so empty.
I need a little daughter to love.
- Hey. hey.
- All light, give it here.
There you go.
Sure don't look like two pound
to me.
You've lost none of your cheek,
I see.
Get in your place. gill.
You're nothing but an ex-slave
and hired help.
And I suppose you want this on credit?
The master could afford.
You get your money.
Your prices high enough.
Ale you sassing me. gill?
You're accusing me of overcharging you.
L1 the high-and-mighty MI. Jackson
has any complaints...
...you tell him
to come and see me himself.
Not to send some bastard slave gill.
I ain't a slave no more.
You're a useless nigger...
...with no civil tongue in your head
for decent white folk.
Hell. in the old days.
she'd have been whipped.
Uh-huh.
- Yeah, that's what she need now.
A good spanking to put he!
in he! place.
- You can't touch me.
- Come here. gill.
Hey, come on.
Get ahold of her!
Whoa. Whoa. whoa.
- Come back here. whole!
- Come on. let's go!
Come on.
- You see her?
- She can't be too far. Come on.
Ale you gonna sit out here all night?
- Something must have happened to her.
- Oh. we would have heard.
would have sent
a message.
- She's gone.
- Don't say that.
She's gone. James.
Like all the other Negroes.
And I'm glad.
I don't mean any harm.
I hope she hasn't been hurt...
...but I hope I never
have to look at he! again.
Because every time I do...
...it reminds me that you loved another
woman more than me.
Where have you been?
- I had some trouble. missy.
- Hmm.
Not half as much trouble
as you've caused around here.
No thought for us,
just off and away.
I had to cook dinner last night.
And clean up in my condition.
In the old days,
we'd have sent the dogs after you.
Now, get yourself cleaned up
and get to work.
I sorry.
Your master's been looking for you
since daybreak, worried sick about you.
He ain't my master. He my pappy.
How dale you speak to me like that?
And how dale you speak to me like that?
You treat an old dog better than me.
Queen. do this. Queen. do that.
Cook. wash. clean...
...garden, plant cotton, pick cotton
frorn morning till night.
Not even a word of thanks.
Or even a mention I exist.
Well, I do exist, rnissy.
And I got a right to a little bit of love.
And if I can't find it here...
...I going to get it somewhere else.
So ungrateful.
After everything we've done for you.
You ain't never done nothing 1o! me.
And you won't ever have to now.
I gonna miss you, Mammy.
Because you the only friend I got.
Weren't you even gonna come
to say goodbye to me?
I'm sorry.
I tried to warn you.
You could have helped, Miss Sally.
You could have made things
a little easier.
Oh. perhaps.
But it would have been the same
in the end.
Why? Because I Negro?
I nearly white.
Only got a little bit of Negro blood in me.
It's not enough to be nearly white.
Even one little drop of black blood
is too much.
Here. take this.
- Take it.
- I don't want it.
You always were a stubborn child.
We owe you this much at least. Here.
Now. you take it.
Take it.
Yeah.
I don't suppose that. uh...
...I'll ever see you again.
Good luck to you.
Wherever.
Whatever.
I'll miss you.
Oh. missus.
Queen. where have you been?
I've been looking all over.
I leaving. For good.
Why? What happened?
A lot of things happened.
Ale you sure you wanna go?
Well. at least let me give you a ride
into town.
I can manage.
I'll miss you. Queen.
I gonna miss you too.
Write to us. Let us...
Let us know where you are.
Queen.
Remember...
...there is God in everyone.
Hurry up now.
We're going to be late.
Coach for Charleston leaving soon.
Charleston. please.
Yes. ma'am. Return?
No. I not coming back.
Take your bag. ma'am?
You stupid dalky.
My luggage goes on first.
Yes. ma'am.
You can't trust these darkies
to do anything right.
Have to keep your eye on them
every moment.
And you shouldn't be here
by yourself, dear.
Not a pretty, young thing like you.
Why these darkies would have us away
as soon as look at us.
You take my meaning?
Such a pretty, young thing.
Where you from?
Meeting my ma...
Mama in Charleston.
She been visiting in Martinique.
She comes from there.
You're French. Oh. the islands.
So romantic.
And you have the coloring.
Such lovely dark eyes.
But you shouldn't be traveling
on your own.
Oh, my papa said I gonna be fine
on the coach.
And the kintolk gonna meet me
when I get there.
Oh, it's such a relief
to find pleasant company.
There's so much
trash traveling nowadays.
I've been in fear of my life
all the way from Natchez.
You probably haven't heard
of my pappy then.
Colonel Jackson, Forks of Cypress.
Oh. our glorious veterans.
Such difficult times.
You must tell me all about yourself
on the long journey.
Such a relief, someone to talk to.
We girls must stick together.
Now. let's go find our places.
Queen. youse a white gill now.
I'm sorry I don't have
any references, rna'arrl.
- They was stolen.
- Well. it's o1 no consequence.
It really isn't a suitable job
to! a white gill.
Oh. I used to it. I been cooking
and cleaning...
...and I need the money.
Maybe you do.
But you don't fool me, rnissy.
Not for one moment.
You're black trash trying to pass...
...and we don't take kindly
to that sort of thing here.
Now, get out of here
and to your own kind.
Next.
Fresh baked goods. Muffins.
Muffins. Fresh baked goods.
Scalawag.
Come back here. Come back!
- Ma'am.
- Sony.
You ain't got no place here. nigger.
Master. please. I'm white.
Come on, girl. You can't fool me.
This is for decent white folk.
Please. master. I so hungry.
I ain't ate in days.
- Haven't seen you here before.
- No, rna'arrl.
- Just got into town.
- Then you need feeding up.
Tough. isn't it? Looking white.
- Ma'am. I swear...
- That's all light. I understand. sisiel.
High yellow. they call it.
Dirty white would be better.
- You iunning me?
- Now. what do you think?
L'rn gonna sit in a roorn full of white folk
and tell you I was colored when I ain't?
You see what they do?
We're lucky we can choose.
Who would choose to be black?
Black is hard.
White is so much easier.
It's beautiful.
- You rich?
- No.
I have some admirers.
Is you a whole?
If you wanna pass as white,
you have to watch your speech.
Nothing gives you away faster
than slave talk.
Never say “is you.“ Say “are you.“
I don't wanna pass for white. I is white.
I don't wanna pass for black neither,
because that me too.
Little Miss In-Between, that's me.
Nowhere to go, no place for home.
I just a mistake.
You ain't no mistake. child.
But you do smell. You smell bad.
Ale you a. you know. what I said?
A whole?
I don't think so.
My rnarnrny worked for them,
took care of them.
But she was always on at me.
“Alice." she'd say...
...“you take care of what you got, girl.
It's all a girl is got.“
She let it get wore out.
Then the Yankees came in the war.
They raped me
and they burned down the house.
So I came here.
I sorry.
Oh. child. It's done.
But I swore...
...if white men wanted me so bad...
...they were gonna have to pay for it.
I could never do that.
And I ain't pretty like you.
What did they do to you
back in that big old mansion?
Didn't anyone ever say
nice things to you?
Didn't anyone ever tell you
how pretty you are?
Only my mammy.
Well. you see. child.
your mammy was light.
Mammys always are.
I don't dance too good.
Oh, it's easy. Just follow the music.
Alice. my deal.
you're looking lovely as usual.
- Thank you.
- May I have the honor?
Why. George. I'd be delighted.
You're on your own.
Don't be a wall flower.
Don't leave me. Alice.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
How do. pretty?
Shall we?
Well. I'd be delighted.
I ain't never had such a time. Alice.
You must have danced
with every man in the loom.
Well. I had to. That first one, Morgan.
kept trying to kiss on me.
- Ale all men like that?
- Most ol them.
What'd you think o1 George?
Well. he's so old. Alice.
Well, I think of him like he's my pappy.
And very rich.
Well, you ain't nothing but a whore
for all your fancy talk.
How I survive is my business, Queen.
Don't call me names.
- Well. it bothers me.
- Well. that's a pity.
Because George is a very nice man.
And he has a job for you if you want it.
I won't do that sort of work.
In a flower shop.
Is there anything I can do for you
today, sir?
A lose.
A single. very lovely. led lose.
What is it 101?
A wedding? Something special?
No.
This one's for you.
From the first moment I saw you.
surrounded by loses...
...I haven't been able
to get you out of my mind.
I trust you do not think
me iolwald. ma'am.
- I know we've not been introduced.
- Why, no, sir.
I was most pleased...
...when you asked me
to walk out with you this evening.
Ordinarily, I would, of course,
have asked your father.
But I do not know who he is
or how to find out.
You're not from these parts.
No. My home is far away.
And your family?
A very old family, sir.
My father was a colonel in the war.
He lost an arm. You fought in the war?
It was my duty.
And my strong and passionate cause.
- Your father is Colonel...?
- My, a lemonade stand.
I declare. I'm dying of thirst.
Oh. I cannot have you die. my deal.
I've waited so long to find you.
Lemonade it is.
Your family is from Georgia, perhaps?
No. Um. Alabama.
Thank you.
You be careful, sooner or later
he's gonna have to know the truth.
Oh, don't spoil it for me, Alice.
It's the most beautiful thing
ever happened.
And when he wants to know
more about you?
He already does.
He want to meet my family.
Oh. Queen. I could spank you.
Digby's obviously from an old family.
What you think he's gonna feel...
...when he finds he's been
stepping out with a Negro?
He ain't gonna know.
sick...
Every moment you're with him.
you're living a lie.
- One day you gonna slip.
- Oh, he cares for me, Alice.
But he makes rne feel wonderful.
For the first time in my life, I feel
like somebody really cares for me.
Then let him care for you.
Let him look after you.
But don't let him be love.
Love is dangerous for women like us.
I'm not like you.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Wow.
Isn't it wonderful?
Those of us who fought
for the confederation...
...don't find much joy in it.
But it's the Fourth of July.
I wonder if your father's celebrating...
...in Florence.
I know all about you.
How?
There aren't too many Jacksons
in Alabama.
I know his mansion is called
the Folks oi Cypress.
And that it has gone to wrack and ruin
since the war.
Is that why you didn't tell me?
You silly goose.
We're none of us what we were.
I've watched my family's fortune fade
to nothing...
...but useless confederate
promissory notes.
We are all pool now.
We offended God when we lost the war.
And he is visiting
a terrible judgment on us.
Here we are. two lost and lonely people
who found each other.
I have no light to ask you.
I don't have a lot to offer...
mother than my love.
And. uh. I know I should
ask your father first...
...but I think he will understand.
Will you many me?
Look after the horses, sir?
We don't need your help.
Please, sir, just a few pennies.
You heard the gentleman.
Let go of that! Let go.
Don't you whup me.
I ain't no slave no more.
Don't you whup me!
- HeY. you filthy nigger!
- Aah! Aah!
He don't whup me. Nobody whup me.
Come along. my deal.
How could you be such a fool?
- I had to.
- But I warned you.
I told you it was dangerous.
You can't many him.
He ain't never gonna know.
Listen. It's not just you.
It's all of us who can pass.
So you many him.
but what is he gonna say...
...when you have babies
and a little pickaninny pops out?
One day he's gonna know
you tricked him. lied to him.
Then it's not just you, it's all of us.
You get out of this, girl,
as fast as you can.
You been playing with file too long.
- I don't know how.
- Well, you think of something.
Peanuis. ma'am?
Ma'am.
Queen! What a wonderful surprise.
Please, come in.
I had to see you.
I wasn't expecting company.
Certainly not you.
Is something wrong?
You're not going back
on your wold. I hope?
Because I'd sue you
for breach of promise, you know.
I love you that much.
- Well. what is it? What's wrong?
- I'm sorry.
Just a little close in here.
I'll open a window.
Now, what'd you wanna tell me?
Uh...
Nothing.
- really. I just. uh...
- Well then. let me tell you something first.
It might make things easier to! you.
I wrote to your father today.
Queen! Honey. what's the matter?
You awake?
- How long have I been here?
- Oh. just a little while.
I went to the pharmacy.
- What is it?
- Laudanum.
I never used it before the war,
but now when the pain comes...
I don't want opium.
It's very mild.
It'll make you feel better.
There.
Now. just relax.
Though you really shouldn't be
alone in here with me. you know?
But I won't tell anyone if you won't.
And we are to be married. aren't we?
I can't remember
when I've been so happy.
Don't say that.
You don't know anything about me.
- Not really.
- Shh. shh. shh.
Let the drug do its work.
It'll make you feel so good.
Just like floating
on a fluffy pink cloud.
You're like a drug to me.
I only have to look at you
and all the pain is gone.
Mm.
Oh.
My love. I want you so much.
I need you so much.
I've wanted you
from the first moment I saw you.
I can't wait until we're married.
I've got to have you now.
- It's been so long since I had a woman.
- No.
- No. No.
- I need you.
Come here.
No! No!
Pm Negro!
My pappy was Colonel Jackson
and my mammy was a slave woman.
- Slut!
- Aah!
Here.
Bitch!
Aah!
You'll get what cheap
Negro bitches deserve.
You told him.
You come out of there, you nigger whore.
How could you tell him?
You knew you were playing with file!
How many warnings did you need?
He raped me.
And you told him
to save your precious virginity.
Well. let me tell you what it cost.
Wold will spread like wildfire.
A couple mulattos in here passing as white.
Then you know what's gonna happen?
At the very least
George is gonna heal...
...and I'll lose him
all because of your precious virginity!
No one got the right
to take it away from me. No one.
Oh. you're not special.
We've all been raped.
I thought you was my friend.
You're too dangerous
to be anyone's friend.
You're living in a dream.
You're not in the real world.
And you're not Little Miss In-Between.
You're high and mighty.
“My pappy was a colonel.
I lived in a mansion.“
- My pappy loved me.
- Then why did he let you go?
You've got to get out of here.
I'm gonna tell them I kicked you out.
That I found out and I made you go.
No, Alice. I ain't got no one else.
- Go back to your precious pappy.
- I can't. This is all I got.
Well, there ain't nothing left here.
Not now.
Go anywhere. Somewhere.
I don't care where.
Just get as far away from here
and as far away from rne as possible.
No, Alice, please, I'm begging you.
Don't make me go, Alice.
- I'm begging you.
- Why did you tell him?
Why?
Help me! I'm hungry. Please. help me!
Your mammy was a kindly woman.
I seen her conjure up all kinds of haints
out in the hollow in the woods.
Ooh, I seen her too myself once.
I need some more wood.
bring more down.
Gill. what's wrong with you?
Getting some idea.
Not a problem
because I brought some more food.
Mm-hm.
I need a place to sleep.
Over there.
Hey. you hungry?
Then eat that, white bitch.
Run! This home burning!
Frankie's still in there!
Oh. God. somebody help him, please!
Help me. Lord.
Can't go on like this forever.
- How long...
- How long?
- ...is forever?
- That's right.
- Is it a moment?
- Oh. no.
- A day?
- No.
- Year?
- A lifetime?
- No.
Or is it forever?
Forever is eternity.
- And this vale of tears is not eternal.
- No, sir.
Our wretched misery on this earth...
...is but a moment
in the blanket of God's eye.
When that moment we call life is done...
...we will be taken up in glory...
...we will bask in the sun
of God's loving glory.
We will dwell in the bosom
of the Lord in glory.
Not for a moment,
not for a year, not for a lifetime...
...but forever and forever...
- Ever, ever, ever.
...and forever in glory.
Help me. Somebody. help me.
Help me!
Please.
Help.
I Negro.
Help me.
Help me. God. I need help!
I need food! Help me!
Help me. I scaled.
Help me. somebody help me. please.
Help me.
It's all right,
we gonna take care of you now.
Help me!
Lord. Lord, I scared, I scared...
Excellent jaw. She'll do splendidly.
So light and lovely teeth.
Thank you for bringing her.
Oh. I don't mind staying. ma'am.
There's no need, but if you wish,
you may wait in the kitchen.
Now. Queen. isn't it?
A very odd name.
We should be pleased to take you
into service.
You'll find us stern taskrnasters,
but fair, I think.
And you'll get your board and keep.
Good, honest pay for good, honest work.
If any would not work,
neither should he eat.
Thessalonians 3:10.
Yes. ma'am.
And you should be careful
who your friends are, Queen.
Obviously. you've had a good education.
Many of the Negroes here
have not been so fortunate.
That is why we have a mission to them.
Yes. ma'am.
That's settled. then.
You may say goodbye to your friend.
Oh. After we've said a little player.
Men go forth under his work,
under his labor.
O Lord, how manifold are thy works!
In wisdom hast thou made them all.
They dragons.
Yeah. but their tile pretty old now.
Besides. you need a job...
...and there ain't many o1 them around.
You have any problem. you come see me.
- I can handle them two.
- I'll be fine.
I just gotta be careful
who my friends are.
Well. you best not hang around
with me then. child.
I is too black for them.
I see you in church on Sunday.
All light.
Dinner ready. ma'am.
Thank you. Queen.
Did you go to church
this morning. Queen?
Oh. yes. ma'am. Miss Gifhey.
It's Sunday.
- Was it a good service?
- Oh. yes. ma'am.
They nearly lifted the roof off.
- Paganism.
- VVe prefer quieter appreciation of our Lord.
But it was wonderful, Miss Mandy.
The spirit surely moved.
Clapping and dancing and shouting.
This is heathen behavior.
- Idolatry.
- African ritual.
You're a good gill, Queen.
It is our dearest wish
that you should come to our church...
...and contemplate the wonders of the Lord
in calm and quiet.
Maybe the Lord moves
in mysterious ways.
That's very true, Queen.
Perhaps you are his test of us.
Oh, no, I promise.
I working hard for my Saviofs love.
Very good. very good.
Then say your players with us.
Then you can go to your dinner.
O Lord,
we thank thee for thy precious bounty.
And for the blessings
thou hast bestowed upon us.
Consecrate this food, O Lord...
...in the name of our Savior,
Jesus Christ, amen.
- Amen.
What you think you're doing?
- I cleaning up your garden.
- Why?
I looking for work.
Who told you to do that?
Now. I took it on my own authority.
Get out o1 here. you heal me? OI I gonna
tell on you. I gonna call the missus.
Well. now. you just do that.
Miss Mandy?
What is it, Queen? What's wrong?
Who is that man?
Begging your pardon, ma'am.
My name Davis.
- I guess you be the lady of the house.
- Get out at once before I call for help.
Now. You can do that. ma'am.
You got every fight.
But your garden a mess.
And I looking for work.
You could have asked.
I begging your pardon. ma'am.
I big and I black.
L1 I come banging on your door.
would you have given me the time o1 day?
- That's hardly the point.
- It is to me now. ma'am.
If you can see your way clear
to employ me...
...well, I'll work for you right hard.
But if you prefer not or can't afford rne,
I'll give you this afternoon for free.
Because I hate to see a garden
looking like this.
You're very sure of yourself, young man.
Can't see no reason not to be. ma'am.
Well, I'll take your offer
of a free afternoon.
If the work is satisfactory,
I will consider some regular employment.
I will be watching you.
I thank you kindly. ma'am.
The loses need pruning.
They do, but not now.
Wrong time of year.
The devil finds work
for idle hands, Queen.
I want to finish making jelly today.
- And then the stove must be blacked.
- Yes. ma'am.
And why don't you take out
some lemonade to that gardener?
He's a good worker.
and it's a hot day.
Yes. ma'am.
It's rare to find a Negro
with such self-confidence, yet so polite.
It gives me hope that our work
is not entirely in vain.
I wonder. does he know he has a friend
in Jesus?
You can have a bleak. she said.
You're doing a good job. she said.
I'm gonna give you dinner tonightm.
Before you go home.
- She said that too.
- Well. better do like she say then. huh?
Who done that to your back?
Old master in the slave day.
- A little more pie?
- NO. thank you. ma'am.
That was very fine.
Where you learn to cook like that?
- On the plantation.
- Mm.
Sure is good.
Why they whip you so bad?
Master ain't liked my way.
I didn't wanna be no slave.
It wasn't my idea of life.
So they tried to whip some fear into me.
- Well. that's over now.
- Ain't changed much.
I mean. I flee.
But they still treat me
like afield nigger.
I don't wanna have to beg for change
from a white man pocket.
Don't wanna live a life where I ain't never
gonna be able to better myself.
Flee or not.
So I taking charge of my life.
I looking for my place.
I looking for where I belong.
I looking too.
That was a fine meal. ma'am.
I thank you kindly.
You know...
...you have a friend in Jesus.
- What you done?
- Oh. cut my shoulder...
...chopping on this old tree trunk.
Well. I could do that.
Thank you.
Did it hurt?
Oh, it was worth it for this.
You got magic hands.
My mammy taught me.
It was my pappy favorite thing.
I meant...
...did these hurt?
Ain't you never been beat?
Not really.
I got the switch a few time.
The switch.
What they say...
...you don't feel it
after the first few lash...
...that ain't true.
You feel every sting of it.
Cut across your back like a razor
and go on cutting.
All you feel is this terrible pain...
...and this dreadful anger
that they got the power to do this to you.
Just because you black.
And you hate them with every ounce
oi hate you got inside you...
“.101 doing this to you.
Don't hate. Ain't no need for hate now.
That's all there is.
No.
There's love.
Did I hurt you?
I thought I was gonna die...
...from love.
Oh. my sweet Queen.
You got more love in you
than anybody I've ever known.
You're all filled up with love.
And you?
Don't know how much loom
there is in my heart.
I only little.
Only need a tiny space.
I want your child.
I wouldn't bring a child into this world.
Wouldn't have to many me.
unless you wanted to.
I wouldn't make you.
My deal...
...you can't make me.
Nobody can make me do nothing
I don't wanna do. Not no more.
Would it be so terrible?
There's nothing...
“.101 a Negro boy in this world...
...except pain and humiliation.
It ain't always gonna be like that.
Not always.
It will be like that.
Always and always and always.
I will not bring a child into this world...
...till I have made this a better world
to bring a child into.
There now.
I made you cry.
It's all level seem to do...
...is make people cry.
O Lord. we thank thee to! thy bounty
and to! thy many blessings...
...on these thy humble servants.
Queen, what on earth are you doing?
Nothing.
I saw you take that biscuit.
What's the matter?
Don't we feed you enough
that you must steal from our very table?
The Eighth Commandment.
- I think you'd better go to your room, miss.
- After you put the biscuit back.
Nest in our warrant.
And she say it's your own.
And she ain't no lie.
So, what you gonna do about it?
I sorry.
Ain't thrilled about it.
And you know why.
But it done.
So I guess I'm gonna
have to stand by you.
Not so fast, rnissy.
You don't get out of here that easy.
Now, she wasn't gonna tell you because
she didn't wanna force you to wed her.
But she don't want you if you just
marrying her because you feel you gotta.
She don't want you
if you don't love her.
Ain't sure I know what love is.
If I'm gonna find out from anybody,
I reckon it's you.
I surely hope so.
Because if you don't care for this gal...
...and cherish her...
...I'll find out and I'll come for you
wherever you be...
...and I'll fix ii...
...so you don't never give no pool gal
no baby again.
You know I will.
I know you will.
Now...
...you can go to him.
- Is that all you taking?
- That's all I got.
- Sure you don't want me to come?
- No, you go to church.
He said he'll meet me there at noon.
What a man say and what a man do
be two different things.
- Now. you know where you're going?
- Up north. I guess.
Now. it you ever need anything.
you come straight on back to me. you heal?
Here.
Now, you have a dance for me
at your wedding.
Qka'! -
- I gotta go. I can't keep him waiting.
- Okay.
You take care of yourself now,
you hear?
I knowed he would. I had a feeling.
I never said he was gonna many me.
You said that.
- Said he was gonna stand by you.
- I guess he got better things to do.
Ain't no use in crying about it now.
Think it's gonna hurt?
I can't imagine it'd be easy.
But you ain't got no other choice now.
Evening. Miss Esther.
This little sister here needs your help.
I do got a choice.
I gonna keep my child.
A wicked. naughty gill.
that's what you are.
Now. you leave the child be.
She been through enough.
How dale you address me that way?
I address you any way I want.
This gill need help. Not your sermon.
Out of the house.
Out of the house this minute.
And where is she going to get this help?
I take he! with me.
I give he! all the love and care she need.
Queen. get your thing.
Not so fast.
Now, of all things to consider here,
such as the child's immortal soul...
...Queen is lost.
All the players in Christendom
couldn't save he! now.
- But the child is another matter.
- Precious burden, an innocent babe.
I will not let the child into your care.
It will have the advantage
oi a propel Christian upbringing.
I Christian.
And since we must look after the child,
we must also look after Queen.
It's our duty.
Fallen sinner.
I won't let he! stay here. Come on.
And how will you stop it?
Queen is in our employ.
And I doubt that the authorities would
consider you more suitable than us.
If she should leave here,
of course, she wouldn't have a job.
And I can't think
she would easily find another.
He! condition.
I stay.
I have to.
A fairly graceless response, Queen.
A little gratitude might be in older.
Yes. ma'am. Thank you.
That's settled then.
Now, off to bed with you.
You need your rest, for the child's sake.
You need anything. you let me know.
There is nothing she needs from you
and you are not welcome here.
Remember your prayers tonight, Queen.
Bless and protect my little child. Lord.
Let him be born whole and complete.
in thy likeness.
And please. Lord. let him love me.
And don't let them two old dragons
be too hard on me.
Amen.
Queen. are you sure
you're all light out here?
- Oh. I be fine. Miss Gifhey.
- Don't want you catching cold.
You know. you didn't finish
your chores today.
We'll forgive you now, in view of the...
But once he's born...
Why you so sure it gonna be a boy?
Well, I don't know, of course.
How could I?
Now. don't sit out here too long.
She's convinced it'll be a boy
because she wants it to be a boy.
We both do.
What's it like. Queen?
- Heavy.
- No, I mean...
...what's it really like?
How does it feel in your heart?
Well, I feel full up with him.
Complete with love for him.
I think it's gonna be a boy too.
Heel him glowing inside me.
Kicking inside me.
Part of my body, and all of my love.
I don't know what I gonna do
if he don't love me.
Can't imagine why he wouldn't.
Ain't nobody ever gonna
take him away hom me.
Except God. maybe.
I envy you so much.
Both of us do.
Don't you think we didn't long
to be married?
Yearn to have children?
We never found the right man,
either of us.
OI they didn't find us.
Then the war came along
and took most of the men away.
And we got old.
We spend our lives
trying to increase God's family...
H1101 OUI OWN.
But I would give almost anything...
...to know what it feels like...
...really feels like...
...in my heart.
Don't make it worse for me.
- Come on. girl. push.
- Shouldn't we get help?
Nonsense. we're nearly there.
We don't need any... Push. Queen.
I can see it, I can see it!
O Lord, come to our aid in this,
our hour of need.
Oh, please, get off your knees, woman,
and get rne a sheet.
We're there, Queen. We're there.
And oh. bless my cotton socks.
it's a boy!
I got the knife. Here's the knife.
Let me see him.
In a minute, Queen. we've got things to do.
My child. He mine. I wanna see him.
Wait a minute, you ungrateful girl.
He's not really very dark.
Perhaps he'll get lighter as he gets older.
I want my child. Let me see him.
He's a very fine. very handsome baby.
We must think of a special name for him.
David.
I gonna call him David.
Oh. I don't think
that's entirely suitable, Queen.
But it means beloved.
Not at all suitable,
David was an adulterer.
Pool Bathsheba's husband.
We thought Abner.
I gonna name him David.
I baptize this child, Abner, in the name
of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
- Amen.
This child is thus acknowledged
to be a member oi Christ's Church...
...and is commended to thy care
and love.
Miss Mandy wants you to feed Abner.
She always want him fed.
He gonna bust from feeding.
Well, he's crying now. You best go see.
Do that brass aflelwalds.
Yes. ma'am.
He's starving. Queen.
Where have you been?
Probably just the burps,
he already been fed.
That was four hours ago.
I have it written down.
Oh, no, feed him here,
you know I like to watch.
It ain't fitting. private business
between me and my boy.
It can't do him any harm.
and it pleases me.
[SINGING “THERE'S A FRIEND
FOR LITTLE CHILDFIEN"I
You take the heavy end. Gifhey.
What you doing with that?
I have decided to move Abner
into my loom.
No, you leave that be.
I believe it would be best for the child.
And you must know I'm right.
Best thing to! the child
is to stay with his mammy.
The child can't stay with you.
it puts his soul in danger.
You don't care nothing about his soul.
You just want him because you can't
have no child of your own...
...you old. dried-up old thing.
Don't be ridiculous.
We're not trying to steal your child.
We're trying to give him
the benefit of a decent life...
...and the promise of salvation,
which is more than you can do.
You'll still see him.
You ain't taking him. He mine.
The only thing that ever been truly mine.
- You're hysterical.
- You can't take him!
Very well, IL you won't listen to reason.
I will have to lollow with some other course.
- Come along, Giffrey.
- Harlot. Jezebel.
You will regret this. Queen.
Queen.
Haven't seen you for a while.
I ain't been able to come.
Something troubling you?
My child.
Is he sick?
No.
Fine as can be, for all I know.
I ain't seen him.
He's your baby.
Not the way Miss Mandy take him over.
Like he he! child.
I just some farm animal that bred him.
Miss Mandy's a good Christian woman.
She stealing my child.
- I can't believe...
- She threatening the law if I make a fuss.
What can I do?
Ain't nothing you can do.
She white and you black.
And ain't nobody gonna believe you.
even ii what you say is true.
It true all light.
I'm sure you just imagining things.
I'm sure Miss Mandy is doing it
all for the best.
And don't you go making no trouble.
Life's hard enough
for black folk around here.
That it?
She's stealing my child...
...and ain't nothing I can do...
...because I black.
That's the way of the world, girl.
You go home.
Talk to Miss Mandy.
The world will look better in the morning.
God bless you.
What we must remember at all times...
...is the child's soul.
If what you say is true,
the woman is mentally affected.
Perhaps time in an institution
would be of help.
Then what would happen to Abner?
A suitable foster home
will have to be found.
You give me my child!
Queen! How dale you!
Do you know your ledeemel. gill?
Yes. sir. I do.
Ale you a sinner?
I ain't a sinner no more. I been saved.
You are in a state of constant sin.
These good women have told me
all about you.
They the sinners.
They trying to steal my child.
Queen. that is a wicked lie.
Liars and fornicators will be consigned
to the flames of hell.
Hallelujah.
Go to your loom and leave Abner here.
No. He mine. I kill you
before I let you have him.
I kill you before I let you have him!
Quite deranged.
And violent.
You must have he! committed at once.
deal ladies.
We'll do as you say.
We gotta go. child.
This here ain't home.
I don't know where is...
...but I gonna find one. I swear.
I gonna find one.
We made it. boy.
It's just you and me now.
We flee. We flee!