Yucatan peninsula, the year 1240.
Yucatan peninsula, today.
take that Note and mark 'm.
That is the fifth al.
You want to enter them in the computer?
Or do you have one?
One somehow.
I understand there not understand.
Enter the well but in.
Robert, we are so close.
It will do. If you but getting to the point.
- It has taken so long.
We must adapt to our words.
- Yes, we have to be careful.
Yes, let us do that.
- Only we should know about them.
Bowl, and we will do fine a few more.
We are starting the landing to
the Yucatan peninsula.
The weather is clear, 35 degrees
with a humidity of 80%.
delicious holiday weather so.
Thank you flew with us.
: Lauren Sofer Missing.
Call for information its sister Alexis.
You are here somewhere, Hugh sister?
You understand not.
Barry would never against me lie.
He would never ... I trust it
fully. He is my man.
I trust him fully.
But he was off with his friends.
And he smoked cigars. I do not know...
- Mrs!
keeps your shuts up! I beseech you.
We are there. May I ask the money?
This is only half of it.
More I have not.
Wait, wait! Here you can not be! Barry
he would never come here.
I thought you gave me!
Oscar.
- Ha which Nico. How is it?
Best, best.
Give me such a drink with that fruit.
Amigo, your account is too high.
First pay.
That I tell you the whole week al.
This should be enough.
Not really. But what would the? This is nevertheless
a charity, not where?
And? What was it with that woman?
Best, best.
But m'n messed up throughout the day.
Yes, otherwise you could here
the entire day can delirium.
Da gezeik's better than that.
- Go Ahead. What am I doing here?
That 'gezeik' is required so that you make money on
it and can pay the bill.
That chore was three hours.
- three long hours.
You are by far the
most lazy man i know.
As drinking i.
That is indeed something to
be proud of. Way to go, my friend.
I A 'Rumrunner'?
- Definitely, Seno Rita.
You are certainly American?
O my God. How do you know?
a wild guess.
a wild guess, huh?
What is your name?
Allison. And you?
say but Nico, Queen.
O my God, you speak Spanish. What kind.
PLEASE WAIT... 'I go...'
'of the...'
Grand Rapids, Michigan.
When I graduated was
I did not know what I wanted to do.
What should you do with a
university degree in Mathematics?
There is no fun to experience.
And I wanted some fun experience.
So when I am
going to do the Master Training. Strange word, Masters.
What means that well?
That i asked to m'n professor.
He replied...
God, what he said again?
I know many. Back to the subject.
Dolphins so.
I therefore fail to understand why dolphins
always get caught in the nets.
They have absolutely no gills.
The are mammals. Breathing air.
So they need to come out of the water.
and then take a deep breath. Then
they can back under water swimming.
very interesting as
mammalian in the water to life.
That must have been very complicated.
Come on, you speak
a little English?
her team is looking for five days and
you have no idea what they are?
That you do not think?
You said 'police agency'?
That is nowhere in sight.
There is only a lemonade stand.
- Go away, I am crazy about you.
You Speak English now?
Have you discovered nothing after five days?
I think nothing of.
You want at least my flyer hang up?
Is that too much to ask?
Mrs, my sister is
already five days lost...
excuse Mr.
You may have seen this lady?
Good Luck.
- If you hear anything...
sorry, Sir. Does
this lady you may be familiar for?
It is my sister. She is blond, 28 years old.
They are living here about five years.
It is here with a team of archaeologists
to investigate the ruins. Mr?
You kidding me.
Nice, though.
- Pardon?
That ie is very nice.
What is nice?
Well you back. Your Ass.
Very nice.
My ass?
So. That is very nice.
- Incredible.
What have I done heck?
Who is it?
- I have no idea.
I only know that they are looking for this woman.
This.
Wait. Let remains to be seen.
You have read it?
Displayed here is the. It is her sister.
Z. U. S. T. E. R. Sister. He is simple?
- Let's see.
I think I have read it is not good.
- do you think? He thinks.
I am not well read.
- or not at all.
where she is now?
Kweeniet.
I can go back to the city.
It was only six hours ago.
six hours but?
Maybe they are there.
waiting for us.
- waiting for us.
Bowl, than we achieve its.
It is to that tent that which
sells ice cream where you are so fond of.
Who with pepinosmaak?
go here.
What?
- Piss!
But why? Javier...
- come with me, ASAS.
Javier! Do you want an ice cream?
That guests are not good end.
You have hired them.
. They have a week long
sat in a cave. They are about sensitive or so.
Why you took them?
- I could find anything better.
than they?
- Really.
Search that woman. She is a problem.
How you can find her are you looking for self but off.
I have no pull in
annoying snoopers.
No worries. I adjust the self.
At work!
I apologize.
- Yes?
You Are Looking For someone?
Yes! Have you seen her?
Not. But I know someone
who can help you may have.
You know someone? To whom?
This man has helped me
to save soldiers in each other.
where can I find it?
Bar.
What bar?
This bar.
- he is the owner? The bartender?
It is eleven hours in the morning.
You Z'n private number?
No, he is now there.
Well than. On to the bar.
success.
I had called. I find one Nico.
correctly. That is there. You can do
not disturb him better, he is hard at work.
No, huh? You are the.
- What do you mean by that?
Fine. The mutt who can be instructed.
I know you, or so?
We have met each other short.
We...?
Now I know the weather.
The wife of the beach, huh?
Yes, you were still looking for your sister?
You was rude to me.
sit.
tell me what is wrong.
My sister Lauren and her
two partners are missing.
They are archaeologists and
examined the ruins.
five days ago
they suddenly disappeared without trace.
No one who helps me or who
care about. Everyone hate me.
I do anything.
I am nice and calm to everyone.
And yet they help me.
So now you can get to you and I implore you
on m'n naked knees,
help me please m'n sister to find.
No wedding ring, huh?
- I knew it!
you have a boyfriend?
You cannot deny that
they see me at all.
for sure. That is why she went
there as a missile rocket.
You charms were too much for her.
I have done the weather, huh?
You do not need to ask for more or you
behave as a bag.
go there just
that you always do.
That will then be.
Not to worry, Joh.
They did not.
What should you do?
- my apologies.
I had something drunk too much.
- Logical, at eleven in the morning.
That You mean sarcastic.
I am a simple man,
that of simple things.
Swimming, appetizers.
They know me in that bar.
Sleep i do very much. And
Diving. And a well in m'n hammock.
And very occasionally I do agree a job.
They call me private detective, But that is
not true. I know many people simply.
If somebody pays
i search from whom the barge has
or with which local
lady hubby strange.
That is easy and it is always
the same local lady.
You Know How stupid you sound?
Try me not more to cheer.
simply go away.
Go to home.
- No worries. You can see me not more.
That is not the issue. You must be lazy from
the road continue. Here comes misery of.
That my decision.
- The are very dangerous lazy.
I can best for myself.
- Chemistry yet!
You go well but only swears lamb in your
bar, whoring drinker. I care for myself!
Who are you? What do you think of me?
- Head close!
That policeman is a friend of me!
I do everything what you want!
Head close! I will be brief.
So they will at least be quiet.
You drive laps, So... there!
I know where I need to go.
we let her put on a boat
and then thrown overboard.
Or we shoot it by its head
And buried her.
We cut into chunks and its
implement to the crocodile.
That goes a little too far for me.
You drive error. You had left, not right.
That you doing always.
I can make me so angry about.
I get that thing not of your head before
you say you my need assistance.
then speak.
- Make something better for yourself.
Come, I will bring you to the airport.
- No.
No?
- Not without my sister.
You have not seen what has just happened?
O, no. You were blindfolded.
What you saw was not a naive girl
that should not have had to
interfere, but it did and when it
was kidnapped by heavy boys
who had murdered her almost. There are
still many more of the guests.
I am not without its.
Now happens.
Exactly what I did not want.
Now I must work hard.
m'n hip bottle.
What is that?
I have to that car thrown.
We drink.
- That Have you not necessary.
Do you think?
Really, doctor?
How do you know what I need?
When I say that I wish to drink, what
I drink.
about your sister...
She is probably dead.
Sorry, but so are those lazy.
They kill people without mercy.
Surely do what I say, that you would
also like sister. Go home safely.
They is not dead! I do not believe so.
You do not know what they are talking about.
We need to know why
they been abducted. I will pay you.
It will take to ransom.
That happens here as often.
It is not.
- How do you know that?
you see that man behind me?
On the opposite side. In that gray shirt.
He was involved in
a lot of shops here.
Who is he?
He called Lester Hunter.
He is still for a few days.
He came today. He owns more
than a documents Mayan art museum.
and sometimes
he steals them from a museum.
He is the greatest
collector of Maya treasures.
He is wrong loads.
And he owns the people here.
The police has already helped you?
No.
- that is due to him.
But about him you
do not need to worry.
previously to the man who are brunt
. Javier Alhabo Olivares.
He is a grave Rover. A thief. He gives
to nothing and no one, only has itself.
How did you know that he would be here?
- This is his bar. And the bar also.
And the bar in addition.
The entire street is of him.
you can see where you have?
- What should he with my sister?
They would have found something?
- Maybe.
How we come to know this?
- We?
You have not heard me?
- I pay you!
No... How many?
No! Orphan no hero.
Keep your outside, they make you wonder.
Then I ask him yourself.
- Go Ahead.
I am sure.
- Do not leave but what you can.
They does not work.
- Lester!
Walking really not the road!
as well... I love it!
I try to help you. Jesus!
go well no suicide.
Why have you drink
thrown about yourself?
she has her drink
about who love thrown.
My sister is five years ago to
come and I have never visited her.
It is my own stupid debt.
She calls and emails often
but i always to pressure.
I had the best time. They
always did things in order to improve the world.
And you must see what I do.
They is a fantastic man.
I took the reproached that
they moved to Mexico.
My parents went to separate. I
had to mediate and she sat nice here.
I do not know what I blame.
They wanted hassle not in her life.
And i had to her that
considerably if necessary rub.
You know that I really am a trut am?
You have found it?
- No, not yet.
It is not so difficult.
You are already a week in progress. You said
that it would take a couple of days.
Where do I pay you?
Explain to me that once again.
We are almost there, man.
- Make sure that you place.
We are close to,
we can find the any time.
So difficult is it not possible!
Enter the pressure continues on!
I must do everything yourself?
and make sure that you find it.
- Do i.
I do not need to tell you what
happens if you do not find it.
I do not think.
I do get a headache. And hemorrhoids.
I swear none of man. Get well but
not to worry, you get your mask.
Make sure, otherwise I care for you.
Get your but nothing in your head.
No problem, I go further.
- do you do it in your pants?
You chatters as a chicken without head.
Make well but that you find it.
Do you want to do your work, then I do my own.
understood?
All these documents
on the Mayan calendar.
O that. We will all be dead in 2012?
That is the end of the Mayan
calendar and the world.
The end of the world is but a
rumor. My sister writes something about it.
There is that they
stick to one and the same time calendars two.
And that the count every
52 years starts again.
And it ends in 2012.
- Yes, but...
you see? The ends.
Everyone says that the Mayas wisdom.
And we feel that their calendar
ends, but not that the imminent apocalypse?
You Know How stupid you sound?
- we leave this guest questions.
They is at a shaman.
- a shaman?
here is the village and his address.
- Then we go to him.
Am around ten hours awake,
we go there.
No, we are right now.
Now?
Okay.
Hopefully we make him not awake.
He is not there.
What is that for music?
We go and have a look.
What do you think?
Well, it is in any case wake up.
We say goodbye.
That was not such a good idea.
Alexis?
your sister is a good friend of us.
We have you on a photo seen.
Your wedding photos.
foreign wedding.
So'n wedding is nothing for me.
your sister is entered properly
in the Mayan culture.
They came with me a week ago.
They said they
had discovered something important about the location of the mask
of a large king.
Our most sacred leader.
What they discovered?
- a tablet, buried under a stele.
What is a Stele?
A memorial or monument
in the form of a pillar.
You sister and her archaeological
team were working to examine the
under what stele
was buried the mask.
has found it?
- we do not know.
They were close.
Maybe they have even discovered,
but they have disappeared.
What was that for mask?
long ago there was war between
the Totonaken and the Mayas.
They wanted to eradicate us.
was at that time the mask our most sacred
treasure. But they did it depends on us.
The Totonaken believed that the
mask the Mayas.
One brave Maya tried
to get back the mask.
The succeeded to regain the mask,
but he died during his mission.
What happened with the mask?
The legend says that he was hiding in
an underground pool under a stele.
The Ghosts of the cenote, the
underground Poel, protect the.
What a relief.
There breaks a new time, where
the reality belongs the universe.
That guy do not
even what happens in reality.
What would that mask of you are
worth for an American?
people getting lost in the illusion
of life. They see not clear.
So is that.
five million or so?
Name one a global amount.
drinking.
- I know how to use to drink.
That is not best.
I would but discarded.
is correct. It is damaged or so.
It feels good.
What have you got?
it going?
come with me.
Contact What is yours,
let are what is not yours.
come with me.
Contact What is yours,
let are what is not yours.
Good Morning.
where are we?
on the way to your house.
What happened last night?
I have nothing doms done?
completely refuted. You was very quiet.
You have sat here just the whole night.
Nice. I hate it when i flauwval.
I don't as...
Well done, though.
Calm, i get 'm back to that.
Are you really so stupid?
Calm.
It is over 30 meters deep!
The current drags everything below
to the sea!
I get 'm. Quiet.
you doing but quiet.
That USD 800 comes from your salary.
USD 800?
Goodness...
I can not find it.
You considers the.
Wait...
What a surprise.
What a set of idiots.
I never think also good men.
You are a dunce, not where?
Coffee?
I drink in the morning always coffee.
you think that the hassle
of tonight is nonsense?
I hear this meaning still,
I am crazy about.
What said that shaman against you?
A while back I had
some problems in the USA.
I couldn't.
I now why there is here.
Someone death driven with a sip on?
But.
- Sorry.
Tell but.
I was in the army.
One of our operations went wrong.
I got the debt.
Surely this is no reason to leave?
for me.
We need your sister.
And that we are going to do so...
- Tell.
found?
not yet.
There is anything scary at this place.
Is that so?
So eng that you balls have krimpen?
incredible.
And? Nothing?
We have searched everywhere.
Keep looking.
Diego! What have you got?
Are you not good necessarily or so?
Sorry, Javier.
I was in the mud rolls.
Really? That I had not seen.
I searched for your piece of art.
You have found it?
Keep Looking!
It is difficult search...
Even news?
- What are we going to do now?
We must find.
That is the only option.
Or would you like to
repay Lester $400,000?
I do not.
So grab a ships
a flashlight and go graves.
You have easy talk, dwarf.
I get claustrophobic.
And it is fine for me here?
- i could not care less about!
We find Arturo and Josmul.
- I am Josmul. What do you think of me?
You worked for my sister, Lauren Sofer?
- indeed.
You know that she is missing?
- that I heard.
I told you what they found?
I voted against nobody said something,
but someone I know perhaps.
Who then? Please tell us.
He hears me.
He will also remain still.
What are you doing here?
We work on a
glass-bottomed boat.
We put things that
you can see through the glass.
So you carelessly think up the Tourist?
- that is the way it is.
What is it with you?
What flik you me well?
I went nearly dead down there!
You murdered me almost!
We know that you worked for her and
that you have told someone about it. Whom?
I do not recall that I
have told someone. Certainly not instant.
I need no money.
Although i have family,
with two children.
I do it for my family.
- Keep your head.
I was in the church, with my image clean
wife and two bloedjes of children.
We always go on sunday because
his father Ramiro than the sermon.
I love the sermon.
And then we buy an ice cream.
I give the good example, so my
children Salita, Juanita, Ramiro and
Estacio on the straight path.
- let us come to the point.
correctly. After the Miss I ran with my family
hand in hand at the car park.
Then there came a man to us,
he pointed to me and threatened me.
He has a knife and says that ie
me and my wife dies.
So I swim out and save the knife
from Z'n hands. He kicked me
But fortunately I train much in the
sports school, so I skipped 'm.
But when handles are friends me.
I just wanted to say.
smote the from me.
He putted on my kidneys and broke my
nose. And probably also a rib.
It is still doing pain.
What 'dwong' he to tell you?
I do not know more.
He has me so often
on m'n main skipped.
Now I know the weather.
I told him that we had the tablet
where on was where the mask.
where than?
That they told us
we could not and cannot read the tablet.
I only know where we did find it.
Look.
That he has done.
One of its many outrages.
He is a withers!
Evil.
But i had to protect my family.
They are everything for me.
I am away here.
- come with me.
If you want to go on a boat tour
to find you know me. I hope I have helped you.
A week ago was my sister still here.
Now i finally see where they work.
I feel like her feel.
There is no more.
you find that funny?
So long in which smallpox cave
without result?
We have told us what we know.
- I think you don't! Not really!
How we then explain.
- Lieg not against me.
We don't lie.
Do not something you will regret it.
do no harm to him.
- Sit!
Not do so.
I cut it into pieces.
Do you want to know how he looks like?
You are looking for in the wrong place.
- where we must then find?
There.
What chat you're?
You said first, at the fourth stele.
It is the fifth.
Now he wants to talk to.
Where is the fifth stele?
where?
- We do not know exactly where.
The area is approximately 15 square meters.
- Tell on!
It is located 60 meters to the
south west of the stele.
You Play American Football?
You are going to help us.
One of you will note.
Well, 60 meters to the south west
of the stele so. Carlo!
let them go, then I continue!
I will stay!
No, everyone goes. If you me
again that I cut you cheap shots pieces!
I cut your throat open!
walk! And head close!
Come along!
Come along! Hurry!
Look, here is something about 2012.
- What is there ?
that we all die?
- It is not true, that I said right?
That you said but it is next to.
everything ends, the calendar, the time.
A new ice age or so.
Wait!
That side. Run!
You leave me alone?
- Not to worry!
There is a spin in m'n her?
Where do you jerk?
come out!
You have m'n nose broken, no more.
I had home a Tae Bo DVD. I have
a lot of mugs and lamps broken.
And the TV. A flat still.
Bowl, lubricate we 'm. Quiet.
Come on!
- I can no longer.
I can no longer.
- Keep on with those excuses.
Jumping!
Javier?
Diego?
- There is something bad happened.
They are beaten up.
- What Who?
A man and a woman.
- 'A' wife?
Okay, the sister.
say the men but that they were very
good at their job. Excellent even.
especially you.
They get promotion
especially that good work.
They will very happy.
- that I could imagine.
May I ask you something?
- Of Course.
What would it be?
- underground cave.
would be there Lauren?
- Maybe. You have a phone with you?
Yes, but it is very
expensive to call here... Sorry.
I know someone who can help us.
All kits?
- hoi, how does it work?
well.
I have to think about this
and I think it is not a good plan.
Why not?
Because you can go dead.
Or even worse.
What is worse than death?
Why do you make me always
ridiculous if ladies at?
You're right hear,
there is nothing worse than death.
I would just like to say that it
is a maze where you can drown.
a maze sometimes I can.
take someone with you to a cord
, you'll always find the way back.
It is too deep, I am only.
- I go!
Why not?
You Can diving?
- No.
Then you can join in.
Leave the card to be seen.
Those cards do not see everything.
There are huge open up
areas down there.
Some pieces are less than half a
meter wide. I have sat here ever hours.
I was a day in the decompression room.
So there is really nothing.
Incredibly boring.
I have 75 games
played solitaire. Not one won.
Not once. This is due to that of Aces.
You can capture the best below
or still be ready to top...
- Oscar!
Even with card is the difficult
remember where you've been.
I have a good memory.
- This is really not a good plan.
I go, okay?
Well then, you may borrow my stuff.
Because you have such a poor customer
You never paid and
probably die there.
Why pik you do that?
- he is a great host.
He does not pay and
take a mockery of you.
Because i permits. He is a hero.
- It will do. Our military.
Really, he was a variety of awards
and then a shovel under
Z'n ass of the government.
What happened?
He said that a mission expired incorrectly.
He did nothing wrong. The Government.
His team was
sent to a prohibited area.
when it was discovered that
they gave him the debt.
He has never said anything.
He is lost everything.
So he come here.
Dishonorable dismissal is the
worst thing that can happen to him.
worse than death.
Hugh! So that is worse than death.
But good.
I would have done the same.
I am only if the death for pistols.
So I would like to
have become redundant.
That was fast.
You have to keep your hands washed?
You does not come to my
stuff until you have washed.
Thanks, gozer. Goodbye.
You drink not drunk.
You can see that you have a poor customer?
You know that such
beverage me will cost money?
Coconuts do
not grow on the tree, though!
Coconuts grow to a tree.
That I know,
but that is not the point right now.
where is my mask?
your mask?
- I thought it was of the Mayas.
eight hundred years old
- Where is it?
In the banana tree,
send your gorilla but.
A REAL comedian.
- M'n job. I am a scientist.
First boy, then heavy comedian,
now again scientist. Where?
We know not.
So you don't know? I will give you a
six seconds to get to know it.
Why six seconds?
Da's a strange number.
It is an even number.
is correct. You can make the parts by three and
two. It is an even number
But there is an odd choice.
- Your friend is smart. Which number do you want?
No, six is fine. The are the seconds
where i have a problem with it.
rather than six weeks,
or six months, what do you think?
Head close!
What you thought of three?
Three?
Two.
All kits, Les?
What it is. Those two have something of me,
but they do not say where it is.
which of the two do?
All two, I think.
Who of you know?
No one, that we have already told him.
- I see from here that he lieth.
But you know for
sure that you want to do this?
Maybe not,
but I have no other option.
You can
bind one to the anchor and thrown overboard.
Then that other great fear.
So'n scientist.
What a good idea.
But unfortunately the anchors.
pity.
Then you must add it but gunning.
It, then.
What are you doing?
I m'n woman told that i
have bad water drinking and not from can.
No yet?
know for sure. Terribly.
I was three days on the toilet.
save me the details.
I feel a lot better. I must go back
to the hotel, my wife is so.
Do the sharks the greetings.
I love that crazy.
Vissenkop!
standing.
You too. Pull 'm.
remained where was I?
One.
What flik you? That would not have had!
- that needed to be!
And well your head close!
You i will come to you.
you tell me where that mask is?
Well?
of course tell you that.
God bless you.
Maybe we should
think of something else.
This is the best way to do so.
- Can I get something for you?
No, thank you.
It is a final swimming.
I will create something for you?
a sandwich. Something else...
Notify.
Sorry. But I would like to help you.
That you this is all for my family.
I am sorry that at your doubts.
I think I have everything.
I wait until sunrise.
I want to make sure that they are all there.
I agree that guy verified
that you and your girls as for crazy.
I listen.
He shows one or other command.
He was eleven years by the Navy Seals.
He did illegal missions all over the world
. He is responsible for the
murder of Mustafa, you understand.
So say you do that? Mustafa?
You know, those Hibiki Hibiki Wong or
Wang, I know how much that is hot.
He is an experienced murderer.
- Experienced?
He is a type of Rambo, you know
, but then Mexican.
you find that funny?
- I understand. We save us.
He kill your whole gang from
before you know that he is.
Think this through.
Wait effe anders, wait effe anders.
a tequila with ice.
you understand me?
you listen to me?
Of course I listen, ok!
I make no kidding!
I am in a public place.
- Okay, quiet but.
He makes everyone. Is that what you want?
- I have a lot of good men.
They have pistols,
I have trained them yourself.
go there and find my mask. And
then come here. Take me the mask.
Because I want to contribute.
I will put it in my head.
I want to contribute.
When I go to the laundry go.
people think that I love
because I am a mask wearing.
go there and make sure you
are back before he there is. If you do that?
You get your mask!
Really! I promise you!
We have nothing.
He has done nothing!
- Head close!
We have said what it is!
I have found it!
Javier, I have found it!
Andrew, the?
Unzip the!
Shoot!
bring her here! Now!
Peanut Butter.
a sandwich?
What should I do with them?
- We take the woman.
And what do we do with him?
- him? Finish it.
Why killing?
Andrew, do not.
still!
You will go out.
Why?
These caves...
They need to be protected.
The ghosts?
just laugh.
Why do you think nobody
The could find?
Notify your mouth!
You will go out.
How long will that take?
As long as it takes. We are waiting here.
You said something?
Why? I did not say anything.
You believe that gringo is it?
No, but I am not nice.
Javier, you?
How is the water?
- Suit idiot!
Get Up!
It must seem an accident.
it going?
- Go Lauren Help.
They took her note.
where is Ramon?
Ramon, where are you?
Ramon, sign up!
grasp the guns! Quick!
I may borrow this?
It is two to one.
What you said?
He can't have cared, I make her.
Let your arms fall out!
Drop!
Where are you doing?
Back to top.
There is help along the way.
You can see that? Surprise!
What a nice surprise, huh? You can
also find not? Bring her down!!!
Hi, Lauren.
- Alexis, what are you doing here?
I try to help.
- Helps.
What have you done?
Let your arms fall out!
I swear none, I shoot her death!
Shooting, Diego. But beware the mask.
- No, that is not a good idea.
Shoot it down!
It may not otherwise?
- Shoot!
The mask!
You seem to be disturbed.
- Nicolas, you are in good condition?
Sorry, I would just like to help.
Sorry.
- Keep on with help. Please.
sit.
it going?
I thought I was lost once.
- Yes, I too.
I am sorry you
must disrupt family reunion.
I will put it to you paid!
What is this heck?
My legs.
I can no longer feel my legs.
Nice to see you again.
thanks that you have saved my life.
- I had to create what is good.
a pity that you do not have the mask.
- It was not the right time.
The natural did not for nothing.
- sorry that I was selfish.
I have missed.
I have you
treated so badly when you went here.
No apologies.
You have saved me.
You have everything properly created.
I am you owe a great deal.
Yes, that is so.
But I am not alone in doing so.
The Mister helped.
Who is the hero?
go to him.
I otherwise.
I love you.
- I also of you.
Thank You for your help.
Even though I am most itself did.
Thank You for the sandwich.
- I knew you would have required.
I bring you to the hospital.
You are a real hero.
- No, you're the hero.
You are determined, ambitious,
heroic, stubborn, annoying...
I felt really. You are a hero.
You did this all for us. What
happened you earn you not at all.
Thank you that you have saved my family.
We have never discovered
what the shaman referred to.
Contact What is yours,
let are what is not yours.
He will be crazy.
Wait.
Please.
'Contact What is yours'. This is not of me.
What is yours?
What have you got?
Bowl, we will give it that her.
Look what i found.
How have you...
Javier, Javier, sign. Sign, Javier.
There is something wrong.
That are our men.
The police have them.
What do we do now?
Nothing.
We do nothing.
I wanted that mask as happy.
Go here.
I am not sschelen. We stay
here until the new day begins.
than we wait.
No reason to rush.
we enjoy
the latest sunset.
Last? What will you
feel stupid if nothing happens.
There can be any time to do.
every moment?
- each moment.
You Want to see how your mother is wrong?
Say: 'I hope that she is right'.
All archaeologists, Maya,
scientists and smart people
say that it is not the end
of the world. You are the only one.
Not true.
precisely, the sceptics.
you mention your son a sceptic?
He is agrees with me.
You believe me, huh?
you see? He believes me.
- He shook 'no'.
Not true.
- to be true.
How can one man so
often wrong?
We are already in the nine hours.
Come with me, Octavio is tired.
Well than. Another ten seconds.
Maybe that is enough.
- Maybe. A further seven seconds.
Subtitles ripped by cjdijk.
Translation: Three Lines Productions bv