Nothing.
Hit and run.
Whoever it was, they're gone.
War's over. He got the memo.
Ize?
Allen?
Ize.
What?
We got no movement,
not a sign of a shadow.
How...
How long we been here, man?
18-plus?
- Twenty.
- Jesus.
There's nobody
fucking out there, man.
- 'Less he's a pro.
- A hajji?
I'm just saying, maybe.
Six construction guys
on that pipeline.
Huh?
Two-man security escort.
Yeah.
Look at 'em.
What?
Eh, not one body near
to anything resembling cover.
That's just fucking weird to me.
Don't mean shit, man.
Means he took them out
pretty fucking fast.
And I think they're all
fucking head shots, too.
Oh, fuck off. Look, hey.
Check out our boy with
the radio; He got the call out?
Yeah.
That ain't a head shot, Ize.
Okay, fine, so one
without a fucking head shot.
I mean, eight guys, 30 seconds?
So you're saying a hajji
went in there with a semi-auto?
Said he might be a pro.
Oh, right.
We're dealing with Juba now?
Might be.
I'm just saying,
that wall's cursed.
It's a wall, man.
You're scared of a fucking wall?
Nah, I'm scared of
what's behind it.
Could be two hajjis
sucking each other off
behind that thing.
Hey.
What's there is there.
Rest of that shit's
in your head, you understand?
Ize?
Mm-hmm?
What's your vote now?
Got anyone out there?
Nah.
I mean, I was 60% sure.
Now I'm, like, 80.
I don't think so.
Or... yep, he's a pro.
Oh, fuck off.
Probably the same
as it always is.
Four or five hajjis came in
and bushwhacked 'em.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, makes sense.
Maybe.
Or he's a pro.
I'm fucking hot.
I'm calling it.
Ah, see, fuck you, man.
I knew that's what
you wanted to do.
I'm fucking with you, man.
What, are you
fucking hungry again?
Already had four or five MREs,
gorilla fuck.
I'm not fucking sitting here
dancing around
your super-theories
that a fucking super-sniper's
down there, bro.
No fucking way a hajji
sticks around this long.
You shitting me?
I'm fucking hot as shit.
My balls have melted
into one fucking ball.
Later, you're on duty,
you're gonna pry these apart,
all right?
Oh, yeah,
if I can fucking find it.
And you're gonna
fucking like it, too.
I should've joined
the fucking air force.
Nah, you're too fucking big
for the air force.
You'd bring
the whole thing down.
Hey, I'm serious, man.
- Get down.
- I'm serious, too.
I'm going down there,
grabbing that guy's radio,
coming back up here, and we are
getting the fuck gone.
Yeah, Roger that.
Comm check.
Yup-yup. Check-check.
Where have you gone?
Oh, yep.
Movement?
Ah, you look
fucking rigid as shit.
How's that one ball?
Oh, real nice. Real smart.
You'll always be
number one to me, my man.
You got eyes on that wall?
I got eyes on your ass.
Oh, shake that Booty.
Oh, yeah, there it is.
Uh.
Ooh, there we go. There it is.
I think your tampon
just fell out.
Damn right. That'd
usually cost you 25 bucks.
You're clear 360.
Keep them eyes open.
Just watch my six.
Roger that.
Yeah, we're fucking
solo out here.
Lonely as fuck.
Fuck.
I'm getting closer here.
You got eyes on that wall?
Roger that.
- Shit.
- What?
Ah, this...
Man, this fucking thing's
fogging up, man.
You have got to get
rid of that shit.
It was Dean's.
Fuck Dean. Dean was a bitch.
Yeah, fuck Dean.
Dean was a bitch.
Bad Juju carrying around
a dead man's scope.
Something's not right.
What?
Talk to me, man, talk to me.
What's going on down there?
Ize, they are head shots, man.
Can you tell
where they came from?
You know what, fuck it.
Get the hell out of there, bro.
Hey, Ize, just check the...
Ah, shit, I'm hit!
Fuck, man, fuck! I fucked up.
- Fuck!
Fuck! Shit!
Hang on, buddy.
I'm coming down.
Shit.
They see me out there.
Back up! Back up!
- Take cover! -They see me
out there.
Take cover!
What are you doing, man?!
No! Get away from me, man!
No!
No! No!
Back up!
- Oh! Fucking shit!
Take cover!
Get down!
Ah! Shit! Fuck!
Sar'nt!
- Sar'nt Matthews!
Ah, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Ah, shit...
Fuck, I'm sorry!
Shit. Fuck.
No way. No fucking way.
Ah, shit. Okay, uh...
My brother, fucking tell RJ.
You got to tell him, okay?
- What about RJ?
- RJ.
Tell fucking RJ that I got...
I got fucking... I got fucking
22 grand, man. 22 grand.
Stop, stop.
Stop talking, bro.
I don't know what to do. I
don't know what to fucking do.
Tourniquet.
Use your fucking tourniquet.
Fucking... tourniquet!
Use your fucking tourniquet!
Ize.
Ize, I need
your fucking help, man.
I can't!
You know that!
No, no, no, no!
Fucking...
The radio, the radio!
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
You got it?
Fuck.
Fuck, man, you got it?!
One second!
Oh, god.
- Breaker, breaker...
Aw, shit.
Break, break, break,
spartan thirty tree,
uh, requesting extraction.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
Shit.
Shit. No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
Fuck.
You fucking piece of shit.
Fuck!
Fucking fuck!
Break, break, break,
spartan thirty tree,
- requesting extraction.
Break, break, break!
Spartan three tree
requesting extraction!
Radio comm?!
He hit my fucking antenna!
Hit the fucking antenna, man.
Fuck.
You got eyes on him?
I think I got a shot.
What?
I'm going for it, man.
- You got eyes?
Fucking... Sar'nt Matthews!
Fucking...
Sar'nt Matthews!
Sar'nt!
No, no, no, no, no.
He'd shoot you
before you even get...
S...
Sar'nt Matthews?!
You hear me?!
I'm here.
Hang in there.
Please fucking hang in there.
You got eyes on him?
Come on, man,
where'd he come from?
I don't fucking know.
I don't know.
Crack bang.
What's the distance?
Crack bang. Crack bang.
Didn't you hear it?
Crack bang, how many seconds?
Give... give me a fucking...
Ize. You didn't fucking Gauge?
Listen, man,
I got one shot at him.
Don't fucking
touch that rifle, man.
Second you touch that fucking
rifle, you're dead.
Hold on.
Aah!
Fuck!
Oh. Oh.
Fuck.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Fuck!
All right.
Shane, I got eyes on him.
Sar'nt Matthews?
Sar'nt Matthews,
you fucking hear me?
Shane!
Oh, man.
Come... you didn't bleed out.
Come on, man, get up.
Get up
and dress that wound, man.
Oh...
Mm. Oh.
Aah... aah...
Oh! Aah.
Fuck. Fuck.
Oh! Oh!
You motherfucker.
Fu... fucking...
Fuck. Fuck.
Okay.
Last transmission.
Come in.
How do you copy?
Last transmission.
Come in.
How do you copy?
How do you read us?
- Last transmission.
How do you copy?
This is spartan thirty tree.
How copy?
Reading you Lima Charlie, over.
This is spartan thirty tree.
Receiving enemy fire.
Requesting dust-off.
I got a man down.
There's a shooter.
Got us pinned.
Me, got me pinned.
Requesting medevac.
I repeat, I repeat,
requesting medevac.
What's your position, over?
Uh, uh, grid whiskey hotel 7203.
Copy that. Stand by.
Oh, god.
Hey, Shane.
We're going home, buddy.
About fucking time.
All right, come on.
This is spartan tree tree.
Are you there, over?
Okay.
Reading you Lima Charlie.
You're on a radio feed,
and we do not
want to move beyond range
of your signal. Do you copy?
Beyond range of my signal?
You're already
in my local radio.
Are you close?
Need a confirm on your ID, over.
This is Sar'nt Allen Isaac,
51st Oda.
I have staff Sar'nt
Shane Matthews here with me.
But he's down.
Possibly Kia.
I don't know.
He's not responding, so...
Over.
We copy, spartan tree tree.
Prepping medevac.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right,
you little fucker, you.
Ah...
Huh.
Fucking NATO round.
Goddamn.
7.62x51.
No, we got a shooter.
High-caliber weapon.
Requesting UAV.
We need your challenge code
before we send in medevac.
W-what? Say-say that again.
Send your challenge code.
What the fuck is...
No. But, um...
Who is this?
This is captain Otis Simmons.
I need your challenge code
if I'm gonna get you
and your staff Sar'nt medevac.
Uh, Romeo, no... no, wait,
I didn't say
I needed medical assistance.
Do you copy?
Copy that. I assumed.
But this is protocol.
Well, fuck me.
How do I know that?
Huh? That you are
who you say you are?
Allen Isaac. You and your
staff sergeant Shane Matthews
made an overnight worm
into a kill zone
to investigate
a potential sniper
and report back to us.
Okay, okay.
All right, I'm sorry.
I'm-I'm a little fucked up.
It, uh... listen, you
got to bring a heavy escort.
This guy's a fucking asshole.
Where do you keep going?
Do you have a flare, sergeant?
Do you copy?
Uh, yeah. No, I don't.
I have an m4 and a sidearm.
I need you to stand
and fire into the air.
We need to get a lock
on your position.
What the fuck?
This ain't ranger school.
The fucking shooter will get
a fucking lock on my position.
Well, I can't help you
unless I know your location.
Do you copy?
Fuck.
A lot of fucking help
you've been
so fucking far, motherfucker.
This is fucking stupid.
This ain't fucking protocol.
Sergeant, we need
your exact location
to send in medevac.
Say that again.
I need your location.
No, my rank. What's my rank?
Sergeant.
You, uh...
You got an accent.
Not American.
You have seen through
my camouflage.
Fuck you talking about?
I'm talking about
hiding behind words.
Like you are hiding
behind that wall.
You... you're...
Motherf...
Oh, shit.
You fuck!
I've got a question for you.
Your friend... is he dead?
Ugh.
He... he looks dead to me.
This is spartan 33
sending in the blind.
But maybe he's just unconscious.
I got a man down!
Sh-shall I make sure?
I got a sniper.
I got an enemy sniper.
- Requesting medevac!
- Shall I shoot him in the head?
I repeat. I repeat.
- Requesting...
- Does he have a wife?
Children?
Will they enjoy a closed casket
if I take his face off?
All right, all right,
shut the fuck up, man.
All right, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
Is there something
that you want?
Yes.
Well, I don't know nothing.
I'm a buck Sar'nt.
They don't tell me shit.
So fuck you.
That's not what I want.
Oh, what do you want?
You want fucking
12 virgins or something?
I want to get to know you.
I just want to get to know you.
Will you allow that?
Y... you're fucking with me.
I was, but you figured it out.
So now let's be real.
It's just you and me out here.
So, what do you say?
Yeah, I'll talk to you.
Good. Where are you from?
No. Listen,
I don't know shit about you,
so why don't you go first?
Me? There is nothing
to say. No story.
Well, you're the one
who wants to get chatty, bro.
Why ain't you saying anything?
Huh?
Okay. I'll start.
I am just a regular Iraqi man.
A civilian.
A civilian, my ass.
Crack bang.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, bang.
Four plus four.
Four plus four, 800.
Plus...
Okay.
Bullet.
45, 50, 60.
60-degree angle.
Nine, 950...
950 plus...
That gives me...
1,500.
Okay. Okay.
Got the wall,
me, Matthews.
Crane, construction site,
trailers, flagpole.
And you?
What about me?
Are you a regular American?
Uh, yeah, a regular Joe.
A regular g.I. Joe.
Army ranger or marine?
You worked in our
fucking ranks, huh?
Had our training, and then
you fucking backstab us.
Look, these fucking guys
were building pipelines.
Building up your fucking
economy, you asshole.
Pipelines, huh?
For our economy?
Yeah, that's fucking money.
Infrastructure,
education, schools.
These guys
were fucking contractors.
Not here to fight.
War's over, bro.
Bro?
Whatever, man.
It's an interesting
choice of words.
And yet I disagree
with you, bro.
The war's not over.
Definitely not for you.
You say, you say a lot
of fucking fancy words.
What are you, ha...
Hajji Shakespeare or some shit?
Shakespeare?
Military lingo is all poetry.
Battle rattle, ghetto grip...
Johnny jihad, friendly fire.
- Your turn, Isaac.
Or should I say "Ize"?
What?
What-what do you mean it's my
turn? What you want me to say?
- Tell me where you're from.
Where's your family?
I'm not talking
about fucking family.
Oh, god.
Okay, then tell me about your
brothers and sisters at arms.
That's a negative, too, bro.
I don't want any military
secrets, just stories.
Eat a dick.
I will shoot Matthews
if you don't talk.
Go ahead.
- Yes?
He is your second loss.
First Dean, now Matthews.
How the fuck
do you know about Dean?
- Keep talking.
- No, fuck you. How?
You carry his scope around.
What was it your sergeant said?
"A dead man's scope"?
Oh, you...
Just tell me something, Isaac.
Tell me about your comrades.
Or I will shoot
Matthews' face off.
Okay.
Uh... yeah.
Uh, we, uh... we play ball.
- I beg your pardon?
Uh... yeah, no, me, uh...
Me and the squad, we, uh...
We play in the afternoon.
Uh, uh, get baked
in the Iraqi sun.
Uh... nothing else to do.
No war to fight.
"Baked"?
- What does that mean?
Baked, like, uh,
you know, tanned.
Go on.
Go on?
What about sergeant Matthews?
Did he get baked?
Did Dean?
I ain't talking
about fucking Dean with you,
you dirty fucking hajji.
If I were you,
I would start talking, Isaac.
Tell me about Dean.
What's the obsession, huh?
What the fuck?
It's interesting to me...
The bond
between you and your brothers.
And I will shoot Matthews
if you do not speak.
I'm looking at him right now.
It would be so easy
to tear his face off.
- His family won't even
recognize him. -
is that what you want, Ize?
You should just answer
my questions.
All right, all right.
So, tell me about Dean's scope.
Oh, fuck.
I can see it at the base
of the wall there.
Why do you keep it?
Fuck.
You said it's broken.
Why would you carry around
a broken scope, Isaac?
Oh, shut the fuck up, man.
How's this end?
How the fuck's this end?
I'm sorry?
I said, how the fuck's it end?
What's the fucking endgame?
There's no endgame.
I'm just enjoying
our conversation.
Oh, stop.
Fucking stop, all right?
You're not gonna get
to fucking know me.
But I feel
like I know you better already.
No, you fucking don't!
You don't know shit.
You're dehydrated...
I know that.
That's why I aimed
at your water bottle.
No, you didn't. You fucking
was trying to hit me.
No. The water bottle.
Nobody's that fucking accurate.
And your antenna.
No fucking way.
And your knee.
I know the Popliteal vein
in your leg
carries enough blood that,
no matter what kind
of bandaging you have,
you will still be sitting
in a puddle of plasma.
You're feeling fatigued,
lightheaded.
- And you will bleed out
before nightfall. -
what the fuck is going on
with this shit?
You fucker.
You psychotic motherfucker.
What do you want from me?
Oh, fuck!
Fucking...
Fucking... hajji.
Hey, where
do you keep fucking going, huh?
No, no,
you're trying to fucking circle
my wall, ain't you?
Huh?
Trying to circle
around my wall, motherfucker?
That's ironic.
Yeah, I'm right, huh?
You say "my wall."
The very wall your country
came here to knock down,
you now try desperately
to keep from falling.
Oh, you find that
fucking funny, huh?
You should know,
- that wall you're hiding behind
was actually part of a school.
Yeah, well, I'll piss on it.
That's what I think
about your fucking wall.
You're hiding in the shadow
of Islam.
No, I'm hiding in the shadow
of fucking death.
I'm in the fucking shadow
of death.
That's got...
That's got to be a 20 mag.
Eight guys.
It's got to be 20 mag.
One in Matthews,
three in me.
That 76...
That 7.62x51 NATO round
is U.S. issued?
Hey, motherfucker.
You want to talk?
Come on, man. What's up?
You want to know the weapon
I'm using.
M24?
Mark 11?
I would prefer
an M96 windrunner any day.
I thought we were being honest.
I know you're using a mark 11.
No, you believe
that's what I'm using.
But you don't know anything
for certain.
Y-you don't know shit.
Is that how you say it?
- "You don't know shit"?
Say that again.
I can't hear you.
Okay.
You...
Don't...
Know... shit.
I don't know shit, huh?
Well, go on, please.
Educate me, man.
Come on, I'm listening.
You Americans,
you think you know it all.
You think it's simple.
That I am your enemy.
But we are not so different,
you and I.
Yeah, except I ain't
a fucking terrorist.
And you think I am?
You are the one who has come
to another man's country.
- Camouflaged yourself
in his land, -
- in his soil.
No fucking way.
From where I'm sitting,
you look very much like
the terrorist.
You're in the fucking trash?
No fucking way.
Unless he's a pro.
You're him.
You're Juba.
The ghost.
A hundred men out there
call themselves Juba.
I'm just a man.
35 U.S. casualties,
angel of death.
That's why they never find you.
Damn.
You must've been days
in that fucking shit heap.
So, we trained you, obviously.
Learn how to shoot,
trajectory, zeroing the rifle,
no reloads between shots.
Learned all that shit
and then betrayed us?
Depends on the angle
you look at it from.
Only one angle.
- Yes, as I'd expect you to say.
No.
Tell me you're my enemy...
Fine, I'll respect that.
We kill, we kill.
But say you're my friend
and shoot me in the back,
the only angle I see
is a fucking snake.
But if this friend shoots you
in the back and you survive,
is it okay to shoot him back?
I want you
to tell me something, Isaac.
Why are you here?
Why are you still here, Isaac?
How many tours
have you done now?
Why do you keep coming back?
Ooh.
Is it because of Dean?
You've got to...
How the fuck did I get here?
Is that why?
Be honest with me, Isaac.
Is it because of Dean?
- Just tell me...
How... did you know...
How'd you know that name?
Tell me one thing about him.
Just one thing.
We were from around
about the same area.
His cousins...
Went to the same school as me.
My dad knows his...
Seen his kid.
Held him.
More than Dean's ever done.
Clem works
by the fucking stop n' shop.
Clem?
Clementine, his wife.
No fucking way. I can't...
I c...
I can't go back to that.
Fucking day in, day out shit.
And them looking at me.
And they would. They...
They'd look at me and they'd...
They'd see me.
Fuck.
Nope.
I can't go... I can't...
I can't do that.
I can't go back.
Oh, my god.
Fuck.
You happy now, huh?
Now you know everything.
You're fucked up, you know that?
Why is that?
'Cause you got to mess
with my fucking head, too.
Isaac, when this is over,
the skin will be cut
from your face.
Your eyes will be gouged.
Fucking shoot me, you prick.
Your lying tongue
will be stapled to your chest.
Just fucking shoot me,
man. Get it over with.
But I will let them find
your body.
Fuck it,
I might just shoot myself.
All right, you asshole,
where are you?
Okay.
All right,
you stupid motherfucker.
Bite on this,
you fucking hajji bitch.
Come on, show me something.
Send it, bitch.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck, aah.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck!
That was foolish, Isaac.
I could've shot you.
I could've easily shot you.
Ize.
I just want to have
a conversation with you, Isaac.
Why are you trying
to get yourself killed?
Isaac, are you there?
Oh, fuck.
Isaac. Isaac.
The radio
you risked your life for...
It's dead.
Are you dead, too?
You missed. I'm still here.
You're not that fucking good.
He speaks!
Tear up the planks.
Hear, hear.
It is the beating
of his hideous heart.
What's that, one of your
gay-ass hajji poems?
American.
"Tell-tale heart."
Edgar Allan Poe.
I didn't catch a fucking word
you're saying, man.
Edgar Allan Poe. Don't you...
What's wrong with your fucking
radio, man? What is that?
You must've studied his work.
He's an American great.
Writing is really...
What is it?
Not doing a fucking thing.
Did you know
that he was an orphan?
He tried to be a soldier,
but didn't get very...
Shane. Shane, is that you?
He was a better writer
than a soldier.
"Once upon a midnight dreary,
"while I pondered,
weak and weary...
- Sar'nt Matthews!
- "Suddenly there came...
- "A tapping, rapping...
- Is that you?
"At my chamber door.
"And there stepped
a stately raven
from the saintly days of yore."
"Take thy beak from
out of my heart,
"and take thy form
from off my door.
Quoth the raven, 'nevermore.'"
or perhaps you would prefer
Robert frost?
"A voice said...
"'Look me in the stars...
- I see you, man!
- "'...And tell me truly,
- "'men of earth...
- I knew you were taking a nap!
"'...if all the soul
and body scars...
I found that fucking weasel.
Were not too
much to pay for birth.'"
12 o'clock.
In the fucking trash heap.
His poetry is so beautiful.
Fu...
Shit.
So, uh, you studied, huh?
Uh... studied, uh...
You studied here or abroad?
Like, um, I know
they got those, uh,
study abroad programs
or whatnot.
Shane!
A shot from that distance,
he's got to be at least
25, 30 feet up, man.
We're talking 1,500 meters.
1,550 maybe.
Right? Huh?
Why ain't you talking, man?
Come on, you there?
Ah, fuck.
Fuck.
Are you there, man?
It's just, you know, uh,
you know a lot
about books and shit.
I just thought I might even
learn some hajji Shakespeare
or some shit.
Shakespeare?
Is that the only poet you know?
I studied English.
What, you, uh...
You minor in sniping
or something?
I was a teacher in Baghdad,
but a bomb hit my school.
Hey, you got it? Shane.
I got shrapnel
in my left elbow. Still hurts.
Fucking trash heap
behind the white trailer.
1,550.
It reminds me
of the students I lost.
Go on, baby.
Go on, baby, let's do this.
Is that why
you shoot civilian contractors?
As the scripture says,
an eye for an eye.
That's bullshit.
You're no more religious
than I am, man.
That's just a fucking excuse
to shoot up some Americans.
You're good, man.
Just keep going slow,
baby, real slow.
- Is that a question, Isaac?
- Slow is smooth,
smooth is fast.
Yeah, that's right.
You see,
that's what I don't get.
How's an educated person like
you become a fucking terrorist?
You tell me.
Oh, shut your fucking mouth.
You're fading, Isaac.
You like to hear
yourself talk, don't you?
I'm fucking fantastic.
Chilling like a villain, baby.
You are not fantastic.
You have no water.
You're dehydrated.
The sun is...
The sun's baking you.
You're bleeding to death.
Cap...
Captain...
Captain Albright.
What's that?
A legend.
Trained me.
Trained Dean, too.
He's coming for us.
For your bodies.
When we don't report in,
he's on your ass.
Judging from your
and Matthews' performances,
I'm not concerned.
Fuck you.
He's coming for us.
He trained us.
Trained us to survive.
And won't he be disappointed?
You didn't win shit.
You hear me, motherfucker?
- You didn't win shit.
From a place you will not see...
Comes a sound you will not hear.
Just a flash of fucking light.
Boom.
When I'm done with you
and Matthews,
everyone will know
who the winner is.
Shane!
Hold still, man, hold still.
Should I take
sergeant Matthews' head off?
Shit.
Hold still, man.
- Don't fucking move.
- Will you take something
from Matthews?
Like your broken scope?
He's in my crosshairs right now.
I've got eyes on him.
What?
I don't make
empty threats, Isaac.
I'm going to tear his face off.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
I carry around the scope
because it reminds me
why I can't hold a Sc...
Hold a rifle again.
Okay?
You listening to me?
Dean dropped it,
the scope, in the line of duty.
He fell over trying
to pick it up and I missed...
I missed the sniper, okay?
You fucking listening to me?!
I didn't see him.
That's how he got hit.
It was my fault.
Goddamn it,
you fucking listening?!
No. Slower, man.
Slower, slower.
Slower what?
- What's going on?
Who are you talking to?
Who am I talking to?
- I'm talking to fucking god!
He's 30 feet up
in the trash somewhere!
I don't fucking know.
I'm sorry, man.
Give me Max plus four!
Six mils right!
Send when ready!
Fuck.
Did you get him?
Please tell me you got him.
Aah!
- Oh, fuck.
- Fuck!
- You bastard. You fucking...
- Oh, fuck me.
Just fucking let him go,
you piece of shit!
Shane, get up, man!
He ain't a threat
to you anymore.
- Just fucking let him go.
- Oh, goddamn it.
- Don't fucking stop! Don't fucking stop!
- Fuck, fuck.
Just like that.
Just like that, baby. Just go!
Fuck. Come on, man! Move!
Keep coming, man!
You're almost there!
Come on.
Just like that, man.
Reach for me.
Reach for me!
Why? Why?
I want to go home!
I want to go fucking home,
motherfucker.
So go.
Walk away.
You'll just fucking shoot me.
No, I won't.
Yes, you fucking will.
Why wouldn't you?
Because that's not really
what you want.
What?
You don't want
to go home, do you?
The fuck's that mean, man?
The war's over.
You're still here.
Why?
I killed him.
I did.
He went to go confirm a kill.
Enemy sniper.
The guy was playing possum.
Started shooting at Dean.
I tried shooting back, but the
bullet went right through Dean.
Oh, man, I lied!
I fucking lied so much!
Trying to keep
the story straight.
I lied to everybody.
I lied to every single person,
except you, a fucking hajj!
Are you there?
You listening to me?
Do you hear me?
Where are you, man?
Where do you keep going?
No, something's off.
Spartan
33, this is mobile HQ actual.
Spartan thirty tree,
this is mobile HQ actual.
This is spartan 33!
How copy?
Spartan 33 confirmed.
- Name and rank?
- Sar'nt a...
Sergeant Allen b. Isaac.
Affirm.
Good to hear you again, Sar'nt.
What the fuck?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, cap, cap!
Any sign of the
shooter in the last hour?
No, still quiet.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
We're chilling
like villains, cap.
Cap, cap, cap! This is
Sar'nt Allen b. Isaac...
What's Matthews' status?
He's stable, sir.
No, no!
Captain Albright!
All due respect, cap,
that's what y'all said
an hour ago.
Can I get an updated eta?
Eta about an hour 20.
Copy that.
Fuck. Don't do this, man.
We're getting baked out here.
- Little out of it.
- Hang in there, boys.
We'll be approaching
grid hotel whiskey 7203
in approximately 6-0 Mikes.
Had to detour due to hostiles.
That guy called for us.
Fucking hajjis.
Just hoping you get here
before nightfall.
Scared of the dark now, boys?
How many times you done this,
you motherfucker?
Could've fooled me.
Sure you don't need a little
vagisil for the problem areas?
Construction guys
call for security detail.
Security detail calls for us,
and I...
- I call for them.
- I hear that.
We'll see you in 80...
Camouflage yourself in me,
you fuck.
We'll do our best, cap.
Over and out.
Out.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck you...
Fuck off, will ya?
- Hey, damn it!
Hey, you fucking there?
You can't shoot them.
You know that, right?
You shoot, you give away
your position.
And they'll fucking find you.
They will.
You listening to me?
You there?
Fuck.
I'm gonna shut you the fuck up.
Ah.
I ain't afraid of dyin'.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Spread out!
Secure the perimeter!
Go, go!
Casualty, 10 o'clock.
Sergeant Isaac.
All right, go, move it!
The trash. He's in...
It's all gonna be okay.
Two friendlies!
Got two friendlies!
We got you. Just breathe.
- He's in the trash.
- You're gonna be all right.
All clear! Perimeter clear!
Bulldog 1-7, wheel's up.
3-5, wheel's up.
Bulldog flight...
Coming right, heading 2-3-0.
3-5, copy.
Try to relax, sergeant.
You're gonna be all right.
Just relax. Just relax.
I've set up the oxygen.
He's going through it
pretty fast
so prep the backup tank.
We'll reset in five Mikes.
You got that? Five Mikes.
Copy that.
What?
- Holy shit!
- We're taking fire!
Where the fuck's it coming from?
He's in the trash!
- Lie down! Lie down!
- He's in the trash!
- What?
- He's in the fucking trash!
- Hold on!
He's in the trash!
Under fire! Under fire!
Brace! Brace!
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
We're going down!
Helo bulldog 1-7,
Helo bulldog 3-5.
This is Baghdad command.
How copy?
Bulldog 1-7, how copy?
This is bulldog 1-7.
Reading you Lima Charlie.
Over.