We're reporting live here
in Lucas Valley outside
Senator Wyman's mansion...
where a tense,
ongoing hostage situation
has been unfolding for hours now...
Were on the scene with a breaking...
Wyman's mansion involving as well.
Right now I'm standing outside
the mansion of Senator Wyman where...
Right now we have the-
the bomb squad showed up uh...
FBI and the ATF and uh, we...
Hey get Medivac in here now.
I need another team
of sharpshooters.
I'm disappointed in you Detective.
You've had over two hours
to wire that money.
You just don't withdraw a hundred
million dollars out of an ATM machine.
It's not that easy.
Besides, my people want assurances
the senator's okay.
You think I care?
You have fifteen minutes
to make that transfer happen.
God.
All right people, standby.
Nobody fire until you
hear my signal.
There's more than money at stake here.
The senator's counting on us.
Bomb squad en route.
Call for TJ see if he's close.
I got my hands full up here.
- Glass, what's your ETA?
- Twenty seconds.
We got a situation here.
Guy named Milos.
Balkan terrorist.
He's already killed three hostages,
and now he's rigged a bomb...
- in the basement.
- Milos?
He's very dangerous.
Watch your back.
Okay we're droppin' down.
I need sharpshooters covering us.
It's up to you, Glass.
It's all up to you.
Okay man, get ready to drop.
Five seconds.
Glass, talk to me.
- What's goin' on?
- Entering basement. Nothing yet.
Over here.
- Hey Lieutenant, over here.
- I think we found something.
Okay. Looks like we got
ourselves a detonator.
Glass.
We're running out of time.
I got a countdown, one minute...
forty-two seconds.
Listen up people.
No one fire.
Wait for my signal.
Shooters
What the hell's going on?
Hold your fire dammit.
Hold your fire!
You, get your face down!
Talk to me Glass.
All hell's breaking loose up here.
Your time is up.
Something's wrong.
It's too easy.
- That was the decoy.
- Okay, get out of there.
Clear the area, that was the decoy.
You are a dead man.
Come on, everybody...
Let's go.
Seach out, reach out
and touch someone.
- Small gift sir?
- Would you get lost.
There he is, check it out.
Right there.
That's right.
Look around.
We see you.
You sure about this guy?
Let's do it.
I don't like this guy.
You gonna take care of me?
You take care of me
I'll take care of you.
You give me a litle extra,
- I can make some deliveries for ya.
- Yeah.
Show your hands.
Stand up motherfucka.
Hands on your head.
All right big shot.
Turn around.
Hands on your head.
Hands on your head!
Lilly, what the fuck are
you doin' in here?
Nice time with your girlfriend?
I was trying to make some money
for my baby for y'all assholes...
- came up in here.
- Yeah? Well I...
thought you were supposed
to be in a fuckin' shelter.
Too many junkies in there.
What, you gonna give me
a place to live?
Ray, what we gonna do
with my girl here, man?
We're gonna bust her and take
her kid to Social Services.
- Or.
- Or What?
Or we take her down to
Redemption House.
She'll be back on the
junk in no time.
No I promise.
The Rehab was goin' good.
I just needed a little extra
help for my baby.
Look, I wanna do right.
Just give me a chance.
Please.
All right, I see you on the street
again hustlin', for whatever reason,
I'm gonna bust you.
Now come here.
I never seen you before.
And I never wanna see you again.
- Go, get out of here.
- Thank you.
You're lucky you got a daughter.
Sorry Fuzzy.
All right big shot,
you're going to jail.
It's like I keep telling you man,
if you want your
detective shield back,
you gotta start actin'
like a team player again.
What, working garbage detail
for two years? No thanks.
So that's it, you're just gonna
let your demons win?
- What demons?
- What demons he says.
Only the ones
that's been eatin' you up.
Look, all I know is
I can't do this shit anymore.
That's all.
Okay?
You're gonna explode, man.
Let's get a drink.
Let's go explode and get a drink.
TJ, remember that incident
at the senator's mansion last year?
Not good.
What you got on that
computer screen, Captain?
Bad news.
That's an l-R-D.
Instant Retirement Device.
Computerized shifting sensors,
counter-logic traps.
Nastiest class of ticker
I've ever seen.
They first showed up in Africa.
Now they're using 'em in East Timor.
Same stuff that blew up
the senator's mansion.
Whenever there's
a real high-class bomb for hire.
Trust me.
Oh come on...
Fuzzy, give me a break.
Come on, Ray.
Listen man, listen.
I'm your partner. Not only that,
I'm also your friend.
I'm probably the only friend
you got left.
Now I can't sit back and watch you
throw your fuckin' life
down the toilet, man.
You gotta start talkin', man.
You know, let it out,
get it outta your system
'fore it eats you alive.
Thanks.
- Straight ahead.
- Let's go, Vershbow.
Come on.
Turn left when you get
in there, love.
Guess I could do with a drink,
I can tell ya that.
It's a little late for a delivery?
Maybe they need somebody
to sign for it.
Let's sign for it.
Police.
What the fuck are you doin'?
Police!
- Police, god dammit.
- Let me go.
Calm down!
Watch out, Ray.
Look out!
Let's get outta here.
Drop it.
Let her go.
You'll hit her.
Tell him to drop the gun, now
or I'll shoot the girl.
The end of your life has just begun.
Let's go.
Don't worry my dear.
We'll be back for you.
Okay Fuzzy,
they're gone.
Fuzzy?
Hey man, it's gonna be all right.
Okay?
Damn,
you feel that draft?
- What?
- It's cold.
Well just don't talk.
Just don't talk.
Ray?
Yeah?
Ray,
those demons inside you...
let 'em go, Ray...
'fore it's too late.
Oh no man, come on.
Oh no.
Don't die on me.
God dammit.
Don't die on me, man, Fuzzy.
Prints?
We're workin' on it.
What about Ballistics?
The lab's backed up so
we're gonna have to wait a while.
Hey Nettles,
Captain's lookin' for you.
Thanks.
Nettles.
I'm sorry, Fuzzy was a good cop.
He was a good man, too.
- I want in on this, Captain.
- Wait a minute buddy boy.
You're Narcotics.
This is a homicide case.
I saw the bastards, I know...
what they look like.
You gotta let me in on it.
You know that.
I understand, you know the rules.
Until Internal Affairs
clears this up.
She won't talk.
This is all she had on her.
We don't even have a name.
I got a name.
In memory of Brandon.
Somethin' to start with.
- What is this?
- That's the bracelet she was wearing.
Looks like detonation
wire or somethin'.
Run that down
to the bomb squad, Artie.
Let me do it.
On come on, let me do it.
Artie.
Captain,
let me do it.
Okay Ray.
You go home.
You get cleaned up,
you get some rest.
Thanks.
What an asshole.
And then my tongue
stud gets caught...
on- on- on his um, his earrings.
So, there we were,
making out at the concert, right,
things were really getting hot.
Okay, right. So
we're-we're making out, right?
What took you so long?
Excuse me?
Medium everything,
hold the anchovies.
You're the pizza guy, right?
I'm looking for the bomb squad.
I'm sorry- sorry.
L- I just... I assumed that...
Bomb squad where?
Out on a call.
Third and hyde.
Thank you.
Sorry, Mom.
Here it comes, all right?
Feel it?
Tick tock.
I felt it.
That, Dugger, is the very
essence of our existence.
Synchronicity.
Swan, they're holding her downtown.
And what if she talks?
She won't talk.
You trust me on that.
Well that's real reassuring,
Swan, but just in case,
I think I'll cut out now...
and disappear.
And what would Michelangelo say?
You think he'd let one
of his trusted pigment mixers
just abandon him in the middle
of painting the Sistine Chapel?
What the hell are you talking about?
We're about to create
a work of art here, a masterpiece,
a masterpiece that's gonna be
discussed and talked about a
And admired for centuries.
And until that last,
magnificent brush stroke is finished,
nothin', absolutely nothin',
is gonna get in the way
of the artistic process.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
Are we clear on that?
And our business plans
will not change.
And we'll continue our preparations
with or without
our lovely muse.
Well we can't just leave her behind.
There's no way the
cop's will let her out.
Unless we force 'em.
How the hell are we gonna do that?
Through pure and simple motivation.
Is that right?
And I'm motivated.
We got a ticker in the shoebox.
- I better call Meg.
- Ball and chain.
Look, ten bucks says that
he's asking himself right now...
- Excuse me.
- What the hell?
- Who's in charge?
- He is.
Maybe you can tell me what that is.
It's cute.
Swap, Meet jewelry.
Where'd you get this, brother?
Off a girl's wrist.
She still alive?
Yeah.
Why?
Because this is real dangerous shit,
and that means she's probably
a dangerous young lady.
See that outer strand? That's
some kind of high-grade det cord.
- And the inner strand...
- Well yeah the inner strand,
is Semtex.
Excuse me?
Semtex is a...
kind of a rich man's C-four.
Same stuff they used to blow
up that jet in Lockerbie,
same stuff they used in...
the embassy in Nairobi,
Dar Es Salaam.
I think you get the picture, y'all.
Yeah.
That right there is usually harmless
and easy to manage by itself.
But you combine that
with a detonator...
Yeah, so anyway uh...
if this is her idea of fancy jewelry,
you can bet she's into
some nasty shit, brother.
Thanks.
All right let's go fishin'.
Okay now Pooch,
ease off
the top just real slowly.
Easin' and pleasin', boss.
Getting' that warm, tingly feelin'.
Slowly.
Slow.
TJ, get on in there
and just tell me what you see.
- Jump in there TJ.
- Shit.
Shit.
Oh come on wimpy, grab it.
Keep talkin' to me.
Come on Teej. One size fits all.
Looks like we got ourselves
a hot little number here.
What the hell is that?
All right.
Yeah, I told ya
there wasn't nothin' there.
A hula girl?
It kinda looks like Barbie
with a little ass on it, don't it?
This is whacked.
We came here to do a money job,
not to risk our lives saving the girl.
Gentle, my good man.
She's been an accident
waiting to happen,
- ever since you hooked up with her.
- And if it was you in there Vershbow,
I wonder if you'd be havin'
the same feelings.
Oh yeah, like you'd put it
on the line for me.
To keep you in good health
and quiet, I'd do the same for you.
You mix, I paint.
You've been a good student, Dugger.
Maybe next time I'll
let ya sign the canvas.
Here, Captain.
Did we get a hit on the girl's prints?
Not yet, and you know what?
That's none of your concern.
Captain, line 1. He says it's important,
says it's something about the girl.
Winters here.
- Go get Glass on a conference call.
- Yes sir.
What?
I said if you don't release her...
you'll have a lot of dead people
with missing body parts
on your conscience.
It's four o'clock now.
And if she doesn't walk by five...
let's just say uh...
you'll have a very bloody happy hour.
We need more time.
Your time's up.
Phone company said it was scrambled.
- What the hell did he mean by that?
- A bomb.
A bomb?
Her bracelet is made out
of detonation cord.
They're pros.
They're a bunch of chumps,
playing a bluff card.
Bomb squad found traces
of Semtex on the bracelet.
Semtex?
Nasty stuff.
Ring down to the bomb squad.
I want 'em on alert.
- Right.
- I'll do it.
We're a team here, Nettles.
You stay on the bench.
- Why?
- Just do it!
Jackass.
Man I love the Internet.
You should see the recipes
for death and disaster...
- on this thing.
- Hey Joey, it's Daddy.
Fourteen different ways to
blow up, kill, maim.
With whichever kind of
bomb you would like.
- Thank you America.
- Did you help Mommy like I told you to?
For the Freedom of Information Act.
Buy me dinner or I'll bring you up
on harassment charges.
Baldie.
Hey that's the guy
I was tellin' you about.
Yeah we just got
a bomb threat upstairs.
My my partner was killed last night,
the dirtbag who did it is the bomber.
Now what do we do?
Well we are not gonna do anything.
You are gonna get together
with your detectives
and do some detective work
and see if you can find the bombers,
or the bomb, so we can do our job.
And let's just hope it is a crank'
cause maybe nothin' we can do.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means...
- we deactivate explosive devices.
- You're the bomb squad.
Right, isn't your job to
stop these things?
We need detectives up there...
so that we can do our job.
You're right.
Let's just sit on our hands
and wait for innocent people to die.
What the hell was I thinking?
What you should be thinking is,
get up there and do some...
detective work.
Bye.
Well, hello beautiful.
May I buy you a drink?
Sure.
What would you like?
Shot of Tequila.
A shot of Tequila?
Barkeep,
a shot of Tequila for the lady.
- And I'll have a Coca-cola.
- Yes sir.
I'm workin'.
I'm workin' you.
Nettles, I've got that info for you.
A bar called Happy Hour in the
Warehouse District at Beach Street.
Yeah, I know that dive, thanks.
What's your position?
I'm in Chinatown.
I should be there in two minutes.
So,
- told you a little about myself.
- You did?
Yeah.
It's your turn.
What would you like to know?
Well I'd like to know how to get
to know you a little better.
To get to know me.
I'll tell you this.
The whole world's gonna know
who I am, baby.
It's music to my heart.
You da bomb, baby.
What?
Ding-dong, the bitch is dead,
the bitch is dead.
Ciao.
Police. Get down, get down!
Pooch, give me something.
Not much to go on.
Whoever this guy was knew
what he was doing, that's for sure.
Let me sample this.
Watch your back.
Watch your step, sir.
Please,
my husband and daughter
are in that building.
- M'am, no, no.
- Please.
I'm sorry, we can't let
you through here.
They're my whole life!
Please m'am.
Please.
You know, every time you show your
face, there's some fuckin' disaster.
Why is that?
At least I was trying
to do something.
Oh yeah?
You know, I keep tellin' you,
you don't belong here.
Why you still here?
You touch me again,
Pluchinsky, and uh...
Wh- and what?
You gonna shoot me?
No I'm not your fuckin'
partner, all right?
I will make retirement.
Falta subtitulo.
What-what, motherfucker!
Let go of me.
You son of a bitch,
don't you touch me fuckin' again.
- Fuck you.
- Get outta here.
Get outta here before I kick your ass.
Oh Artie, Artie, listen to me,
listen to me.
I've been talkin' to Nettles
a little bit, you know.
I kinda feel like he's got
some intel that's...
real vital to our group.
You don't mind if I sneak him
on in with us, do you?
He's all yours.
Thank you man, I appreciate that.
Right guys,
we appreciate it, don't we?
Oh I love it.
Why the save?
I'm tryin' to save you
from yourself, man.
What's that supposed to mean?
You gotta get beyond hope and fear.
Learn the nature of your own mind.
And then,
you won't be suffering anymore.
You comin'?
Traces of Semtex just like the braid
on that det cord bracelet.
Check out the sequencing.
I've never seen anything
so beautifully choreographed.
Yeah the detonator's made
out of Semtex, that's for sure.
So what kind of bomb was it?
Did you say the B word?
Excuse me?
Nettles you gotta be more Zen.
- Device.
- Don't use the B word.
Device.
B is for boom.
So you're the Device Squad
and you defuse...
devices.
We treat devices.
Anything else I should know?
Yeah.
Watch where you step.
Check it out boss, we got action.
Stay close to us.
What ya think?
Computer chip.
That could be from an IRD.
Very, very nasty piece of shit.
Let's hope that's not what this is.
Hey remember, I'm watchin' your ass.
You know Pluchinsky, pretty words
and a smile just aren't gonna
get me to kiss you.
Captain, we got a hit on the prints.
I was wondering why it took so long.
Turns out she had
high-security clearance.
- Department of Defense contractor.
- Claire Manning, twenty-nine,
San Francisco.
Married to a Brandon Manning,
- an architect, died last May.
- In memory of Brandon.
She was an Rand D Skunkworks
nuclear specialist.
Trained at Lawrence
Livermore and Langley.
- Resigned abruptly last year.
- Sir, it's him.
Yeah.
How will you tell them, Captain?
How will you explain to the families
that their loved ones
didn't have to die?
You got a name?
No, this time,
I'll give you two hours.
But if she isn't released by then...
another bomb will go off,
and then another and another until...
every man...
woman and child in this city...
is either dead...
- or in mourning.
- Talk to me, please.
Tick tock.
Tick...
tock.
Find him.
Hey Angie um,
I wanna check on
Brandon Manning's work history.
I want a list of every project
he's ever been involved with,
and uh, call the Feds,
see if they'll give us
any details on the girl
without a court order, ok?
Officer Gordon, hi.
She's tough, huh?
Tough?
Tough is, where's my lawyer.
Well the Captain wants me
to take a crack at her.
Fine.
- You baby-sit her for awhile.
- Okay.
You remember me?
Yeah, I remember you.
Sorry about the eye.
You didn't give me much choice.
First my partner,
then all the others.
What makes you so valuable that uh,
they'd slaughter all these innocent
people just to get you back?
Look, I know you don't wanna talk.
Somebody once told me
that that's the only way you can uh,
you know, get better, feel better.
You see uh...
you see not too long ago um,
not long ago I...
I lost two people
I loved very much...
too.
Your husband uh,
was a gifted architect...
Brandon Manning.
Famous, was about to expose
a massive cover-up,
they were gonna build
a elementary school on a toxic
waste site downtown.
But before he could blow the
whistle he dies in a car accident.
It was not an accident.
That's what the grand jury
said it was.
He was murdered in cold blood
because of his integrity.
And nobody gave a damn.
So that's why you're
with these terrorists?
That's why you're
First my partner, then the bar.
Now, who is he?
Tell me his name.
Why is he killing all these
innocent people for you?
Why's he want you back
so bad he killed all these people?
Now tell me his name.
Who is he?
Tell me.
God dammit, tell me his name!
What's his name!
What is his goddamn name!
Hey listen the police aren't gonna
let you go and l- you- you know that.
When your boyfriend realizes this,
a whole bunch of innocent people
are gonna die, kids and families,
for no good reason.
Now there's blood on your hands.
Okay?
Now...
help me put an end to this.
You're the only one who can.
We met at a convention in Europe.
I was lonely, as you might imagine.
He was...
brilliant,
charming,
a fellow scientist, so he claimed.
By the time I learned the truth,
I was too scared.
Too scared for what?
Oh come on.
Tell me.
I can't.
- Bullshit.
- You don't understand. I can't.
If you want it stopped,
you have to let me go.
Let you go?
You gotta get me out of here.
You gotta get me outta here, okay?
Take your hands off me.
Don't touch me, don't touch me.
Drop dead.
Hey Nettles.
How'd it go with the girl?
Not good.
Hey Nettles...
what do you think
it would take to kind of
give me all this from the beginning?
So what made you think
they were here?
Hey, you're the expert.
Looks like a really good
place to hide explisives.
Discreet,
quiet, out of the way.
We might even find an IRD here.
You mentioned you saw
one of them once.
- Where?
- Across the pond.
I was uh, headin' a team, E-O-D.
Some shit went sideways.
Lost some of my boys.
But uh, I made a choice to live.
So I light candles
for my boys that didn't.
So you live it too.
If you call it livin'.
You know I never cried when...
I don't know.
Maybe it's the guilt.
After the funeral
I never went back...
you know,
to where they're buried.
Yeah.
I'm afraid if I do,
I'll blow my brains out.
It's just- it's just way too much.
Well you know one thing
about hittin' the bottom.
After that,
there's only one way you can go.
And that's up.
Yeah.
That's enough talkin' for now.
Time's up on our first session.
It's right over here.
Yeah, um...
girl was here with me.
Guy in charge over there
with one of his men.
Another guy was over there.
So...
these bombers,
what's the typical profile?
If you were a dog trainer
you'd call 'em fear biters.
They wanna bite before they get bit.
People who uh,
feel like...
they'll blow something up
to kill somebody or make a statement,
but always from a long way away.
Long distance.
Never wanna get up-close and personal.
Not that kind of people.
Except if you don't play along,
these guys will blow you up.
Most of 'em.
You know uh, it's a power trip.
But uh,
some of 'em don't follow through.
- And the other one percent?
- Those are the dangerous ones.
Criminal minds that are geniuses,
smarter than most law enforcement,
most anti-terrorists, most military,
they've got access to the most
sophisticated,
deadly devices in the world.
Those are the ones
we gotta worry about.
That's why we're here.
Hm, what do we got here?
Galois.
Eurotrash.
Jazz Cat. Do you like the blues?
Scotch on the rocks, please.
Couple drinks?
No thanks. Hey...
you know anybody who smokes
these French cigarettes?
Galois cigarettes, Inspector.
There's a guy in the club
who smokes these Frenchies.
Is he here tonight?
Yeah. He's right over there.
Thanks, are you new here?
Let's go talk to him.
What d'ya say?
Police!
Show me your hands!
Show me your hands.
- Show me your hands!
- I didn't do nothin'.
Show me your hands!
- Put the gun down, brother.
- Show me!
Don't move, don't move.
Let the girl go.
Come on, let's go.
I'll shoot you.
- Let her go.
- No I won't!
- Let the girl go.
- Let me go, please.
Do you think I'm crazy?
- Let the girl go.
- Fuck you!
I'll shoot you.
- Go right ahead.
- Shoot.
- San Francisco is gonna blow.
- Let her go!
Go 'head.
You know I could've used him alive.
Gotta learn to listen to me.
But that was good shootin'.
That was a good shot.
So uh, should I get ready to die?
No, you know what?
This is not very sophisticated at all.
See?
I'm glad you were here.
That's your new lucky number.
You've heard of the twelve stages
of enlightenment, haven't you?
No, just one day at a time,
twelve steps.
Oh yeah.
Well we haven't made
it through this day yet, have we?
We're doin' good, so far.
The bomb didn't go off
but Duggers died.
Oh, you disappoint me.
It's time to bring in the boys.
Are they ready?
Yes sir, ready and waitin'
for your signal.
It's never stopped before.
Well, let me see it.
Okay.
Yeah, main spring's stuck.
All right...
let me show ya a little somethin'.
I'm gonna teach you
the way I learned.
I'm gonna hand this back to you
and give you the only tool you need
to fix this. It's real simple.
Well, I'm an idiot when it comes
to mechanical things.
You're not an idiot, man.
Just never tried it before.
Take a look in there, you'll see right
away how to do this. It's very simple.
Thing of it is, if I baby you,
tell you how to do it...
in one ear and out the other.
If I make you figure it out
you're gonna own it.
Go for it.
It's workin' again.
Good job, man.
Youjust made your first ticker.
We need to talk, Nettles.
Shit.
I got a call from upstairs.
They say you questioned the girl
yesterday. Is that true?
Yeah, that's true.
Claiming that I'd given you permission
in direct contradiction to my orders.
Yes sir.
Under any other circumstances
I'd have your ass canned.
That said...
she wants to talk to you again.
Alone.
His name is Alex Swan.
The one with the tattoos
and piercings goes by Dugger,
and the other one
calls himself Vershbow.
Dugger's dead.
So's the bomb he was carrying.
Now, Swan's planning
a big hit now, isn't he?
I don't know.
Oh come on, tell me the target.
Tell me the true target.
This bombing was
a distraction, wasn't it?
Wasn't it?
Look, you said you wanted
to talk to me, now talk.
Claire?
Alex Swan is planning
a really big hit, isn't he?
I don't know.
Come on.
Tell me the target.
Tell me how to find him.
Claire, come on, please.
Tell me how to find him
before it's too late.
All right, the last I knew,
they were...
staying at a motel downtown,
somewhere around the corner
from the warehouse.
What was the name of it?
The Sunburst uh,
room one thirty-eight.
Sunburst, room one thirty-eight.
Yeah.
Thanks.
He'll kill me for this.
Even if you catch him,
he'll send someone else.
It doesn't matter anymore anyway.
I've lost too much already.
You know what?
There's always hope.
You just took a small step
back towards life,
and ain't nobody gonna kill you.
Cover all the entrances.
Stay alert.
Always, baby.
Move.
City, he can't even
save his own family.
What did you say?
You didn't hear me?
- Come here, say it again.
- Oh sure.
I said, how can you save the city if
you can't save your own fucking family.
That's what I thought you said.
Just coming up to an open door.
After you, my good man.
, get on in there
and just tell me what you see.
They're gone.
All right.
Clear the building, bring the dog.
We'll check the other rooms.
Copy that.
Sparky's on his way.
You're the one, Thursday...
three-sixteen in the AM.
Thirty-seven cents.
You were the short change.
A little light.
Where's your partner, officer?
He's dead.
Now the guys who killed him, we
think they live in this neighborhood.
You wouldn't know anything
about any bad people around here...
- would ya?
- One has a beard.
The other is tall...
thin. Thin one wanted to offer me...
a donation, wanted to trade
for something I haven't used
for a long time.
What kind of car did they drive?
- Did they drive a car?
Originaly,
plate M-L-A-l-5-8 Ford van.
But they switched late
Thursday night to a blue Taurus
with G-O-E-N-43 plates.
G-O-E-N-43?
That's what I said.
A steel trap.
Okay.
That's my life savings.
G-O-E...
N-43.
Steel trap.
Sir Lancelot is a good knight.
He could save the,
no-no, he could save the kingdom.
Afternoon gentlemen.
Sure this is crazy,
you're gonna get us busted.
It has to be done.
They've tested my patience
and my resolve long enough.
Now if you're afraid, then go.
I'll be in the car.
Fine.
Excuse me officer.
Lawrence Bombeck, esquire.
I represent Claire Manning.
She wants her property
released to me,
her credit cards actually,
to secure my retainer.
Wait here.
I'll have to make a phone call.
Angie, I have a man here claiming
to be Claire Manning's lawyer.
Everything's fine.
Captain...
there's a man downstairs,
says he's Claire's lawyer.
Put him on.
Hello.
Sir?
Sure enough, the uh, plates belong
to a car rented Thursday night...
downtown.
Guy's name's Alex Swan.
A-K-A, twenty other names.
Guy's a legend
in the bomb-for-hire business.
He's the cat who blew
the senator's mansion.
The other one, Vershbow,
he's a freelance demolition expert.
Just so happens he's worked for half the
governments in the Western hemisphere.
Including ours
during the Reagan Administration.
Let's get out an APB y'all.
Right away.
This wasn't the deal.
You want her property that bad,
you wanna be close to your girl,
well you couldn't get
any closer than this.
I'm not gonna end up like Dugger.
Now get the hell out of here.
Game over.
I offered you a chance
to be part of history,
and fame and fortune, you fool.
Give me the briefcase.
You're forgettin' some'in'.
Detonator.
You're makin'
a great mistake, Vershbow.
Now beat it,
Michael-fuckin'-angelo.
Nettles, suspect spotted in area.
Repeat, suspect may be
in police parking lot, over.
I need backup.
- Let's go we got a perp!
- Stay down!
Drop the weapon
and get outta the car.
Put the bag down!
Move your fuckin' car, chief.
Move that fucking car...
or I'll blow it out of the way.
Wait on command.
Come on buddy,
time to go to work
Let's go check out the tire.
Get your sniffer up there.
Come on, come on.
What you got.
Nothing?
Come on, you're not gonna
get your raise like this.
Let's go around back.
- Come on, come on.
- Engine clear.
Sniff.
What you smelling?
Nuggets.
- You smellin' nuggets.
- All right babe, once...
I sweep this truck
it's cocktail time, baby.
Pooch hurry that mutt up.
You're buying.
Come on. What'd ya smell?
What'd ya smell?
You're smellin'TJ?
Head and tail are clear.
Reach out,
reach out
and touch someone.
Oh no.
Pooch!
Thank you and call again.
You got a minute?
I just wanted to...
ljust wanna say thank you.
It's no big deal.
That's uh...
that's Pooch's wife and kid.
I'll talk to 'em.
It's him.
Gotta get back to you.
Quiet.
Winters here.
You people
just don't learn, do you?
We're ready to talk.
Oh you mean stall, don't you,
so your little team...
team of techno-geeks
can try and trace me?
This is my final warning.
The city has one hour to release
the girl exactly where you found her.
Fifteen seconds.
One hour, you understand?
The girl in exchange for...
let's just say,
there're not enough cemeteries...
in the city or enough hospital
beds for the maimed.
Well wait a second.
You know we can't just let her go.
How do we know we can trust you?
You can trust me.
One hour.
What?
No.
I want ya
to drop it off at the museum.
Captain,
it's a radio station downtown.
They just received a bomb threat.
Sir, we're getting bomb threats
from all over the city.
Sir, your wife received one too.
What do you wanna do?
Send a squad car.
Okay.
Also notify the bomb squad, hospitals,
fire department.
Right away, sir.
Hey boss.
She says that uh,
she'll only talk to Nettles.
Okay, do it.
All right.
We're meeting with your boyfriend.
You have to convince them
to let me go.
It's your only chance to stop him.
Look, use me as the bait.
There's not a lot of time.
Hey, I've been looking for you.
Here's a list of buildings
Brandon Manning designed.
This guy's done
some pretty major stuff?
He even designed
the new wing at City Hall.
I can't see.
Thank you.
Shit!
Vincent.
Vincent, do tou hear me?
Swan, we're settin' up
the fuel-air explosives.
Set it up and tell me
when you're ready.
All right, hurry up,
come on, move out.
Captain Winters.
You gotta get the okay
to let the girl go.
Let her go?
I mean, we gotta use her.
She's our only chance.
I'm not bullshitting you, Captain.
I wouldn't bullshit you about this.
If you let that girl go,
I'll catch this creep.
Is the tracking device on the girl?
The ankle transmitter is in place.
The tracking transmitter is working.
We're good to go with the drop-off.
Okay, I got her.
I got her, she's right here.
There you go.
You're lucky we still have that.
Some guy says he was your lawyer,
tried to take your property.
All right, go on, get outta here.
Go on, get out of here.
I'm goin' northbound on Sixth.
Moving northbound.
Repeat, northbound.
Position One she's not
headed your way.
She's headed northbound on Sixth.
She's headed northbound on
the Sixth Street alleyway.
She's headin' towards the flea market.
Captain she's moving fast.
Stop right there!
Swan, the device is armed and
standing by for your word to activate.
Activate.
Activate stage one.
She's in a black BMW.
L-Q-Y-A-1-niner,
westbound on Vermont.
Don't I even get a thank you?
Bye boys.
We've lost her.
The transmitter has
been found abandoned.
Repeat, we've lost her.
What were you thinking,
trying to take the watch?
What, you gonna ditch me?
Now you yourself said
that the painting is far more
important than the artist.
And what about our masterpiece?
Nothing can be allowed
to interfere with the
creative process that we share.
You're right.
A masterpiece that'll be
discussed, admired,
and studied for centuries to come.
Our Michelangelo.
Is everything in place?
Of course.
Pull over.
It's time to trigger the decoy.
Our masterpiece.
Yes.
I did this all for you, you know?
I love ya.
I know.
Reverse the charges, my love.
Please reach out and touch someone.
Oh dear.
Swan's car just went.
- What about Claire?
- Looks like it took 'em both out.
Hang on, there's something a
little strange about this.
...placed throughout the city...
- Glass.
Glass!
Only the male suspect is there.
Claire's gone.
...opening of the new wing,
designed by the late Brandon Manning...
will go off without a hitch.
This is Jamie Rosen
for Channel Six News
reporting live from the Masquerade
Ball at City Hall. Back to you, Don.
Jamie, we're heard that the traffic
down there is absolutely terrible
Hey are you there?
Come in man are you there?
Nettles, are you there?
- I know where she is.
- How do you know where she is?
She's gonna blow City Hall.
Meet me there.
Go around the City Hall,
make sure backup's in place.
All right, call for TJ.
I got my hands full.
See if he's close.
Nettles, where are you?
Tell me what you see.
Keep talkin' to me.
I'm movin' as fast as I can, man.
Hurry up, meet me in the lobby.
Okay men, get ready.
- Got the radio on?
- Yeah.
This is the San Francisco police.
Put your weapons down.
Divert them so
I can get to the elevator.
Hey brother, what took you so long?
Claire's husband was about to blow
the whistle on the downtown
redevelopment zone.
It's a toxic waste dump.
Would've cost a fortune to clean up.
But before he could,
he got capped.
So now Claire wants revenge.
It's been her all along.
She's gonna blow this place up, Glass.
All right listen, you take
the basement, I'll take the roof.
Okay.
Move away from the building.
Stay calm.
Step back away from the building.
Stay back.
Grenade! Go!
Go! Go!
Claire, put your hands in the air.
Now.
Don't make me do this.
I'm afraid it's time.
Put your hands in the air Claire.
Come on.
Put you hands in the air, now.
My husband never got his due.
That's all gonna change now.
Son of a bitch.
Glass.
Glass, I'm in the basement.
Claire's out cold.
There's a bomb, it's set to go off
in ten minutes.
What do I do?
Do you read me, Glass? Glass.
Okay Nettles.
Shit.
All right,
Glass, I got a ticker down here
and I don't know what to do.
Wejust got our first
North American FAE bomb.
That's a Fuel Air Explosive.
It'll take up to a square mile.
T minus ten minutes.
Now you better get down here
and help me, help me with this bomb.
Nettles,
I got a FAE bomb up here.
In case you're wondering what that is.
Black ops use these over in Africa, man.
It's a wide cloud of highly unstable
gas suspended over the city.
When it's ignited the shock...
waves will shoot down
and kill everybody breathing.
Now something tells me that you
got the detonator down there with you.
Glass, I'm gonna die down here.
Just relax, brother.
Talk to me.
Glass, talk to me.
Glass, just tell me what to do.
- I'll do it. Just tell me what to do.
- Stay calm. You can do this.
Glass, I don't know what to do.
Tell me what to do!
- Talk to me!
- Now listen to me man,
you're just gonna have to go
beyond hope and fear.
Don't be attached to living
or dying, or anything else.
And understand that death
is just another stage
on the playground.
You have to be able to feel it.
And the way...
you'll be able to learn how to feel,
is by coming to know
the nature of your mind.
And even if you do go today
you'll be back.
So if you're not attached
to living or dying,
you have nothing to fear. If you have
nothing to fear you're gonna calm down
and just listen to me gently
guide you through this.
All right?
Okay, I've finished assessing,
I have taken a deep breath.
- Now what do we do?
- Can you get inside that ticker?
- What do you mean?
- Look around the back...
for something that looks like
it's sealed,
it may even be sealed
with some kind of epoxy.
You wanna scrape that off...
and open it up.
Look around, there's a hole man.
There's a hole, look for the hole.
I see somethin'.
I got an opening.
There you go.
Okay reach in and tell me
what you feel. Gently.
Heat, a lot of heat.
Cold metal,
- somethin' soft.
- Don't touch that.
Okay.
What else?
Keep going man,
you're doing a good job.
Somethin' round...
and two wires.
Two sets of wires, yellow...
and black with red.
No, stop.
What's wrong?
It's too easy. There's gotta be
another way. That's a set-up, man.
There's gotta be another way.
Make up your mind.
Ease your thumb over to the right.
Feel anything?
Yeah, another round thing.
The device that you have there is
the decoy. It's very, very primitive.
You'll find two sets of wires.
Go to the timer
and try to pop
that switch straight out...
and pull the yellow wires
out of the timer.
Well which one's which?
All right, it's up to you.
Pick one.
What?
It's up to you Nettles, just pick one.
I did it. I'm not dead.
You did it brother. Now uh...
I got a whole shit storm up here
that I gotta deal with, so sit tight.
We're clear on the roof.
Repeat, clear on the roof.
- Send in the sweep team.
- Don't fire. Wait.
Class said it's over.
Go on man,
talk to them, they'll listen.
When everyone dies,
live the day.
There is tunnel.
And that's a long tunnel.