(static buzzing)
(gentle ringing)
[Voiceover]
Scientists and dreamers.
They travel the world
with watchful eyes
and guzzled hope like water.
The journey's were separate,
but their purpose was common.
To map the world.
One begged for
money and pencils.
Another tore his
shirt to strips,
carefully wrapping
his shredded feet.
Yet another thirsty,
near starving
suckled the sap from plants.
None had an easy road.
Though utterly dependent
on one another,
most found the others'
maps unsettling.
They denied one's perspective
by charting the land
incomprehensibly,
calling into question
one's very being.
Still when they met
on the lonely roads,
the explorers would present
one another with their maps.
Some seemed to say
so plainly, directly.
The world is like this.
Others were more
oblique, skating,
impressionistic, unstable.
They froze mere slivers
of the infinite earth
as it skittered by in orbit.
If ever these maps could
be gathered together,
they would comprise an
atlas of unsettling vision.
A final proof that truth
is conjecture.
(light music)
(murmuring)
(engine revving)
(grass shuffling)
(foreign music)
(gentle scat music)
(car honking)
(speaking in foreign language)
But in your minion.
Yes.
(speaking in foreign language)
To all travelers.
And to all over ground.
Oliver Ground.
Yes.
I drink to.
Truth.
I drink, you drink too.
Okay.
[Grey-haired man] Bravo.
Fuck off!
(speaking in foreign language)
(door knocking)
(car engine revving)
(joyless music)
(speaking in foreign language)
[Will] Eggs.
[Voiceover] Hmm.
(speaking in foreign language)
Okay.
Come on.
(speaking in foreign language)
I'm gonna show you.
I'm gonna point.
(speaking in foreign language)
Do you want anything else?
Coffee, tea, she'll
bring bread and cheese.
Yeah, coffee.
Coffee or tea?
(speaking in foreign language)
Coffee, she understands.
So, you're Armenian?
I grew up in Yerevan.
You know people are going
to think you're a spy
with all of your maps
and photos there.
That's what I am.
You're not discreet.
I make maps.
I work for a satellite
mapping company.
And you're American.
Yeah.
Northern California.
Great.
(exhales and clears throat)
Shit.
It's okay, I can get them.
You don't have to do that.
These are great.
Thanks.
(singing in foreign language)
(energetic foreign music)
You can drop me off just here.
Sure, where you stay?
With my brother.
But I have a new neighbor
who just stopped travelling
and taking pictures.
So you're the spy.
Takes one to know one.
(energetic music)
Thanks for the
ride, it was nice.
You sure you don't
want me to drop you off?
I could take you.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I wanna walk.
Yeah, yeah.
You know where you're going?
I do, it's my job.
Yeah, okay, thanks.
Travel safe.
(gentle music)
[Gadarine] Shit.
(gentle violin music)
Mr. Shepard.
It's great that you come.
We're so glad that you make.
Yeah, well, thanks.
And how goes work?
It's good, it's okay,
it's getting there.
Good, now I like
to make toast.
Our work leads to big project
with Armenia country.
(murmuring)
Come, come here.
Will Shepard, this
is Vigram Hacharam.
Hi.
Hey, hello.
I was just doing toast
to Mr. Shepard project.
Absolutely.
May we all profit
from your work here.
It sounds exciting.
I'll drink to the land.
Mr. Awitsyan, Mr. Shepard,
this is Valaria.
Hi.
[Man with red tie]
Mr. and Mrs. Harunisyan.
And was it Karina?
Gadarine (speaks
in foreign language).
Yes, Gadarine is apparently
quite an accomplished
photographer.
Will Shepard.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Shepard is working
for a company we contract
to make new survey
for Armenia he maps.
We will use for development,
security, many things.
Mr. Shepard also
goes to Nigaragarawa
so we're including it.
First time we do this since war.
Quite courageous.
Well, I'm not gonna
be getting that close
to the Eastern border,
but I hear it's beautiful
and I can't wait to see it.
We will send him
with guide, of course.
No, it's okay, no.
I work alone.
It's more efficient.
Yes, but it is
disputed territory.
At least the
Azerbaijani thinks so.
(laughing)
Excuse me.
What's the time (murmuring)?
(chuckling)
Small world.
Big world, small country.
(gentle music)
[Gadarine] It was
a good drive today.
[Will] It was.
Amenveres said you'll
be working in Karabakh.
I've been wanting
to shoot there.
[Will] It's pretty.
Yeah.
(gentle music)
[Voiceover] The life
captain travels the land
as points of light.
His voyages possess
the effortless speed
of planetary orbit.
He makes it possible
to strip into darkness
like slamming a door.
His maps are like snapshots,
taken in cruel flashes of light.
There's no room for ambiguity.
The world exists
in sharp planes.
Mountains cast no shadows.
Trees stand as still
as dead stones.
Sometimes he had with
him his daughter,
who looked only to the sides
and never straight ahead.
She missed the many
slashes of land
her father captured and froze.
At night around the fire,
she drew her own
maps like a tunnel.
Sky at the end.
Land down the sides.
To the captain, these were
mere simpleton drawings.
She may as well have
been screwing clouds
into jars.
[Will] Good morning.
Good morning.
One coffee.
(speaking in foreign language)
One, yeah.
How much?
Hey.
So rough.
Here we are.
[Gadarine] Yeah.
[Will] Are you on a timetable?
Not really.
I have a few places I
wanna try to look at
to shoot, but I
can work anywhere.
Well, I have an
itinerary I have to keep.
I have to stop a
lot, hike around,
take measurements,
it can be slow.
That's fine.
What are you doing exactly?
Huh?
Would you, would
you please leave that?
What I'm doing.
What I'm doing is
basically I'm trying
to pin these images
to the right places
on the ground,
over and over again.
[Gadarine] Wow.
That's good.
I mean that's the idea anyway.
Pin that one too.
(gentle music)
Am I right?
It's this way, Will.
Yeah we're,
we're further along
than I thought.
(gentle music)
The summer time
this was a big spot.
My parent's been here for years.
They moved after I went away.
You can turn here.
Turn here?
[Gadarine] Yeah.
Okay.
You know what, I think I
don't wanna do this anymore.
It doesn't feel
like the right time.
Oh come on.
Oh shit, stop, Will, stop!
What, what, what, what, what?
[Gadarine] My father.
(chuckling)
I'll drive us up.
No, no, no, okay.
No, I'll go alone.
I won't have to explain, okay.
Meet me here again in an hour.
Is that okay?
Say something.
A nice start.
(speaking in foreign language)
Gadarine.
(light guitar music)
(water flowing)
(murmuring)
This is gonna blow
your mind, this is us.
That river.
Okay, right there.
(murmuring)
Watch this.
One, two, ah!
Okay.
(speaking in foreign language)
[White-haired
man] San Francisco.
San Francisco,
this is where I live.
You know, my home,
you know, my city, my apartment.
[White-haired
man] All of them.
[Will] Yeah, I live
right there sometimes.
(speaking in foreign language)
Armenia.
(laughing)
Yeah.
(speaking in foreign language)
[Will] Hey, am I late?
No, no, no, I left early.
I saw the car.
Was it a good visit?
Okay, sit down, sit down.
Yeah, no, these
guys (murmuring).
Guys, this is my friend.
Vinnie Dansics.
Gadarine.
Could we get her a glass?
Are you Judas?
(chuckling)
(speaking in foreign language)
Yeah, yeah.
(laughing)
[Will] I'll drink with her.
(speaking in foreign language)
(gentle guitar music)
Ah, okay, pull
over here, there.
Come on.
(sighs)
(giggles) Come on.
Whoo!
(light playful music)
Do you feel the
gas in the water?
The bourbons.
I feel them on my balls.
(laughing)
(screaming excitedly)
(light playful music)
So this is how it
all started for me.
Little hidden places like this.
Yeah.
(giggling)
Leave it off the map.
If you do that, we're even.
(light playful music)
(keyboard clicking)
(foreign music)
(rooster crowing)
[Gadarine] Hope this is it.
Sophia.
Sophia!
(door knocking)
(door creaking)
(speaking in foreign language)
Can you get him
to get me a beer?
(chuckling)
[Sophia] Gadarine.
[Gadarine] Hey.
(speaking in foreign language)
(glasses clinking)
(laughing)
(speaking in foreign language)
[Will] Okay.
You have to eat.
I have to eat.
(scat singing)
Vodka.
Drink.
Watch out of this stuff, okay?
Homemade mulberry vodka.
And it's killed
stronger men than you.
It's a good day to die.
(chuckling) Will!
[Man in plaid] Will.
(speaking in foreign language)
Will.
To drink, bring
and you, Gadarine,
will (murmuring).
[Will] It's okay,
that's good, tell me.
You're good.
Will.
(speaking in foreign language)
(glasses clinking)
She wants me to
translate to you.
She says to us,
to seeing me to you
for being the one
who brought us together
for this visit.
There had to be more.
(laughing)
Yeah, but it's
hard to translate.
(Will murmuring)
Okay, let's see.
Made the new lines on our maps
bring good things to this world.
[Will] Okay.
Will.
(baby crying)
(speaking in foreign language)
Will.
Drink.
(glasses clinking)
We.
We should have come here sooner.
Sooner, we're very happy.
Happy.
[Will] To be here with you.
Friend.
(speaking in foreign language)
(glasses clinking)
(singing in foreign language)
Drink.
(chuckling)
My friend.
(wind blowing)
Hey, where's that old guy?
You gotta go get that old
guy to come and point again.
(chuckling)
Go get him.
Sophia has good two kids.
I saw them sleeping.
So cute.
I mean, she and I play
together every day.
Just girls, another life.
So they're,
what are they?
They're vineyards here.
Pomegranate-yards.
They're pomegranate-yards here.
No, I grew up on a
pomegranate-yard.
A vineyard, a place
where they make grapes.
Good grapes made wine.
You didn't tell me that.
I didn't tell you anything.
Hey, wait, the grape farm.
My dad didn't own
it or anything.
He was just like
the lead grape guy.
They're like your
dad is the hotel guy.
He's a farmer of grapes.
Or a manager of grapes.
There are other farmers
that he worked with.
I had a great time
there as a kid.
The land.
I loved that place.
Why didn't he
tell you to stay?
I used to just go.
I wanted to see how far I
could go before getting lost.
Real lost was the goal.
As a kid, I used
to walk for hours.
In later days.
I just start, you
know, pick a direction
in the morning before
it was light, just go.
And I used to worry them sick,
but they got used
to it, you know.
You get used to it.
I disappeared.
I wanted to find the
edge of the world.
(light beaming music)
[Voiceover] The
astronomer carries a veil
of pure darkness.
Dawn is a disorienting
agent he says.
The stars are
there all the time.
He embroiders maps
on massive blankets
threaded with spiderwebs
and cocoon casings.
Gemstones form planets.
Satin passels are meteors.
He builds a dome over the turf
to trap the darkness,
marking a circle of horizon.
Then lashing sticks
to form a frame.
Over this, he carefully drapes
his heavy black blankets,
painstakingly pierced with
April's constellations.
When it rains, the stars drip
into shining puddles
on the earth.
The needle grows slick
and dangerous in his hand.
(light music)
(giggling)
(playfully exclaiming)
(speaking in foreign language)
[Gadarine] Good morning.
Morning.
(child blabbering)
[Gadarine] Want to eat?
No.
(child screaming)
We'll just fix it,
will this make it better?
We'll just fix it just to
make everything better.
That doesn't help.
(chuckling)
[Gadarine] Are you
going to survive?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
(chuckling)
Have you ever been there?
Iran?
No, it's hard to get a visa.
It takes a long time.
I'd love to see that land.
One border at a time.
Let's get into Karabakh first.
(soldiers murmuring)
He wants the passport.
(speaking in foreign language)
Okay, I'll go get this, wait.
[Will] You want me
to get out of the car.
Will.
I need some money.
Now.
(Will retching)
(speaking in foreign language)
Will, come on.
Hey, hey!
Where's my maps?
(yelling in foreign language)
Let's go.
(Will murmuring)
Remember where you are, okay?
Get in the car and let's go.
(car engine revving)
(Will retching)
I warned you.
I'll be okay.
You should rest.
(gentle music)
(wheels squealing)
(water splashing)
(murmuring in foreign language)
Are you okay?
We're okay.
[Will] Oh, shit.
What?
What's that sound?
What happened?
[Gadarine] Sheep.
[Will] Damn it.
Okay, they helped
me to find a driver.
Some local guy.
I don't think he speaks
English so you will have
to show him where you
want to work on the map.
You're gonna be fine
with that anyway.
I could come maybe.
I'll be fine on my own.
Oh, this is probably your guy.
Will.
[Will] I'll be
back six or seven.
(foreign music)
[Voiceover] This
are stone crosses
where (murmuring).
(speaking in foreign language)
[Voiceover] And I will add
that they're very, very old.
(singing in foreign language)
(light techno music)
(speaking in foreign language)
There's a girl I was with.
Could I borrow your pen?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay.
Room 23.
I'm staying in room
23 with a girl.
Has she been here?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
(light guitar music)
(murmuring)
It's not Arizona,
it's California.
(murmuring)
(glasses clinking)
(gentle music)
Hey.
Hello.
Hey, hotel.
Hotel.
Sir, sir.
Excuse me, sir, sir.
Yeah.
Are you fucking deaf?
(door banging)
Hotel or hotel?
Hello.
(speaking in foreign language)
Okay, that's great, thanks.
Just take what I have.
Great bargaining technique.
Here.
Because on you.
Where were you?
You know I don't have
time for this shit.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Where the fuck were you?
Okay, well, after you left,
I took a ride with the
tour group from the hotel.
We ended up to this
amazing monastery.
I didn't know it was an
overnight trip, okay.
And anyways, it
was good, mostly.
And I did some good
pictures of there.
Okay.
What'd you want?
An apology?
I didn't knew I was
uncaring to you.
You blew me off
yesterday morning.
You just could of left
a message at the hotel.
I waited.
What the fuck are you?
My father?
My brother?
I mean, you couldn't handle
one little night on your own?
If I had known you
were gonna stand me up.
Did we had a date?
Did you have flowers?
Jesus Christ.
Mister I'm so independent,
just me and the land.
Did you miss your chaperone?
I don't want a chaperone.
Good, because I don't
wanna be one or have one.
I have waited hours for you
while you hiked all over
the place doing whatever
you want with your shit.
You never ask me permission
to keep me waiting.
Wrecking the car
kept me waiting.
And as far as the hiking
goes, that's my work.
I was working.
I work and I'm
sorry if it delayed
your little backpacking trip.
Work, work.
Making all your fabulous
measurement, huh.
Mapping this place so
that the politicians
and the mafia can
come and exploit it.
Nice work.
That's not why I'm here.
And when did you become such
a woman of the people anyway?
You don't even live here.
You know, you left.
None of this is
easy for me, okay.
Being here, traveling,
seeing family, old friends.
You don't have to
deal with any of that!
Yes, you take your
measurement, okay.
You record your
precious details.
But all you ever really
do is skim the surface.
Your whole life is just a
fucking big excuse to run away.
[Will] And yours isn't?
No!
Not anymore.
I mean there is a lot about
your being here, your work,
that you never had to deal
with, because I've had to.
And then you disappeared.
I didn't disappear.
I came back.
I'm sorry.
(Gadarine breathing heavily)
(car engine revving)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
What's up?
I have to go.
(lips smooching)
(light guitar music)
(door knocking)
(rapid guitar music)
[Will] That's it?
[Woman] Yeah, yes.
(keyboard clicking)
(breathing heavily)
(gentle music)
(kettle whistling)
(door knocking)
Good morning.
Are you Krikor?
(speaking in foreign language)
Take good care of him.
Is he gonna pull through?
He's okay now.
There's a doctor
coming for tests.
But I think he'll be
back till he's old.
(murmurs) If he can
keep away from vodka.
Can he?
Nice that you're here.
Come here.
[Gadarine] So,
you're flying away.
[Will] Maybe I shouldn't.
Tomorrow.
(light violin music)
Flying
via London.
Those words don't
even sound like words.
I'm being some place
else there.
I will be here.
Could find a
way to keep going.
I know.
But don't now.
Maybe you come back,
you'll get a contract.
Find me again.
(Will chuckles)
It's not looking likely.
You wanna come to San Francisco?
You have to go.
(lip smooches)
But (lip smooches).
I'm not saying goodbye.
(gentle violin music)
(light music)
[Voiceover] One famous month,
the explorers gathered together
to map the same
difficult terrain.
Though utterly dependent
on one another to survive,
they struggled with
the unusual proximity.
Each evening they
made their maps
while sitting on the
ground, backs to the fire,
elbows crooked
over their papers.
The flames shrunk in the
cruel lands they came to,
and the explorers used
to cold hands and faces
now worked with
cold backs as well.
As the journey
eked on, they took
to walking in an
outward facing circle,
taking turns moving forwards,
backwards, and sideways.
The supplies insupportably low.
The direction wheel whirled
into a small unnamed town
where it finally spun
out and scattered.
The small plot of land
in which they had arrived
was fenced off.
It remains blank on every globe.
Every atlas.
In every roaming heart.
(wind blowing gently)
* Put your sins until it's made
* And kick it to the county line
* Shake your change
* Cold moons
* Nothing's safe in your stars
* In and out of sleep
* Easier to rise and fall
* I pull the mattress
out the window
* Laid out under the smoke ring
* And from across
* Shake your song break
* Down
* Sad, sad complication
* In and out of sleep
* Even with the rise and fall
* Goes in like a worn out friend
* We've cut our hair
and fake our death *
(light guitar music)