#HUNT FOR THE UNICORN KILLER#
You sure you want to come back here again?
- Things are different now, Daddy.
I just wasn't sure what I was
doing up here the first time.
I still don't know what's wrong
with all the colleges in Texas.
Well, I don't know if
I like it here, Honey.
Don't worry, Daddy.
- Oh, Honey.
Don't say that doodlebug,
I'm your father.
That's my job: to worry.
You haven't called me
that in a long time.
Well, for a few years
there, I didn't think
you wanted to hear it,
so I was real careful.
I guess I didn't like a lot
of things there for a while.
But you don't have to be
so careful anymore, Daddy.
We're okay.
- Yeah.
Come on!
- I don't know.
So you were here before. - Yeah.
I left after freshman year.
Why?
- Just not sure what I wanted to do yet.
Did some traveling.
Tried college back home.
That was not a good idea.
You're born in Tyler, Texas, you
usually die in Tyler, Texas.
All my friends from high
school married each other.
Some of them have their
first baby already. Not me.
There's still too much I want to do.
How old are you?
Twenty-one.
- Cool!
Hey everybody! Holly can buy beer!
Where you goin'?
Dear Meg: Well, it's less
intimidating here the second time "
Megan, a few years
off was healthy, I suppose.
So was putting in all that time
and effort to lose my Texas twang.
I went to my first anti-war
march the other day. Don't tell Daddy!
Don't tell Daddy!" There's an exclamation
point after that, so don't tell.
Don't tell, Mary. - I won't
tell. - "Funny. I never felt
like I fit in back there in Texas, but "
I don't really feel like
I fit in here, either.
Who knows?
Now, remember: remember you guys can
use my room and stereo but only if you
turn it up really loud once in a while
so Daddy thinks I'm still at home.
What are you guys doin' up there?
Turn it down!
Love you all.
Holly.
Join us at the rally.
What's going on?
- Earth Day.
What's Earth Day?
Better when Khrushchev
does it, isn't it?
Too much with a sandal.
Greetings! I'm Ira Einhorn!
On behalf of the City of Philadelphia.
The City of...
Brotherly Love
I'd like to welcome you to
the very first Earth Day!
Earth Day is not about confrontation.
It's a celebration! Isn't it?
Vibrant! All right.
Excuse me.
All right.
This revolution I'm talking about
cannot happen without legislation.
So, it is for that reason that we're
going to allow a politician to speak.
All of us here should listen to him.
But if he lies if he
feeds us any sort of
self-serving political
crap, we will let him know!
Ladies and Gentlemen, Senator and former
Vice-Presidential nominee, Ed Muskie!
We're very excited about your book.
It's groundbreaking.
Part poetry, part philosophy.
Well, it speaks to this generation.
But we do need one more thing from you.
A title.
Ira?
- I don't believe in titles.
It immediately categorizes it.
I don't want the content compromised.
Well, doesn't the Library of
Congress decide on a number?
Sure.
- There's your title.
Let me get this straight:
You want to use a
Library of Congress number
as the title of your book?
Ira, where ya goin? Come on.
This is important.
So is this.
I was wondering how
long this would take him.
But he's already got a date with him.
Like that makes a difference with Ira.
I'm Ira.
Holly?
- Which is it?
Singing or dancing?
- Dancing.
How did you know?
- You're a Taurus.
You're all musical.
Brahms was a Taurus.
Hey, come on.
How did you know this?
It's a very complex psychic technique.
I've mastered the art
of reading upside down.
May I borrow your pen? I'm having lunch
with me editor over there.
Since he's paying, it'd be a little
rude to leave, so here's my number.
Call me sometime.
I'll do your chart for you.
Earth Day.
That's where I saw you last year.
You and the rest of the world.
Have you really read all those books?
Yup.
I read a book a day.
Excuse me.
Yeah, this is Ira.
- Hi.
This is Holly.
- Well, hi.
Hey can you hold on for a second?
I'd like you to have that book.
- Really?
I'd like you to go back to
your dorm, read it, and when
you're through, call me and
we'll discuss it. Okay? - Okay.
Bye-bye.
Hey.
I was hoping you'd call.
You're kind of a celebrity.
Celebrity helps my work.
- What is your work?
Enlightening the planet. - Well, I
thought maybe you were a housekeeper.
Your place is so much cleaner than mine.
Yeah, my mind doesn't
function well in chaos.
I need an orderly environment.
This is beautiful.
- It's me.
It's my underground name.
- Einhorn.
Ein: German for "one".
Horn: Self-explanatory.
One-horn.
Hence the Unicorn.
A mythical beast.
How appropriate.
You speak German?
- And Greek.
Spanish.
French.
I'm very impressed, Holly Maddux.
I figured if I learned a
lot of accents it would...
Help you get rid of your own?
Yeah.
When you were young, you'd sometimes
provoke family and friends, wouldn't ya?
Especially family.
Your skin is very sensitive.
Your innate sensuality frightens you.
You wish to be the object of love.
Isn't that a real generalization?
I mean, doesn't everyone?
- Yeah, but
we require unrestrained
Always unrequited
Unconditional love.
This is a real leap of faith
you're making here, Holly.
I mean, how long have
you known this guy?
Long enough.
You're right, Sheila.
A leap of faith.
That's exactly what it is.
Well you graduate in a month
and then you have to move out.
Why rush it?
- It just feels right.
That's all.
- And what do I say if your Dad calls?
Tell him I'm not there and
then call me right away.
You can talk all you want
about car-polluting the planet,
but when you want to move,
they sure come in handy.
I'll grant you that.
They do serve a purpose.
I don't know how the two of you are
going to fit into that apartment.
I made a few changes.
I gave 'em all away.
- Well.
We'll start over again.
One book at a time.
I've never seen Ira so happy.
What's the matter?
It took him years to build up
that collection of books and then
he just gives them all away.
Doesn't that seem a bit obsessive?
Well, maybe he's in love.
Holly could finally be the one.
Ira? One woman?
She'd have to be pretty amazing.
At least this one has a brain.
Yeah, that's what scares me.
Well, you never know.
Maybe it'll work. - Bye-bye!
Such an optimist.
So is this new place nice?
- Yeah. It's great.
Safe neighborhood?
- Yes, Daddy. It's very safe.
Tell Buffy I'm making her
a special card for her birthday.
I'll do that, doodlebug.
I'll do that.
If you need anything, you call me.
- I will.
Bye, Daddy. Love to you all.
- Bye, honey.
So you didn't mention me.
- Not yet.
What?
He wouldn't approve?
No, they're a bit conservative.
Ira.
That's my journal.
Yes.
And some of its very good.
Please.
Don't ever do that.
I'm sorry.
- I mean it.
It's private.
- I'm sorry.
It's just you're the first woman
I've ever really wanted to know.
It's something I've never
felt before and I just
want to know everything
about you, that's all.
Please forgive me.
I'll never even peek into
your journals ever again.
All right?
Yeah? You like that one?
It creeped me out a bit.
Really? - Yeah, a little bit, I...
- Hello, Ira.
Evenin', George.
- I need your help.
These longhairs think they're tearin' down
my city, they got another thought comin'.
I'll make a look like a...
I don't either.
- They listen to you, talk to them.
Get them to keep it peaceful
and I'll keep´ the law from
turning this into a bloodbath, all right?
- Okay. I'll try.
Would somebody take Holly home?
- No.
Honey, it's going to be dangerous.
- No, I want to stay.
Come on.
Okay, okay here.
This is not what it's about!
Please, please, be quiet! Please.
This is not what it's about people.
This is not revolution.
This is not peace.
You're burning buildings
Mindless destruction, the
blood of other human beings.
This is what we're fighting against!
Let's follow the principles of Gandhi
and Martin Luther King, not those of
Richard Nixon and Mayor Rizzo! Okay.
Wake up.
I want everybody to sit down.
C'mon, everybody sit down.
Okay, let's join hands.
Everybody join hands here.
Everybody joining hands over there?
We're all settled?
Now I want us to sit here
and peacefully
protest the atrocities in Vietnam.
"Amazing Grace,
how sweet the sound"
You can come in anytime you want.
"That saved a wretch
like me.
I once was lost
but now I'm found...
What's goin' on here?
Nothin', Mayor.
Nothin' at all.
Follow the bouncing ball,
I want this stinking
hippie out of my city.
I've been looking into some
pretty wild stuff lately.
Currently, I'm investigating
of paranormal powers
which will afford us huge insights
into the cellular consciousness.
Put it into English, Ira.
- Psychic Phenomena, Harry.
The power of the minds.
Channeled correctly, the mind can
emit enough energy to bend this spoon.
You got any proof of this?
That's the trouble with
journalists they always need proof.
I will have proof, Trevor, soon.
- Well, here it is.
It's totally organic, even the flour.
And I hope it's okay because
I've never done this before.
Hello?
Ira Einhorn? We have a search
warrant for this apartment.
So who sold you the pills?
Well. A pharmacy. You know
you guys are really on the ball.
You're arresting me for possessing a
legal drug prescribed for a kidney ailment.
Start telling the truth.
You got a problem, officer?
He's under arrest, lieutenant.
- I just heard about this, Ira.
Call the lab, George.
Call my doctor. It's legal.
All the charges were dropped.
In a nutshell, Ira Einhorn was arrested
for only one reason:
because he's Ira Einhorn.
Right.
All right.
First of all I'd like to
thank the City of Philadelphia
for the lovely accommodations.
Secondly, I'd like to
take this opportunity to
announce my candidacy for
mayor of this great city.
My experience has
been and I pinch myself
now as the Department of
Energy as an Ensyme.
They send me their weekly bulletins
and it comes out: "Ira Einhorn Enzyme."
...part of an international
conspiracy to make the planet livable.
Now, if I may, with my remaining time
What is he doing?
If you had cut your hair, you
would have gotten more votes.
Get rid of that beard
and you'd be mayor today.
Hello, holly. - Hello, Mrs. Einhorn.
- I've told you before, it's Bea.
Call me Bea, here. I'll take the laundry.
You go get something to eat.
I just can't picture you as a jock.
Ira worked very hard for that.
He was so skinny as a boy.
He made us buy all
these weight-gain drinks.
Look, let's just change
the subject, shall we?
He's the most fascinating
man I've ever met.
There's nobody like
him back there in Tyler.
Everybody that comes to
Philadelphia stops by for a visit.
Allan Ginsburg, the poet.
Abby Hoffman.
Jerry Rubin.
We write together.
We read constantly.
Subjects I've never even thought about.
And probably never
would have without him.
He teaches at a thing
called the Free University
and his classes always in enrollment.
Politics. God. The War.
Sex.
Ira makes us think about all of them.
I feel like I'm back in school again.
I'm sorry about not making the family
camping trip, it's just too busy this year.
Love to you all, Holly.
In the 1980's, everybody's
going to have one of these.
Every home will have a computer.
These computers
will link together in a network
Thank you.
Who's the guy in the two thousand
dollar suit? - That's Arthur Whitler.
He's the CEO of the Mid-Atlantic
Communications Company.
Whitler.
I thought I saw you out there.
Hi. I'm Ira. - Yes.
Of course you are.
The problem is: how do you
get the information out there?
A network.
We phone them.
I have access to some of the
brightest people on the planet.
They send him articles, essays.
Really enlightening and important ideas.
So Ira has that and
you have a mailing list.
Stamps, envelopes, an office
full of Xerox machines.
What I was saying is:
it'd be a network, Arthur.
A network of ideas.
All this is it's
very interesting, Ira.
Careful with that.
Well, honey.
You be careful up there in Philadelphia.
- Don't worry.
All my girls always
tell me not to worry.
You be sure to tell Holly
she's welcome home anytime.
You tell her that?
And you?
You be careful with this package.
Oh, you too.
What do ya think?
So, I got an extra mat for you.
Hope you don't mind
sleeping on the floor.
No.
- Holly?
Where the hell you been?
I needed you here.
I the files we're copying today
I was picking up Meg.
She's gonna stay with us for a few days.
Hi.
I'm Ira.
You don't look like sisters.
Well, I look like Daddy.
Welcome to our home, Sister Meg.
She's asleep. - I don't care.
- Come on.
Ira, please don't.
Touch me then.
No.
Look, I'm sorry.
But I feel funny with
her in the same room.
I understand.
Where are you going?
- Out.
Come on.
It's all right.
Just be very quiet, okay?
So, Daddy's getting' downright liberal.
He let Mary go out on a date last week.
He never let me do that at her age.
Yeah, well. You were always the
groundbreaker, but
But what? He still isn't liberal enough
to like my living arrangements,
is that what you're trying to say?
- Well, you know Daddy.
Yeah, I know Daddy.
Look, Meg.
I don't want to put you in an
awkward position or anything.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't say anything about it.
Thanks.
Now this.
This would look great on you.
I'm not wearing used clothes.
Oh my God.
Now you're starting to sound like Daddy.
Holly?
Oh my God, are you okay?
I think I'm pregnant.
What are ya gonna do?
Ya gonna get married?
You don't have to get
married anymore, Meg.
You do back in Tyler.
- Well, things are different here.
Things are just different.
You can't say anything about this.
- I won't.
Promise: not to anybody.
Especially Ira.
Why not?
- Because you can't.
I'll tell him when the time is right.
I will tell him.
Okay.
You know. - You think he was a vegetarian?
- He was devoutly Jewish
What about the fishes.
The fishes.
You see, that's what's happening today.
We're all struggling for some story.
Because you know, we're basically
trying to find it in myth.
A new story for us to that's
a really pretty sweater.
The joy of celebrity.
Ira?
Hey, take Holly home for me, will ya?
Ira, you can't do that to her.
She'll understand.
Don't worry about it.
See and that's what's happening
today, we're all struggling for
some story and that's the meaning
for what hat whole story is, man.
The reason why there's so
many wars in the world
So how was she?
Vacuous.
Come on in.
Why do you do this to me?
I never lied to you, Holly.
You know I have the need
for another woman sometimes.
It's not something I'm proud
of, it's just the way I am.
And you've known this from the
very beginning, haven't you?
Haven't you?
- Yes.
Please, Holly.
I mean I love you but
I cannot be tied down.
I've been honest about this
from the day you moved in.
I'm pregnant.
Come here.
Sweetheart.
I'm so sorry.
I'll arrange everything.
Arrange what? - We can't have a baby.
- I don't want to have an abortion.
We're not ready for a baby, Holly.
But I love you.
I want us to start a family.
Holly, look.
Look at me.
We're not bringing a baby
into a world that's unlivable.
My work is trying to corrects
one of that but I can not
and will not have a child
until that work is finished.
All right?
We have to do this, Holly.
We have to.
Okay, Holly.
Put this gown on.
Will you please?
I'll be right with you.
Ira? You know the drill.
You've got an hour.
Dear Meg: Just a quick note to let
you know I took care of that problem.
I'm fine, so don't worry.
Well, what's your
sister got to say, Meg?
Oh, nothin' much.
What, Daddy?
- Somethin' wrong with your sister?
No.
You just sit there,
read Holly's letters,
laugh your head off and
read all the good parts.
But ever since you got back from
that place what is it, Meg?
It's a lot of things.
She doesn't look good and they
live in a ghetto, I swear
They?
She's livin' with this fellow isn't she?
Yeah.
Swore you to secrecy, right?
Well, Mom and I weren't born yesterday.
We figured it was something like this.
Can't say we approve.
Well, don't worry.
Your secret's safe with me.
I can buy this material in bulk.
I can do all sorts of things.
I can make dresses,
tablecloths, anything.
There's a real market for
this kind of stuff. - I know.
I just need a little start-up money.
Hello.
Hey, Daddy.
I have no desire to go to Texas. - I haven't
seen 'em in so long and they were hurt
when I missed the family camping trip.
- I'm not stopping ya, Holly.
If you feel you have to do this, do it.
- They want to meet you.
I want you to meet them.
Look, this means a lot to me.
I don't ask you for much, do I?
Please?
Lord, I want to thank you for
the food we're about to eat
and for sendin' Holly
here to share it with us.
Amen.
Ira.
I don't know, but you cut my hair.
Hey, Holly?
Holly?
Ira, you've got to see this oh look
I need you to brush my hair.
Look-it, that's me.
Holly?
I want you to brush my hair.
Okay.
Holly.
Did you read my book, Frank?
Yep.
So what d'ya think?
Well, Ira, I'm not
really much on poetry.
Robert Frost is about as far as I go,
but I thought I should read it.
I can see we have different tastes.
I don't think I've ever seen quite
a collection of books on Hitler.
World War Two had quite
an influence on me.
Most things do
when you're a teenager.
Saw an awful lot of evil, ugly things.
I guess I'm still trying
to figure some of it out.
You do realize
how offensive that is, I hope.
That flag. Yeah, well we
found that in a post office
in a little French village we liberated.
They found it pretty offensive, too.
Of course, as a Jew,
I find it particularly.
Well, we had to defeat the
biggest anti-Semite of all time
and I'm proud to say, I
was a small part of it.
That flag reminds me of it every day.
It's just a souvenir.
That's all.
You wanna make more
of it, go right ahead.
This is a big charade, you know?
Forcing us into separate bedrooms.
I'm old-fashioned.
Holly and I live together, you know?
We sleep together.
Ira, I have to fill
you in on a couple of things.
Just because we talk a little slow
down here, does not mean we are stupid.
I think you're the most ill-mannered
man I have ever met in my life.
And I know you're an intelligent fella.
And you probably can turn on
the charm any time you want.
You just came here into my
house and you chose not to.
I know that you want me to make
a big scene, probably want me to
throw you out of the house you wanna
drive a wedge between Holly and us.
I don't like you.
And I really don't like the
way you treat my daughter.
But you're a guest in my house
and I'm gonna be civil with ya.
For Holly's sake.
I don't want Holly to
have to choose between us.
I'm not gonna put her through that.
So you can be as obnoxious
and condescending as you want
I'll deal with it.
Well, I got something for you, Holly.
Here.
It's
handmade.
All your sisters got one.
I wanted to give it to you personally.
Oh, Daddy, I can't.
Oh, honey, sure you can.
It's beautiful, honest it is, but
He wouldn't approve of it, though.
Just hold it for me, will you?
All right, honey.
All right.
When you want your present,
you call me all right?
Call me.
- You're not interested in my...
Your first book, it sold.
- It sold. - Two thousand copies, Ira.
That's it.
Look.
I don't need a big advance.
I just need something
to, you know, hold me over.
You know what, champ?
Your stuffs just too out there.
Who are you? Look, I don't
have to explain anything
to you! Look! Don't
hang up on me, please.
Don't hang up.
My phone is essential to my...
We need money.
Ira. No. Please.
- What?
You'd be great at this.
I'll get a job.
- Not making this kind of money.
Come on. It'll be good for you,
Holly. It'll be good for us.
It'll liberate ya.
Make you explore your sensuality,
make you less inhibited.
Holly, look.
The work we're doing is so important.
Does it really have to stop because
of something so mundane as money?
Nervous?
- No.
Mr. Geller. Thank you.
We've seen some amazing
examples of psychic
phenomenon here today.
I'd also like to thank
Dr. Poharak and the man
who arranged all this
for us today, Ira Einhorn.
Your water, sir.
Thank you.
You don't drink?
- Glass of wine, occasionally.
That's it?
- A little pot.
For mind-expanding purposes only.
My LSD days went out in the sixties.
Why do you ask?
- Oh, I'm just curious.
Hi. I'm Ira.
- Yes, I know.
Barbara Bronfman.
You honestly believe the CIA's
experimenting with this sort of thing?
Absolutely.
Along with the Defense Department.
You see what Geller was doing today?
- Amazing.
What better radar than the human radar?
See, we're gathering proof that
both the CIA and the Russians
are developing this psychic ability in
people to make them into human weapons.
I don't mean to interrupt
but we should get going.
It's getting late.
Would you excuse me?
- Of course.
Holly.
You ever heard of Seagram's Whiskey?
Sure.
- Well, that woman is Barbara Bronfman.
She is Seagram's Whiskey.
She's the richest woman in Canada.
And she's interested in my work.
Well, I'd like to talk to her.
- Well, what are you going to talk about?
Stripping?
Go hang out.
You know, Arthur. Your labs should
investigate Geller's power.
There could be some
groundbreaking stuff here.
A little too groundbreaking.
Look, Ira.
It might be a good idea to be careful
about some of the things you're saying.
About the CIA?
Defense Department stuff?
Those people don't have a sense of humor.
You could be making some powerful enemies.
Don't worry about me, Arthur.
I'm also making some powerful friends.
Holly?
It's unbelievable.
I mean, Poharak wants me to come up to
his farm, this summer and help him with
his experiments on mind control and the
Bronfmans have asked me up to Canada.
It's great!
- What about me?
You keep saying they want you
to come up there. - What about me?
Holly. We're experimenting
with psychic phenomenon
that is someday going
to effect all of us.
I want you there with me.
All right?
- Maybe you should go by yourself.
What?
I can't go there without you.
You'll find another woman.
I'm sorry.
You scared me.
- Then don't provoke me.
Honey.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I need you.
Come with me, please.
Don't say things like that.
Hey hey!
Ira.
We are going to have such a time.
I made you some bread.
Raisin bread.
Thank you...
- Holly. - Holly.
Poharak is here and
some psychic phenomenon
experts from Europe.
- Perfect.
The signs are all obvious, yet, we sit as
if paralyzed at the edge of the millennium.
Waiting.
The darkness of the past looms.
He sensed the mark of the future
is being carved deep in his bones.
Since that time, he has
slowly been exploring
the realm of the mythological mother.
Hello.
What are you drawing?
Nothing.
You're missing the lecture.
I have no idea what they're
talking about half of the time.
I have a feeling some of
them aren't even too sure.
Then why are you here?
I was bored this weekend.
Don't let me interrupt you.
- No. It's okay.
Sit down if you want.
I'm Saul.
Saul Lapides.
Holly Maddux.
So I sold the business and I've just been
sorta bummin' around on my boat ever since.
I've got it docked at Fire Island.
Have you ever been there? - No.
I'd love to take you out on it sometime.
I live with someone.
- Yeah, I know.
Ira.
We'd better get back.
- Wait.
Could I see your drawings?
No.
They're no good.
Please.
It's beautiful.
- No. It's crude.
There's no style.
- It's lovely.
It's fragile.
The life energy never leaves.
It is here with us, no?
Open yourself to it.
Open your self.
Think about a safe haven.
Make the body safe
place to look inward.
Look inside.
Your self.
I see something.
It's a girl.
I see a girl.
A girl.
What else?
It's nothing.
It's not important.
Tell us, what did you see?
- Don't encourage her...
It's a little girl.
She's frightened.
Very frightened.
Because she's learning to ride a bike.
It's a two-wheeler and it's her
first time but she's doing it
and she leaves the person who's
holding her and she starts to
Starts to what?
A little girl on a bicycle?
Look. It's obvious Holly isn't
sophisticated enough to distinguish
between true, psychic energy
and her own, little imagination.
Just shut up and listen, honey.
You know? What that woman has
to say is every bit as important
as anything the great
Ira Einhorn has to say.
You don't understand
our relationship, Saul.
Holly.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what got
into me. It's just,
you see, sometimes I
don't think you understand
how important this is
to me and to my work.
If I hurt you it's because,
well I want you to grow.
Look.
I know I'm a little rough sometimes.
You know, sometimes it just...
I lose my patience and...
well, look.
I'm sorry.
Will you forgive me.
Holly.
Holly?
Daddy?
Thanks for sending me the money.
Worth every cent.
She's done her little
disappearing act before,
but never more than a day or so.
Why don't you call her parents?
They hate me!
No one hates you, Ira.
- Look.
The father's a Nazi. They're trying to
pull her away from me. I can feel it.
You're not going to know
anything until you call.
I'll get that.
It's probably one of Mary's boyfriends.
Hello?
One minute.
Holly?
It's him.
King of the Piggies.
Don't be like that.
Daddy... - I'm not lyin' for you and I'm
not gonna do your dirty work.
Now you've gonna get some
backbone, talk to him. Tell him.
Go on.
I don't want to talk to you, Ira.
No.
Please, don't.
Not after the way you've treated me.
Goodbye, Ira.
Don't call here again.
I mean it.
Way to go, Holly! Yeah!
I see.
You got a degree from
one of the best colleges
in the country and you
want to make dresses?
My dresses and my designs.
I need to do something on my own.
Something I can take some pride in and then
And then, you can go back to him.
Go back there, Meg.
Whether Ira's a part of it or not.
I can't stay here.
I don't belong here.
I miss you.
I love you and the hurts I know
I've heaped upon you, pain me too.
And I feel so stupid for
doing it, for you were
soft and lovely and I want
you to just be with me.
The rest are distractions, Holly.
They do not allow me the
constant focus I need.
Please come back to me, Holly, please.
I will share you work
and you can share mine.
Please.
Feed my being with your very presence.
Well, I've been back for six weeks,
and so far here, things are better.
Repeat: so far.
Ira's been incredibly
considerate and supportive.
I've started to make my dresses
and working in our local food co-op.
I've even been selling
some of my baked goods.
All organic, of course.
You'd probably hate them, daddy.
I know you were worried
last time, but don't be.
Content and busy and
plan to stay that way.
Sounds good, doesn't she?
In a few years, Holly,
this will all be obsolete.
Just hit a button on
a computer and all the
research material you need will
be aright at your fingertips.
Rita?
Oh God. - How are you?
God, I thought you moved away.
Don't touch me! Don't come near me,
you son of a bitch! It's just like
What?
- Do you hear me, you bastard?
Don't you ever touch me!
It's on sale.