(WATER LAPPING)
MICHELLE: How could you
be so dumb, Tracy?
No, I just cannot
believe you agreed.
TRACY: (ON PHONE) Well,
it's easier for him.
I don't care if it's easier
for him, it's homecoming.
Big deal, I'll meet
him at the dance.
You're not going to meet him at the dance.
Don't be such a dork.
Well then, how do I
get out of this?
Look, just tell him that you're not
going to go unless he picks you up.
I don't know. (CLANKING)
You know, I think they're home.
I gotta go, bye.
Hi.
(CREAKING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SCREAMS) (LAUGHS)
- Jerk!
- (LAUGHS) I'm sorry, I couldn't resist.
Oh!
Come on, I want to
show you something.
(MICHELLE LAUGHING)
How's the water?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(CHUCKLES) Got ya.
You think that's funny, huh?
(LAUGHS)
You think that's funny?
(CHUCKLES) A little boy
and a girl, how perfect!
I know.
What does this guy do, anyway?
MICHELLE: He makes
money, lots of it.
Hey, come here, I want
to show you something.
How'd you like to see me in this
for homecoming? (BOTH CHUCKLE)
I'd rather see you in nothing.
Mmm. (LAUGHS)
$485, yeah, you're
out of your mind.
(WHINES) You are.
But wouldn't you love
to live like this?
Sure, who wouldn't?
(CAR APPROACHING) Oh, my God.
They're home! Go, go!
Did you have a good time?
Yeah, thanks.
Bill's ready to take you home, so,
we'll just see you tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Everything go all right? Yeah, fine.
They're great kids.
Yeah, they are. They
really like you.
They talk about you all the time.
(LAUGHS)
So, you're what, a senior? Yeah.
What are you going to
do after graduation?
College, state probably,
unless I get a scholarship.
You must be a pretty
good student.
Mmm, athletic scholarship.
Swim team.
I've been competing
ever since I was a kid.
And then what, after college?
I don't know. (CHUCKLES)
You have to set
goals for yourself.
You got any real solid goals?
- I don't know.
- (CHUCKLES) Yes, you do.
To live like you do, I guess.
Well, just remember it's
not so much what you have
as who you share it with.
Mrs. Bartrand's really lucky.
Thank you. I'll tell you
a little secret though.
I'm the lucky one.
MICHELLE: Goodnight. Goodnight.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Hey.
Well, I took your advice.
Yeah? And, uh, he blew me off.
No way!
God! He's such a punk!
Well, you know, I have my pride
but no date for homecoming.
Tracy, I'm so sorry.
Do you hate me?
No, no.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, he doesn't deserve you
anyway, right? (CHUCKLES)
Hey Stanley, you remember the
once great Detective O'Keefe?
Good afternoon,
sir, how are you?
Mr. Bartrand, how
are you today, sir?
I am fine, Stanley,
never better, in fact.
He's better than
fine, he's lucky.
Beat me by two strokes.
You know, luck, luck
had nothing to do...
What can I get you gentlemen today?
The usual.
I'll have an ice tea.
Oh, come on, have a drink.
I got to go into the office, I
got some paper work I got to do.
This is interesting, I'm looking
at the 14th hole, which,
if memory serves, you scored and
next to your name I see a four.
What'd you get Sally
for her birthday? Huh?
No, no, I tell you, you tell
Norma, Norma calls Sally...
I swear to God I will not
say a word this year.
Forget it, suffice it to say,
it's something I think
she's going to love.
I know I would.
You know what I hate
about birthdays?
I can never, ever decide
what to buy Norma.
Yeah... And she gets so damn
depressed on her birthday.
Makes me sick.
Really? Yeah.
Sally too. She's been
really moody this year.
I think it's the age thing.
You think so? Yeah.
I don't know, maybe, look at
her, she looks so beautiful.
She looks fabulous. I thought
maybe it's 'cause...
She wants another baby.
Like I would say no.
You guys trying?
Every chance we get.
(GIGGLES) All right.
(CHILDREN LAUGH)
How do I look?
Oh, wow, you look incredible.
Really? Do you think so?
That dress. Oh. Thank you.
Sorry, I'm late.
Daddy!
Hi, guys.
They're beautiful.
Shall we give Mommy her present?
Yeah. Yeah? Come on.
Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, Michelle
SALLY: Looking forward to this.
Happy birthday!
You like it? Does it matter?
KYLE: Can we go for a ride?
Well, better yet,
how about we all go out to
dinner in Mommy's new car?
JENNIFER: Yeah!
Honey, I made reservations
at the Wharf tonight.
I thought you and I'd just have a
quiet dinner, just the two of us.
(SIGHS) I canceled.
I thought it would be more fun if we
could all go some place together.
Okay. I'll go change then.
(CHUCKLES)
SALLY: So, after tennis, they
both have piano lessons,
which Kyle's going to try to talk
you out of, okay? (LAUGHS) Okay.
Okay, here, I wrote
down the directions
and their music's
on the piano bench
and I should be home around 5:00,
really no later than 5:30.
Great. Thanks.
Okay, come on, kids. Time to go!
(PHONE RINGING) Hello.
Okay, I'm leaving!
Hon, aren't you going to
be early for your flight?
I got to stop by the office and
pick up some papers I forgot.
Hey, look, can I call you back?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yeah?
Okay, thanks, bye.
BILL: Hey, buddy?
Okay, we're off.
Hey you two, you be good, okay?
Listen to Michelle. I love you.
BILL: No, it sounds great but
I'm running kind of late,
so I'm going to give the phone to Sally and
you can work out the details with her, okay?
Would you give that to Sally?
Yeah.
Thank you.
The Griffins want to have dinner
next week, make it at the club.
Hello?
SALLY: Hi, George.
Were you gonna leave without saying
goodbye to your old man, huh?
Love you, I love you,
get out of here!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh thank you, yeah, we'd love to.
Okay.
(WATER SPLASHING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Hey, Doreen.
I got to run back to the house
real quick, I forgot something.
No problem, we still
got 20 minutes.
- Great, thanks.
- DOREEN: Okay, ready?
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
BILL: (OVER PHONE) Hi, it's me.
I'm in my car on the way to the
airport and I just realized...
Mrs. Bartrand? I forgot
the kids' piano books.
Mrs. Bartrand?
BILL: ...I love you.
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
Ah, keys.
(GASPING AND PANTING)
(SOBS)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
MAN: I'll be upstairs.
I'm Detective Jacobs,
and I'm not going to ask you
how you're doing right now
'cause I can imagine
not so good.
Frank?
(GASPS)
You didn't hear
anything strange?
Just Mr. Bartrand.
At first, I thought
he was here, but um,
then I realized it was just
the answering machine.
He was leaving a message.
Detective Jacobs, this is Mrs.
Bartrand, she's Bill's mom.
My condolences. Thank you.
The children are asking to see
Michelle, if that's all right.
Are you up to it? Yeah, sure.
(SIGHS)
What the hell happened here?
Well, there's, uh, no
signs of forced entry,
nothing seems to be missing,
looks like a suicide.
What about the gun?
We're checking the registration.
No note?
We haven't found one.
Next couple of days, Billy,
are going to be real rough.
I'm not going to leave
your side, all right?
- So, anything you need, you ask me, all right?
- KATE: Hello?
You know, she was fine, Frank.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, I know.
Frank?
Yeah?
The gun wasn't registered.
Did you know she had it, Mr.
Bartrand?
My wife hated guns.
She would never have allowed a gun
in the house with the children.
(SIGHS)
Billy?
Come on. It's okay, it's okay.
(SOBS) It's okay, it's all
right, it's gonna be okay.
(SOBBING) All right.
It's all right, it's all right.
Come on, it's going to be okay.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Michelle, there's
somebody here to see you.
Come on in. Hi, Michelle.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Can I get you anything, honey?
Ms. Jacobs?
Oh, no. No, thank you. I'm fine.
Call me if you need me.
Excuse me.
Michelle, there are a couple of
questions I need to ask you.
Sure.
You're a swimmer?
I know this isn't easy.
I still can't really believe it.
There are a couple of loose ends
that I need to tie up, okay?
I listened to the message that Mr.
Bartrand left his wife
and in it, he said that things
had been crazy that
morning, crazy how?
Just the usual family stuff,
kids playing, TV, everyone
was running late.
There were both on the phone.
On the same call?
No, um...
Mrs. Bartrand was
on the patio phone
and he was on his cell phone.
Do you know who she
was talking to? No.
But he was talking to some friends
who wanted to have dinner.
How do you remember that?
Well, because I gave
her his cell phone
to set it up and
then we all left.
So, "crazy" didn't mean they were
fighting or anything like that?
Oh, no.
I never saw them
fight, not once.
But then you hadn't worked
for them that long, had you?
Well, no but you can just kind
of tell about people, you know?
They weren't the kind of
people who would fight.
So, Sally Bartrand
seemed happy to you?
Yeah. She had a great life.
I mean, everything
you could want.
It was perfect.
No, I know. Okay, yeah.
How far back do you guys go?
Oh, 20, 25 years.
We played football
together in high school.
FRANK: Billy?
Hey, Frank.
You remember Detective Jacobs?
Hi.
Mr. Bartrand, once again my
condolences to your family.
Thank you.
I realize that this might not
be the most appropriate time
but was your wife under
psychiatric care?
Kate, let's talk about this later.
I'm sorry, of course.
Well, no, that's all right.
Um...
(STAMMERS) Well, she wasn't,
but why do you ask?
The autopsy revealed traces
of Danol in her system.
What's Danol?
It's an anti-depressant.
Some users are prone
to wild mood swings.
You didn't know your
wife was taking it?
No, I'm ashamed to say I didn't.
(SIGHS) You live with
somebody for 12 years,
you think you know them.
Let's go see the
kids, huh, Billy?
I'll be back in a
couple of minutes.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I'll see you later, Chris.
You're going home?
That dog, Willie,
more demanding than
my last husband was.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I need to speak to someone
about Sally Bartrand's death.
You can speak to me about it.
I'm Paul Richards.
I was Sally's lover.
BILL: I found this
in Sally's dresser,
it was under a pile of sweaters,
I mean, you know, it's unmarked.
I don't know if it's
what you're looking for.
All right, we'll check it out.
It wasn't a whole lot of fun going
through her stuff, you know.
You know, sometimes life
throws more crap in your face
at the times when you
can least afford it.
She ever mention a guy
named Paul Richards?
I don't think so, no, why?
Well, according to this guy,
they were having an affair.
(SIGHS) What?
The guy's a computer
analyst from South Bank.
He says he was out of town
when it happened and, uh...
He just read about it in the
newspaper when he got back.
And on top of that,
he says she was
about to leave you.
I'm sorry, Billy.
I wanted to be the
one to tell you,
I didn't want you to hear it
from somebody else, you know.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
So, she was just lying there
all bloody when you found her?
Yeah.
Well, I would've lost it.
You're not going back
to work there, are you?
I don't know, I just, I
feel bad for the kids.
Now, wait a minute, he can find
somebody else to babysit his kids.
(MICHELLE SIGHS)
Look, you're not going
back there, Michelle.
Hi, I'm so sorry I'm late.
I had a hard time getting
away from the office.
Stanley, bring a carafe of
the house Merlot, would you?
Right away, sir.
Since Sally's death, it's
been difficult going to work
and when I do, uh, um...
Don't worry about it, I
didn't mind waiting.
Thanks for meeting me
here, is this all right?
Oh, yeah, this is great, Mr.
Bartrand.
Mr. Bartrand was my
father, call me Bill.
So, um, how are
Kyle and Jennifer?
They're okay, they...
Well, they miss you.
I miss them.
How's school? It's good.
I mean, it's homecoming so everyone's
worried about getting their date.
I mean, I'm sure that's
not a problem for you.
(CHUCKLES)
Michelle, my mother's
leaving soon, and...
I was just hoping that you
might be able to help us out,
just at least until things get a
little bit more back to normal.
Of course, whenever you need me.
I mean I know I have to hire somebody
full time and I will, I just...
No, really, I don't mind.
Just give me a call, I'm available.
Thank you.
Sure.
Sally used to love coming here.
(SIGHS) Life is so...
It can change in a heartbeat.
Hi. Hi.
Kids in bed?
I keep asking myself why I didn't
see how much pain she was in.
(SIGHS) I wish there was
something I could do to help.
The way you've been taking care of
the kids has been an enormous help.
Which reminds me...
Come on. What?
You'll see. (CHUCKLES)
Come on.
(MICHELLE GIGGLES)
I want you to use the new car.
MICHELLE: You're kidding, right?
My kids are all I have now,
and when you drive around, I would like
you to be in something safe and reliable.
You know, I'm totally cool
with the station wagon.
Oh, no, please, it's old
and it breaks down.
Indulge me, okay? Press
the button there.
Go ahead.
(BEEPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Michelle!
This is sweet!
This is more like unbelievable.
Are you sure this was his idea?
Yes, Mom. He trusts me, okay?
Michelle, you are 18 years old,
you do not need to
be driving a car.
Not everything is
about need, Mom.
Some people, they just do
things because they want to.
Give me a ride to school.
Jeff, you know, maybe you should
ask Mom if you "need" a ride.
You lose the attitude, Michelle.
I don't have an
attitude, you do, okay?
Look, I'm sorry.
Do you want me to drop
Jeff off at his school?
Yes, yes.
This is going to make your life
easier too, you know that, right?
All right, all right.
For God's sake, be careful,
this car cost almost twice as
much as what I make in a year.
Mom.
(CAR STEREO PLAYS)
(HORN BLARING)
Hey.
Girl, what'd you do?
Steal this thing?
He gave it to me to use,
can you believe it?
What'd you have to give him?
Very funny.
Oh, it's even got
a phone in here!
I know. I'm not trying to be
funny, Michelle, I'm serious.
Look, this guy just lost
his wife, all right?
His whole world is a mess
and I'm helping him out.
This makes it easier, okay?
What do you want from me?
What does he want from you, Michelle?
That's the question.
Hello? What's his problem?
(SCOFFS)
I don't know but this thing is bad.
Awesome. (GIGGLES)
I was just looking for you.
Yeah, I'm out here
feeding my habit.
Yeah, so I see. Where
are you off to?
I got to go let Willie out before
he chews up the living room again.
You treat that dog better
than you treat me.
He does more for me. (CHUCKLES)
Listen. Yeah?
I left the results from the lab test
on Sally Bartrand on your desk.
Everything check out?
Not really.
What do you mean?
There wasn't any gun powder
residue on her hand.
Which means she was either wearing
gloves when she shot herself,
managed to hide them after she was
dead, that's a pretty neat trick.
Those residue tests aren't 100%
conclusive, you know that.
Yeah, I know that.
And I also know that Sally
didn't kill herself.
Now, do you want to
tell him or should I?
(SIGHS)
BILL: Good one! Yeah, all right!
Beautiful, beautiful!
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
It's Uncle Frank, you guys
carry on, I'll be right back.
Okay. Got it? Yeah.
(MICHELLE LAUGHS)
Ready?
Kids seem better.
Yeah, yeah, I'm trying to
spend more time with them.
Wish I'd done that
when Sally was alive.
Oh, boy, what?
What is it that you
don't want to tell me?
The lab test failed to show gun
powder residue on Sally's hands.
So, what does that mean?
Well, maybe nothing,
or maybe Sally
didn't kill herself.
Oh, God.
I still think it was
a suicide, Billy.
But, uh...
Kate wants to check it out.
Right, okay.
I mean, we got to
look at everybody,
we gotta look at
this guy Richards,
we got to look at you, you're
the husband, you know.
And then there's the babysitter.
Michelle? Yeah.
I mean how well do
you really know her?
Come on, Frank, you
can't possibly think...
Well, she had access
to the house.
For example, she comes back,
she thinks no one's home,
Sally surprises her,
she's stealing something,
it happens all the time.
No, it's ridiculous,
she's, she's a good kid.
Well, she may be a good kid but you've
got a serious situation here, Billy,
- and you can't afford to be too trusting.
- (SIGHS) God.
BILL: Damn, okay.
See you. Yeah.
It wasn't suicide, was it?
No.
Thanks.
Is this where you guys would meet?
Most of the time. It was safe.
From what?
Her husband, I told you she
was scared to death of him.
He could've fooled everyone
else who knew them.
Oh, let me guess.
The perfect family, right?
Was she under
psychiatric treatment?
Are you kidding?
Bartrand'd never allow that.
The guy's a control freak,
everything and everyone
in their place.
Sally wanted to get back to work
since the kids were both in school.
You know what he told her?
That it was time to
have another baby.
Bartrand says he didn't
know about your affair.
Of course he'd say that.
He knew.
In fact, Sally was sure he
was having us followed.
Oh, really? Why would
she suspect that?
The way he acted.
Things he'd say to her
after we'd been together.
It frightened her to the point
where one day she called
and said it was too
dangerous to see me.
She broke it off?
PAUL: No.
Yes, but, you know,
just for a while
until she could figure
out what to do.
I loved Sally.
I wanted to spend the
rest of my life with her.
No one remembers seeing you in
West Palm the morning she died.
I wasn't interested in the speaker
so I took a walk on the beach.
Anybody see you?
I'm sure someone did. Who?
You have a name?
You don't actually suspect me?
This is insane.
I'm the one who came to
you people, remember?
I'm the one who told you she
was going to leave him.
But she left you...
Didn't she, Mr. Richards?
MAN: (ON PHONE) Mr. Bartrand,
shows no case under your name.
I'm sorry, I could've sworn I
used your detective agency.
No, it wasn't us but...
But what if?
We keep very accurate
files, you should try it.
You're absolutely right, I should keep
better records, it's just that I...
(DIAL TONE)
(PHONE BEEPING)
WOMAN: (ON PHONE)
Securex Investigations.
Yeah, hi, it's Bill Bartrand and I've lost
some of my files and I was wondering...
Oh, yes, Mr. Bartrand, I
remember you, this is Suzy.
Suzy. Uh-huh.
Yeah, Suzy, about that job
you did for me a while back,
I seem to have misplaced my report.
I was wondering if you could
send it over with any photos.
Well, it's been archived already but I
could modem it over to your computer.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Um, anytime you're ready.
I'll pull it up right now, Mr. Bartrand,
I just need your case number.
Right, my case number. Mmm-hmm.
You know I'm not at
the office right now
and I'll have to get
back to you with it.
No problem. Thanks.
You're welcome.
(PHONE BEEPS)
I can't believe you're going
to blow me off Saturday.
We were supposed to go
shopping for homecoming.
I told you I have
to watch the kids,
besides, why do you need a dress
if you don't have a date?
(SCOFFS) Oh, and
whose fault is that?
KATE: Michelle?
You're a very difficult person
to connect to these days.
Oh, you know how it is, her
being a working mother and all.
(CHUCKLES)
My friend with the
mouth would be Tracy.
Tracy, Kate Jacobs. Hi.
She's a cop.
(CHUCKLES)
So...
You've grown pretty attached
to the Bartrand kids, huh?
Actually, uh...
They've grown attached to me.
Ever since, you know...
Sally's murder.
Mmm, what?
You didn't know?
No... (GASPS)
I mean, I was in
the house and...
(SOBS)
Who would... Who would do that to her?
We don't know yet, honey.
That's why I want
you to be careful.
You hear me?
Mmm-hmm. (SIGHS)
Oh, my God.
What was that all about?
What happened?
Hey, wait a minute, you
can't go in there.
I'm sorry, Mr. Bartrand,
I couldn't stop her.
Oh, that's okay, Pam, this is
Michelle, she's our sitter.
What's the matter?
I don't think I can
work for you anymore.
What?
What's going on? What happened?
That detective, Kate,
she told me that
Sally was murdered.
She told you that?
But that's not true right?
I mean...
No, Sally killed herself.
As hard as it is for
all of us to accept
and only Detective Jacobs
is running around town
looking for a killer.
Right.
You think I'd let you
and the children
stay in that house for a second,
if I thought that was true?
No, no.
I'm sorry.
Oh, she really frightened you.
(EXHALES)
Why would she think
something like that?
I guess she can't believe that
someone who had everything
would just throw it all away.
As for quitting,
I won't allow it.
Coming home to you and the kids
is just the best part of my day.
Why don't you give them
dinner early tonight
and you and I,
we can have a late
supper and really talk.
Okay?
That'd be nice.
Bye.
Pam, get me Diane Watson on the
phone, would you? Yes, sir.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, you're late.
Oh my... You were
making dinner tonight.
I cannot believe I
forgot, I'm sorry.
Diane, this is our
babysitter Michelle.
Um, I'm just going to go
upstairs for a minute.
Michelle, would you show Diane
to the living room? Thanks.
Um, I'm so sorry.
I didn't, um... God!
I didn't mean, I just...
You look beautiful.
I'm sorry that I
hurt you tonight.
Can you forgive me?
Can you?
(MOANS)
I already made one mistake
tonight, I, I think...
We better stop this before
I make another one.
- Frank?
- FRANK: (OVER PHONE) Yeah?
Oh, I'm sorry to bother you so late.
That's okay. What's up?
Well, it's about the
babysitter, Michelle.
What?
Yeah, I just came home
and I found her going
through Sally's things.
You kidding?
She was even wearing
one of her dresses.
Oh, man!
I don't know, maybe I'm
making too much of it.
It's... Well, it's just
after what you said, I...
I thought you should know.
No, no, I'm glad you called me.
Just be careful, Billy.
Thanks. All right.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Yes, I'm in.
(KEYS CLACKING)
Son of a bitch has it at home.
Michelle, Jeff's game has been
rescheduled from 10:30 to 1:00
and I have to be at
the hospital at noon,
can you take him?
Oh, I can't. I have way too
much to do today, Mom.
I have to interview
housekeepers all morning.
Interview what?
Housekeepers.
(SCOFFS) Exactly what do you
know about housekeeping?
Who do you think runs
that house, mother?
I know what Bill and the kids need.
So, it's, "Bill" now?
It was his idea.
Like the car was his idea?
You're wearing heels to babysit?
Look, he asked me to do this
and I'm not going to show up
looking like some teenager.
You are a teenager, Michelle.
I'm sorry to stick you with
this housekeeper thing.
Do not worry about it, I
have it all under control.
What would I do without you?
(CHUCKLES)
The skirt's a keeper, yes?
(GIGGLES)
Hey, have a good day. You too.
Detective Jacobs, hi.
Mr. Bartrand, until you called me
today, I thought you were avoiding me.
I left so many messages.
Not at all, this hasn't been a
great time for returning calls.
Forgive me.
Reason I got in touch
with you today is...
If you have any questions
about my wife,
I'd prefer you ask me
and not the hired help.
Come on in.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
You're a guy.
So are you.
I never knew guys wanted
to be housekeepers.
This guy does.
Come on in.
Thank you.
You're supposed to wait there.
Great.
So, Mr. Bartrand, tell
me about your marriage.
Wasn't perfect.
We loved each other, we
were happier than most.
So, the neighbors just
imagined the blow-ups,
most of them within
the past few months?
Oh, come on.
You know... I told you.
Sally wasn't herself, she was having these
mood swings for no apparent reason,
and yes, sometimes
there was shouting.
The Danol, no doubt.
Now that we know she was taking
it, it does explain a lot, yeah.
In the real world, married
people fight occasionally.
But they don't all take lovers.
(SIGHS)
Is that why you killed
your wife, Mr. Bartrand?
Because she found someone else?
Are you finished insulting me?
'Cause...
I have a lot of work to do.
Thank you. Sure.
It was lovely to meet
you, Mrs. Bartrand.
Thank you for coming.
I'll see myself out.
All right.
You're not Mrs. Bartrand,
that was my mom.
(SIGHS) Jennifer, come here.
Sometimes, it's just, um...
It's easier for me to say...
It's kind of hard to explain.
Where's the man? What man?
Kyle said there's
a man maid here.
What are you doing in here?
Uh, just looking around.
Boy, this is some
fabulous place,
kind of a bitch to
keep clean though.
I know most people aren't
too keen on male help
but just given the opportunity...
I'm calling the police.
No, uh, no...
(BANGS PHONE) Please, uh...
My name is Paul Richards.
I was a friend of Sally's.
I know she didn't kill herself.
Get out!
Please listen to me!
Bartrand killed her because she
was having an affair with me.
Don't you see?
Get out now!
Just let me pull up the document.
Get out!
BILL: No, Frank!
Not tomorrow, now!
I want a restraining
order out on this guy.
(STAMMERS) Look, Frank, just
listen to me, listen to me!
Please, look! Michelle
is very upset here,
and I think she has
every right to be.
No, not... Look not tomorrow.
I don't want this guy within 10
miles of Michelle and the kids.
Do you understand?
All right!
Okay, all right. Thanks.
(DIAL TONE)
(YELLS)
I just... (SIGHS)
I don't know what
I would've done
if something had happened
to the kids or to you.
It wasn't suicide, was it?
No, the police don't
think so anymore.
Detective Jacobs was right then.
BILL: I wish I'd believed her...
It just seemed so impossible
at the time, you
know, so ridiculous.
That guy, Richards...
Why would he say
that you killed her?
I mean, you know, the
police think he did it.
He's desperate.
He said there was some kind of proof
or something in the computer.
I mean, there's... There's
nothing on that computer but
couple of games for the kids,
and some household accounts.
I...
I got it for Sally but she never
really learned how to use it.
I'm scared Bill. I mean...
It's just getting way too weird for me.
Look...
I know. (SIGHS)
I know. I'm really sorry.
What if he comes back? He won't.
Frank just told me,
he thinks they have enough
on him to arrest him soon.
(SIGHS)
Do you think he did it?
(SIGHS) I...
He... He told them that...
That Sally broke the affair
off a couple of months ago.
He... He was still
in love with her.
See, if she knew him, she
would've let him in to the house.
(SIGHS)
Do you want to go home?
Or...
Maybe you could stay here and just
let me take care of you for a while?
That'd be nice.
Good.
You get some rest and...
(SIGHS) I'll look after the kids, okay?
(COMPUTER POWERING ON)
(CHUCKLES)
(HARBOR BELLS RINGING)
BILL: Wake up, sleepy head.
(CLICKS)
(GASPS)
Hi, Paul.
I just wanted to see what kind of
man steals another man's wife.
I didn't steal Sally.
You lost her.
You wouldn't have kept her.
She was high maintenance. And...
Look at you, you're
strictly chump change.
Hey, want to go play
on the computer?
Let's put up the family photos.
(GUN COCKS)
Pretty please?
(KEYS CLACKING)
(PRINTER WHIRRING)
BILL: Ooh.
Well, you... You have been a busy boy.
Oh, yeah, yeah...
(KEYS CLACKING)
That's very good of you.
Scroll down, scroll down.
You know when I first
saw these, I was...
Understandably, I think, enraged.
I felt betrayed.
I felt...
Dirty, you know.
But, the more I looked at them,
something happened.
It wasn't my wife anymore.
It wasn't Sally.
It was... It was like another woman,
I'd never felt
so much passion for anybody before.
The sex was
incredible, Paul.
And I have you to thank for that.
You're sick.
Delete it.
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
(BILL GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(CHOKING)
(BILL GRUNTS)
(STRUGGLING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(STRAINING)
(GUN FIRES)
(SIGHS)
BILL: Wake up, sleepy head.
(CHUCKLES) Hi. Hi.
Feeling better?
Yeah, a little.
Maybe this will help.
(WHISPERS) Oh.
I can't take this.
I want you to have it.
It's Sally's.
It's yours.
It's my way of saying...
I love you.
This afternoon I realized
just how much...
I don't know what I'd do
if I lost you, Michelle.
You're so beautiful.
(KISSING CONTINUES)
(DOG BARKING)
Willie! Willie!
Boo! (GIGGLES)
Hey, hey. Hello.
So, what's the big secret?
(LAUGHS) Come on, what?
He gave this to me last night.
Are you kidding me?
And... Oh.
He said he was falling in love with me.
(GIGGLES)
The guy's got to be 40, Michelle.
You're sleeping with him, aren't you?
No!
(SCOFFS) Bull.
It's his money, right? I mean...
You know what, forget it.
I knew you wouldn't understand.
Gosh.
Um, you know you're the one who called me
over for this little show and tell deal.
Okay, well, I'm
sorry I did then.
I got to get ready for work.
(SIGHS) You know, I
am so sick of you
acting like you're better
than the rest of us.
Tracy, some of us have
responsibilities.
No, I mean if you want to play
house with this guy, go ahead.
But stop expecting me and everybody
else to get excited about it.
'Cause personally, I
think it's really weird
and kind of creepy.
You know, so does Danny.
(SCOFFS) (SIGHS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
You told Danny about my necklace?
(SIGHS) Look, he asked me
what was up with you lately
and, I mean, it just kind of slipped out.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? That's it? That's
all you're going to say to me?
(SIGHS) Forget it.
(SIGHS)
Tracy!
Hey! I thought you were my friend.
Oh, no, you're way too mature for me.
You've got all your, "responsibilities."
You know, the house, the
car, the kids, the jewelry.
You are so jealous.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, right.
At least he treats
me with respect.
I mean something to him.
I count for something.
He treats me like I'm an adult.
Who wants to be an adult?
You got to wake up, Michelle.
Adults... Adults are
old and boring.
Just like you.
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
MICHELLE: Yeah, so are they.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
CHILDREN: Hey, Uncle Frank.
Hey, kids.
Hi, remember me, Frank?
Oh, right, hi.
How're the kids doing?
Oh, they're doing fine.
We're actually meeting Bill
here later for dinner.
That's nice. All together,
like a family, huh?
How are you doing?
Me?
Yeah.
Why?
I was just wondering.
Things are going pretty good
for you lately, aren't they?
You're driving a nice car, you're
taking care of a nice house.
You know, your friend, Tracy tells
me you're in love with Bill.
Is there any truth in that?
I said, "Tracy, no, that's not possible."
(FRANK CHUCKLES)
'Cause if it was...
That'd be just like stepping into
Sally's shoes, wouldn't it, huh?
(RADIO PLAYING)
I want these put away and I
don't mean on the floor.
Okay.
What's that around your neck?
Um... Where'd you get that?
Bill gave it to me but I
don't think it's real.
This is way out of line.
I was going to return it.
I'll save you the trouble.
Give it to me.
(INTERCOM BUZZES)
- Yeah.
- PAM: Mrs. Winston is here.
Oh, show her in.
Mrs. Winston, I'm so glad
to meet you finally.
You have such a
wonderful daughter.
I think so.
Can I get you a cup of coffee?
I believe this is yours.
You're absolutely right. I, I...
I should not have loaned it to her.
It's just that she was admiring it,
and then she mentioned
about the homecoming dance
and I just thought...
Yeah, well, I mean obviously
I wasn't thinking.
Michelle tells me that you're
looking for permanent help.
Yeah, but so far
I haven't been able to find anybody
as wonderful with the kids as she is.
She's...
She's really helped to
keep their lives together.
I'm sorry for your tragedy, Mr. Bartrand,
but I have a daughter
who has her own life
that she has to keep together.
I'll expect you to find a replacement
by the end of the month.
Of course.
I've been thinking...
Maybe it's time to...
Clean out Sally's things.
Her, her clothes, her shoes.
I don't know. It might
upset Kyle and Jennifer.
No, it's time.
It's time. We can't live in the past.
Not me, not the kids.
Do you think that you could...
(SIGHS) Just pack it all up and I...
I'll give it away to a charity.
Yeah, if that's what you want, yeah.
I want us
to start our life together.
Close your eyes.
(LAUGHS)
Are they closed? Yes.
Still closed? (LAUGHS)
No peeking.
There.
Now it's back where it belongs.
(CHILDREN PLAYING IN THE DISTANCE)
Okay, come on, kids. Let's go!
CHILDREN: Hi, Uncle Frank.
FRANK: I like your
sweater, Michelle.
(WHISPERS) I liked it on Sally, too.
- (LAUGHS) Hi.
- BILL: Hi.
There you go.
Thanks.
That friend of yours
followed me again.
Frank? (SIGHS)
Why would he do that?
Come on, you sure?
Ask the kids, they saw him.
I thought you talked to him.
I did.
Then why is he still bothering me?
I did something, uh...
It may have backfired.
I told him how much
I care about you.
I think he might be
having a hard time
dealing with it.
Sally was his friend, too.
We needs some time together,
just the two of us.
I could have my mother come
and take the kids for a weekend.
Would you like that?
I don't know. Maybe we
should stop for a while.
It just doesn't feel right.
You're the only thing in my life
that does feel right.
Don't you know that?
Look at this! I... (CLATTERING)
I just... I kept telling her I wasn't ready.
She's got the pendant, Billy.
All right, the friend saw it.
I know. Now, you say the word,
I'll have her picked up.
What am I supposed to do?
Tell Kyle and Jennifer that Daddy's
having their babysitter thrown into jail?
They... They've grown really
attached to her, Frank.
You're not doing anything stupid
with this kid, are you, Billy, huh?
No.
(CHUCKLING) I mean, I wouldn't
fault you if you were, you know.
She's just as cute as a button.
Mmm, tell me about it.
But the kid's not playing
with a full deck, all right?
So, I'm telling you.
Get rid of her, now.
I think it's perfect,
(CHUCKLES)
With your hair up and these.
No, Mom. These shoes, they
cost more than the dress.
Oh, I love it.
Don't you?
Yeah. It's fine, it works.
(SIGHS)
Homecoming.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Mom, um...
Tracy wanted to know if I could
spend the weekend at her house,
because, you know,
we're doubling.
And then Saturday, we were just
going to kind of hang out.
Is that okay?
You're not working?
No, um...
He's going out of
town on business
and their grandmother
is watching them.
ALICE: Oh, well.
Okay, as long as you make Tracy's
mom promise to take pictures.
(SCOFFS) Please.
Hey, I'm a mom. What can I say?
I'm going to buy you these shoes.
Mom, no. They're way too expensive.
Oh, come on, let me.
They're perfect.
(RADIO PLAYING)
Did you talk to Lieutenant O' Keefe?
Mmm-hmm.
So, what's the problem?
He thinks you killed Sally Bartrand.
(SCOFFS)
You know what your
employer's been telling him?
That he has caught you going
through his wife's things,
wearing her clothes,
her perfume...
That you stole an
expensive diamond pendant
pretty much like the one
I see you wearing now.
Well, he... He gave this to me.
He also said you went
through his wife's closet,
and threw away everything.
Yeah, well, he asked me to.
I mean, Frank's obviously lying.
Oh, is he?
And why would he do that?
Frank hates me because I'm not Sally.
Oh, is that what Bartrand told you?
Well, Bill told him, you know,
how much he cares about me
and then, I guess
he's just been having a really hard
time dealing with it, you know.
I know Frank, Michelle.
He's a good cop.
He's not in the habit
of trying to frame
a teenager out of some
personal vendetta.
But that's what he's doing to me.
No, dear.
Frank is not trying to frame you.
Bill Bartrand is.
Are you sleeping with him?
Michelle.
Oh!
(SIGHS)
Michelle? I'm home!
Michelle?
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey the phone's ringing, dummy.
(RINGING STOPS)
Hey, I thought you
were going to Tracy's?
Where's Mom? I called her
at work, she wasn't there.
She's at some training thing.
She left the number somewhere.
Hi, Daryl. Hey, Kate.
Oh, just the lady I came to see.
I'm so lucky.
I, you know, I wanted to find out
if anything broke on the case
and then Frank suggested that I let you
know if I was planning to leave town.
He didn't want you to think I was trying
to escape the long arm of the law.
Are you? (CHUCKLES)
Escaping?
Hardly.
I'm going to Tampa in the
morning on business.
I had my secretary
type out an itinerary,
left it with the Desk Sergeant.
Very thoughtful of you.
I heard you filed a missing
person's report on Paul Richards?
That's right.
Well, I want you to let me know the
minute anything comes in on that.
(SCOFFS) You know,
anything we can do to make
you happy, Mr. Bartrand.
(SCOFFS) (PHONE RINGING)
Yeah? Hey, Pam.
Uh-huh.
BILL: Yeah, yeah.
Mr. Bartrand?
Just a sec, yeah?
Is that the phone you
use in your car?
Uh, yeah.
So, you were on that phone when you tried
to call your wife the morning she died?
Just a second.
Yeah.
Have a nice trip.
You know, Pam, I'll call him back.
BILL: That sounds great, but
look, I'm running late,
so, I'm going to give
the phone to Sally
and you can work it
out with her, okay?
Okay. Would you give that to Sally?
Thank you.
BILL: The Griffins want to have dinner
next week. Make it at the club.
Hello?
(PHONE RINGING)
BILL: (ON TAPE) Hey, it's me.
I'm on my way to the airport
and I just realized things
were so crazy this morning
I forgot to kiss you goodbye.
So, I'll call you from the hotel tonight.
Gotcha.
Chris.
You get those cell
phone records for me?
I'm working on it. Find Frank?
I paged him.
Uh, it's Willie time.
Yeah, yeah.
(BUSY SIGNAL)
Come on, Michelle.
JEFF: It's like a...
Hey. Get off!
I told you I was waiting
for Mom to call.
- I, I got to go, okay?
- GIRL: Hey, call me later.
Yeah, bye. What's your problem?
(PHONE RINGING)
Mom? Michelle, honey?
I thought you were going
to meet me at the house?
No, um...
You know what, I got caught and
my mom found out I wasn't
going to homecoming.
She grounded me.
Oh, well, maybe I should come
over there and talk to her.
You know, tell her how badly
I need you this weekend.
You know that's not a good idea
'cause she's really mad and, uh,
she told me I can't
work for you anymore.
Look, sweetheart, I'll
think of something.
It'll work out, you'll see.
I think she's coming,
I got to go.
Michelle? I love you.
(SLAMS PHONE)
Hey! Are you really grounded?
(WHISTLING)
(DOG BARKING)
(HISSING)
Willie!
(SIGHS)
Now, how did you get out?
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(BARKING) Oh, Willie!
(KNOCKING)
(EXHALES)
I'm so glad you're here.
Homecoming?
(SIGHS)
Right. God, I forgot.
(GROANS) Am I surprised?
Look, I got to know something.
That cop, when he
was talking to you,
why would he think that
I stole the necklace?
Because the guy told
him it was missing.
He said that it...
That it was missing?
Are the lights in the attic
finally coming on, Michelle?
Did you tell him that I had it?
Yeah.
It just kind of... Slipped out.
Right, I know.
I'm sorry. No, it's okay.
Are you...
You know, you don't look so good.
But, you look amazing.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm so sorry for being such a...
Such a major bitch?
That. (BOTH CHUCKLING)
And more.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
You know, we're just going to
the dance as friends, right?
His date blew him off too.
How stupid was she?
(SNICKERS)
(KNOCKS)
Hi, I'm Bill Bartrand, is Michelle here?
(BEEPS)
Don't be home. Please
don't be home.
(SIGHS)
Bill?
(KEYS CLACKING)
(SIGHS)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
It's really frustrating, isn't it?
(GASPS)
Hi. Hi.
You smell good.
Here. Try this.
Here you go. Watch...
Watch this.
There. Is that what
you're looking for?
Yeah, take a look. Take a really good look.
Look at that.
(MICHELLE WHIMPERS)
BILL: I sure know I did
when I first saw them.
You killed her?
Well, of course I did.
She was going to leave me.
(SOBS)
She was going to take
my children, my family.
No! Stop it! (WHIMPERS)
(SCREAMING)
I thought you were grounded.
(SOBBING)
No, please don't!
(GROANS)
- Here we go.
- (CRYING) No!
No!
(GROANS)
You know...
You're the best
babysitter we ever had.
It's going to be really
hard to replace you.
Come on.
(GROANING)
(THUDS) Oh, that's
got to hurt, huh?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why not?
(GATE SLAMS)
Don't bother pressing the
buttons, 'cause they don't work.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
All right, Kate...
Easy, easy.
(MICHELLE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ELEVATOR SQUEAKING)
You were right all along, Frank.
(CLATTERING)
BILL: ...trying to tell me.
She's going crazy.
She tried to kill me, Frank.
(CLATTERING CONTINUES)
BILL: I got two words for you, Frank.
Amy Fisher!
This girl...
(THUDS)
BILL: I had to do it, Frank!
I had to do it! I...
(BILL CONTINUES
SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTING) I...
Had to do it!
(CONTINUES SHOUTING)
(DIALING)
(PHONE RINGS) FRANK: Yeah?
BILL: Frank. Oh, thank God, listen.
I just walked in the door
and I found the babysitter
trashing the place.
Can you get right over here?
Don't touch her, Billy.
I'm on my way. Great, thanks.
Billy's got the sitter.
I'm going to get some back up.
(PANTING)
Michelle? Michelle?
Look what you did to me!
Michelle!
(CLATTERING)
(WHIMPERS)
(SNIFFS)
(STRAINING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
That's Sally's perfume, isn't it?
See, I'd know it anywhere.
You loved being her, didn't you?
Didn't you?
Come on, let's get this over
with before Frank comes.
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(LAUGHS)
We're locked in.
We're all alone for the weekend.
Just like we planned.
Please.
BILL: Michelle!
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE) Hello?
Emergency operator.
Yeah, I'm sorry, operator.
One of my kids thought
this was funny.
It won't happen again.
Please see that it doesn't.
Thank you.
DOLL: (RECORDING) Mama, mama.
(GRUNTS)
No. Please. No!
Please, no!
(GRUNTS)
Where you going, Michelle?
Where you gonna go?
(SOBBING)
Hmm?
(SHOUTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GROANING)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Around the back.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Drop the knife, Michelle.
(BILL GROANS)
BILL: Frank? That's right.
(GASPING)
Michelle, honey, come here.
Frank!
What is it, Billy? Huh?
Frank...
You want to tell
me a story, huh?
Oh, I love your stories.
(BILL GROANS)
Are you okay? You all right?
It's over, honey.
(COUGHS)
Get him a doctor and
read him his rights.
Request an ambulance.
Roger, a paramedic.
MICHELLE: Wait.
There's something I
don't need anymore.
BILL: Frank! (GROANS)
KATE: Michelle, come on.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMS)
Frank!
Ah!