Hello!?
- Hello?
- Daniel!?
How did you folks get here?
Where you from?
- Brooklyn Heights.
- Sarah!
- Where is everybody?
- How long has it been?
You come into contact
with anyone else from..
Brooklyn Heights?
Yeah, we're gonna need a couple of guys
up there, if that makes any sense?
You stay put.
8 million New Yorkers disseminated
in three short weeks.
People will do crazy things when
they're backed into a corner.
Black Friday is when it all began.
The origin of this disease
is still unconfirmed.
But, there are many
theories speculated
that it could be the result of a
well orchestrated terrorist attack.
By the time Washington had the first
report of a small pox outbreak,
it was too late.
I tried to get my wife and
daughter out of New York.
Too bad, the military had
the city locked up tight.
I tried my best to keep my family safe.
Repeat control of the city...
we have received word now that,
Shanghai, Hong Kong and London...
are just the few of the other locations
where this outbreak has been reported.
We have just got warning that we've lost
comms with the entire New York city.
If it's anything, now is
the time, Mr. President.
Sarah thinks that it is an adventure.
She has always been an optimistic kid.
I'm leaving soon.
I haven't told 'em yet.
This is the hardest part.
Dad!? Dad!?
What happened with the TV?
Trisha's first reaction is usually panic.
Still I can count on her
when thing's get tough.
I haven't been completely
honest with you.
Look! There is a division that is activated
during a catastrophic emergency.
A safety switch, when more of less fails.
I am part of that division.
Our objective is simple:
Restore law and order.
This is Daryl, override! All copy?
Can you hear me?
John here.
Get your stash locations quick.
Then rendezvous on me.
All units please be advised,
I'm getting reports of some heavy
looting in the vicinity here.
- Keep those eyes peeled.
- Copy that!
C'mon unlock the
door, I won't bite.
911, what is your emergency?
Several men just smashed the
windows downstairs.
I can... I can hear them.
Ahh!
Infected money.
Black Friday, there the first supply.
Take out the American public...
but who is responsible?
Three words: Government, Sleeper, Agents.
- And who are these sleeper agents?
- Well It could be anyone.
It could be you.
It could be me.
- It could even be Mia.
- Even!?
Yes, even.
Well, I'm gonna go get you
guys that pizza. Okay?
Love you, babe.
Hey, not too crispy, right?
Look Saj,
I think you been inside
a little too long,
and it's starting to mess
with your head now, Bro.
Oh yeah? Maybe Mr Jackson
could convince you.
A sample.
A bill infected with the virus.
Woo! What the hell dude?
- You gotta infect us all.
- Relax!
It's hygienically sealed.
Hygienically sealed?
It's a sandwich bag.
No, no! Two sandwich bags.
Judging by your reaction,
you believe me.
I gotta hand it to you, Saj.
I have no idea how you
figured this all out.
But it's obvious...
you know way too much now.
Dude! What the hell!?
Ow! Dude that's a costly replica!
Totally costs hundreds!
- Did you hear that?
- What?
What are you doing?
Do not open that.
They can smell the pizza.
I thought I heard the looters outside.
It's an freaking apocalypse!
Of course there are looters outside!
Hey Saj! You know,
we love having you here and I know it's the
apocalypse out there and everything but...
how long were you
planning on staying?
Sorry, the truth capped
your ass so hard, Mia.
But when a man comes bursting through those
doors, you be glad, Saj is on your side.
Oh God!
Oh my God!
Saj, it's... it's time.
Um, time for what?
- Pizza!
- Yeah!
Yeah!
- No, no, no!
- It's fake! It's fake!
This is Daryl, up and running.
All copy?
- This is Mia.
- Everett here.
Yeah I was hoping to get
the call a little sooner.
No way!
Get to your stash locations quick
then rendezvous on me...
- Copy that! Copy that!
- Copy! I'm on my way.
Hand me the bag.
The other bag.
You coming' back, right babe?
That was hot!
I've lost all contact
with the JTF checkpoint.
Ah..anyone have
confirmation on this?
Where the storm come from?
Can't see anything
out here, let's go!
Hey? Hey?
- Everett!
- Michael!?
What are you doing here?
Was about to ask you the same question.
If anyone wants supplies.
Keeping an eye on a few people.
Last thing you need to be
worried about is work.
It could be dangerous around here.
You by yourself?
Will be.
Looking for something in particular?
Yeah... morphine.
She's in lotta pain.
I just wanna make it easy on her.
Alright! Let me see what I can find.
Hey!?
Hey?
Here.
Stop, c'mon!
Okay! okay!
Stop! Just give me the bag.
Stop! No, no!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
Hey!
Don't hurt her!
Mother!?
Sorry. Bad kids! Trouble.
Sorry! Your bag, here.
Here! Antibiotics.
Food.
This is Daryl, up and running.
All copy?
- This is Mia.
- Everett here.
Yeah I was hoping to get
the call a little sooner.
Get to your stash locations
quick then rendezvous on me...
- Copy that! Copy that!
- I'm on my way.
- Thank you.
- Next time, just ask!
Yeah, dispatch we got fires popping up
all over the place. You guy's see this?
We got two garbage trucks
just pulled up outside.
What the hell is sanitation doing here?
- What the hell!?
- Run! run! run!
Matches anyone?
You need water, I need fire.
This is Daryl, up and running.
All copy?
- This is Mia.
- Everett here.
Yeah I was hoping to get
the call a little sooner.
Get to your stash locations quick...
then rendezvous on me.
- Copy that!
Copy that.
No guys! Wait!
Please, wait.
Wait! Please, no!
Please!
Dad! dad!
It's John.
We are at the rendezvous point.
Where are you?
John here. Hold tight.
I'm five minutes out.
We are picking' up a lotta chatter,
East of Manhattan.
It's a JTF stronghold supply drop!
Everett! See if you can
tap into the wait pool for us.
Roger that.
OK! So what's our move?
- Everett, on over watch.
- Copy.
Scanning.
- Conserve ammo.
- Copy.
Holding.
On me...
Three, two...
Go! Go! Go! Kill them!
Kill them! Let's go.
Mia rapid fire.
Move!
Keep cover! Keep your heads down!
- This cover Isn't gonna last.
- Alright! i'll make a move.
Go! Go.
Go! Go! Go!
Put the gun down!
Or I put a put a hole in her head!
Alright, okay!
Take it.
Hey?
You gonna see him again.
- Alright, what's your ammo count?
- Down to my last mag.
I'm blank on ammo.
I'm getting a lotta comm chatter.
You guys going' back out there?
After all that?
I do not know what's left of the station.
But whatever you find, consider it yours.
Least I can offer.