Where am I?
Reconsider your answer
or be excluded
from the games forever.
This is not the time.
Let us not broach the subject again.
Quintus, why are you from bed?
The medicus gave plain instruction
you are to rest.
A week upon my back
sees advice well-heeded.
More, and even my cock
will cease knowing how to stand.
His spirit returns.
I am not a babe new dropped
from fucking womb.
- See meat and wine set out.
- Yes, Domina.
I always follow the wine.
Your wounds... they
are less gruesome.
Has she not yet found
some fool's bed to fall to yet?
Or is her sole intent in Capua
to drink us dry?
She has been of great comfort.
And seeks the word for herself.
Who do you think dried my tears
when my husband was returned to me
bloodied and broken,
his life in question?
I live
and continue thoughts
towards doing so.
I would not see my injuries
wound you as well.
Oh, it's a balm
to see you on your feet.
You're going to speak
to the magistrate about this?
Towards what end?
Quintus.
He is a puppet.
What redress would Sextus offer,
when the man who grieved me
holds his strings?
Tullius has always
been a favored son of Capua.
I cannot believe he would be capable
of doing such a thing.
A man of ambition
is capable of anything.
My dealings with the magistrate
take precedence tomorrow.
I would have you greet Varus
in my stead.
The honor would be mine.
The man pisses wine and shits gold.
Varus is but a stream
leading to an ocean of coin...
one I would see break wave
upon our steps.
He comes to choose men?
For the games of the Vinalia,
to ensure his vines bear fruit
in the coming year.
I will present
only our finest gladiators.
I would enrich our stock
and offer him Gannicus as well.
This had best be
the Falernian promised.
If I find you've served
your usual swill,
we will have words.
Put mind to ease.
Tullius.
Note sun and mountains
etched in the amphora...
proof of its authenticity.
Yes, of course.
I was unaware you had an appreciation
for such tastes, Solonius.
A gift for a friend
recovering from unfortunate injury.
Please.
Allow me.
Generous but unnecessary.
I believe it is.
I've done nothing to deserve it.
A matter shortly to be rectified.
Come, I would discuss message
to be delivered with our gift,
better received from your tongue
than mine.
The Gaul is quite the beast.
What name does he take?
Apologies. I do not know.
His name is Crixus.
He trains
in the style of murmillo.
You have an interest
in the games
or does it land only upon the men
who play them?
So easily made to blush...
a sign of tragic inexperience.
I have not turned such a color
since before you were born.
How I envy your youth
and all the wonders
you have yet to discover.
Do not be afraid to pursue
every delight
this world has to offer.
Melitta cautions patience.
Plucking flowers too quickly
will bruise the petals.
Words from a mouth
that has only known
her husband's cock.
You charge like a crazed goat,
absent thought.
When faced
with stronger opponent,
draw him to you, then counter.
Again.
Finally words find way
through thick skull.
Crixus, join the recruits.
Continue your training.
Yes, Doctore.
The mighty Gaul returns.
Or is it his corpse,
too stubborn to fall to grass?
Ah, Dagan expresses his joy
at finding you yet among us.
We feared you were fated
for the mines,
with all the sand
you have been eating.
An acquired taste.
Come, I should serve you
some more.
You've done well with the man.
Crixus is undisciplined
but not without promise.
He brings to thought
a wild fuck I schooled
when we yet called
Batiatus's father Dominus.
I yet feel
the sting of your lessons,
their knowledge now bestowed
upon simple recruits.
I will seek word with Batiatus
towards your return
to the arena.
- Gratitude, Doctore.
- Close fucking mouth.
I but seek not to have wasted
long years
of pulling your head
from your ass.
Doctore,
I require
a more worthy opponent...
perhaps if Oenomaus is finished
sipping drink?
Instruct Gannicus in the ways
of a true champion.
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Do you recall Magnetius
when he fought Trux of the East?
A glorious victory.
For my father.
Hadrianus...
Acerbitas...
Dolor...
Zephyros...
my father's champions,
my grandfather's champions,
the storied history
of the House of Batiatus.
With new chapters
yet to be added.
Etched upon what tablet?
I'm excluded from the games.
Or have such details slipped
memory's grasp?
Apologies. I did not mean...
Fault is mine for baring teeth
at trusted friend.
Gratitude for the gift.
It's well received.
I claim only its delivery.
He's willing to see
his bid for Gannicus doubled.
If accepted, he will grant your men
strong position
in the upcoming games
of the Vinalia.
This wine is from Tullius?
I did not seek him out.
He approached me
in the marketplace,
expressing regret
that his business with you
turned to excess.
He even paid for the wine
that I'd selected for you...
a gesture of goodwill.
- Do you see these marks upon me?
- We must consider...
- Do you fucking see them?
- I see them.
That is the man's true gesture,
the only to be considered.
You counsel to suck the cock
that pisses on me!
I merely counsel reason,
as your father would.
To what purpose?
He brings word and gift
from Tullius,
who yet seeks Gannicus
to swell his ranks.
After what he
fucking did to you?
Well, let us sweep aside
such petty grievances
in service of reason and reward.
He offers twice the sum refused.
And what, I wonder,
does good Solonius receive
for convincing me
to spread cheeks
and accept deeper ramming?
I would share equal position
in the games.
Oh, you are in remarkable condition
to claim my reflection.
Our fates move
towards similar end,
despite outward appearance.
Refuse Tullius's offer,
and I shall join you
in exclusion from the arena.
He makes such a threat?
With exacting clarity.
I did not mean
to see you burdened so.
I will think upon the matter.
Tullius requires answer.
I require a fucking moment!
He wishes to present your man
to Quintilius Varus tomorrow.
Varus? He comes to Capua?
Vettius is to meet him
as he enters the city midday.
I held his acquaintance in Rome...
a man of great influence
and coin.
You would beg
for Tullius' scraps?
Without them, I fear
we shall both go hungry.
Think upon it.
And know that I stand with you,
whatever your decision.
I have witnessed greater spine
within a snail.
What are your thoughts?
Doctore!
Send that fucking man
to the mines.
Do it!
No, Doctore.
No, please, Doctore.
Dominus!
We do not surrender
in this fucking house!
I will see these walls fall to ruin
before missio is given!
It appears decision is made.
Gannicus will one day stand
the Champion of Capua
for the House of Batiatus.
How do we manage such honor
if excluded from the games?
Tullius but brokers interest.
If a man of wealth and position
such as Varus requested my men,
even he would be
unable to refuse.
He meets with Vettius.
You expect that fucking child
to make introduction?
No, I expect him to bleed
as I rip Varus from his grasp.
Halt!
Rest.
Eat.
Ah, your numbers shrink
like frightened cock.
A man is condemned to the mines
and they all fucking jest.
If it were a brother lost,
you would find the mood solemn.
We must earn the fucking mark
to gain respect...
or follow Indus to his fate.
I will not die a faceless slave,
forgotten by history.
We shall rise together.
One day all the Republic
will marvel at the sight of us.
Fucking savages.
They pissed in the porridge.
I have had my fill.
Oh, finally someone who can
hold their wine.
I did not realize
we were for company.
He leaves presently.
Oh please,
after we have finished the jug...
the last of my spoils to be shared
with dearest of friends.
Replace "dearest" with "only"
and sentiment becomes truth.
Settle argument... who was the better man
as we sparred today?
- My husband.
- Ha.
You are swayed
by the title of wife.
One day we shall face each other
upon the sand
and have true decision.
What would really happen
if you had to face each other
sine missione,
no quarter given,
no mercy shown?
I would give your husband
a glorious death.
You joke of killing
a man you love
when someday
you may be asked to.
Oh, you two are a perfect match,
are you not...
both always fretting about
what tomorrow may bring?
We are slaves,
burden of choice and conscience
equally removed.
We are truly free when we fight
or when we fuck, which I shall leave
to do presently.
It is you and my husband
who are of a perfect match...
one hides true thought
in brooding silence,
the other in boastful jest
meant to hold all at a fair distance.
- Melitta.
- I do not hold you at a distance.
You are my two favorite women
in this world.
And what happens,
brave Gannicus,
when presented with circumstance
you cannot laugh
or fight your way clear of?
Well, I may have to
fuck my way clear of it.
Good night.
Gannicus.
Never come up upon my back!
Apologies.
I seek only advice
for coming days.
Heed Oenomaus's instruction...
you will earn your brand.
Till then you stay from sight.
It is not the brand
that concerns me.
It is becoming champion.
There is only one way
to become champion...
never fucking lose.
See Barca readied.
He is to accompany me
to the city.
Another stunt in the market?
Does my last bodyguard's death
fucking elude?
Barca is to serve as such?
He is a gladiator, not...
He is whatever I fucking say.
Have the Syrians also prepared,
absent shackles
and clothed for the streets.
Ashur, Dagan?
What use do you see them to?
None of your concern.
With respect, Dominus,
I am the doctore.
The men are my only concern.
A duty awarded you by my father.
A man who would not condemn
a promising recruit
to the mines out of a mood.
Recruits, gladiators,
even you are but slaves,
mine to command
despite my fucking moods.
You truly believe this man
ripe with potential?
Indus will never be champion,
but he is not without skill.
Have him loaded
with the Syrians.
I will give him opportunity
to prove his worth.
Dominus.
Has Venus herself ever appeared
in such rare form?
You blaspheme.
Frequently and with great relish.
Where is Gaia?
The appointed hour is upon us.
She stands ready.
- Quintus...
- Do not give voice to doubt.
We are committed
and will see this to its end.
You each know your parts.
See this act to successful completion
and earn the mark of the brotherhood.
Without proving ourselves
in the test?
This is your test.
But turn thoughts toward escape
or fail in this charge,
and I will have you parted
from your cocks and crucified.
You're clear to your purpose?
Yes, Dominus.
Take up your positions
and await my signal.
I do not trust the Syrians.
If this does not end
in our favor,
they will appear
as common thieves,
absent my fucking mark upon arm.
This will never work.
Of course it will. Look at you.
What man or otherwise
could resist such charms?
Gaia.
Oh, still fluttering heart.
I would not deny myself such pleasures
if presented again,
yet necessities
shift attention to cock,
and a golden one at that.
You set eyes towards Varus?
He is without wife, last I heard.
We do this to aid my husband,
not to secure one of your own.
He arrives.
Let us end discussion
and set mind to purpose.
Good Vettius,
thank the gods I have found you.
Your gratitude is misplaced.
I do not know you.
I am Varus's man.
He sends word of pressing desire
to see the new arena
before retiring to business.
The arena? No.
I am of clear instruction to meet him
as he enters the city.
Of course. Apologies.
I will deliver word
of your refusal.
Wait.
Varus is honored guest.
As such, I am
but humble servant.
It's quicker, I think,
if we pass through here.
Apologies for the inconvenience.
Dominus will be most pleased
that you've accompanied me.
You've turned yourself about.
This is not the direction
of the fucking arena.
No.
It is not.
We are to leave this one alive,
you simple fuck.
Our charge is met.
I will not see the mines.
I fear they would have been
a blessing.
Apologies, brother.
Vettius saw your face.
Dominus gave instruction.
Where the fuck is Vettius?
Quintilius.
It is you.
Gaia. What finds you
in such horrid climes?
A visit to see dearest friend.
Lucretia.
Lucretia and
her husband Batiatus
are the saving grace
of this ill-bred town.
This is Quintilius Varus,
an acquaintance
of my late husband.
His wine is the toast of Rome.
Your tongue has lost
none of its silver.
It's an honor.
And what good fortune blesses Capua
with your presence?
I come to choose gladiators
for the Vinalia,
or would, if young Vettius
ever deigns to appear.
We shall entertain you with
diverting conversation while you wait.
I fear it shall be
tragically one-sided.
The sun threatens
to bake me senseless.
We cannot have such esteemed guest
expire so, can we?
Well, my husband's villa
is but a little ways from here.
You'd be more than welcome to...
Gratitude, but I would
seek Vettius out
and put foot to ass for his delay.
Lucretia's slaves know the man.
It would be just as easy
for them
to bring him to her villa
when discovered
and give us much needed pause
to reacquaint ourselves.
Well, it would be ungrateful
to refuse such kind offering.
Your villa then.
My husband will be most pleased
to receive you.
What good fortune
to run into you.
The last time I was graced
with Gaia's presence
was at some sober,
airless affair
hosted by...
oh, what was the man's name?
- Atticus.
- Atticus, yes.
Desiccated specimen.
I fear without Gaia's charms,
pronounced boredom
would have carried me to the afterlife
that very night.
Oh, my husband returns.
Fetch more wine.
Lucretia, apologies.
I did not realize
we were to entertain.
An unexpected pleasure
chanced upon in the city.
Quintilius Varus...
an old friend from Rome.
Ah, the name is not unfamiliar.
You honor us with your presence.
The honor is mine, to fall upon
such warm hospitality.
Ah, forgive unsightly
countenance.
A mount long trusted
threw me from purchase.
One must be cautious
when dealing with such animals.
Yeah, a lesson painfully learned.
What finds you so far from Rome?
Games of the Vinalia.
You come to choose men?
I have many fine offerings...
Gannicus in particular.
Apologies. You are a Lanista?
Oh, he has already set purpose
towards Vettius' men.
Ah, well,
fill cup and strike ill-spoken word
from mind.
A thing of no concern.
Vettius will see you well attended.
At considerable savings.
Do I appear so light of purse
to require such?
You have never been so taken
with the games.
I only assumed you would not waste
excessive coin towards them.
True, yet the gods
must be properly honored
and Vettius remains
annoyingly absent.
Your men...
how stand they
in comparison to the boy's?
Well, I would not speak ill
of a brother Lanista.
You are too modest.
Vettius offers shit.
I was told by good Tullius
that his stable is well stocked.
The boy chooses gladiators
as carelessly as his wine...
high quantity
of the lowest quality.
Come, let us sample
a finer vintage.
Please.
Doctore.
Gladiators, form up.
Present yourselves.
Batiatus! Batiatus! Batiatus!
Did I not tell you?
The finest gladiators
in all of Capua.
Hmm, a demonstration perhaps?
Of course.
Gannicus, step forward.
Behold my finest champion.
No man stands his equal.
And who would you have face
this god of the arena?
Barca perhaps or Oenomaus,
who fought so bravely?
What about the Gaul?
Who would not marvel
at seeing such a creature
locked in mortal embrace?
Crixus? Apologies.
The man does not yet bear
the mark of the brotherhood.
Yet he is presented.
I fear such a match
would be overly brief.
A blessing,
considering the heat.
Well, let us move to it then.
Crixus!
Step forward.
A fucking jest.
The House of Batiatus is humbled
by the attentions
of Quintilius Varus.
Let us show him
they are not unwarranted.
Apologies. Are they to use
those little wooden sticks?
Well, it is the tradition
when blood is not the purpose.
So they are to fight
as children, not men?
Why, I would not see you
to such an impression.
Doctore, have wood
give way to steel.
Gladius.
The gods have heard you.
They present opportunity
to become champion.
Begin.
Oenomaus has trained you well.
Yet you are a pale imitation
of the man.
You lie. I did no such thing.
A fine attempt.
Has there ever before been
such a demonstration?
What say you, good Varus?
Should the Gaul live or die?
Well, Gaia chose the man,
let the choice be hers.
Let him live.
He may yet find his use.
What of my man Gannicus?
Did you find him to your liking?
The man is weary
from his travels.
Let us not press him
with further business.
Come see yourself inside
to sample other indulgences.
Some delights
from Cyprus perhaps?
A region I'm most fond of.
As I recall.
What the fuck are you doing?
What I do best.
Varus is a man
of particular appetites
which grow strong
under influence of wine and opium.
See your man Gannicus
oiled and scented,
to be presented
as the hour passes.
I risk all to lure Varus
to our house
only to find I am no longer
the fucking master of it.
She knows the man
more intimately than we do.
We must lend her our trust.
Let us pray it is not soiled
upon return.
See Gannicus prepared
and brought up to the villa.
And what will be
required of him?
Whatever I fucking desire.
Ashur and Dagan returned absent Indus.
Did he not prove himself?
He did, and was well-rewarded.
And the Syrians...
are they to be rewarded as well?
With the mark of the brotherhood.
The mark?
Without proving themselves
in the test?
They proved themselves in my test.
See it done.
- Your father would never approve.
- I am not my fucking father!
A fact well-known.
See to Gannicus,
brand the fucking Syrians
and inform Oenomaus
that he is to assume
mantle of doctore.
Dominus.
You are a relic,
as is my father...
shadows from the past,
soon to fade from memory.
See to Gannicus.
See how it caresses the wine?
Is there anything so enticing?
I have seen its rival.
This house indeed offers
many pleasures.
With more yet to be presented.
Pleasing this man must now become
your sole fucking purpose.
Please him? In what manner?
I have had my fill of being
questioned by slaves.
If Varus wishes you
to suck his cock dry,
you will savor every drop.
Are we of a singular mind?
Dominus.
In honor of distinguished guest,
I present my finest man
for your personal viewing.
Behold Gannicus,
yours to command.
You are quite the Lanista,
Batiatus.
I have never been so well-plied
towards aid of a sale.
This is not about business.
This is how they live.
They grab life and squeeze
until the juice flows.
How do you always come by
such marvelous acquaintance?
It is a gift.
One among many set before me.
Is he not of a form...
our champion?
I have not seen his like.
And more than a few
have stood before me.
The man stands as a god,
the arena his Olympus.
He once thrust a blade so deep
into an opponent's breast
that tears turned to blood.
I'm not impressed
by inflated tales.
My interests are grounded
in what I can see,
what I can touch.
Now that is impressive.
Are you as skilled in its use
as you are with a sword?
I would have demonstration.
The man is yours.
We will lend privacy.
No, you mistake intent.
No, I've had too much wine
and other pleasures
for such rough exertion.
No, I would prefer
a feast of the eyes.
Oh, have him fuck this one
and I shall watch.
Apologies.
For what? Is she not a slave?
She is and will do as commanded.
Welcome to the fucking
brotherhood.
- Why are we gathered?
- The Syrians receive the mark.
Absent the test?
Wait, are we not
to recite the oath?
I will not see more shit
heaped upon sacred rites.
You may bear the mark, but don't
ever think yourself a gladiator,
you little cunt.
Doctore!
Do not fucking speak to me
in such tone.
Apologies.
You believe yourself my equal,
Oenomaus?
No, Doctore.
Gladius...
bring fucking swords.
Now let us see
if you have learned
all I have to teach.
Remove her dress.
Is that what I taught you,
Oenomaus...
- Doctore.
- How to turn upon heel?
Doctore.
Doctore, stop.
Fight me, you coward.
- Melitta, l...
- See it done.
Prove yourself worthy, Oenomaus.
I taught you well.
- The man is dead?
- I did not want it.
He forced me to fight.
And I do not know the reason
for his anger toward me.
The reason falls
to my own tongue.
Earlier I revealed intent
of raising you
to position of doctore.
I am not to return to the arena?
You are beyond such things now,
proven by your training
of Crixus.
Let us put the past behind us
and look to future glories.
My wife... I know it
is not our time,
but I would ask to see her.
I will send her to you
when she has finished her duties.
Gratitude.
Apologies. The demands
of a Lanista seldom offer respite.
Oh, none required.
This night has been filled
with unexpected joys.
You remain in Capua?
Until more adventurous
opportunities present themselves.
Ahh.
I'll take my leave then
with promise of further discourse.
Oh, your man Gannicus...
I would see him perform again
in the primus of my games.
And you shall have him.
Terms to be discussed.
Gratitude for your hospitality.
It will not soon be forgot.
Primus?
Did I not tell you
I knew the man?
May the gods strike me
for entertaining doubt.
You were magnificent.
Did I not tell you?
You have elevated this house.
Yet speak of how we came
by such honor
and see brotherhood shattered
and a husband lost.
I have done a terrible thing.
We do what we must
in this house.