(dog barking)
(clattering)
(barking continues)
(panting)
(breathing heavily)
(gasping)
(engines revving)
(tires screeching)
Find it.
(grunting)
Alas... it has come
to this, Mr. Chang.
(weapon powering up)
What a dreary setting
for your final stand.
(clunking)
How long have you been running?
Are you not tired?
Be reasonable.
Give me the amulet
and walk away.
I'll even
pay you for your troubles.
(gasping)
(man)
A king's fortune.
Sorry.
Idiot.
You see, I am not
a cruel man, Chang.
I have no wish to shed blood.
But do not take this to mean...
I won't.
(weapon powering up)
(groaning)
(breathing heavily)
So nice of you to drop in.
I think it's
fair to say, Mr. Chang,
the amulet is finally mine.
Time to let it go.
As you wish.
No!
Find me that amulet!
♪♪
(clanking)
(boy)
Hello there.
Manny Garcia.
Nice to meet you.
Manny Garcia, gosh, oh golly,
it is my pleasure
to, uh...
make your acquaintance.
(dog whimpering)
Remember, Rufus, you only get
one chance to make
a first impression.
Blow that and all your
hopes and dreams wash away.
(whimpering)
So I gotta nail this.
Okay, Rufus?
(barking)
I'll try...
Garcia...
Manny Garcia.
(whimpering)
Oh... sorry.
How about...
yo, yo, yo,
Manny G is in the house?
(barking)
(man)
Manny G is in
the bathroom.
(knocking)
And he's been
in there all morning.
At the moment,
this house only has
one working bathroom, Manny.
I need to get in there.
Sorry, Dad,
it's just the first day
at a new school, in a new town.
I gotta perfect my Manny mojo.
Your mojo will be fine.
Just be yourself.
"Be yourself."
That's all you got?
Son, I gotta go.
"Be yourself" is not bad advice.
You're a wonderful young man.
Look at this face.
Who wouldn't want to
be friends with you?
(barking)
See, even Rufus agrees.
♪♪
Manny Garcia, Sagittarius.
Hi, I'm Manny.
Rhymes with "fanny."
Ah, definite nope.
Whoa, lots of new faces.
Whoa.
Controversy.
New school colors take Taft.
The old cobalt
and white are out.
Red and blue are in.
Where do you stand,
student on the street?
Um...
Don't have a strong opinion yet.
I was in Texas until
like last week.
(gasping)
You're new.
Apologies.
Paige Prescott.
Ace reporter for
"The Taft Tattler."
Ah, Manny Garcia,
ace... new kid.
Well, welcome to
Taft Middle School,
Manny Garcia from Texas.
Hey, one more
man-on-the-street question.
Our spring dance is just
around the corner.
Theme is still open and
suggestions are welcome.
What gets you up and moving?
Uh, I guess my dog, mostly.
Dogs?
Hmm, K-9 themed.
Original.
I shall suggest this
to the committee.
(school bell ringing)
Interview over.
Well, here we are.
School sweet school.
And the new colors look good.
You're gonna do great.
Thanks.
And, um, anytime you wanna
interview me, I'm there.
Manny Garcia, I think you're
gonna fit right in at Taft.
Yeah, I think so.
Oh!
(all laughing)
Oh...
(cell phones clicking)
Now, that's
front-page material.
Oh...
Sorry, Manny, we're not
moving back to Texas.
Connecticut's where
our jobs are at now.
How bad can it be?
I was blue!
Okay, the whole school
saw it happen.
I know it wasn't
an ideal first day
but it'll get better.
It was embarrassing.
Okay, I have no friends here.
(barking)
I wouldn't say
"no friends."
Yeah, you've got the best
one ever right there.
And he's been
stuck inside all day.
Come on, Rufus, I found
a cool park near by.
Whoa, boy.
Whoa, hey, boy.
Okay, easy, easy.
Can you get it?
Bet you can't.
Come on, there are rules
to this game, all right?
Easy.
(laughing)
(barking)
There she is coming up.
Looking to the left,
looking to the right.
Can Rufus steal?
Oh no, he can't.
Garcia gets it.
Squirrel!
Got ya.
And goal!
(barking)
Rufus, where are you going?
No, no, no.
Rufus...
Oh...
Dude, you're a soaking mess.
Mom's gonna kill us.
What's that?
A necklace?
What, you wanna wear it?
There, now you're the coolest
dog in all of Connecticut.
Happy?
Ahh...
Oh man,
wet-dog smell.
Come on, Rufus,
we gotta go home.
I can't believe I have to go
back to that school tomorrow.
What a first impression.
Let's get some sleep.
(barking)
Don't worry, you can keep
your new necklace on.
Here.
Go to bed, boy.
Come on.
♪♪
Good night, buddy.
You're a good friend.
In fact, in this town,
you're my only friend.
(barking)
I just wished you were
the kind of friend who could
talk back, be there
for me at school.
Maybe make my life
not so generally... lame.
♪♪
(Dad)
Manny, rise and shine!
Okay, Dad,
I'm rising, I'm rising.
Rufus, are you ready
to start our day?
Rufus, are you awake?
Ahh!
Ahh, whoa!
Okay, who are you?
It's me, Rufus.
I've always wanted to
try out this people fur.
It's clingy, I like it.
No, you can't be Rufus.
What did you do with my dog?
I'm a boy now.
Wow, isn't this awesome?!
Oh, wait, I got an itch.
Oh boy.
(groaning)
There we go, okay.
Ooh... ooh!
All right, yeah,
that's the sweet spot.
Wait, a little bit,
a little bit.
There we go, okay.
You can't be Rufus,
you can't be.
I would like a treat now!
Was it that thing, the necklace?
Is it magic?
I would like one treat, please.
And, oh man, I did say
I wish you were a kid.
Mm-hmm, duck,
chicken, jerky...
I'm not that picky.
You gotta give me
that necklace.
I have to turn you
into a dog again.
Whoa, no, no, no,
hey, hey!
What if I wanna be a boy?
You can't be a boy.
You're a dog.
(Dad)
Hey, Manny.
Hmm?
Dad.
♪♪
Hey, Dad.
I'm up, I'm very up.
So up.
(whimpering)
Stop goofing around with Rufus
and let's get ready for school.
Okay?
Okay.
(barking)
Bye.
I'm a boy again!
(sighing)
Whoa.
I got thumbs now.
What am I gonna
do with you?
(panting)
I can't leave you here...
unless you give me
that necklace.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hey, no, no, no!
Hey, hey, hey, no,
not until I've eaten pizza
and learn how to play the piano
and pee standing up.
What am I gonna do?
I can't take you to school.
Why not?
I mean, you wished for a friend
you could take to school, right?
Well, here I am,
your best friend, right?
So take me to school already.
I guess I could pass you
off as a normal kid.
Would it work?
Oh, yeah, I'm very normal.
Wait!
Where... where...
Where's my tail?
Wait, wait, where's my tail?
How... how will I know
when I'm happy?
(gasping)
I can give you
the thumbs-up.
Problem solved.
(laughing)
These people furs are tight.
Why do you guys wear these?
If we don't wear pants,
we end up in the people kennel.
What?
Here.
These might fit you better.
Catch.
(growling)
♪♪
Later, Mom and Dad.
Don't wanna be
late on my second day.
Love school.
Bye.
Yeah, later,
Mom and Dad.
Shh!
Okay, we made it out okay.
But if you're
gonna be a normal boy,
you gotta start acting like one.
Wow!
I can be normal, Manny.
(barking)
Oh, hey, Larry!
What's up?
How's it going, man?
Yeah, oh...
All right, all right,
sniff you later.
(laughing)
FYI, the generic kidney
and trout you're feeding Larry
is giving him gas.
Um, good to know.
Spend a buck.
I'm sorry.
That's what I'm talking about.
(farting)
Sorry, Larry.
I've been watching
you for years, Manny.
Dog years... do you know
how long that is?
I can be normal...
(squirrel chattering)
A squirrel, a squirrel!
Squirrel!
I want the squirrel,
I'm gonna get you!
Just get away, just get away!
Dude, you're human now,
get a grip.
You don't get it, Manny.
It's a squirrel.
Buddy, I get it, okay,
but why do dogs hate
squirrels
so much anyway?
Oh...
If only you knew the evil
behind their bushy tails.
The stories I could tell you.
The things dogs have seen.
This is gonna work
but you gotta blend in.
Okay, no chasing squirrels,
just don't be weird.
Okay?
Rufus?
Oh... you're not doing
what I think you're
doing, are you?
What, aren't we
going for a walk?
This is what I always do
when we go for a walk.
Seriously?
Did you not bring a bag?
This is awkward.
(school bell ringing)
Hmm...
Your cousin.
Yes, he's, uh, visiting...
from somewhere for, uh,
I don't know how long.
(sniffing)
You have cats, don't you?
I smell cats, do you smell cats?
(all laughing)
Hmm...
Seems weird.
But they don't
pay me enough to care.
Okay, Rufus, sit.
(all laughing)
I meant in a chair.
Oh!
I'm not allowed to sit
on the furniture at home.
(all laughing)
Uh... okay.
(mumbling)
(sniffing)
(all laughing)
So...
What?
We were talking about
themes of transformation
in Kafka's "Metamorphosis."
You are hilarious, dog.
Oh...
Thanks but I'm not a dog.
I'm a human boy.
(all laughing)
With squirrels,
the key is to get it
before it gets in the tree
'cause once they're
in the tree, it's over.
What's up?
Well, see you later, Rufus.
What's your name again?
Manny.
Oh, right, Marty.
Dude, your cousin is awesome.
Catch you guys later.
Okay, later.
And it's Manny.
Did I do good?
Yeah, really good, Rufus.
Oh, so we can play ball now?
No.
We've got more classes.
More?
Man...
(ball bouncing)
(gasping)
He's got a ball!
Ball, ball,
ball, ball...
Here, boy!
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Doing what you're doing ♪
♪ Every time
you move to the beat ♪
♪ It gets harder for me ♪
♪ And you know it,
know it ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Doing what you're doing ♪
♪ Every time
you move to the beat ♪
♪ It gets harder for me ♪
♪ And you know it,
know it, know it ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Doing what you're doing ♪
♪ Every time
you move to the beat ♪
♪ It gets harder for me ♪
♪ And you know it,
know it, know it ♪
♪ And don't stop ♪
♪ 'Cause you know
that I like it ♪
♪ Every time
you walk in the room ♪
♪ You got all eyes on you ♪
♪ And you know it, know it,
know it, know it ♪
♪ And don't stop ♪
♪ 'Cause you know
that I like it ♪
♪ Every time
you walk in the room ♪
♪ You got all eyes
on you ♪
♪ And you know it ♪
♪ Every day
it's the same ♪
♪ All the games that you play ♪
♪ Back and forth
round and round ♪
♪ Kinda like it this way ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Doing what you're doing ♪
♪ 'Cause every time
you move to the beat ♪
♪ It gets harder for me ♪
♪ And you know it,
know it, know it ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ 'Cause you know that
I like it ♪
♪ Every time
you walk in the room ♪
♪ You got all eyes on you ♪
♪ And you know it,
know it, know it ♪
Squirrel!
Hey, don't go behind that tree!
I got you, I got you!
It's just a squirrel.
♪ Every time you move to the
beat it gets harder for me ♪
♪ And you know it,
know it, know it ♪♪
(whistle blowing)
(man)
So you're telling me there's
no sign of that amulet?
I'm sorry, Mr. Black,
but we've searched everywhere.
I have devoted countless years
to finding that amulet,
unthinkable sums of money...
I will not give up!
Okay.
But it's gonna take a miracle.
(squirrel chattering)
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
(tires screeching)
Whoa!
Sorry, sorry!
My friend here has
a real problem
with squirrels.
Hey.
(squirrel chattering)
♪♪
Hey, what's that?
Rufus, wait!
A miracle indeed.
(laughing maniacally)
♪♪
Dude, dude, you gotta
rein that in, okay?
Squirrels are not
worth getting run over for.
Squirrels are evil, Manny.
They have big plans,
terrible plans,
plans humans couldn't
even comprehend.
Sure, okay, right,
evil squirrels, whatever.
Tell you what, I'm hungry.
How about a snack,
okay, your choice?
(dog barking)
Really?
I love Power Puppy Kibble
so much.
Okay, whatever,
if you want Power Puppy,
I'll buy you Power Puppy.
Oh, sweet!
(bells jingling)
Paige!
Oh, kittens!
I love kittens!
All dogs secretly do.
The problem are cats.
I hate cats.
Quiet.
Maybe she'll see us.
Who?
Paige.
She's a girl from my school.
I met her on my first day.
Oh, so she's a friend.
Not exactly.
I mean, I'd like her
to be but I'm afraid...
Hey, Paige!
What are you doing?
Well, you said you wanted
her to be your friend.
Paige, over here!
Hi, Paige.
No, no, no, bad, Rufus.
I'm Rufus.
Uh, hi.
You go to my school, right?
You're Manny's cousin.
Oh, right.
I wanted to let you know
that Manny's afraid to...
Afraid I'm covered in kittens.
Oh!
So cute.
Yeah, you think that...
before they dig their claws in.
Oh...
So, uh, what's the news
at school?
Any big scoops coming up?
(chuckling)
Page one is you two.
From out of nowhere,
you guys are
the two most
popular dudes in school.
Okay, popular twins,
catch you later.
My goldfish gets
grumpy when it's hungry.
Later.
(bells jingling)
(coughing)
You are the best wingman ever.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I don't have wings.
It just means if you
look good, I look good.
It's win-win.
Oh, it means good.
The point is you rock.
The target is coming your way.
We're ready.
Thanks to you, I've got
the town eating out of
the palm of my hand.
I love eating out of
the palm of your hand.
Know what
we're doing today?
Chase squirrels.
Yes, we're gonna
chase some squirrels.
What a...
What a great idea.
I got this.
(groaning)
(Rufus)
Why am I the only one
who wants to do that?
I feel like... I feel
like you don't get me.
I smell garbage.
(sighing)
Idiot.
Manny, did you know about this?
The dance.
Oh yeah.
They used my suggestion.
They're going to the dogs.
I guess Paige really sold it.
Awesome!
She's the best.
You should ask
Paige to the dance.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe?
(Mom)
Manny?
Where's Rufus?
Uh, I haven't seen him.
Why?
He chewed my
patent leather shoe.
I can't even find the other one.
Ugh, that dog!
Dude?
You ate my mom's shoe so she
still thinks we have a dog?
Genius.
Right, 'cause that's
totally why I did that.
You wanna know what else I did?
I pooped behind the couch.
(laughing)
Why wouldn't you ask
Paige to the dance?
She's really pretty.
Yes, she is...
Whatever.
(cell phone ringing)
(sniffing)
Hello.
Manny Garcia.
Hey, Paige.
I was jus t talking about you
with my...
um, dog... yo.
(laughing)
Yeah, dog, that's funny.
What's up?
Well, being the school's
top newspaper reporter...
okay, only newspaper reporter,
I was wondering if I could
score an exclusive interview
with Taft's most interesting
new student?
I'm pretty sure
I can arrange that.
Awesome!
Have Rufus meet me after
school tomorrow
on the quad.
Wait, what?
Rufus.
I wanna interview Rufus.
Oh, right, Rufus.
Popular guy, class clown.
The big dog.
Right!
So you'll set it up?
Yeah, I will.
Awesome.
Later.
I mean...
who would want to interview me?
I'd interview you.
You're almost out of popcorn.
♪♪
Me?
Paige wants to interview me?
Yes, you.
Wow.
Me?
Yes, you.
Are you mad about
something?
No.
Uh, you sure?
I'm not.
You sound kinda mad.
Like that time I chewed up
your baseball glove.
Okay, it's a little
annoying that you...
I got this.
(Manny)
I like to do things a lot.
(Rufus)
Like play catch.
Time to wrap things up.
(horn honking)
Idiot.
(Paige)
Thanks for agreeing to
do this interview, Rufus.
Oh, of course.
I think newspapers
are very important.
You do?
People need newspapers
to do their business.
I've been
doing my business on them
ever since I was a pup.
Finally!
Someone gets it.
Yeah.
So, Rufus, over night...
(sniffing)
you've become the most
popular kid in school.
How does that feel?
Weird.
Because you're the new kid?
Because I'm new at being a kid.
(ball bouncing)
Ball!
(laughing)
You are funny.
Is that your secret
to making friends?
Uh... sort of.
I mean, when I see someone new,
I kinda just bounce around
them 'til they smile
and then... boom...
Instant friends.
Works with everybody.
Well, except cats.
Dogged determination.
I like that.
(recorder beeping)
Now, Rufus, the whole
school wants to know,
will you be taking a special
someone to the dance?
Well, Paige, turns out I've
been meaning to talk to you
about that very subject.
(cheers and applause)
♪♪
(Rufus)
So, guys, best in show,
you know who to vote for.
The big dog, am I right?
Yeah.
♪♪
♪ Let's make some noise ♪
♪ You thro w
your hands up ♪
♪ You throw you r
hands up ♪
♪ Make some noise ♪
♪ Your body's stomping t o
the beat of ♪
♪ Beat of... ♪
Oh, hey.
(girl)
Yeah, let's go dance.
♪ Raise your voic e
girls and boys ♪
♪ And mak e
some noise ♪♪
A real human dance.
So cool.
Yeah, cool.
I mean, there's
music and friends
and they're gonna announce
best in show
and... ooh, ooh...
I'm pretty sure I know
who it's gonna be.
Congratulations
in advance, Rufus.
And the best part
is my big surprise.
Paige.
Who told you?
I'm gonna...
go get some punch.
(barking rhythmically)
♪♪
Huh?
Yo, dog, this is your song.
(barking rhythmically)
This is my song.
Come dance.
♪ Hey ♪
(barking rhythmically)
♪ Roor ♪
Whoo!
♪ Hey ♪
(barking rhythmically)
♪ You thin k
you're top dog ♪
♪ You think you'r e
top dog ♪
Yo!
♪ You thin k
you're top dog ♪
♪ Go ♪
♪ You think you're top dog ♪
♪ Go, go, go,
go, go, go ♪
♪ Go, go,
go, go, go, go ♪
♪ You think you're top dog ♪
♪ All righ t ♪
All right!
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ You think you're top dog ♪
♪ In the hous e
on the street ♪
♪ On the bloc k
off the leash ♪
♪ You think you're top dog ♪
♪ Dog, dog, dog, dog, dog,
dog, dog, dog, dog, dog, dog ♪
♪ You think you're top dog ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go, go ♪♪
(cheers and applause)
(howling)
♪♪
Manny, did you see?
I made a dance.
It's amazing what you can do
when your knees
bend the other way.
Being a human boy is even
better than I ever dreamed.
Yeah, awesome.
I'm sure your date loves
the dance too.
Probably gonna write a
front-page article about it.
"Dog Dude Designs
Dumb Dance."
Manny?
This move has been really
hard for me, Rufus.
Somehow you've made my
terrible life even worse.
And ever since you've put
that necklace on,
you've been...
A bad dog?
A bad friend.
(whimpering)
Hey there, Manny.
Your date just left.
Um, you're standing
right in front of me.
What are you talking about?
Rufus is your date.
Oh, news flash.
You are my date.
What?
Rufus asked me out for you.
Turns out I've been
meaning to talk to you
about that very subject.
Will you go to the dance with...
my best friend Manny?
I would love to.
Rufus did that for me?
Yeah.
He said you were too
shy to do it yourself.
Oh man.
I think I just stepped
in a big pile of...
(man)
Manny Garcia and Paige Prescott,
come on up!
You're best in show
of the dance!
(cheers and applause)
Whoo, that's right!
Give it up for your
royal couple!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Now, don't you two
look surprised.
I thought it was gonna be Rufus.
It was Rufus' idea.
(all)
Yeah.
You know who to vote for.
The big dog, am I right?
The big dog!
And you guys know
who the big dog is?
That's right, my boy Manny.
All right.
But what about me?
That was his idea too.
And vote for Paige too 'cause
Manny really likes her.
So how does it feel to be king?!
Right now, I don't feel
like a king.
I feel like
a low-down dirty dog.
Thank you, everyone...
for this very kind
and thoughtful honor.
But... after the way
I treated my friend,
my best friend,
there's...
no way I can accept this.
What?
I also cannot accept.
If you read
my three-part series,
"The Shameful Sham Of Class
102's Homeroom President,"
then you know I find
these popularity contests
objectifying and demeaning.
On the other hand...
tiaras are kind of cute.
(scattered applause)
Rufus?
Hey, Rufus.
Manny.
What's going on?
Paige, I can't
explain it to you.
You'd never believe...
me.
Rufus is a dog.
How could you
possibly know that?
A reporter's instinct.
And he told me.
Oh, and also...
I'g.a do
That would be D-O...
A dog?
(Paige)
Told me about
the magic necklace,
your wish and everything.
Of course he did.
Look, I owe Rufus
a huge apology.
Can you help me find him?
You go that way,
I'll go this way.
We meet on the other
side of the library.
Thanks, Paige.
Rufus, where are you, boy?
(howling in the distance)
Rufus?
(Dad)
Hey, Linda,
did you walk the dog?
Nope, did you?
No.
I haven't seen him either.
Maybe he's eating
your wedding dress.
It'll match your shoes.
That's not funny.
Rufus?
Rufus... Rufus?
(whistling)
Rufus?
Rufus... Rufus?
He's not here.
We lost the dog.
(sighing)
This move has been hard
enough on Manny.
If we lost his dog,
he'll hate life forever.
Remember when we
had Rufus tagged
with the GPS chip
and you thought it
was a waste of money?
(beeping)
I may have been
wrong on that one.
He is at the school?
Let's go!
Give me the keys!
You drive too slow!
(tires screeching)
(cat shrieking)
Rufus?
Rufus, buddy...
you there?
(howling in the distance)
Is that you?
Look, I'm sorry
I was being such a jerk.
(howling in the distance)
Rufus?
(howling)
You're not here
for the dance, are you?
Let's go!
Hey, let me go!
You're coming
with us, kid.
Where are you taking me?
Help!
(Rufus howling)
Manny?
(howling continues)
(Manny)
Help, let me go!
(woman)
Let's go!
Let me go!
Help, please!
What do you want?!
Rufus?
What's wrong?
Manny's in trouble.
Manny?!
Paige...
(tires screeching)
those men just
took my best friend
but why would they...
They're working for
the squirrels, aren't they?
No, Rufus.
This is why.
All right, I'll bite.
What do you want with me?
With you?
(chuckling)
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Think about it.
This magic thing, this amulet
must have incredible power
and be crazy valuable,
so someone must be
looking for it.
Rufus, we gotta
find Manny right away!
I can do that!
(sniffing)
But not with this nose.
Follow me.
(barking)
Rufus, wait for me!
(Manny)
Where are you taking me?
(Mr. Black)
To a place your dear Rufus
won't be able to resist.
We've gotta find that dog.
Manny will be crushed!
Crushed!
Get a grip!
Do not go soft on me!
(whimpering)
Come on, Rufus,
don't lose the scent.
You can do this.
Find Manny.
Go, Rufus!
I don't like
the looks of this place.
Ha.
You drag me into a creepy
warehouse
in the middle of nowhere
and think I'm gonna worry?
My best friend will find me
wherever you take me.
Oh, we're counting on that.
Oh.
This is a trap and I'm the bait.
Clever boy.
But children should be seen...
(muffled shouting)
and not heard.
I understand a certain
K-9 with a very...
♪♪
I found him!
I found him, Manny's in there.
(sniffing)
Oh, I smell my favorite snack.
Power Puppy Kibble.
My nose is never wrong.
It must be in that huge
barrel of dog food.
Shh, Rufus.
They took Manny
knowing you'd come for him.
They're expecting you
and the amulet.
I got an idea.
Let's give them
something they don't expect.
Yeah.
♪♪
Eight years I've been
hunting down that amulet...
across six continents.
But now I'm not pursuing it.
It's being delivered to
me on a silver platter.
Or should I say
a golden Labrador?
(laughing maniacally)
Excuse me.
Are you the owner
and/or proprietor
of this property?
May I ask who's inquiring?
Paige Prescott, ace reporter.
My paper's doing a feature:
"Wild Warehouses
Of The Westside."
Who lives here?
Why live here?
Could I get a quick comment?
Unfortunately...
we have no comment.
Now, off you go, little girl.
This can be a very unsafe place
and we have work to do.
(barking)
You!
Now, Rufus!
(yelling)
(laughing)
(barking)
There it is!
(growling)
Get that dog!
(weapon powering up)
(muffled shouting)
Hey, you okay?
I'm better now.
(Manny)
Don't worry about it.
I'll get the rest, you go find
Rufus and let's get out of here.
♪♪
(Mr. Black)
Here, Rufus!
I think I hear him.
It sounds like he's over here.
Uh-oh.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
You're not going anywhere
until we find that dog.
Stay.
Or I'll make you stay.
(chuckling)
(groaning)
Hey...
(machine whirring)
Hey, hey, hey!
(shouting)
(Dad)
Turn right here!
(Mom)
Okay, I'm turning,
I'm turning!
What is this place?
Rufus?
Rufus, come.
(whimpering)
♪♪
(laughing)
Rufus, shake.
Look, man, I'm sorry about
what I said at the dance.
I should've known
you would never hurt me.
Whatever I am, boy or dog,
always remember, Manny...
I just wanna be your friend.
I...
You do not lick my face.
So have we kicked
enough butt here?
Violence as a means
to resolve conflict.
Children, what are they
teaching you in school?
Oh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
gym, math, his-history...
I wish I could end this in
a more civilized manner,
but I want that amulet
in the worst possible way.
Now, who wants
a doggy nap?
(weapon powering up)
♪♪
Eeny...
meeny...
miny...
boy!
Manny!
No!
(chuckling)
(whimpering)
Now give me that amulet!
Sorry to crush your dream.
(screaming)
(laughing)
Oh no.
Rufus.
(whimpering)
No, you can't leave me.
(Manny)
You gotta be okay.
You're my best friend.
My best friend.
(whimpering)
(crying)
Dude?
It didn't even hit you.
Get up, you big baby.
(barking)
Oh, Rufus, you're okay.
Come on, buddy.
You're fine, Rufus.
(barking)
(laughing)
Oh...
He may be okay but
the amulet is done for.
I guess Rufus is
stuck being a dog.
Not just any dog.
My best friend.
Oh...
Oh, Rufus, is all right.
What a relief.
(Mr. Black groaning)
Rufus may be fine,
but something else
here sure isn't.
Hello, police.
Manny, are you all right, son?
Yeah, I'm better, Dad.
(laughing)
Better than ever.
(Mr. Black)
We barely escaped before
the authorities arrived!
If you let me live,
I will do everything in my
power to help you
fulfill your master plan.
(chattering)
You failed me for the last time.
Idiot!
(screaming)
(laughing maniacally)
(Manny)
Get it, boy, get it,
boy, get it, boy!
Get it, boy!
Get the ball, get the ball.
(barking)
That is one
happy hound.
Yeah.
(barking)
So nobody legit
will run your story?
"The Crazy World Weekly"
was very interested.
"The New York Times,"
not so much.
The story of a lifetime.
Pulitzer Prize material.
And no one believes
a single word of it.
If I hadn't lived it,
I wouldn't believe it myself.
(barking)
There'll be other stories.
You'll get your Pulitzer.
Do you think
he misses being a boy?
(growling)
Rufus said it himself.
Boy or a dog, he just
wants to be my friend.
And, you know, who knows?
Maybe he'll be
a boy again someday.
Stranger things have happened.
♪♪
Get it, boy, get the ball!
(barking)
(laughing)
(Manny)
Come on, come on, Rufus!
(barking)