Oh, sorry.
I thought you were gone.
Ron, this is
my bathroom.
If you're gonna
stay here,
you're gonna
have to use
the bathroom downstairs.
Dad's in that one.
Well, then,
you're going to
have to wait.
How long?
Close the door.
(SIGHS)
(MAN GARGLING)
(RON SIGHS)
(ELECTRIC TRIMMER BUZZING)
Shit.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
(URINE SPLASHING)
What the hell
are you doing?
God! God, Jesus!
Dad, um...
Your mother
puts orange juice
in that thing.
I'm... I'm gonna wash it.
I... I was just...
Can I have some
privacy please?
Well, where do you
want me to go?
Just, away! I can't...
I can't pee while
you're looking at me!
(THUD)
Sally?
What are you doing
on the floor, Chief?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
I... I can't...
What's going on?
Dad!
The curling iron!
Come on, Chief, get up.
Oh, my God.
Can't move.
Okay.
Dad, call an ambulance.
Okay. It's okay.
You're okay.
I know the dog days
Of the summer
Have you
ten-to-one outnumbered
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(BEEPS)
Routledge Publishing.
John. It's me.
Becca, I'm so sorry.
I know I missed
the appointment.
I, uh... I got swamped.
I thought I was
going to make it, but...
(OVER PHONE)  Doctor say,
"Baby looks good"?
Yeah, it was fine.
We can talk about
it another time.
Oh, okay. Um...
Could I actually call you
in a few minutes?
I'm going through
a little bit of
a thing here at work
and...
Hey.
How did you even
get in here?
I thought you
needed a card to...
John, listen. Um...
Your dad called me,
and, um,
he wanted me
to tell you...
JOHN: My dad called you?
Your mom had
a seizure this morning,
and they think that it
might be a brain tumor.
What?
So, um, I booked
you a flight
that's going to get
you in around, uh, 3:30.
I know this is a lot.
But your mother's in
the hospital, so, um...
You do need to go now.
Yeah.
I'm a man on fire
Walking through your street
With one guitar
And two dancing feet
Only one desire
That's left in me
I want the whole damn world
To come dance with me
Oh
Come dance with me
Over murder and pain
Come and set you free
Over heartache and shame
I wanna see
our bodies burning
Like the old big sun
I wanna know what we've been
learning and learning from
Huh. Look at
that kitchen.
I'd get rid of
that ugly island.
Take the whole wall out.
Great idea.
What are they asking?
Uh, $300.
For that?
I wouldn't even
walk by that house.
(LAUGHS)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
No.
Never! Never.
Can't be.
Do you think they pay
for their own labor?
No, has to be donated.
Let's watch  The Brothers.
No.
Just knock it down
and start again.
Hey, Mom.
Oh, my goodness.
How did you know?
Don!
(LAUGHS)
How you doing, Dad?
It's great
to see you, son.
Good to see you, too.
Come give Mom a hug.
How you doing, Mom?
I'm doing great.
Feeling all right?
Doing great. Doing great.
What happened
to your wrist?
Brain tumor.
Have you been smoking?
No.
You smell like an ashtray.
I don't know...
John.
Don't lie to your mother.
She almost died today.
What?
RON: She didn't almost die.
DON: That's not
what the doctor said.
He wasn't a doctor.
He was a nurse.
We haven't seen
a doctor yet.
And you're scaring Mom.
I'm not scared. I just...
I just don't want John
dying of lung cancer.
I only had one, so...
SALLY: Well,
don't have another one.
You're going to
be a father soon.
I know.
That guy was a nurse?
Yeah.
He was in John's
class in high school.
Who was?
Jason.
Jason... Jason Owens?
He married Gwen.
Wow.
Mmm-hmm.
Just had a kid.
JOHN: Really?
I can't believe I
didn't know that.
You never call, so...
Who's Gwen?
Gwen. Gwen?
Johnny's girlfriend
in high school.
They were engaged,
for God's sake.
John had
a girlfriend
in high school?
Don!
It was complicated, Dad.
It was...
Jesus Christ, Dad,
where have you been
our whole lives anyway?
Work... I've been
working to send
you kids to college,
that's where I've been.
Yeah. A lot of good
that did.
What did...
What did you say?
Nothing.
No, what did you just
say to me right now?
How long has
she been married?
RON: I didn't say anything.
About a year.
You better watch yourself.
Oh, is that a threat?
No, that's a promise.
RON: (SCOFFS)
It doesn't even make sense.
I'll punch you
in the face.
(LAUGHS) What?
I swear to God I will.
Really?
Yeah.
What's stopping you?
What... (GROANS)
Guys.
Don, you apologize
to Ron right now!
All right, Ronnie,
I'm sorry,
but you can't be...
Yeah.
Oh!
Guys, are you kidding me?
He... Did you see?
JOHN: Guys.
Guys.
Guys!
SALLY: Boys!
JOHN: Guys!
What?
(MAN CLEARS THROAT)
Uh, Sally Hollar?
Yes, that's me.
I'm Dr. Fong.
Sorry for the wait.
I was golfing.
No... No problem, Doctor.
So, I, uh,
looked over
your CAT scans.
You have
a pretty big brain tumor
near your frontal lobe.
Oh, Christ.
Jesus Christ!
Wait. What does
that mean, "pretty big"?
It means "big."
Well, what do we do?
Well, we have
to remove it soon.
I've scheduled
a craniotomy for
the end of the week.
JOHN: Wow.
We can give your
mother steroids
to reduce
the size of the tumor,
but the seizures
will continue
if nothing's done.
RON: Steroids.
Excuse me, Doctor.
What will the steroids
do to her muscles?
Will it make her bulky?
Ron.
No.
DON: (SOBBING) Christ. Christ.
Christ, Christ,
Christ, Christ.
Get a grip, Dad.
Christ, Christ,
Christ, Christ.
I don't understand.
How... How did something
like this happen?
It could be any
number of reasons.
We really have no way
of knowing right now,
but I will say this.
It is not a young tumor.
(LAUGHS)
I'd say it must
have been growing
inside Mrs. Hollar's head
for the past 10,
maybe 15 years.
What?
Yeah.
To be honest, I'm surprised
there haven't
been more symptoms.
Would loss of sight
in one eye
be a symptom?
Possibly.
SALLY: Oh, what about, uh,
numbness in
the toes and fingers?
DR. FONG: Probably.
And temporary paralysis?
Definitely.
Shit.
I told you.
What are you
talking about?
Well, there...
There might have been
some symptoms before today.
Why wouldn't you
get those checked out?
He sent me
to Jenny Craig.
JOHN: Oh, my God.
I thought it was
a weight thing.
Dad, temporary paralysis?
I didn't know.
Jesus Christ, Dad!
But I lost six pounds
the first week.
Okay, uh, well, it seems
like you guys have
some stuff to work out, so...
RON: A weight thing?
You thought it
was a weight thing?
Stop, stop.
JOHN: So, what is
with you and Dad?
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
He seems pretty pissed.
He fired me, John.
Fired you?
I didn't even know you
were working for him.
Yeah, you should
really call more,
you know.
So, what did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Well, then,
why did you get fired?
The business has been
operating at
a loss for over a year.
Dad's about
three weeks away
from total bankruptcy.
When I confronted him
about it, he fires me.
Wait. What?
Are you kidding me?
Just don't say
anything, okay?
He made me promise
not to tell anyone.
He doesn't want Mom
to worry about it right now.
Well, what's he
going to do?
I don't know.
Medical bills are
going to be crazy.
They don't have any savings.
They're totally screwed.
Oh, my God.
(MUSIC STOPS)
So, how's Rebecca?
She's good.
Yeah?
Mom said things
haven't been great.
Is that why you're not
going to get married?
I don't even know
why you would say that. I...
Do you think
your kid will mind
being a bastard?
Okay, first of all,
I'm pretty sure
people don't think
like that anymore.
And, uh, two, no.
I don't... I don't know.
You sure?
Well, I'll ask him
when he gets here.
What are you doing?
Stacey started
seeing somebody.
This is Stacey's house?
Yeah.
Ron, you divorced her,
like, years ago.
I agreed to divorce.
I didn't agree to
some strange man
hanging around my daughters.
Okay, Ron, we got to go.
This is...
Oh, shit! Get down!
Get down!
What? What? What is it?
John, get down.
What?
He's at the window.
Oh, my God, mine doesn't work.
RON: What?
Mine doesn't work.
Don't grab... Put it down.
My seat doesn't work.
My seat...
He's coming.
RON: He's coming over?
RON: Is he coming over?
Oh, my God, Ron.
I'm going to kill you.
This is very...
RON: Just be cool.
This is very
upsetting to me.
RON: Be cool.
This is, uh...
This is not good. This...
Hey.
Hey there, Ron.
How you doing?
RON: Fine.
Wait. You guys
know each other?
Yeah.
He's the new youth pastor
over at Mom and Dad's church.
Reverend Dan.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, whoa.
Whoa.
Hey. John Hollar.
I'm embarrassed.
I heard about
your mother.
I'm very sorry.
Oh, thank you very much.
That's nice of you to say.
How is she?
You know, I think...
She's fine.
No thanks to you.
Well, he didn't
do anything, Ron.
Yeah? How do you know?
He's supposed to
talk to God, isn't he?
Maybe he put in an order
for a brain tumor
or something.
I'm afraid that's not
how it works there, Ron.
Oh, yeah? (LAUGHS)
How does it work,
Reverend Dan? Tell us.
Well, I'm just
a youth pastor, so...
(RON SCOFFS)
Really?
What's the matter?
Couldn't get a job
as an adult pastor?
No, I just...
Yeah. I like kids.
That's nice.
Yeah? That's creepy.
That's creepy.
Yeah, look, Ron, uh...
I know you're going through
a hard time right now,
okay?
Oh, really? You do?
Yeah, yeah, I do.
And I appreciate
that very much.
However...
Yeah?
Stacey was wondering
if you could maybe...
Stop parking out
in front of the house
and staring at her
with your binoculars.
Yeah?
Well, fuck you,
Reverend Dan!
(ENGINE SPLUTTERING)
What happened?
I don't know.
I mean, it sounded
like you...
You have
a broken T-chain there.
I could... I mean,
I could take a look at it
for you if you want.
That would be helpful.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Pop the hood.
This guy...
Shut your mouth.
I'm not afraid of the dark
We've been here before
Fallen on hard times, honey,
we've fallen on swords
So if a long shadow
falls across your heart
I'll be right here with you,
I'm not afraid of the dark
when the sun goes down
You can have our old room.
I'm in the den.
Wait. You live here now?
RON: We're in a recession!
I'm not afraid of the dark
Out on the hills,
the hounds are baying
Out on the moor,
the foxes run
To stay alive
until the light has faded
Then pray for light
that seems so long to come
I'm not afraid of the dark
(WHISPERS) Dad.
Dad.
What time is it?
JOHN: It's 8:00.
Oh, shit, shit.
Shit, I'm late for work. Shit.
JOHN: No,
don't worry about it.
Look, I got your
briefcase right here.
Coffee.
Thank you, John.
Yeah, you got it.
So, just go to work
and I'll stay here
with Mom.
DON: You sure?
JOHN: Yeah.
I just don't know what
I'd do if I lost her.
(CRYING)
Dad.
Dad, you can't
think like that.
I know.
It's gonna be okay.
You'll see.
I know.
(SNIFFLES)
Yeah.
And he's gone,
so you can stop pretending.
Thank God.
How you doing?
He cried all night.
If I didn't know
any better,
I'd think
he was the one
with the brain tumor.
I think he might be
going through
a little something, so...
Ron told you we're
about to go bankrupt?
Come on.
He said no one knew.
I keep the books.
Is he gonna be all right?
I don't know.
Well, I brought breakfast.
Pretzels and ice cream?
If you don't want it,
I can just...
No, no, no.
I'm not saying that.
So, how you doing?
I feel great.
You know, I've been
googling brain tumors.
A lot more common
than you'd think.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Did you know
Bob Marley had one?
How'd that work out
for him?
Well, he sold
a lot of records,
so... Got a little
catching up to do.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You're gonna be okay, Mom.
You'll get through this.
I mean, even
the procedure seems simple.
Just a tiny little hole
in your skull,
and they go in and...
John.
How's Rebecca?
She's good, you know...
JASON: Oh.
Hello. (LAUGHS)
What's this,
Mrs. Hollar?
We're having some
ice cream for breakfast?
Ice cream and pretzels,
one of my mom's
favorite things.
Yeah. Hey, how 'bout
heart attacks?
Is that one of her
favorite things, too?
No. What? Why?
Why? Well, because
your mother's
a borderline diabetic.
That's not true, is it?
Maybe.
JASON: Yeah. Yeah.
No, it is. So this
probably wasn't
the best idea, was it, pal?
I'm gonna take these.
And, believe it or not,
we actually keep our patients
on a pretty strict diet
for a reason.
Sorry. I was just trying to do
something nice for her, so...
Next time,
like, try a gift card
or something harmless,
you know?
(LAUGHS)
I'm sorry, do you have
a problem with me or...
I don't know. Maybe.
Want... Want a little
chat in the hall?
We'll find out.
I'll be right back.
What's going on, man?
Uh, "What's going on, man?"
Well, Gwen has been
asking about you,
like, nonstop
since she found out
your mom was here.
Yeah. No, I heard
you guys were...
Married?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Congratulations.
She just had a kid,
too, so...
Well, you both
have a kid, so that...
That's awesome.
Congratulations for
both of you, right?
Dude, please,
can we cut the shit
here for a second?
Yeah.
I mean, like, are you
gonna try anything?
What?
Are you gonna try
anything with her
while you're in town?
No, no, no.
No. No, no, no.
Yeah?
No, I... I have
a great girl in New York,
and we're actually
about to have a baby, so...
Oh, great.
So you're married.
Uh, no.
No, we're not.
I thought you said you...
You're gonna have a baby.
I did say I was
gonna have a baby, but...
I'm not married.
Well, why aren't
you getting married
if you're gonna have a kid?
Well, it's a long story.
You know, we talked about it.
But, uh...
Why does that matter?
I don't know.
I'm just saying,
like, don't you think
your kid's gonna resent you
for making it a bastard?
It's not gonna be
a bastard.
Technically,
the kid will be a...
That's what a bastard is.
Point is, I...
I haven't had any
feelings for Gwen.
Not for a long, long time.
So...
Yeah.
She still looks good.
I... Bet she does.
Like, great.
Okay.
You know,
maybe better than before.
I don't even know
what that means, but...
In that case,
you want to get dinner?
What?
Tomorrow night.
Gwen wanted me
to invite you to
dinner at our house.
That's why
we're chatting out
here in the hall.
Um, yeah, no, I...
Yeah, that would be nice.
All right, good.
Well, I'll let her
know you're coming.
Great. All right, well,
it was good to see you.
This is good.
Yeah? Glad you like it.
It's a nice combo.
(SIGHS)
Where is everyone?
Not here.
Well, where are they?
Called in sick.
Everyone?
Mmm-hmm.
Why?
I'm guessing it
had something to do with
not getting paid
for two weeks.
Well, don't they
know about Sally?
Unfortunately, guilting
people into free labor
only works on family.
I wish I had more sisters.
Yeah, me, too.
How's she doing?
(SOBS) I don't know.
I better go check on her.
No, I'll go check on her.
You need to get to work.
We got an order
this morning, thank God.
All right. Here.
Take this card
and pay everyone
for last week.
You can't afford that.
Just do it anyway.
And tell 'em to get
their asses back to work.
Okay.
What about your
cartoon story?
They don't call it
a cartoon story, Mom.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I mean, what's it called?
A graphic novel.
How is it?
(SIGHS)
Let's face it, Mom,
I made a mistake.
I'm not an artist.
And that's okay.
Rebecca sent me
some of it.
Oh, my God,
she did not.
She says she thinks
you should try
and get it published.
Yeah. I bet she does.
Why don't you?
Because, Mom,
you know, sometimes
things aren't good enough.
I like Rebecca.
She's pushy.
Yeah.
Men need to be pushed.
You know,
when your father and
I first got married,
we lived in Detroit.
He worked in
a small office downtown
next to
the Fox Theatre.
I'd pick him up every day.
He never really knew why.
Your father would
get off work at 5:00,
and I'd leave our
apartment at 3:00
and walk down to the Fox.
There was never
a show on at that time.
And I'd go in
and I'd sit in
one of those seats.
And I'd look up
at the ceiling.
It was...
Unlike anything
I'd ever seen.
And this enormous chandelier.
It was breathtaking.
And every day,
I'd go back,
I'd go in,
and I'd look up.
You've never
told me that story.
I never really got a chance
to pursue anything creative.
I was so young when I
married your father,
and then Ronnie came along.
So...
Do you ever wish you
did anything different?
Oh, yeah, big-time.
Really?
Definitely. Definitely.
Like what?
I'm not sure
I ever should have
married your father.
Wait. What?
Grandma!
Girls! Oh, my goodness!
Oh, what are you two
doing out of school?
I don't want you
to die, Grandma.
Don't you worry
about that.
But, Dad said you will.
Well, what does he know?
We brought
pretzels and ice cream.
Oh, that is so sweet.
CONSTANCE:
Whoa, grandma,
is that your tumor?
Oh, come here, honey,
and give me a hug.
Okay. I'm gonna go
for a drive, so...
Do you need anything?
I wouldn't mind
a bag of Doritos.
I was asking Mom.
No, honey, I'm fine.
Okay. Great.
I'll be right back, okay?
See you guys
in a little bit!
Bye-bye!
Ta-da!
Ah!
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Oh, thank God you're there.
It is so good to
hear your voice.
REBECCA:  Hey. How are you?
Not so good.
Uh, Doctor wants
to do a craniotomy
by the end of the week.
Dad is... Gonna lose
his business, I think.
And... Mom said
she actually thinks
she regrets marrying him.
It's been great.
And on top of it all,
my mom's nurse hates me.
Wait, why does your
mom's nurse hate you?
Who knows?
It's just some jackass
from high school.
Well, what's his problem?
You need me to
come down there?
I don't know, you know?
Nothing.
He's married to Gwen.
Gwen...
Gwen. Your Gwen.
Well, it's not
my Gwen anymore.
Right? So...
Well, no, yeah, but...
Oh, boy.
Look, Rebecca, don't worry.
Nothing is gonna happen.
I don't feel anything
for her anymore, okay?
I mean, she just had a baby,
for God's sake.
Oh. Yeah.
Oh. What an incredibly...
Insensitive thing to
say to me right now.
No, that's not
what I meant. I...
REBECCA:  What is that sound?
Are you smoking?
No. Yes.
You don't smoke.
Can you just put
that out, please,
and just call me
a little later?
Okay, Rebecca,
I didn't mean to...
No, I... It... I'm...
I'm fine. I just...
I need to get back to work.
Okay.
Okay. I love you. Bye.
Stupid.
MAN: Look, Don, I, uh...
I don't think I can get them
to give you another loan,
given your current
financial status.
Business is picking up.
Oh, yeah, no,
I should've told you.
Yeah. In fact, I'm gonna
hire a new salesman.
Soon, to drum up
some more business.
Jim, I need to cover
payroll for a month
and that's it.
Well, I...
I wish there was
something I could do.
Jim,
I'm a member of
the chamber of commerce.
I can't even take
my own kids out
for dinner. (CHUCKLES)
Look, Don,
you may be uncomfortable
talking about this, but...
At this point,
filing for bankruptcy,
it might be
your safest option.
Bankruptcy?
Yeah.
I gave my life
to this business.
I gave my life!
Wasn't supposed
to be like this!
I'm sorry, Don.
I don't know if you heard.
Sally's really sick.
Yeah, I know.
I'm very sorry.
Okay.
Thanks, Jim.
All right.
These are just flames
Burning in your fireplace
I hear your voice
and it seems
As if it was all a dream
I see a world
A world turning in on itself
Are we just like
Hungry wolves
howling in the night?
I don't want
no music tonight
Can we go on
Like it once was?
Every time I
hear another story
Oh, the poor boy
lost his head
Everybody
feels a little crazy
But we go on living with it
Yeah, they go on
living with it
Perfect.
These are just flames
Burning in your fireplace
I hear your voice
and it seems
As if it was all a dream
I wish it was all a dream
Can we go on
Like it once was?
Can I help you?
Yes.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER TV)
(LAUGHING)
You remember that one?
Oh, my God.
There you are.
Hey, Mom.
I have been looking
all over for you girls.
What are you doing?
Why didn't you go
to school today?
Dad brought us
here instead.
You can't take our
kids out of school
without calling me, Ron.
Grandma has a tumor.
It's the size of
a basketball in her head.
It's only a softball,
actually.
Sally...
I'm so sorry.
Thank you, Stacey.
What is he doing here?
Can I talk to you
for a second? Alone?
Okay.
What the hell
are you doing?
You are scaring the girls,
not to mention your mom.
What do you care?
Come on, Ron,
don't be a child.
What did you
bring him here for?
I was worried.
He comforted me.
He comf...
He comforted you?
The reverend?
So are you...
Serious now?
Ron.
You were the one
who wanted a divorce
in the first place.
Uh...
What if I wanted
to change my mind?
Change your mind
about what?
You know...
Us.
You and me and...
The girls.
Are you kidding me?
I just wasn't ready.
I know you think
you're hot shit
ever since you
moved to New York,
but don't be
an asshole, okay?
This guy's got
Mom's life in his hands.
What are you
talking about?
I don't think
I'm hot shit.
Sure you do. You think
you're better than us.
That's why you never call.
Here we go.
I don't call
just because
I don't use the phone
that much anymore.
You used to call
Gwen all the time.
She was my girlfriend!
It's okay.
I understand. Leave it.
Understand what?
You're jealous.
(CHUCKLING) Of you?
You live in Mom
and Dad's basement.
You resent me, don't you?
You resent all of us.
That is why you
moved so far away.
I moved to New York
because there's
nothing here.
There's nothing here?
Well, whatever.
Yeah. Yeah, whatever.
I don't care, either.
Just don't offend
this guy, okay?
How can I help you?
Yes, thank you
for taking the time.
My brother and I
were just wondering
if you could
explain the procedure
a little bit more...
I wasn't wondering.
I trust you.
My mom and dad
trust you, too.
Um, well, thank you.
The procedure.
JOHN: Yeah.
So, what we plan on doing...
I took karate
as a kid.
Ron.
My instructor
was actually black,
but I'm pretty sure
he spent some time in China.
Why?
With the Chinese.
Well, I'm Taiwanese Laoshan.
Taiwanese Laoshan.
So, doesn't apply.
Doesn't apply.
You're lotion?
It's pronounced "Lau Shan."
What martial art
do you do?
None.
None?
Okay, so the difficulty
here is
that the tumor is
taking up a large part...
Does it help to
have small hands?
You're a very busy guy.
In... In the surgery?
Thank you so much
for taking the time,
and we really appreciate
all you're doing for our mom.
You're offending!
Hey, Gwen.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
This is for you.
(BABY CRYING)
Oh, hey, man.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You... You invited
me to dinner.
What day is it today?
I'm just busting
your balls, man.
Oh, that right?
Yeah.
All right.
Are those for Gwen, or...
No, they're...
Well, yeah.
They're for both of you,
so, you know, there you go.
(SNICKERS)
Yeah.
All right, well, I'll find
a nice place for these.
Come on in.
Gwen's getting ready, and...
Great.
Yeah, do...
Nice house.
Beautiful place.
Thanks. Yeah.
Look out.
Is that your baby?
Nah, real kid's
in the fridge.
It's just
a screaming decoy.
(BOTH CHUCKLE AWKWARDLY)
What's, uh...
What's the name?
Quinn.
Oh, yeah.
He's adorable.
No, it's a she.
Oh.
We named her after
Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman,
you know,
because... 'Cause it
seemed like a funny idea
at the time.
It's good.
I think it's clever.
You don't really think
that far ahead and then...
Yeah. It's a good show.
It's the kid's
name forever, but...
Yeah.
Yeah. You want a beer, or...
I'd love that.
All right.
Thank you so much.
You got it.
Now, is she okay?
'Cause she seems upset.
No, she's good.
The crying's actually, like,
good for kids' lungs.
It makes them
strong or something,
you know.
Oh, all right.
Well, I don't think
that's true.
Right?
Hi. You okay?
You okay?
She likes you.
Hey.
Wow, you look...
Beautiful.
Well, I look...
Different.
So, how are you?
Good. Good.
Little weird to
be home, you know?
You have
an amazing-looking child...
Your husband's
right in the kitchen.
Yeah. It's not working out.
But, he could come in,
and any moment...
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
You should have
called me.
(BOTTLES POPPING)
I know.
Have you ever read this?
Yes, that is
my favorite one.
Yeah, I thought
you might like it.
Yeah.
Really? I think
that book's depressing.
Oh, you think
everything's depressing.
Well, you've seen
Seven, right?
I have, yeah.
Whatever.
How did you get
Quinn to stop crying?
Oh, I didn't.
John did it.
Oh, what, are you, like,
some kind of baby
whisperer guy, or...
Mmm. No. No.
Jason can never get
her to stop crying.
JOHN: Oh, really?
Well, that's
probably just bad luck.
Yeah, I mean...
It's just bad luck.
You hungry?
Starving.
Yeah, let's eat.
Okay, great.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Okay, kiddo,
it's bedtime for you.
You want...
(QUINN WAILING)
Are you kidding me?
It was really good.
Thank you very much.
So, uh, what's the story
with your girlfriend?
Why didn't she
come back with you?
Girlfriend?
Mmm.
Oh, yeah,
I didn't tell you?
No.
Yeah. No, they're gonna
have a kid together
and everything.
Oh, wow.
Wow. Congratulations.
Thank you.
So, when's she due?
Soon, very soon.
They're not even married.
Hmm.
Well, you know, we...
Really wanting a bastard,
so we got it.
I proposed to Gwen the second
I saw the pregnancy test
in the trash.
I jumped on it,
'cause you don't
want to, you know...
That's romantic.
Yeah.
So, how'd you meet her?
At a comic book store,
actually.
Oh, she like a...
Like a nerd or...
No, she's, uh...
Adorable.
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
What she do?
She has her
own company, actually.
Oh, doing what?
She designs pet clothing.
So, just collars and hats
and sweaters and...
Nice.
JASON:
Oh, you can make a living
designing pet clothing
in New York?
That's...
No, not... Not really.
Um, I don't
understand then.
Her parents
are rich-ish.
Hmm.
How rich?
They bought her
a brownstone
for graduation.
Wow.
Okay. Well, now I see
why you don't want
to get married.
(LAUGHING)
Why is that?
Mmm. Well, it's like,
what's the point, really?
Going through
all that, you know?
Getting everything
you want out of it,
and she's taking
care of you, so...
GWEN: Jason.
What?
Well, no, no, it's not...
It's not like that.
I mean, we keep our
money separate, so...
But you don't have
any money.
You're drunk.
So?
So go do
the dishes, okay?
Okay.
Right. Okay. Sure.
You don't have
any money, right?
Jason.
Okay.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
John! Oh, my God!
I haven't heard from
you in, like, two days!
I've been worried!
JOHN:  Rebecca,
I just saw Gwen.
I went over to her
house for dinner,
her and her husband,
he was there.
And okay, honey,
I'll just tell you,
she kissed me!
Okay.
Okay, so...
You kissed her?
No, no, no,
she kissed me.
Whoa. No.
Major difference.
Major.
I just thought that you said
you didn't have
feelings for her anymore,
and she just had a kid.
I don't. She did.
Oh, by the way,
she still looks great!
Meant to tell you that,
so, you have nothing
to worry about.
Dude, what?
John, you sound
like a basket case.
No. No, no.
I know exactly what
I'm saying, I promise.
REBECCA: You're not making me
feel very secure right now.
I know.
I know, but I will.
I will, starting right now.
Are you drunk?
A little bit, but no,
that's not why
I'm saying this.
Rebecca, what I'm
trying to tell you is...
I love you.
I love you,
and I don't know,
I just wanted you
to know that.
I love you, too.
Dad?
Hey, Johnny,
what's going on?
What are you doing here?
John?
I'm working.
Rebecca, I have
to call you back.
Are you kidding me, John?
(SIGHS) Dad,
I can give you
some money.
Don't be ridiculous.
You don't have any money.
Rebecca has some money...
I'm not going to take
any money from her.
John, come on.
You got your own family
to worry about now.
I'll figure this out.
How?
Well, I'll, you know...
Dad... How?
Well...
I'm sorry.
That I didn't spend
more time with you
growing up.
Come on, Dad,
you know I don't
care about that.
Yeah, well, I do.
Johnny, it's terrifying.
It's not that bad.
How much do you owe?
No, not that, no.
It's terrifying
to find out
this late in your life
what you
should have done.
Wow.
We still have time.
I tried, you know.
I did try.
You got to know that.
I do.
Yeah.
(THUDDING)
John.
Hi.
Is this a dream?
No.
Why is he wearing
my mother's robe?
Hi.
I'm Ron, uh,
John's brother.
It is so good to
finally meet you.
JOHN: Hey, Ron?
Yeah.
I think we got it
from here, bud.
Sure. Okay. Yeah.
Hi.
So, don't ever hang up
on me again, okay?
No, I won't.
Okay.
Oh!
Wait.
How did you get here?
I took a cab.
How far is that?
Far.
JOHN: Wow.
Oh, what are these?
I was thinking maybe
some wallpaper
for the baby's room.
I read somewhere that
babies like contrast.
(CHUCKLES)
They're beautiful.
I missed you so much.
I really missed you. Oh.
How are you feeling?
My ass is really sore.
JOHN: Cannot believe
you took a cab here.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(FOOTSTEPS RUSTLING)
(SHUSHING)
Hey.
Dad?
Hi, angels.
What are you doing here?
I missed you guys.
Did you miss me?
Yeah.
Yeah. Can I come in?
(GIGGLES)
Yeah.
I'm coming in.
But, Mom said that...
Don't...
Don't worry about Mom.
Move... Move that.
Okay.
Coming in.
Okay. Ow.
Okay. Here we go.
I'm good. Okay.
(CLANG)
(ALARM CLOCK RINGING)
(RON SHUSHING)
RON: Don't wake Mommy.
Okay.
Hi. Hi-ho.
Slumber party.
Get in here.
Oh, my goodness.
I missed you guys.
I missed you.
I love you.
Whoa, oh...
What? What is it?
Oh.
Is it... Is it a kick?
No, it felt like a stab.
Is that normal?
I don't know.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
It's from being
in the car so long.
I don't think
that's what that is.
That's not helping.
Okay.
Is this real?
Well, it feels real.
All right. Sorry. Yep.
Ah! Ooh!
Yep.
Okay...
Constance.
Matilda.
Wake up, it's time for school.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Okay, okay, just hear me out.
Ron!
Stacey, please.
(BABIES CRYING)
John?
How is she?
She's fine.
She just needs to rest.
Oh, good.
You can take her
home tomorrow.
Thank you.
And the... Baby is okay?
Their vitals are good.
"Their vitals"?
Did you know we
were having twins?
Yeah.
And you didn't
tell me because...
It was the same day,
when we found out
about your mom.
And...
Honestly, with everything
you've been going through,
I can't even tell
if you want to
have a baby at all.
So I thought
if you knew that
it was two, you'd...
It would be too much.
Wait. "Everything
I'm going through"?
You're not happy, John.
It's obvious.
At work, in your life and...
I don't know,
maybe with me.
And I know that you're...
No, I...
Just going
through something and
maybe everything
in your life isn't
exactly what you
want it to be right now.
Um, and you're scared
and I get that.
Having a baby is scary.
And you think that
everything's
gonna change and...
We're not gonna be fun anymore
and you're not gonna
drink beer with your friends
and you're gonna
have to be stuck in
this job that you hate
and you're not gonna
kiss your
high school sweetheart
ever again...
Becca, that's not...
No, I'm saying...
I'm saying it's fine.
And we're gonna
work through all of it
and you don't need to worry.
Okay?
That's not what
I'm worried about.
Okay. It's not?
No.
I don't care
about any of that.
Having twins is...
Is one more person and...
That's one more
person that...
I'm gonna be failing.
And I just don't know
if I can take that.
What?
Is that what you think?
I don't know, yeah.
I didn't drive eight hours
'cause you were failing me.
I came here 'cause I need you
so much.
I'm just waiting
for you to come back.
Okay.
(SNIFFLES) Okay.
I need you
to get me out of
this hospital, though.
Okay.
For real.
I'm not having two of
your enormous babies
without my doctor,
you monster.
Okay.
I'm not doing it.
It's not funny.
You are not allowed
in this house again
under any circumstance,
do you understand?
Come on, Stacey,
don't you think
you're overreacting?
Watch the flowers, please.
Come on, man.
Dan, good to see you.
Good morning.
Good to see you.
Damn it! Damn it!
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, shit.
You know what? You win, man.
Okay?
You win.
This isn't about me.
Yeah, whatever.
Your girls called me.
They called you?
What were you doing
in the house, Ron?
RON: I don't know!
I was lonely,
and I... I didn't
know where else to go,
and... And they're...
They're my kids.
I mean, they're...
They're my kids, too.
Would you like
to talk about it?
No. No.
I mean, kind of, but...
Hey, come on.
I'm gonna buy you
a cup of coffee.
No.
Come on.
No, it's okay. I'm okay.
I'm good.
Thank you, Mike.
Wait, you're not gonna
push any of that
Jesus shit on me, are you?
No.
You promise?
I don't force my
beliefs on people, Ron.
Really?
Really.
What are your beliefs?
(DAN LAUGHS)
JOHN: Mom?
What are you doing up?
Where is everyone?
Gone.
Mom, what's wrong?
Dr. Fong just came by.
And?
He said they might
have to shave my head.
(LAUGHS)
Well, Mom,
that's okay.
I don't want to do it, Johnny.
Look ridiculous.
Look like Rod Steiger.
No.
(SNICKERS) Yes, I will.
No, you won't.
When are they
coming to do it?
I don't know.
I'll just stay right here
until they do.
How are you?
We're having twins.
And you're terrified.
(BOTH SNIFFLING)
Oh...
Don't worry.
You won't know
till you get there
that you're okay.
Okay, Mrs. Hollar,
you ready for your new 'do?
Oh.
Uh, hey, man.
Hey, man.
Um...
Look, I...
I got to give your
mom a haircut, so...
You want to hop over here?
JOHN: Yeah.
Easy as pie.
Hop on in.
Just gonna pop this on...
Real easy.
And we'll get you
done in no time.
Bing, bang, boom,
nothing to it,
nice and easy.
You ready?
All right, here we go.
Wait.
I'll do it.
JASON: Oh, yeah?
Yeah, just leave the clippers
and I'll give her the haircut.
If that's all right with you.
JASON: All right.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
SALLY: How do I look?
Beautiful.
You're just saying that.
JOHN: No, I'm not.
You have a really
nicely-shaped head.
Well, thank you.
Give me my lipstick.
Well, what now?
I don't know.
Wait for supper.
It's my last meal.
What do you mean,
your last meal?
They're not letting me
have any food tomorrow.
I guess you're not supposed
to eat before the surgery.
Well, what's on
the menu for tonight?
Yogurt and a boiled egg.
Well, that's not
a good last meal.
No kidding.
Let's go.
What? Now?
Yeah.
They're never
letting me leave.
I'm gonna sneak
you out of here.
SALLY: You'll get in trouble!
I'm not letting you have
a yogurt and
an egg for dinner.
SALLY: Ooh!
(YELLS)
Excuse me.
(SCREAMS)
(SHUSHING)
WOMAN: Push, push, push.
You can't be in here.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
No, no. Get out.
Sorry.
So sorry.
Sorry. Yeah.
You're doing great.
This is for 310.
No, no, no. Hey. Hey, hey!
Hey!
John! You're going so fast.
(SHRIEKS)
(SALLY LAUGHING)
We did it.
We did it. We got away.
Hey, hey, hey! Wait,
wait, wait! No, come on!
You can't leave
the hospital...
What an asshole.
Oh, my God.
I haven't been to this place
in a really long, long time.
JOHN: Hmm.
I think those women think
I just escaped from...
A mental institution.
(LAUGHING)
I don't even think
they've noticed.
Which scares me more.
Mom, what did you mean
when you said
you might have
regretted marrying Dad?
Did I say that?
Yes.
Must've been the tumor.
Mom.
You never met my mother.
She was tough.
Quiet, but tough.
The day I married your dad,
she only had one piece
of advice for me.
"Don't waste your time
with the bad.
"Live with the good."
So...
Your father and I
have lived through
38 good years together.
I love this place.
Hi.
Boy, we thought we missed you.
Hey.
Ta-da.
Whoa. Nice haircut.
What do you think, Donald?
I think you look great, Chief.
Who do you think I look like?
It's weird,
but you remind me of my wife.
That's... I knew you
were gonna say that!
In the morning when I get up
In the evening
when I go out
(WHISPERING) Rebecca...
You're so good for him.
Love you.
What time is it?
It's 8:30.
So...
Thanks for being here,
everyone.
We love you, Mom.
I love you guys.
Don...
It's gonna be fine.
I'm going to be okay.
(SOBBING) I'm...
I'm so sorry
about Jenny Craig.
Oh. Come here.
Take care of Ron for me.
He needs your help.
Okay.
Chief.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
It's been on there so long.
(LAUGHS)
Hold it for me.
Take care of your dad for me.
He needs your help.
I got it.
Take care of both of them.
They need you.
You got it.
Okay, are we ready,
Mrs. Hollar?
JOHN: Ready, Mom?
I don't...
Mrs. Hollar?
(CRYING) I don't
want to do this.
Okay. Okay.
I don't want to do this.
It's okay.
I don't want to do this!
JOHN: Mom,
you're gonna be fine. Okay?
I'm trying to tell you
something 'bout my life
No!
Maybe give me insights
Between black and white
The best thing
you ever done for me
Is to help me take
my life less seriously
It's only life after all
(LAUGHING AND CRYING)
Yeah.
SALLY: Yeah.
Well, darkness has
a hunger that's insatiable
Is that the Indigo Girls?
Yeah. She loves this song.
That's hard to hear
ALL:   And I wrap my fear
around me like a blanket
And I sailed my ship
of safety till I sank it
I'm crawling on your shores
I went to the doctor
I went to the mountains
I looked to the children
I drank from the fountains
There's more than one answer
to these questions
Pointing me
in a crooked line
And the less
I seek my source
For some definitive
My source
The closer I am to fine
I went to see
the doctor of philosophy
With a poster of Rasputin
And a beard down to his knee
He never did marry
Or see a B-grade movie
He graded my performance
He said he could
see through me
I spent four years prostrate
To the higher mind
Got my paper and I was free
I went to the doctor
I went to the mountains
I looked to the children
I drank from the fountains
There's more than one answer
to these questions
Pointing me
in a crooked line
And the less
I seek my source
Less I seek
For some definitive
My source
The closer I am to fine
Yeah
(SIGHS)
I'm gonna get some air.
I'm gonna be right back.
How you feeling?
Better, thank you.
Thank you for being here.
How's the job search going?
Okay.
I'm waiting for
a second interview at Amazon.
Really? That's amazing.
No, not...
Not that Amazon. I...
The... The club in Bristol.
They need bartenders.
Yeah.
Do you bartend?
No.
(LAUGHS)
No. Never.
You know,
Dad wants to hire you back.
What?
No.
Yeah, what he said.
Dad wants me to
work for him again?
Nope, not for him.
Dad wants you to run
the company with him.
He's just too proud to ask.
I mean, he won't be able
to pay you right away,
not until the company
gets back on its feet, but...
The job's yours.
He can't pay me?
You're living in his house
rent-free, Ron.
Yeah, well...
That's his duty
as one of the people
who brought me into this world
without asking.
That's one way
to look at it.
What do you say?
I'll think about it.
Good.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Hey, Dad?
Yeah?
Ron wants his job back.
What?
Yeah.
Said he'll work for no pay
till the company's
back on its feet.
He said he'd work
for no pay?
Yep. That's exactly
what he said.
Huh.
DR. FONG: Guys.
Well, the operation
was a success.
Oh, man.
Okay...
We're moving her
into intensive care,
just to keep an eye on her,
see how she progresses.
You can visit her
once she's settled.
Well, I just... I can't
thank you enough, Doctor.
(LAUGHING GIDDILY)
You don't know how
much I appreciate this.
Well, Mr. Hollar,
you're very welcome.
Do, do-do
Do, do-do, do-do-do
Do, do-do, do...
I'll stay here with your mom.
Why don't you two boys go home
and get some rest?
I want to stay.
DON: No.
No, you...
You got to take
Rebecca home.
She needs to spend
the night in a real bed.
You sure? I...
Yeah, yeah.
Go.
We started looking for you
Ron. You too.
In the darker caves
It's going to be fine.
We had a lot of love
We thought would
light the way
(SIGHS)
We saw the wrecks
of buildings
They're good boys.
And ships that sank
in starlight...
RON:  She's going
to be okay, right?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Better than ever.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Tell Dad I'll take the job.
Hey.
STACEY: Hey.
Come on, girls.
Bye, Mom!
STACEY: Bye.
Hey, guys.
Thank you.
Hey, wait for me!
Do, do-do, do-do-do
Do, do-do, do, do-do
Don?
Oh, hey, Chief.
How you doing?
Did... Did they get it?
Yeah, they got it.
Tumor's gone.
Good.
You did great, Chief.
Sally?
Sally.
(MONITOR TONE FLATLINES)
Sally!
MAN: What happened?
I don't know.
I need everyone in here now.
Stephanie,
check her pulse for me.
Sally! Sally! Sally?
MAN: Got to get ready
for bagging.
Kristin, lower the bed
and get ready for CPR.
WOMAN: Page Dr. Fong stat.
MAN: I need a crash cart now.
Someone's called a code.
What's going on?
Sir, we need you to
step out of the room.
No, I thought the surgery
was a success, they...
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't understand.
MAN: Mrs. Hollar,
can you hear me?
Do we have a pulse?
WOMAN: Med code.
MAN: Start bagging.
Mrs. Hollar, can you hear me?
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(BEEPS)
Hello.
Hey, Dad.
Once I knew a girl
in the hard, hard times
She made me a shirt
out of fives and dimes
Now she's gone,
but when I wear it,
she crosses my mind
And if the best
is for the best,
then the best is unkind
(INAUDIBLE)
I realized
that Illinois was more
than I could stand
They say that working's best
'Cause poverty
is hell on a man
Now I ride a lazy river
through the Mississippi fan
And if the best is
for the best
Then the best
can be damned
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(SIGHS)
Hey, Mr. Hollar.
I'm... I'm really,
terribly sorry about...
What do you want?
Um, Sally asked me
to give you this,
in case she ever,
you know, uh...
She was a wonderful woman.
Thanks.
(SIGHS)
SALLY:  "If you're
reading this letter,
"then I guess I
didn't make it.
"I'm sorry I can't be there
to help you
through this, Donald,
"but you're going to be okay.
(CRYING)
"Buck up.
"You gave me a great life.
"I love you so much.
"Sally."
I love you, too.
I can't.
Chief, I can't, I can't.
(SOBBING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What?
Sorry. Uh...
She asked me to
wait a couple minutes
and then give you this one.
SALLY:  "Stop crying.
(LAUGHS)
"You've got a funeral to plan.
"Don't forget I like orchids."
Everything okay?
Thanks for this.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Once I knew a girl
in the hard, hard times
Once I knew a girl in
the hard, hard times
Now, as far as caskets go...
Well, we want
the best one you have.
Dad, that's a lot of money.
I don't care.
Well, how are we
going to pay for it?
You're just gonna pay for it.
Actually, all the expenses
have already
been taken care of.
What? By who?
An anonymous party.
I don't understand.
Yeah, we don't know
any anonymous parties.
Is that it?
That's it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You ready to go?
No, I think
I'm just going to
be here for a minute.
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
Okay.
Did you just pay
for my mom's funeral?
I wanted to do something
and you said you were
strapped for cash, so...
Don't tell your dad, okay?
It's incredibly generous,
but, unfortunately,
we can't accept it.
(SIGHS) Why not?
I just can't, Becca.
This isn't how it was
supposed to be, and...
John...
Please accept it?
This is not an issue, okay?
I have money now.
You'll have money later.
We're family.
It doesn't make a difference.
Marry me?
What?
Marry me right now.
Now?
Are you sure
this is the best time?
Well, they say
"for better or
for worse," right?
I can't think of
a worse time than now.
(CAR DINGING)
Take me someplace she loved.
Do you, John,
take Rebecca to be
your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
And, Rebecca,
do you take John
to be your husband?
I do.
I got a new lover now
She knows just what I need
when I wake up in the night
She can read me
back my dreams
And she loves them,
though she never needs
to tell me what they mean
All right, that'll do.
By the power vested in me,
surrounded by nature
and under the eyes of God,
I now pronounce you
both husband and wife.
Kiss your bride.
I got a new lover now
Thank you for being here
to celebrate my mother.
She once told me,
when I was going
through a time in my life
where I was very lost...
She said,
"You won't know
until you get there
that you're okay."
And...
She was right.
Ooh!
My mother was strong.
She was really strong
and she was
strong for all of us.
I know
there's a number of people
here today that are wondering
what we're going
to do without her.
(CHUCKLES)
But, uh...
John, your wife's
going into labor.
No, I'm not. No, no, no.
No, I'm fine.
You okay?
You sure?
REBECCA: I'm fine.
You okay?
No, no, no. No.
Okay.
Sure, all right.
(GROANS)
I'm so sorry. Oh.
I think I might be fine.
I think.
Oh!
No, no. You're not.
Okay, we're going
to the hospital.
Come on. Come on.
Good-bye, Mom.
We love you.
Oh!
Come on.
Okay.
Good? You in?
All right.
Okay.
You're doing great.
You're doing great...
Doing good.
Everybody got
your seat belts on?
Go. Go.
(ENGINE SPLUTTERS)
Oh, shit!
Never got that fixed.
Come on, Ron.
Yeah, we're going
to get in here
'cause this is...
Come on, here we go.
We're good.
Okay, all right.
We're all blocked in,
we really are. Oh, boy.
Uh, this feels like a bad way
to bring kids into the world.
No, no, no, it's fine.
It's fine.
It is?
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
Hang on.
Go.
Ron, Ron, Ron.
Them's got ears,
let them hear
Them's got eyes,
let them see
Turn your eyes
to the lord of the skies
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(GROANS)
I'm coming! Emergency!
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
REBECCA: John?
John!
We're coming. I'm coming.
Here we go. We're coming.
REBECCA: John.
Come on, come on, this way.
(LAUGHS)
Excuse me.
We're having a baby.
Where do we go?
That's the next building.
What?
Go down the hall,
to the right.
Down the hall, to the right.
Okay.
Wait!
You can't all go.
What? What do you mean?
I can...
John!
Sweet John.
All right, we're gonna
go get a room, Dad.
Sweetie...
Thank you.
All right!
Yeah.
John, I'm scared!
Me, too.
You're not
supposed to tell me that.
No, it's going to be okay.
You're going to do great.
Here we go!
Your ticket you obtain
On this heavenly
airline plane
You think
they're going to be okay?
Yeah.
They're going to be just fine.
(CHUCKLES)
Maybe in daytime,
might be night
What about us?
To your home
beyond the skies
Turn your eyes
to the lord of the skies
Take that airline plane
Mrs. Hollar?
Yes.
Right this way.
To your home
beyond the skies
Them's got ears
let them hear
Them's got eyes let them see
Turn your eyes
to the lord of the skies
Take that airline Plane
It will take you
home again
Tell me something,
give me hope for the night
We don't know how we feel
We're just prayin'
that we're doin' this right
Though that's not
the way it seems
Summer gone,
now winter's on its way
I will miss the days we had
The days we had
Oh, I'll miss
the days we had
Loving, leaving,
it's too late for this now
Such esteem
for each has gone
Has time
driven our season away?
Cause that's
the way it seems
In the world of
the speech that is new
I'll be back again to stay
Again to stay