[water running]
[faucet squeaks]
-[hanging man groans, grunts]
-I got you.
[in Japanese] Guard!
Guard!
[in English] I got you.
-[grunting]
-[man] Come here, you.
[man 2] Get on your knees.
-[guards grunting]
-[prisoner speaks Japanese]
[man 3]
Are you proud of yourself for saving him?
You’d better mind your own business.
You thought you could get this note out?
What is this?
[cries out, grunts]
[man 3] Look.
What is this?
I’m asking you! What is this?
I don’t speak Japanese.
Throw him in solitary.
[guards shouting]
[shouting]
[man 3] Nobody knows that you’re here.
You’ll never get out of here.
[hanging man yells]
-[blows landing]
-[guard shouts]
[helicopter passes overhead]
[door opens]
[shouting, gasping]
[screaming]
[panting]
[spits]
[faint chatter]
Get out of the way.
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[door slams]
Food.
[man] Food.
Kiyoshi.
[in English] My name is Kiyoshi.
Nick.
I need your help.
When someone tries
to commit suicide in prison,
they take you to the hospital.
Once I am there,
my brothers will come for me.
And then, I will have them come for you.
Okay?
[guard speaking Japanese]
[guard 2 speaking Japanese]
[guard 2 shouting in Japanese]
Break is over!
Go back to work.
-Walk!
-Hurry!
Hey! Go!
Hey! Walk fast!
[sniffles, exhales]
I need you to keep me from dying
and make sure the guards come.
[panting]
[in Japanese] Guard!
Guard!
Hey! Hey!
Help!
-Be quiet.
-[Nick] He cut himself!
Number 129. Emergency!
Ring the emergency bell!
[bell ringing]
[guard] Number 129. Emergency!
Emergency!
[guard 2] The emergency bell!
[ringing continues]
[door slams]
[guard] Move… forward!
One, two. One, two. One, two.
-Move!
-[guard 2] Go to work!
[guard continues cadence in Japanese]
The entire Shiromatsu family
would like to start by thanking you
for what you did for our member.
Do you speak Japanese?
[in English] A bit.
[in English]
Kiyoshi says we should offer you a job.
We have a problem
with one of your fellow Americans.
We have tried to reason with him
for a while now.
Maybe…
you could help us with that.
Yeah, maybe I could.
Good.
[woman] Wow, Mr. Gaijin.
Come visit us. We’ll give you a discount.
[vendor] Try this. Welcome!
[man, woman laughing]
[loud chattering]
Wait here.
Get some sleep at an inn.
Someone will pick you up tomorrow.
Wait for them.
[in English] Hey, cowboy.
American beer?
It’ll be 100.
One hundred?
Yeah.
-[laughing]
-[Nick] Okay.
You’re pretty good.
Hold on a second.
Here.
[in Japanese] Thanks.
Beer?
[man in English]
Can’t believe you punched that guy.
-[in English] See the way he looked at me?
-He was a little out of line.
-Right.
-[man] Let’s make some money.
All right.
-[man] Excuse me.
-[man 2] Excuse me.
[people shouting in distance]
[horn honking]
[train rumbling past]
[sighs]
-Park over there.
-Yes, sir.
[in English] Good luck.
Let’s go over to Mr. Panetti’s office.
Mr. Panetti?
I got a guy out here,
says he’s here about a contract.
Just give him a minute.
Look,
I’m sure you got respect for these people
because they wear silk pajamas
and they bow like you’re the fuckin’
sun god when they pour the coffee.
Frankly, I don’t give a shit
about their rules or their traditions
or whatever the fuck it is
that you’re here to try to explain to me.
We won!
What’s the point in winning a war
if now you gotta worry
about steppin’ on Japs’ toes?
-I wouldn’t call ’em Japs.
-Okay.
-So you’re one of those.
-One of what?
I got a deal with the United States Army.
Your fuckin’ country gives me metal
at two cents a cubic yard.
Do you know
where they get this metal from?
Any idea?
They get it
from breaking down war machines
that these fucking Nips built
to sneak attack us.
So excuse me
if they gotta buy it back from me cheap.
Now, I don’t know
if you’re bangin’ some slanty-eyed broad
and you’re gettin’ all gooked-out
and sympathetic,
but that’s the way it is.
-That’s the way it is?
-That’s the way it is.
And now,
you can get the fuck outta my office.
[Nick grunting]
-[Panetti grunts, wheezes]
-[exhales deeply]
He’s all bloody.
[sighs]
[in English] Did you kill him?
He’ll live.
[in Japanese] Let’s go.
[up-tempo jazz playing]
Brother,
recently I’ve been doing some impressions.
-Let me see.
-May I?
It’s a worm.
And now… two worms.
-[laughing]
-[Kiyoshi] That’s not funny.
[big man] You can’t say it’s not funny.
[in English] Nick. Your turn.
A penguin walks into a bar.
Says to the bartender…
“Hey, have you seen my brother?”
Bartender looks at the penguin and says…
“What’s he look like?”
[laughing]
[in Japanese] A penguin walks into a bar
and asks the bartender,
“Have you seen my brother?”
“What’s he look like?”
“A penguin, of course.”
Everyone, laugh.
Laugh. Whatever it means, laugh.
[man] Laugh, laugh.
Shit, it’s them.
It’s the Seizu family.
[man] They’d better go back to Kobe.
This is our city.
Hey, you, calm down. Sit down.
[Kiyoshi] What do you want?
Smart move.
This is our territory. Go home.
The Yankee warehouse,
think you can get away with it?
We made a deal with the GIs, not you.
The warehouses are ours now.
Hey, handsome, listen up.
You came in here and talked to us,
like your boss told you to.
That’s impressive.
We’ll pass it on, if we don’t forget.
[Kiyoshi] I hear your family made a deal
with the Americans,
but that won’t make this port yours.
Get it?
You expect me to take you seriously
with this little white kitten
at your table?
Oh, ho! You have a cute face.
Then why don’t you take him home
and pet him?
No, you keep her.
You haven’t heard the news in town?
The name Shiromatsu means nothing anymore.
Your boss is half-retired.
He’s blind to what’s coming.
Shut up.
[Kentaro chuckles] It’s true.
If your boss and our previous boss weren’t
on good terms,
I would destroy your family.
It’s the other way around, idiot.
Next, we will take your women.
[Kiyoshi] Go home.
[Kentaro] We’ll take your dirty balls
while we’re at it.
Just like we took your port
before you knew it.
Go home.
-[woman screams]
-[Nick grunts]
[Orochi] Go back to Kobe.
Let them go.
[Orochi] Get lost!
Don’t come back, fool.
I’m going.
Where are the dancers?
Dance!
[man] Dance! Let’s start drinking again.
Cheers.
[child singing]
[singing continues]
[singing stops]
[singing resumes]
[car horn blaring]
[horn blaring]
[women chattering]
Whose place is this?
Yours, if you want it.
It’s nice.
[key clatters]
Think about it.
There’s a suit in the closet.
Should fit you.
[men laughing and chattering]
[shouting]
[shouting continues]
Let me join you.
[shouting stops]
How much?
Why isn’t anyone saying anything?
-Who is in charge? You?
-[man] No.
I’m asking who’s in charge.
You?
Is it him?
What’s your name?
Kimura.
So you’re Kimura.
Nick. Kimura.
I want to ask you.
If my friend Nick was looking
to play cards in Osaka,
should he ask you?
I don’t work with Americans.
[Kiyoshi] Don’t be bossy.
Who are you?
You have a family in the Osaka docks?
Are you the boss?
I don’t know.
Who owns Osaka?
I’m asking you. Who owns Osaka?
I wanna hear it.
Who is it?
Who owns Osaka?
The Shiromatsu.
Say it again.
-Shiromatsu.
-Wrong. Say it once more.
Shiromatsu.
It’s “Mr. Shiromatsu.”
Stand up.
Sato let me use this place.
We’ve been friends with Sato
since the old days.
I hear you threatened to tell his wife
that he’d slept with one of his actresses.
He got her pregnant.
It’s your child.
She says you raped her.
Hey. It’s over for today. Off you go.
If you have any debts,
pay them to Akihiro Shiromatsu.
Never play in Osaka without paying.
Hurry up and get out.
[gamblers murmuring]
Now.
-I’ll pay if you want money.
-Pay.
How much is the Shiromatsu’s usual cut?
I’ll pay double.
Okay, pay.
[in English]
He wants to know what Shiromatsu’s cut is.
Can’t you even negotiate
without permission from your white dog?
[gagging]
[Kiyoshi] Are you okay?
Don’t make such a fuss.
Aren’t you being dramatic?
Don’t weep.
This is what happens
when you resist the Shiromatsu.
-[choking]
-[Kiyoshi grunting]
[Kimura gurgling]
[gasping]
[people laughing]
Why is he still hanging around here?
What do you mean?
That gaijin has already served
his purpose, hasn’t he?
Why? He doesn’t mean shit to me.
You sure?
Don’t worry. It’s fine.
What’s fine?
I’m asking you if you owe him a debt.
And I said no.
Listen, Kiyoshi.
He doesn’t care about you or this family.
Send him away.
Okay?
He doesn’t like me very much, does he?
What’s the story with his fingers?
[in English] When you dishonor your boss
and you want to show remorse,
you give your finger.
It’s called otoshimae.
I see you’ve got all your fingers.
I guess I got lucky.
[whispering in Japanese]
-[in Japanese] I’ll go down there now.
-Yes, sir.
[in English] Stay here.
[band playing mambo]
[singing in Spanish]
[woman] What?
[Kiyoshi] That’s enough.
[woman] Wait. Stop it!
I get it. Let me go.
What are you doing here?
What does it look like? I’m dancing.
-I told you not to come here.
-Why? What’s wrong?
-No reason. Just go home.
-No.
Don’t test me.
What would you do if the Seizu men
walked in with guns in their hands?
Why would they come? Where are they?
I’m saying what if they came?
Nick.
[in English]
Take my sister home. She’s drunk.
[in Japanese]
That’s enough. He’s taking you home.
Go home.
[in English] Thank you for taking me home.
Yeah.
[chuckles] Um…
I’m gonna close the door now.
You’re very beautiful.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
-You want to come inside?
-Yes.
[laughs]
[engine starts]
[rain pattering]
Morning.
[thunder rumbling]
I should go.
You should.
[thunder rumbling]
[clears throat]
Orochi says the US Army is shipping guns
back to the States.
Their plan is to sell some of it
before it leaves the port.
The US Army cannot know
that the Shiromatsu is involved.
Makes sense.
You will have to do this on your own.
I understand if you won’t do this,
but if it goes right,
everything will change.
And if it goes wrong?
It will come down on you and no one else.
Sounds like fun.
[thud]
[in Japanese] You hear that?
This is our water. This is our port.
Your dead friend knew that very well.
He said you’d sneak in tonight
to buy all the guns before us.
[laughs]
Your skin is so soft.
Should I lick it?
Brother, I can’t find it.
Where is the money?
[in English] Where is the money?
Shoot him.
[in Japanese] Burn the truck afterwards.
[man] Kneel down.
-[man] Lower the gun.
-Brother…
Lower the gun!
[in Japanese] The guns?
-Where are the guns?
-I don’t know.
Father, I apologize.
It was my idea.
Two Seizu men are dead!
[in English]
It was my idea, not his. I killed them.
Speak Japanese…
or I’ll cut your throat!
If you kill him,
you’ll have to kill me first.
Are you choosing this gaijin
over your family?
[Kiyoshi] Who warned the Seizu?
We brought two million yen in cash.
But the Seizu didn’t find it.
In other words,
someone told them where it would be.
Isn’t that so?
Nick put it under the engine block.
They only looked under the seats.
What’s going on? This could’ve only
happened if someone told them.
Who sent you?
I sent him.
Osaka is ours,
and I sent him to make a statement.
Are you…
the new boss?
Are you the new boss?
[Nick grunting]
[panting]
He fucked Miyu.
That night when you asked him
to take her home.
He is no different from the Seizu.
He takes what he wants.
Wait outside.
Please allow me to do the same.
Good.
[elevator bell dings]
Father.
The Shiromatsu man is here.
Can that man still be trusted?
Yes.
It’s still fine.
Who is the traitor?
[in Japanese] I don’t know.
If you knew, would you tell me?
Yes.
You have no family.
You have no home.
You are a stray dog.
But today…
you may have a home.
You have to decide.
You can drink and join me…
or you can stand here, outside.
[Kiyoshi] Nick.
[in English]
Grab the sakazuki and take it.
[man] From this auspicious moment,
they have become father and son.
Everyone, we will now clap.
Ready.
[all clap]
Congratulations.
[chanting]
[cheering]
[cheering, laughing]
[helicopter whirring]
[in English] She’s 28 years old.
She can meet whoever she wants,
marry whoever she wants.
But not me.
Not yakuza.
The people here, they cannot love anyone.
You understand?
What if I promised you she’d be safe
with me?
What if I told you that before the war,
four men killed Akihiro’s wife
and his son?
Akihiro found them and for three days,
he kept them alive,
begging for their deaths, their mothers,
while he cut off everything
that identified them as human beings.
Yakuza can never have that.
To become a yakuza is a choice.
You trade one type of family for another.
You can never go back.
So why does she work for you?
So I can watch her, keep her safe.
I have many brothers, but only one sister.
She was a virgin.
I don’t think so.
Don’t see my sister.
Congratulations.
Now we are real brothers.
[men laughing]
[man] Thank you for visiting us.
-[Orochi] Let’s go.
-[all] Yes, sir.
Do you know what your tattoo means?
Do you know what it means?
It’s a fable.
The koi fish who can swim up a waterfall
becomes a dragon.
It means you’re arrogant.
What do your tattoos mean?
[Miyu] What?
-Mine?
-Yeah.
Do you get the same one as me? [chuckles]
-[Nick] You have two koi fish.
-I do.
One swimming up…
and one swimming down.
[Nick] I understand.
[Miyu] You do? Tell me.
[Nick] Well…
I guess, in life,
sometimes we fight the current.
And other times…
it’s important to flow with the river.
[pop music playing]
-[man shouts]
-[cheering]
♪ Gomen nasai ♪
♪ I’m so sorry, gomen nasai ♪
♪ I’m so sorry I made you cry ♪
♪ Won’t you forgive me, dear? ♪
♪ Gomen nasai ♪
♪ Nights have been lonely
My days are blue ♪
♪ Because I made a fool of you ♪
♪ Won’t you forgive me, dear? ♪
♪ My butterfly heart ♪
♪ Has brought you pain ♪
♪ Won’t you forgive? Won’t you forget? ♪
♪ Let’s be sweethearts again ♪
♪ Gomen nasai ♪
♪ Nights would be heaven
Love fill my days ♪
Old man, let’s go.
What’s the deal?
Young man, just a little longer.
It’s time to go.
This way, this way. Let’s go.
Cheers.
[together] Cheers.
♪ My butterfly heart ♪
♪ Has brought you pain ♪
[shouting]
♪ Let’s be sweethearts again ♪
♪ Gomen nasai ♪
♪ Nights would be heaven
Love fill my days ♪
[woman giggles]
[no audible dialogue]
♪ I love you, gomen nasai ♪
Seizu tells me
he has a business proposition,
but he doesn’t have the respect
to meet in person.
He sends a kid like you…
and this gaijin.
Do I look like a radio salesman?
I’m not selling you radios.
I’m selling you stock.
In ten years,
they’ll be making more than radios.
After the IPO,
they’ll be pouring money into research.
TV, automobile technology…
[in Japanese]
They have a subsidiary in the US.
Good for them.
Where is Seizu?
He’s in Kobe.
He offers you this opportunity
for a joint venture.
He offers me…
indignity.
Seizu wants my family to come
under his command, and not only that…
he wants me to pay you?
I am just a representative.
And we’re talking about ten percent
of millions in dividends.
In US dollars.
With 400,000 shares, we could make
500 million yen in ten years.
All the Kobe families are participating
in this investment.
Are we in Kobe?
I will not come under the command
of Hiromitsu Seizu.
He doesn’t have the guts to pay me…
but he sends me this college grad boy…
to beg for my money.
Not to a man like that.
I’m just saying
this sounds like a smart investment.
Let’s have the non-Japanese
leave the room. You, leave.
[in English] Nick, get out.
[Kiyoshi] You should go home, brother.
Why? You know I’m right.
It’s not for us to decide.
[Orochi]
Father doesn’t want a war against Seizu.
He’ll bow to him all day long.
He’ll offer our fingers,
but then he spits at Seizu’s money
for his honor.
He’s stuck in the old ways.
You really think
he should share investments with Seizu?
He would rather die.
If you don’t take it, someone else does.
You’re too drunk.
Yeah, I’m drunk. So what?
My head still works fine.
[in English] Stay, brother.
You and I never really talked.
You see that guy?
When I was little, I didn’t go to school.
I worked.
One day, I walk home…
and a chinpira, a wannabe gangster,
puts a knife at my throat.
He takes my money, 200 yen.
I go home to my father.
He’s drunk. Angry.
He takes his glass.
I bleed every fucking place.
I run.
I run all the way to the river, crying.
A boy comes to me.
He says his name is Kiyoshi.
He walks with me
back to my father’s house.
He takes a metal pipe.
He breaks my father’s head.
From that day, I am yakuza.
And Kiyoshi,
he is my brother.
And now…
You understand?
Gaijin.
You understand my English?
Huh?
[Kiyoshi clears throat]
That’s enough. Go home.
Whatever you say, brother.
[clears throat]
Sorry, he’s busy.
-[Orochi in Japanese] Move aside.
-He’s busy.
[Orochi]
You’ve turned into a beautiful woman.
To whom do you owe becoming such a beauty?
Hmm?
-What’s this?
-Don’t touch me.
-Try and stop me.
-Stop it.
I’m not the same person I used to be.
Me neither.
What are you doing here?
I missed our times together.
[laughs]
We were over a long time ago.
I know.
Lonely, aren’t you?
You can’t hide what’s inside your heart.
You…
-You still care about me.
-Stop it.
Why do you tell me to stop? You like this…
No.
Stop.
You wanna be a whore?
That white bastard’s whore?
Why do you like him? Tell me.
Huh?
What does he have that I don’t?
Tell me!
[Miyu gasps]
You think he’s going to protect you?
Is that what you really think?
If that’s the case,
I will make you a whore.
Like every bitch around here.
No, no, stop it! Let me go!
[screaming]
[sobbing]
[Orochi] Sorry.
Sorry.
[muffled introduction]
[muffled cheering]
[crowd cheering]
[drumbeats]
[referee shouts]
[cheering]
[speaking Japanese]
[crowd cheering]
It’s the Shiromatsu.
I heard you were insulted
by my representative’s offer.
I was insulted by you.
You think I have no respect.
I respect you more than you think.
Let me speak with respect.
I’m offering to build a fence around you…
to invite you into my garden.
There, you can retire…
and live for years.
What about my family members?
They can join my family.
They can do as they please.
As long as they do not form
any new family in Osaka.
You call this…
an offer of respect?
You understand nothing
about your father’s generation.
We are wolves.
We’re not dogs.
Can you keep wolves inside a fence?
[cheering]
Careful on your way back to Kobe.
[man] Nick?
Nick fuckin’ Lowell?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
-Wow.
-You look fuckin’ good for a dead man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, it’s me. It’s Paulie.
Just on weekend leave.
[Paulie] Let me buy you a drink.
You got somewhere you need to be?
Or you got five minutes for an old friend,
Captain?
Congratulations.
It’s bullshit.
Three years in Okinawa.
There’s no one fighting anymore,
so what’s the point of this?
I don’t know.
You ever go out there?
Where they dropped the first one?
No.
I did.
The fuckin’ rats
almost built it all up again.
Look at you.
Looks like made
a good fuckin’ life for yourself,
dressed up like a lounge singer.
You live here? Osaka?
I got a little place.
[chuckles]
You weren’t always so calm and quiet.
You know that?
Maybe you just didn’t know me so well.
No, I guess not.
I got leave for another day.
I should come by, see your place.
No.
-No?
-No.
Your five minutes is up.
-Is that how it is, huh?
-Yeah.
Can’t drink with a guy
from your own fuckin’ unit.
Congrats on your stripes.
Yeah? Hey, fuck you.
If I didn’t know better,
I’d say you were dodging court-martial.
Can’t wait to hear what the guys are gonna
say when I tell them who I bumped into.
I’m sure someone would love
to come pay you a visit.
No, you know what? I’m sorry.
Wow.
Why don’t you come back
and have a drink with me?
Old times.
You can see half of Osaka from here.
Not bad, huh?
Americans.
I still got a couple contacts.
Cheers.
Old times’ sake.
Listen.
I know you’re not in the army anymore,
and I can see you got
a good thing going here.
Man, I always liked you.
Don’t worry. Okay?
Your secret’s safe with me.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
All right.
Jesus, man.
I mean…
Yeah.
You like whiskey?
I have got a surprise for you.
Do your best.
-I’m sorry.
-What?
[gasps, gurgles]
[Nick] Miyu.
[knocking]
Miyu?
-Are you okay? Hey.
-[whimpers]
-Hey.
-Just…
Who did this to you?
-Just go.
-Who did this to you?
There’s a baby in me.
It’s ours.
Who hurt you?
[in Japanese]
It doesn’t matter who did this to me.
Just leave it.
Maybe you want to protect me…
but I don’t want that.
Do you get it?
I’ve been fine my whole life.
I’m fine with it.
[knocking]
Who’s there?
Nick.
I betrayed you.
She’s gonna have a kid.
You want me to leave? I’ll leave.
You say the word.
You leave my sister…
with your child?
Is that who you are?
I don’t know.
Get inside.
[in Japanese] Hang on.
[in English] You know what these are?
They were my father’s.
He left our home when I was young.
My sister was a baby.
The day he left, he was drunk,
and he came to me in the night with these.
And he said,
“This is daisho.
One for war, one for honor.
One to kill, one to decapitate.
One for murder, one for suicide.”
Katana and wakizashi.
This never left a warrior’s side,
even in his sleep.
It was his honor.
My father told me the daisho was mine now.
Because I was the one
with a family to look after. My sister.
She’s yours to protect now.
You understand?
If you are my brother, take them.
What?
There’s just one other thing.
What is it?
[panting]
That will do.
Okay.
[Kiyoshi grunts]
-Thank you.
-You’re welcome, brother.
Thanks to you, I’m now in a conflict
with my father’s childhood friend.
Do you know what the other families think?
Does it look like I’m in control?
Hey. I’m talking to you. Look at me.
The Shiromatsu family is broken.
They pose no threat.
Trust me.
You don’t need to get your hands dirty.
[giggling]
[man] Welcome, Mr. Shiromatsu.
I’m all yours.
[man] Please come in.
It’s a beautiful day.
Beautiful day.
[choking]
-[gunshot]
-[Akihiro gasping]
[Kiyoshi] Father.
[in Japanese] Get in, Nick.
What’s going on? Where is Orochi?
What the hell?
We will circle the streets
until we find them.
Please duck down.
Fuck.
[Nick] Are you okay?
[tires squealing]
Kiyoshi.
Kiyoshi. Kiyoshi.
-No. Oh, jeez.
-[moaning]
[in Japanese] Brother.
[in English] It’s okay.
It’s okay.
[man] Orochi, Yasushi, Banjo, Shuichi,
Ryuhei, Taro, Ichiro,
Kazuo, Yuta, Eiichi.
That car was full of Seizu,
not our people.
[man] Orochi!
You can’t be sure.
A fifth of our men have betrayed us.
We cannot go to war with Seizu.
We cannot win this!
[in Japanese] It doesn’t matter who wins.
You should care who wins.
They will send the killers into hiding
in Kyoto, Nara, Tokyo.
Now is not the time.
Then…
when is the time?
This is for your sake too.
Don’t you get it?
Is this war?
Nick.
Miyu is outside. You should go to her.
[no audible dialogue]
[screaming]
[Kentaro] You’re making me hard.
[woman]
You like this kind of thing, right?
[Kentaro] Where are you going?
You fucking gaijin.
That’s right.
[man] Hey, stop.
[Akihiro] What is it?
-I have a message from the Seizu's boss.
-[grunts]
Please come tomorrow to the port factory,
which is neutral territory,
with no guns.
He said he wants to end the war.
He sent you here to tell me this?
Yes.
Thank you.
You can leave now.
He told me to bring back your response.
Right now?
Yes.
Understood.
I will meet him.
[man] Father.
I know you are here!
Get out here now
and show me your dirty face.
What are you doing?
I’m here!
Here!
[Hiromitsu] You are a stubborn old man.
A tough one.
I’ll give you that.
You killed many of my most important men.
What do you want?
I don’t want anything from you.
But I have someone here who might.
Orochi.
You are my son.
It’s not too late.
Come back.
I wanted to.
[all shouting]
My son.
The Shiromatsu family no longer exists.
The head of the Seizu is a generous man.
He wants all of you to live.
[in English] For you…
I can offer you peace if you leave Osaka
and your woman behind.
We make no promises for her safety
if you stay.
[in Japanese] Do you accept?
[in English] You’re all idiots.
[Takeshi] You are a traitor.
-Fight me.
-Takeshi.
Fight me.
Fight me!
Orochi!
[gunshot]
[winces, groans]
[Nick shouts]
-Get out!
-[crowd murmuring]
[officer yelling]
What--
Shh.
Akihiro.
He’s dead. He’s gone.
Orochi, he killed him.
Now, you pack a bag and we go together.
Yes?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Now get your things, and we leave.
Now. Now.
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
Hello?
Nick.
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
[exhales]
-You!
-[shouting]
[all yelling, grunting]
[panting]
[Hiromitsu] Look at me.
[in English] What do you want?
[in English] I want you to allow me…
to kill him.
Give this warrior a weapon
and let him show us
how strong and brave he really is.
What do you have to fear...
[in Japanese] brother?
[in English] You walk into my home.
You take my brother,
you poison my father’s mind.
Poison him against me.
Someone has to put out the fire.
You think you are a yakuza with this?
You aren’t a yakuza.
You are a gaijin. Outsider.
You are just the way my brother found you.
Get up.
Get up!
No. I won’t fight you.
[shouting]
[in Japanese] Don’t shoot!
[gasping]
[panting]
[Hiromitsu in English] Go now. Go.