Wow... where are we?
In the future.
The final battle between the
Men and machines.
Oh, brilliant! Just a
Nice way to save me!
Perhaps the only.
- Here comes the crazy fool...
- Hold fast.
Accelerates... is approaching!
Go, Go! It is approaching!
Ah!
Well, what the plan?
You have a plan, true?
Skynet.
What Skynet?
S.
I ask because there
We are directing?
You do not want to know.
Here is where it starts!
Go, go!
Approaches...
Go to the right! Right!
Oh, no! Go to the left!
Left, Left!
No... go right, I feel.
To the right, we go!
John, I beg you to stop
To help me.
Behind us!
I noticed.
Ahhhhh!
Hey, you do not need to worry for me...
I am well.
Here...
For God was really close.
Bad sign.
That?
What was that?
There are others, walk!
Careful!
We go!
Finiscila make noise!
All well?
To the ground!
Hey! Head to watermelon!
Your friend?
It was my roommate at college.
Take its ammunition.
Ammunition?
Excellent.
Not to do so.
Huge.
Well, we go inside Skynet.
I was afraid that I told...
- We must move.
- Andiamo.
Fast!