Get down.
Get down!
Now...
Take it.
I do not fear death.
Don't you take another step!
What do you want?
I am Black Hawk.
Son of Chief Yellow Hawk.
I know who you are.
What do you want?
My wife...
...Elk Woman.
Our son, Little Bear.
And my sister, Living Woman.
A gift... for the lady.
I would...
be honored...
...if she would wear these.
And Captain, I--
Enough!
Sit down.
Experiencing loss such as she has...
...requires great strength.
The Comanche are still near.
They are Rattlesnake people. The worst kind.
I know who they are.
They do not discriminate.
They will track and attack your party. Ours, too.
We are ready for them.
You don't understand
how grave the situation.
They are of unsound mind.
And very dangerous.
Remove the binds.
We can be of great help.
I'm not removing them.
You are making this
more difficult than necessary.
Captain?
What?
The Chief is still uneasy.
He says Comanche will soon return.
He thinks we should...
talk to them.
You and us.
I disagree.
But Captain--
Hold your tongue.
I've given you my opinion.
I told you.
We must stand as one or they will kill us.
When one hunts for a rattlesnake...
...one may find it.
But it bites...
before one can ever see it.
Thank you.
I am Elk Woman.
Father!
Grandfather!
Tell me.
They've taken Mother!
Horses with iron feet.
Fur hunters. Three of them.
When whitemen return to their shelter...
we advance.
As one.
You are not well.
We will handle them.
My daughter. I lead.
We discuss no further.
Chief...
I'm sorry for what happened to the women.
Is there anything I can do to help?
The rains are approaching. We should move.
Chief...
Our treatment of the Natives
cannot be forgiven.
Please...
accept this tobacco.
Have mercy on us.
For you, Grandpapa.
To make you feel better.
Thank you for this gift.
It will give me life.
Are you well enough to continue?
Very soon.
After my body is nourished by the earth.
We're very close to your home.
You speak the truth.
Chief...
I had a friend...
I lost many friends
and you have lost many as well.
They are a great loss for us both...
but we know death comes to us all.
Don't look back, my friend.
Go in a good way.
A part of me dies with you.
Valley of the Bears, Montana
We're home.
It's never looked more beautiful.
Little Bear, a gift.
It's now your time to put this to use.
Caesar...
one of the bravest men I've ever read.
Thank you.