- Shuji, what's the matter with you?!
- Run!
Nakamichi, come with me.
- Shuji!
- Hurry!
Why are you running?
Come with me!
Nakamichi, run, quickly!
There always is someone following you.
Tax collectors?
Today the police
has interrupted my public speech.
Maybe you were shouting
in the loudspeaker...
I was only talking cinema!
One day you might get yourself
into real trouble.
You aren't Yukio Mishima!
Times have changed,
the people and the police are not
as tolerant as they used to be.
Hadn't it been for this evening's
projection, I wouldn't have run away.
If they arrest you,
there won't be a projection.
I am tired!
Wherever I go,
there's someone who wants
to stop me with some kind of law.
Why do I need a permit for?!
Is there no place left
where I can show a film?!
That's absurd!
Cinema will die.
May those who destroy
the cinema be cursed!
"CINEPHILE TOKYO - 78TH PROJECTION"
"BUSTER KEATON: SHERLOCK JR.
HIROSHl SHIMIZU: OYA"
Cinema's artistic value
is dying!
Nowadays there only
exist entertainment films.
Let's not forget the time
when cinema had grandeur.
When everyone of us could enjoy
as well the artistic side.
As the entertainment side of a film.
I beg you.
Watch again the old films.
The multiplexes have gained
the upper hand.
Let's take back our cinema.
Let's grab it from the moneygrubbers!
Only this way
the cinema
will shine a new light and
will inspire us.
Let's let them rather starve,
what do we care?!
They don't have the right to destroy
the great cinema.
Little by little they're putting it under!
They're holding it locked up
like a bird in a cage
and then they'll kill it.
We can't let them do that!
The cinema. Like us.
Must be free to roam around the world.
The true cinema
should be free.
"AKIRA KUROSAWA"
Sensei...
...what would you do in my place?
The great masters' legacy
is dying with every day.
I want to make the kind of films
you and the other masters made.
I want to make my films.
Cinema is dying.
I want to survive!
Hi everyone
and welcome to the 78th projection.
There's a wind blowing tonight.
But it's really worth seeing
this films.
They are two silent films,
the wind bristle will provide
a pleasant sound track.
I hope you'll agree.
As you well know,
we don't have where to
project the films,
that's why we had to move
in this small space.
Thanks to Tokyo Cinephile's support
we can project these
beautiful films here,
and, for that, I give them my thanks.
So,
tonight we'll see...
a 1924 Buster Keaton silent film,
and a Hiroshi Shimizu
silent short.
They were both shot some 80 years ago,
and they still strike us
by their topicality.
After the projection
we'll be having a discussion.
Have a nice viewing!
Let's enjoy the wind sound track!
Did you know your brother
was working for us?
Did you?
He used to say that,
if he'd manage to sell your films,
he'd pay the money back,
but that moment never came,
so he went on asking for money
at high interest rates.
Twelve years...
Shingo was with us for twelve years:
He was like a son to me.
Whatever we'd ask him to do,
he'd do it without complaining.
I trusted Shingo.
But those were the boss's money
and Shingo knew it.
I tried to help him buy some time...
but he
went to make money somewhere else
and without telling us anything
sold our turf to the Chinese mob.
We had to make him pay.
Your brother was a shilo,
a professional,
he knew the rules.
Whoever borrows money
he knows very well what can happen
to him if he doesn't repay his debt.
This
is the grand total of Shingo's debt.
¥12,540,000.
I don't have this kind of money.
The only thing that I've got
are three films shot with the money
my brother lent me.
You've got two weeks,
only two weeks to make good
on this debt.
And remember,
we're also adding the interest.
If you don't,
the Boss will resort to measures.
We'll force you to work for us,
or we'll kill you
to pocket your insurance.
This was your brother's bottle.
Tuesday, July 27th.
23:27
It seems I can't get hold of you.
I'm in big trouble.
I'm too ashamed to answer.
What will I do without you?
Brother...
Shuji. It's me.
- What will I do?
- Answer!
They are after me.
Where did you end up?
Shuji. I am out of time.
Where are you?
You're never at home.
Call me.
I'm in danger. I must talk to you.
The money?
- Have another game!
- Shut up!
- I'll lend you the money.
- Get lost!
You know you are not safe in here...
This is the safest place for me.
Where's the mahjong money?
Time has run out.
I'll have it tomorrow.
Listen...
Don't let him in,
if he doesn't have money.
Uncle, he's Shingo's brother...
I don't care, throw him out.
If the Boss finds out he's here,
we're in deep shit.
Take it,
it's part of the money I owe you.
If you play smart with the Boss,
you'll end up like your brother did.
Tell me where my brother was killed.
What do you want to do?
There were blood stains
of his blood on the window sill.
I cleaned everything up.
What the fuck did you say?!
Son of a bitch!
That's not how you play.
You've cheated!
Don't you play smart with me.
Asshole!
Say that again if you have guts!
Repeat what you've just said!
How dare you?!
Speak, you son of a bitch!
Look into my eyes and
repeat what you've said!
Understood, asshole?
That's enough!
Go fuck yourself!
- Who is he?
- Shingo's brother.
Hey, you, Shingo's brother...
- You must leave!
- I'll buy you a drink.
Please, Takagaki-san!
I am Takagaki, Masaki's friend, got it?
Yes.
I need money,
give me something to work, please.
Something to work?!
What can you do?
Tell me, what can you do?
I can do everything.
Everything?!
Really?
Go and bring that piece of merchandise.
Bring it here, asshole!
Takagaki-san,
he doesn't belong here.
Slow down, Yoko-chan,
Shingo's brother says
he can do everything:
I now want him to prove us that.
Hey, you!
Put this gun into your mouth
and press the trigger.
What's the matter?
You said you could everything, try!
Come on!
I don't want to die.
What the fuck are you saying?!
You don't know if there's a bullet inside,
not even if it's unloaded!
You're a film director, right?
I like movies.
Doesn't it look to you like if
you were in a movie?
Come on,
do it!
How much will you give me?
Count it.
¥140,000.
¥140,000... Well, what will you do?
Takagaki-san...
Fuck!
Why is it unloaded?!
Take it!
- May I?
- Yes.
- Fucking asshole!
- Forgive me.
¥11,395,000 are still missing.
You keep it.
Hiroshi,
did you enjoy the show?
He says he is Shingo's brother.
This son of a bitch didn't load the gun.
He only made me lose time!
I am sorry!
What's the matter, Hiroshi?
Any problems?
Hiroshi,
hit Shingo's brother.
Make him wake up!
What do you mean?
If you hit him, I'll give him ¥10,000.
Do you agree, or not?
¥10.000 for a punch.
Maybe that's too little for
Shingo's brother?
Guys. Punch him in the head!
- But I'll only give you ¥5,000
for each punch. - Takagaki-san...
Hit me. Please.
But only...
in the place where my brother died.
How many more punches
can you still stand.
Champion Shimazaki?
Come on!
That's enough, stop it.
Chill out, Yoko, he'll make it,
he needs money.
Nice hit. Bro'!
Well. Are you throwing the towel?
Projection No 17:
"The Tales of the Pale Moon After
the Rain" by Kenji Mizoguchi,
from 1952,
33 viewers.
Projection No 36:
"Lola Montes" by Max Ophüls,
from 1955,
18 viewers.
Projection No 47:
"The Boy" by Nagisa Oshima.
From 1969.
30 viewers.
You can hit him harder!
What the fuck are you saying?
Take this!
Max Ophüls...
Nice hit, much better!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10...
KO!
Twelve punches, that's all.
How many hit had he already taken?
Eighteen, that's a total of 30,
that makes ¥150,000.
Projection No 12:
"Johnny Guitar" by Nicholas Ray,
from 1954.
47 viewers.
Projection No 39:
"ll Posto" by Ermanno Olmi,
from 1961,
Projection No 31, "Throne of Blood"
by Akira Kurosawa...
- What the fuck is he blabbering?
- Haven't got a clue.
Enough, that's over!
Projection No 12...
"Johnny Guitar" by Nicholas Ray,
Not yet.
Hit me.
Tell him to hit me, please.
Takagaki-san,
he wants you to hit him too.
630,000 plus 145,000.
Did you know my brother well?
You assholes who have ruined the cinema,
you morons who have smeared
the cinema with money,
you who cheat the audience
in the name of entertainment...
Shame on you, morons!
Shame!
If you want to be a punching bag,
there are places where you can do that,
go there,
go in a safe place.
If I may not do it in here,
l won't do it anywhere else.
Why in here?
It must be in here,
in the bathroom where my
brother was killed.
Here they can hit me as much
as they want. I don't feel any pain.
For my brother's sake.
Let me do it in here.
Listen,
l want to tell you only one thing...
If you want to get smart with the Boss,
like Shingo did, don't count on me.
Is that clear?
I've understood.
Then go...
Leave!
It is dangerous.
It's more dangerous this time.
How many days until it's due?
Counting today, 11 days.
He won't make it.
Please,
I need money.
Instead of the punching bag,
hit my stomach.
Please.
¥1,300,000.
"KENJl MIZOGUCHI"
Shit movie! Shit movie!
Shit movie!
Whose turn is it?
Get up!
Stay back!
Hit him!
Shit movie!
Shit movie, shit movie...
What's the date today?
The twelfth.
Why don't you also join in?
I've run out of money.
How much does he charge a punch?
Yoko has raised the price:
today it's ¥8,000 a punch.
Hiroshi, why don't you also hit him?
For me...
...it's enough hearing him scream.
Support true cinema!
Only entertainment films
exist nowadays.
In the past,
the cinema
was either true art,
either true entertainment.
Today,
there still are directors
who know how to do their job.
Who know very well
what quality cinema is.
Go watch their films!
You'll find
truth.
Art
and. Even. Pure entertainment.
You look like the actor who plays the
father character in Ozu 's films.
Ozu?
I've seen his movies on TV:
They are really touching.
Ozu is one of the greatest directors
that ever lived in the world.
Projection No 58,
"Late Spring" by Yasujiro Ozu.
"The Searchers" by John Ford.
A masterpiece.
Two of the greatest endings
in the history of cinema.
Projection No 51:
"Shadows" by John Cassavetes,
from 1958, 62 viewers.
Come on!
Hi everyone.
Tonight I'll show you
Kaneto Shindo's "The Naked Island".
From 1960.
I think
"The Naked Island"
is one of the most important
Japanese black and white films
from all times.
At that time,
black and white Japanese films
were appreciated world wide.
We'll have time
to talk about this later on.
I'll answer your questions
after the projection.
For now,
enjoy watching "The Naked Island".
Did you get into a fight?
No, I fell down.
- All these bruises from falling down?
- Yes.
You lost it and came to blows,
didn't you?
No, I just stumbled.
Alright, I'll pretend I believe you.
You really are something else!
You go on with the projections,
even in the state you are in.
That's the least I can do,
as long as I can't make a film:
Nothing will prevent me.
What about you, Nakamichi?
Where are you with your script?
I've finished and showed it around,
but nothing gives.
It's been three years
I haven't made a film,
I feel I'm going nuts.
What about you?
I'm working on a script.
And how is it going?
I'm putting all of me into it.
Hello?
Speaking.
What are your intentions?
Hey!
Hiroshi, here's ¥30,000.
Now I'll make him KO.
The Boss doesn't want
another death in here.
Go away!
But he won't be able to repay
his debt this way.
Who do you think you are talking to?
I must do it in here.
Even if you kill me,
l won't leave from here.
Then, you'll pay rent for the bathroom:
¥100,000 a day.
These are the Boss's orders.
There's nothing to discuss.
You have three days to pay your debt
and the rent.
I'll leave two of my men here.
You'll pay another ¥40,000
for them and their car.
If you die,
they'll get rid of your corpse.
I knew right from the start
that it'd happen.
I had warned you.
I'm sorry,
there's nothing I can do for you now.
Time has almost run out.
Remember just one thing:
You can't trust the Boss.
He every time says something else.
Why don't you give them the money
and get out of it?
I'll lend you the money.
This way...
...we'll end all this.
You'll give it back when you can.
If it's true you want to lend me money,
hit me for every yen that's left.
I can't hit you.
As you have your reasons
for not hitting me,
I too have my reasons
for not accepting money without being hit.
Money is not the issue.
Had that been the case,
I'd have gone rob a bank.
Until now,
Masaki-san,
I've caused a lot of trouble,
and I am very sorry for that.
You've even gone against the Boss
to help me out.
What's more,
in this bathroom,
you've allowed me to make money
and for that I am in your debt.
I had to pay the rent to those guys,
that's why I made less money today.
Tomorrow, I promise you,
I'll make up the difference.
"YASUJIRO OZU"
How much have we made?
¥330,000.
How many days do I have left?
Two days.
You must pay the rent.
I must make more money!
Hit me. Punch me in the face!
The auction starts at ¥30,000!
Hit me in the face!
Come on. Hit me in the face!
I need money,
hit me in the face.
Cowards!
Hit me in the face!
Come on, hit me!
I bid ¥30,000!
More, more!
35,000!
More. More!
Kill me!
45,000!
Hit me, hit me!
I'll pummel him now!
- 47,000!
- More. More!
I'm biding 51,000!
More!
I'm alive! I'm alive, damn it!
I'm alive!
I need money!
Hit me, hit me!
¥710,000...
That's not enough.
Hiroshi, Hiroshi...
How much have we made?
¥710,000.
That's not enough.
"LAST TWO DAYS, ¥10,000 A PUNCH"
I can't die for ¥3,619,000.
I want to live. I want to make films.
I want to live, I want to make films.
"LAST DAY"
"THE DEADLINE IS TOMORROW,
¥3,619,000"
"I WANT TO TEST MYSELF"
"I'LL GET 100 PUNCHES"
"I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL MAKE IT."
"WHILE THEY'LL BE HITTING ME,
"I'LL REMEMBER THE BEST 100 FILMS
IN MY LIFE."
"100 FILMS, 100 PUNCHES"
"THAT'S ALL"
That's enough now!
Cinema is not a whore.
Cinema is art.
Gentlemen.
Shall we begin?
I've kept you waiting.
This way, please.
Shuji-sama wants 100 punches.
Bet on how many he'll be able to stand.
Any one of you can hit him.
Whose turn is it?
The cinema as an art is dying.
Those who make big budget films.
Those who make superficial movies.
Are killing the cinema!
The multiplexes have
gained the upper hand.
Let's take back our cinema.
Let's grab it from the moneygrubbers!
We must bring the true
cinema back to life!
So that happens.
You must watch real films.
In the past. The cinema was
either art. Or entertainment.
In the past we were capable
of making quality cinema.
Don't forget that.
Let's see to that!
Today, multiplex cinema
only fulfills the most
trivial entertainment.
It's fair that entertainment films
should also exist.
But we mustn't lose the opportunity
of watching quality films.
We shouldn't forget them.
True cinema...
...isn't based on money.
True cinema is made
of flesh and blood
and shows true images.
Not fake ones.
There still are directors who
know how to do their job.
Who know very well what
quality cinema is.
Such directors exist all over the world.
Go to the cinemas to see their films.
Please!
You'll find
truth.
Art
and. Even. Real entertainment.
Support...
...the directors
by going to watch the real films!
Please.
See again the old movies.
Help us to bring the true
cinema back to life!
The cinema. Like us.
Must be free
to roam around the world!
True cinema must be free.
That's how things should be.
Come on!
Get back, get back!
It's 30,000.
Come on. Come on!
That's enough now!
Cinema is not a whore.
Cinema is art.
"THE VOID"
"THE ACCOUNT HAS BEEN SETTLED"
Well?
How about you staying and
working with us?
For the last time,
lend me some money.
What?!
What have you said?
How much do you want?
¥35,000,000.
What for?
You've just put your life on the line
to repay a debt.
Why don't we ask the Boss?
Wait here.
Camera...
Action!