♪ Once you've had a taste of her
you'll never be the same ♪
♪ Yeah, she'll make you go insane. ♪
Sing it Puss!
♪ Upside, inside out... ♪
Give it up guys, you're
getting me a headache.
That's really sweet Gingy.
You ever heard of ginger snap?
Aw, wizzers on you guys.
Come on, they just having fun.
They really not that bad.
Not that bad?
I will take that as a compliment, princess.
- You should.
- Simon?
Because I rarely give them.
Easy Simon. The competition
hasn't even started, yet.
I can't help being judgmental.
It's who I am.
Alrighty. Who's up for little contest then?
Yeah, bring it on!
Welcome to, Far Far Away Idol.
Where you, that's right, you at home
get a vote, along with our judges.
Shrek, Fiona and Simon.
To crown the next,
Far Far Away Idol.
First up tonight...
It's Donkey time.
♪ The heat was on, ♪
♪ rising to the top burn yeah! ♪
♪ Everybody's going strong ♪
♪ That was when my spark got hot ♪
♪ I heard somebody say ♪
♪ Burn baby burn! Disco inferno! ♪
♪ Burn baby burn! Burn that mama down...! ♪
You on fire Donkey!
♪ Burn baby burn! ♪
No, you really on fire!
Oh yeah, yeah!
AHHHH!
♪ Domo arigato, ♪
♪ Mr. Roboto, ♪
♪ Domo ♪
♪ Domo. ♪
Come on, get real Pinocchio
I find his performance
quite wooden, actually.
♪ Some boys take a beautiful girl ♪
♪ And hide her away
from the rest of the world ♪
♪ I want to be the one to walk
in the sun. ♪
Yeah you go!
Girl?
Yeah. Go girl and get a extreme
make over and some singing lessons.
♪ Burn to the ground,
I break through the crowd ♪
♫ I'm on the hunt, I'm after you ♫
♪ I smell like I sound,
I'm lost and I'm found ♪
♫ And I'm hungry like the wolf ♫
Hungry? It sound like I gonna die!
What?
- I'm hungry for some talent, here.
- Oh aye.
And the dress, hideous.
♪ I'm too sexy for my shirt
too sexy for my shirt ♪
♪ So sexy it hurts ♪
Oh!
♪ And I'm a model you know what I mean ♪
♪ And I shake my little tush on the cat ♪
- AHH!
- Oh!
That was the artist formerly
known as Prince... Charming.
♪ We can see clearly now,
the rain has gone, ♪
♪ We can see all obstacles in our way ♪
♪ Sugar... ♪
♪ Ah honey honey. ♪
♪ You are my candy girl... ♪
They're so sweet together.
I just know that you say that Fiona.
What's next? A singing doughnuts?
♪ I, ♪
♪ am hooked on a feeling, ♪
♪ I'm high on believing ♪
I couldn't agree more Tinky.
Heard, line and stinker.
♪ I ♪
♪ You keep saying you
got something for me. ♪
♪ Something you call love, but confess. ♪
♪ Hey, these boots are made for walking, ♪
♪ And that's just what they'll do ♪
Arriba!
♪ One of these days these boots
are gonna walk all over you. ♪
The cat got my tongue and possibly my vote.
Always breaking the rules.
♪ What I like about you. ♪
♪ You hold me tight. ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Oh, tell me I'm the only one. ♪
♪ You gonna come over tonight. ♪
♫ Yeah ♫
♫ Keep on whispering in my ear. ♫
Oger all impression. Rather wonderful.
♪ Cause it's true ♪
♪ That's what I like about you ♪
♫ Yeah Yeah ♫
Hey!
♪ That's what I like about you ♪
And now!
Who will be named.
Far far Away's next idol.
Will it be,
Pinocchio
Doris.
- The Big Bad Wolf.
- Pick me!
Charming.
- The Three Blind Mice.
- Oh! Oh!
Gingy.
- Captain Hook.
- Me me!
Puss In Boots.
- Shrek and Fiona.
- Pick me!
- Or...
- Me!
Yes you too Donkey.
And the next Far Far Away Idol is...
No,.. You got to be joking.
Nope. It's me everyone.
♪ For what is a man. ♪
♪ What has he got ♪
♪ If not himself ♪
♪ Then he has not ♪
♪ To say the things ♪
♪ He truly feels ♪
♪ And not the words ♪
♪ Of one who kneels. ♪
♪ The record shows ♪
♪ I took the blows ♪
♪ And did it my ♪
♪ Way ♪
Ladies and gentleman our time is up here
But we are look for to seeing
you next time on.
Far Far Away Idol.