Joining where there is more fun;
danishbits.invite@gmail.com
www.DanishBits.org
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Eduardo Deacon.
- Eddie.
- Sharing?
- Third battalion. Marine Infantry.
- Postings?
- Three.
In 2011 and 2014.
- On what dates?
- Three in a row.
Sangin district?
- Was it as bad as that was said?
- Yes.
- Physical hemisphere?
- No.
- Is there something you do not want?
- I want it all.
- Do you want to clean the toilets?
- I will do everything.
Your psychological evaluations
have passed, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Listen up.
You are now in our database,
so the trip was not in vain.
However, we do not have anything to suit you.
- What about the job I came for?
- Was allocated a week ago.
- I saw it on the page two days ago?
- Our system is stopping.
Hear. I have been home for a year now.
I have not worked a single day.
My old car falls apart.
My wife and child are two states away.
So when I say I want to do
everything, I mean everything.
I do this every day and
it will never be easier.
Also enter the minimum wage into the profile.
- You are a commander and have the right to more.
- I can not wait for that.
I need one now.
Have a good day.
Wait!
Minimum wage. Shorter working hours.
- And 40 minutes from here.
- That means nothing.
The job did not arrive because your
evaluations were not intersected.
- a typo error
- Safely enough.
Thanks.
- You start tonight.
- Javel.
All-wheel drive and armored
Like last week.
- Charges?
- On the back of the car 2.
Translated by UNiTY
www.DanishBits.org
How did the testify?
As a child.
We do not arrive until
about an hour and a half.
Not in this weather.
We are lucky... hello?
The smoke signal.
Check your phone.
No signal.
It must be the storm.
The road is still closed, right?
Jo. Why?
We get guests from behind.
It's car 2.
There are cars from behind.
Can we identify them?
Car 3?
Car 3, can you hear us?
- The radios are down.
- There is something wrong.
See.
What the hell?
Move!
Cover me!
Out of the car!
Hear.
When I say so you run
against the forest.
Do not look back, continue
until you find someone.
Now! Run!
We got 9 out of 10.
The goal is gone.
Get cleaned up.
Hello?
Eddie?
Where are you?
Hear...
I have found a job.
It's great.
- Where?
- Nearby.
So I stay here a little bit yet.
Are you okay?
Eddie?
I'm fine.
- They have sent...
- I'm fine.
There are also doctors here...
I'll be back.
I just have to work through something.
Silvia is here.
She asks for you all the time.
Say that I love her.
Goodbye.
Can I help?
Eddie Deacon.
Regarding the job.
The papers?
Thanks.
Okay.
You start with $ 15 per
hour and no overtime.
Two breaks in one block.
Understood?
Yes.
Eddie Deacon, this is the
shopping center in Ridgeside.
We go to Montclair department store.
Great location.
Built in 1986, never modernized.
Shops with clothes for the whole family.
However, the sports department stops.
The barrel at the end at a time.
Keep it clean
Our headquarters.
You will receive a box.
Write it on your free time.
What...?
It does not work.
It must be the weather.
Now you have to meet the team.
I'm Vince.
Natholdet and the boss.
The princess here is Mason.
He is too good at his job, and
thinks he should sell houses.
- He is here for the sake of wages only.
- Yes, what else?
That is why we call him Løn-Mason.
You make it the only
one and no one laughs.
He understands that.
- Then what's the matter?
- Touch me and I'll throw up.
Thanks.
You're missing something? Water?
Cover me for an hour.
Just take a little.
It brings us to...
... staff department.
In the bed we have Ruby.
She has taken double watches for
two days now. So she's allowed.
We have no choice anyway...
Just look.
No fan of thunderstorm, what?
What do you say to lightning?
I only show him it.
30 days and a security course,
you can get your own.
But until then you have to look at me.
There is one more.
Johnny, how are you?
Where are you?
In the noses.
It's Zone D in normal language.
It's Johnny Changway, -
- but I call him "Levevej",
he lives almost here.
In the noses?
Yes, you see...
It looks like a jumper with noses.
But otherwise it looks like a gun.
Now you will have a tour.
Five zones. A-E.
Montclair, from where we
came from, is Zone A.
You should also dress well.
Take it on.
First stop. Zone B.
Shopper road.
Here is all shopping.
If you want to buy something delicious
for the wife, then this is the place.
Zone C. Madafdelingen.
Everything here kills you.
Take a packed lunch.
Just around the corner you
can see the parking lot.
There are the fine gentlemen.
- and blinking with the
lights but doing nothing.
Zone D. Hover this part.
But they compete over here.
Once a week it should run so
that the battery does not die, -
So maybe you're lucky, El Fuego.
If it's a real name?
And now for the big finale.
The second department store.
Which is much better.
Here is amazing.
Here are designer clothes, branded goods -
- and coins with one's name on.
Our headquarters should be there, -
- but Montclair was here first,
so we were sent that way.
They replaced us with a barricade
It was actually the tour.
Questions?
- Only one.
- Fire away.
Barricades, power gun,
five guards at night.
Not to offend anyone, but you
were forgotten in the 90's.
Funny now, cowboy.
You're not from the area, right?
What are you really doing here?
- I needed a job.
- Javel.
Here comes the next town.
The population is 12.640.
Last year there were 48 murders.
Herovre is another city.
The population is 25,328.
- Last year there were 81 murders.
- Myth.
Lots of meth.
And a violent gang.
So many steal to get food.
You quickly catch the essence.
You are in pretty good shape.
So I have to ask...
The army?
I only have a sixth sense.
Were you a sergent?
- Commander.
- Really?
Oh boy. Not bad.
I have experience with your kind, -
- and you forget who decides.
- No no...
- That's the way it's supposed to sound.
I knew we would be friends.
I do not usually touch guys.
Sorry.
Let's move on.
You have your radio.
You must always be on channel 4.
When you go round,
you always go twice.
If you hear or see
something suspicious, -
- Then sign it in before doing anything.
- So you do not do anything wrong.
- Javel.
- Welcome to, soldier.
- Really?
You know... good luck.
You are not too scared of darkness?
Do the cameras still have power?
He also thinks about everything.
We control it.
Give it a moment.
We are ready.
- Continue, soldier.
- Received.
Fool.
Okay.
The people there is something outside?
Can you see someone?
It's a little girl.
Repeat. A girl?
- She is afraid. I'll shut up.
- No, wait.
No I will not.
Quiet now.
A moment.
Come on.
They are coming!
Calm. There is no one.
Who's coming?
What the hell is it now?
- Do not ask.
She is cold.
Bring a blanket.
- Where is her ID?
- She's 12 years old.
So she has no ID.
- What do we do?
- Call the police.
- She's completely from it.
- Is she stabbed?
I hope that's the problem.
The phones are dead.
Do you have a signal?
No.
Look straight
It is at Montclair.
Hello?
Hello.
Such. Are you okay?
I'm looking for my daughter.
She is 11 years old.
- We have her. She's okay.
- Thank goodness.
Her father is standing here.
Come down with her.
Hold on.
She was scared when she arrived.
Someone was after her.
Farmand is not always the good one.
Is there a problem?
- What's her name?
- Jamie.
Why did she stop at night?
We scolded, then she stopped.
It is her.
She has some scratch marks on her
arm, but otherwise she is okay.
- She ran through the woods.
- What is her date of birth?
April 16, 2004.
- Eye color?
- They are brown.
Does she have hangers?
Sir?
No.
What is wrong with you?
He is new.
Your father.
No!
Children.
Find her!
- What is it?
- Have no idea.
Jeez.
1.25 million.
In unlabeled,
useless US dollars.
Delete the surveillance, it was the storm
and you've never seen me and the girl.
- What do you want with her?
- Nothing good.
- I can not.
- Why?
- She's only...
- And that makes it less true?
Give me a smile and get rich, -
- or you will all
die in a cruel way.
And nobody gets rich.
When I say cruel,
- I mean truly cruel.
Go away, Vance.
If you leave the door,
your answer is no.
- Do you decide here or not?
- Go away now.
Listen up. You are five guards
with power guns and strips.
You have no phone connection.
The nightmare police patrol does not come.
You can not stay
out or live alive.
What do you choose?
What do you choose, Vance?
- Vance? Vance!
- Shut up!
I decide.
"They do not let us go.
- I'm not saying it again!
They can not.
Think about it.
That's right.
What are you doing?
The real leader.
You should let him take the trash.
To get everyone in the building killed.
The country thanks for your service.
She is in the mall.
Exit the search.
Get all off the road.
- What do we do?
There are two approach roads.
There and there. Sniper on both.
There must be men you trust.
Spread them around the parking lot.
The radios are secured,
but no talk, -
- unless it is vital to life
Jamie?
My name is Eddie.
And...
I know what happens.
You must trust someone.
You know that too well.
You know what?
I have a daughter of your age.
Her name is Sylvia.
And...
That was my mother too.
Jamie?
I knew you were smart.
I need dry clothes.
- Javel.
- And food.
You should not speak to
me, as I was a child.
It's a deal.
May I turn around now?
It's not even charged.
One last thing. You must
promise to protect me.
Yes.
- On scouting?
- You would not be treated like a child.
There is nothing in the way of scouting.
Oh God. You are the witness.
- Which?
- Tires 666.
Her father was the auditor.
Until he got the brilliant idea,
to help the FBI against them.
They discovered it and killed him.
She saw it all.
She will testify tomorrow
- I read the news?
Maybe they think she's safe now.
- Then you're kidding.
- The nacker and hell FBI escort, -
- but five fools in the
mall are too much.
They come back.
They closed the phones before
they knew she was here.
They knew how many we
are and where we were.
He came to the Montclair
entrance, not the other.
How can they know?
- The police patrol...
He said they did not come.
- Weapons?
- We have none.
Let's get away.
- How many are they?
- Is there a hiding place?
What? Forget it.
I will join.
- You promised...
- To protect you.
We can not keep them out.
They come in, it's
just a matter of time.
- We must save her. Now!
- I know somewhere.
Come on.
Oh God.
Okay.
It is just ahead.
It's not much but hard to find.
Well.
Here is a flashlight, -
- water and a radio
I know.
It's low frequency, but it works.
Its range is not long.
- Do not be afraid if nobody answers.
- I do not get scared.
Well. Do you miss anything else?
- A teddy bear or something?
- A teddy bear?
Did not you have a daughter of my age?
- You do not know anything, right?
"We do not see each other much.
My parents are dead. I have been in
witness protection for four years.
Even though I survive and testify,
- I have neither a
family nor a home.
You'd better come.
Listen up. Lock the door.
Be quiet.
Do not get out, no
matter what you hear.
It's some fissure.
I promised to protect
you, so I will do that.
Lock the door.
Look here.
There.
- It is well.
- Pardon?
It is well.
Fun, because I think it's
the worst night of my life.
- He's bleeding.
- What do you mean?
If he knew that the
patrol did not come,
Then they had stormed the place.
But what are they doing?
Sets our cars out of game.
- They find Betty.
- What?
My gun under the seat.
A hidden weapon.
What is the meaning of a weapon
if you do not go with it?
Rules. No weapon here.
- We must go away.
- Impossible.
Yes, we can and should.
There are men on their way to killing us.
And who are you really?
- You do not decide.
- He does now.
I will not die tonight.
If he can do better, get
up with your hands.
- sure.
- He is afraid.
He'll kill you.
He is professional.
High-Profiled.
Do you want to go home to your wife
and child, so stay in the building.
If you do not want to
help, find a hideaway.
Nobody condemns you.
Do you have a plan?
The attack took place 45 minutes ago.
The FBI now knows that she has disappeared.
- They will search for her.
- When?
We dont know.
But right now time is our enemy.
Let's make it to our friend.
There.
Come on.
How do we get up on the roof?
It's too bad.
Status?
Free lane at Route 6.
Free lane here too.
Off.
What the hell are we doing?
- Sends them a message.
Oh God!
Move!
It's probably not up to this.
Quickly!
Get cleaned up.
Run! Run!
- Fast!
- Wait...
Vance! Damn!
Wait for me!
Pis.
No...
- Ruby?
- Come on.
The worst guard to
have hangover on.
Take the sleeping bag.
Get the car away.
- Flashlight.
- Okay.
Jeez. Hit the cards down.
What's really going on?
A girl appeared, now a
psychopath will kill her.
Now we have a whole gang behind us.
- The doors?
- Holds so far.
- On top...
- I have arranged that.
- Is it him?
- Eddie. He decides.
- Did you tell me what's happening?
- In general.
A girl and a gang.
I'm ready.
We do not have much time.
We have 30 minutes before
you reach Montclair.
A further 10 minutes to Zone B.
We must be ready.
- What is the plan?
- Buying time.
Get has on as many
of them as possible.
If you get the chance to
turn on, do not hesitate.
- I can shoot with a bow.
- I can make bombs.
What?
- the internet
- Let's get around.
Ruby, save yourself here.
Vance, the kitchen department.
You are the first line of defense.
Mason, garden supplies.
You are the guard post.
We just have to distract them long
enough, so the FBI will arrive.
Okay.
Calm. It's a bomb.
- Then it's ready.
- Departed.
- Do you have it?
- Yes.
Okay. Come on.
Okay.
When the patrol comes...
If you see them, you will not go out.
They must come in here.
Remember. SEA.
Short, short...
... long, tall, long
Short, short, short.
Short, short, long, long, long.
- Short, short...
- Listen now.
Do as I say, you can do it.
Off.
- What are you doing?
- Fit to myself.
If one of me gossip
to them, I'm done.
If I have to save, nobody
should know where.
- I can help.
- No, we've talked about it.
- I have an idea.
- Real.
Clear the place. The car is ready.
Put it on.
Pis.
She is in the building.
Nobody gets out alive.
They are inside.
Channel 47.
47 is open.
What should I call you?
- Eddie.
- Call me Charlie.
Jaså...
Last chance, Charlie.
The girl is gone.
Our patrol soon appears.
And the FBI, who has
discovered she's gone.
We also have the home side advantage.
A little message to my men.
Eddie, now where we talk together,
- It would also benefit
your team to hear this.
Do everyone listen?
To my men...
I have talked to our employer.
After the mess of the evening,
- is there a bonus in place.
If the girl dies, each
gets 100,000 on top.
There comes a 'but'.
But if we fail...
... and she survives.
Then everyone will be chased and killed.
Your family, friends and
pets are then shot.
So that's just to say...
... that I recommend we
get hold of her tonight.
Let's get started.
Bastard.
Reports.
That's Vance.
I'm innocent.
I'm fine too.
I smell of cheap
hats, but I'm fine.
Mason? Can you hear us?
I'm on the way. Stay out
Mason?
You just have to thank me.
Satan.
Mason, it did not work.
You must be away from there.
The Sheriff has just turned off.
We have guests outside.
Nobody is shooting.
Unless anyone tries something.
Do not do anything wrong.
A car.
Okay.
What in...?
It is broken.
I'm trying the door.
- I'm going out there.
- No.
I do it.
Hey!
Nice try.
Free path.
Clear the food department.
Listen up. We just lost Johnny.
They mean it seriously.
You must be extremely careful.
Please reply.
That's Vance.
I'm still stuck.
I do not think I can get away.
Okay, Vance.
Can you see the food department?
No.
Okay.
- Ruby? Mason?
- I'm still in D-2.
Stirs on Vance's ugly feather.
Are you still alive, Mason?
Mason? Do you hear?
- Yes...
- Listen carefully.
We need someone to the food department.
What do you say?
No.
Mason, if you do not
move, they'll get you.
Are you still in the garden department?
- No...
- Where are you?
The warehouse.
I can not move myself.
It's Jamie.
I can help.
Jamie, can you see in the food department?
Yes.
"I have to know how many they are.
- Received.
Listen for everyone.
We meet at Clives...
... about exactly three minutes.
Received.
Pis.
They are five.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Follow it!
No!
Are you okay?
- I was worried.
- I'm fine.
Beware!
I've got you! Satan!
My Goodness!
Stop Mason!
It is me.
Okay?
Well.
Are you afraid?
We are going on.
We need it. Come on.
Close the gate! Close the gate!
If you want something done,
you have to do it yourself.
- You saved him.
- You were not bad either.
Open it.
Hey.
I have a gift for you.
If you get trouble
and I'm not there...
-... so press here.
- I can use a power gun.
My mother had one.
Lovely house.
Here is quite small but nice.
It reminds me of something.
- Where?
- At my Uncle Will.
I lived there in the
summer when I was little.
Then it was...
... normally.
One year my father said that
I could not have anymore.
Do you see...
... fathers are not always perfect.
At least, some are at
home and not criminals.
- You defend him.
- Not at all.
It's hard to know why people
are doing some things.
He may also have been scared.
Afraid? For what, though?
To put you in danger.
To blame you for something.
Maybe he was afraid of...
... himself.
I do not know completely.
But right now...
... there is nobody
I feel safe with.
Let's talk together.
Fire away.
You are at Clives,
without escape.
Only a single steel gate, -
- keep us cut off
I therefore offer
this one last time:
Give us the girl.
Or I'm breathing ..
... and praise.
It's been two hours since you
let a child get away from you.
The FBI can come at any time.
You're done, Charlie.
The patrol ran again, but you
probably remember your friend.
The answer has been received.
- Ready or not.
- Come here.
Police... oh god!
The police are outside!
Eddie!
The police are outside.
Just wait.
Communication carriage.
We must get rid of it.
Get rid of her.
Wait for me.
How are you doing, Vance?
- It's solid steel.
It is not good.
Help is on its way.
The ball is given up.
- Down on Earth!
- I'm the guards.
- He has a weapon.
- No I have not.
- Is the girl here?
- Yes, in the warehouse.
We hear shots from there.
Move!
I need help.
- Can we reach her?
- Can I use this?
Yes.
Mason, come with the girl.
No, I can not move.
Mason, get along.
Jamie, are you listening?
When i get up
... then you run into hell.
- What do you want to do?
- Do not think about it.
But you get away from here and
get them down with your neck.
- Promise me it.
- Yes...
Let's do it.
It will be OK.
Come on.
Such. What a shit guard.
She trusts you so she's
coming here, right?
Jamie, keep in mind.
You can not go home without your teddy bear.
What?
Johnny!
Mason?
Vance? Jamie?
I thought you were dead.
- Are you in love with you?
- No.
- I think you shot him.
- Pokkers.
Listen up.
They are in the store.
You must be very quiet
and very strong.
What our team has accomplished
must not be in vain.
You must also go home.
To your daughter.
Exactly.
What do we do?
Do you remember what we
did with Ruby's stuff?
Where we put them?
In the seniors department.
Get her radio.
The real one.
Guard radio.
Okay.
It has emergency channels.
There will be noise first, but
clear sound if I can handle it.
When that happens, find
a hideaway and shout.
The good ones will listen and help us.
When you get through,
wait for me.
Then I get you.
On scouting?
On scouting.
Are you able to do it?
Can I count on you?
I can do that.
See you soon.
You and I, dare.
You and I.
He goes after the noise transmitter.
Jamie?
I know you're in here...
... and that you can hear me.
We were on a 20 km country road.
The rain removed the
tracks and we the cars.
They do not know where we
joined the FBI escort.
There is no one.
It's time to negotiate.
Pis. Get the cart away.
Jamie?
Jamie ?!
Jamie? Do you hear me?
Jamie?
Jamie, can you hear me?
My name is Jamie.
The shopping center in Ridgeside. Help...
Do not shoot. He is mine.
Nice to meet you, Betty.
Pis.
Jamie...?
Jamie? This is the police.
Jamie, can you hear us?
He's gone, Jamie.
Like everyone else does when
things get complicated.
When I was at your age,
- My father woke me up and
asked me to pack a bag.
I was happy.
I had only been from
home quite a few times.
I fell asleep.
When I woke up, my
father was gone.
There were 50 caps in my jacket pocket.
I never saw him again.
Now we make an appointment.
From one left soul to another.
You do not have to die,
you just can not testify.
You come with me.
I'll get both of us safe.
Then we start from somewhere else.
I will help you.
Maybe I can teach you one thing or two.
Who knows?
You must make an important decision.
You can be the child in vain
waiting for the white knight.
You can be immature and stupid
if you fly where I saw...
... have no choice
but to kill you.
You can also get up.
Then we arrange this as adults.
So...
What will it be?
Okay. If that's the way you want to play?
No! No!
Eddie!
Eddie...
You could have been rich.
I said you should take the
money and turn your back.
As you said, Charlie, it's me...
... that determines.
You said...
Jamie.
You know how it works.
Get up. Come on.
Come on.
Look at me.
There she is.
We have contact with
Jamie, alive at Ridgeside.
Stop! Hands up!
Hello.
Hi...
You look like shit.
I feel like that too.
I will travel soon.
Evidently.
So...
I just wanted to say
thank you before I left.
You have nothing to worry
about, with your daughter.
She is lucky to have you as a dad.
- Where are you going?
- For a foster family.
They did not tell me.
You will be fine.
I have a good feeling.
Who?
Uncle Will!
Come on.
Translated by UNiTY
www.DanishBits.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org