Maya! Maya!
Open the door!
Open the damn door!
Didn't I say I'm sorry, huh?
Damn it!
Maya, I'm so tired of your shit.
I'm so tired of it.
How could you make
me do it again?
I love you, baby.
Listen to me.
Blush, floss, rinse,
repeat just to be sure.
Good dental hygiene
is very important.
If we move the couch,
the rug will last another
2 years, at least.
Bye, Grandma. I'll see
you at... lunch time.
Hello.
Why do you guys lock the freaking bathrooms?
You think we're gonna steal
your high-class toilet paper?
Hey, Magellan, you think
you can pick it up?
I got to pee like a racehorse.
Do you have to go to the bathroom?
Is anybody home?
I just wanted to use your phone.
Oh, my gosh.
Get out, asshole.
Get out!
You live in this thing?
I had to brush my teeth.
It's 10:30 am.
What's that?
It's a 1987 delivery truck,
manufactured my Chevy, V12.
The VIN number is 08027614.
Why is there a bed in it?
So I can sleep.
Are you - Are you angry?
I don't see angry very well.
Do you know who I am?
You're the lady with a gun.
Are you a boxer?
That lady at the house -
- is that your grandmother?
I can draw you a map if you
tell me where you're going.
Maps tell us nearly everything.
I'm Duncan. Nice to meet you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to freaking Sri Lanka.
Hmm, I don't have a map to there.
I'm in a hurry. Okay?
How can you be in a hurry
if you don't have a destination?
It's an expression.
I don't like expressions.
If you're gonna
be a pain in my ass,
you can just walk back
to town with your brush.
What do you mean?
I'm annoying you?
Am I hurting your butt?
Expressions.
I have to go to the bathroom.
I read it's bad to hold it in,
so I go 7 times a day.
In the summer I go
8 times.
It's time to make
lunch for Grandma.
Tuesday's wheat toast,
tuesday's a turkey sandwich.
She's, umm -
Turkey and Swiss cheese.
I have to go.
Can you - I don't know
how to drive my truck.
Can you - Can you -
I have 1 blue pill
and 2 purple pills.
Can you take me home?
I have to go to the bathroom
and I have to make a sandwich.
Yeah, okay!
Okay.
I'll drive you back there.
We can figure it out with
your grandmother, okay?
That's nice.
But, that's it. Get in the car.
I'm sorry.
Why?
About your grandmother.
What about her?
She died.
She was 82.
Based on current
census statistics,
she lived 23% longer
than the average person
in this part of the country.
That's good.
You're not sad?
Yes, it would have been
better if she lived 25% longer.
You're not gonna miss her?
I know the correct answer is yes.
Nice, Duncan.
Yes.
Nothing. Let's go.
911, what's your emergency?
Hello! 911, what
is your location?
Time to go to the bathroom.
You don't even like your mother.
We have gone this way -
Do you need one of these?
Do you have a blue one?
Thank you.
So, who's James Richards?
He sends his
money, but we can't visit.
Why?
We can't fit it all in.
Okay. You go this way,
you can travel this speed limit,
see your parents and still
get to Reno by Friday.
James Richards, is he your dad?
Yes.
We should find him.
I have to eat now.
I have to eat food right now.
Keep your voice down.
I was already supposed
to have food inside me.
Hey!
This is a family establishment.
I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave.
I've had a really, really bad day
and you don't want
to make it worse.
Look, young lady.
Do I look like a lady to you?
My friend is on a schedule
and he needs to eat right now.
And as soon as we're
done, we'll go.
We don't want any trouble.
Get off of him! Stop!
I need more paper.
He likes to draw,
so we're gonna take
some paper towels too.
Anybody have a
problem with that?
Can I take both of them?
Yep.
This better get a whole
lot easier real soon.
Are you sad?
- I need you to act like a normal person
for like 5 minutes
and not freak out.
We just need to find your dad.
Do you know where he is?
Please slow down.
I get motion sickness, is why -
That's why I walk, I don't -
That's why we don't
drive the truck.
Thank you.
Were there potholes?
Where are you going?
I'm going to a place
I know, to see somebody.
This things been
blinking for like a hour
and I have no idea
where a gas station is.
There's one coming up on the right,
but I don't think we're -
No way. Come on!
Yep.
You gonna get out
and help me or what?
Help you do what?
Just get your ass
out here, right now.
Come on, Duncan, just push.
We have to have, like, a plan B.
How many plans are there?
Is plan B better than plan A?
Does plan B include food?
Okay, look, we're just
gonna go to the gas station,
get the gas container
and bring it back here.
Okay? Let's go.
I can't leave the truck.
One out to of 27 vehicles
in this region are stolen,
are stolen in this region, in
this region they're stolen.
We're not be gone
for more than 10 minutes.
Duncan, let's just go, okay?
Just come with me.
I can't.
Okay, you know what?
Mm-hmm.
And I'm gonna go
and I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere, okay?
Okay.
Just go brush your teeth or something.
Just try not to make
things too complicated.
How much complication
is too much complication?
What you normally do,
it too much complication,
so just try to do the opposite.
Hey! Hey!
Whoa, whoa, hey, that's my car.
Get in.
No, I want you to get out.
Either get in or I'm leaving.
So what's your name?
Tony Sanchez Rodriquez
'Filerberto Sanchez the 3rd.
There's 2 Sanchez's
there. I don't know why.
I'm gonna give your car back
as soon as I get
back up to mine.
Yeah.
Do you like to drive fast, man?
It's cool.
Is this your first time stealing
a car at the gas station or -
That was a stupid question.
Do you like to drive fast?
I like to do a lot of things fast.
Duncan, roll down the window.
Roll down the window.
Duncan, stop the car.
Left pedal, stop the car.
Press it really hard. Okay?
Stop the -
No, no. Not the horn. The pedal.
Stop it.
Please stop the car.
Stop the car, Duncan, please.
Stop the car, Duncan!
What the hell do you
think you were doing?
You could have killed yourself.
What are you doing?
I'm fixing the sign.
It was wrong. See.
What does this mean?
The world is tough.
Take it. Be tough.
Don't show weakness.
The world is tough.
Take it. Be tough.
Don't show weakness.
The world is tough.
Take it. Be tough.
Just don't ever
leave me like that again.
Don't show weakness.
Maryland is 2,046 miles away.
How the hell did you
even get the truck started?
I used the gas from the gas cans
in the truck, for emergencies.
Was that too much complication?
Yeah.
You didn't think to
mention that earlier?
You forgot to ask.
You coming?
I've haven't seen the
sunset in forever.
But, it happens every night.
What's this mean?
It means, fuck you.
That's a good thing, then?
It can be.
I'll let you know when.
Okay. Thank you.
Last night I dreamt a
racehorse peed in my bathroom.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Has anybody ever told
you that you're different?
Not so different.
Man, I'm hungry.
It's funny you should
say that, Maya,
because I'm pretty hungry too.
What should we do, Duncan?
I don't know. Maybe we could
find a restaurant somewhere.
Oh, that's a great idea, buddy.
What a fantastic
traveling partner you are.
Come on. Come on let's go.
Let's go.
They named a town after you.
Hey, Duncan. Duncan.
You have to stay close to me.
Okay?
Just go back to sleep.
Yeah, I love you too.
I don't have time for this.
I need -
I want to draw.
Okay.
Can you see if
they have paper towels
in the bathroom,
brown paper towels.
Okay.
I need to draw.
Yeah.
Hey buddy.
How you doin'?
You hitting that?
No, but she hit me earlier.
Yeah? That's kinky.
What are you? You a fruitcake?
No.
You're a little timid
there, aren't you?
Huh? Yeah.
You know what's really gonna
make her feel like a woman?
I want you to walk behind her,
put your arms around her
and grab her tits real hard.
Trust me, dude. She'll love it.
Here, don't worry about it.
Just have a drink.
Drink it up. There you go.
What the hell are you doing?
Why can't he have a drink?
You okay?
He's fine.
Don't worry about anything.
Am I fruitcake?
No.
I like those little scars on your arm.
- Paper.
Here. Why don't we
go back to the truck, okay?
Yeah, go back to the truck.
No! No! No! No!
No! No! Oh, get off! No!
Bitch.
Oh, oh, man. Ahh.
I used my dental pick.
Take it back.
I can't. I don't want it anymore.
I can't use it anymore,
it's got blood on it.
Just take it back anyway.
Don't show weakness.
You left the door open.
Where'd you put my alarm clock?
Everything's everywhere.
Why are you yelling?
Why'd you do that?
I didn't do anything.
I have to go to work.
What?
- Today's my day to go to work.
What are you talking about?
- Look. Okay? Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Oh, Maya, look. Okay?
What?
Look, Maya.
- What?
Look.
Okay. Okay.
We're right here and we
got to take me to work.
We're gonna go from here,
all the way to here.
What are you doing with my maps?
You have to take me to work.
You shouldn't put
them on the ground.
Where's that piece?
Duncan, where is it?
You don't understand.
I have to go to work.
You think you could draw
that part of the map for me?
What do you think? Huh?
You left the doors open
and it got too hot in here
and all my
books came off the shelf
and everything's everywhere.
Duncan, I just need you -
You can do all of that. Okay?
You have to take me to work!
Hey, listen to me right now!
You understand me?
We are not going home!
You do not have a home anymore,
your grandma is gone! Do you
understand? You're not going back!
There's nothing to go back to!
You do not have a job anymore!
Do you understand me?
I need you to draw a map,
so we can find your dad,
so I can take you there.
Okay?
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
I need you to help
me find your dad.
Do you understand, Duncan?
Do you understand what
I'm saying to you?
Are you hearing me?
Where are we gonna go now?
I'm sorry that I yelled at you.
Are you sick?
Well, looky here. It's Mutt n Chop.
Funny you say that.
Why's that?
I bought this hat and
I wanted you to let me know
if it brings out my chops.
You got some weird feathering
going on up here,
but entirely intentional.
It looks kind of nice.
Stock joke number 27.
I'm running out of ideas.
What do you expect?
I'm just gonna jump right into, BAM!
Look at that fine
looking creature I am.
Feel no shame for what you are.
That's what I always say.
You look all right, for a cowboy.
Ain't you gonna say anything?
Oh, look, look, I said I was sorry.
I'm sorry I lost your horse.
Maya.
I missed you.
What's so funny?
I don't know.
I guess I just didn't think,
I didn't think it'd be
so hard to talk to you.
Her name's Candice.
I don't really
want to know her name.
Are you happy?
I don't know if I'm comfortable
with you asking that question.
I made a mess of
everything, didn't I?
Sometimes the world
ain't ready for your splendor.
I don't feel very splendid.
You're safe now.
But you're here,
you might as well take
the time, just rest.
We're staying here,
because Maya is very tired
and the people are very nice,
except for one drunk man
who keeps calling me Chauncey
and wants me to
work on his garden.
Dave says he's drunk.
They bring me food and
Ramone really likes my maps.
She didn't answer
yesterday either.
Shit.
No! No!
Stop.
No! No! No!
No!
Hi, Dave.
Good morning.
Hi. Good morning.
How's Maya?
She hasn't left yet.
She's still in the room, 7 days now.
Okay. I'll check in on her.
Okay.
I was thinking you
two might take a ride today.
You know, fresh air
might do her some good.
Fresh air.
Birds don't need roads.
Their maps look very different.
Yeah, I guess it would
look different, wouldn't they?
Someone told me that
if you go up high enough
that there's no such
thing as east or west.
Is that true?
I don't know.
I think there'd still
be an east and west.
I wonder what we
look like to them?
Small tiny birds with no wings.
You like that, huh?
I didn't know you were so funny.
So, are you all right, buddy?
Is there anything I can get you?
Can I use you shaving cream again?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Okay.
Anything else?
No. Thank you.
Okay.
Am I dismissed?
I can stay here, if you like.
I'm okay.
- Oh, okay.
Do you want to?
I was going to check in on Maya,
but it's up to you, buddy.
- Okay, yeah. Okay.
Okay.
Hey, maybe you could a -
maybe you could draw me
a map of the grounds.
Would you do that for me?
Yeah.
That's excellent.
I would appreciate that.
Yes.
Wow.
Stop.
I looked a lot better
when I was high.
I think Duncan misses you.
I saw him on the way.
I don't know why.
I gotta find his dad.
How much of this
is really about him?
What do you mean?
I mean, you could
have gone anywhere.
You could have driven up
the Coast of San Francisco,
but you come back here.
My car broke down.
It did.
What about them,
your mom and dad?
Shouldn't you see them?
It's been a long time.
Yeah.
It's the one good thing
he ever gave to me.
I never want to
see his face again
after what he did.
I just don't think I can.
Maya, when I
woke up that morning
and saw that letter in
place of you on that pillow
next to me, my whole
world lost shades of color
I don't think I
will ever get back.
In the back of my mind I knew,
I knew this town was
too small for you,
I knew I was too
lucky to have you.
No you weren't.
I want to give you something.
This is long past due,
but I couldn't get
myself to give it to you,
because I couldn't have myself
keep you from your dreams.
The world will embrace
you one day, Maya,
and I will forever
be proud of you.
You owe me for your folks.
You owe me for my
wife.
That comes to $74,700.
Have you met my sister?
She's single and she owns a cow.
Hell, everybody's met your sister.
Dave: Ladies and gentlemen,
I have a very special
surprise for you.
All the way from Las
Angeles, California,
one of the dearest friends
of the Buckcorn Opry,
I bring to you Maya.
I saw myself together
Through the holes in my sweater
Once you flash your smile to me
Yes, I know you
think you're clever
Go on, steal my sick away
And give me whatever's left
Come on, get down
from your throne
'Cause we all know what we own
And I won't let you stay
I gave you my time
and 16 second chances
And you got no follow through
I'm not going back
Under these circumstances
I say, I don't mind,
I close my eyes
Do you realize how I
tried to forget you
I say, I don't mind
You make me wish I was back
I came through your eyes
through your lenses
They disguise your
worst intentions
Does the fire in your whiskey
Make you feel the
burn to kiss me
Don't you stand seductively
and turn around
And bare your teeth
Every move that you make
Feels like you're
dancing on my grave
I say, I don't mind,
I close my eyes
I say, I don't mind
Do you realize
how I tried to forget you
I say, I don't mind
You make me wish I was back
Now I wonder round the city
trying to figure out what hit me
As I'm reliving all the scenes
What could I've done differently
If I gave myself
Would you know what
you were missing
If I gave myself permission
Would you get out of my system
Why do you have Christmas
lights in the truck?
They put the lights in
the store November and December
and then in the back closet
next to the toilet paper and
bleach for the rest of the year,
so now I put the lights in the
truck for the other 10 months.
Am I a thief?
No.
I never asked you, why
do you live in the truck.
Grandma's walls
are too complicated.
And, the truck got
very good safety
and fuel economy ratings.
Yeah?
Yes.
Can we go sledding in Colorado?
Why Colorado?
There's snow.
Well, we could go
sledding in the sand.
Is that a metaphor?
I understand -
I don't like when one
thing means another.
Lots of things mean
lots of different things.
Ow. Oh, my -
Duncan.
If you're sick, you go to the doctor,
like Grandma.
There's a lot of damage,
scar tissue, inflammation.
Usually, when I see
things like this,
it's consistent with
childhood trauma.
So, what does that mean?
I don't see that it's likely
that you will be able to conceive.
You were supposed to love me.
Get off!
What are you doing?
What the hell
are you doing with that girl?
Hey, dumb ass.
Yo, chief, what the hell
do you think you're doing? Huh?
No!
Wait a minute.
Duncan!
Hi. Excuse me. Can you
help me real quick?
My friend, he was outside.
Are you a member of his family?
I need to go see him.
Maya.
Hey, buddy.
They don't have
brown paper towels here.
I'll have to get you some then.
Okay.
You ever celebrate 4th
of July with your grandma?
We sell fireworks
and hotdogs at the store
and potato chips
and potato salad.
But, I don't like potato salad,
because I don't like mayonnaise,
but I do like eggs, which
Grandma thinks is weird.
But, she has to shave.
That's how I learned
how to shave.
I think that's weird.
Yeah.
Do you like fireworks?
Roughly 400
Americans lose their eyesight
due to fireworks, every year.
I take that as a no, then.
I want to go sledding in Colorado
where it snows.
Have you ever seen the snow?
I have something for you.
What is this?
It's the missing piece in the middle.
Based on your map,
it says he should live
right around here.
I don't think we should bother him.
I'll be with you the whole time.
Okay?
That house must have
a lot of bathrooms.
I'm gonna wait in the truck.
I think I want to draw.
We came all this way.
Are you sure you
don't want to go in?
Hi. Can I help you?
Yeah, does James Richards live here?
Is he expecting you?
Not exactly.
My name is Maya.
Hi. Jeff Richards.
You must be his son.
Yeah. Can I ask
what this is regarding?
You know, it's probably
better if I talk to your dad.
Is he home?
Hey, thanks to everyone who donated
to help our friends in Honduras.
I want to give a special
thanks to Reverend Peters
for all of his guidance.
His sermons have been such
a comfort to Kendra and me
over the years.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, thank you.
Seeing that the world needs our help,
my wife and I have sponsored
several children from Honduras
and several of you
have pictures of these,
just beautiful, beautiful,
adorable children.
We'll send these around.
Thanks for your donations.
Keep giving and there's
more champagne in the back.
Thanks enjoy.
Yeah. Thank you for coming.
Thanks.
I'm gonna show Reverend.
Great.
Dad, this is Maya. She
was hoping to speak with you.
Oh, of course, hi.
Are you a new member here?
Not exactly.
I was hoping maybe you and I
could speak in private.
Oh, of course.
Oh, is this a friend of yours?
Yes. This is Duncan.
You know what?
I forgot to check
on your sister.
Would you do that for me?
Okay.
Nice meeting you, Maya.
You as well.
Hello, Duncan.
Hello.
Um, what is this?
What are you talking about?
What is he doing here?
- I thought you would want to see your son.
Why would you think that?
Why don't you come with me?
Why don't we talk
about it inside?
I'd rather not talk
about it outside.
Come on, Duncan, follow us.
Come on. Come on.
Come and follow us.
I thought you'd want to see him.
His grandmother died.
Oh, she lasted longer than I expected.
How did you find him?
I mean, why is he with you?
I don't quite understand this.
I ran into him in.
You know, I thought
it would be nice
if we came and found you.
You came all this way,
so he can find me.
I mean, you seem to be
quite the humanitarian.
You found me. Here I am.
So, what would
you like me to do?
Hey, buddy, you want
to step outside for a minute?
Right now?
Yeah. Thank you.
You have a great kid out there.
I'm just glad he doesn't
know what a shit you are.
Just tell me how much?
- What?
To take care of him,
how much do you want?
That's why you're
here, isn't it?
I came here because you're
the last person he has in the world.
Really? And now he
has you and he has my money
and so you'll be all set.
Right?
I'm coming back in now.
I don't like it out there.
It's okay.
Close the door.
Close the door. It's cold.
Just close the door.
You're letting the heat out.
Your wife and your
kids have no idea, do they?
If you don't want my money
then there is nothing
that I can do for you.
Do you understand me?
You live like this
and he's been in a truck
waiting for you for 20 years.
Just how much?
$74,700 and I want the globe.
All right, maybe
we can work something out.
Oh, you don't think
he's worth that much?
No. I don't have that right now.
James, is everything all right?
Yeah, everything is fine.
Why don't you check
on the guests.
Darling, everyone's
waiting for you to cut the cake.
Honey, I'm sorry.
I just need a few
minutes please.
Are you friends of Jeff's?
I asked you to leave!
Well, I'll be outside then.
Maya, I found Sri Lanka.
I found it.
It's really tiny.
It's 9,750 miles away,
give or take 200 miles.
I am sorry for the
circumstances as you see them.
He won't fit into my life
and it's best for him
to find a simpler life.
I have done my fair share of
supporting him over the years.
What, checks in the mail?
Yeah, that makes a really
great family photo album.
You're outrageous.
You flaunt your
way into my house.
You find some kid who doesn't
know shit about the world
and you con him
into taking my money
and you are judging me!
He's from another time!
He's from another world
and he doesn't fit in here.
I don't know what I'm
doing here talking to you.
You want to know what I think?
I don't give a shit what you think.
What do you think your
little society buddies out there
would think, if they
knew what you did to him?
He's your son.
How do you think Duncan feels?
He doesn't feel.
He doesn't know any better.
Quit fooling yourself.
You have no idea.
Take my money, take him
and go back to whatever life
you dug your way out of.
I'm being generous.
I'm being extremely generous.
Accept and disappear.
The world is tough.
Take it. Be tough.
Don't show weakness.
You don't want a
chance to get to know him?
Take it. Take it.
Come on, buddy. Let's go.
I can have it?
- Yes, you can.
Hey, Duncan.
You said I was from a different life.
My life is in a different place.
I like it.
Thank you for the world.
Who was that?
I'm glad we did that.
Yeah?
Yes. It felt good.
Now, let's go see your dad.
Do I not fit in your life?
What?
Like what my dad said,
he said I don't fit in his life.
I don't know how to fit
into a person's life.
If I don't fit right, will
you tell me what to do?
You fit just right, Duncan.
That's good.
You -
You are my favorite singer.
Thank you.
What is that?
I don't know!
Look like snow.
Ahh!
The wind here is like
an ocean, it has currents.
You know, this used
to be the ocean floor.
That must have been a long time ago.
Well, yeah.
Otherwise, we'd be under water.
How do I show wind on a map?
You can't see it just
by looking at it.
My maps are flat, right?
You've seen them, they're flat.
Right, north, south, east,
west, northwest, southwest,
southeast, northeast?
But, now, I need maps
with roads that go up.
Yeah.
Does your dad
have a big house too?
No.
Where does he live?
Can we go see him?
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
Stay here and I'll get it.
Stay here, Duncan.
Uh-oh, Maya!
Uh-oh!
Maya, this is like sledding.
Whoa.
Let's do it again.
Francine really likes
the strong, silent type.
You've seen, you know, those
guys on TV with your grandma?
Okay.
It's like this.
You just gotta stand up real tall
and kind of puff your chest out.
Yeah, like that.
Keep your arms
down by your sides
and keep your elbows out,
almost like your arms are
so big they can't touch.
Yeah, just like that.
Just don't say anything unless
someone asks you something.
Okay.
You.
Your daddy's gone, dead.
His ashes are taking
up space on the shelf
if you want to
pay your respects.
Meet me out back.
You don't have
to hold your breath.
Ohhh, okay.
You're doing good.
I think you were right.
I think she likes me.
Yeah. Come on.
Hey. Would you like some wine?
Hey, you, give me
that can over there.
Yes.
You know what your daddy said
before he did this
world a favor?
You've come all
this way out here
and your daddy's dead,
so why don't you just
take his rotten ashes?
Why the hell do you still have this?
Why?
You're just gonna sit there
and pretend like
nothing happened,
like you didn't know
exactly what was going on?
If you didn't like it,
why didn't you say
no, like I did?
But, I guess one of
us had to take it.
What the hell is this?
It's not loaded.
Oh, like I would
shoot my own fucking daughter.
Hey, buddy, why don't you
go wait for me out in the car?
Okay.
Is was nice to meet you, Mrs Maya.
What's with the retard with you?
Don't you ever say that word.
You shacking up, huh?
He do you good?
You know, after that waste
of spit, dad of yours died,
I went around and I picked
up all of the photographs
of you and him.
I have just been waiting for
the right time to burn them.
You know, a nice little
family gathering?
Why, we could do it together,
just my bitch daughter and me.
You're pathetic.
No, dear, we're pathetic.
You hate your momma? Huh?
You know what it's
like to lose a man
and not to another woman,
but to your own daughter?
You, you just get on by with
your pretty little smile
and your pretty little ways.
Do you know what it is
like to slowly decay away
into the shadows?
Dreams die in a crumbling
old house of dirty memories,
drinking cheap beer and
watching your life turn moldy
like an old piece of cheese.
That man, that man
buried me in this life
and you come back
here, out of the blue
and you start preaching to me.
Well, you have a future.
You stand there with
a future ahead of you
and I have nothing!
I have nothing!
I am all done, gone and wasted!
I hate you!
I hate you for what
you took from me!
I'm sorry that your life
doesn't meant that much to you.
Mine does.
Mine does now.
Fuck.
You fiend.
Get out!
Are you leaving?
Where are you going?
Aren't you gonna pee?
Are you leaving?
It's okay, go ahead.
I'll wait for you.
Don't go.
I'm up here.
Don't say a word.
That man deserves nothing.
Is it a good time to do this?
Yeah.
Hey, Duncan.
Yes.
Thank you.
Feel no shame for what you are,
is what I always say.
Good morning, sleepy head.
I'm a sleepy head?
Not really.
Where are we going?
I have a surprise for you.
What is it?
If I told you, it wouldn't be a surprise.
Okay.
All right, get ready.
Can you close the curtain?
Yeah.